Heh... Means this evening's
program has just been altered.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh yeah! They're here!
The bandits are finally here
for their ass-beating!
Let's go, suckers! Huh...?
Why are there so many of them?
[RIKICHI YELLS]
Fire at will.
[KIKUCHIYO] Seriously,
you guys were awesome!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
Bring me a rope.
♪ opening song ♪
Hee-yaw!
[TESSAI] Master Ukyo...
I really hate to intrude, but--
[UKYO] Then don't.
[TESSAI] It's just
that one of our spies
has sent back a very
interesting report.
[UKYO]
Fine. You may enter.
[TESSAI]
Thank you, master.
Well, out with it...
[TESSAI]
Yes, master.
It appears that war has
broken out between the Nobuseri
and the villagers of Kanna.
And I should care why?
Ah, just the card
I was looking for!
[GIRLS LAUGH]
Surely you haven't
forgotten already?
Kanna Village is where
that farm girl came from.
Ah, my beloved Kirara.
So... her village is
at war with the Nobuseri--
I guess that explains what
she was doing with those
Samurai thugs we saw her with.
We have lost contact
with Hyogo and Kyuzo,
who were dispatched
to follow them.
Our scouts discovered
a fresh grave in the desert
and dug it up...
It was Hyogo, Master.
Grave robbing...?
Honestly, isn't
that a tad morbid?
Hyogo's wound was clearly
the work of a skilled swordsman.
Since Kyuzo is nowhere to
be found we have to assume...
...he may be responsible.
Have you told
my father yet?
[TESSAI]
No, Master.
Let's keep it that way...
Oh and I suppose you can
call off that Samurai Hunt now.
As you wish.
So my Kirara's
still alive... huh.
Tessai, I want you to tell me
everything there is to know
about this Kanna Village.
And keep an eye on them...
for a storm is on the
horizon that will soon
throw the very
heavens into disarray.
We offer you the
Samurai as atonement
for this shameful
display of arrogance.
Please accept
and forgive us!
[SOBEI SIGHS]
[SOBEI] Huh...?
Kyuzo, is that you?
I can't believe
you've fallen so low.
Likewise.
[SOBEI]
What did you say?!
Is this what you call fallen?
You're nothing but a stray dog,
bought by the likes of peasants!
Before, I counted seven
samurai altogether.
What happened to
the other three?
We killed them.
We shot them down
when they tried to run!
[SYUSAI] Really?
[RIKICHI] They taught us
how to use bow and arrow.
When we realized how wrong
we'd been to betray you,
we turned on them!
They were outnumbered,
and we shot them as
they tried to escape!
[SOBEI]
We're not convinced.
[SYUSAI]
Seize them!
[BANDIT 1] Yes, sir.
[BANDIT 2] So, you've
been hiding rice from us?
[KATSUSHIRO GASPS]
Wait, what are you doing?!
[SOBEI] You miserable cheats
will serve as a lesson
for the other villages.
Hold on a minute...
If you kill us,
who will grow your rice?
[SYUSAI] Oh, There are
plenty of other villages.
But we promise you...
We'll never betray you again!
[SOBEI] You may have
had a change of heart,
but you've also showered us with
arrows, and killed our men.
We cannot let such defiance go.
We have no choice
but to brutally punish you for
these transgressions against us!
Please give us another
chance, Great Nobuseri!
[MANZO]
D-Don't do this!
Great Nobuseri!
[KIRARA]
Please wait!
[RIKICHI]
Water Priestess!
[MANZO]
What are you doing?
I have an offer for you.
Priestess, what are
you talking about?
[SOBEI] I take it...
you are the girl who went to
Kougakyo to recruit the Samurai?
[KIRARA] Yes.
[SOBEI]
What do you want?
I'm offering to give myself up,
to whatever fate
you choose for me,
in exchange for
my people's safety.
[SYUSAI] You want to
trade your life for theirs?
That's right.
You have a right to be angry.
And I realize it
might be satisfying
to destroy this village.
That would be the
easy thing to do.
But you Nobuseri were
once great samurai,
so you know a warrior doesn't
always do what's easiest.
If you allow yourselves to
be angered by mere farmers,
you will show
weakness and fear.
You will have nothing
distinguishing you from
the merchants or the samurai.
You'll be insignificant--
[SYUSAI] Silence!
You think you can get what you
want just by flapping your lips?
[SYUSAI LAUGHS]
I like that...
Well, little girl...
you belong to us now.
Bring her to me!
[BANDIT 1]
Yes, lord!
[SOBEI] Who would have thought
you could appease our rage
by making us
nostalgic about honor.
I hope you know what
you're doing, Priestess.
Elder?
[KATSUSHIRO GRUNTS]
[SYUSAI]
Don't get too cozy.
We're delivering
you to the capital.
Capital?
[SYUSAI] You sound
surprised. You didn't think
we were going to put you in
with those Samurai, did you?
After all, sweet girls
and sweet rice,
they both fetch a high price.
So is that where you've taken
all of the other women
you've abducted
from our villages?
[SOBEI]
You mean saved.
They're in paradise now
compared to the dung
heaps they called home.
How can they possibly be happy
when they're torn away from
their homes and their families?!
[SYUSAI] You'll see for
yourself soon enough.
[KIRARA GASPS]
[KIRARA SCREAMS]
[SYUSAI] Bring us up!
Take a last look.
Soon your memory
will be all that's left
of this wretched
village and its people.
But that's not
the deal we made!
You said you would spare
them in exchange for my life!
[SYUSAI]
I agreed to nothing.
All I said was that
you belonged to me.
And you call
yourself a samurai?
[SYUSAI]
Samurai are a thing of the past.
Please don't do this
to them! I'm begging you!
Oh man... Now I know
how the rice feels.
With as much as
you love the stuff,
I'd have figured...
you'd enjoy it!
I do like rice.
In fact, after we finish up
here, I could use a bowl or two.
[KAMBEI] Heihachi...
Get to the engine room.
You know what to do.
[HEIHACHI] Sure thing.
[KAMBEI]
All right... Let's go.
[BANDIT 3]
The samurai!
[BANDIT 4]
Get them!
Sorry to drop in
on you like this!
[BANDIT 5 LAUGHS]
[BANDIT 5 GROANS]
Heihachi... Go!
Hey...
I'm already gone!
Us too?
Kikuchiyo,
let's move!
[BANDIT 7]
What's wrong? Gotta go?
Too bad you're just
a lowly prisoner--
[BANDIT 7 GRUNTS]
You bastard!
Well then...
I guess it's time
to earn my keep.
What's the matter?
You haven't untied yourself yet?
Yeah, well I didn't study
circus tricks like you.
You gotta be kidding me...
No fun at all.
[SYUSAI]
Move in a little closer!
Please, Nobuseri, where is
your honor?! You can't do--
[SYUSAI]
Shut up and watch.
Come on guys...
You can at least try.
[BANDIT 10]
Quickly! Inform Lord Syusai!
Shichiroji!
I'm all over it!
[BANDIT 10] Damn you!
[KAMBEI] Come on.
That was incredible,
Gorobei-dono.
[GOROBEI] In case you
feel like helping out...
[BANDIT 15 YELLS]
Katsushiro!
I don't need your help!
Good to hear!
[KATSUSHIRO] I...
I am indeed...
...a samurai!
[KATSUSHIRO YELLS]
[BLOWS LAND]
[KATSUSHIRO BREATHES HEAVILY]
[KATSUSHIRO SCREAMS]
[FOOTSTEPS]
Let's go.
[HEIHACHI]
Here goes nothin'!
[RUMBLING]
[SYUSAI] What's this?!
We seem to be losing altitude!
[SOBEI]
Take care of it!
[YAKAN 1]
Yes, lord!
[KIRARA GASPS]
[SYUSAI] Huh...?
[YAKAN 2]
Show yourself!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Hey, what took you so long?
[BANDITS YELL]
[KIKUCHIYO] Come on!
Hurry it up there, body!
Great Kambei! You made it!
[SYUSAI]
Clever trick, samurai...
But now it ends.
[KIRARA GASPS]
[RAIDEN TEAM]
Raiden Squad, reporting!
[SYUSAI] They say
you are quite skilled.
But you're sadly outnumbered.
[BANDITS YELL]
Then let's even
things up a bit!
[KIKUCHIYO]
The ass kicking begins!
[SYUSAI]
Kill them!
[RAIDEN 1]
With pleasure...
What the...?!
[RAIDEN 1 YELLS]
[SOBEI] Kyuzo!
[GOROBEI]
You stay right here.
Whatever you say.
[GOROBEI] Heads up!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Yeah, funny.
Oh, yeah! Kikuchiyo's back!
Once I get my hands on you
Bandits, you're gonna seriousl--
[KATSUSHIRO YELLS]
Oh, no. Katsushiro!
[KATSUSHIRO SCREAMS]
[KIKUCHIYO] Hey, guys!
Leave some for me!
Sword! Sword?!
[SOBEI] Kyuzo...
[SOBEI YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO] Kyuzo!
[SOBEI]  Huh...?!
Kyuzo, go for his chest!
It's his weak point!
[SYUSAI]
Cursed samurai!
I hate guns.
[KIKUCHIYO] Look out!
[GUNFIRE]
[KIRARA GASPS]
Kyuzo-dono!
[SOBEI GASPS]
[SYUSAI]
I've had enough of you!
Ahh!
[HEIHACHI SCREAMS]
[VILLAGERS MURMUR]
[VILLAGERS YELL]
Great Samurai! Ah!
Lady Kirara!
[SYUSAI] You. In the
Great War, who did you serve?
From your tattered appearance,
you must have fought
on the losing side.
[KATSUSHIRO
BREATHES RAPIDLY]
[HEIHACHI GRUNTS]
Everybody, move!
[HEIHACHI YELLS]
Heihachi!
Get out--she's gonna blow!
Shichiroji.
Find a way out of here.
Sure thing!
You should get moving as well.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Don't have to tell me!
We did it!
[SHICHIROJI]
Not quite yet.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh. whadda ya mean?
[SHICHIROJI]
You're the anchor, big guy.
Kambei-sama!
[SYUSAI]
Samurai relic...
I am indeed... a samurai.
[KAMBEI]
We're done here!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Take your time there, Kambei!
[SHICHIROJI]
Let's move!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Yeah, okay!
So... this is it huh?
This is how it all
ends for Shichiroji?
Hanging off the
side of a canyon?
I must be losing my touch.
[KIKUCHIYO] What, you want me
to drop you, or something?
'Cause I will!
[SHICHIROJI] Whoa! Hey! Come
on now! Don't do anything rash!
[KATSUSHIRO
BREATHES HEAVILY]
♪ closing song ♪
[OKARA SNICKERS]
[OKARA] Hello.
It's Okara again.
[KOMACHI]  Hey! Why do you
get to do all the talking now?
This was my idea...
[OKARA] Okay, fine!
We'll do it together...
[KOMACHI] All right!
[OKARA]
I have a lot more respect
for your sister now, Komachi.
[KOMACHI]
Really? How come?
[OKARA]
She was willing to give her life
to the Bandits, to save us.
That takes some guts.
I doubt I could do it.
[KOMACHI]
I'm worried about her, though.
Ever since Katsu killed
his first Bandit,
she's acting been
kind of strange.
She seems really
sad about something,
and she isn't
talking very much.
[OKARA]
Oh, don't worry.
She's probably just
trying to help Katsu out.
[KOMACHI]
Help him? What do you mean?
I thought we were all trying
to help out all the samurai.
[OKARA] I'm not talking about
building walls, Komachi.
I'm talking about
grown up emotion stuff.
[KOMACHI]
You're so smart.
How do you know so much
about being an adult?
[OKARA] I don't know.
Guess I was born with it...
Oh, and all the
spying helps, too.
[OKARA SNICKERS]