[MASAMUNE] Besides being
accused of the envoy's murder,
he made an attempt
on the Emperor's life.
Sensei failed...
And now he's in trouble.
I knew it...
He never should have tried
to rescue them on his own.
I just wish you would've let me
bring you something other than
a riceball for your final meal.
No... After all, it was rice
like this that hired me...
I will not eat anything else
until that job is complete.
Aren't you brave enough to
kill without hiding your face?
So be it... Here you are.
Don't miss now.
♪ opening song ♪
I knew it.
Not bad!
For your own safety,
I recommend you get inside.
Amanushi, please!
[UKYO]
Oh, Kambei! Nicely done!
I must say,
seeing these feats of Samurai
skill is quite inspiring!
But hear me now...
Everyone here...
The time has come
to lay down our arms
and put aside
our differences...
The war is over!
And your days of
suffering are at an end.
But as your new Emperor,
I swear to you...
I will shatter
the cycle of violence...
And I will protect the
lives of all my people!
Beloved subjects!
Uhh...
It is true...
This samurai did try to
kill the former Emperor...
But his intention was
only to free the women
taken by my predecessor.
My friends,
I understand his actions...
Therefore, I have decided
to grant Kambei Shimada
a full pardon.
As for the women...
I hereby declare them all free!
Does he really mean all that?
I guess we were
wrong about him, huh?
Hoping for an heir,
my predecessor ruthlessly
abducted these women...
I know, it's terrible...
I honestly cannot blame
Kambei for his anger.
But Amanushi...
Tessai! See to the release
of the women personally...
Understood?
Well dear Kambei,
that's the end of that.
What about Kanna Village?
We are releasing the women...
It's all over...
Kanna Village is
free to live in peace.
Are you sure about this...?
Surely it will set
a bad precedent.
It's the old Emperor's fault...
And now all the
people know it...
They will blame him and
look to me as their savior.
I've just established my power.
Oh, it's you...
and how's Kirara doing?
It's Katsu!
Boy I tell ya...
he has got the worst timing.
Hey now, take it easy...
I just made a deal with your
gray-haired friend over there...
You wouldn't want to ruin it.
As if you could succeed
in taking the women...
You'll never make it
out of the Capital alive!
Hey, shut up...!
I don't want to hear
another word out of you!
It's not us you should
be worried about.
We're not bringing
you along with us
because we enjoy your
company, Ayamaro...
You're our human shield.
You don't scare me, farmgirl.
You're tougher
than I thought, Kirara.
Your sword.
Halt...!
Honored Ayamaro, this
is the inner chambers.
No one is allowed without
the Emperor's permission.
I'm sorry, but that
does not include you,
the Guardian or the--
What?
Intruder!
Uh, what gave us away?
Please, don't hurt me!
I'm their prisoner!
All right! Who wants some?!
Stop!
Kambei!
Thank goodness.
Tessai, what is
the meaning of this?
I've received orders from
the Emperor himself...
You are to release all of
the peasant women immediately.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Release? What's going on, Katsu?
I suggest you take the girls
and leave immediately...
Never return to the Capital.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Don't have to tell me twice!
[TESSAI]
Please, my lord.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Attention, ladies...!
We're looking for Sanae, wife
of Rikichi of Kanna Village.
Anyone?
[WARYA] Sanae?
Oh, you mean the
late Emperor's woman.
[KIKUCHIYO] I do?
She's in the back room.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh, thanks for the tip.
[KAMBEI]
Katsushiro.
Tell me why you've come.
I came because
I wanted to help you.
[KAMBEI SIGHS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
Daa-duh-duh-duh-Daaaa!
Rejoice! Kikuchiyo's here!
You're free!
You can all go home now!
Really?
We can return to our village?
[MIZUKI] Kambei!
Sanae...! Did you hear that?
[KIRARA] Sanae?
You're alive! I'm so relieved.
Who are you?
[KIRARA] Oh...
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to scare you...
It's Kirara.
The Water Priestess
from Kanna Village...
I'm here to take you back home.
Is it really you... Priestess?
But why...?
It's time to go home, Sanae.
Rikichi's waiting for you.
I can't go... I can't...
[MIZUKI]
Sanae, you shouldn't say that.
Your Emperor is dead now.
[KIKUCHIYO]
You know what's going on?
No.
Lady Sanae is carrying
the late Emperor's child.
[KIKUCHIYO]
What?! A baby?
Actually...
What happened?
The baby...
[SANAE]
...is dead.
My child is dead
and I killed him.
[MIZUKI] That's not true.
You couldn't have done anything.
The old Emperor died
and you fell ill from grief.
It's not your fault!
You needn't explain.
And I... I can never
return to Rikichi.
I will mourn the death of
my Amanushi and his child,
for the rest of my life.
[KIRARA] Sanae...
You will return home with us.
I won't leave you.
I cannot believe my predecessor
went to all that trouble
with the Nobuseri...
when the peasants are
so easily convinced
that the Capital is a true
friend of the people.
The peasantry is on your side...
Without exception, they have
embraced your reign...
Thanks to your
release of the women...
And your praise of Kanna,
they hold you in the
highest respect.
Huh, do you really think so?
Then perhaps we should
go visit them all.
What...? I don't understand.
The peasants have
never seen the Capital...
That is why they fear us...
Therefore we shall
bring it to them...
We shall make peace with
the farmers on their turf,
and they'll have no reason
to be afraid anymore.
And the final stop on
our list... Kanna Village.
Yes, milord.
If Kanna Village hadn't
hired those samurai,
we wouldn't be so close to
a glorious revolution right now.
The time has come
to repay the favor.
As you wish.
However... There's a slim
chance we may have a tragic...
...accident.
Huh...?
Any peasant who
has experienced war
will never be able to
return to peace...
I lived among them for so long
I understand how they think...
Now that they've enjoyed the
feel of political revolution
they will continue to crave it.
And that makes them
a danger to the Capital.
My Lord, take advantage
of this opportunity,
and flee the Capital with them.
You once ruled the
great city of Kougakyo.
You should not be forced to
waste away your remaining days
as a mere warehouse manager.
Then come with me... Tessai...
No, my lord, I'm afraid
that's not possible.
But... why not?
You were my most
trusted attendant.
And now I serve the Emperor.
[AYAMARO] Tessai...
[KIKUCHIYO]
Ladies! Please!
[TESSAI]
I'll tell the young master...
The peasants from Kanna took
you with them as their hostage.
He'll come after me.
No... It pains me to say it,
but you're no longer
of value to him.
But I... I'm his...
Sister!
[KOMACHI]
Komachi!
Sister!
[KOMACHI]
I'm so glad you're not dead!
I watched everything from here.
I saw Kambei do his
amazing escape trick
and I heard the new
Emperor tell that ugly man
to set all the women free...
And I guess we were
wrong about Ukyo--
I mean the new Emperor--
cause he's really great, huh?-
Don't you think so, sis, huh?
Uh... Uh-huh.
Do you really
believe that garbage?
Huh...? What garbage?
Those promises from
our "new Emperor"...
I don't care what Ukyo said,
I still don't trust him.
I can't bring myself to
believe it's all over.
[KIKUCHIYO] Enough with the
negative stuff already!
Everyone's safe! You're a hero!
Sanae! Sanae,
it's you! You're alive!
Whoooooa. Pretty kimono.
Oh, man! Did you get rich?
Little... Komachi?
The one and only...
And this is my sidekick... Kiku!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Your sidekick...!
What are you talking
about you little twerp?
I'm a samurai warrior!
[KOMACHI LAUGHS]
Is Rikichi here with you?
Huh?
[MAN A] Rice!
The Capital is giving
away free rice!
[MAN B]
Hurry, bring a basket!
So they think they can
win us over with rice, huh?
[PONYTAIL MAN]
Works for me!
[BUN MAN]
Hey, wait up!
[MEGAPHONE GUARD]
The Capital is promoting
its new revolutionary
government...
This rice is the celebration
of the inauguration
of the new Emperor.
Please limit yourself
to only what you can use.
[KIKUCHIYO BELLOWS]
[KIKUCHIYO LAUGHS]
Another samurai triumph!
[MASAMUNE]
Now then...
What's our next move gonna be?
We've got a pretty big crowd.
We'll go to Firefly House...
We can stay there for the night,
and then we'll head for
Kanna Village in the morning.
My sister's there?
No. We'll meet her on the way.
Oh, yes... I borrowed this.
This used to belong
to my mother.
Then, I humbly apologize...
Without it however, none
of us would be alive now.
Well... Maybe...
But I don't know Great Samurai,
this does make you a thief.
I guess it does.
Time to change, everyone!
Yeah! We got you something
real comfy, Sanae!
[AYAMARO WHIMPERING]
[AYAMARO WHIMPERS LOUDLY]
[MOHAWK]
Hey, Maro...
W-W-Wait...! What do
you want from me?
Did... Ukyo order this?
[AYAMARO]
K-K-Kyuzo?
Kyuzo... It's me...
[KYUZO] You will not harm him.
Nor Shimada Kambei.
Why not...? They deserve it.
[KYUZO]
Sorry you feel that way.
Wait!
Kyuzo, take me with you!
[YUKINO] Why do I
get the feeling
you didn't come for the tea?
We hoped you
could give us rooms...
We won't be staying very long.
Please, don't be so formal.
You're all welcome to stay
for as long as you would like.
Shichiroji is still
in Kanna Village.
Oh, that old bum...?
I'd almost forgotten
all about him...
And besides...
I've gotten used to
Shichiroji always being
the one who stays behind...
By the way, I heard what
happened to you today.
I'm glad you're all
safe and accounted for.
As I said, stay as
long as you like,
and don't worry about the bill.
I'll collect from
'Roji big-time later.
I made your bed for you.
So it's ready whenever
you want to turn in.
You must be exhausted.
I'm so sorry.
How is she doing?
Mizuki's with her right now.
But I'm worried about her...
I think we're going to take
turns looking in on her tonight
to make sure she's okay.
You won't get much
sleep that way...
If you'd like I would
be more than happy
to take turns with you.
Oh, we'll be all right...
But thank you anyway, Yukino.
How could everything
have turned out so badly?
How can she honestly believe
the man who held her hostage
is worth mourning over?
I saw the truth in her eyes...
She truly loved the Emperor.
You stormed the
Capital all by yourself
and that's all you have to say?
It is... I found my
weakness there, something...
...I couldn't kill with a sword.
[KATSUSHIRO]
Then I misjudged you, Sensei.
That's enough, you two.
[KIRARA] I feel
so bad for Rikichi...
What can we do to
help them, Kambei?
There's nothing
we can do for them.
How can you be so heartless?!
Then you tell me,
what can we do?
[KIRARA] You just don't
get it, Katsushiro.
You don't understand
how we women suffered
while the Bandits bled us
for rice all those years.
We were beasts of burden,
giving them our lives,
just to avoid
giving them our bodies.
Sanae sacrificed herself
willingly so the rest of us
would be allowed to stay in the
village with our families...
She gave her life for us...
And I didn't... I didn't do
anything to stop her...
If I had any kind
of courage at all...
Then she and Rikichi would
never have been apart.
That's enough...
It's all in the past.
[KIKUCHIYO] Well,
listen to you, Great Samurai!
Some female tricks you
into puttin' your head
on a chopping block and
you go all mushy on us!
She really did a number
on you, didn't she? Heh heh.
Why don't you put a lid
on that can of yours, Kiku?
That woman needs some time
to put her life back together,
and in the meantime
she needs our support...
Rikichi is the one
who can help her now
and your cracks aren't needed.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Why don't I crack your face?
That might be needed!
Then who's gonna repair you?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Hah!
Anyhow, you rescued
the women like you said,
and I guess that's
all that matters...
You completed your mission...
Isn't that right, Kambei?
You fools!
♪ closing song ♪
[KOMACHI] Dear Okara...
I couldn't wait to tell you
what happened today!
Remember how last time
I was so worried,
because Kambei was going
to get his head chopped off?
Well you should have seen it!
Right as the big mean
guy was swinging his ax,
Kambei did the most amazing
samurai escape ever!
He got away and
had his chains cut
and got the guy's weapon
all at the same time!
And then Katsushiro came out,
ready to save the day,
and Masamune was like,
"Boy, he's got bad timing!"
Heh! It was pretty funny.
I guess Katsu didn't need to
worry about Kambei after all.
Now the two of them seem
pretty mad at each other,
and I'm not sure why.
Oh yeah, even bigger news!
We saved Sanae!
Turns out she was
the old Emperor's Okata--
which means special
person, or something,
and she was going to
have the Emperor's baby!
She's really different now.
She says she doesn't
want to go back home,
or be with Rikichi at all.
Oh, you better not
tell him about all this.
I'm scared it's going
to make him really sad.
Well, I'll write again
soon, okay? Bye-bye!