[HEIHACHI] Let's go.
[SHINO]
Great Samurai, please! Wait!
Don't talk to me, girl.
I don't need any
more provocation.
If I had my way,
I'd take his life now.
[MANZO YELLS]
You must take care
of your swords...
I have made the blade
of your daito sharper.
A samurai is
one who kills.
[KIKUCHIYO] I can't blame Manzo,
conniving and pathetic as he is!
He just played the odds and
the Bandits won! That's all!
Farmers are corrupt!
But Bandits are corrupt!
And Samurai are corrupt!
Why would anyone risk
their lives for anyone?
But I'll fight for 'em.
I'll kill all the
Bandits! Damn it!
[KIKUCHIYO SOBS]
Damn it...
At last the seven are complete.
♪ opening song ♪
[KAMBEI] My lady.
[SETSU] Hmm...
Oh, it's you,
Great Samurai. Hello.
I wasn't expecting any
visitors in this dense fog.
Oh, but please,
come right on up.
No thanks,
this will be fine.
Hmm...
[SETSU]
Impressive, aren't they?
All of those books
belong to Kirara.
Your granddaughter
seems very well read.
I'm amazed
myself sometimes.
She's adored books
since she was a child.
She gets them from
Tortoise Express riders,
and passing merchants.
That interest in the
world sets her apart
from the other villagers,
don't you think?
[KIRARA]
Grandmother, I'm home.
[KOMACHI]
Oh! Hey, Katsu!
His name
is Katsushiro.
Show him respect
now, Komachi.
[KIRARA] May I ask you
why you're here, Kambei?
[KAMBEI] I've come to
ask a favor, Mikumari.
[KIRARA] A favor?
The Nobuseri could be
coming at any time...
and when they do,
I'd like the women and
children to stay here with you,
if that's all right.
If you're worried,
Katsushiro will stay
with you for protection.
No, Great Samurai,
we'll be fine alone...
Won't we now, Grandmother?
Yes... We'll be just fine.
Katsushiro, please...
Join the fight
alongside the others.
[KOMACHI GIGGLES]
May I speak with you...
privately please?
[KIRARA] Katsushiro?
He is still unable
to take a life
unless it is
for protection.
I fear he is too
naïve for real battle.
With respect...
I believe Katsushiro knows
himself better than you do.
Perhaps you're wrong.
[KIRARA]
But no matter what,
I will stand beside him on his
path to become a great samurai.
And if any bloodstains
are left on him...
I will be the one
to clean them off.
I believe that is my duty
as a leader and
a friend, don't you?
I see... Then I ask you only
be prepared for what may come.
Of course... I understand.
[KOMACHI]
Whoa. Too much drama.
[OKARA]
Hey! Did I miss anything?
Keep it down.
We're on a covert
operation here.
Hey! Did I miss anything?
[KIKUCHIYO] Boring.
Huh...?
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS] Haa...!
[RIKICHI YELLS WORRIEDLY]
[RIKICHI] Kikuchiyo!
[KIKUCHIYO] That's not
how you hold it, you know.
What are you doing
with that sword?
I... just...
[KIKUCHIYO] It's too
late now to keep secrets.
I just want to learn
how to defend myself.
I'm sick and tired
of feeling helpless!
I want to fight
for my village!
I want to use this sword
to kill the bandits!
How can I get a
body like yours?
[KIKUCHIYO] You want
to be a machine samurai?
Mm-hmm...
[KIKUCHIYO]
And why is that?
So I can kill the bandits...!
I don't want to sit back
and watch you samurai
do it all for us!
I can't be weak anymore--
I want to be like you!
[KIKUCHIYO]
You don't want this.
But why not?
Rikichi... When you
get your wife back,
how will you love her
if you look like this?
Stand up!
You want to learn
to use a sword or not?!
[RIKICHI AND KIKUCHIYO GRUNT]
That Kikuchiyo.
He's completely forgetten
he's on guard duty.
You're surprised?
Let him be for a while--
I'll take his post.
Why?
'Cause he's found a much
more important job.
[RIKICHI GRUNTS]
[FARMERS LAUGH]
It happened again!
Most of us are
getting pretty good,
but not you Yohei!
Just ignore him.
It was a pretty decent shot
for having your eyes
closed the whole time.
It's not my fault!
It's the bow!
Heh. Yeah, sure,
blame the equipment.
That's not fair!
I work twice as hard
as the rest of you guys!
[FARMERS LAUGH]
Great Samurai?
It's time.
[FARMERS GASP]
[GOROBEI]
It's quiet... Too quiet.
They can hide the sound.
But not the smell.
What's that mean?
Heh... Means this evening's
program has just been altered.
[SHICHIROJI] Oh, yeah...
About seven or eight miles off.
[CLACKING]
It begins.
[HEIHACHI]
Okay, that looks good!
Let's get to our
battle stations!
Get all the women and children
to the Mikumari's home, now!
I want all of them
off the streets
when the fighting begins.
[HEIHACHI]
Heave...! Heave...! Heeeave!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh yeah! They're here!
The bandits are finally here
for their ass beating!
Let's go, suckers!
Huh...?
Why are there so many of them?
There's a lot more
than we were expecting.
[MOSUKE] Hey!
How's it lookin' out there?
Ahh...!
[MANZO]
We did make the Bandits angry.
They're gonna kill us!
I just know it!
Manzo, how can you say
that after all our work?!
Are you kidding me?!
Just look how many there are!
There's no way we
can beat all of them,
no matter what the
samurai have taught us...!
Maybe we should go
beg for mercy now.
And you think
they'll forgive us
after we've been training
so long to defeat them?
We have to make sure they
aren't alive to punish us later!
There's more than expected
but our mission's the same.
Whoa.
That's a lot of Bandits.
[RUMBLING]
And stop!
Okay! Let's pin it down!
[KAMBEI]
You've done good work!
[HEIHACHI] Hey, anybody
order some bandits?
Cause there's a whole army
of them headed this way.
You worried about them?
Why should I be...?
I got nothing to lose...
Hey, by the way...
Have you seen Kikuchiyo around?
[KIKUCHIYO]
I'm right here!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
You know your post.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Right, boss!
[KAMBEI] Rikichi.
You will fire it.
[RIKICHI] I will?
You wanted revenge, didn't you?
Don't worry,
it's easy--
all you have to do is
knock off the clasp--
it's just like hitting a nail.
Everyone! Man your stations!
[SHICHIROJI]
Man your stations!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Move! Move! Clear a path!
The trigger-men
are coming through!
Load the ballista!
[FARMER 2]
[KIKUCHIYO]
I'm on it!
[KIKUCHIYO GRUNTS]
Ah! That was my house!
That was my house!
Don't be an idiot, Manzo!
We'll build you
a new one, okay?!
[MANZO SOBS]
[HEIHACHI]
That's good! Stop!
[GONZO]
[KIKUCHIYO BREATHES HEAVILY]
[HEIHACHI] Ballista
armed and ready to fire!
[KIKUCHIYO] Come on...
[BANDIT 1]
This is no idle threat.
Drop your weapons, and
cross the bridge one at a time.
Fire.
[SHICHIROJI] Fire!
[FARMER 4] Fire!
[RIKICHI YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
There it goes!
[FARMERS CHEER]
[KIKUCHIYO] Yeah! You had
that one coming! Ha, ha, ha!
[FARMERS CHEER]
Kan-na! Kan-na! Kan-na! Kan-na!
[KOMACHI]
Wow! They did it!
[OKARA]
Awesome!
[KIRARA] Girls!
What are you doing up there?
Come inside!
[KOMACHI] But, sis,
we wanna watch.
It's a war.
And the war has only just begun.
[FARMERS CHEER]
Wait...! Look over there!
They're... They're coming!
[KAMBEI] Stay calm!
All archers ready your bows!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Here they come!
This is gonna be great!
Fire at will.
[MANZO YELLS]
Don't lower your bows.
Keep firing.
[KIKUCHIYO] Heh, heh...
Serves you right!
Who's tough, now, huh?!
For all their weapons,
metal and might,
not one could endure
a wall of fire,
and a hard canyon floor.
[FARMERS BREATHE HEAVILY]
None of the samurai
even broke a sweat.
Just killing as if
it were nothing...
and watching it all
with those cold eyes.
[KIKUCHIYO]
You guys were awesome!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[MANZO GASPS]
Bring me a rope.
[MOSUKE]
Elder...! Elder!
[MOSUKE BREATHES HEAVILY]
[ELDER] The first wave
of Bandits were stopped?
Yes... They were...
We killed them...
We shot them down with
our bows and arrows.
And did you make
the Bandits suffer?
Yes, they
suffered horribly!
[ELDER LAUGHS]
[ELDER]
That's as it should be...
[MOSUKE] But, Elder, you know
the bandits will never give up.
They'll be back!
What'll we do then?
We may have won this time,
but how can we stop them again?!
Mosuke...
Elder, I really think we
made a big mistake here!
Mosuke!
You want to live,
don't you?
Yes, of course!
Then fight,
Mosuke. Fight!
[BANDIT 2]
What a damned disgrace.
We attack them head on,
and this is what it gets us.
[BANDIT 3] The farmers have
been taught to wield bows.
[SOBEI]
Quite a declaration of war.
They must think they'll
get away with defying us.
[SYUSAI] Forget the farmers.
I want the samurai.
Behind.
What, sister?
The turbulent fog...
It calls for change.
[ELDER] Huh...?
They're back?
Don't worry.
We'll be fine, no matter what.
Kiku will take care
of everything. He promised.
[FARMERS YELL FEARFULLY]
[SOBEI] Wait.
Over there... The farmers.
[MANZO YELLS FEARFULLY]
[FARMERS YELL FEARFULLY]
[RIKICHI] Please,
we beg you, let us explain!
[SOBEI]
Very well... You may try.
We realize now that we
made a terrible mistake.
We were hungry and
scared we'd starve,
but we had no right
to do what we did--
we had no right
to turn against you.
[SOBEI] And how did you make
such an error in judgment?
[RIKICHI] We forgot that
we're merely farmers.
That we're tenants of this
land and have no right to it.
We hired samurai to fight
the Nobuseri for us,
But we didn't know
how war would be.
And now we owe them too much
and we just want our
simple lives back.
We were selfish and greedy,
and thought we
didn't need you...
Foolish...
We should have known we'd never
be able to make it on our own.
We realize we don't
deserve your mercy,
but we beg you to believe us.
We'll never try to go
against you again. We swear!
Please, say you'll spare us
just this once, Great Nobuseri.
We want to give you this
rice as a peace offering.
And there's more
of it come! Please!
[SYUSAI]
Of course we'll take your rice,
whether it's for peace or not.
But we want more than that.
Where are the samurai?
They're here...
We offer them to you also.
♪ closing song ♪
[OKARA SNICKERS]
[OKARA] Okara here...
Today was finally our
chance to face the Bandits.
The giant crossbow
we built was amazing.
It shot the trunk of one our
biggest trees through the air,
all the way across the canyon,
and drove right through
one of those giant ships.
All the men were jumping
around and yelling--
it was probably the most
exciting thing I've ever seen.
I've got to hand it to Kambei.
He sure knows how to fight.
But then, I've heard he's
lost every war he's been in.
I wonder how that could be.
Maybe we'll see with
the next secret plan of his
if he's not so
perfect after all...
I mean, Kirara did tell him
he was wrong in the forest,
when she was
sticking up for Katsu.
You have one heck
of an older sister,
don't you, Komachi?
She's not scared of anything.
They say the samurai came
here because of the rice,
but I think they came for her.
Well, the Bandits are
really angry right now,
and they're bound
to want revenge.
I wouldn't be surprised if this
is the last one of these
messages we get to make!
[OKARA SNICKERS]