I'm offering to give myself up,
to whatever fate
you choose for me,
in exchange for
my people's safety.
[SOBEI] You want to trade
your life for theirs?
That's right.
Katsushiro!
[KATSUSHIRO]
I don't need your help!
Good to hear!
[KATSUSHIRO YELLS]
Kyuzo, go for his chest!
It's his weak point!
[SYUSAI]
Samurai relic...
I am indeed... a samurai.
♪ opening song ♪
Thanks. I'm all right.
[KIRARA GASPS]
This looks bad.
It looks worse than it is.
[KIKUCHIYO] Persistent
little bugs, aren't they?
Tobito!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO GRUNTS]
Kikuchiyo-dono!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Damn! Huh...?!
[KIKUCHIYO GRUNTS]
[KATSUSHIRO GRUNTS]
[BUZZING]
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KATSUSHIRO
BREATHES HEAVILY]
[KIKUCHIYO]
Back to where you came from.
[GUNSHOT]
[KIKUCHIYO] Huh?!
A sniper!
Now that's a problem...
In this fog, we can't tell where
the shots are coming from.
So what do you suggest now?
We send out a scout.
[KIKUCHIYO]
No problem. Just leave it to me.
You'll be too loud.
[KIKUCHIYO] Don't have
to be a jerk about it.
I can take care of it.
You'd die.
Heh...
[GUNSHOTS]
Don't worry,
he'll be back.
He still has a score
to settle with me.
The smoke and mist
will be his allies.
[RAIDEN 1] Huh...?
[RAIDEN 1]
Damn them!
[SYUSAI] No...
[RAIDEN 1]
What--?!
[SYUSAI] Not like this.
We can't defeat them
if we're not prepared.
They're too well trained.
And I do intend to defeat them.
Especially him.
He has the eyes of a dead man.
[FARMER 1]
It's them!
[FARMER 2]
They did it!
[FARMER 3]
The samurai are alive!
[FARMER 4] I can't
believe it. They made it!
Sister...? Sister!
Komachi!
[KOMACHI] Sister!
I'm sorry my darling...
it's okay.
I should have known.
You always make it, don't you?
[KIKUCHIYO]
You got that right.
Your sister's somethin' else.
Didn't flinch for a second when
she was facing those Benigumo.
She's got more guts than
most warriors I know.
Wow... You really think so?
[KIKUCHIYO] You should
go get yourself a bath...
Maybe get some sleep as well.
Yes...
We all should.
Great Samurai, we can never
thank you enough for this.
The Nobuseri have
finally been beaten.
Uh... But where's Kyuzo?
[KAMBEI]
Scouting the enemy.
They will be
back, you know.
What for?
Why would they?
Just look what we did to them.
[YOHEI]
They lost...!
They'll be too afraid
to come back, right?
[KAMBEI]
That's not how they work.
[FARMERS] Oh...
Those who have been
wounded want only one thing,
and that's revenge...
We have no doubts
that they will be back.
It's just a matter of when...
but, they're desperate now.
Will you be ready to face them?
[ELDER GRUNTS]
[KIRARA] Rikichi...
There's something I need
to tell you about Sanae.
[RIKICHI] The capital?!
[KIRARA] Yes...
The Bandits' leader told me
that's where they brought
the rice and the women...
And he had no reason to lie.
[ELDER]
To the capital, eh...?
[KIRARA]
Yes, Elder.
I always assumed the Bandits
kept Sanae and other
women for themselves,
but apparently they sell them
to the Emperor, instead.
What can we do?!
We don't even know
where the capital is!
Great Kambei...
Do you know its location?
[KAMBEI] No.
Who knows how many great cities
are floating above our heads.
Rikichi...
Can you fight?
Of course...
I'll fight... I have to!
The villagers...
I know they're
storing rice.
I want you to tell them
to bring it out of hiding.
What for?
Tell them they
can eat their fill...
Tell them there's no need
to hide it anymore...
That tomorrow's dinner waits
for them in the fields...
The Nobuseri won't
get one grain.
[BIRDS CHIRP]
[DING]
[SETSU] I offer my thanks
for protecting my granddaughter
and bringing her
home to us safely...
For putting off the time when
she is reunited with you.
I am grateful.
Huh...?
Is that you, dear?
You can come in, you know.
[KIRARA]
Yes, maam.
[SETSU] Come over here
where I can see you.
Well, dear... Is there
anything you want to say
to your mother and father
now that they're listening?
We were just talking about
how reckless you were,
running off with the bandits
and giving your poor
grandmother a heart attack.
Hmm...?
I wanted to be strong
like the samurai.
They give to us so selflessly.
My word...
How wonderful it must feel to
be in love in the midst of war.
In love?
[SETSU SIGHS]
[FARMER 5]
C'mon, push harder!
[FARMERS GRUNT]
[GOROBEI] Well...?
If you want to talk, speak up.
Gorobei...? I know you used to
be a street performer, right?
Well, I was wondering
if you'd ever...
If you'd ever been...
[GOROBEI]
...to the capital? No.
Oh, I see.
[GOROBEI] My understanding is
that merchants built the city
shortly after the war ended.
Are you planning a visit?
[RIKICHI GRUNTS]
[GOROBEI]
Well then...
We'd better make sure
to win this war first.
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KIDS LAUGH]
[KIKUCHIYO]
I'm coming after you!
Here I come!
[BOY 1]
Take this, bandit! Hah!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh! They got me! Oh!
[BOY 2]
We defeated the bandit! Yeah!
[BOY 1] You can't beat us!
We're samurai!
[BOY 3]
Don't ever come back!
[KIKUCHIYO] Please, don't!
Samurai are so scary!
Hey, that's pretty good
acting... for a machine.
[KIKUCHIYO]
For a machine?!
[KOMACHI] Yeah. And it's
really good for a 13-year old!
Really...?
He's only 13?
[KIKUCHIYO] Shut up.
[BOY 2] Come on,
Mr. Samurai, play again!
[BOY 1] I get to be
head samurai this time!
[BOY 3] Yeah!
You keep being the Bandit!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh... Again?
[CLANK]
Ha, ha, ha! I win!
[BOYS LAUGH]
[KIKUCHIYO] Those parts
cannot be replaced!
Ohhh...
Kikuchiyo sure is popular
among the kids, isn't he?
And it's been like
that since he got here.
I'm sure he's sick of them.
Hey mom, we're hungry
can we have some rice?!
Where did you boys
leave the samurai?
Take it easy, boys.
Oh, Kambei.
[KAMBEI]
Has the rice cooled yet?
[SHINO]
Yes, help yourself.
Actually, if it's
alright with you
I'd like you to give it
to the men instead.
[SHINO] Sure!
Kirara... Is it ready?
Yes.
It's right here.
Like you asked.
Thanks.
Is your wound still
hurting you at all?
Not so much.
Is that
firefly gruel?
[KAMBEI GRUNTS]
I had a certain
craving for it today.
Are you sure you want that?
We have plenty of
riceballs for everyone.
White rice prepares
a man's body...
But only firefly gruel
prepares his soul.
Kirara... Shichiroji, too.
[KIRARA]
Here you go.
All right... If you insist.
The people of Kanna village
are like this firefly
gruel, Shichiroji.
A simpler food often
ignored or thrown aside
for the heartier grain.
And we samurai are the cup...
A symbol of our
duty to protect
those less fortunate than
ourselves. Understand?
[SHICHIROJI] I understand
you're as kind as ever.
Perhaps that's why
I keep losing battles.
[SHICHIROJI]
What do you think?
It's great!
White rice
is my favorite ever!
Is that so...? Then you'd
better eat some more.
You want to grow up big
and strong, don't you?
Yeah! I wanna grow
up big and strong
so I can be a samurai like you!
Me too!
Me three!
And why do you want
to become a samurai?
Because you samurai
are really strong.
And you can totally kill
all the bandits, easy!
[KAMBEI] You really think
you want to be like me?
Uhh...
Good job, guys!
I don't know how you
guys stay so serious
with these great
riceballs to eat.
Mm! Oh, man...!
I've said it before
and I'll say it again:
Kanna grows the
best rice around!
What's the matter?
Aren't you hungry?
Great Samurai
Katsushiro says
the Bandits may
come at any time.
We can't afford to relax--
We must always be prepared
to defend our village.
If a guard is truly
performing his duty
he has no time for food.
But if you stand here
looking fierce all day,
you won't have any strength left
to fight when they get here,
and how will
that help anyone?
Dig in!
I will not let
Katsushiro down.
Oh, well... You're too
tough for me to crack.
[KATSUSHIRO] Listen up.
This village is a fortress
and it must be guarded.
Do not forget: you are now
soldiers of Kanna Fortress.
And as soldiers,
you must always--
[HEIHACHI] You know you're just
making them nervous, right?
Heihachi-dono...
How can you act so casual?
Sensei told us the
war's not yet over.
Are you guys scared?
Mm-Hmm...
Fine...! But I'm not scared.
No? Then you must not be
seeing things very clearly.
Katsushiro...
When you have taken a life...
you've never looked your
opponent in the eye, have you?
What's that got to
do with anything?
[HEIHACHI] You know, before
we fought the Bandits,
I had never taken
a life either.
It's no secret that you and I
have less battle experience
than the other samurai.
That's a bond we share...
And like you,
when this war began,
I was seeing things
through different eyes.
I couldn't see
the enemy clearly.
But something in my memory
poked to the surface...
You know where it came from?
The battlefield...
Long ago, I was in a
place just like this...
And when I realized that,
I felt at ease...
It was like...
I was home again... You know?
Now you can see... your enemy?
[HEIHACHI] Yes...
And I have no more doubts.
That's where you and I differ:
You're growing more passionate,
and I'm just growing
more cynical.
[KATSUSHIRO]
But Heihachi-dono...
You'd never end up as bitter
as Honoka or Manzo...
[HEIHACHI]
Betrayal leaves a wound
far worse than any
sword, Katsushiro.
Regardless of the reason,
it can never be justified.
The pain of betrayal
remains in the traitors heart...
And it never goes away.
[KATSUSHIRO] Sensei!
[HEIHACHI]
When did you get here?
[SHICHIROJI] Oh, around
"Like I was home again."
[HEIHACHI]
Man, you guys are everywhere!
Is that--?
[SHICHIROJI] Firefly gruel.
Uhh...
Don't worry.
It's not for you.
A samurai toast before battle.
A samurai toast?
[CLACKING]
What is it,
Great Samurai?
Be quiet.
He's alone.
Yes... But...
Kyuzo-dono!
[HEIHACHI GRUNTS]
Think we can use it?
[HEIHACHI]
I'll check it out.
Good work, Kyuzo.
I took out a Raiden...
Thirty remain.
Mostly Yakan and
Tobito... A few Yoroi.
When will
they be here?
By tomorrow.
I need sleep.
Katsushiro.
[KATSUSHIRO]
Yes, sensei?
Tomorrow we win or
lose this battle...
I want you to make sure
the guards get some sleep
by changing shifts
once every hour.
Do you understand?
Yes.
[KATSUSHIRO GASPS]
[KYUZO]
Do you want to die?
I...I think you're...
you're an admirable person.
That's all I wanted to say...
Forgive my rudeness.
Hmm...
You should go get some sleep.
No thanks.
I couldn't sleep now.
When you close your
eyes you see her...
[SHICHIROJI]
Kambei-sama.
You need rest too, you know.
I'm finishing our plan--
I want to destroy them
completely, one by one.
I guess it's karma.
[SHICHIROJI] I never imagined I
would stand beside you again...
to gaze at the moon
over another battlefield.
[KIRARA GASPS]
[KIRARA] A storm!
A storm is approaching!
Are you sure?
[KATSUSHIRO]
All of them are so amazing!
But not like Kyuzo-dono.
In fact, what he did today was
the first time I really sensed
his true samurai spirit.
He's strong and he's brave.
He took that gun
from the bandits
without showing the
slightest hint of fear!
He's both a man and a warrior.
I have nothing
but respect for him.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Heh! You're really somethin'.
You know that, kid?
If he's so damn great,
why was he playing bodyguard
to a merchant pig like Maro?
Well, he--
[KIKUCHIYO] You're lookin'
up to the wrong guy, buddy!
Every samurai has
made hard choices!
Kyuzo-dono
became what he is
because he refused to give up
what it means to be a samurai.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh, enough all ready!
Don't you have somewhere
you should be right now?
Go stand watch or somethin'!
[THUD]
Oh, man...
I thought I was on edge.
[KATSUSHIRO]
And then Heihachi-dono said,
"You've never looked your
opponent in the eye, have you?"
...and he's right.
My hands still don't
feel like they've killed.
I get this rage and
my body's on fire...
I can't feel my feet
on the ground... and I...
I guess it's better than nothing
but I should be calm...
Like sensei is...
like Kyuzo-dono is...
I don't think I'll ever be able
to wield my sword like them.
I'll never be...
strong like them.
And that's why...
Why I can't let you
fall with me anymore.
[KIKUCHIYO]
What are you doing?
[KAMBEI] In case our own
swords should break.
I want a good battle.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Right. You can count on that.
[KATSUSHIRO]
Sensei, they're here! Sensei!
It's time.
♪ closing song ♪
[OKARA SNICKERS]
[OKARA] Hey, it's Okara.
Don't tell Komachi
I'm here without her...
Rain's such a pain.
And it'll make this
war even tougher.
I'm tired, and all the
other villagers are, too.
But the samurai
still have energy.
The longer this goes on,
the more lively they get.
I wonder if they're
really machines,
just with skin on top,
and fighting is like their fuel.
That'd be pretty weird.
That quiet samurai, Kyuzo,
earned a lot of points
today with everyone,
jumping into the
enemy's camp like that.
And now I think he's Katsu's
favorite--even more than Kambei.
That guy's such a flip-flopper.
But he's not all bad.
He really wants to prove
he can be a real samurai.
Kambei says that win or lose,
everything will be
decided in this fight.
That's putting a lot of pressure
on us all, if you ask me.
Honestly, I'm pretty scared.
I think I'm going
to go hide now.
I hope people are still
around when I come back.
[OKARA SNICKERS]