[RURAL GIRL AND
RURAL BOY LAUGH]
[RURAL MAN GASPS]
Shichiroji...
We're going to drive straight
into that enemy battleship...
Buy some time for our allies.
So they can retreat safely.
A losing battle, huh?
[KAMBEI]
It's all we've got.
Commander, flip the
Pressure-Valves to wide open.
Propulsion Drive to Maximum.
Pulse Armor on Forward Defense.
We're going in.
[YELLING]
[PERCUSSIVE CHIMING]
[VILLAGERS CHANT]
[KIRARA] ♪ Patient
looking, ardent search, ♪
♪ Searching for the truth... ♪
♪ Ardent looking,
patient search, ♪
♪ Find the truth we need... ♪
♪ Open soul... Open eyes... ♪
♪ Divining world
wherein truth lies... ♪
♪ Patient looking,
ardent search, ♪
♪ Nature, hear our call... ♪
♪ Ardent looking,
patient search, ♪
♪ Water, hear our plea... ♪
♪ Open soul... Open eyes... ♪
♪ Divining world
wherein truth lies... ♪
♪ Patient looking,
ardent search, ♪
♪ Searching for the truth... ♪
♪ Ardent looking,
patient search, ♪
♪ Find the truth we need... ♪
[PERCUSSIVE CHIMING]
[KIRARA]
The water has spoken. How many?
Seven tablets.
Dig seven times with seven turns
where the Dowsing
Crystal points.
The water will be waiting.
Will it definitely
be enough for a well?
This will sure help us out.
Yeah, I was scared
when the well dried up--
I thought it was the last
thing our village could take.
But the Priestess
has saved us.
[MANZO GRUNTS]
Thank you for your help.
We would be lost without you.
She helps us with everything.
Hey what's the matter, Komachi?
[KOMACHI WHINES]
My stomach's growling!
[KIRARA LAUGHS]
[KIRARA SIGHS]
[KIRARA GASPS]
[RUMBLING]
[RIKICHI]
Why are they here?
They know it's not
harvesting season yet.
[MOSUKE] They take
more than rice now.
I heard of another village where
they took their livestock--
and then they came back
and took their women too,
daughters, wives,
it didn't matter.
They took them all.
[RIKICHI] Then we have to
get the Water Priestess
to the shrine!
What if they see her?
[MOSUKE]
Cursed Bandits...
[RIKICHI] It's almost
harvesting season.
They probably came today to
see how the rice was growing--
to see how much
they could get.
[MOSUKE] I can't believe
it's already been a year.
[MANZO] And they're going
to take it all again.
[RIKICHI]
It gets worse every year.
It's like negotiating
with wolves.
You give them your arms,
then they ask for your legs!
Can't we do something?
I can't sleep anymore.
Every night, I think
I hear them coming.
I hear that rumbling
of their machines.
[YOHEI] We're all suffering.
But what can we do?
[RIKICHI] We have
to fight the Bandits.
Rise up and kill
them ourselves!
[MOSUKE] Kill the No-Buseri?
That's madness.
[RIKICHI] It's the only
way we'll keep them from
taking all we have!
[YOHEI]
How can we battle them?!
We're just farmers, and they're
the Bandits! The No-Buseri!
They've turned themselves
into weapons--
they fly in giant machines,
with swords the size of houses!
They rule over everything!
[RIKICHI] So we should
break our backs all year,
just so they can
have fat stomachs?
[MANZO] It's like an
earthquake, Rikichi.
All we can do is bear it, and
give the Bandits what they want.
Other villages have
tried to fight back,
and they were massacred.
It's better to lose
our rice than our lives.
[MANZO YELLS]
[RIKICHI]
What are you talking about?
Without the crop,
we'll be dead anyway!
[MOSUKE]
Rikichi, please. Stop.
[RIKICHI] No. We can't
be cowards anymore!
[MOSUKE] I know you're mad,
but we've all had losses.
[RIKICHI]
You haven't lost anything!
[ELDER]
We'll fight them.
We'll make our stand...
Against the Bandits.
Elder,
that's impossible!
We're rice growers--
We don't know
anything about war!
That's why we're hiring Samurai.
[GASPING]
[VILLAGERS MURMUR WORRIEDLY]
But I've never heard
of a village of peasants
hiring samurai, Elder.
I have witnessed it
with my own eyes,
after the Great War
ended, and the Bandits
pillaged the countryside
completely unchecked...
Out of all the
villages that I passed,
only one had not
been burned to the soil,
one that had hired Samurai--
Only they can
compete with Bandits.
[RIKICHI] Yes, Elder, of course!
That's what we have to do!
[MANZO] But Samurai
are expensive and proud,
and the only thing we have
of value is the harvest.
I doubt they're going
to fight to save us
in the name of sympathy
and a few bowls of rice.
[ELDER]
Then find hungry samurai.
[VILLAGERS]
Huh...?
Even bears will come out of the
forest if they're hungry enough.
[GOSAKU]
But if we really want Samurai,
then someone will
have to go into the city.
[MOSUKE]
And that's dangerous, too!
[RIKICHI]
Then I volunteer.
[ELDER]
Ahh... Very good, Rikichi.
[KIRARA] Elder?
I'd like to go too,
if you'll let me.
[MATRIARCH]
Kirara, please.
I must... I can use
my talents to divine
which Samurai are most
suited for saving us.
No one questions
your abilities, Priestess,
but Samurai don't
behave like water...
Besides, the city is
dangerous for anyone,
especially
young girls...
I'm not afraid of it...
And Rikichi will be with me.
Of course, I trust
your wisdom over mine.
Then it's decided...
We are counting on you
as always, Water Priestess.
I know.
Before the ears of
rice begin to bend,
bring us Samurai
who can defend us...
Our hope... Now rests on that.
You girls don't need to worry.
I'll protect you with my life.
And we are grateful
for that, Rikichi.
I'm not worried at all, sis.
I know your crystal
will find them.
You were very sweet
to come along, Komachi.
I wanted to
go exploring too,
and see the whole
big rest of the world.
I can't let you have
all the fun on your own.
So that's why...
I thought you wanted to help.
[HISSING]
[DOGS BARK]
Oh boy... That smells good.
[RIKICHI GRUNTS]
[KIRARA GASPS]
[RIKICHI]
The rice...
Thief! Stop!
[RIKICHI]
Please, that's our rice!
Help us, somebody!
Thief!
Stop whispering
and walking
and pretending like
you don't even hear!
Just somebody
stop him, please!
Catch the thief!
[THIEF YELLS]
[RIKICHI BREATHES HEAVILY]
[KATSUSHIRO] You're lucky
I'm not turning you in.
[RIKICHI] Oh, Great Samurai,
thank you so much...
We don't deserve
your graciousness.
Please, get up, it
wasn't that big of a deal.
Get away from that...!
That's our rice!
Please, stop it! Stop!
[KATSUSHIRO]
Leave this man alone!
[MEN YELL FEARFULLY]
No...
Our precious rice...
[RIKICHI]
Just help... It's okay now...
I was afraid... it was gone...
I'm... hungry...
And we almost lost it...
We almost lost it all...
But we didn't,
Komachi, okay?
But what if we did?
Then we wouldn't have anything!
No, Great Samurai, please!
Don't get on your
hands and knees for us.
We can pick it up on our own.
You're going to embarrass me
if you keep talking like that.
It's a part of Bushido to
help those in need... Here.
Thank you.
[KOMACHI]
Thanks for everything!
[KIRARA] Yes, we owe
you a great deal now.
[KATSUSHIRO]
Some advice;
don't walk around with your
rice in plain view.
Find a safe place to stay,
away from all the crowds.
[KIRARA] We will.
[KATSUSHIRO] I wish you the
best of luck. Farewell.
[RIKICHI] Wait, Great Samurai,
can we ask you something?
Go ahead.
We wanted to, uh--
No...
He isn't the one.
Are you sure, Priestess?
He is a samurai, and he's
stopped one thief already--
and he seems
perfectly willing to help.
The Dowsing Crystal
didn't choose him.
He doesn't have
the scent of battle.
[HOTEL KEEPER]
Rooms to rent for the night!
Clean floors and fair rates.
Don't miss out!
[ONLOOKER] Come on! He's holed
up at the end of the street!
Sounds like there's
some trouble down there...
Huh...?
[KOMACHI]
Sister, wait!
[SHOP WOMAN]
Please, help us.
My child's in there.
[KATSUSHIRO]
Can you tell me what happened?
[SHOP MAN]
A burglar broke into our shop.
He was sneaking
around in the back.
I found him, and
I tried to scare him off,
but he grabbed the baby--
he said he'd kill our child
if we called the authorities.
[KATSUSHIRO]
Then it's just the one man?
Yes, and he's still inside!
[KOMACHI]
Hey... is that the same one?
[KATSUSHIRO]
All right. I'll do what I can.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Hold on there, boy...
You're going to need some
muscle in a battle like this.
I'll help you out.
A battle...?
Look, I mean
no offense,
but this
isn't warfare...
It's just a
burglary gone wrong.
[KIKUCHIYO] Right...
Everything's a battle, kid.
Hey, shopkeeper, I might have
to crack a few eggs here--
Lose the shop to save the kid.
But you're not going to raise
a stink about that, are you?
[SHOP MAN] No, please--
Whatever it takes!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Very good. You're a wise man.
[KIKUCHIYO LAUGHS]
[CROWD MURMURS]
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[BABY CRIES]
[KIKUCHIYO]
The standoff's over...
Hand me the kid.
Wait, you're a samurai,
aren't you?
[KIKUCHIYO]
'Course I am!
Now, why'd you go causing
all this trouble?
If you were really a samurai,
you'd know that answer...
I haven't seen
food in a week...
I've been on the
street since the war!
I had greater
ambitions that that!
I was supposed to be an officer,
not some beggar in the slums!
[KIKUCHIYO] How sad...
I'm warning you!
Keep away from me!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO] Huh...?!
[CROWD MURMURS WORRIEDLY]
What's wrong,
samurai...?
If you want to save
the kid, then strike me now!
[CROWD YELLS FEARFULLY]
Stay away...!
I'm not bluffing!
Maybe you're afraid
to die, but I'm not...!
If the battles are over,
I'll start one here!
[KIKUCHIYO] What are you
talking about, you senile mule!
This isn't a battle!
It's just a burglary!
Just a burglary gone wrong!
It's high time
I found you... Samurai.
You don't recognize me...?
I'm not surprised.
The name's Zaemon
Yoshichika the Peaceable.
I was only a boy when
you killed my parents.
I've devoted my life
to their vengeance--
and though I wasn't
expecting to find you today,
it's an opportunity
I won't turn down.
[KIKUCHIYO]
What are you talking about?
[KAMBEI]
Don't deny it.
I could never
forget that armor.
Hey... What is this?
You are, without
a doubt, my sworn nemesis...
Tsukumozaka
Jurobei Mitsuharu!
[KIKUCHIYO] Wait!
[THUD]
Unbelievable...
Forgive me...
I don't mean to intrude.
Just... stay away...!
You hear me?!
[BABY CRIES]
[THUD]
There, there, child...
You're all right now.
My sweet Kotaro...!
Oh, thank goodness
you're okay...
[STATIC]
[SHOP MAN] Great samurai,
I can't thank you enough.
You've saved my family...
Let me offer you something
--a drink, perhaps?
[KAMBEI] You don't need
to thank me at all.
You never asked
me to get involved.
I'm just a nosy man...
Now excuse me...
[KIKUCHIYO DISTORTED]
Hey! Wait!
That hurt you bastard!
How dare you use me
to get to that thief!
Maybe we should
be sworn enemies!
[CROWD GASPS]
You say you're a samurai.
I have my doubts.
[KIKUCHIYO] What?!
You carry a sword,
yet you hesitate.
[KIKUCHIYO DISTORTED]
Don't walk away from me!
We're not... finished yet!
Hey, what are you fooling
around for, you headless beast?
Bend down and pick me up!
Priestess, slow down...
I divined it, even before
the Crystal told me--
He's the samurai who's
going to save our village!
♪ closing song ♪
[KOMACHI] Dear Okara.
Hey, it's me, Komachi!
Everything okay?
I promised I'd write once
we got in, so here it is!
The trip out of the
village was pretty.
The city's name is Kogakyo,
and it's way different
from the country.
It's big and noisy and full of
people, and kind of smelly, too.
This one guy was even
selling cooked frogs!
I asked sister why the Bandits
have to steal our rice,
if there's so much food here.
But maybe it's like you said--
the Bandits are so big,
they just have to eat and
eat until all the rice is gone!
Sister says during the
Great War, we fed samurai,
so we've always been
giving food to someone.
But if we grow it all,
how come we have to go hungry?
Well, I guess that's
why we're hiring samurai.
To drive the Bandits out!
I hope I can tell you
more about it soon...!
Bye-bye!