That's what samurai do!
[KIRARA GASPS]
You could come with me Kirara.
[RIKICHI]
Do you remember this?
Please, for me... Wear it again.
I can't--I belong
to the Amanushi.
I won't accept that...
You are my wife...
And no matter what you say,
I am taking you home...
Since you and Heihachi are here,
I assume the village is secure?
We rebuilt
all we could...
Their attitudes on the other
hand, well--Give them time.
I'm afraid
Katsushiro has left us.
[KATSUSHIRO]
I'm sorry I couldn't be
what you wanted sensei.
♪ opening song ♪
[KIKUCHIYO]
If we keep this up,
we might just get
outta here by noon!
[KAMBEI] Yes.
[KIKUCHIYO] Huh...?
What? You wanna help?
Don't bother!
We know you merchants
never pick up anything
heavier than a teacup.
Is it true you men
are actually planning
an assault on the Capital?
That's the plan.
[AYAMARO] You've proven you
can kill Bandits--that's good.
The odds may even
be in your favor...
But never underestimate Ukyo.
Oh wow, thank you so much
for your advice, pal.
Do I detect a hint of sarcasm?
Hey Kambei-dono,
you tellin' us
we're actually supposed
to trust this guy?
I take it that means you don't.
[KIKUCHIYO] Oh man,
Heihachi, not this again!
Can't you trust anybody?
It's not up to me.
If Kambei trusts him,
then I trust him.
Even though he is
a blood-sucking merchant.
Not long ago I put
a bounty on your heads
with that samurai hunt.
I suppose I can't blame you
for having doubts about me...
But for what it's worth
I give you my word,
I am neither the Capital's
ally, nor their foe.
You gentlemen saved my life,
and I will dutifully
repay that debt.
[AYAMARO]
Oh, Kyuzo...
Isn't this just marvelous--
the two of us working
together again?
[KAMBEI] Heihachi.
May I have a word with you?
Sure.
[KIRARA] Rikichi, how
long do you plan
on sitting there like that?
I can't do this...
I told Sanae I wasn't bothered
by what happened to her...
But... I don't know if
I can be the kind of man
she needs me to be.
Don't push yourself so hard...
Just give it some time.
Rikichi... Some of us were
discussing it earlier,
and if it's all right with you,
we would love for her
to stay here with us...
...for a little while.
Many of the other girls she was
with will be working here, too.
Whether we take in
two women or three,
it doesn't make much
difference to me.
[RIKICHI]
I don't know what to do...
That monster kidnapped
my wife and kept her prisoner!
How can she say
she's in love with him?
Was life in the Capital
that much better?
I'm sure she was fed
all the finest foods
and given all the
fanciest kimonos...
So now... It's no wonder she
doesn't want to come back
and sweat in the fields.
[SHICHIROJI] Rikichi!
It may have been just a clone,
but she was carrying his child.
When you're held
captive that long,
emotions can do funny things.
Of course!
Just think about it,
I'm sure the Emperor had
whole teams of experts
finding ways to control her
feelings and make her love him--
like that whole baby angle with
the maternal instincts and such.
Pure trickery!
Yep, Ukyo and his
predecessor are exactly alike!
That still doesn't help me
figure out what to do.
Pull yourself together, Rikichi!
[YUKINO] Mizuki?
[MIZUKI] If Rikichi doesn't
do something to help Sanae,
who else will?
She didn't just leave
her heart in the capital--
she left her soul there, too.
Now he's the only one
who can restore them both.
Sure, we dined on delicacies
we never had in our villages...
And yes we wore the finest
clothes every day because
there was never any dirt or
dust or sweat to worry about...
But look...
Look at my hand.
When I was taken, it was
tough and calloused.
These hands could do anything--
they could work any field.
But now--after years
in the Capital
they've turned soft and fair.
They put nail polish
and lipstick on me
and told me to always smile.
But no matter how pretty they
made me on the outside,
I knew I was no more than
a harvesting field
to these people.
That I'd gone from
working a farm to being one.
[RIKICHI]
What do you mean?
Well isn't that what we were?!
They planted the
Emperor's seed in us,
hoping to yield
a crop of clones.
How is that any different
from our rice fields?!
Do you know how
dehumanizing that is?
[RIKICHI SOBS]
I'm sorry, I guess you
know better than anybody.
Maybe I can ask Kambei to
help me like he helped you.
I need you all to
destroy the Capital!
Not just for our own sakes...
...but for my mom and dad
who were killed by them...
and for all the other villagers
whose lives were ripped apart,
I want revenge!
[HEIHACHI]
You know...
...no one ever died by my sword
before I met you, Kambei-dono.
But that doesn't mean
I hadn't killed people.
[KAMBEI]
By betraying them... you mean?
[HEIHACHI] Heh...
How'd you figure me out?
[KAMBEI] It's why you're so hard
on others for their betrayals--
because you can't
forgive your own.
[HEIHACHI]
You're right...
I was weak...
And the intel I leaked ended up
getting my whole unit killed...
It was a stupid thing to do,
and I've spent every day since
trying to make their
lives count for something--
trying to do some
good to set things right.
I guess it's why I tagged
along on this crazy mission--
to find redemption.
Then stay with us, and see
this job through to the end.
So... You think killing
bad guys will erase my sins?
It's a good first step.
[HEIHACHI] Your endless ability
to trust people is one I lack.
At first I questioned how wise
you were forgiving traitors,
but now I admire your faith.
I guess I've been afraid they'd
only be as dependable as I was.
If only I'd met
someone like you sooner...
I'm nothing special.
[HEIHACHI] Looks like they're
trying to get rid of us.
I think Rikichi's
feeling better now.
Great Samurai...
I have a request...
I beg you... Make the Capital
pay for what they've done.
No need to ask,
it's already been decided.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Yeah! Just leave it to us!
[KAMBEI] The Capital is on
its way to Kanna Village.
[KIKUCHIYO]
That rat Ukyo!
We're gonna knock him back to
the fields where he belongs!
Woo-hoo!
[MASAMUNE]
Not so fast.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Huh? What's up, old man?
I threw this together for you...
It should launch anything
you can fit in it... My treat.
Thank you.
When this is over I want
to sharpen that sword again...
You get me?
[KAMBEI GRUNTS]
Time to go.
Whatever you say...
Good luck, now.
Oh come on, I just got back...
and that's the most passionate
sendoff you can give?
Well maybe if Momotaro
had brought some treasure
like he was supposed to...
Ouch, that hurts.
[KIKUCHIYO] Ooh, look at
the lovebirds going at it!
[KOMACHI WHISTLES]
[GROUP LAUGHS]
Be true to your heart, Kirara.
I'm really gonna miss
you girls--you know that?
[CHIAKI]
We'll miss you, too.
You take good care of Sanae!
[MIZUKI] I will.
[KOHARU] Yeah, and come back
to see us some time, okay?
[MIZUKI] Okay.
We'll be back in
Kanna real soon.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[MIZUKI]
Goodbye everyone!
[KOHARU AND CHIAKI]
Goodbye!
And away they go.
You think really Sanae's
going to be okay?
She'll be fine.
She's with a man who loves her.
As for you, merchant man...
It just so happens
that our attendant
in the bath boiler
room has quit.
You needn't worry,
I can take my bath later.
A comedian!
Now get down there and start
preparing baths for our guests!
I'm ah... not sure I know how.
[RAIDEN] My time has
come, Tanomo. I am sorry.
[TANOMO] Don't give up now...
We're almost there...
Look, there's the Capital.
Aw, you got yourself injured.
War can do that, you know.
I suppose we should
treat their injuries.
Tessai, go find a mechanic.
[RAIDEN]
Divine Emperor!
Do you think it wise to
interrupt me in your state?
[RAIDEN]
Please, let me speak.
[TANOMO]
No. Let's get you repaired.
[RAIDEN]
This can't wait, Tanomo.
[TANOMO]
Yes it can.
If you two are just going to
hang there and bicker all day...
Then out with it.
[RAIDEN]
Thank you, Emperor...
You see, we were ambushed
by peasants and ronin.
That's how I wound up like this.
But the odd thing is,
the peasants told us the
samurai weren't ronin at all--
that they were
defending the village
in service to the Emperor!
Is that so?
[RAIDEN] Your Excellency,
with all due respect...
You sent us into those villages
to collect rice for you.
Now look at me.
Are those miserable dogs lying,
or did you actually pit
us against each other?
Which is it?!
[UKYO]
Which do you think?
[RAIDEN]
I think I deserve an answer!
As we speak, our scouts are
being blindsided and slaughtered
by those peasants
and their hired swords!
I'm not seeing the problem.
[TANOMO]
Emperor, I don't understand.
[RAIDEN]
You heartless...
You Bandits, the peasants,
the ronin Samurai--
I gave orders to everybody...
No one's lying,
just doing as they're told.
[TANOMO]
But why?
"Why?" For the future.
[TANOMO]
"The future?"
Sure--after taking over the
world you need loyal subjects...
Farmers and samurai are
proving their allegiance
by killing Nobuseri.
And you Nobuseri are proving
your allegiance by being killed.
And really, is there no greater
honor for any proud warrior
than to give his life in
the service of his master?
[TANOMO]
Dishonoring swine!
Oh wow! Impressive.
So that's the
Capital's Main Cannon?
[PRIME MINISTER] Forgive me
if I overstepped my bounds.
No, not at all--
in fact I quite enjoyed that.
[TESSAI] My lord,
this won't be the
last time we face such dissent.
We need to be prepared.
These wretched samurai,
and their sense of honor.
[PRIME MINISTER] How would you
feel about Nobuseri,
with no free will of their own?
[UKYO]
We can do that?
[PRIME MINISTER] Our doctors've
toyed with the idea for years.
We strip them of their souls,
leaving nothing but the machine.
I like the sound of that.
Build me an army.
Yes, lord.
[GOROBEI]
Hey there! You boy!
That's right,
I'm talking to you.
Gorobei-dono?
What's wrong...?
Come, boy... You look gloomy.
What do you want from me?
I see you here like this,
and I have to ask...
Where are you going?
[KATSUSHIRO] I'll go
anywhere I find a battle.
In your current state, boy,
you don't stand a chance.
Hold your tongue!
I will not be defeated!
Let's go.
[HEIHACHI] Don't these
guys ever get a head rush,
hanging around like
that all the time?
[MIZUKI] You say
my sister is... here?
[KAMBEI]
Yes. Bring us ashore.
[SHICHIROJI]
You got it.
[MIZUKI]
Sister?
Sister, it's me!
Mizuki?
Mizuki!
Sister!
[HONOKA]
Is it really you?!
Those brave samurai over there
rescued me from the Capital!
[HONOKA]
Great Kambei!
Thank you so much
for saving her.
You've got it backwards--
she's the one who saved me.
I'm so happy for you, Mizuki.
Thanks Sanae--
and I know you and Rikichi
will work everything out.
Thank you for all your help...
I'm gonna be fine
here with my sister.
So I guess this is goodbye then.
So it is... Take care
of that memento.
Well, should be easy without
you around... Kambei the thief!
"Oh, Kambei, it's
all thanks to you!"
Little do they know he never
won so much as a coin toss
before he met up with us!
Yeah but he still had
the stink of battle!
What do you mean by that?
He smells pretty
darn scary to me!
[HEIHACHI]
Did I miss something, Kirara?
What are you blushing for?
Nothing.
[KIKUCHIYO] Hey, uh...
Why are they staring at us?
Oh... I completely forgot!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Forgot what, sprout?
We left their scary
suits at the Capital--
and we didn't untie
their friends either!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh...
We're so sorry!
[MESSENGER] We've received a
report from our recon team.
Go on, I don't have all day.
They've lost visual on
Kambei Shimada's position.
Oh...? Where?
[MESSENGER]
He and his group were last seen
entering the cave
of the Guardians.
I knew they'd hide in there.
Any sign of my father?
[MESSENGER] He's doing
menial labor in a teahouse.
[UKYO LAUGHS]
Menial labor...?
That's great, I love it.
What better punishment is there
for a man who so blatantly
abused his status?
I don't really care
about him anymore...
Let's just leave
him to that fate.
[MESSENGER]
What about Kambei Shimada?
My lord, please.
You mustn't forget
our arrangement
with the
Shikimoribito.
Oh, I haven't forgotten.
Pardon me, Amanushi.
We'll be arriving at
Ushioda Village soon.
[UKYO] Find Kambei and
his team of Samurai...
I believe we need to make
an example out of them.
[MESSENGER]
Yes, my lord.
[KIKUCHIYO] We're sorry!
We're so very sorry!
If it makes you feel any
better, you can kick my ass.
Hard! I mean it!
[KIRARA] I don't blame
you for being upset.
What we did was inexcusable.
[KOMACHI[ Yeah,
I'm really sorry too!
Come on, can't we just
put aside our differences
and settle this peaceably?
Huh?
Please find it in your hearts
to forgive these people--
if it weren't for them
I would never have been
reunited with my sister.
[SHIKIMORIBITO] We never
said we would not forgive them.
[KIKUCHIYO] You mean you're
not gonna slaughter us?
[SHIKIMORIBITO] Until the
Capital has been defeated,
you shall remain
indebted to us.
[KIKUCHIYO]
"Indebted?"
Indeed... You may
prepare for your war here.
I thought you guys had
a treaty with the Capital.
[SHIKIMORIBITO]
We do...
But this is an opportunity to
break free of the Capital--
One we cannot let pass us by.
Ah, now this is
the way to travel!
Those Guardians are okay!
I can't believe they
let us borrow this thing!
[KIKUCHIYO LAUGHS]
[KIKUCHIYO] Wow, I'm
even higher up than
when I ride on
Kiku's shoulders!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Yeah? Then how 'bout this?
Now you're the
Capital air-ship! Yeah!
[KOMACHI LAUGHS]
So who exactly are
those the Guardians?
Former samurai.
Rather than becoming
Bandits or ronin,
they chose to lay
down their swords.
Right... I should've guessed...
No wonder they have so
many of these old ships
from the war lying around.
And they're surprisingly
easy to bargain with...
I guess all their dealings
with the merchants
has rubbed off on 'em.
[VISOR] You're not to allow
those samurai into your village.
If they return,
hand them over to us.
Now gather up the
rest of the villagers.
And I don't want just the men...
Bring all your women
and children too...
You're about to find out
exactly what it means
to surrender to the Capital.
[HEAVY FOOTFALLS]
Who could that be?
Those footsteps--
It sounds like the...
Tortoise Express.
Look like Katsushiro...
Katsushiro, you're back!
Retreat to safer ground--
All of you.
Hiya kid... You come
looking for a rematch?
What are you filth
doing in Kanna?
Heh... Last time we met
it only took one hit
to put an end to
your heroics...
Sure you wanna try again?
I'm the one asking
the questions.
Don't cop an attitude
with me, boy...
I've been given
exclusive privileges
by the Divine
Emperor himself.
You might say my
word is his word,
so show a little damn respect.
What business
do you have here?
Why were your sentries
trying to start a fire?
Sure you're not
just seeing things?
Don't toy with me!
[KATSUSHIRO BELLOWS]
[KATSUSHIRO] Why did
you come to this village?
[VISOR]
Why do you think...?
To destroy it...
Wh-What?
We will burn this
village to the ground...
And the flames will serve...
...to herald the arrival
of the young master.
They're here...
surrounding the village...
The fire... starters...
[KATSUSHIRO YELLS]
You will fall!
♪ closing song ♪
[KOMACHI]
Ooo-kara... Big news!
The war's about to start again!
And we're storming the Capital!
Whoo-ee, was I ever surprised!
And speaking of surprises,
it turns out that scary guy,
Ukyo, used to be a farmer!
But instead of becoming
a samurai like Kiku,
he became the Emperor!
That would be pretty
amazing, I suppose,
but Ukyo's a liar and
a mean, mean bad guy!
Everyone thinks he's
this super-great person
'cause he gives away rice
and says nice things...
But then he turns around
and does really bad things
when nobody else is looking...
They say that's how the
Merchants fight their battles.
It's pretty scary,
and not very fair!
Sanae's heart is still far away,
so it's been hard on Rikichi.
The good news is that we went
back to the Guardians' cave
and reunited Honoka with
her little sister Mizuki,
who was one of Sanae's
attendants at the Capital!
I'm so happy for them...
And I'm happy Kambei was
able to keep his promise!
Hope everything's okay
back in the village.
We should be coming
home pretty soon,
so you can tell
me all about it!
See ya! Bye bye!