[TESSAI] No!
[GOROBEI] Get down!
Katsushiro! No!
Young Master...!
Do you have any idea
what would happen if you
hit one of the Guardians?!
You're frustrated as
anyone would be...
And that is enough.
These two are grateful
for your sacrifice.
And they should be.
You are the fifth samurai.
Sensei!
Well, what are you waiting for?!
Go kill them!
That's what we hired you for!
[RIKICHI GRUNTS]
Your death won't be
worth anything here.
[RIKICHI] At least it
would stop the shame...
I sold my wife...
I sold my wife to the bandits!
[KIKUCHIYO] Rikichi...
[RIKICHI SOBS]
[KIKUCHIYO] So, I don't suppose
those Nobuseri were you guys?!
♪ opening song ♪
[MOSUKE] The samurai
should be here by now.
[GOSAKU]
Rikichi and the Water Priestess
haven't sent us a
letter in a long time.
[MANZO] It was a stupid
idea in the first place.
Now what are
we s'posed to do?
Samurai or not,
the bandits are coming.
[GOSAKU] The only thing
we can do now is wait.
Wait for the bandits
to come for us...
Wait for the
samurai to save us...
Wait for the sun to shine...
Wait for the rain to fall...
[MOSUKE] We're good at waiting.
That's what farmers do.
[MANZO]
The crop looks good this year.
The rice is bending already.
We won't be able to hold off
the harvest much longer.
[ELDER] We will hold off the
harvest as long as we must.
[MOSUKE] Elder!
We meant no disrespect, but
we can't wait for them forever.
If we harvest it now,
the bandits will come.
Is that what you want?
We wait as long as we must
until the samurai are here.
[YOHEI] But the bandits will
come to check on the crop!
What do we say when
they ask why we're waiting?
[ELDER] We're the ones
that know the rice. Not them.
Remember that!
If we say we cannot harvest
the crop yet... then we cannot!
[VILLAGERS YELL]
[VILLAGERS SCREAM]
[RIKICHI] Honoka?
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
Maybe we should rest
here for a minute?
Honoka, this waterway
leads to the entrance
on the other
side, correct?
There's really no need
for you to guide us.
Not quite.
The route splits into
different directions up ahead.
You'll need someone
familiar with the path
who can lead
you to the Bandits.
Follow me.
[GOROBEI] Thank you for
your help, Lady Honoka.
Anybody else think
Kikuchiyo's turning out to be
a little more trouble
than he's worth?
Starting to feel like we're
cleaning up after a teenager.
More like a toddler.
Ah... But that's part
of his charm, isn't it?
Is that what we're calling it?
[KOMACHI] Hey sis?
I think he's asleep now.
I know how badly he
wanted to go with Kambei.
Yeah, but if he did, he just
would've been in the way.
Ah... Shh...
I think I know
what you meant before.
He doesn't have the scent
of battle like the others do.
Katsushiro just
isn't that scary.
[KATSUSHIRO GROANS]
What is it, Great Samurai?
We're surrounded.
[HONOKA AND RIKICHI GASP]
[RIKICHI] The bandits.
Great...!
A welcoming party!
But why...?
How'd they know?
Gorobei... protect
Lady Honoka and Rikichi.
[GOROBEI] You got it.
But I want to fight, too!
[RAIDEN 1] I see the
rumors were true, then.
[RAIDEN 2] And they reek of the
filthy peasants they're with.
What is it you want from us?
[RAIDEN 1] You are the samurai
hired by the peasants, correct?
So much for surprises.
And what if we are?
[RAIDEN 1] Then we cannot
allow you to go free.
[KAMBEI]
How you have fallen.
[RAIDEN 1] What?!
You've given up
your honor as samurai
and reduced yourselves
to common thieves...
Have you no shame?
[RAIDEN 1] You allow yourself
to be hired for rice...
and you dare talk
to me about shame?!
Great Samurai!
[RAIDEN 1] What--?
[KAMBEI] I'm amazed you
were ever called samurai.
Shichiroji!
[SHICHIROJI] Right!
You sure know how to
heat things up, old man.
[RAIDEN 2] Kill them.
Wood Chop Strike!
[ROBOT GUY YELLS]
Yeah, that was sloppy.
This way! Quickly!
[GOROBEI YELLS]
[GOROBEI MOANS]
They're incredible.
[GUNSHOT]
Kambeii-sama!
Packs quite a wallop...
I should've tried guns before.
[RAIDEN 2]
Hyogo! What are you doing here?
[SHICHIROJI]
Kambei-sama, hold on!
[GUNSHOT]
[HYOGO] Actually, I'd rather
you stayed there for now.
[HYOGO GASPS]
[RAIDEN 2]
What the hell?
[RAIDEN 2] You...!
[KYUZO] Only I will have
the pleasure of killing you.
[HYOGO GRUNTS]
[GUNSHOT]
[SOBEI] You can stop.
[HYOGO]
Why would I do that?
[SOBEI] We know how
strong they are now.
That's all we needed.
We're leaving.
So it was a test.
You alright?
I am sorry that you can
no longer return to your allies.
[KAMBEI]
Let him go.
[SHICHIROJI]
Does it hurt?
No. It's just a scratch.
Are you all right?
Yes, we're fine...
The Water Priestess was right
about all of you samurai...
I've never seen anything
like the way you fight!
It's amazing...!
The bandits
threatening our village
don't stand
a chance against you.
We can't withstand firearms.
But...
During the war I watched
hundreds of fellow samurai
fall to men with
guns and no honor.
Heh. You know somehow
I didn't expect Maro's men
to use the bandits against us.
But I guess I underestimated
the buying power of the
merchants, didn't I?
So that's it...
I wondered how they were
able to ambush us like that.
The Shikimoribito have numerous
exits up to the surface...
I wonder how they
knew we'd use this one?
[KAMBEI] Why don't you
tell us, Lady Honoka.
[HONOKA AND RIKICHI GASP]
You gotta
be kidding me.
What's this about?
She guided us straight to
this exit without hesitation.
Yes... She did.
Have you forgotten that
bandits destroyed her village
and killed her family...?
What reason would she
have for helping them?
Her survival, perhaps?
[RIKICHI]
Not you, too, Gorobei!
[SHIKIMORI 1]
Do not blame her.
[GOROBEI]
The Guardians...
Hey, whaddya know?
Turns out
they can talk!
Afternoon, gentlemen.
[SHIKIMORI 1]
Your suspicions are justified.
She is a Nobuseri spy.
But your harm was
not her desire.
Oh, sure...
She only ratted us
out to the enemy--
why would we
blame her for that?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Come on! Kill me, already!
What, you afraid to
spill a little oil?
Come on, you little soft-handed
weakling chicken bastards!
[HYOGO] Silence!
You know, I really
do enjoy this gun...
It has a versatility
that a sword simply lacks.
[KIKUCHIYO]
A samurai with a gun!
You're a disgrace!
Heh... Keep it up and you may
just get your wish after all...
The young master did make
a request for your head!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Ah, cram it.
[SOBEI]
Your men are incompetent.
We were told there were five
samurai besides this one.
[HYOGO]
There were.
[SOBEI]
Kyuzo, was it?
I'm surprised Maro would
employ such a traitor.
You should watch what
you say about my Lord--
though I'd be curious
to know where you get
such detailed information.
[SOBEI] Ha, ha, ha, ha...
I'm sure you would.
[HYOGO GRUNTS]
[KIKUCHIYO LAUGHS]
[KIKUCHIYO] Fight! Fight!
Kick him in the gears!
[THUD]
Aww... sorry.
Rest assured, Sobei-dono,
I fully intend to correct
that mistake, but I think
we should stop those peasants
and their samurai first.
[SOBEI] Agreed.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Hey. You guys.
You better finish me off now.
Otherwise you're
gonna regret it!
[KIKUCHIYO LAUGHS LOUDLY]
[SOBEI]
Just kill him already.
He's annoying.
[HYOGO] Not yet.
He may still be of use to us.
[SHIKIMORI 1] The Nobuseri
who used Honoka as a spy
were after our energy
cell generators...
They're trying to gain
control of the technology.
But how did
you know all that?
[SHIKIMORI 1]
You underestimate us.
Letting a mole
relay misinformation
is basic strategy.
[HEIHACHI] So, I take it the
bandits know everything about us
and our mission, right?
Yes.
But why...?
That story about your family
being killed by bandits,
was that all a lie?
No, it was all
true... except...
Except what?
My sister...
My little sis--
[HONOKA SOBS]
They took her, didn't they?
Just like they took my wife.
[HONOKA]
They promised...
not to hurt my sister
if I obeyed them...
so I did everything
they told me to.
[RIKICHI]
You believed them?!
She did what
she had to do.
Not that...
She didn't
have to do that.
Isn't that why your wife
let the Bandits take her?
To protect the people she loved?
We do what we must,
Rikichi. All of us.
You can't blame her for that.
[HONOKA SOBS]
I, too, searched
for a way to survive,
and found a life as
a street performer.
Compromise is
the age we live in.
Tell us what you told them.
I told them you were headed
to Kanna village after this.
You told them what?!
[KAMBEI SIGHS]
What are you doing?
You're up...!
Are you feeling better already?
Yes, and my fever's gone, too.
It's the medicine!
It worked, huh?!
I'm going after them.
[KIRARA] But...
Sensei has finally acknowledged
me as part of the team...
A samurai must always
be prepared for battle,
so I must do my duty.
Huh...?
So how do you want to do this?
Please don't hurt her,
Great Samurai.
[HEIHACHI]
If we let her live,
she'll endanger
the Guardians, too.
[SHIKIMORI 1]
Do not worry about us, samurai.
[KAMBEI]
Lady Honoka.
We will reunite
you and your sister.
[RIKICHI]
Thank you, Great Samurai!
Aren't you being
a little easy on her?
It is not a samurai's
duty to punish someone.
Shikimoribito.
[SHIKIMORI 1] Yes?
May I leave Lady Honoka
and Rikichi in your care?
[SHIKIMORI 1]
Certainly.
[GROUP GASPS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[HYOGO] Kyuzo.
Now why did you go
and kill that bandit?
The village of Kanna is
defying the laws of this land.
They need to be
taught a lesson.
Don't tell me you're
causing all this trouble
just to fight a silly old man.
Killing one poor old samurai
isn't going to win you
any fame, you know...
Tell you what...
I'll keep this a
secret from our Lord
if you come back with me
to Kougakyo right now.
You know I don't
want to hurt you.
Kyuzo-dono.
He did... all this?
[HEIHACHI] Looks like they're
not the forgiving type.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Kikuchiyo-dono!
[GOROBEI]
Are you sure that's wise?
No.
Kambeii-sama!
[GUNSHOT]
Damn it.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Ha ha!
Dirty tricks like using a
hostage don't work on him,
you powder-faced freak!
Shut up.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Didn't you know?
He...
No, they...
...are samurai!
And real ones, too.
Not gun-toting,
fancy-dressed fakes like you.
You follow me?
[KIKUCHIYO LAUGHS]
Kyuzo...! If you want to
fight against him that badly,
then go ahead and do it!
I'll even watch! You can
have the honor of his death.
If you succeed
and rejoin us today,
your actions will
go unquestioned...
If you die, then
I'll kill him myself.
Regardless of the outcome,
we will have finished our job.
[SHICHIROJI]
Kambei-sama!
Damn it!
[GUNSHOT]
[KIKUCHIYO GRUNTS]
Kyuzo!
[KATSUSHIRO GASPS]
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
Ha, haaaa! That felt good!
Thanks for the help, Katsu!
Katsushiro.
You all right?
Yes, Sensei.
I'm fine...
The Guardians brought me
here so I could help you.
[KOMACHI] Hey...!
We wanna help, too, Kambei!
[KIKUCHIYO] Well what are you
gonna do? Bug 'em to death?
[GROUP LAUGHS]
[HYOGO] You've fallen
for our trap, samurai.
Right about now, Sobei-dono
should be arriving
at the Upper Shrine.
Soon all the Nobuseri
will know of your plan.
Why... Kyuzo...? Why did you...
Because... I wanted to live.
You're a hopeless fool.
May I ask you
to come with us?
When do we leave?
Immediately.
[SHIKIMORI 1] We will
be sorry to see you go.
The Nobuseri know
about our mission now,
so I'm afraid we have
no time to spare.
Great Samurai?
[KAMBEI] Don't worry
about what happened.
You wait here.
My little sister
and Rikichi's wife--
the bandits are probably
keeping them both
at the Upper Shrine.
[KAMBEI] Let's go.
That man is our enemy.
[GENZO]
We heard a disturbing rumor...
And we'd like to know
whether or not it's true.
[ELDER] Yes?
[GENZO] We heard that
this village was trying
to hire some samurai
to defeat the Nobuseri.
Is that true?
Who told you such
an outrageous tale?
We're peasants.
We couldn't afford to hire
samurai if we wanted to.
You know it doesn't do
any good to lie to us.
[ELDER]
I never lie.
[GENZO]
We could burn the village now,
and be done with it...
However, our leader has
given you a grace period...
Be thankful for his generosity.
If it's true we'll find out...
And each one of you
will be punished.
If any samurai come here,
you will hand them over to us,
and we will forget
about this troubling rumor.
Think of the
well-being of the village
and I'm sure you'll
know what to do.
[ELDER SIGHS]
All of you need to
stop looking up in hope...
Just keep your eyes down
on the dirt where they belong.
[GENZO LAUGHS]
♪ closing song ♪
[KOMACHI] Dear Okara,
I've got exciting news today!
We found samurai number six!
Remember Kyuzo?
That weird one I told you about
who's scary 'cause he hardly
ever says anything, and he's
strong and uses two swords
and he tried to kill Kambei?
Well now he's on our side!
Yeah, isn't that crazy?
He's really good at fighting,
but I don't think
I like him, personally.
You just can't trust
the quiet ones.
Besides, sis doesn't
like him either,
and it makes me nervous
seeing her upset.
Oh, and another thing--if he
was going to join us all along,
why didn't he just say
so back in the city,
and save us all this time?
Honestly, sometimes
the way these samurai act
doesn't make any sense...
Oh yeah, more news!
Katsushiro's feeling better.
The medicine those Guardians
gave him really did the trick.
They should sell that stuff--
they'd probably get even
richer than the merchants!
Then maybe they could buy
clothes that weren't so creepy.
But anyway, tell our Elder
we're crossing the desert,
and we should get
back to Kanna soon!
Can't wait to introduce
you to Kiku! Bye-bye!