Don't!
[EMPEROR]
Just bear with me for a moment.
Ukyo...? Could he really be...
You're trembling.
I'm worried, Mizuki...
That man they call Ukyo...
I'm afraid of the things
I see in his eyes.
By the way, the true murderer
is right here in this room.
And why would you
assassinate the Imperial Envoy?
I only did it because
I was asked to.
Do you really think it's wise
for a nation to have two rulers?
[EMPEROR]
It is entirely unnecessary.
I so agree.
But don't you worry
about a thing...
I will help ease your burden.
Good night, Emperor.
♪ opening song ♪
Divine successor to
the honored Amanushi...
On this, the occasion of
your ascension to the throne...
we pledge our fealty...
and humbly ask for an audience.
[GONG]
I have but one wish...
To make this world
a better place.
I want to give work
to the unemployed...
And to give food to the hungry.
And I will...
As your new Amanushi
I consider this my duty.
Divine Emperor.
Tessai, we've been
together far too long
for you to call me that.
[TESSAI]
As you wish...
The leader of the Nobuseri
has finally arrived.
He would like to congratulate
you on your new title.
Huh... Would he, now?
[TANOMO]
Your Excellency...
I am Kobayakawa Tanomo.
Forgive my appearance.
I came as soon as I heard.
It doesn't matter.
I detest all machine samurai.
[TANOMO]
I had heard our new Emperor...
...knew the life of a farmer.
[UKYO] You'll find
I know many things.
I know the brutality your kind
inflicts on the farmers...
And I know I am
now in a position
to rid the world of
monsters like you.
[TANOMO] Are you saying you
want us to perform Harakiri?
I'm no child.
I understand full well
how this world works.
After the war was over,
the clever Emperor rescued
you brutes from vagrancy...
To keep the
farmers in disarray...
allowing them to live
but never to prosper...
And as for the city...
They're so happy not
to be stuck on the farm
they never complain.
[TANOMO] Please,
Your Excellency...
...tell us how to proceed.
Since learning of the
rebellion in Kanna,
the farmers have
gathered strength.
We don't know what they'll do.
Yes... I know...
I'm curious, too.
[TANOMO]
What does that mean, Emperor?
Everything will stay the same.
You will continue taking
rice from the farmers,
as you always have.
[TANOMO]
I thought you despised us.
Oh, I do... But this is
necessary for the Capital...
You all work for
me now... little man.
[TANOMO]
Yes, Your Excellency.
They will all be
dead soon enough.
[UKYO]
Following Kanna's example,
other villages will
rise up against them.
The Nobuseri will be
a sacrificial offering
which will please the people.
Don't you see, Tessai?
The former Emperor hated
the Nobuseri, too,
he merely chose to take his
revenge by controlling them.
Look, sister, there it is!
Last one there's a loser!
[KIKUCHIYO]
What's that?
Nobuseri?
That air-ship must
be the capital.
[KIKUCHIYO]
How do you know?
Remember what that
Nobuseri leader said...
All women and rice are
taken to the capital.
The Nobuseri would have
a strong presence there,
to maintain trade...
What other air-ship city would
so many bandits swarm around?
That's where we'll find
Sanae and the others.
Yes. And Sensei
must be there, too.
Sanae... I'm glad you're awake.
[SANAE]
My child.
Tell me, is my child all right?
He should have
survived, not me...
The Emperor will
never forgive me...
How can I make this up to him?
[KOHARU muffled]
Okata!
What's going on?
[KOHARU]
I think we have a problem.
[MIZUKI]
What is this?
We serve the Okata, but now
we're supposed to serve you?
Who gave this order?
Why, the new
Amanushi, of course...
The inner chambers
are ours now...
Your mistress's reign
has come to an end.
If that's true,
then you can just let us all
go back to our villages.
Oh, I'm afraid not,
you see, we're going to need
quite a few servants...
We must always be
beautiful for our Emperor...
It's the least we
can do, right girls?
At least wait a while...!
The Okata isn't well
enough to be moved.
[WARYA] That's not
really my concern.
Go ahead, boys.
Right.
Wait, what's... going on?
[footsteps]
The execution will
commence at 6pm...
Your body will be on
display until midnight.
I ask you to grant a dying
samurai one final request.
[LEAD GUARD]
Go ahead.
I would like to die
as a warrior...
Allow me to honor the
ritual of cleansing
and to commit hara-kiri.
Denied.
[KAMBEI]
Why?
Your request for ritual
cleansing is granted...
However, you will not be
given the use of any weapon
before the time of
your execution.
By whose order?
Who else...?
Our new Emperor, of course.
Look... They finally
caught the guy.
About time.
[KIKUCHIYO]
What's this?
[KOMACHI] Aww, man.
I can't see anything.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh... Here.
Hey, Kiku... What does
that thing say, anyway?
[KIKUCHIYO]
It says uh...
"Little girls shouldn't read
what's on this board."
Kambei!
No... It's about... Sensei.
[KIKUCHIYO]
It is?!
Huh...?
Hey.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Hey what's up old man!
[MASAMUNE] Whaddaya know,
you're still in one piece.
Masamune-dono.
It's been awhile.
[MASAMUNE] I guess I don't
have to ask what Kambei's up to.
Besides being accused
of the envoy's murder...
he made an attempt
on the Emperor's life.
[KIKUCHIYO]
An attempt?
What's going on?
Sensei failed...
And now he's in trouble.
I knew it...
He never should have tried
to rescue them on his own.
[PRIME MINISTER]
Before you arrived,
I was unaware of your
noble heritage...
Forgive me.
Ohhh... I suppose
that's all right...
Besides, I didn't
know about it either.
[PRIME MINISTER]
I am humbled, my lord.
Thanks to your actions,
my position as an Imperial
Advisor is once again secure.
I hope I--
[AYAMARO] Unhand me!
I haven't done anything!
Father!
My lord... you
shouldn't eavesdrop.
I swear, I didn't hear a word.
Was there something you wanted?
[AYAMARO] I came to see
how you were doing.
Oh, I'm fabulous.
An ex-farmer becomes Emperor?
It's quite a change, isn't it?
It's a change other
people are starting
to take note of, my son.
One that can be frightening...
What will they say,
do you think...
when they find out
your secret...
You were the one who killed
the Imperial Envoy, weren't you?
So you were listening...!
Technically... He drove
in the blade, though.
See, this poor man
needed my help...
He knew the Envoy wanted his
position, and I... wanted yours.
So? What do we do with him?
Let me think...
Young Master, we'll be docking
at Kougakyo any moment.
Oh, is it that time already?
Ukyo!
[UKYO]
Unlike those filthy Bandits,
I have the capacity
for true compassion.
I wish to show my gratitude
for all you have taught me.
From now on, Father...
...you will be my
Warehouse Manager.
Go greet the Shikimoribito.
I see you're getting some
use outta this baby.
[MASAMUNE] Well, that makes
sense-- you are a samurai now.
But this thing is useless.
I'll have to
re-forge it for you.
[KIKUCHIYO] We'll just borrow
these until you're done... Here.
Easy.
We're going
to the Capital.
Oh...? And what do you
think that'll accomplish?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Savin' everyone, of course!
We can't just
leave them to die.
Maybe we should wait.
What?!
Kambei isn't the type of man who
would let himself be executed
without putting up a fight.
Yes, but how...?
How can he rescue anybody
from his jail cell?
I don't know...
But still...
I don't think we
should interfere
with whatever plan
he might have.
So you think we
should do nothing?
[KIRARA]
For now.
For a samurai, the failure to
act is a path of eternal shame.
[KIRARA] But won't it
be shaming Kambei
if we refuse to trust him now?
[KIKUCHIYO]
When a samurai makes a mistake,
he pays for it with his life...
Katsu and I aren't gonna
let that happen to Kambei...
We're gonna save him and
show him what samurai can do.
Whoa... It's HUGE!
Your final meal...
Great Samurai.
Don't cry.
I can't help it. If you
won't cry for yourself,
then I'll cry for you.
I just wish you would
let me bring you
something other than a
riceball for your final meal.
No... After all, it was rice
like this that hired me...
I will not eat anything else
until that job is complete.
But you can't save any
of us if you're dead.
You think not?
[UKYO]
Oh, dear...
That look is no good for you.
You know, I don't hate you.
I thought I would,
but it's because of you
that I've become what I have,
so I wanted to come down
here and bid you farewell.
I'm sorry you won't be
afforded a samurai death.
You must feel shame, being
unable to commit hara kiri.
What would you
warriors call that?
A losing battle?
I'd suggest you be careful
until you actually
cut my head off.
That is adorable!
You're still going!
You will be dead soon, Kambei,
then Kanna Village is next.
Look! It's Kambei!
So... That's the assassin.
Sensei.
[KIKUCHIYO] They got him
chained up like a dog.
What do you think
he's gonna do?
This may be the one
he doesn't walk away from.
[KIKUCHIYO] You know,
if we're going to save Kambei,
now's the time.
If we save only Sensei,
then we will not have made
enough of a difference
here today...
We need to find a way to
rescue all the women as well.
[KIKUCHIYO] Oooohh...!
We're gonna have him foaming
at the mouth with jealousy.
I know what
you're going to say.
However, this is
something we must do.
You understand, don't you?
I understand.
Kikuchiyo-dono...
I need you to help me find
a way into the Capital.
[KOMACHI] Hey,
check it out: Guardians!
[KATSUSHIRO]
Wait! Please stop for a moment!
Shikimoribito, where, may I
ask, are you taking your cargo?
[SHIKIMORIBITO]
Ah... You're one of the guests
we had a short time ago.
[KATSUSHIRO] I am. My name
is Okamoto Katsushiro.
[SHIKIMORIBITO] We are
on our way to the Capital.
To honor the ascension
of the new Emperor,
we bring a gift
of energy cells.
I was hoping you'd say that.
Well... Bet they didn't
see that one comin'!
Forgive me... My friends...
If anyone finds you, tell them
you were ambushed by Bandits.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Well?
[KOMACHI] I'm not
so sure about that.
Maybe you should just pose
as the Guardian's
samurai bodyguard, huh?
I dunno, Katsu said
we'd be less suspicious
if we dressed as Guardians.
Wow, Katsu, that's
a clever plan for you.
I suppose I should take
that as a compliment.
[KOMACHI] Seems more
like something
Kambei would come up with.
I don't know about that.
Sister! What do you
think you're doing?
I'm going with them.
Do you think we're not
capable on our own?
No, its...
Neither of you knows what Sanae
looks like so you'll need me...
I am going to go with you.
[KIKUCHIYO]
I think someone's startin'
to like the smell of battle.
Oh... Now you look scary, too.
[KATSUSHIRO]
You two stay quiet.
I'll do all the talking.
[KIKUCHIYO] I know, I know,
you've told us, damn it.
When we get inside,
you're saving Kambei,
and we'll go after the women.
Stop right there.
[KATSUSHIRO] We come here today
bearing gifts of energy cells
to celebrate the ascension
of the new Amanushi.
Let's be sure... Check 'em out.
[KATSUSHIRO] Stay back!
Why do you think
we're dressed like this?
We are transporting
energy cells!
Come any closer, and
risk life-long contamination!
It's all right,
we're expecting you.
You may pass!
[KIKUCHIYO]
What is this place?
[AYAMARO]
Welcome to the Capital.
It's your old friend, Ayamaro.
I have been assigned to the
post of Warehouse Manager.
It is my job to assess the
trade value of your gifts...
In bales of rice.
[KIKUCHIYO] Do you Capital-types
really eat this much rice?
An odd question...
You are a Guardian,
I would expect you would
know the answer to that.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Aww, shut up, you bastard!
[AYAMARO]
Damn you--
[KIKUCHIYO LAUGHS]
[KATSUSHIRO] Kikuchiyo,
what are you thinking?!
[KIKUCHIYO]
This is just wrong!
What makes all this rice
so damn important?
[AYAMARO]
Who are you people?!
[KIKUCHIYO]
I'll ask the questions!
You've been taking
this rice for a long time.
Have you even eaten any of it?
No... please, of course not!
It's all used to purchase
energy cells, to... trade.
[KIKUCHIYO] What?
[AYAMARO] The Nobuseri take
rice from the farmers,
we then trade that rice
to the Shikimoribito
in exchange for energy cells.
That is the arrangement
devised by the Capital
to ensure its prosperity.
It's the only way!
[KIKUCHIYO]
That's not the only way!
You could grow your
own damn rice,
or give the farmers
what they deserve!
They're all breaking
their backs, suffering,
while you sit
around getting fat!
That poor wasted rice!
I feel sorry for it!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
Kikuchiyo-dono!
[KIKUCHIYO] Damn the Capital!
I swear I'll kill them all!
Stop, I beg you!
You'll destroy the arrangement!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Screw you! I don't care!
Kikuchiyo, stop it!
Have you forgotten
what we came for?
We're here to
save Rikichi's wife!
[KIKUCHIYO]
You're on your own. I'm done!
We're looking for the women
the Emperor kidnapped...
All of them...
You know where they are.
Take us there now.
[KIRARA]
Katsushiro.
Do me a favor...
keep an eye on Kikuchiyo...
I'm going after Sensei.
Hello...! Good to see you!
It's Ukyo!
He's the new Emperor?
That's it, it's the
end of the world.
Attention all
citizens of Kougakyo.
It is my honor to present your
new Divine Ruler: Emperor Ukyo.
Many of you may recognize
him as a former resident
and the current
Magistrate of your city.
He offers his greetings to you
and his appreciation
of your support.
He has made this journey today
to witness the execution
of Kambei Shimada,
the man who assassinated
an Imperial Envoy
and threatened the life
of the former Amanushi...
Aren't you brave enough to
kill without hiding your face?
So be it... Here you are.
Don't miss now.
[DRUMS BEATING DRAMATICALLY]
♪ closing song ♪
[KOMACHI] Wow, Okara.
Things are really getting
stressful here, in Kougakyo.
Did you know the Capital
is a big flying airship
that floats over everyone,
and is full of all these
treasures and pretty things,
and old bearded guys
and beautiful ladies,
like Rikichi's wife?
But it's also
surrounded by Bandits--
apparently a lot more than
the ones who came to Kanna.
And the Emperor does business
with them--can you believe it?
And can you believe
Ukyo's the new Emperor?
I never saw that coming!
The only reason
I know all this stuff
is because the Capital came down
to Kougakyo, and Kiku and Katsu
decided to take things
into their own hands,
dress up like those
scary Guardians,
and sneak into the Capital.
And not just to
rescue Sanae, either!
Because you know
who else was there?
Who's head is about
to get cut off?
Kambei's!
It's absolutely terrible!
I just hope Kiku and Katsu and
sis can figure this out alone.
Because to be honest,
I'm pretty nervous.
I'll talk to you
again soon, okay?