[MOSUKE]
Tell us, Elder...
What's the news from
the Priestess?
Is she bringing us Samurai?
She promises
she will not fail us.
She's going to find
seven, and then return.
Great Samurai,
you're beautiful...
So beautiful...
that I'm in love.
Heh, heh... Your diction's
perfect--like a pro...
But your delivery needs
some work. Ha, ha, ha...
Great Samurai, you're beautiful!
So beautiful I'm in love!
That's the spirit!
You're alright man! Ha, ha, ha!
I know--chopping
wood with my sword...
...hardly lives up to
the whole samurai tradition.
Nonsense...
Looks like a lot more fun
than chopping up people.
So what does that make you...?
The King of Monkey Mountain?
[HYOGO YELLS]
[KIRARA SCREAMS]
No!
[KATSUSHIRO GRUNTS]
[MARO]
What?! Envoy!
[MARO YELLS]
♪ opening song ♪
[PATROLMAN A] The wound
spans from the right shoulder
to the left hip.
Classic cut, with
a very sharp blade.
Chances are he lay
suffering for some time
while he bled to death.
[TESSAI] Hmm...
[UKYO GRUNTS]
Young master
you mustn't.
It's dangerous.
[UKYO]
You're no fun.
This is no toy,
it's an important
piece of evidence.
Ukyo, perhaps you
should wait outside...
I wouldn't want your delicate
sensibilities to be offended
by such a scene.
[TESSAI] My Lord.
It doesn't make sense.
How could such a highly
skilled swordsman
be imprudent enough to
leave the murder weapon
at the scene of the crime?
Did this sword commit murder?
What?
I'm asking if this sword
magically walked in here
of its own volition and
killed the Imperial Envoy.
The question is... what type
of person carries a sword?
A samurai
does, My Lord.
Then I want you
to arrest all samurai.
Begging your
pardon Lord,
but shouldn't we
narrow it down
to a handful of
possible suspects?
When searching for
one single grain of sand,
a wise man will choose
to run the entire beach
through a sieve.
Understand?
[TESSAI]
Yes my lord.
I suppose those two are no
longer considered samurai then?
On your feet, you are
all under arrest for murder!
Just try...!
Merchant patrolmen
and their sticks
are no match for the
samurai warrior's blade.
Your compliance or your life.
What?!
[SAMURAI B YELLS]
Consider this your warning!
All samurai will be
taken, dead or alive!
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[SAMURAI C SCREAMS]
[SAMURAI D] Move!
[SAMURAI D YELLS]
[ANNOUNCER]
Attention.
An Imperial Envoy has
been brutally murdered
in the Magistrate's house,
and evidence shows the
assassin was, in fact, samurai.
In response to
this heinous act,
the Magistrate has
launched a citywide hunt
for all remnants of
the warrior class.
For those who provide valid
information concerning
the whereabouts of samurai,
there will be a reward
of ten bundles of rice.
For an actual capture,
one hundred bundles.
Regardless of whether
they are dead or alive.
You're kidding me.
I see...that explains things.
A hundred
bundles of rice--
that's a much better
deal than we're getting.
Wonder if I can
turn myself in.
I'm sorry
you're in trouble.
Don't be so negative, man!
At times like these
one should just laugh!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
[RIKICHI LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
[ONLOOKERS WHISPER]
It appears the road ahead of
us will lead to more trouble.
Trouble often
begets good fortune
when you least expect
it, my friend.
Do you know
something I don't?
Any samurai foolish
enough to be caught
isn't worth our time
to begin with.
[GOROBEI]
I see... Excellent point.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Let go of me, you jackasses!
Didn't your mothers ever
teach you any manners?!
This isn't how you treat
a guest you know!
[PATROLMAN B]
Keep it down!
[KIKUCHIYO] Hey! You scratched
my metal, you pea-brained goats!
You're gonna' pay
my repair bill! Hey!
Where are you going...?!
Can you at least
bring me my sword?
Ah... Bastards.
I got captured on purpose.
What...? Why would
you do such a thing?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Isn't it obvious, old man?
I'm here to help you poor
fools make a prison break.
Prison break?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Sure...!
But I need you to do
something for me in return...
I'll explain once
we're out of here... Deal?
I would like nothing more,
if it were possible.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Possible?! Heh...
Heh... What do you call that?
[SAMURAI GROUP LAUGHS]
[PATROLMAN B] Huh...?
[SAMURAI GROUP] Get 'em!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Let's do this!
[SAMURAI GROUP] Yeah!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO] Come on!
[KIRARA]
Welcome back.
[KOMACHI]
Bring us any samurai?
[HEIHACHI] The samurai
store was fresh out...
...but the candy shop wasn't.
Thank you, red's my favorite!
Heihachi... that was
so generous of you.
[HEIHACHI] Aw, it's my
pleasure. Don't mention it.
So... no luck?
I'd call that
an understatement.
It's because of
the samurai hunt.
The samurai hunt?
Mm-Hmm... Apparently we all
teamed up to kill an envoy--
any samurai who aren't
in jail are in hiding now.
Don't worry, we'll
think of something.
[KIKUCHIYO] Hey guys!
Check out what I found!
[HEIHACHI]
Kikuchiyo-dono!
[GOROBEI]
You're kidding me.
[KIKUCHIYO] Thanks to me your
search is officially done.
Look, Kambei...!
Now you can have
your pick of the litter...
Almost too much
to take in, isn't it?
That's one way to put it!
[KIKUCHIYO] What?!
And just where
did you find them?
[KIKUCHIYO]
I broke them out of jail.
[GOROBEI SIGHS]
[GOROBEI]
Losers, every last one of 'em.
What did you say?!
Draw...!
You won't think
we're such losers
once you're lying
face down in the dirt!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Whoa whoa whoa, relax!
[SAMURAI GROUP YELLS]
[SAMURAI GROUP GROANS]
[KAMBEI]
You see? Useless.
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[MASAMUNE] You sure know how
to attract attention, Kiku.
Let's go...
they'll be coming soon.
[KAMBEI] We must act
wisely, and with speed.
[GOROBEI]
The Magistrate's patrolmen
will be coming from
the upper tiers.
We should work our way down
to the lower parts of the city.
Stay ahead of them.
That seems
too obvious.
[GOROBEI]
You have concerns?
They'll be
expecting it.
All of the checkpoints
will be guarded.
[KAMBEI]
Would you happen to know
of a less conspicuous route?
Hmm...
We might be able to use
the old elevator train.
I'm not familiar with it.
[MASAMUNE] It's a freight lift
they used to run between
the old ground city
and the top...
but I'm not even sure
if it's still working.
[KIKUCHIYO] Great!
What are we waiting for?!
[GOROBEI] Since when
do you make the decisions?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Somebody's got to!
[KAMBEI]
Let's go.
At present we have
no other option.
I want you to make sure you
keep up with everyone, Komachi.
We can't have you
holding us up, okay?
Relax--I'm the
fastest kid I know!
We're leaving here with
only three true samurai--
At this rate I don't know
how we're going to find
enough to protect the village.
[KOMACHI]
You mustn't lose hope.
[KOMACHI GIGGLES]
I sounded like sister, huh?
I know it's a lot
to ask, Sensei,
but do you think it would
be alright if I came with you?
I suppose
you'll have to.
Do not
misunderstand...
as long as you and
Kikuchiyo insist on
passing yourselves
off as samurai,
remaining here will
only endanger Masamune.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Don't sweat it, Katsu,
I know he doesn't think
we're real samurai.
But he'll change his
mind soon enough.
I'll bring up the rear!
Oh, yeah, now that's
what I call a samurai.
[KIKUCHIYO] Heh, heh...
At least you get me!
[GOROBEI]
They're here.
[MASAMUNE]
This way!
[KIKUCHIYO GRUNTS]
[KIRARA]
You ready?
[KOMACHI] Yep.
[PATROLMAN A]
The informants reported
several veteran samurai
were hiding out in here,
so keep your guard up.
Let's go.
[CRASHING SOUND]
[PATROLMAN A] Samurai!
We know you're in here!
Hmm...?
[THUD]
Ow!
[HEIHACHI] Here.
[KOMACHI] Thanks.
I gotcha!
Uh...!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh, you alright?
Yeah... I'm good.
[KOMACHI] It's not easy
being the new guy.
[PATROLMAN C] We've pulled
up the maps of this area.
There's an old
elevator train nearby.
[PATROLMAN A]
Let's check it out.
[KIKUCHIYO] Uh... You sure
this piece of junk is safe?
[MASAMUNE]
Uh...
Heihachi,
come with me.
Sure. Right behind you.
Is everybody ready for this?
[KIRARA] Yes.
[GOROBEI]
Come on, we'll be on lookout.
[KIKUCHIYO] Right!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Well, they're here!
[KAMBEI]
Masamune!
[MASAMUNE] These things
take some time you know!
How's it coming kid?
Do you think we'll be
able to get her started?
I'm not too
worried about it.
Huh...?
We'll get down one
way or another.
Whatever will be,
will be.
[KIKUCHIYO GRUNTS]
[GOROBEI] Hey! You wanna bet
you don't make it in time?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Shut your face!
[KIKUCHIYO SIGHS]
[GOROBEI]
Let's go!
Welcome
aboard, folks!
Well, this is where
we part ways.
[KAMBEI] Someday I'll
repay this debt. I promise.
[MASAMUNE] Wh-What the hell
are you doing that for?!
It's for your own good.
There will be less trouble
for you if they think
we forced you
into helping us.
Oh I see, thanks Kambei.
[MASAMUNE YELLS]
It's pointless if
it doesn't look real.
[KIKUCHIYO] Yeah, I better rough
him up a little, too. Heh...
No way...!
You get away from me!
[KIKUCHIYO]
C'mon! I'll be gentle.
Ahh! Kiku!
[BLOWS LANDING]
[MASAMUNE YELLS]
You... I'm not going
to forget this! Ahh!
[KIKUCHIYO] Looks like I
need to buy some time.
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
Just try to get past me!
[KAMBEI]
Kikuchiyo!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Go! I'll catch up.
[HEIHACHI GRUNTS]
[MASAMUNE YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
Anybody else?!
Well, in that case...
[PATROLMEN] Huh...?!
[KIKUCHIYO]
See ya, suckers!
What do we do now?
Light up the beacon!
[PATROLMEN] Go!
[GOROBEI]
Are you all right?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Damn right I am.
[SCREECHING]
[KOMACHI GASPS]
[MASAMUNE THINKING]
Kambei, my friend...
may fortune be with you.
[KAMBEI]
Katsushiro, take the villagers
to the passenger car.
Right.
I think your friend here's
going to be quite useful.
We need to cut
the passenger car.
Go outside and
attach this to it.
[HEIHACHI]
I am all over it.
[KIKUCHIYO] I was wondering
what was taking them so long!
You have got
to be kidding me.
Kikuchiyo!
[KIKUCHIYO] Relax, you can leave
those hunters to me, Boss-man!
[KAMBEI] Good to know,
but I need one more thing.
On my signal, reel this
in as hard as you can.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Okay...
Don't have a clue what
you're doing, but you got it!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Here we go!
[KAMBEI]
You set?
[KIKUCHIYO] Yeah!
That'll do.
We ready?
Ready as we'll ever be.
Good. Disconnect it.
Right.
[KAMBEI] On my cue,
start the smoke-screen.
Sure thing!
I'm on it!
[BEEPING]
[SCREECHING]
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[PATROLMAN A SCREAMS]
Let's do it.
[EXPLOSION]
Kikuchiyo... Gorobei!
PATROLMAN B SCREAMS]
[GOROBEI]
Kikuchiyo! The cable!
[KIKUCHIYO] On it!
[KIKUCHIYO] You go ahead...
I got a handle on all this!
Once you finish reeling...
get down here quick...
...you got it?
[KIKUCHIYO] Gotcha!
[KIKUCHIYO GRUNTS]
Come on, I dare you.
[HEIHACHI] Hey Kambei,
I finally see what you're up to.
[KAMBEI]
Katsushiro.
Yes?
As soon as the
train reduces its speed,
we're going to jump
onto the platform.
Understood.
[KOMACHI YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
Ah! Piece of junk!
Looks like I'm gonna have
to do this the hard way!
I don't have time for this!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
Prepare yourselves!
You ready for this?
Yeah!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS FRANTICALLY]
[KAMBEI] Now!
[KATSUSHIRO] Hurry!
[KAMBEI] Kikuchiyo, that's
good-- jump to the platform!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS FRANTICALLY]
[KIKUCHIYO] Hold on!
[KATSUSHIRO] Sensei!
[GOROBEI]
Forget them! Come on!
Kikuchiyo!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
You better not screw this up!
Save those farmers, okay!
[SCREECHING]
[KIKUCHIYO SCREAMS]
[KAMBEI] Let's go.
But Kikuchiyo-dono...
Sensei...
This isn't like you!
[KAMBEI]
In my life...
I've had to step over
many an ally's corpse...
That is the kind of man I am.
Komachi!
I won't let you!
[KOMACHI SOBS]
I won't let you leave him!
I won't let you leave Kiku!
[KOMACHI CRIES]
♪ closing song ♪
[KOMACHI]
Hey Okara, it's me again.
Things have been
going terribly here!
One minute everything
seems okay, then the next
we're wanted criminals running
from these really mean,
weird looking guys
with big, sharp sticks!
It has something to do with
this whole samurai hunt,
though I don't know why,
since we haven't done
anything wrong.
So now it looks like we'll be
returning to the village soon,
even though we don't
have all seven samurai.
But that's not the worst of it!
We were on this
big scary train,
trying to get away from
those mean men, you know,
and Kiku was being really brave
and fighting them off
so we would be safe,
but he didn't jump from
the train in time
and now I don't think I'll
ever get to see him again!
And stupid Kambei never
gave Kiku any credit,
even though he was the most
bravest samurai that ever lived!
Kambei didn't even care when
Kiku disappeared in the crash!
Okay, well I guess I'm going
to cry myself to sleep now...
Bye bye.