Lady Honoka, may I
ask a favor of you?
Of course.
[KAMBEI]
Tell the Guardians...
the man who killed the Imperial
Envoy was Shimada Kambei.
The bargaining chip will be me.
[RIKICHI]
Please, I want to go with you...
[KATSUSHIRO] I'm afraid you're
in no condition to go to war.
But I swear to you,
we will bring your wife back.
[SANAE]
I will not leave with you.
My Amanushi needs me,
and I cannot leave his side.
♪ opening song ♪
[Okara]
That's a pretty comb.
It's Sanae's isn't it?
You shouldn't go around peeping
into other people's homes.
It's the Harvest Feast...
How come you're
sitting here all alone?
Do I look like I'm in
any shape for a feast?
Still using the crutch, I see.
I know you're trying to
get your strength back,
Rikichi... but,uh...
I don't think carrying
two heavy swords around
with you is the way to do it.
I should be out there
helping save Sanae!
I need to be there--
I can't let others fight
my battles for me anymore!
Uh-Huh.
Did Gorobei tell you that?
'Cause, you know, this is the
sword he always used to carry.
I don't know. They all
look the same to me.
Seems like fate...
If you're joining the battle,
Gorobei must want to
fight at your side.
Wait... Kambei-sama
wanted him to stay here.
I had a feeling it would
eventually come to this...
Rikichi's gotten
a taste of the battlefield...
And I think he's proved
himself worthy, don't you?
Shichiroji, please
let me go with you!
This is my wife
we're talking about!
All right, I'll let
you go into battle.
Just as soon as you can walk.
[Prime minister]
Shimada Kambei...
I bring a decision
from the Emperor Amanushi.
This decree is final.
You are sentenced to death.
In five days time,
you will be beheaded.
I threatened to
kill the Emperor...
That's a serious charge.
Why don't they kill me
now and be done with it?
There was a request for delay...
Ukyo's asked that your sentence
be carried out in Kougakyo.
Ukyo eh?
[wind blowing hard]
[Tessai] Young Master.
They've come as well.
[Ukyo]
S-So many machines.
[Tessai] Yes, my lord...
The capital is this way.
Presenting Lord
Magistrate Ukyo...
Of the Kougakyo District.
No, please... Don't get up.
[Emperor]
That's far enough.
[bubbling and
mechanical breathing]
On your knees, Ukyo...
Show respect.
Hey, let go! Tell these
machines to get off of me!
[Emperor] So you are Ukyo...
Successor to Ayamaro.
[Prime minister] None may speak
with the Emperor directly.
[Emperor] It is all right...
I will allow it.
[Prime minister]
Yes, my lord.
[Emperor]
Come closer.
[gasps]
[Emperor]
This may sting.
Don't!
[Emperor]
Just bear with me for a moment.
Ukyo...? Could he really be...?
[Emperor] Ukyo...
You are without question,
flesh of my flesh...
My 49th clone.
My lord, is this true?
Is master Ukyo a clone?
[Emperor] Ayamaro,
I thank you for taking
my clone into your home...
You have honored me well.
Emperor, I apologize
a thousand times,
but I deserve no credit...
When I took him in, I believed
he was a mere peasant.
I had no idea he was yours.
[crowd murmurs]
[Emperor]
Silence!
Forgive my ignorance, Emperor,
but why so many clones...?
Is this not a dilution
of the bloodline?
In order to produce
the finest possible heir,
several women were
implanted with
the divine ruler's
genetic copy.
After many failed attempts,
a farm woman was chosen,
finally yielding
successful results.
The clone was named Ukyo...
And through the divine
grace of the Amanushi...
his identity was hidden
among the peasantry.
For the only way
to establish an heir
worthy of the Emperor's name,
--was to ensure that the heir
--C'mon enough, already.
had knowledge
of all social classes.
[crowd murmurs to each other]
[Ukyo] Why should it
matter to you what I am?
I was born from
the Emperor's seed,
I have his blood in my veins.
I was raised as a peasant.
And my adoptive father
taught me all about trade.
So what am I really...?
Am I...
An heir...? Am I a peasant...
Or am I a merchant?
[Emperor] I will
decide what you are.
Begin immediate
preparations for... The Test.
[crowd murmurs in shock]
[Komachi whines]
[Komachi]
I'm thirsty.
[Katsushiro]
We only have a little water left
you'll have to stick it out.
[Komachi] Katsuuuu! I can
barely take another step!
[Kirara] Just hang
in there Komachi.
[Kikuchiyo] Hey! You don't hear
me complaining, do you?
Be strong. Like me!
Okay. Guess I'll just have
to give you a piggy back ride.
All right!
Ow! hot.
Komachi.
Back off Kiku's buring up!
That's because I'm a hot guy.
Yeah, keep tellin'
yourself that...
[Kikuchiyo] Just spit on
me first. See if that helps.
Look. There's someone coming.
[Tessai] My lord... What is this
test they're preparing for Ukyo?
[Maro] It's a three
day examination
of the subjects'
method of reasoning,
in order to ascertain
his worthiness as heir...
Ukyo is going to be asked
a series of judicial and
economic questions.
The Divine Emperor
possesses the wisdom
of several generations
of rulers in his mind.
Ukyo must display the same
knowledge in order to pass.
And what happens if he fails?
Then within three days...
he will be dead.
I've heard that no clone who has
been examined has yet passed.
They've all been killed.
[Old minister 1]
Look there.
Those are memorials for
those who failed The Test--
who were deemed unworthy of
becoming the Emperor's heir...
All of them were born
and raised in the Capital,
under his guidance,
but none have lived up
to his expectations...
I wonder how Number 49,
with his peasant
upbringing, will fare.
[Emperor]
The clock has begun.
The Test will now commence.
This thing really
lasts three days?
[Emperor]
Only if you can last three days.
All right... We might
as well get started, then.
[Emperor]
Question One...
If a man suddenly finds himself
successor to a departed ruler...
What must be his
first course of action?
Well first he must
strengthen his bases...
Take up where the ruler
before him left off,
then make subtle changes...
in order to assert his power
without risking upheaval.
[Emperor]
I see.
I brought you your dinner.
Thank you, Mizuki.
By the way...
Uh, Great Kambei...
Do you happen to know
Ukyo from Kougakyo?
[Emperor]
Question 56...
What will cause the most
damage to an Emperor's rule?
That would be the
disapproval of his subjects...
If that happens, a ruler
can no longer truly govern.
[Emperor]
Hmmm.
Which is why an Emperor
must be decisive.
If his ability to make decisions
weakens, he should step down.
The other side of
that coin, however...
is it's just as dangerous to
incur the anger of the people.
[Emperor] I assume
you have a plan
to avoid incurring this anger?
Simple. The Emperor
will no longer
take anything from
his subjects.
How then, will you
maintain the Capital?
They'll pay a tribute...
...in return for our continued
generosity and protection.
[Emperor]
Just the answer I expected.
Living among peasants
has served you well.
You have shared their lives,
and thus, know their minds.
You are the first of my clones
to have achieved
this insight, Ukyo.
Question 57...
Given the options of a land of
order rife with injustice...
Or a land of justice
which has no order...
It's been two days and
the Emperor has been
without his attendants
since the Test began...
I hope he's not straining
himself too much.
I sympathize, Okata...
But it is law-- no one
may enter the chamber
until the Test is done.
Yes, but...
Please, Okata... Come rest.
Okata!
Thank you so much.
You really saved us.
You keep it. What's a
favor between samurai?
[Kikuchiyo]
That's right!
We samurai have
to stick together,
that's what I always say. Heh.
[Komachi] Haven't we met you
samurai somewhere before?
In Kougakyo...
We were looking for samurai
to help us in Kanna Village.
Yes, I remember you now...
We've been hearing stories
about what you did in Kanna.
Yeah. Everyone's heard about
the famous Seven Samurai
and what they did...
They're already legend
around Kougakyo.
[Kikuchiyo] Ooooh!
Then you've heard of
Kikuchiyo the Bandit Basher,
mighty machine samurai master!
[Komachi] So, tell me,
where are you guys headed?
We're going to Nodate Village...
Magistrate Ukyo
has given us a mission.
Ukyo, you say?
He's taken over
his father's position...
He's sent all the samurai
on missions of goodwill.
[Kikuchiyo] Wait...! What did
you say about that powder face?!
We're following
your good example...
Ukyo says you're right
and the villagers should
be protected from the Bandits...
All samurai have been
released from custody...
He says we should remember
that samurai were given
a responsibility to the people.
To the people?
All of us ronin who were
starving on the streets
have a new mission.
Protect the villages...
I can't tell you how happy
we are to have our jobs back.
And we all owe
our thanks to you.
[Emperor]
Question 108...
You are the Emperor and you
must select your advisors...
Who do you choose...?
Former enemies,
or former allies?
without a doubt.
It would be an opportunity
for reconciliation, for one.
Also, it would make the enemy
reluctant to be seen as hostile,
no matter what his politics,
therefore reducing
the risk of war.
[Emperor]
Are you afraid of war?
[Ukyo] No. But only a fool has
his mind set on fighting.
[Emperor]
What you say interests me.
That's good,
then let's continue...
Am I answering the
questions well so far?
[Emperor]
Yes. So far...
Question 109...
As an Emperor who aspires
to accomplish great deeds,
of what must you
always be aware?
[Ukyo]
Two things.
[Emperor]
Continue.
Well first of all...
The times we live in...
In our current world
climate, the wars are over
and the Merchants are
building toward the future...
However... All of those
efforts will be for nothing
unless the ruling
class can understand
the needs and desires
of the masses.
[Emperor]
And the second...?
The doctor told us
it was fatigue.
Do not be concerned for me.
How is the Amanushi?
Are you still worried about him?
Yes, I've always felt
sympathy for the Emperor...
How can I not when he's
never felt the sun on his face
or the wind in his hair...
He's trapped in that tank,
a prisoner of frailty,
all alone, fulfilling
his duty to us all.
You're trembling.
I'm worried, Mizuki...
That man they call Ukyo...
I'm afraid of the things
I see in his eyes.
The Test will be
over soon, my lady...
Maybe they've found an heir!
But then... what will
happen to this child?
[Emperor] As Emperor,
how will you distribute...
He's lasted far
longer than the others.
Then perhaps he is the one.
There has to be
equilibrium between...
[OVERLAPPING DIALOGUE]
[Emperor]
I have one final question...
What is the most important
qualification for an Emperor?
Talent, I suppose?
What do studies
matter, after all...
When you are faced with
an immediate decision
and must rely on instinct.
What about virtue?
Honesty, and goodwill?
You've grown up disguised,
your true origins hidden.
Isn't that alone an
affront to the people?
My life in trade has
taught me diplomacy.
Sometimes a lie
can be... prudent.
[Gong]
Hey, there.
He's... alive...
[Emperor] This man is my
true and rightful heir...
He will be the next Amanushi...
He is me... And I am him...
So let it be known.
All true!
[Emperor] How are
you feeling, Sanae...?
Better, I hope.
[Sanae] I am, but you must
be tired, my Lord.
[Emperor] Please, rest,
for the child's sake.
[Emperor] You carry my heir,
the last of my clones...
He, too, will
succeed me someday.
What about the one
called Ukyo, my Lord?
What if he tries
to harm the child?
[Emperor]
Worry not, my dear...
We are one and the same.
Ukyo is me...
As is this child.
[Ukyo] So how is Kirara these
days... Kambei Shimada?
I know you didn't kill
the Envoy, by the way...
The Emperor says you did...
...but I just can't quite
believe it for some reason.
[Ukyo] So tell me,
what does it feel like
waiting to be executed?
What is it you're
trying to do here?
[Ukyo] Why, conquer
the world, of course!
By the way, the true murderer
is right here in this room.
And why would you
assassinate the Imperial Envoy?
I only did it because
I was asked to...
You see, I was in a position
to do someone a favor...
This is a bad omen.
[Emperor] The ceremony
will take place soon.
For now, you must
become accustomed
to life in the Capital.
[Ukyo] May I ask
you a question now?
Anything you wish.
You see a long time ago...
there was a great
and powerful dragon...
...with two heads...
One said it wanted
to live in the south
and dive for big juicy fish...
But the other one
wanted to live in the North...
and search the skies
for tasty little birds.
And do you know what happened
to that beautiful dragon...?
Starved to death.
Now my question, Emperor...
Do you really think it's wise
for a nation to have two rulers?
It is entirely unnecessary.
I so agree.
Our forebears have
known it for untold years...
Even in the greatest
of civilizations...
crippling imperfections
will appear.
The government must be willing
to change with the times.
And after so much struggle...
Surely you've grown tired.
But don't you worry
about a thing...
I will help ease your burden...
After all... I am
you and you are me.
[Ukyo]
Good night, Emperor.
Ah yes, he is me...
But I... am so much more.
[crowd murmurs]
[Sanae]
Amanushi?
Amanushi!
[UKYO-EMPEROR]
Sanae, is that you?
Then you're all right?
Please... Stay there.
My dear, are you familiar
with the term zenjo?
It is when an Emperor of
virtue abdicates his throne
in favor of a new Emperor
of even greater virtue.
I don't understand.
Farewell... dearest Sanae.
I wish that just one time...
we could have run through
the hills and plains together...
But that is not to be.
Amanushi, please...!
Raise up the screen...!
Why will you not
let me approach you?
The rest... I leave in
the hands of my clone...
Ukyo... Step forth and
claim what is yours.
Those words were
far too good for him.
Amanushi.
Amanushi... Are you
certain about this?
From now on...
I am the Amanushi.
His... His Excellency...
The new Amanushi...
All hail the Divine Emperor!
Hail! All Hail! All Hail!
♪ closing song ♪
[KOMACHI] Shhhhhh. Quiet.
I'm trying to use
the Dowsing Crystal.
You know when sis retires,
I'm the next in line!
Well, I'm back
on the road, Okara,
and even though the Bandits
are out of Kanna for now,
it feels like there's a whole
lot more at stake this time.
I couldn't believe
the news about Ukyo--
he's the one in the makeup
who tried to kidnap sis,
and then chased us around
and shot Katsu in the leg--
I'm sure I told you that.
But now he's in charge,
and he's ordering samurai
to go other villages like ours,
and protect them
from the Bandits.
And I thought he
was the bad guy...
You should have
seen Kiku, though,
when he heard he was famous.
He was all, "I'm mighty Kiku!
Defender of the weak!
I have dragon breath
and elephant feet!" Heh...
How can I not love the guy?
But seriously,
I'm getting worried.
Is Kanna really safe?
Is Rikichi's wife
going to be okay?
It seems like the whole
world is changing,
and I'm not sure that's good.
I hope I can see
you soon! Bye-Bye.