My splashing days are over.
I'll be right here for
the rest of my life...
Because I owe this life to you.
Knock it off...
or I might believe you.
Is something wrong?
It's good to find
you alive... Shichiroji-san.
Have you grown tired of battle?
I'll be at
your side.
There's no reward or fame,
only a bloody war--Are you sure?
Yes.
This time we may
meet our deaths.
[YUKINO]
So, that young samurai...
[KIRARA]
You mean Katsushiro?
[YUKINO]
He is awfully cute.
[KIRARA]
I really hadn't noticed.
[YUKINO]
I can tell he fancies you.
[KIRARA] I'm just not
interested in men right now.
[YUKINO]
So you're really leaving?
[SHICHIROJI] I'm sorry.
I knew you weren't through
being a samurai yet.
I hope, I hope the
Nobuseri get you...
♪ opening song ♪
[KAMBEI]
Stop the boat.
[ENGINE ACCELERATING]
There's nothing
to worry about...
Let's go after them.
That would be a
violation of the treaty.
We can't.
[BOWMAN] Ah...!
No!
[GOROBEI]
Get down!
[KATSUSHIRO YELLS]
Katsushiro! No!
Young Master...!
Do you have any idea
what would happen
if you hit one of
the Guardians?!
And do you have any idea
what will happen to you
if I don't get Kirara?
The Guardians
cannot be angered,
no matter how much you
want your peasant girl...
They could reduce Kouga
Valley to ashes in seconds
if they decided
we were a nuisance.
Huh...
This is gonna hurt.
Ahh!
We're withdrawing...
Turn around.
Tessai,
really are no fun.
[KIKUCHIYO]
They're running away!
Who the hell are you guys?!
[KOMACHI GASPS]
So we're out of one danger
and into the next, huh?
Should we keep going?
Metal City is just
beyond this point.
We have
no choice now.
Oh, wow...
Would you look at that.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Say, Momotaro.
Who you
callin' Momotaro?
My name is Shichiroji.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Yeah. Whatever...
What is this
"Metal City" place?
No one knows,
but I've heard stories.
Coming down here
is forbidden.
Well the good news is
we're about to find out.
Look... we're almost there.
I don't like them.
[GOROBEI]
I'm sorry Katsushiro...
I've gotten rusty.
I should never have let
that arrow hit you.
No...
It was my own inexperience
that caused me to be too slow...
But thank you,
Gorobei-dono.
Well, Kambei...
[KATSUSHIRO]
I'm alright. I promise...
We should keep going, Sensei.
We need to get to the village.
Don't worry about me.
[KIRARA]
No, Katsushiro.
We need to rest and
take care of your wound.
[KOMACHI] Yeah.
Hmm...
[GOROBEI] Rikichi!
Easy, pal...!
What are you doing?
The rice...
Look at the rice...
Okay...
Rikichi...! Don't move!
[SPLASHING]
[KAMBEI]
Bring us ashore.
[SHICHIROJI]
You got it.
Rikichi!
The Ri-rice!
[HONOKA] Stop!
Put the rice back, please.
We'll be in trouble if
we waste a single grain.
You're samurai. Is that right?
What are so many
samurai doing here?
Put your mind at ease!
I once was a samurai,
this is true...!
But now entertaining
is what I do...!
Observe!
Great Samurai!
[HONOKA GASPS]
Eww...
Huh...?
[GOROBEI GRUNTS]
[HONOKA SIGHS]
And he's okay, folks!
Again!
Do it again!
[KOMACHI GIGGLES]
[MARO]
Take a good look, Ukyo.
Those are the energy cells
supplied by the Shikimoribito.
The Guardians.
Without those cells...
this city and surrounding
area cannot thrive.
Couldn't you've just
drawn me a picture?
Energy cells cannot be created
by ordinary human hands.
They're filled with
extraordinary power.
It's said that if
a man touches one,
scars of agony and misfortune
are carved on his flesh.
Well then why don't
you just put all these
Guardians on
your payroll?
We tried that, naturally...
But the Shikimoribito
value their independence,
and insist on trading instead.
Oh I see...
Someone's more clever
than you, Father.
Young Master.
That's all right...
The energy cells are
just like the samurai--
a double-edged sword...
Someday, Ukyo,
you will understand.
[UKYO] Letting the samurai
escape turned out to be
bad news for you,
too, didn't it father?
That's why the
Emperor has ordered
you see him
in person, right?
You must be
awfully nervous.
Remember that while
my lord is away...
you'll be ruling this city
for him, young master.
Yes... I know that, Tessai.
[MARO] That is why I showed
you this place, Ukyo...
This is the foundation
of our power...
Burn that into your brain.
[GOROBEI]
There's no need to fear us.
We're on our way
to Kanna Village to...
...take care of some things.
That's where I come from.
We've just hired
these samurai.
They're going to help
us kill the Bandits.
But no one can
face the bandits.
We don't spend our
lives farming for them...
Let them grow their own crops
if they want them so badly!
I'm sorry...
What did you say
your name was again?
It's Honoka.
Pardon my saying,
but you don't look
like a Shikimoribito.
No, I guess not...
My village was crushed
by the Bandits too...
...along with
everyone else here.
We come from
all over the place.
Now in exchange for
letting us live here...
we make food for the Guardians.
[HEIHACHI] Mmmm. This rice
is from Akane village.
Oh! But how can you tell?
It's got a
sweet aftertaste.
The Guardians' diet
is quite specific.
They eat only the sap
from these trees.
[KIKUCHIYO]
They sure are a freaky bunch.
I get the feeling we're
constantly being watched.
[HONOKA]
We are...
That's how it is here.
Come, Great Samurai.
If you wish, you can
rest at my home for a while.
[SHICHIROJI]
How's he doing?
[KIRARA] Not good.
His fever is rising...
I think he's having trouble
sleeping because of the pain.
Who's there?!
A Guardian...
[SHICHIROJI]
What was it?
You recognize
it, don't you?
It's a pharmaceutical dart
the medics used to use.
Yeah, and look at
the color markings--
I'd say it's the exact
same model from the war.
Well whatever it was,
it sure made the pain go away.
But why would they
help us like that...?
Who are these Guardians--
what do they want?
At the least, we can assume
they're not our enemies.
Sensei, please...
You must continue on
to the village now...
Just go on without me.
I'll only be a burden to you.
Stop acting so
brave, Katsushiro.
I'm not trying to
act brave. I'm serious.
You're frustrated,
as anyone would be...
And that is enough.
These two are grateful
for your sacrifice.
And they should be.
You are the fifth samurai.
Sensei!
Rest that leg for tonight...
Tomorrow we leave.
Well, congratulations...
You're a samurai.
Giving chances where
no one else would...
Guy's never changed.
You talk like you've
been friends forever...
Are you old, Momotaro?
How many times do
I have to tell you?
I'm not Momotaro!
[GROUP LAUGHS]
[KIKUCHIYO] So, you've got
a good side after all.
Come on! That'll put
some energy in the group!
His wound'll probably
heal overnight now!
Tell me... Why do you
want to become a samurai?
[KIKUCHIYO]
I am a samurai.
I swore an oath to you
I would save the farmers...
I'll keep my promise...
But it's time you return
to your previous life.
[KIKUCHIYO] But...
Hey! I am a samurai! I am...!
I am, I am, I am! Aww...
[RIKICHI] Here.
Oh, that's kind of you.
[RIKICHI] Listen,
I'm sorry about before.
I was just so surprised
to see you making rice here.
Can't say I blame you.
I was shocked too
when I first saw it.
You could come with us
to our village, if you want.
You don't have
a real home, right?
The samurai will
kill the Bandits.
Then you'll have
somewhere you can go.
[GOROBEI]
Now, Rikichi...
Are you using samurai as bait
to catch yourself a wife?
No, that's not
how I meant it!
Honestly... I just...
I can't stand...
to see suffering!
Not from Honoka or anyone else.
I know the pain
the bandits cause
so it's harder to
watch, that's all!
Thank you.
Do you have family?
I see.
I had a sister...
but not anymore.
So what happened...?
Taken by the bandits?
[HONOKA GASPS]
[RUMBLING SOUND]
[RIKICHI WHIMPERS]
[RIKICHI'S WIFE SCREAMS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
What's that sound?
[KATSUSHIRO GASPS]
No. Lay down.
You shouldn't be up yet.
Sister...
I know that sound.
[VILLAGERS SCREAM]
[KIKUCHIYO]
Where are they?
Where they coming from?
[RIKICHI]
The Bandits...
[KIKUCHIYO]
Ah, there you are, Bandits!
[RIKICHI WHIMPERS]
Well, what are
you waiting for?!
Go kill them!
That's what we hired you for!
[HONOKA] No!
[HONOKA]
You can't interfere...
They're the Guardians'
trading partners.
What?! How can
you say that?!
It's the Bandits!
They're the enemy.
[HONOKA] I may not understand
the Guardians' motives,
but we can't
defy their wishes.
We have nowhere else to go!
We do what the
Guardians tell us to...
or none of us would survive.
Honoka.
[KIKUCHIYO] You're the
boss, Kambei. What do we do?
Rikichi wait!
How can you all just
sit here like this?!
There's Nobuseri right
in front of your eyes!
There's nothing we can do.
Fine! If you won't
do your job...
...then I will!
Stop!
Foolishness.
[CAVE FARMER 1]
You! Stop!
It's against the rules
to go past the gate!
[CAVE FARMER 2] Come back!
Everyone'll be killed!
But it's the Bandits...!
Don't you understand?
The Bandits!
[GOROBEI] Rikichi!
[RIKICHI YELLS]
Your death won't be
worth anything here.
[RIKICHI] At least
it would stop the shame...
I sold my wife...!
I sold my wife to the Bandits!
What?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Rikichi...
[RIKICHI SOBS]
[RIKICHI]
To protect the village,
my wife threw herself
to the bandits.
I couldn't convince
her not to go.
And I was too scared
to do anything myself,
so I just watched
them take her...
I was a coward...
and I did nothing. Nothing!
But, what about you...?
The Bandits are the Guardian's
trading partners, huh?
And that's just fine
with you, isn't it...?
You accept it just
to live down here?!
The things that killed your
parents are right over there!
But you do nothing
because of some stupid rule!
And you call yourselves human...
Rikichi...
That's enough.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Let him talk.
He's been holding
it in long enough.
All of you...
You and the Guardians...
You're all just as
bad as the Bandits!
Yeah...? And what
would you have us do?
[RIKICHI SCREAMS]
[RIKICHI SOBS]
Rikichi... Tell me now,
what is your wife's name?
It's Sanae.
Then I promise
you now, Rikichi...
I will swear to you...
We will save Sanae.
Well, I guess that
means more work for us.
Yes, but we'll take care
of the village first.
Thank you, Great Samurai.
Hey... Now where did
Kikuchiyo run off to?
[KIKUCHIYO GASPS]
[KOMACHI]
Kiku...! Kiku! Hi!
[KOMACHI GIGGLES]
[KIKUCHIYO]
Hm...? Uh-oh.
Whoa! That was
a close one, huh?
[KIKUCHIYO]
It certainly was, little one.
Now, what are you doing here?
I was about to ask
you the same question.
[KIKUCHIYO] Well, I was
following those giant Bandits.
Well, I was following
the giant Kiku.
[KIKUCHIYO] What for?
'Cause you're always getting
yourself into so much trouble...
And I'm left behind
to worry and worry.
[KIKUCHIYO] I don't need
you to worry about me.
[KOMACHI YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
Listen up, little one...
I'm a samurai...
And samurai
are only respected
when they achieve great
glory in battle...
Now, I don't want you to worry
about me, but I have to go...
I can't just stand around
after hearing Rikichi's story.
If you understand,
just hurry back...
If the Bandits find us,
they'll rip off our heads.
[KIRARA]
Kambei!
What's wrong?
I can't find Komachi anywhere.
[KAMBEI] What?
Uhh... You mean that Komachi?
Kiku's gone.
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO GROWLS]
[KIKUCHIYO] H-Huh...?
Oh, it's you...
So, uh... I ah...
I don't suppose those
Nobuseri were you guys?!
♪ closing song ♪
[KOMACHI] Dear Okara, I met
some amazing people today.
They're called Shikimoribito,
or the Guardians for short.
But I don't know why
they're called that.
I haven't figured out
what they're guarding--
besides their rice
and their cave.
They wear weird masks,
and weird clothes,
and drink weird sap,
and hang upside down in
their home called Metal City.
And the big evil merchants
can't even touch them!
Can you believe that?
But there's one thing
I've learned for sure--
There are some crazy
people in this world!
We still don't have
seven samurai,
and I don't know where
we're going to find more.
But Kambei finally
told Katsushiro
he was part of the team.
I'm so happy for him--
he really wanted it bad.
I have a feeling
it was just 'cause
there aren't enough
samurai without him, though.
Kambei can try to act
sneaky and mysterious,
but I've got him all
figured out! Heh, heh...
Huh? Uh-oh.
Kiku's acting funny again.
I better go see
what he's up to.
Talk to you later! Bye bye!