[KATSUSHIRO]
I'll get you out!
Go!
There has to be some other way!
Heihachi-dono...
[HEIHACHI]
I'll be in the rice!
Kyuzo-dono!
[KATSUSHIRO gasps]
[KAMBEI] I need you to
keep living Katsushiro...
...until this job's done.
♪ opening song ♪
It's Heihachi's...
[rumbling]
[BANDIT DRONE LEADER] Emperor,
communications are down.
Awaiting your command.
I'm starting to think this
thing isn't going to stop.
[PRIME MINISTER]
Its inertia will
push it across the
ravine, Emperor.
The village will be destroyed.
[UKYO] Well, that was the goal,
so I suppose we win either way.
Now then...
Which way is the exit?
[PRIME MINISTER]
I'll show you.
There's a luxury vessel
prepared for your escape.
[UKYO]
How thoughtful.
Now be sure to use all
the Main Cannon's ammunition
before you leave.
[PRIME MINISTER]
Of course.
Oh dear, they won't
be easy to replace.
[MANZO] Nothing's working!
The Capital won't stop!
There's got to be some
way to slow it down!
It's going to wipe out
our entire village!
[PRIME MINISTER] No,
not the escape ship!
[UKYO] What in
the world is this?
I'm terribly sorry, Emperor.
How could you let this
happen?! Where are they?!
I--
[crashing sounds]
[whimpering]
[KIKUCHIYO] Guess
Kambei was right.
The real one would
try to escape.
No! Not you!
[SHICHIROJI] I dunno...
Maybe he's a fake, too.
[KIKUCHIYO] Don't worry.
I got the perfect test.
[KATSUSHIRO]
What are you going to do?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh yeah. Smells pretty girly.
If he smells like court ladies,
he must be real--
they wouldn't waste
perfume on a fake.
No, I'm just a farmer!
They gave me a bath
when I got here!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Enough! Your acting's terrible.
But you were a farmer
once, weren't you?
I was too. So I know why
you'd want to rule the world.
Hell, I turned myself into
metal to climb the ladder.
But you must've learned some
dignity from the upper class.
So have a little self-respect
and slit your
stomach like a man.
If you really were a farmer
once, then you should know
how important it is
that I remain Emperor.
Peasants like us spent our lives
tormented by the Nobuseri.
Now that I'm in control,
I can change that for good--
that's the point of all this!
I'm doing what I must
to set the peasants free,
and yet here you are
trying to murder me!
Stop feeding me lies,
you bastard!
[UKYO] Don't shoot!
If you kill me, then life will
only return to the way it was.
Kanna has to be sacrificed
to keep the peace--
a small price to pay to
live in a world of order.
Kambei taught me
a long time ago,
when samurai raise
their swords...
...they don't hesitate
to bring 'em down!
[screaming]
[booming sound]
Kikuchiyo- dono !
[KIKUCHIYO] Damn cowards.
I hate machine samurai!
I hate them, I hate
them, I hate them!
Treating me like
a filthy insect!
--Get off him!
--And the old Emperor,
I hate him, too!
Making me a peasant to be
bullied by you machines,
all for his stupid plan
I never asked to be a part of!
Merchants! Peasants!
Samurai! Machines!
I hate you all!
I'll turn this whole
world upside down!
I'll treat you all like bugs!
Anyway, we should be going.
Emperor.
[GUARD LEADER] But the
escape ship is disabled.
Well, then get one of
those Bandits out there
to carry it with us in it!
You're not too bright, are you?
[GUARD LEADER] No,
Emperor. Forgive me.
[explosion sounds]
Tell me where Kambei is.
I don't know.
Huh... Is that so?
[screaming]
Stop!
I won't ask again.
[GUARD LEADER] Your Excellency,
please board the escape ship.
[UKYO] By the way,
how is my Kirara?
Considering the Capital
here is going to
wipe out her entire village,
I need to know where
she is so I can rescue her.
[GUARD LEADER] Your...
Your Excellency...
What? I'm in the
middle of something!
[screaming]
[BANDIT DRONE 2] Samurai.
Raise a sword to the
Emperor and we attack.
[UKYO] Wait, you idiots!
Don't fire in here!
You'll kill us all!
[BANDIT DRONE 2]
We must protect you.
Sensei...
The Bandits are mine.
W-Wait! It was the
former Emperor who
made deals with the Nobuseri,
stealing rice and women!
I wasn't even here!
But you are the
Emperor now, Ukyo.
No, it was him--
the Prime Minister,
he was the one in control!
He came to me in Kougakyo,
said he needed someone killed
and if I helped him, he'd
let me make the world better!
But he tricked me!
I just wanted to give
everyone's lives more pleasure,
but he said sacrifices
had to be made!
He said we had to destroy
Kanna! I didn't want to!
You can't kill an Emperor!
You'll be a traitor
to your people!
So be it.
[screaming]
[BANDIT DRONE 2] Cursed samurai!
[explosion]
Katsushiro, take care of
the rest of the Nobuseri.
Right!
[SHICHIROJI] Kambei- sama ,
you're hurt pretty bad.
[KAMBEI] Don't worry about me.
We have to stop the Capital
from crossing the ravine.
[SHICHIROJI] You got it.
Kikuchiyo!
[BANDIT DRONE 3]
I have you, Emperor.
[RIKICHI] Kikuchiyo!
Kiku, can you hear me in there?
Are you going to be okay?
[KIKUCHIYO] Yeah...
Kirara! There you are!
[gasping]
[UKYO laughing]
[BANDIT DRONE 3] Emperor.
You require medical attention!
My lovely jewel.
What's wrong with him?!
He's scaring me!
I knew it...
You came to rescue me!
Things were so confusing before
you appeared... Thank you.
[BANDIT DRONE 3]
Emperor, please.
Everyone else is dead, but you
and I can return to Paradise!
Get away from them, you creep!
[BANDIT DRONE 3] Traitor!
[metal clanging]
[metal chinking]
[explosion]
[KIRARA] Kikuchiyo!
[KOMACHI] Kiku, you're hurt.
[KIKUCHIYO] There's
no time for pain now.
Rikichi, take me right
in front of the Capital.
[booms]
Now get outta' here.
You can do it, Kiku! I know it!
[KIKUCHIYO] You're
the greatest, sprout!
Please be careful!
[KIKUCHIYO] Y'can count on me.
[metal clinking]
You're not making it to Kanna,
you Capital piece of crap!
You got a full-fledged
samurai making sure of it!
[crashing sounds]
Let's get out of here.
Kirara, my jewel...
[explosion]
[whimpering]
[ELDER] Lay down your weapons.
This war is finally over.
Come out, Nobuseri!
Where are you?!
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you all!
The Nobuseri are dead,
Katsushiro...
And the Capital is no more.
It appears we have
survived yet again.
Yeah, I guess we have.
[sniveling]
Grandmother...
Are you certain of this?
Passing the Dowsing
Crystal to Komachi?
You've seen it, too... My
days as Priestess are over.
[SETSU] You mean the
tainting of the water?
Yes, I've seen it.
It symbolizes my impurity--
my sins from this war.
My dear girl,
it's not your fault.
Stop blaming yourself and think.
Do you really want
to make this decision?
[footsteps]
I swore I'd protect you.
But for a long time,
I was the one being protected.
You told me we'd fall together
and you will never know how
much strength that gave me.
--[KIRARA] Katsushiro, I--
--The scent of battle...
To please you,
I yearned for it,
but to get it, I had
to deny my heart.
Are we interrupting?
[KATSUSHIRO] All
this time, Sensei,
I've wondered what
it was you saw in me,
what made you choose me
as the fifth samurai...
And with every battle,
every wound...
...I got a little
closer to the truth.
You told me once
not to value death.
You told me to live on and to
finish what I'd begun...
And yet,
these brave men who had
nothing to gain from this war
who did give their lives
in the defense of Kanna...
Aren't they the most
noble samurai of us all?
Do you feel ashamed
for surviving?
No... It means I can
fight new battles...
Find more chances
to honor their names...
...just as you have, Sensei.
I pass this to you.
I'll use it well.
♪ Today a cherry
blossom blooms ♪
♪ The dark rain tries to stop ♪
♪ What should I,
a poor peasant, do? ♪
♪ Nurture the young rice crop ♪
♪ Once the fields are
tiered and trimmed ♪
♪ Then bring the water,
winter's ice ♪
♪ Fill the paddies
to the brim ♪
♪ It's time to plant the rice ♪
[RIKICHI winces]
Sanae, you're up...
Let me take over for a while...
After all, we are
a team, aren't we?
[RIKICHI laughs]
♪ Let clumps of
weeds wither away ♪
♪ I do not want them here ♪
Once again, old friend,
we fought a losing battle.
Huh?
This war's victory goes to the
farmers, the rice, and the soil.
But not to you and me.
[FARMERS continue singing]
Empires rise and fall,
but the land is forever.
We take our leave, Elder.
Now is a farmer's season.
♪ Weeds are picked
and water splashed ♪
♪ Don't slow until it's done ♪
♪ Put in constant effort and
sweet tasting rice will come ♪
♪ closing song ♪
[KOMACHI]
Well, this is it.
The war's over.
But Kiku isn't here
to share it with me.
The fight that started
with the Bandits
and went on with Ukyo becoming
Emperor was hard on us all,
especially the brave
samurai who died
so we could live in peace.
I promise never to forget them.
But I'm not just gonna remember
the sad and painful things.
I'll remember all
the happy stuff, too.
Like Heihachi's easygoing ways
and Gorobei's funny tricks.
I'll remember every samurai,
because we needed them all.
It's like Heihachi said.
There are seven kami who
live in the rice and protect it,
and that's what these
seven were for us.
So thank you,
serious-talking Kambei,
and smooth-talking Shichiroji,
and Kyuzo, who hardly
talked at all.
And thank you, Kiku,
for being my best friend,
and the most bravest
samurai there is.
I'll keep your scroll forever...
Well, it's late and
I better get my sleep.
After all, I'm the
Water Priestess now
and I'm gonna be busy!
Okay. Bye-bye!