Is it true you men
are actually planning
an assault on the Capital?
That's the plan.
[AYAMARO] You've proven you can
kill Bandits--that's good...
The odds may even
be in your favor...
But never underestimate Ukyo.
[UKYO] Is there no greater
honor for any proud warrior
than to give his life in
the service of his master?
[TANOMO]
Dishonoring swine!
Oh wow! Impressive!
So that's the
Capital's Main Cannon?
[KATSUSHIRO] Why did you
come to this village?
We will burn this
village to the ground...
And the flames will serve...
...to herald the arrival
of the young master.
♪ opening song ♪
[ELDER]
Is it true what you've told us?
That the Capital is on
its way here...? For us...
[UKYO]
We're releasing the women...
It's all over...
Kanna Village is free
to live in peace.
[KATSUSHIRO]
This village has changed...
You've faced the Bandits and
learned to defend yourselves...
And when the enemy appeared,
you did what had to be done.
But if I was their leader...
I would not accept defeat
at the hands of farmers...
[GOSAKU]
Then we'll fight them again!
We'll do what we must,
to protect our homes
and our families
until the end...
Isn't that right?!
[FARMERS] Yeah!
Do any of you know
how big the Capital is?
How much damage it can cause?
No. We don't know anything...
We've never seen it.
[KATSUSHIRO] The Capital was
the Central Combat Airship
of the fleet during the war.
You mean that mother ship
with all the cannons
is the Capital now?
[KATSUSHIRO]
That's right.
Then everything we've done 'til
now will have been for nothing!
If the Capital comes
and attacks the village,
we won't stand a chance!
That's what you said last time
and look how that turned out.
Why's this keep
happening to us?
Can't they pick
on someone else?
We defeated the Bandits once...
It's no wonder
they're still angry.
Then we'll just have
to fight them again!
I mean, if we're
going to die anyway,
we may as well die fighting!
It's not the dying part I mind
so much. It's the killing.
[FARMERS MURMUR]
[MANZO] Uhh...
Could you maybe ask
the others to come back?
Others?
I'm sorry, it's just,
we're kind of worried
with only you here.
We were hoping your
leader would help us, too.
[FARMERS MURMUR]
We don't need Sensei's help!
[OKARA LAUGHS]
[ELDER]
Great Samurai...
What is it?
It seems you have finally
learned how to wield that sword.
[PRIME MINISTER]
The work is moving along
as hoped, your Excellency...
We will be ready to proceed
with your plan upon your orders.
Those villagers
and their samurai
are becoming so troublesome...
Pity I can't do
this to them, too.
Once Kanna Village
is destroyed,
what do you intend
to do with the land?
By the time I'm done with it,
the land itself won't
be much to look at.
I'll give it to some
Magistrate and charge him rent.
Marvelous idea, Lord.
[TESSAI]
My lord...
We've lost contact with
the preliminary force
we sent to
Kanna Village.
According to our scout...
the entire assault party was
wiped out by the peasant rebels.
The mountain of bodies
found were impaled
by dozens of arrows and
burnt beyond recognition.
Barbaric.
Yes, that's
a tragic loss...
On the other hand,
we now have all the
justification we need.
Indeed.
Peasants with pitchforks.
How very terrifying.
[KIKUCHIYO] Ahhh!
That cave went on forever!
Sister, I'm getting hungry.
You just ate.
[SAMURAI 13]
The Emperor? Sure.
He came here himself.
When?
[SAMURAI 13]
A couple of days ago.
Looks like I beat you
to the punch here...
Don't worry. I'm sure
there are other villages
in need of your help.
Huh...?
I assume you're
looking for the Emperor
so he'll assign you to
a village that needs protection,
but you'd better hurry up--
[KIKUCHIYO]
No, no, no!
We're looking for the Emperor
so we can put a sword
or two through his belly.
[LAUGHTER]
[KIKUCHIYO]
What? What's so funny?
Sorry, I shouldn't laugh...
You're thinking of the old
Emperor, not the new one.
It's a whole new age.
How does it feel to be the last
people on the planet to know?
[LAUGHTER]
[KIKUCHIYO] Shut up!
Try pullin' your
noses out of his butt
long enough to see the truth!
Kikuchiyo! Enough!
[KIKUCHIYO]
They started it.
Please ignore my
mechanical friend here.
He's got a
slight malfunction.
[KIKUCHIYO] What?!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Hey, Kambei...!
Why didn't you just tell 'em
the truth about Ukyo?
[KAMBEI] Sometimes people
aren't ready for the truth.
[KIKUCHIYO] Huh...?
Hey! Stop the ship! Now!
[KOMACHI YELLS]
What's wrong, Kiku?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Delicious durians!
[FLIES BUZZ]
[KIKUCHIYO] Ahhhh...!
[KOMACHI]
Durians are smelly.
[KIKUCHIYO] Hey, in my village,
these were a delicacy!
We ate 'em whenever we could.
The smell is
a bit... you know...
but the inside's like
sweet, stinky heaven! Oh!
[SHICHIROJI]
He's gotta be kidding.
Why not?
I'll try anything once.
I can't believe you're actually
putting that thing
in your mouth.
It's actually pretty good.
Here, give it a taste.
I'll take your word for it.
[KIKUCHIYO] Rikichi!
Take some with you, to plant!
They'll grow just
about anywhere.
You could make 'em a Kanna
specialty! You'll be a hero!
That smell...
[KIKUCHIYO]
Ah, you get used to it.
Hey...! You wusses
won't even try one?!
Wait, is that...?
Whaddaya think?
Remnants of a battle between
Samurai and Nobuseri?
These aren't sword cuts.
Whoa, you're right.
I think a cannon did this.
An awful way to go.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Man! Look at this mess!
Heihachi... Is there
anything here we can use?
Let's see...
[KIKUCHIYO]
How bout this thing?!
You want one of
these big ones, right?
[KIKUCHIYO GRUNTS]
[THUD]
[KOMACHI]
What is it?!
[KIKUCHIYO]
A heap of junk, apparently.
He's probably right,
it's no good.
I'm not sure...
Gorobei-dono...
I realize now you
led me back here
because they needed my help.
Ah... The spirits
guided you back.
[KATSUSHIRO]
After I saw a vision of him,
I thought I should come
here one last time...
A final goodbye before
joining the battle...
The Capital's henchmen
were already here--
I must've been
guided by Gorobei.
Great Samurai, where's Kirara?
[KATSUSHIRO]
She's with Sensei.
Huh... And all this time
I assumed my granddaughter
went off with those samurai
to be with that young man.
Kirara did what?
You're slow, old woman.
Okara...! You know
something, don't you?
You've got her reasons
for leaving right,
but you've got
the wrong samurai.
Then who...
[KAMBEI]
How's it look?
I think she'll fly for us.
Good... As soon as
the repairs are done,
we'll head
for the Capital.
All right.
Well it might not be
much of a war ship,
but it certainly is faster
than that old wagon...
It's too bad we don't have time
to find something with defenses.
The Capital isn't
going to wait for us.
[KIKUCHIYO]
So we're finally gonna strike?
[KAMBEI GRUNTS]
How many years has it been
since we've taken on
one of those airships?
I'd say I'm nervous,
but I keep thinking of what
Gorobei-san would
say if he were here.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Yeah! He'd say...
"Nervous? You gotta be kidding!
Get out there and
die with honor, man!"
[KOMACHI CRIES]
Komachi, what's
the matter with you?
I don't want Kiku
to die with honor.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh. Well, listen. I was just--
That's--That's just
tough guy talk.
Who could ever die and
leave you behind, sprout?
Really? Promise?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Here, I tell you what...
I want you to hang
onto this for me.
It's my proof that I'm samurai.
The scroll
that you stole?
[KIKUCHIYO]
I didn't steal it! I found it.
Anyway, that doesn't matter.
You were the first person who
ever accepted me as a samurai--
Who believed in me.
So I want you to have my
most valuable possession.
Keep it safe for me,
and I'll be back for it.
I promise.
[KOMACHI]
It's a deal!
But you have to promise me
something even more important.
[KIKUCHIYO]
All right, lay it on me.
'Kay don't laugh...
But when I grow up,
I want you to be my husband!
[KIKUCHIYO GASPS]
[SHICHIROJI LAUGHS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
In this heap of metal?
I can't even farm rice.
Well I love you just
the way you are, Kiku.
I'll even cook for you!
[KIKUCHIYO SOBS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
I'm so happy.
Are you sure
about this, sprout?
I'm sure.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Ha, ha, ha...
Oh! Hurry up and get
older, little Komachi!
I'm gonna be your
husband! Ha, ha!
Do you know how
happy you've made me?
I'm the luckiest
guy in the world!
[KOMACHI]
I'm the lucky one!
Have you ever been to
the Capital before?
[KYUZO]
Once, with my former lord.
[KAMBEI] Are the defenses
the same as during the war?
[KYUZO] Mostly.
[KAMBEI] Hmm...
What do we do about
the main engines?
I say we disconnect 'em.
If the're still running
when it crashes...
all this beautiful farmland
will be destroyed.
[SHICHIROJI] You mean
all this beautiful farmland
that's needed to grow
the rice you love.
[HEIHACHI]
Hey, we are the rice kami.
Gotta protect it too.
Alright, then we'll leave
cutting off the main
engines to him.
So what's our move, Kambei-sama?
I assume you have a plan.
No.
[HEIHACHI] Huh...?
Really... None at all.
Tomorrow... Death awaits.
It's late...
You should get some rest.
Oh, don't worry about me...
Just call me if any
of you need anything.
She's a great girl.
Guess we should give
Ukyo some credit...
At least he has
great taste in women.
[SHICHIROJI] It's hard to tell
who the enemy is these days.
During the war it was easy...
You just killed anything
that held a sword.
Perhaps the days of fighting
battles with swords are no more.
Rikichi...
Yes.
We won't wait for sunrise.
As soon as the repairs are
completed, we're heading out...
We leave the
women in your care.
Make sure they get home safely.
That's your job.
We're counting on you.
Right.
[FARMERS MURMUR]
Great Katsushiro,
we're all done over here.
What do you want us
to work on next?
Nothing... That's all
we can do for now.
Divide into three
shifts for guard duty.
[YOHEI]
Right away.
If you see anything unusual,
send out the warning
with the clappers,
then wait for my signal
to take action, understood?
Yes, sir.
[KATSUSHIRO]
Is everything ready?
[FARMER]
Yes, Sir!
[MOSUKE]
Great Samurai!
All clear so far!
Where's Kiku?
He's gone, Komachi.
But he... can't be...
I didn't get to say
good-bye to him!
Your sister thought it would be
less painful for you this way.
Sister, why didn't you
let me say good-bye to Kiku?
We can't worry about such
petty things now, Komachi,
not when the war
is about to begin.
We need to be grown ups, okay?
Water Priestess...
I promised them that
I would be strong,
but I feel like I'm breaking.
Take it from someone
who has been broken,
when your heart
opens a new window,
there is no gain in hiding
your eyes from the light.
But if I allow
myself to admit it
then I won't be able to keep
from telling him the truth.
That I want him...
Body and soul.
Then we just have to
pray as hard as we can
that they'll come back.
If we pray with all our
strength we'll be fine, right?
We're a Water
Priestess family--
It's our job to pray.
So we just have to do our job.
You're exactly right,
my darling...
I love you.
[SNORING]
[FAINT RUMBLING SOUND]
[KATSUSHIRO]
Mosuke! Wake up!
[MOSUKE YELLS]
[CLATTERING]
Look, here comes the Elder.
[FARMERS] Elder!
It is time.
[RUMBLING SOUND]
[KATSUSHIRO GRUNTS]
[GASPING]
[PRIME MINISTER] Silence!
Do not be frightened!
This is the Capital!
It appears the Main
Cannon was deflected.
My lord, only the sword
of a true samurai
is capable of
accomplishing that.
Samurai?
I knew it.
It may be too risky
to use the cannon again.
No...
I should remind you
that during the Great War,
Samurai were the only
ones who could ever
bring down
a ship like this.
So, they're looking
for a fight, are they?
That leaves us no choice.
Call out my new soldiers.
[UKYO OVER P.A.]
Good morning, everyone!
[BANDIT DRONE LEADER]
All drones: Launch!
And they'll really do whatever
I tell them to, no matter what?
Give it a try,
Your Excellency.
If you insist.
About face!
[UKYO LAUGHS]
Did you see that?!
They're mindless...!
Just obedient heaps of metal!
[APPLAUSE]
Very impressive,
Your Excellency.
When I was a peasant
I despised them so.
Their mere presence
made me sick.
But they're kind of cute
like this, don't you think?
We're attacking one
measly farming village.
There is no need
for such numbers.
We can't go easy on them.
One thing I learned
as a Merchant is that
any compromise leads
to a lack of respect.
Think of it as
ridding ourselves
of a failed business partner,
Tessai, nothing more.
Just like I did
with that envoy.
Ahh...?
[BANDIT DRONE LEADER]
Unit 1--attack!
Keep it together!
[MOSUKE]
Yeah, sorry.
Take all the fury you've buried
inside and release it on them!
Get ready, they're here.
Let's kill them with the very
weapons we stole from them!
[GUNFIRE]
Yeah!
[FARMERS CHEER]
Let's stay sharp!
Hurry and get the
second round loaded!
[FARMERS YELL FEARFULLY]
Get all the wounded out of here!
[MOSUKE]
Just hang on, guys!
Heh, this won't take long...
We can't do it!
There's no way we can win
against something like that!
[KATSUSHIRO YELLS]
Katsushiro,
behind you! Look out!
[KATSUSHIRO YELLS]
[MESSENGER] Emperor!
There's a lone attack ship
approaching from the rear.
Attack ship...? Is that so...?
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
Kikuchiyo and the boys...
Out to kick some Capital ass!
♪ closing song ♪
[KOMACHI]
Dear Okara, I have great news,
and I wanted you to be the first
in the village to know...
Kiku and I are
going to be married!
Can you believe it?
I mean not now, of course--
but when I grow up!
The samurai were getting
ready for their big fight
against the Capital, and it
was gonna be super dangerous,
and I was worried.
But Kiku said it'd be okay,
and that's when he promised
we could be together forever!
I always knew he
was a special samurai,
ever since we met in Kougakyo.
I was the one who
found him, you know!
Sis and Rikichi had
their doubts about him,
I think, probably 'cause
he's a big machine,
and likes to yell and be noisy,
and most the other
tough samurai act like
they've forgotten how to talk,
but I've always known
Kiku was a real hero!
And now he's gonna
prove it against the Capital,
and we'll never have
to give away our rice
and be miserable again.
I bet he'll be the
biggest hero of all!
Well it's a big day tomorrow,
so I better get some sleep.
See you soon. Bye bye!