[KAMBEI]
Your determination and loyalty
have won me over to your cause.
I will help you.
I shall not let your
treasured rice go to waste.
[RIKICHI]
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
[GOROBEI] Do it!
[GOROBEI MOANS]
[KATSUSHIRO]
Please. Forgive me!
Forgive you for what?
[KATSUSHIRO] For failing in
my duty to protect you...
I told you not to
let go of my hand...
but I let go of yours...
[KAMBEI] No. We will not be
taking these two with us.
But, Sensei!
I need
real samurai.
[FOOTSTEPS]
Heh, heh... You've
got to be kidding me.
Excellent.
♪ opening song ♪
[CYCLOPS LAUGHS]
[GOROBEI]
Gentlemen...
How about a little wager?
A bet?
[GOROBEI]
That's right.
A simple bet with
very high stakes...
I will give you my word...
not to move from this spot
and your archer there
will fire one arrow at me.
Hmm...
One shot would
be too boring...
How about five?
Hmm...
Five shots, huh?
Scared you can't
handle it, old man?
Not at all...
I accept your terms.
[KIKUCHIYO]
What?! Is he nuts?!
Let us watch and see.
If any of your arrows
pierce my skin
before I'm able to stop them...
Then you've won, and you can
have my head no questions asked.
That's not enough for us.
If you fail, we get the heads
of all the samurai and
peasants we came for.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Wait a second! Five shots?!
Don't leave our
lives to him!
He's weird! He's got
some sort of deathwish!
Sensei?
On the other hand,
if I do win...
You promise to let us go free.
Peasants and samurai alike...
I won't even ask you for
your heads in return...
[KIKUCHIYO]
That bastard!
The deal was for
you to let us go!
The deal was never agreed upon!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
Kikuchiyo, no!
You gotta be kidding me.
[PINKY YELLS]
Is he trying
to kill us?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Crap. Sorry!
Quick, everyone
outside! Now!
[RIKICHI]
Priestess, go!
[KIKUCHIYO COUGHS]
[CYCLOPS YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[CYCLOPS GRUNTS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
We're not done yet!
Ahh!
[PINKY GRUNTS]
[CYCLOPS SCREAMS]
[CYCLOPS GRUNTS]
[CYCLOPS] Heh, heh...
[CYCLOPS WHIMPERS]
[GOROBEI] I told you to
let us go, did I not?
To think that instead, you
would choose your own death...
[CYCLOPS SCREAMS]
[BUZZING]
[THUD]
You idiot.
I could've finished them off
a lot easier if you hadn't
brought the roof crashing
down on our heads.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Well maybe you should ask me
before gambling with my head!
No time for
arguments...
You've made quite
a mess, Kikuchiyo.
[KOMACHI] Woah!
That was impressive and stuff...
but we're gonna get in trouble.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Fine, fine, everyone just dump
all the blame onto Kiku.
I'll clean it up!
I'll just put on my little
servant cap, and get to work!
[KIKUCHIYO GRUNTS]
Well...? What are you
guys gonna do now...?
If Ayamaro's set
his dogs on you,
you can't go strolling around
looking for samurai anymore.
We'll continue no matter what.
I have no intention
of leaving this city
until we've found all
the samurai we need.
Hmm...
Well, you'd better
come to my place then.
[HORN BLOWS]
[KOMACHI]
Wow. It's dirty.
[KIRARA] Komachi!
[KOMACHI]
I'm sorry, but it is.
[MASAMUNE]
That's alright.
I know it's small,
but you're welcome to
make yourselves at home.
We thank you.
Old warriors help each other...
...don't they?
Mmm...
[SPLASH]
[CLAPPING]
[UKYO] I suppose you've
heard you're next...
You do know what
happened to them...?
Tessai's assassins, I mean?
They were cut down by
the samurai yesterday...
It's really such a pity.
[TESSAI]
Master Ukyo.
Ohh...
No, these won't do.
Yes.
You know what
I want right now...
I want the
farm girl...
I want to hold
her in my arms!
You've said it yourself,
Master, she's a peasant.
The difference in
class is too great.
You can't touch her.
[IMPERIAL ENVOY] I hear that
commoners have been causing you
quite a bit of trouble
these past few days, Ayamaro.
[AYAMARO] And in the merchants'
model city, at that.
I suppose even the
finest meat draws flies.
Of course you're
in control, magistrate,
but I believe stains
should be removed quickly,
before they can no
longer be washed out.
Who's there?
Kyuzo...
...and the young
master, my lord.
Goodness...
You can sense them...
Quite impressive.
Father!
You dare yell in front
of our esteemed guest?!
[UKYO] Did you give the
order to kill Kirara, too?
[AYAMARO] Of course.
[UKYO] Why?
[AYAMARO]
She's just a peasant...
And this is the last I want
to hear of her, understand?!
You will cease this obsession!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Young master...
you live in a city of merchants,
built by your father...
Peasants and samurai
live in separate worlds,
far from the
beauty of this one...
My advice is to stay
in the merchant world
where you belong
and leave the
peasant girl to hers.
I really don't remember
asking your advice.
You insult an
imperial envoy!
[UKYO] And you
insult me, father...
You can't even kill peasants...
much less samurai.
I hear samurai can only
be killed by other samurai,
is that true?
Mere mythology,
bred from the Great War.
Well I bet you and
Kyuzo could do it.
Don't even entertain
the thought...
I will not
allow it...
They're my
strongest bodyguards.
Tessai's henchmen most certainly
won't be able to handle them...
So I guess that means they
bested you, right, Father?
What about
the Bandits...?
Isn't that
what they're for?
[AYAMARO]
The No-Buseri?
[IMPERIAL ENVOY]
That's right...
Samurai who
transformed themselves
into weapons in
the Great War...
They continue to be
unrivaled embodiments
of fear for the
peasants, even now...
I think they'd be
perfect for this.
The No-Buseri are machines!
No-Buseri... are honorable
warriors who sacrificed
their human vessels for
more efficiency in battle--
they are models in
an age of progress.
[UKYO]
I hate machine samurai!
[MESSENGER]
My lord, the Shikimoribito
are here to see you.
[AYAMARO]
I'll be right there.
[UKYO] I'm not
done talking yet!
Ukyo, I want you to put those
people out of your mind,
do you understand?
I will take care of it.
Imperial Envoy,
if you will excuse me.
Shikimoribito...
You have performed well...
Raise your heads,
so I may see you.
The ears of rice are going to
bend sooner than we'd hoped.
Then we'll move faster.
[KATSUSHIRO] Lady Kirara,
you continue to surprise me.
[KIRARA] Me?
You know that bad men
are looking for you...
yet you go to the
middle of town anyway...
just to hold
a rock over some water.
Heh, heh...
It's not just a rock.
It's a Dowsing Crystal,
handed down the Meikumari line.
It's an extension of my soul...
It lets me use water to
divine truths about the world.
Ah... I see, you don't believe
things like that
are possible, do you?
No! I-It's not that!
Back in the village, I could
always feel the outside world...
I could sense its energy
without ever seeing it...
That's partly why I wanted
to come here so much.
Quite a dangerous trek
to make just because
of a little curiosity,
don't you think?
Yes, I know, but
I can't have regrets,
because now we've found
Kambei to help our village.
Of course we got to
meet all of you, as well.
Y-Yes, of course.
And besides, no matter how
dangerous the city might be,
it's full of new experiences.
Things I would never
see in my village...
Not as long as our
fear of the bandits
holds us captive, at least.
Get outta the way!
[HORN HONKS]
Katsushiro.
I told you, I will never
let go of this hand again.
[KATSUSHIRO] Hello?
[KIRARA] Excuse me, would
you please deliver this letter
to the village
of Kanna for me?
[POST MAN]
It would be my pleasure.
Go tell the lord
they're here.
We leave the letter
in your care.
You got nothin'
to worry about!
Hee-yaw!
Anything,
Great Samurai?
Want a look?
I just wish I knew exactly
what we were looking for here.
What the old mechanic said
made me start thinking...
if we can't escape
a battle with Ayamaro,
then it's best we know as
much about him as we can,
so we're spying on
him for a while...
You have a better idea?
Me...?
I'm just a farmer,
Great Samurai...
How would I
know what to do?
Well, you never know.
What do you see?
[GOROBEI]
A samurai... A good one.
[TESSAI] Kyuzo...
we'll take care of the girl.
[HYOGO] You're planning
to hunt the samurai...
You realize those aren't
the orders you were given.
Wait a minute--
Hyogo... are you sure?
[BLOWING AIR]
[KOMACHI COUGHS]
[KAMBEI LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
[KAMBEI] Let me help.
No thank you.
I wouldn't if I
were you, Kambei...
The little one's
pretty mad at you now...
She thinks you were too
hard on Kikuchiyo back there.
You're grumpy!
Always pickin' on Kiku and
he never did anything to you!
People have
different paths in life.
Sometimes that's
hard to accept.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
All I know is you're
not very nice, okay!
All right...
I'm about finished.
[BLOWING AIR]
[MASAMUNE]
An elegant sword.
[KAMBEI]
Thank you.
Seems you take very
good care of it.
I'm impressed you take
the time these days...
Most samurai don't...
[MASAMUNE]
The Great War ended more than
a few years ago, didn't it?
And yet...when
I look at your sword...
it tells me you're ready
to charge into battle
at any moment.
Maybe you miss the excitement
and purpose of war?
It's said when you
kill a man in battle,
you are haunted by
his ghost forever...
I'll be back...
We still need five more.
Not a chance...
That's an insult.
No true samurai
would take such work.
[KIRARA SIGHS]
[KATSUSHIRO GASPS]
[KIRARA]
Katsushiro?
It's nothing.
For a moment it felt like
we were being watched.
[CROWD MURMURS]
It's Kambei!
[KATSUSHIRO] Sensei...
we couldn't find any samurai.
Really...?
I'd say one found you.
[KIRARA GASPS]
So we were followed.
So it would seem,
Katsushiro.
I am Shimada Kambei.
May I have the honor
of knowing your name?
Kyuzo.
I ask only because
I know you are samurai.
Challenge.
Two swords... What an honor.
Good luck.
He's already here.
I am in love...
...with your skills, that is.
I am seeking skilled
samurai for a difficult job.
Care to join me in a new war?
Against the No-Buseri,
is that right?
If you already know,
this can go quickly... Join me.
I'll pass!
[KAMBEI GRUNTS]
What a shame!
KOMACHI YELLS]
Sensei!
[KAMBEI]
I cannot defeat you...
[KAMBEI BREATHES HEAVILY]
...but before you kill me
there is something
I have sworn to do...
And I cannot let you stop me.
I am sorry, but I have
to turn my back on you.
[KAMBEI]
Kyuzo-dono was it...?
We will fight again once my
team has defeated the Bandits...
You'll have to
wait until then...
Unless... You would kill me
while my back is turned.
[KYUZO] Hmm...
Wow... This is scary.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Ah, heh, heh... Finally done!
Huh?! Look out, Kambei!
[GASPING]
It's Kiku!
[KIKUCHIYO]
I'm coming!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO] Owww!
[KYUZO]
Another time, then.
[KAMBEI SIGHS]
I want him.
♪ closing song ♪
[KOMACHI]
Hey Okara, Komachi here.
Whew! Things have been
pretty crazy around here.
Just listen to this!
First Sister got kidnapped by
that crazy boy with the makeup
who was trying to
butter her up.
Then he sent his goons after her
and Katsushiro and
Kiku fought them off.
Mostly Kiku, though.
Then they came after us again
and Gorobe and Kambei sliced
'em to pieces! Whack! Whack!
We really got to see them in
action, and they are scar-ee!
Kiku got a little carried away,
though, and made everyone mad.
Then, when everything
was calm again,
this weird samurai
comes out of nowhere
and starts fighting Kambei.
He said his name was Kyuzo,
but that's about all he said.
Didn't seem like
much of a talker,
but that just made
him scarier...
I thought no one
could beat Kambei,
but this guy was just as good.
And you wanna hear
something strange?
I think Kambei kinda liked him.
Now why would you like
someone who wants to kill you?
I'm too tired to figure it out.
Good night!