[KIRARA]
He chooses for us, in silence,
and expects us to follow?
Any hope I had of understand
this man is quickly fading...
Lower your voice!
Or do you want us to
be caught and gutted?
No...
Now you are making
me beautiful, aren't you?
Oh, naturally...
Though you won't be as
lovely as Eminosuke here.
We're doomed...!
The two of you have gone insane!
Would you please stop with that?
Oh, you can try to hide it...
But... I can tell that you are
totally in love with her!
[KIKUCHIYO LAUGHS]
[KIKUCHIYO] Oh, I think
you might be right, sprout!
Look at him blush!
[KIRARA] Thank you saving
my life, Great Samurai.
Thanks for the stitch.
I'd say our journey
went... well.
Yeah, I guess so.
♪ opening song ♪
[GOROBE]
Slacking off. What a surprise.
Have they left?
Yeah, just now...
So, uh... do we really have
to get in that nasty thing?
[FLIES BUZZ]
Where's Kiku?
We don't know
where he is right now.
I just hope he doesn't
cause any more trouble.
[KIKUCHIYO GRUNTS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
The way of the samurai
is to always climb... up.
It's... quiet...
[KOMACHI]
Hey! Come out!
The samurai are here!
[RIKICHI]
Where are they?!
Hey, quit being rude!
The samurai are here!
Come on! Say hello!
What are you doing...?
The samurai are here!
This is dishonorable!
So this is
our fortress, huh?
The samurai are here...
So where the hell
is everybody?!
I'll inform the
Elder you're here.
[KOMACHI BREATHES HEAVILY]
[OKARA]
Welcome back.
[KOMACHI] Huh?
Okara! Hey, where
is everybody else?
[OKARA]
Hiding of course...
They're all afraid
of the samurai.
Hiding?
But sister and Rikichi
went to a lot of trouble
to bring them all here.
Manzo made a big
fuss, as usual.
You know what
a coward he is.
C'mon, hurry!
We're waiting for your sister.
Dad! What are you doing?!
The samurai will
be here any day!
You're going into hiding
with the rest of the girls!
No! I want to
see the samurai.
Do not be foolish, child!
How can you do this when
they're coming to save us?!
The samurai aren't
coming to save us!
They're coming to take
our food and our women
like they always have!
[OKARA] So now all the women
are in the hidden
storehouse with the food.
So, how come you're not hiding
out with the rest of them?
[OKARA]
I don't know.
Well, I guess
this just means
you'll get to meet
the samurai first!
[KIKUCHIYO]
A hidden storehouse...
Where is it, girl? Hmm?
What's that thing?
Oh, that's Kiku!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Call me Kikuchiyo!
So what is he? Your sidekick?
[KIKUCHIYO] Huh?!
[FOOTSTEPS]
I've found them--
they're at the Elder's now.
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive this
unfriendly welcome.
Kiku, is this another test
of braveness or something?
[KIKUCHIYO] Hah, hah...
This time it's a test to see
if all farmers think alike.
They are not going to fool me.
Ha, ha, ha! Found it.
This is the
storehouse, isn't it?
Come on, Kiku...
[KIKUCHIYO]
Sorry about this, sprout, but...
Uh-oh...!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[OKARA LAUGHS]
[ELDER]
Farmers are foolish people.
Always worrying
about something.
Too much rain, too much sun,
strong winds, no winds.
They wake up worrying and
they go to bed the same way.
Today's no exception.
They're just scared--
pointlessly scared.
[MANZO] Please go away!
Doesn't anyone remember what
the bandits said they'd do to us
if they find out samurai
have actually arrived?
I'm not sure what you think
we came here for, good farmer,
but it certainly wasn't to
watch you all be slaughtered
by the Bandits
while we do nothing.
But they're Bandits!
Yeah, think we covered that--
what's your point?
He mentioned threats--
have they come recently?
[ELDER] Two days ago.
They heard we had
hired samurai,
said they would kill
us if it were true.
Then Great Elder... what
exactly do the villagers
expect us to do
now that we're here?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Well... look what I found!
Rice and women!
Whaddya know? Huh?
Thought you could hide
the goods from me,
but I'm too smart for farmers!
Shino!
Give back our rice!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Back off, suckers! Ahhh!
Shino!
How'd you find the hidden
storehouse, samurai?
[KIKUCHIYO] Yeah,
I'm a full-fledged samurai,
but I can think like a bandit
when rude villagers need
to be taught a lesson. Eh?
Any objections, Grandpa?
No...
Alright by me.
[KIKUCHIYO] Ha, ha, ha, ha...
If you think you can back out
now that you've brought us here,
you're wrong!
Bandits never forgive a
village that betrayed them.
[VILLAGERS YELL FEARFULLY]
[KIKUCHIYO]
But don't worry!
Now that I'm here,
everything's going to be fine.
Let go of me,
you big pack-mule!
[KIKUCHIYO] Okay, don't
get twitchy, sweetheart.
Well I'll be damned,
the big oaf can be useful.
[KAMBE] Heh, heh...
I've returned, Grandmother.
Mm-Hmm...
And have you brought samurai?
Yes ma'am.
We brought seven of them!
And are they
good samurai, child?
Yes... I believe
they are, Grandmother.
Well... that's so
nice then, dear...
Good samurai are very hard to
come by lately, you know...?
When I was young they weren't
so few and far between...
but then those were
much better days.
[KIKUCHIYO] Oh, you
are so ravishing! Ha, ha!
[KIKUCHIYO MAKES
MUSICAL NOISES]
Oh, Rikichi!
I had no idea you had such
good taste in women's clothing.
Kikuchiyo.
[KIKUCHIYO] Ha!
Who wants to dance with me?
Hey! Don't worry.
I wasn't going to pick you.
Kikuchiyo!
Don't bother.
He wouldn't get it.
[KIKUCHIYO] Get what?
[MANZO YELLS]
Oh, I was just, uh...
...going to see how
the rice field was doing.
[MANZO SCREAMS]
[KYUZO]
The war has already begun.
[SHICHIROJI]
I'm beginning to worry
Rikichi's buying into
Manzo's paranoia...
[HEIHACHI]
You might be right...
[SHIKA]
Ooh, look at his sword!
[UMA]
Does he kill people?
He looked over here!
He's as handsome as an actor.
[HIE] And so much
more dangerous.
[HIE GIGGLES]
[GIRLS YELL]
[HIE] Oh my gosh,
he totally looked at me!
[UMA]
He was looking at me.
[SHIKA]
No. He looked at me!
[UMA] Oh, you're delusional.
[SHIKA] You always think
everyone's looking at you.
[HIE] He was practically
staring at me.
[OKARA] You're popular
with the girls, samurai.
But your back is vulnerable...
If I was an assassin,
you would already be dead.
[OKARA AND KOMACHI LAUGH]
[OKARA YAWNS]
The preparations for
our defense begin now.
We have been told the
Nobuseri have forty units...
Has this changed?
[ELDER GRUNTS]
We've heard from
other villages--
ten more big units, and
maybe sixty more footmen
and Yakan combat shells.
We should send out a scout
soon for exact numbers.
Heihachi-dono, you'll
be on weapons detail.
[HEIHACHI GRUNTS]
Shichiroji, I trust you
know what to do... right?
Just leave it to me.
Kyuzo-dono, I want you
to gather the village men
and teach them to
use a bow and arrow.
Understood.
What should I do sensei?
You'll be on guard duty.
Oh, great. Guard duty.
Do not let any enemy
scout get away...
They cannot know about us
before defensive
preparations are complete.
Yes sir!
If we do not work together now,
then we've lost this war
before it's begun...
Let us band together
against the Nobuseri
and defend Kanna Village!
[FARMERS MAKE
WEAK BATTLE CRIES]
[KIRARA SIGHS]
[ELDER MAKES STRONG
BATTLE CRIES]
Ahhhh!
Ahhhh! Ahhhh!
Ahhhh! Ahhhh! Ahhhh..!
[KIKUCHIYO]  Heh...
I don't care what
the samurai say.
There's no way a few
rice farmers with arrows
can beat the Nobuseri.
They're machines.
We don't even
stand a chance.
We should beg them for mercy.
Yes, I agree.
A bandit patrol will be
here around 7 o'clock...
Maybe if we were to go and
appeal to them right away...
You think they'd let us go?
[RUSTLING]
[MEN YELL]
[KIKUCHIYO] Hey!
That's what I call good timing!
Ahh...!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Yeah, that should do for now...
Alright. Let's begin.
[GONZO]
Begin what?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Your training.
All right, listen up!
From this moment on,
I am your commander!
[GONZO] Huh?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Now stop whinin' and follow me!
Hello, water... miss me?
[TORA] Kirara!
Kirara, there's something
we want to ask you.
[UMA]
It's about the samurai.
Don't worry. They're all
very strong and reliable...
Especially Kambe.
He's the most--
We don't care about him!
[UMA] We want you to tell us
about the youngest samurai.
You know, the
handsome one!
You... You mean... Katsushiro?
Oh! Katsushiro!
Ohhhh! He's so cute!
What is he like?
He's a good person...
but I believe...
...as a samurai he
still has a lot to learn.
Yeah, we really
don't care about that!
Does he have a wife or
girlfriend or anything?
I don't know. I never asked.
Come on, you have
to know something!
Now don't you
hold out on us.
If you want to know so
badly ask him yourselves.
No! We're too shy!
[KIRARA SIGHS]
[GOROBE] Well... this
is an incredible place.
We believe it to be sacred.
I think we can use these...
We're going to have
to chop a few down.
I must warn you, however,
they won't come down so easily.
Heh... The tougher the better.
Hold your breath
when you draw the bow.
Okay.
See your enemy closer
to you than he really is.
Draw him to you, then fire.
[FARMERS YELL]
[OKARA LAUGHS]
[KOMACHI] Aww...
[GOROBE]
There is one good thing.
At least we won't
have to worry about
them attacking us by water.
Let's build a dam,
just to be safe.
Just beyond us is a waterfall.
It's a bit deeper
than I thought...
A difficult place to attack,
but also tough to defend.
That will not escape
Shichiroji's notice.
No. I guess not...
He is your right hand man.
I know it's heavy, guys, just
put it over there would you?
What are you guys doing?
We're strengthening
our defenses.
How ya gonna do that?
Kambe's planning to make this
little village into a fortress.
Kinda like a castle.
This place is gonna be a castle?
An impenetrable one.
The only problem is the sky.
Hey, sweetheart...?
I don't suppose you
know if the villagers
have any weapons
stashed away?
They do, but
you can't have them.
[KAMBE] We'll have to
destroy the bridge.
[GOROBE] You may be right...
But what do we do about the
three homes on the other side?
[KAMBE]
It's unavoidable.
To have any kind
of solid defense,
they must, unfortunately,
be sacrificed.
[KOMACHI] They've been here
since before we were born.
[OKARA]
They're broken.
These are a really
great find...
Thanks, sweetheart.
[KOMACHI LAUGHS]
[SHICHIROJI]
By the way...
I've got a very important
mission for the two of you.
--[OKARA] Huh...
--[KOMACHI] Oh...!
So, tell us about
yourself, samurai...
Are you married?
Have a girlfriend?
Hey, less talkin',
more workin', grandma.
[KOMACHI] Heihachi!
C'mon, c'mon.
Quick as you can...!
Momotaro has a question about
machines or something.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Huh? Maybe I should handle this.
Nobody asked
for you, Kiku.
[KIKUCHIYO GRUNTS]
Dad, wait! Don't go!
Move, girl!
You're going to sell the samurai
out to the bandits, aren't you?
Did you know they're going
to destroy the bridge?
That we'll be isolated from
the rest of the village...?
If we're going to lose
our farm anyway,
what was the point of hiring the
samurai in the first place?
If it'll help save the village,
we have to make that sacrifice!
I'm doing this
for you, girl...
Once our farm's been destroyed,
who will want to marry you?
What do I care?
I'll marry a samurai!
[MANZO]
Foolish child!
You will never disgrace
me in such a way!
I hate you!
Oh yeah, I'm pretty sure
I can do what you want me to.
[KIKUCHIYO] You guys
are having all the fun.
Hey! Kikuchiyo!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Can't hear you.
Kikuchiyo-dono...
I think I'm gonna need
your help on this one.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh! Why didn't you say so?
Be right down!
[THUD]
Kirara! You have to
help me stop my dad
before anyone finds out!
He's going to
betray the village.
He's on his way to tell
the bandits about the samurai!
We can't allow
him to do that.
But if that quiet samurai finds
out about Dad he'll kill him!
I know he will...! Kirara...
I'll think of something, Shino.
Oh, thank you.
[KIRARA]
Now where is Manzo?
[SHINO]
He's on the North cliff,
waiting for the
seven o'clock scout.
[KIRARA]
Katsushiro?
You heard all of
that, didn't you?
I would like to
ask for your help.
I'll do my duty.
All right big guy...
Nice and easy through here!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Uh, hey, so what are you
gonna make with these things?
Oh, you'll see.
There he is.
[MANZO] Sir, you honor
me with your presence.
[GENZO] Are there any
changes in the village?
[MANZO WHIMPERS]
[GENZO] What is it?
[MANZO] I'm sorry!
Tell me what happened.
[MANZO]
S-Samurai came to the village.
Samurai? How many of them?
[MANZO]
S-S-Seven, sir.
So it's those samurai...
They travel fast.
You've done well.
[MANZO]
Thank you, sir.
Great Samurai...
Don't worry, Shino.
I won't hurt your father.
Can you defeat him?
I must.
[KATSUSHIRO GASPS]
[KATSUSHIRO YELLS]
[MANZO YELLS]
I can't let you
leave here alive.
Heh... And how will
you stop me, little boy?
You've betrayed me.
No, Great One!
That samurai just
followed me on his own,
I swear to you! I didn't
know anything about it!
[MANZO YELLS]
A pitiful excuse.
Father!
Katsushiro!
[KATSUSHIRO YELLS]
You're like a child
swinging a stick...
And children cannot kill...
They can only play pretend.
Katsushiro, are you all right?
Find another job, kid.
Get a hold of yourself!
No you don't!
[KATSUSHIRO YELLS]
Impossible!
[SHINO] Dad!
Oh, Katsushiro.
♪ closing song ♪
[OKARA SNICKERS]
[OKARA] Thanks for
your letters, Komachi.
After all the time you spent
bragging about
the "Great Samurai,"
I couldn't wait to see
what the fuss was about.
I asked other villagers
what they thought, too,
but they were scared,
and wanted us to hide.
At least, the men were scared.
The girls were excited and
that made things even worse.
You know Shino--
she's really pretty, right?
Well her ugly old dad chopped
all her hair off like a boy's,
'cause he's afraid of these
warriors running off with her.
So yeah, all this samurai talk's
made everyone a little crazy.
But now that they're here--
what a let down.
They're all old, and their faces
are rough and full of scars.
And I haven't seen them swing
their swords or anything.
They just sit around
and talk plans. Boring!
The only cute one is
that young Katsushiro.
So the older girls
are fighting over him.
I doubt they stand a chance,
but it's fun to watch 'em try...
Anyway, these samurai
are eating our rice,
so they better be
as good as you wrote.
But I guess
we'll find out soon...
[OKARA SNICKERS]