[FARMERS]
♪ Ending season, bending ears, ♪
♪ It's time to harvest rice! ♪
♪ Sharpened reapers,
severed stalks... ♪
Finally harvest time.
Yes...
And as it should be.
[UKYO] So, Kanna Village fought
off those dreadful machines...?
Nicely done Kirara darling.
[KIKUCHIYO] I don't know.
Maybe you died in vain.
That's for Gorobe-sama
to decide, don't you think?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Ahh, it's all just too much!
And what the hell's the
deal with Kambei, huh?!
Bastard up and left and
didn't even take the time
to light single piece
of incense! Coward!
He will be
back, Kikuchiyo.
[KIKUCHIYO]
How can you be sure?!
He'll be back.
He is a samurai,
after all.
♪ opening song ♪
[GUARDIAN] We cannot
transport you to the Capital.
[KAMBEI] Why not?
[GUARDIAN] It is in the best
interest of the Shikimoribito
to remain neutral.
We must keep our
involvement to a minimum.
The Capital and the Nobuseri
are our trading partners.
If we appear to choose sides,
both we and the energy
cells we produce
will become
pawns in a new war...
Therefore, we must ask you to
find another way to the Capital.
[HONOKA] The Guardians are
far too pragmatic to ever risk
alienating a trading partner
without some clear reward.
I see... What if I had
a bargaining chip--
something to make
it worth their time?
They're always
willing to listen...
But it's too much to ask.
You doing all this...
Just for my sister.
[KAMBEI]
I stand by my promise to you.
I will find your sister.
All I ask is that you visit
Gorobe's grave someday.
Lady Honoka, may
I ask a favor of you?
Of course.
Tell the Guardians...
the man who killed the Imperial
Envoy was Shimada Kambei.
They'll know what
you're talking about.
The bargaining chip will be me.
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[KOUGAKYO GUARD
BREATHES HEAVILY]
[MOHAWK] Heh...
May I speak?
[UKYO GRUNTS]
Master Ukyo, you told the girls
to "show their hospitality"
to these samurai
while they're here...
And of course they
want to obey you,
but they're scared
of these men.
Can't say I blame them.
They are rather rough.
Very impressive.
[UKYO CLAPS]
I was right!
Your training in Machiba City
has made you far
deadlier than our boys.
So... who wants to go next?
[KOUGAKYO GUARDS GROAN]
We don't have all day!
Master...
[UKYO] What?
We've gathered the Samurai--
they're ready to hear you.
Ah, good. At least someone
still follows my orders quickly.
[SAMURAI MURMUR JOYFULLY]
Welcome, welcome, and
thank you all for coming.
Isn't this nice? Everyone looks
so healthy and refreshed!
This R and R has
done wonders for you!
Still, you are samurai.
And my tyrannical
father had no right
to lock you up and steal away
your last shreds of pride.
For his transgressions,
I humbly apologize.
And I beg your forgiveness.
My lord, what do you need
us to forgive you for?
Yeah that's right, you've never
done anything wrong by us.
[UKYO] But now that I'm
in charge, I am the city--
I am Kougakyo...
And all of her past
mistakes are now mine to bear.
You're being too hard
on yourself, My Lord.
Though your sense
of responsibility
means a great deal to us.
As you know,
this age of Merchants
has not been kind
to the Warrior class.
However you've shown
us nothing but kindness.
Whatever you ask of the
Samurai gathered here,
we'll gladly do it.
Your words humble me, but I
realize you are men of action.
I have a plan to prove my
dedication to your class.
How may we be of
service, milord?
[UKYO] I want you to
divide into groups,
and head to the
surrounding villages.
What for?
Do any of you remember several
peasants who came to the city
looking to hire Samurai?
They had nothing
to offer as payment
but a few measly
grains of rice.
Perhaps they approached
somebody here?
[SAMURAI 4] Yeah, I know
the ones you're talking about.
I was the first they asked!
I met 'em too!
Me too!
My, they met so many of you...
They did find
some who said yes.
They enlisted seven
Samurai to be exact...
And those extraordinary
seven somehow managed
to drive back the Nobuseri!
Mind-blowing, isn't it?
Now I've been asking around
and it seems these Nobuseri
are actually being
dispatched by the Capital.
It's just awful, to think that
the Capital itself is in effect
stealing from the very people
it should be protecting!
And it's not just the peasants!
The Capital also imposes
unfair trade restrictions
on the merchants, keeping
them from rising higher.
With all due respect,
Lord, aren't you a merchant?
Yes, and proudly so.
We merchants first
came to power because
we wanted to help rebuild
a world torn apart by wars...
But the Capital
has grown corrupt,
and as long as they remain
at the center of this world...
how can any of
us find prosperity?
When they're using Bandits--
common thugs--to do
their evil bidding!
Our eyes have been opened
to what is possible
by our brothers in Kanna.
We must learn from them...
For us now to ignore the
plight of other villages
would be to neglect our
moral responsibility.
All who have suffered at
the hands of the Capital
must unite as one!
And to do so, we must follow
the example set by the
samurai in Kanna Village.
So you're asking us
to defend the peasantry?
Certainly there's no purpose
more noble for a Samurai's sword
than to protect the helpless.
Our honorable new lord has
charged us with a new mission
and expects great
things from us...
Now, who's ready
to go back to work?
A new war!
Let's do it...! I'm in!
Sign me up!
Great...! In that case let
me return your weapons.
Your villages will be
assigned to you shortly.
[GUARDIAN]
We'll be outside shortly.
May I ask why you
killed the Envoy?
[KAMBEI]
What's the saying...?
Ask no questions, hear no lies.
[GUARDIAN] I'm merely curious
as to what you could've gained
from such a reckless act
as attacking the Capital.
[KAMBEI]
Nothing at all.
[GUARDIAN]
How utterly pointless.
This is the Capital.
Perhaps it brings back
memories for you...?
What was once the flagship
of the old Imperial fleet,
is now the center of trade
and government for
the new Merchant empire.
It's time to go.
Sanae...
Okata, sorry!
Okata?
The sun is strong today
and your skin is so fair.
Perhaps it would please
you to go indoors now?
Oh... yes.
[MIZUKI] Finally...
we can breathe!
All this polite-speak gets
my tongue all twisted up!
I feel the same way--
and having to call Sanae
"Okata" all the time.
But those formalities are
the way His Excellency likes it.
You needn't get so
worked up over it--
the Amanushi is far more lenient
than any of you seem to realize.
He's really got you brainwashed
there hasn't he, Sanae?
Quite the opposite.
I've come to learn I simply
misjudged him at first.
How can you defend that brute?!
You've been fooled by
his cold exterior Mizuki.
He's actually a very
kind and gentle man.
He's a kidnapper, is what he is!
Keep it down Mizuki!
Yeah, if they ever hear
you talking like this
there's no telling
what they'd do to us!
[GUARD 1]
Pardon us, please.
Okata, Lord Amanushi
requests your presence.
I'm sorry, My Lady's body
is in a highly fragile state
at the moment and
she must abstain--
I mean refrain from
any strenuous activity.
Thank you Mizuki...
But I will go see him.
[GUARD 2]
Presenting the Divine Emperor!
His Excellency, Lord Amanushi!
[VENTILATOR SOUND]
[GUARDIAN] Divine Emperor,
we come before you
with information about the Envoy
who was murdered in Kougakyo.
This Samurai has
confessed to the crime.
And so, in accordance
with the Capital's decree
and as an act of good faith on
the part of the Shikimoribito,
we're turning him over to you.
We trust you will punish
him as you see fit...
and we hope you will
remember our fealty.
[EMPEROR] I thank you for
your efforts, Guardian.
[GUARDIAN] Yes, lord.
And we thank you for your grace.
[EMPEROR] Ayamaro...
This samurai is accused
of murder in your home.
What do you know of him?
[MARO] Forgive me, your grace.
But I do not recognize this man.
[GUARD 2]
Presenting the Okata!
[EMPEROR]
Ah, Sanae. Come forward.
You asked to see me, My Lord?
[EMPEROR]
Was my summons inconvenient?
I was just outside enjoying
the beautiful day we're having.
[EMPEROR] Sanae...
I have called you here
because I wish for your
insight on this matter.
The Samurai before us claims to
have murdered an Imperial Envoy.
I see.
[EMPEROR] Turn your face
toward me, Samurai.
Look well...
This is not some corpse you
see, but a living being...
Thanks to the endless
wars of your kind,
this is what I have become.
You may address me directly.
What is your name?
I am Shimada Kambei.
[EMPEROR]
Shimada Kambei?
Ha, ha, ha, ha...
You are a fool...
I do not believe
you are capable
of killing a
helpless messenger.
Impostor.
[GASPING]
[GUARDIAN]
Is this true, Samurai?
I've said I killed him--
what more do you want?
[EMPEROR]
I want my time not to be wasted.
What is the point
of this charade?
Why don't you guess?!
Bite your tongue, Samurai filth!
[EMPEROR] Silence! I did not
give you permission to speak!
I beg your pardon.
[EMPEROR]
Kambei Shimada...
Can you tell us the
true killer's identity?
Or is this some
ill-conceived joke?
You do not answer...?
Perhaps a jail cell
will loosen your tongue...
Take him away!
[GUARD 2]
Shikimoribito, you are excused.
[GUARDS YELL]
[IMPERIALS YELL]
[MARO]
Don't just stand there!
Shoot him! Shoot the criminal!
Go ahead and fire.
You'll kill your
beloved Emperor.
Don't listen, he's bluffing!
Do you want to risk it?
Think very hard about where
the bullets you fire at me
will come to rest.
This is blasphemy!
Let's be reasonable here!
I'll spare his life
on one condition...
Let the women go.
Are you the Sanae from
Kanna Village? Wife of Rikichi?
And the rest of the women...?
[MIZUKI]
They're in their chambers.
Apologies, Amanushi-dono.
You will act as our shield.
[EMPEROR] Coward.
[SANAE]
I will not leave with you.
My Amanushi needs me,
and I cannot leave his side.
[GASPING]
[SANAE]
Please, I beg you. Have mercy.
[MIZUKI]
Sanae, what are you saying?
I love him. I adore my
Emperor with all my heart.
[EMPEROR]
Ha, ha, ha...
Perhaps now would be
the time to mention
this woman is
carrying my child.
Your move, Samurai.
[EMPEROR]
Ha, ha, ha...
Well now, isn't this amusing?
[SETSU]
Out of the question!
You are a peasant,
not a warrior!
[KIRARA] I understand
that grandmother, but I...
[SETSU] No.
I do not think you do!
[KIRARA] Then why shouldn't I
be allowed to go with them?
Because those men are going
off into battle, my dear...
What purpose would a
Water Priestess serve
in the midst of war?
I have a responsibility
as the one who brought
the samurai here.
And I intend to see this
war through to its finish.
You speak with the
maturity of an adult...
However, I fear you do not yet
understand your own feelings.
[KIRARA SIGHS]
I think the real problem is
I understand my
feelings too well.
We've been working
closely for some time, but...
...now I find my gaze
lingering on him...
I've done my best to
deny these feelings,
but instead, all
I feel is shame.
[SETSU]
And the Samurai?
[KIRARA]
He hasn't noticed.
[OKARA]
Do you believe that?
[KOMACHI]
What a shocker!
[SETSU] Can you
conceal these feelings?
[KIRARA]
I am a Water Priestess.
I will do whatever is
best for our people.
It will be difficult.
[SETSU SIGHS]
But you're stronger than I was.
[KIKUCHIYO] Hey, what're
you goats doin' up here?
Now is that any way to
speak to fellow samurai?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh, sorry--goat-dono!
Look, I'm pissed at you guys!
How come you didn't tell us
you were planning
a rescue mission, too?!
We're part of this team!
Sorry, big guy. We weren't
trying to exclude you.
Last time we were on the road,
Katsushiro got injured
and you let the
Nobuseri kidnap you--
not the best of records.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Bah! Excuses, excuses...!
Just 'cause you're older than
us, doesn't mean we're children!
C'mon, Katsu.
Help me out here.
Hello?
My place is with Sensei,
fighting at his side!
Because you think rebuilding
a village is somehow
beneath you as a Samurai?
No, that's not what
I meant at all...
Have you taken a
moment to think about
why Kambei-sama might have
left you behind this time?
Let's just leave it
at that for now...
Here, take some
rice for your trip.
Kanna grows the best
in the world, you know.
Thank you, Heihachi.
[KIKUCHIYO]
All right, Katsu, let's move.
That sword's not gonna
do you much good, is it?
[KIKUCHIYO] I'll get
Masamune to fix it up for me.
Masamune seems
pretty well-traveled.
I'd be willing to
bet he can tell us
where we can find the Capital.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Huh? Rikichi?
[RIKICHI] Please...
I want to go with you.
[KATSUSHIRO] I'm afraid you're
in no condition to go to war.
But I swear to you,
we will bring your wife back.
[KIRARA]
Please, wait!
[KOMACHI] Kiku!
[KIKUCHIYO]
What is it, sprout?
[KIRARA AND KOMACHI
BREATHE HEAVILY]
Please you've got
to take us with you!
Yeah, you gotta!
[KIKUCHIYO] You know
we're not going off to play.
We understand
the risk involved
and we're prepared
for whatever comes.
Please, we can help!
[KIKUCHIYO] Help us how?
This is war we're talkin' about.
But if you go without me, I'll
be worried sick about you...
An' you don't want that!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Heh. Of course not.
[KOMACHI LAUGHS]
I can't expose you
to any more danger.
[KIKUCHIYO] But you know...
Kirara is pretty good
at finding things with
that crystal of hers.
[KATSUSHIRO]
Don't leave my side.
I won't.
And don't you
leave mine, sidekick!
[KIKUCHIYO]
I couldn't if I tried. Heh...
[ELDER]
A thing such as this
would have never been
allowed in older times.
Perhaps our Kirara
is simply not meant
to be a Water
Priestess any longer.
Only she and the
waters can decide that.
[MIZUKI] Hello.
I've brought dinner for you...
...and for the prisoner as well.
Let me guess, Great Samurai.
You're wondering what
happened to Sanae...
How she could show such
affection for the man
who plucked her
from her home--
but it's more
complicated than that.
Did the Emperor speak the truth
about Sanae? Is she with child?
[MIZUKI] Yes...
I see.
[MIZUKI]
But it's not what you think.
She only did it for our sake.
She told us that as long as
the Emperor favored her,
he would leave the
other girls alone...
It was just for show,
but now I think she's starting
to believe her own act.
Please, you have
to do something...
In case you hadn't noticed
I'm about to be executed.
I'd like nothing more
than to help her,
but I'm in no
position to do so.
[MIZUKI] Liar.
Yeah... You've got
something planned.
That's why you went through
so much trouble to get caught--
Because you have a plan
to rescue all of us...
The good news is,
I can help you.
How many women
are there, in total?
About ten including me.
By any chance, do you
know if one of them
has an older sister
named Honoka?
Yeah, I do.
You don't say.
My name is Mizuki.
Pleasure to meet you,
Kambei Shimada.
[KAMBEI] Hmm...
[UKYO]
Oh? It says here
the the Envoy's assassin
has been arrested.
That's nice.
I wonder what he's like.
[TESSAI]
What do you wish to do?
He's a terrorist who incited
panic throughout my city.
I want to look this
man in the eyes...
While they're still attached
to his body, that is...
Perhaps the time
has finally come
for me to be reunited
with my father.
♪ closing song ♪
[KOMACHI]
Here, water, water.
Come out, come out
wherever you are.
Tell Komachi
where you're hiding.
Dear Okara...
I've been practicing
with the Dowsing Crystal,
but it's a lot harder
than it looks.
I figure I should
learn how to use it,
just in case sis decides
she doesn't want to
be Priestess anymore
now that she's got a crush
on a certain Samurai.
I thought it was Katsu,
but now I'm not so sure...
When me and Kirara told them
we wanted to go with them,
those dumb boys
said we couldn't!
Kiku's mad at Kambei,
and Katsu's all
confused about stuff.
What would they do without me
keeping 'em out of trouble?
And speaking of trouble,
I, the brave new
Mikumari, have a vision:
That creepy weirdo, Ukyo,
is planning something evil!
Y'know, we haven't heard
from Kambei in a while,
but he can take
care of himself...
Wow! I tell ya, Okara,
all this dowsing power is
making me kinda dizzy...
I better go sit down
for a while... Bye bye!