You gotta be kidding. Get down!
[GOROBEI] I see it!
[YOHEI]
Serves you right, Bandit!
You'll have to
forgive me, Rikichi...
Looks like I can't take you
to the Capital, after all.
Oh, Great Samurai...
Your life... I have stolen it.
You... gotta be kidding me.
♪ opening song ♪
[BIRD CALLS]
[FARMERS]
♪ Ending season, bending ears, ♪
♪ it's time to
harvest ri-i-ice! ♪
♪ Sharpened reapers,
severed stalks, ♪
♪ for better meals
toni-i-ight! ♪
♪ Flung in bundles,
hung in rows, ♪
♪ then ripened by the su-u-un! ♪
♪ On our knees like
honored prayers, ♪
♪ don't slow until
it's do-o-one! ♪
♪ Ending season, bending ears, ♪
♪ it's time to... ♪
Finally harvest time?
Yes... And as it should be.
[CHILDREN LAUGH]
[KIKUCHIYO] Hey! What are
you runts laughing at?!
You're just not cut out
for harvesting work, Kiku.
[KIKUCHIYO] Excuse me?
I may look like this now,
but in my farming days,
they called me the "Swift God
of the Rice Field Workers!"
Really?
Long name...
don't you think?
[KIKUCHIYO] It sounded better
when they sang it, okay!
It's not my fault!
These sickles are too small!
It's like I'm cutting rice
with a toothpick!
They're not too small--
you're just too big.
Or too clumsy.
[CHILDREN LAUGH]
[SHINO] Great Samurai.
We'll take it from here, okay?
[KIKUCHIYO] Why?!
We know you were a farmer once,
and that you mean well,
but that body of yours
is only meant for war now--
You're simply not built
for harvesting rice anymore.
Please, Great Samurai,
you've shown your
skills fighting Bandits.
Now let us do
what we're good at.
We've lost so much
harvesting time already
because of the battles.
We just want things
to go smoothly now.
[KIKUCHIYO] Fine.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Hey there, Goro.
You enjoying the sun today?
Heh, heh...
Damn these farmers.
Apparently, I'm useless now.
Just a heap of metal in the way.
I'm restless...
I'm sure you understand,
bein' stuck just lying there...
They're acting
like farmers again.
Worrying about
weather and rice.
Like they've forgotten
all about us, already.
I don't know.
Maybe you died in vain.
That's for Gorobei-sama
to decide, don't you think?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Ahh, it's all just too much!
And what the hell's the
deal with Kambei, huh?!
Bastard up and left and didn't
even take the time to light
a single piece of
incense! Coward!
He and the farmers!
They're all just
a bunch of cowards!
He will be back,
Kikuchiyo.
[KIKUCHIYO]
How can you be sure?!
He'll be back.
He is a samurai,
after all.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Hey. What is a samurai, anyway?
[HEIHACHI]
Look in a mirror...
You'll see one staring back.
[YOHEI] And heave!
[FARMERS] Heave!
[GOSAKU] And pull!
[FARMERS]
Heave ho! Heave ho!
[FARMERS MURMUR]
[ELDER] This good
weather helps them work.
[SHICHIROJI]
So does the organization.
You mean these work teams?
That's right. To get ready
for the Nobuseri in time,
we split up all the villagers
into specialized divisions.
The teams were selected based
on each farmer's strengths.
They're working today
in the same teams
they fought yesterday.
And the bonds they
forged during training
are helping them
rebuild quickly.
Combined with Heihachi's
engineering genius,
they probably doubled
their efficiency.
[HEIHACHI]
Pull! Come on! Pull!
[KYUZO] Next.
Draw.
Fire at will.
I wonder if Kambei planned
this from the start...
Keeping you here
to help rebuild.
Sure...
We were hired to save
Kanna from the Bandits...
...and the Bandits
destroyed your homes.
Until you can grow
rice safely again...
...our job's not done.
[DOOR OPENS]
Lady Kirara, I'm sorry.
[KIRARA] You know you don't
have to call me that anymore.
Is that a book about war?
[KATSUSHIRO] Yes...
Since the fighting
ended, I've felt uneasy.
Like I still crave
the battlefield.
[SOUNDS OF BATTLE]
[KIRARA] In the old age,
war was constant.
As one battle ended,
another began,
and always another
after that...
The battles begat each other,
with power moves
and vows for revenge
calling for each new
season of bloodshed.
War defined the culture,
passing from one
generation to the next.
Every aspect of life revolved
around the preparation, support,
and fighting of war.
For the sake of
victory and survival,
weakness could not be afforded.
To be stronger, the samurai
turned themselves into machines.
The size of their metal bodies
became a symbol of rank.
The bigger they were, the more
authority they possessed.
To be samurai was
no longer an option.
It was the only way to exist.
And the samurai got their wish,
becoming stronger than
any man had dreamed.
But the war would not end.
It brought no good
to the people.
It scorched fields,
crushed houses,
and covered everyone's
faces with ash.
The goals of the war
had been forgotten,
and yet they had to go on,
because without war,
they would have no purpose.
And as long as the
fighting continued,
the samurai would
remain on top.
Every one wanted to be samurai.
Even peasants found their
way into the metal brigades.
But in the end, it was the
samurai's own lust for strength
that enabled their defeat.
The demand for new technologies
created weapons that
could destroy them.
And the weapons were
given to the merchants.
In return, the merchants
used the technology
to rebuild people's
homes, restore cities,
and bring smiles to
faces blackened with ash.
The Great War was finally over.
The samurai were scattered.
And a new era began.
And now here I am,
a man without purpose...
a samurai in an
age of merchants...
Why did you show
that book to me?
[KIRARA]
I've read it a hundred times.
I know the tragedy
of the samurai.
The impossible
feelings it creates.
Yet I did it to you anyway.
I'm so ashamed.
You can't think that way.
I chose to walk the path of
the Samurai of my own free will.
It's only natural that
the path ahead of me
would be rocky sometimes.
You must take care
of your swords.
I have made the blade
of your daito sharper.
A Samurai is
one who kills.
[KAMBEI] Why did you
come to this village?
To save it, of course.
[KAMBEI]
Then you have done your job.
If you wish to continue
on the Samurai path
you must be prepared to carry
the weight of those you kill.
We are nothing but scarecrows,
driving away the Bandits
who swarm over the crop.
Take your sword
back now, Katsushiro.
Then get yourself some rice...
You'll need your
strength to kill again.
I want to be able to feel proud
that I chose to
become a samurai.
[KAMBEI GASPS]
[KAMBEI] Grab on.
Didn't I tell you
to search elsewhere?
[KIRARA] I knew it.
That why I jumped, because
I knew you would save me.
I know that you're the one.
Your determination and loyalty
have won me over to your cause.
I will help you.
I shall not let your
treasured rice go to waste.
I hardly think I'm worth
a hundred warriors,
but I appreciate the flattery.
Flattery may well be the only
reward you can expect from this.
The only payment we will
receive is the rice we eat.
Hmm...
I accept.
...but at the end of it all
I crawled out of a ship,
covered in soot and
still breathing.
I call it triumph...
If you die, you lose,
if you survive, you win.
It's simple as that.
You really think so?
That's my belief,
for whatever that's worth.
[HEIHACHI]
Much obliged.
[GOROBEI]
Oh by the way,
I don't suppose
you'd be interested
in killing about
forty Nobuseri.
[SHAMISEN MUSIC]
♪ I once cut down bandits
from all three thousand lands. ♪
♪ Cut them down
and got cut down, ♪
♪ but still,
but still I stand. ♪
I'll be at your side.
There's no reward or fame--
only a bloody war. Are you sure?
Yes.
This time we may
meet our deaths.
Sensei, please...
You must continue on
to the village now...
Just go on without me.
I'll only be a burden to you.
Stop acting so
brave, Katsushiro.
I'm not trying to act brave.
I'm serious.
You're frustrated as
anyone would be...
...and that is enough.
These two are grateful
for your sacrifice.
And they should be.
You are their fifth samurai.
Why... Kyuzo...?
Why did you...
Because... I wanted to live.
Hopeless fool.
May I ask you to
come with us?
When do we leave?
Immediately.
[KIKUCHIYO]
I can't blame Manzo,
conniving and
pathetic as he is!
He just played the odds and
the Bandits won! That's all!
Farmers are corrupt!
But Bandits are corrupt!
And Samurai are corrupt!
Why would anyone risk
their lives for anyone?
But I'll fight for them.
I'll kill all
the Bandits! Damn it.
[KIKUCHIYO SOBS]
Damn it...
At last the seven are complete.
This uneasiness I feel...
I think I'm finally
beginning to understand
what Kyuzo-dono meant, when
he said that he wanted to live.
Katsushiro.
[UKYO] So, Kanna Village fought
off those dreadful machines?
Nicely done Kirara darling.
[TESSAI]
With all respect, young master,
the samurai are the ones
responsible for this,
not those peasants.
[UKYO] Ah yes,
but it was Kirara who
assembled those Samurai.
She obviously has a talent
for choosing good men.
[TESSAI]
I've done some more digging.
According to our informants,
the samurai's leader
is named Kambei.
[UKYO]
Who cares what his name is?
The point of the matter is
that a simple farming village
hired samurai and
defeated the bandits.
[TESSAI] Yes.
One more thing...
Tell the other
villages, will you?
Make clear to all farmers.
They have nothing left to fear.
From the bandits... or me.
But... won't that
disrupt the order?
[UKYO]
Just do it, Tessai.
I'm far too busy to be
explaining things to you.
[TESSAI]
As you wish.
[MESSENGER]
Young master...
An urgent message
from the capital.
Oh, then please, do tell.
[MESSENGER] For his inability
to find the envoy's assassin,
Ayamaro has been
stripped of his title.
He will remain in the capital
until the Emperor
decides his fate.
His fate?
Poor Father,
whatever shall we do?
[MESSENGER]
The Emperor would like you
to continue your father's
duties as Magistrate,
Well, that makes sense...
I can't say I want the job,
but who else is there?
[TESSAI SIGHS]
Your tanto--let me have it.
[TESSAI] Huh?
You heard me.
Give me your short blade!
[TESSAI] Yes, young
master, of course.
[CLANGING]
[FACTORY WORKERS MURMUR]
[UKYO]
Hello. Workers!
This is your magistrate!
I know this is a wretched place,
and I'm sorry to keep you here!
But I promise very soon
you will all be free!
Um, Kiku? You do know you
caught something, right?
[KIKUCHIYO] What...?
Look in a mirror...
You'll see one staring back.
Hey sidekick, what's wrong?
I've never seen you this quiet.
[KIKUCHIYO]
What do you think a samurai is?
Somebody like you, you goof.
[KIKUCHIYO] Huh...?
[KOMACHI] Kiku's feeling
kinda lonely now.
[OKARA] How come?
[KOMACHI]
'Cause Kambei isn't here.
[OKARA]
Oh yeah. That makes sense.
[KIKUCHIYO] Shut up!
[KOMACHI] Kiku acts
like he doesn't like him,
but he's followed
Kambei from the start.
You don't recognize me?
I'm not surprised.
The name's Zaemon
Yoshichika the Peaceable.
I was only a boy when
you killed my parents.
I've devoted my life
to their vengeance--
and though I wasn't
expecting to find you today,
it's an opportunity
I won't turn down.
[KIKUCHIYO]
What are you talking about?
Wait!
You saved the girl so you
must be worth something.
Or is that what you
call a losing battle?
Oh, they suffer for you
and you still won't help?!
I'll kill you right here!
[KAMBEI] On my signal,
reel this in as hard as you can.
[KIKUCHIYO] Okay...
Don't have a clue what
you're doing, but you got it!
[GOROBEI] Come on!
Kikuchiyo!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
You better not screw this up!
Save those farmers, okay!
You were born a farmer...
Weren't you, Kikuchiyo?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Okay, I was a farmer, so what!
I figured if I acted
like a samurai,
people would think
of me better!
I want a good battle.
Right. You can count on that.
[OKARA] Kambei's fighting
a one-man war now.
He's not letting the
other samurai help.
[KOMACHI] Yeah.
Momotaro and Heihachi are
busy rebuilding stuff.
But everyone else
is just bored.
[OKARA] Everyone else has
other interests, at least.
Farming's the only
other thing Kiku knows,
but he's no good at it now.
[KOMACHI] Still, they
shouldn't just replace him.
Aah! What are you doing
you dumb fish?
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh, enough already, okay!
I'm a samurai, damn it!
Now it's time for me to
start acting like one!
[RIKICHI] At least it
would stop the shame...
I sold my wife!
I sold my wife to the Bandits!
What?
[KIKUCHIYO] Rikichi...
[RIKICHI SOBS]
[KAMBEI] Rikichi...
Tell me now, what is
your wife's name?
It's Sanai.
Then I promise
you now, Rikichi...
I will swear to you...
We will save Sanai.
But why...?
That story about your family
being killed by bandits,
was that all a lie?
No, it was all true... Except...
Except what?
My sister... My little sis--
[HONOKA SOBS]
I swear, Lady Honoka,
we will reunite
you and your sister.
[KATSUSHIRO] But why would
he just leave like this,
without asking for our help?
Especially if he's gone to
the Capital, like we think.
He won't be able to get
past their defenses alone.
[KIRARA] Kambei has
more wisdom than us all.
He wouldn't do anything
unless he had a good plan.
The Priestess is
right about that...
And Kyuzo must have
had a plan of his own,
because he's
disappeared as well.
I'm not surprised.
The whole reason he came here
was to battle sensei
after we won...
With sensei gone
there's no challenge...
...and no reason to stay.
That does
sound like Kyuzo.
The rice is safe,
but the seven kami protecting
it have been separated.
Kami?
Oh yeah...
I'd almost forgotten that.
Speaking of old traditions,
have you folks heard
the one that says that
rice contains seven kami?
Kami...?
Like deities?
That's right.
Seven deities who live inside of
good rice grains and protect it.
How can I not love the stuff?
It's a gift blessed
from the heavens!
[KIKUCHIYO]
Hey! Rikichi!
I'm getting out of here!
Can't let that mule
Kambei hog all the glory.
What are you talking about?
Wait a minute, you're
going off to help rescue Sanai?
But Sensei left us
here for a reason.
We need to help
protect the village.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Decision time, kid!
Samurai or sheep--which are you?
Then you're a... samurai?
I'm samurai.
[KIKUCHIYO] That's right!
And it's time to step up!
Kambei may treat
us like children,
but you know in your heart
what a true samurai would do.
We have an opportunity--
no, an obligation to
find Rikichi's wife.
We can do it!
And we can show up that crusty
old jerk while we're at it.
Come on, I know you're
itching for a good fight.
[WIND BLOWS HEAVILY]
Great Samurai, you're back!
But what about
the rest of them?
Katsushiro, and Rikichi...
and Gorobei--are they safe?
[KAMBEI]
Gorobei is dead.
I see... Then what
about Kanna Village?
[KAMBEI]
The Nobuseri were defeated.
I have come to
fulfill my promise.
Rikichi's wife and your sister
are likely in the Capital.
That's where your
masters will take me.
The Capital?
[HONOKA GASPS]
♪ closing song ♪
[OKARA SNICKERS]
[OKARA] Well, the Bandits
are gone and we're still alive.
And I thought we'd all
end up in the ground.
But with the fighting done,
and Kambei off on his own
for whatever reason,
and Momotaro and
Heihachi fixing the village,
that left the other two
pretty much useless.
And just watching them
mope around, I knew it
wouldn't be long before they
wanted to do something crazy.
I guess when you're
used to fighting those
big crimson spiders--which
are super scary by the way--
and having swords at
your throat all the time,
taking a nice day to relax
just isn't quite the same.
Kiku was funny trying
to harvest, though.
I love saying things
to make him angry,
'cause he starts screaming
and flailing his arms,
and he's like a big monkey,
It's hilarious...
Of course, he can make
you nervous, too,
when he's in your face, and it
does get him what he wants,
'cause now Katsu's going on
some big adventure with him.
I should learn how
to yell like that...
Komachi! Give me your rice!
Give me your rice, you mule!
[OKARA SNICKERS]