[PLUTIA]
Hello, everyone.
My name is Plutia.
It's nice to meet you.
I'd like to take a
moment to propose a toast
to Plu-Plu, Planeptune's
lovely new CPU!
[NEPTUNE]
Whoa, whoa, hold up!
Compa, you're
making it sound like
Plutie here stole my whole
country out from under me!
No, not like that at all--
It's just that she's
a Planeptune CPU, too.
Yeah, but not
this Planeptune!
She's the CPU of a
completely different one!
And don't you forget it!
I think what
she's trying to say
is Plutia comes
from another dimension--
One with its very
own Planeptune.
I must admit, it's
a bit difficult to know
how to react to a
casual declaration
of different dimensions.
I take it you
can transform, too?
Yes, I can.
But, uh,
everybody tells me that I
shouldn't go around doing it.
Not unless I have to, that is.
Yeah? Why's that?
[PLUTIA]
Hm...
...I wonder...
Hey! Cut it out, P-ko!
That's mine!
But I want meat
in my tummy!
Have this instead. Here you go!
[screams]
Get it away from me!
I hate eggplants!
They're super grody!
Come on, I cooked
today, give them a chance.
And they're pretty tasty,
if I do say so myself.
No way, no how,
no thank you!
Just the smell alone saps all
the strength out of my body!
[NEPTUNE]
I don't wanna.
[IF]
But they're so good!
You're missing out on a big
part of life by excluding them.
[NEPTUNE] Yeah,
we'll I'd rather die!
[HISTOIRE] Well, you just might
if you don't eat your veggies!
[NEPTUNE]
Gross!
Even Histy's shoving
eggplant into her mouth!
[HISTOIRE] Neptune, you're
setting a bad example
for your citizens
by being a picky eater.
Ah-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba!
[IF] Miss Histoire!
Are you all right?
--[HISTOIRE] I-I don't know!
--[NEPTUNE] It's the curse!
--I just--Ah-ba-ba-ba-ba!
--The dreaded curse
of the eggplant!
[IF] It is not!
There's no such thing!
[PEASHY]
Mmm!
Sorry about that.
I'd never received a call
from another dimension before,
you see, so I had to
sort of scramble through
the instruction manual
to figure out how to answer.
No, I apologize for
calling you out of the blue.
I wanted to thank you for
looking after Plutia for me.
You're a bit small,
aren't you?
Hey!
Don't go writing me off
just because I'm small!
I was the one who sent
Plutia to your dimension
in the first place,
I'll have you know.
[HISTOIRE]
Is that so?
Well, you certainly
surprised me!
I never dreamed there
were different dimensions,
or that travelling
between them would be so easy,
for that matter!
It's not easy at all!
Actually, it's quite difficult.
[HISTOIRE]
My apologies, then!
[MINI HISTY] Well, it is
covered in that same manual,
if you read all the fine print.
It took three days!
[HISTOIRE]
I see.
I'll try to track that down.
[COMPA]
Who wants dessert?
Me! Me!
P-ko!
I wanna eat this one!
But that one is mine!
It says "Nep" on the
package and everything!
Come on, Peashy.
They all taste the same. Really!
But I want Nep's
pudding! Blaaah!
What's your problem?
Nep's pudding means pudding
for Nep stomachs exclusively!
It's mine now!
You little brat!
Wanna fight for it?
That's not very
mature of you.
No need to get
worked up about it.
Don't fight, Neppy.
[HISTOIRE] So why exactly
did you send Plutia
to this dimension?
[MINI HISTY]
Well, you see,
We detected a large
energy transfer
from our dimension to yours,
and it's caused some concern.
Someone or something seems
to have traveled there,
but we're not sure what.
[HISTOIRE]
Ah.
[MINI HISTY] Either way,
whatever it is,
its energy is so massive that if
we don't do something about it,
and soon, we may not
be able to maintain
our world's
structural integrity.
[HISTOIRE]
Ah.
[MINI HISTY] So the plan
is to have Plutia find out
what the great presence is,
where it is, subdue it,
and bring it back here.
[HISTOIRE]
Good thinking.
So how exactly does one go about
finding this "great presence"?
[NEPTUNE laughing]
[PEASHY]
Pea Punch!
[boxing bell]
[MINI HISTY]
Not sure.
We searched for three days,
but we still can't find it.
Really? Then...?
All we can do
is try to sense
any changes in your world
and investigate them
as soon as possible.
I believe that when a
change of that nature occurs,
if you look around,
you'll find the presence
somewhere nearby.
[HISTOIRE]
I understand.
I'll relay that
information to everyone here.
[HISTOIRE]
So like she said,
if you notice anything
strange happening,
--please report it
--[NEPTUNE] I see you, AIDA!
as soon as possible.
--[NEPTUNE] I'm gonna crush you!
--[PLUTIA] Poke and pull,
Poke and pull.
[PEASHY]
I'm gonna play with this!
[NEPTUNE]
Oh, no you don't!
[NEPGEAR] Give it back!
Come on, please?
[HISTOIRE]
Ahem! Are you listening?
Oh! I'm sorry!
Yes, I'm listening!
You were saying--
Wait! Come back!
[NEPTUNE] "If anything
strange happens", right?
Nothing strange
going on right now.
But you haven't even
stepped outside to check.
I'll go on patrol.
If I see anything,
I'll let you know, okay?
That's much appreciated.
Sorry you're always
covering for them.
No problem.
Compa, don't you need
to get to work now?
Wanna catch a ride with me?
[COMPA]
Yes!
Yay! Thanks, Iffy!
[PLUTIA]
All done!
Plutie!
Whoa, is that who I think it is?
Wow, it's Neptune!
That's right! It sure is.
Oh, how cute!
Yeah, totally!
It's an itty-bitty
fluffy version
of everything that
makes me so moe!
Glad you approve.
If there's one thing I love,
it's making stuffed dolls
of all my friends!
Me next! Will you
make one of me?
Of course!
I'll make a Peashy doll ASAP.
And after that, I'll
make one of Neppy Jr.
Yay!
Cool, huh?
Okay, then.
I'll get right to it!
Keep your eyes peeled, guys!
We're about to witness
some mad crafting skills!
Yeah!
And look! She's gonna do it
without even using a pattern!
What the--
She's asleep!
That's kind of a
mad skill in itself.
[yawning]
[IF] There's a lot of
construction today
for some reason.
Sorry we're running late.
That's okay, Iffy.
I'm with you, so I'm having
fun no matter what's going on.
Oh, yeah?
What's going on?
[IF] Compa, quick!
Hold your breath!
You walked right
into my little trap.
[IF] Don't tell me
you're the one who--
[NEPGEAR]
Neptune!
Sis, please, wake up!
No, I can't eat
another bite.
Enough clichéd dreams!
Wake up already!
Aw man, you suck.
It was just getting good.
[NEPTUNE gasps]
[NEPTUNE]
What happened?
That's not very nice.
They sent it in an
anonymous email.
And there was a
map attached, too.
We gotta go save her!
Yes, of course.
But who would do such a thing?
The time has come
for my revenge.
Whatever you've got planned,
it is not gonna work.
Once Nep and Nepgear get here,
they're gonna take
you down, got it?
Things will go
differently this time.
See, I've got a secret plan.
More specifically...
...these eggplants!
Huh?!
[ARFOIRE]
That's right!
I know your CPU's weakness!
Feel free to tremble in fear
as you gaze upon my carefully
constructed eggplant hell!
A dried up old hag
like you will never win,
no matter what you try!
We'll see when they
get here, won't we?
[giggling mischievously]
[ARFOIRE] That's right,
swallow it all down, girlie!
Otherwise, you'll be missing
out on a big part of life!
Isn't that what they say?
[IF coughing]
[IF]
You are one sick old lady!
That's enough!
[IF whimpering]
Come on, don't fight it!
They're good for you!
Eggplant skin is packed
with polyphenol, you know!
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
Stop it! Now!
[ARFOIRE]
So you're finally here.
Imagine that.
Late to your own funeral!
If you want to pick a fight,
I'll be happy to oblige.
But let Iffy go--
Whoa! Sis, are you okay?
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
Sorry, it's just...
...I smell eggplant.
Finally noticed, did you?
I bought this entire farm
to take advantage
of your weak point!
It will take you down
like an arrow to the knee!
Don't be ridiculous!
Yes, I hate eggplant.
But it's not like
they're going to kill me!
Is that so?
Come forth!
Now, my purple servants!
What are those?
[screaming]
What the--
Wait a minute, where am I?
[WARECHU] Someplace where
we can be alone together.
[WARECHU]
Chu, chu.
Mister Mouse?
That's me, in the flesh.
I, uh, wanted to
see you so badly
that I crawled back
here from hell's pits.
Wait, you did what?
And how does hell spit?
Listen, Compa.
I can't hold back
my feelings anymore.
Today is the day I tell
you what's in my heart.
Huh?
Eggplants are scary!
Save me! Help!
[PLUTIA]
Cut it out.
Neptune! Plutia! Hang on!
Out of my way!
Pull yourself
together, Nep!
They're just some
little monsters
the old lady here
"magicked" up, so get them!
It sounds like you
haven't learned your lesson.
[ARFOIRE] I'll force-feed
you every eggplant I've got!
Stop! Don't you dare!
Nepgear!
[NEPTUNE] Now there's
eggplant stink everywhere!
[ARFOIRE]
What's that?
Eggplants aren't bad
raw, now are they?
You can handle more.
Go on! Swallow!
It's good for you!
[ARFOIRE laughing]
[NEPTUNE]
Nep what?
That's enough of that.
I'm getting angry.
[gasps]
[PLUTIA]
Why?
You should be ashamed.
[PLUTIA] Why would you go
so far to bully poor Iffy?
What? I'll do what
I want with her!
She's my hostage, after all!
I get what you're saying,
but that's not very nice.
Okay, then.
Then just to make things fair,
perhaps I should do
what I want with you!
Plutie, did you--
Her change is even more
drastic than Neptune's.
Awful cocky, but who are you?
Oh, me?
I'm Iris Heart.
I know it might be
hard to remember.
So perhaps I can
help by beating it into you!
[ARFOIRE screaming]
[PLUTIA (IH)]
My, my.
It seems you're not
nearly as hardcore
as you make yourself out to be.
Oh, no!
[PLUTIA (IH)] You've been around
so much longer than we have,
old lady.
Show me what you've learned.
Fight!
[NEPGEAR (PS)]
I think she's having fun.
Well, I'm not getting in
her way, so A-okay with me!
We have some work
of our own to do.
Time to wrap this up!
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
You take care of Iffy.
I'll deal with these
eggplant creatures.
[NEPGEAR (PS)]
Right!
[WARECHU] I figured
something out about myself.
Without the one
I love beside me,
my whole life's as
hollow as Swiss cheese.
Understand?
Take me! Now!
Compa, baby!
Mister Mouse?
Sweet dreams!
[PLUTIA (IH)] Aww,
and here I thought
you'd actually be
fun to play with.
You're all bark and no bite.
[ARFOIRE]
Shut your mouth!
You just caught me
off-guard, that's all!
I thought there was
life in this old dog yet,
but all you do is cry.
Yap, yap, yap, and you
expect me to throw you a bone?
But if I can't teach
you any new tricks,
you'll never satisfy me.
Maybe I should just
finish you off.
Plutie, hold on.
That's enough.
Did you really think I
wouldn't have a Plan B prepared?
I have plenty more purple
peril in store for you.
Now!
Behold my terrifying new form!
[ARFOIRE] I have have become
one with the eggplants!
It's super effective!
In this form,
I am called Eggoire!
[ARFOIRE] Thought I'd get a
bigger reaction than that.
[NEPTUNE (PH)] At that size,
you seem less like an eggplant
and more like some
confusing purple eyesore.
[ARFOIRE]
Why, I never!
Unfortunately for you,
I'm more angry than amused.
I'll make you regret
doing that to Iffy,
and for bringing disgusting
eggplants, of all things,
into a fight.
It's time to put an end to this.
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
Nepgear, Plutie, you ready?
[NEPGEAR (PS)]
Yeah, you bet, Sis!
[PLUTIA (IH)]
Oh, I'm always ready!
[ARFOIRE screaming]
[ARFOIRE]
My plant plan is ruined!
What a poor choice.
You should've absorbed a more
balanced nutrient profile.
[WARECHU]
Okay, Compa.
Epic kiss time. Pucker up.
Chu...
Mister Mouse?
Chu?
I need to ask you.
Are you still a bad person?
I don't like and would
never kiss a bad person.
Well, what if I
wasn't a bad person?
What then?
Hey! Who are you and why
are you ruining our moment?
You revolting beast.
Why don't you go back to
crawling around the sewers
where your kind belongs, huh?
You've got some nerve, trying to
sully our cute little Compa.
Oh, great!
So what are you? A new CPU?
A CPU?
Vulgar little
disgusting rodents like you
need to call me by a
different name, got it?
Call me Madame Goddess!
[laughing maniacally]
Wow, look at that!
Mister Mouse's body
is so soft and stretchy!
He's like one of those
memory foam pillows!
[PLUTIA (IH)]
Do it! Come on, now!
I don't speak "dirty rat"!
Say my name!
Loud and clear, you vermin!
[HISTOIRE] Are you
feeling better now, IF?
Yes, I wasn't actually
injured or anything.
[HISTOIRE]
Even so,
Arfoire was quite the
fearsome enemy, was she not?
Mmm-hmm.
But there was
someone there today
who was even more
fearsome, if you ask me.
Yeah?
Who d'you mean, Neppy?
Oh, no one!
Well, at least I know
now why her friends
don't let her transform.
Come on, everyone,
the food is ready!
--Food time, food time!
--Food time, yay!
[NEPTUNE]
What the--
Eggplant stir fry?
Yep!
Why would you make eggplant
after what we just went through?
It was a special
request from Peashy.
I couldn't say no.
I guess she really
liked yesterday's batch.
Eggplant! Eggplant! Yum!
Plus, I heard you conquered
your eggplant phobia
and I wanted to
celebrate, Nep-Nep!
I wouldn't say that!
It was more of an
adrenaline-fueled
burst-of-strength
type of thing, you know?
[IF]
No eggplants!
They're scary and I hate them
and I never want
to eat them! No!
[HISTOIRE] IF!
Calm down! Please!
So now Iffy has an
eggplant phobia, too?
Actually, I can kind
of understand that.
Iffy, now we're
kindred spirits!
Eggplants are yummy!
[WARECHU] You seriously want
to be an eggplant farmer now?
Really? What about the
quest for world domination?
[ARFOIRE] I give up.
I'm feeling tired.
Besides, that last
strategy of mine
wiped out all
of my savings.
Either way, I've got
nowhere else to go.
Wait, why are
you helping me?
It's not like I have
anything better to do.
You know, it's funny.
For the first time,
I really feel like I'm living.
[WARECHU] I'm charging you by
the hour, just so you know.
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
A solitary island.
A mysterious, enormous machine.
Far too many flesh tones,
and the occasional sexy pink.
Is it a trap, or...?
Next time on
Hyperdimension Neptunia!
The Stirrings (Prelude)
of the Nightmare!
If you don't watch,
I'll delete your save data!