[NEPTUNE (PH)] Heed my words,
all those who make
Gamindustri their home.
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
This day represents the
first step into a new era,
and I am thrilled that you and
I are able to greet it together.
Welcome to the next level.
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
As I'm sure you know.
In the past years,
this fantasy star of ours
has been plagued
with constant war.
[NEPTUNE (PH)] Lastation, ruled
by the goddess Black Heart.
[NEPTUNE (PH)] Lowee, ruled
by the goddess White Heart.
[NEPTUNE (PH)] Leanbox, ruled
by the goddess Green Heart.
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
And last, but not least,
Planeptune, ruled by
yours truly. Purple Heart.
Our kingdoms have
vied for Share energy,
the source of a
nation's strength.
And on occasion even
the goddesses themselves
have come to blows in
this fruitless struggle.
But that shall be no more.
The friendship treaty
we shall sign today
will ban all taking of
Shares with military force.
From now on we shall
increase our own Shares
by improving our
beloved countries.
And fostering a healthy
development of the entire world.
We hereby vow
to overcome our past
and create a world of hope,
so that all people may
prosper as long as we live.
Whoopdie whoo!
We did it, guys!
And now you're a
bite-sized idiot again.
How charming.
[NEPTUNE] Whatever, Noire,
you know you love me!
But how did you like the speech?
It was, adequate, I suppose.
Though I'm sure
Histoire wrote it for you.
[NEPTUNE]
Boo.
Either way, I'm still
pissed you had
to attention whore
all over our moment.
[NEPTUNE] Aw, Blanc,
I won my chance
to give the speech
fair and square.
Don't be smug.
It was just rock-paper-scissors.
Well, we did all agree.
No use bickering over
it after the fact.
[NEPTUNE] For real!
'Cause we're like,
all on each other's
friends lists now, right?
[HISTOIRE thinking]
I'm sure this is the beginning
of a productive future.
It's been a month
and you're still not doing
your CPU job at all, Neptune!
Sonic Jump! Aw! Dang it!
Are you listening to me?
Hmm? Hey, even a goddess
needs a break, right?
A break from what?
All you've done is
sleep and play games!
[NEPGEAR] Neptune!
The tea is ready!
Huh?
Sweet, thanks Nepgear.
So, you wanna do some PVP?
[NEPGEAR] Mm-hmm.
Et tu, Nepgear?
Let's see you play games. Now!
No!
Hey, it says in the user
manual not to do that!
Don't try this at home,
boys and girls!
[COMPA] Iffy!
Hey, Compa!
[IF] Did you just get off work?
[COMPA] Yep!
Now I'm on my way
to see Nep-Nep!
Hey, that rhymed.
[IF] Good. I guess
I'll join you, then.
[FEMALE] ...without goddesses!
Now, we should live our lives
by regulations that--Oof!
Hmm?
Here, take a look!
At the Sharicite, not at me!
[NEPGEAR] The Sharicite?
Why, is there
something wrong with it?
The Share energy
levels in our crystal
have been declining.
As I have clearly
indicated here.
Sweet graph, but
what's the big deal?
We've still got
plenty, don't we?
[HISTOIRE] No, we don't!
Do you know where
Shares come from
or do you need another diagram?
[NEPTUNE] Uh...
[NEPGEAR] It's like
how much a country
believes in its goddess, right?
Their faith.
[HISTOIRE] Yes, exactly.
Which means the hearts
of the people are starting
to drift away from Neptune,
which is no wonder, really.
What? But I haven't
done anything
to make them hate me,
I don't think!
[NEPGEAR] Hmm, you
haven't done anything
to make them like
you either, though.
I mean, uh...
[IF] Nepgear's right,
and you know it.
Please, excuse us,
Miss Histoire.
But we overheard you talking.
[HISTOIRE] IF, you and
Compa, are always welcome.
[NEPTUNE] You're siding
with Histy too, Iffy?
But Compa still loves me, right?
Well, Nep-Nep,
she has a point.
[NEPTUNE] Hmm?
"We don't need goddesses."
[COMPA] If they understood
you a little better,
then everything would be fine.
Don't worry!
It's nothing hard
work can't fix.
Uhhh! Everyone's against me!
I'm in a major pinch!
It's this country of
yours that's in a pinch!
Eh...
[HISTOIRE] Remember, CPUs are
goddesses who are supposed
to work tirelessly for
the good of their people.
Why do you think you
have those powers of yours?
As a wise man once said...
[NEPTUNE thinking] Ugh. Man,
I hate getting lectured.
I wonder if I can
just, like, run away?
Wait! Of course!
I am gonna get me some
schooling in the goddess arts!
Huh? Okay, but
schooling from who?
[NEPTUNE] From, uh... Noire!
[EVERYONE ELSE] What?!
Time for a
Lastation vacation!
I'm not following
the situation here.
Why exactly is my
neighboring country's' CPU
napping in my Basilicom?
Ahhh... Just ignore
me and do your job.
I won't mind one little bit.
[NOIRE] Yeah, well, I do mind!
I'm sorry,
'bout this Noire.
Get up, Neptune, please!
Why?
You wanted to be a
better CPU, right?
[NOIRE] Yeah, about
all that--no thanks.
I have no intention of teaching
my enemies how to do their jobs.
[NEPTUNE]
Aww, but we're buddies now!
That's what we signed that
friendship treaty for, right?
So we could--
As long as we're
competing for Shares,
that still makes
us enemies. Get it?
Bluh! Why you always gotta be
such a meanie all the time?
See, now this is why you
don't have any friends!
I-I do too have a friend!
Whoa. For real?
What's her name, then?
Huh? Oh, you don't know her.
Hey, Noire.
I finished these
documents for you!
Oh, thanks, Uni, that's nice.
Just set them over there.
[UNI] My job, uh...
I was, pretty fast, right?
I worked really hard this time.
[NOIRE] It was average.
But that's still an
improvement for you.
[NEPTUNE] Wait.
Was Uni the mysterious "friend"
you were talking about?
'Cause little sisters
are little sisters--
they don't count as friends.
Of course not!
I have another.
Oh really?
'Cause you sure look
like a lonely loner to me!
[NOIRE] Then you need
to get your eyes checked!
[UNI] Nepgear.
I'm sorry Neptune kind
of hijacked your talk
with your sister.
[UNI] It's okay.
My conversations with her
always turn out the same anyway.
[UNI] It's like she has
this rule, where she won't
compliment me unless
I do a better job than her.
[UNI] But we both know
that's not possible.
Uni.
[UNI] I can't even transform
into my goddess form yet.
[NEPGEAR] That's nothing
to feel down about.
I mean, neither can I,
and neither can Rom or Ram.
Well, I suppose
I'll just have to transform
before the three of you
to prove my superiority.
How's that?
Good!
But you better hurry,
or I might beat you!
[NEPGEAR] A message.
From Rom, actually.
She knows I'm in Lastation,
but who told her?
I'm sorry, I couldn't resist.
And let me tell you,
she was super jealous.
[ROM] No fair.
Nepgear and Uni are so lucky,
getting to play together.
How come we gotta stay home
while they get to do cool stuff?
[BLANC] Maybe because
you're noisy and selfish?
[RAM] I wanna hang out
with Nepgear and Uni, too!
I have work to do.
You suck!
You suck! You suck!
[RAM] Come on!
Shut up! I said
I had work, didn't I?
You're a big meanie,
you know that?
Let's go, Rom.
[ROM] Ram, wait a second.
I'm sorry you had to
listen to that mess.
[VERT] Oh, nonsense.
I don't mind at all.
In fact, I envy their innocence.
The little sisters don't have a
history of fighting like we do.
Now that the gears
of war have stopped,
should we try to
be more like them?
[BLANC] Just because we're not
having a punch out anymore.
Doesn't mean we're going
to turn into good
neighbors overnight.
And more importantly.
Yes, of course.
Let me tell you the
rest of my little proposal.
[NEPTUNE] Whoopsie!
Uh-oh, uh-oh!
[NOIRE] Stop it!
Your paper-touching
privileges are revoked!
[NEPTUNE] What?
But you said, and I quote:
"a goddess' first duty is
taking care of paperwork"!
[NOIRE] Yeah, your paperwork!
Mine is sacred!
Lame. You need
an attitude check.
[NOIRE] What?
Oh no, you did not
just say that to me.
[IF] Uhmm.
Do you have requests from
the citizens to kill monsters,
or something like that?
[IF] If you teach her
to be a monster hunter,
that might help her
improve as a goddess, too.
[COMPA] Oh, good idea.
And it'll keep her away from
all those precious papers!
[NOIRE] This is a good one.
Here, take a look.
And it's right near
Planeptune as well.
[NEPTUNE] Is that your
not-so-subtle way
of saying you want me
to go home after this?
[NOIRE] I have a job to do.
Of course I want you gone.
[NEPTUNE] Okeydokey guys, let's
go do some monster hunting!
[NOIRE] Right! I mean, shut up!
Why are you acting like
the leader all of a sudden?
[NOIRE] We'll be clearing
monsters from two places.
The Nasuune Highlands and
the nearby Toruunay Cave.
Neither of them are--
[UNI] Hey, sis?
[NOIRE] What is it? Huh?
[UNI] Nobody is listening.
[COMPA] I'm too pooped to move!
[IF] I'm fresh out
of piggybacks.
[NEPTUNE] Whoa!
Look, this is the famous "sign
you can't read from behind"!
[NEPGEAR] I think most
signs are like that.
[NOIRE] Get moving!
[NEPTUNE] Yeek!
[NOIRE] You're walking too slow!
[NEPTUNE] Aw, c'mon!
You are like all business all
the time, now aren't you!
[NOIRE] Is that a problem?
[NEPTUNE] Doesn't it tire you
out having a stick up your butt?
[NOIRE] I want to make this
country as great as I can.
And the only stick here is
the one I'm using to poke you.
[NEPTUNE] Well, yeah, I wanna
make a great country too,
of course, but isn't
it better if it's fun?
[NOIRE] I don't see what's
so fun about failure!
[VILLAGE GIRLS]
She's here!
--It's the goddess!
--Lady Black Heart!
[NOIRE] Oh, oops. Access!
[NEPTUNE] What?
You're gonna transform now?
[NOIRE (BH)] Second rule
in the Goddess handbook.
One should always try
to project a majestic air.
[NOIRE (BH)] Ladies.
Would you mind telling me
about the monsters
that are troubling you?
[NEPTUNE] I dunno
if getting naked in front
of a bunch of
strangers is "majestic."
[NOIRE (BH)] This is the
Nasuune Highlands, correct?
[VILLAGE WOMAN 1A] Yes.
We've been overrun by Dogoos,
and we don't have
any heroes to slay them.
[NOIRE (BH)] You needn't worry.
Miss Neptune and Miss Nepgear
from our neighboring country
have volunteered to
deal with them for you.
[NEPTUNE] Nep what?
Wait, I gotta work?
[NEPGEAR] Well, it doesn't
look too hard, I guess.
[NOIRE (BH)] Rule number three.
Show off, whenever you can.
[UNI] I'll record it for you.
We can make a PR reel!
[NEPTUNE]
You're making us grind?
Well, these guys are so weak
you could beat them
with a Cypress Stick.
[NEPTUNE] Let's do
this thing! Come on, Sis!
[NEPGEAR] Right! You got it!
[NEPTUNE] Now that was awesome.
Must run in the family.
[NEPTUNE] Chest buster!
[NEPGEAR]
I'll use my true power!
[IF] There's simply
too many of them.
[COMPA] Then we better
get stomping, Iffy!
Let's go!
[IF] Sounds good.
[NEPTUNE] Iffy! Compa!
[COMPA] And here I come!
[NEPTUNE]
They're just a trash mob.
This is a piece of cake!
[UNI] Hey Noire.
Maybe we should help
them out before this gets--
[NOIRE] No.
It's meaningless if they don't
accomplish this for themselves.
[UNI] Oh.
[IF] Don't touch me there!
[COMPA] This feels gross!
Cut it out!
[NEPGEAR] Are you kidding me?
Stop, you naughty dog!
[NEPTUNE giggles]
[NEPTUNE] Oh, that tickles,
I'm gonna die laughing!
[NEPGEAR] Please no more!
[NEPTUNE giggling]
[IF yells]
[IF] All right you little punks.
I'll send your souls
to a world of despair!
[IF] Flame Soul Slice!
You're dead!
[NOIRE (BH)] Neptune you're
not even trying, are you?
[IF panting]
[NEPTUNE] Ugh that settles it.
I'm never eating jelly
again as long as I live.
[NOIRE (BH)] Why didn't
you use your goddess form?
Those dogoo would've
been a piece of cake!
[NEPTUNE] Who cares!
It turned out okay, right?
[NOIRE (BH)] Only because
you had other people
to cover for you!
This is why your
Shares are always--
[NOIRE (BH)]
You know what, never mind.
I'll take care of the rest
of this ordeal on my own.
[NOIRE (BH)] Lead the
way to Toruunay Cave.
[VILLAGER GIRL BRAIDS]
Right. Yes ma'am.
[UNI] I'll come with you.
[NOIRE (BH)] I'll be all right.
You stay here and try
to clean up all this goop.
[VILLAGER GIRL BRAIDS] This way.
[NOIRE (BH)] Thank you.
[NEPTUNE]
Man, she sure is uptight, huh?
Oh! Uni, did you
get any good pics?
[NEPTUNE] Dude!
So cute! Let's forward
these to me. Bloop!
[NOIRE (BH)] Perish!
[NOIRE (BH)] A dead end, huh?
Guess that's a wrap, then.
[NOIRE (BH)]
That's an Ancient Dragon!
[NOIRE (BH)] You might
actually put up a fight!
Take this!
[NOIRE (BH) gasps]
Oof!
[NOIRE (BH) groans]
[NEPTUNE] Hi. Yah!
[NEPTUNE] Whassup?
[NEPTUNE]
Hey, you're human again!
What happened?
[NOIRE] I don't even know.
It's strange. Look out!
[NEPTUNE] See?
This is the time when a goddess
should transform for real!
[NEPTUNE] Check it out, yo!
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
Witness the power of a CPU!
[NOIRE] This was my fight!
Don't show off!
[NEPTUNE (PH)] I am grateful.
Now leave this one to me.
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
Cross Combination!
[NOIRE] I-I could've handled
that thing on my own, you know.
I didn't need any help from you!
[NEPTUNE (PH)] Perhaps not.
However, comrades
help each other out.
[NOIRE] We're really more
"rivals" or "enemies,"
if you ask me.
[NEPTUNE (PH)] Why did you
choose this place today?
[NOIRE] Because it's
close to your home
and I wanted you out of my hair.
[NEPTUNE (PH)] Since it's
close to the Planeptune border,
word of my heroics will
surely spread there as well.
[NEPTUNE (PH)] You were worried
about my Shares, weren't you?
Thank you, Noire.
[NEPTUNE] Me kicking
butt was cool,
but you almost getting eaten,
now that's the real story!
[NOIRE] You wouldn't dare tell!
[NEPTUNE] Hey guys, get this!
Noire did something super lame!
[NOIRE] Hey! Nepture! I-
I thought we were comrades!
Come back!
[VILLAGER GIRL GREEN]
Lady Black Heart
and Lady Purple Heart beat them!
[VILLAGER GIRL RED] They beat
the monsters with power of love
and probably also lasers!
[VILLAGER GIRL GREEN] Yipee!
Yipee!
[NEPTUNE] Misinformation
sure spreads fast, huh?
[NOIRE thinking] Why did my
transformation break?
[ARFOIRE] They cleared out
all the monsters for us.
How sweet.
[WARECHU] Good.
Now we can search
for that thing in peace.
[HISTOIRE] Very impressive!
[HISTOIRE]
I meant Noire, not you.
[NEPTUNE] Nep what? Don't hate!
I was awesome back there!
[HISTOIRE] Previous
instances would indicate
that you are actually
useless and not awesome.
[NEPTUNE] Oh my gosh, rude!
[NEPTUNE] Nepgear,
is something wrong?
[NEPGEAR] It's awful!
There're weird pictures
of me on the internet!
[NEPTUNE] These are the
pictures I mailed to myself.
You're such a cutie
in these, Nep Junior!
[NEPGEAR] It's humiliating!
[IF] Are you sure
you didn't send those
to the wrong e-mail address?
[NEPTUNE] Who do you
think you're talking to?
I, oh--I forwarded it to
the nationwide mailing list.
[IF] I thought so.
[COMPA] On the upside,
the comments are all
pretty positive, though!
[COMPA] "I'm in
the fantasy zone."
[NEPTUNE] "It's like
a journey of dreams."
[IF] And this one says
"hail to Planeptune, baby."
Seems you've got some fans!
[NEPGEAR] Wha-What?
[HISTOIRE] So does that mean
your Shares went put because of
[NEPTUNE] These pictures?
Maybe. Wow, Nepgear, nice work!
[NEPGEAR] Well, if you say so.
[NEPTUNE] That's handy
'cause I've got plenty more
where those came from!
[NEPTUNE] Nepgear!
Do it for your country, okay?
[NEPGEAR]
Wait, that's a joke, right?
[HISTOIRE] I'm worried about
this country on so many levels.
So many levels.
[NEPTUNE] I'm gonna
leak 'em now! Here we go!
[NEPGEAR] My dignity!
[REI] We should live
our lives by regulations--
[IF] Whoa, now that is intense.
[COMPA] Hey, this art really
is an explosion, isn't it?
[IF] Huh?