[ABNES] Ga-Thunk!
Time for another
action packed day
spent saving the
children of the world!
[NEPGEAR] Wow! It's even
prettier than I thought.
[NEPGEAR] Y'know, I've
always wanted to visit Lowee.
[NEPTUNE] Yeah,
you haven't exactly made
that the best-kept secret.
[NEPGEAR] It was so
nice of Rom and Ram
to invite us to stay with them.
I just wish that Blanc
would let them travel
to other countries so they
could come and visit us, too.
[NEPTUNE] Oh, yeah. Blanc's
got a real stick up her butt
about that kind
of stuff like that.
You know, she really
ought'a pull that thing out
before she ends up
friendless like Noire.
[NOIRE] You realize
I can hear you, right?
And I've got plenty
of friends, dammit!
[NEPTUNE] Sorry,
forgot you were there.
Well, maybe hearing that
said right to your face
is just the thing you
need to make a change.
[NOIRE] I don't need to hear it
from a slacker like you!
I'm starting to regret
letting you talk me
into coming on this trip.
[CHURCH WORKER A
falls and screams]
[RAM] She fell for it!
[ROM] That was just perfect!
[CHURCH WORKER A]
Miss Rom, Miss Ram!
How could you? Come here now!
[RAM] Run for it!
[CHURCH WORKER A]
Hold it right there, you two!
[VERT] Are you sure about this?
You do realize what this means?
Carrying out this plan
will entirely alter the
world as we know it.
[BLANC] I'm well aware of that.
We have to make sure
no one finds out about it
until it's implemented.
[RAM] Run faster!
[BLANC growls]
[BLANC] Alright,
you little turds.
How many times have
I told you to pipe down
while I'm working?
[CHURCH WORKER A]
I'm so sorry, Miss Blanc!
[ROM] Hey, big sis.
[RAM] Check this out!
[BLANC] This is my...
[RAM] It's a drawing of you!
[ROM] We got the
sharp teeth just right!
[BLANC] You've destroyed
my precious book.
[BLANC] I'll kill you!
[RAM] That's the face we drew!
[ROM and RAM giggling]
[BLANC] Get your
asses back here!
[ROM] Run!
[RAM] Hey, Nepgear!
Hi, Uni! You guys made it!
[NEPGEAR] Mmhmm.
How could we say no?
[NEPTUNE] Hiya, Blanc!
How goes it? Let's party!
[NEPTUNE] Alright. Bet you're
wonderin' why we're here.
Well we heard about
this new theme park
that opened up here in Lowee.
So we're gonna crash
with you and check it out.
[BLANC] Histoire warned me.
And she specifically asked
me to give you lessons
in being a worthwhile
CPU while you're here.
[NEPTUNE] Nah. That's
just a waste of time.
I mean that's about all
I learned from my last lesson.
[NOIRE] That makes two of us.
[VERT] Speaking of
the theme park,
I've heard good things about it.
It could be a lot of fun
for us to take the girls
and go as a group.
[RAM] You mean Super Nittenland?
[RAM] I wanna go, I wanna go!
[ROM] Can we, sis?
Please say yes!
[BLANC]
Actually, it would be nice
if you could take care of them.
[NEPTUNE] You're not going?
[ROM] Why not? Don't you wanna?
[BLANC] I want to. I just can't.
[NEPTUNE] It's not
'cuz of work, is it?
You've heard the saying.
"Working means that
you've lost at life."
Now that's a piece of wisdom
from a great man. See?
[NOIRE] Neptune, some
bum on YouTube said that.
[BLANC] It doesn't matter.
I just can't go.
[ROM] Hold on, Ram, wait for me!
[NEPGEAR] C'mon, girls,
you've gotta wear your coats.
[UNI] Wait, Nepgear!
You forgot to grab the tickets!
[RAM] Hey, Nepgear!
Where are you guys?
[ROM] I don't see 'em.
[NEPGEAR] Hey, girls!
[UNI] Over here!
[UNI] A coin with a Dogoo on it!
[NEPGEAR]
This one's got a Kupokitty!
[ROM] It's a Terits.
[RAM] Yeah, so is this
one. Talk about lame.
[NEPTUNE]
One rainbow road special!
[NOIRE] Seems like
Blanc should be acting
like more of a
diplomat when CPU's
from other
countries are visiting.
I mean, she's the
face of her country
and it could be prettier.
[VERT] That's a little harsh.
I know what you're saying
but I think we've all still
got some growing up to do.
[VERT] Well, maybe not me.
[NOIRE] Actually.
Come to think of it, what is
it that brings you to Lowee?
[NEPTUNE screams]
[NEPTUNE] Help me!
This monster turtle
wants my peaches!
No! Somebody call
a plumber! Stop it!
[RAM] Look, Rom!
It's a Guardragon coin!
That's a totally rare item!
[ROM] Well there sure
are a bunch of them.
[RAM] Oh, wow!
They're all Guardragons!
[RAM] Although. Maybe
we've got enough already.
[ROM] We do, but I wanna
bring some home for Blanc too.
[RAM] Seriously?
I don't see why, she didn't
even bother to come with us.
[ROM] I know, but.
[RAM] You're right.
Maybe if we pick up 100,
she can finally get a life!
[ROM] Yeah!
[ROM and RAM giggling]
[TRICK] Lickie.
[NEPGEAR] Where did...?
[UNI] What's up, Nepgear?
Somethin' wrong?
[NEPGEAR]
Where'd Rom and Ram go?
I don't see them anywhere.
[UNI] How 'bout there?
They were picking up
coins a second ago.
[NEPGEAR] Rom, Ram!
Where are you?
[MONSTER giggling]
[ROM and RAM struggling]
[NEPGEAR] Rom! Ram! What the--?
[UNI] Drop them!
What do you think you're doing?
[TRICK] Lickie!
[TRICK] Run along now, ladies,
you're far too
large for my tastes.
[UNDERLING]
Like candy from a baby.
Well done, Trick.
[TRICK] I'm the party star
and don't you forget it!
[NEPGEAR] Oh, no.
Bring them back!
[CHURCH WORKER A] Please
believe me, I understand.
But Lady Blanc has
explicitly instructed me
not to let anybody inside.
[NEPTUNE] Come on.
We're all goddesses here,
what's the big deal?
[CHURCH WORKER A] I know.
But I'm afraid
that doesn't matter.
[NEPGEAR] We just wanna
apologize, that's all!
[UNI] It was our fault
Rom and Ram got kidnapped!
Please let us help find them!
[CHURCH WORKER A] Thank you,
but that's not necessary.
We've already mobilized the
guards to search for them.
[NEPTUNE]
We know, but we can still--
[BLANC] Just go home.
[BLANC] All you'll do is
cause even more trouble.
[BLANC] Rom. Ram.
This is all my fault.
If only I...
[BLANC] ...was a
better sister. I'm sorry.
[BLANC] I've gotta
help them somehow.
[BLANC] How can I find them?
What can I do?
I know! I'll use--
[ABNES] Ga-Thunk!
Ga-Thunk! Ga-Thunk!
[ABNES] Now I've got you!
[BLANC] Who are you?
[ABNES] My name is Abnes!
And I fight for the
children of the world!
[BLANC] What?
[ABNES] Don't act
like you don't know me.
I'm the star of the hit internet
series the Abnes Channel!
Everyone knows me.
Okay, let's get this
live broadcast going!
[BLANC] Live broadcast?
[ABNES] Hello, Gamindustri!
It's your best friend,
Abnes, here!
Idol of the world's children!
And today, I'm confronting
the little girl CPU of Lowee!
Say hello to Blanc!
[BLANC] What? Little girl?
Listen, you annoying--
[ABNES] Now, Blanc, are the
rumors we've been hearing true?
Did you allow your own little
sisters to get kidnapped?
Well did you? Huh?
[BLANC] How did you
know about that?
[ABNES] Sounds like a yes!
Those poor little girls. So!
Just how does it feel to be such
an awful, neglectful big sister?
Honestly, now.
[NOIRE] That Blanc.
What is her problem?
This is an emergency--
it's scarcely the time
for her to be so pig-headed!
[NEPTUNE] Yeah, really,
Noire's the one
with the patent on being
an unlikeable hardass.
[NOIRE] Watch it.
[VERT] Girls. You see--
The truth is--
[NEPGEAR] Hey, Neptune.
What do you think that's about?
[ABNES] Shoot straight
with me here, Blanc.
The kidnapping
of your little sisters
entirely your fault, right?
Just admit it.
[BLANC] I... I don't.
[ABNES] You hear that, kids?
The little girl CPU can't
even properly defend herself.
Little girls just aren't
cut out to be goddesses.
[ABNES] It's too
much responsibility.
They should just be playing
games and enjoying life.
The Abnes Channel is firmly
against little girl goddesses!
[NEPTUNE] Hey, what the
heck's going on in here?
[ABNES] Who do
you think you are?
[NEPTUNE] I know I'm Neptune!
The goddess of Planeptune.
[ABNES] Oh, really,
another goddess?
Well, I suppose you
look passably old enough
to just be hitting
puberty. Although!
[ABNES] You've barely
begun to develop!
You're a little girl!
I declare you too young!
[NEPTUNE] Say what?
Am I really being
called a little girl
by a girl littler than me?
[ABNES] What? I am
certainly not a little girl!
And besides, it takes
one to know one, missy!
[NEPTUNE] Yeah, and since
you're throwing down
all these "little girl claims,"
that proves for
sure you're one too!
[ABNES] I can't believe
you said it again!
Leave my crew alone!
[ABNES] You're gettin' off with
a warning today, little girl.
But I will be back!
[NEPTUNE] Oh, yeah, little girl?
Well I'll be waiting for you!
Poor whiny widdle girl!
[NOIRE] For heaven's sake.
What was that about?
[VERT] I wonder how she and
her crew even got in here?
[NEPGEAR] Whoa, Blanc!
[NEPGEAR] It's okay,
Blanc! Hang in there!
[CHURCH WORKER A] I'll...
I'll go get some help!
[NEPGEAR] What do you
think's wrong with her?
[UNI] Maybe everybody in Lowee
just watched the interview
and her Shares took a
sudden turn for the worse.
[NEPGEAR] Hey wait, can't
a CPU lose her powers
if she doesn't have enough
Shares? That's not good.
[NOIRE] I don't think her Shares
dropping would make her faint.
There's no way she'd feel the
negative effects that quickly.
[NEPGEAR] Then why?
[VERT] Listen, ladies.
[VERT] There's a
way we can fix this.
We can track down Rom and Ram,
and I know exactly how to do it.
[VERT] The truth is.
Blanc has been working on a
certain plan for some time now.
[VERT] And part of it.
Well, I'm guessing
you must have heard
about the old satellite service
that was based out
of Lowee, right?
[NEPTUNE] Oh, yeah.
I remember that.
Wasn't it called
the Basillaview?
[NOIRE] Yeah, didn't they shut
it down around ten years ago?
[VERT] That's right.
It actually turns out
that all of the satellites
are fully functioning.
They're still capable
of relaying images
from around the entire world.
[VERT] However,
they're low resolution.
But Leanbox labs have developed
a new type of software
that can analyze
and process the data
and produce high-res
imagery from it.
[NEPTUNE] Awesome!
Just leave it to Nerdy Vert
and her tech savvy ways!
[VERT] Once we came up with it,
I approached
Blanc with an offer.
If Lowee will provide
the image data
from their satellite system,
then we'd trade. And Leanbox
would provide the software.
[NOIRE] But that would
give the two of you
a complete monopoly on all
of the world's information!
[NEPTUNE] Oh, man,
that's messed up!
Do you realize how much
trouble that'd cause us?
[VERT] Oh yes.
Trust me, we know.
And that's exactly
why we planned
on sharing all of the
information with the world.
[VERT] It was Blanc's
suggestion of course.
The way she saw it, we'd all
signed the friendship treaty,
so it's only right our four
countries use it equally.
[NOIRE] You don't say.
[VERT] It's true.
We were just waiting
for the right time to
go public with the news.
Sort of, a surprise present
to celebrate the treaty.
[VERT] The data
analysis just finished.
We'll know exactly
where the kidnapper fled.
Really? I see.
[TRICK] Well, lickie, lickie,
lickie, lickie, lickie, lickie.
[ROM] No!
[RAM] What's wrong?
[TRICK giggles]
[TRICK] There's nothin' better
than little sleepyhead girls!
They're the perfect
taste for licking!
[TRICK] Lickie, lickie,
lickie, lickie, lickie!
[RAM] Hey! Let go of
my sister you creep!
You stop that!
[TRICK] Lickie, lickie, lickie,
lickie, lickie, lickie!
[RAM] No! Put me down!
Stop licking!
[UNDERLING] I'm on top
of things, Trick, sir.
I made the call and demanded
the ransom just like you asked.
What the hell are you doing?
[TRICK] What do you
think I'm doing?
My saliva's got
healing properties.
I'm improving their health!
Nothing weird
going on here at all!
[UNDERLING]
Uh... Sure, whatever.
[RAM and ROM screaming]
[NOIRE] So they were
hiding out right here
beneath a ride that's
under construction.
[NEPTUNE] Okay, let's do this!
Time to kick some
kidnapping butt!
[VERT] Just one moment.
[VERT] We can't rush into this.
Our first priority should
be securing the hostages.
[RAM] Stop it! Let us go!
[ROM] Please, I wanna go home!
[VERT] That is quite enough.
[RAM] Big sis?
[TRICK] Another little
girl's come to play?
[ROM] Help us, Vert!
[VERT] I demand that you
release you those girls.
Let them go and
I'll take their place instead.
[TRICK] No thanks.
I'm a gentleman
who sticks to his word
and these little girls
were part of a deal.
Besides, I'm really
not into big boobs.
[VERT] Oh, and just what exactly
do you have against
large breasts?
[TRICK] They'll just
end up sagging someday.
[VERT] I see.
Well, Mr. Gentleman,
you certainly do
have a way with words.
[TRICK] You're a CPU?
[VERT (GH)]
That's Green Heart to you.
Now prepare yourself.
[UNDERLING] I am officially
no longer worried about
that ransom money.
[TRICK laughs]
[TRICK] If that's all you got,
this fight's not
gonna go well for you.
[VERT (GH)] I was
just testing you out.
Taste this spear
of the maelstrom!
This is the end!
Rainy Ratnapura!
[VERT (GH)] That was
hardly any trouble at all.
Wait. Where are Rom and Ram?
[UNDERLING] Another one!
[UNI] That's the girl.
I saw her take them!
[NOIRE (BH)] I'm not surprised.
Look at her,
she's likely dumb enough
to think she could lick us.
[UNDERLING] Wait!
Trick was the only one
doing any licking, okay?
And look, if it
makes any difference.
We only kidnapped them 'cuz
a weird old hag hired us to.
[NOIRE (BH)] Sounds like the
whiny excuse of an underling.
[UNDERLING] Yeah!
Exactly. That's it.
I'm nothin' but an underling.
So then, I'll let you
get back to business.
[NOIRE (BH)] Like hell
you're getting off the hook!
Lace Ribbon Dance!
[UNDERLING]
Can't blame me for trying!
[TRICK] As a gentleman, it's
my duty to protect those girls.
And the best way to
do that is by licking!
Okay, where did they go?
[TRICK] Oh you sassy things!
Little girls really
are the absolute best!
Lickie, lickie, lickie!
[BLANC] I'm gonna
make you pay in full
for what you've done,
and trust me.
You can't afford it.
[BLANC] You disgusting pervert.
[TRICK] Pervert huh?
Kindest thing
anyone's said to me.
[BLANC] Is that so?
Well then, I'll just have
to kill you with kindness.
[BLANC (WH)] Get ready to die.
You freaking sicko!
[BLANC (WH)] Alright.
Ultra Deviant!
[BLANC (WH)] Cataclysmic freak!
[BLANC (WH)] Tanzerin Trombe!
[TRICK] Goodbye little girls!
[BLANC (WH)] Don't pick
a fight with a goddess.
It's never gonna end well.
[BLANC] Hi, Rom. Hi, Ram.
I'm so sorry that
I let this happen to you.
[BLANC] I'm sorry.
I'm an awful big sister.
[ROM] But, sis.
[ROM] We got presents.
[RAM] They're for you!
[NEPTUNE] Get out here,
you kidnappers!
I'll Nep your damn faces off!
[NEPGEAR] Uh, y'know, sis.
[NEPGEAR] I get the feeling
they already beat the bad guys
while we've been
guarding the door.
[laughs]
[NEPTUNE] For real?
Sleep deprived?
[BLANC] That's right.
That's the reason why
I fainted like that.
That's also why I didn't
go to the theme park.
[NOIRE] Jeez, you're
ridiculous. Honestly.
[BLANC] I've been pulling
a lot of all-nighters lately,
and I just didn't have
the energy to do anything.
I was rude.
But you still helped me
and rescued my little sisters.
Thank you, Vert. Thanks, Noire.
[BLANC] And thank you, Neptune.
That awful interview.
You spoke up and defended me.
[NEPTUNE] Ah, no,
that was nothin'.
That bratty little girl
was just askin'
to have someone tell her off.
[ROM] Hey, Blanc! Look at this.
[BLANC] That's really nice, Rom.
[BLANC] Ram!
Stop drawing in that book!
[RAM] What's the big deal, sis?
You've got so many copies.
They're all the same book.
[BLANC] Just stop!
[RAM] Why, what's wrong?
[BLANC] Be-Because.
[BLANC] I pulled
those all-nighters
in order to write that book!
[VERT] Hold on,
you were writing a book
instead of working
on the satellite system?
[NOIRE] Huh? Uni.
What's Blanc's book about?
[UNI] I haven't read
the whole thing yet,
but so far it's about a
girl who fell from the sky
and a boy with superpowers
who save the world together.
[NEPTUNE] That's weird.
This girl you describe.
She sounds just like you.
[BLANC] Don't read it!
[NEPGEAR] Oh, wow.
The hero is taking her on
an air ride to dream land.
That's intense!
[BLANC] Stop reading it!
[BLANC] How can I find them?
What can I do?
I know! I'll use--
[ABNES] Ga-thunk! Ga-thunk!
Now I've got you!
[ABNES] Whoops,
sorry, wrong place.
[RAM] Hey, wait, rescue us!