Time to dig in!
[PEASHY yelling]
No fair, Neptuna!
That pudding is mine!
It's Peashy's Nep's pudding!
[NEPTUNE] Look, that
doesn't even make sense.
You said it
yourself, it's Nep's.
So how can it be
Peashy's if it's mine?
Mine!
Thanks a lot, P-ko!
Now you've gone and
ruined it for both of us!
I did not. This is your fault!
[NEPTUNE]
What? My fault?
You need to check yourself
before you wreck yourself!
Really! You ruin everything!
You're stupid, Neptuna!
Big dummy!
[PEASHY crying]
Only a dummy calls
people dummies, dummy!
Real nice.
You sure taught her
how to act like a grown up.
[NEPTUNE] What the--
How long have you been there?
[BLANC] Since around the
time you dropped the pudding.
[RAM]
You were mean to Peashy!
[ROM]
Poor Peashy.
[VERT] You see how you
could've handled that
with more maturity, right?
[NEPTUNE] What?
So I'm in the wrong here?
Of course you are.
Mmm-hmm.
Well...
Okay, fine, yeah, sure,
maybe I might've gone a
tad too far, I guess, maybe.
[NEPTUNE]
So anywho!
What brings you guys
to these parts?
And she's changed the subject.
[PLUTIA] Hey, Peashy,
there you are.
[PEASHY]
Hi, Ploot.
[PLUTIA] I've been looking
all over the place for you.
Well, just like I promised you!
Your very own Peashy!
Or "plushy," at least.
[shrieks]
I love it! You're awesome!
Yay for me.
[NEPTUNE]
What, the R-Rated Island?
It doesn't sound too family
friendly goin' by the name.
[VERT]
That's right!
It's an island of forbidden
desires exclusively for adults.
Things happen there!
You know what I mean!
Things of a certain nature
in every shape and form!
It's the most alluring theme
park where fantasies come true!
Oh.
Now I see what's going on here.
Sounds like an episode
for the fanboys.
[NEPGEAR (PS)]
Hang on.
You're telling me we're not just
going there to have some fun?
I wish, but unfortunately,
that's not the case.
I was running a
routine search
on my satellite
network yesterday
and came across
a giant gun battery
installed right in
plain sight on the island.
So we thought it would
be wise to investigate.
Histoire asked us
to be on the lookout
for anything else
strange while we're at it.
In particular,
I'm afraid that they might
be planning to start a war.
This is silly, Neppy.
I'm perfectly capable
of flying by myself.
What?
No, I don't think so!
You just stay like that!
Please, Plutie, I mean it.
[PLUTIA]
Aww.
[NOIRE (BH)]
What's the big deal?
If she can transform,
why not let her?
If you'd seen
what I've seen,
I promise you'd agree with me.
The final answer is no!
[PLUTIA] Aw, you're
such a meanie, Neppy!
[NEPTUNE (PH)] Whoa, hey,
don't kick like that!
[NOIRE (BH)]
C'mon, stop that!
[VERT (GH)] What in the world
are they doing back there?
[UNI] This is a
bunch of poppycock!
I don't care if there's an age
limit, why don't we get to go?
I do not accept this!
Me either!
Yeah, same here.
[COMPA] What's wrong,
Peashy? Whatcha doin'?
[IF] If you're trying to
find something, we can help.
[UNI] Peashy!
We were looking for you.
You wanna play
video games with us?
Are you waiting out
here for some reason?
[PEASHY]
Nuh-uh!
I guess we should have told
her that Nep was gone, huh.
She's probably looking for her
so she can tell her
that she's sorry.
She's a pretty
sweet kid after all.
[IF]
That Nep.
She should've made up
with her before she left.
[COMPA]
Well, y'know.
The two of them
are like family now,
and that kind of stuff happens
all the time between sisters.
All right, we have to go through
the immigration inspection
before we can enter.
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
Uh, is this good enough?
[NEPGEAR (PS)] Is it just me or
does it feel weird to power up,
then put on a swimsuit?
[NOIRE (BH)] Our outfits
are like swimsuits anyway.
[VERT (GH)] They have a
pretty strict dress code here--
swimsuits or all nude.
So take your pick.
That is rather
strict, isn't it?
Oh, it looks like
Blanc and Plutia
are done changing, as well.
Hey, guys!
[BLANC (WH)]
Hello.
You think this
is cute enough?
Oh, goodness me.
That's a yes, right?
[BLANC (WH)] Hey! You sure
changed your tone of voice!
[VERT (GH)]
Huh?
Oh, uh, I didn't mean to.
It's just that...
Don't take
this wrong way,
but I'm a little worried
they might not be convinced
that the two of you are adults.
[BLANC (WH)] Which way am
I supposed to take that?
[PLUTIA laughs nervously]
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Besides, we're goddesses,
I'm sure they'll
understand that we're ageless!
Oh, well.
I guess we might as well
take a crack at it.
[VERT (GH)]
Immigrations check, please.
Hello, welcome
to R-18 Island.
First off, are you an adult?
[VERT (GH)]
Of course I am.
[bell ringing]
[SYSTEM AVATAR]
You've been cleared.
All your boobs are
belong to us. Have fun.
[VERT (GH)] Sadly,
I'm here on business.
All right, see you
on the other side.
Right.
[bell ringing]
[SYSTEM AVATAR]
You've been cleared.
[bell ringing]
Hi, I'm an adult.
Are you really over
the age of 18 years?
Of course.
Me too!
Honestly?
[BLANC (WH)]
What? Yes, honestly!
This thing doesn't believe me.
You're really a
little girl, aren't you?
No, like hell I am!
We can see your chest.
[growling]
Let's go.
Yay! Hooray!
I didn't mean take a
literal crack at it.
[NEPTUNE] Okay, we
made it onto the island.
So, uh, what're we
supposed to do now?
Good question.
Maybe there's someone
we can ask for directions.
Hello, hello, hello!
Welcome! My name is Linda.
If you need anything at all,
I'm your official guide!
And I'll cut you a discount.
Wait. I know you.
It's her! The kidnapper!
Aw, crap, the CPUs?
[BLANC] Well look at this.
So you're the bitch
who stole my sisters!
Wait, no, no, no,
please, hold on!
I totally swear
to you on my life,
I am fully reformed now
and working hard!
You expect me to buy that?
You will regret it if
you're lying to us.
I'm not lying, really!
My criminal past is
completely behind me!
Hmm...
[UNDERLING]
So that's it?
The only reason you're all here
is to see the giant gun battery?
Do you know where it's
located on the island?
Yeah, of course!
I can lead you right to it!
Hey, but you guys!
We might as well check out
some of the party spots
while we're here!
We've told you,
this is not a vacation!
Don't be lame.
[UNDERLING]
Oh! Hey! I know!
I've got just the place
for some quick fun!
This is the most beautiful
spot on the entire island.
Fakekiki Beach!
Oh, wow!
Wait! What, what,
what, what, what?
[PLUTIA]
Whoa!
[NEPGEAR]
What the goodness?
[NEPTUNE]
Well, that's bold!
[NOIRE] But they're--
Where's their--
Everyone's naked!
I mean everyone!
It's like a real life internet!
Oh, my.
How wonderfully uninhibited!
We're wasting our time here!
We need to find the battery!
Hey, what's with the
glowy light streaks?
Oh, those?
That's the
Mysterious Light Grass.
It clings to the nether
regions for some reason.
Wha--
Why can't these people
just wear swimsuits?
Wh--Why the
nether regions?
Great idea!
[NEPTUNE] It's totally safe to
do this with this grass stuff!
Wow, jeez, Neptune.
Uh-oh.
C'mon, Nepgear,
you do it! It feels great!
Well, I'm not going
to pass this up!
Yeah, me neither!
[giggling]
[VERT]
I've never felt so free!
[NEPTUNE]
Do it, Nepgear!
If everyone else
can do it, then so can I!
[NEPTUNE]
Take this!
[giggling]
You're asking for it now!
[squealing]
[PLUTIA]
Take that!
[NEPGEAR] Okay, I thought
this was weird at first,
but you're right, it's awesome!
[BLANC] What the hell
has gotten into them?
[NOIRE]
C'mon, we need to hurry!
[laughing]
Go on and act
modest all you like!
With a little expert use of
the Mysterious Light Grass...
What?
[NEPTUNE]
Voila!
You might as well be naked now!
Such naughty girls!
Good thing they're censored!
Come on!
You know you really are
a serious perv, Neptune!
Perving out's what the
heart does best!
Now hurry up and
strip for realsies!
That freak.
All right. No use fightin' it.
Wait. Hold on.
[NEPTUNE]
Aw, man!
Aw, she figured it out.
What a pity, and it was
just about to get good, too!
I just knew there was
something fishy about this.
I don't get it, Neptune!
I clearly saw you
rip off your bikini!
I had another one under it!
[NEPGEAR]
No way!
[screaming]
What kind of awful
big sister are you?
[laughs nervously]
Oh, sorry, Nepgear.
I didn't think you'd
actually go through with it.
Hang on a minute! I'll
bring you your swimsuit.
[laughing]
[PLUTIA]
All done!
So, whada'ya think?
[VERT]
Wax on.
More wax on.
--[VERT] Up.
--[NEPGEAR] Okay, Vert.
--Down.
--I'm pretty sure that's enough.
I don't know, if the sun
can touch it then so can I.
I can do the rest,
but thanks for your help!
[UNDERLING]
Hey, ladies!
Would any of you care
for some iced tea?
Now that is service.
Tea time, bring it on!
[mischievous chuckle]
Ah! Now that's what
I'm talkin' about!
Have some.
There's plenty to go around.
[NEPGEAR]
Neptune!
[NOIRE]
What's wrong with her?
[UNDERLING]
Party time!
What's wrong, Neptune?
Are you having
trouble breathing?
Are you okay, sis?
[shrieks]
Oh, no!
What happened?
I'm so embarrassed!
Yes!
Why am I
dressed like this?
It's so improper!
Oh, no. Don't look at me!
Is this supposed to be a joke,
because it's kinda
creeping me out.
That is not the sister I know!
[VERT] There can
only be one culprit.
Although it's certainly
a taboo on this island,
I've heard of a drug
that can strongly enhance
a person's sense of shame.
Whoa, hang on,
I don't know nothin'
about any drug, okay?
You're dead, you punk!
To think we
ever believed you!
Wait, I'm sure
she can explain.
You turned over
a new leaf, right?
So what's going on here?
Plutia! Don't get mad!
Huh. Get real, I wiped my
ass with your "new leaf!"
I'm a natural born villain, see?
[PLUTIA]
Well, that's too bad.
No benefit of the
doubt for you. Oh, well.
Uh-oh. This is what
I was worried about.
[PLUTIA (IH)] I suppose I'll
have to reform you myself.
And this is going to
be a long, slow process.
G-Go ahead and t-try it,
I don't care!
[UNDERLING yelling]
[PLUTIA (IH)]
Oh, dear.
[NEPGEAR]
She's running!
She can look all she wants,
but she'll never find
me in the jungle--
[PLUTIA (IH)]
Boing.
There's no point
in taking it easy
on a hopeless cretin
like you, is there?
The only thing that'll get
through to you is a spanking!
Okay, then.
Let's turn over
that leaf for you.
[chuckling]
I hope your body is ready!
[UNDERLING screaming]
[whip cracking]
Goodness!
That's a bit extreme.
That's the most R-rated
thing I've seen today.
You know, it actually
feels kind of lonely
when no one's looking at me!
Oh!
Sorry 'bout that, sis!
I'm watching now, I promise!
[COMPA]
Okay!
We're all set for
swimming, everyone!
[giggling]
[IF] Wait, Peashy, what
are you doing? Don't jump!
[COMPA]
Peashy!
C'mon, you know
better than that! Ugh!
It's cold!
Are you serious?
Our sisters are
vacationing in paradise
and this is what we get--
Augh!
Lighten up!
You're gonna pay for that!
[laughing]
[COMPA]
Now this is relaxing.
Um, hi, Peashy.
Can I help you?
Compa, you're bouncy.
I wanna be
bouncy-bouncy, too!
You will be someday.
You've gotta wait
until you grow up,
but I bet you'll be
bouncy just like me.
[PEASHY]
Bouncy, bouncy!
[PEASHY giggling]
[HISTOIRE]
Coming!
Please, come in
and take a seat.
May I ask your name?
Well, uh, it's um...
Right this way.
We have almost reached our
destination, the gun battery.
Almost gun there battery,
--almost, almost, almost,
--It's like she's hardly even
--almost, almost,
--human now.
What do you expect after
being victimized like that?
Well, the perpetrator
sure seems all right with it.
Feelin' better, Nep?
I think.
I just can't remember anything
about what happened to me.
Well, y'know, that's
probably for the best.
Wait, what, really?
Oh, don't listen to her.
It wasn't all that bad.
And besides, you were so cute.
Huh? Why'd a chill
just run down my spine?
[UNDERLING] As promised,
we have arrived.
--Huh?
[CROWD cheering]
[NOIRE]
Huh? What is this?
[PLUTIA]
A bubble party!
So is this just
a giant disco?
But those are gun barrels!
--Huh?
[NOIRE] So that
thing's the gun battery?
[NEPTUNE] But it's nothin'
but a big bubble maker!
[NEPGEAR]
Hey, it stopped.
No, it's just
about to start.
Get ready to
ransform, everyone.
[CROWD cheering]
That's adorable!
No! Hold on!
Did we really travel
all this way for bubbles?
Why's he here?
Did I imagine that?
I must have.
It couldn't have been him;
he's in jail.
[HISTOIRE]
Thanks again for waiting.
I talked with her
at length about it.
But unfortunately,
Peashy said she doesn't remember
anything about her mother.
Surely she just needs time!
[HISTOIRE]
Well, Peashy? Is that her?
She can't be.
I don't know her.
But of course you do!
I'm--Oh!
I--I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
[HISTOIRE]
It's okay.
Just give me a sec
and I'll fetch a towel.
[HISTOIRE]
Okay, now, here we are.
I'll just wipe that right up.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Mama.
I told you
she'd remember me.
Mama.
So then, you--
You really are her mother?
[PEASHY]
Mama.
[BLANC (WH)]
Wow.
Now that is what I call
a wasted afternoon.
[NOIRE (BH)]
I suppose so.
Noire, is
something wrong?
It seems like you're
a bit distracted.
Huh? No, I'm fine.
Really, it's nothing.
It's all right.
I know you regret
not getting naked,
but there's always next time.
Really?
So are you saying that Noire
isn't just a cosplayer,
but an aspiring nudist, too?
[NOIRE (BH)] Easy, Nepgear,
you're the only nudist here.
[PLUTIA]
Hey, guys.
You've seen me transform now,
so you know
I can do it, right?
So why don't I do a little
Henshin a Go Go and--
[ALL]
Absolutely not!
[PLUTIA]
Biggest meanies ever.
[NEPTUNE]
We're home, you guys!
Hey, welcome back.
[NEPTUNE] I brought
a present for P-ko.
Check it out!
I wrote my name on all of 'em
so we'll have a whole
bunch of Nep's puddings!
Now I can always share
and we won't
have to fight, P-ko!
Hey...
Where's P-ko?
Well, that's the
thing. Actually...
[NEPTUNE] What do you
mean P-ko went back home?
[HISTOIRE] Her mother came to
pick her up and that was that.
[NEPTUNE]
Are you kidding?
Out of the blue?
Just like that?
[HISTOIRE]
I know how you feel,
but Peashy insisted on
leaving with her right away.
[RAM] She didn't even
stop to tell us goodbye.
[ROM]
I miss her.
[NEPGEAR] Okay, but we
can still go visit her
at her house sometimes, right?
[HISTOIRE]
I'm afraid not.
[UNI] She took off before we
could find out where she lives.
Oh, no.
You dummy.
You're a dummy, P-ko!
I'm sorry for what
I said. Come back.
[REI] I brought
her here for you.
[ANONYDEATH]
Nicely done.
I'm sorry, but doing all
this felt really wrong,
and I don't get why it
had to be me that did it.
And another thing, what was
inside that bottle you gave me?
That weird icky black stuff?
[ANONYDEATH]
Rei Ryghts.
That is your name isn't it?
[REI]
Um, yes?
[ANONYDEATH] Then here's a piece
of advice for you, little Rei.
If you clearly aren't
meant to know the answer,
then maybe you shouldn't ask
the question in the first place.
Hey there, everyone!
My name's Plutia.
Get used to this face 'cause
I'm hosting Nepstation today!
This is my special guest.
If you don't know, her name--