[ARFOIRE giggles]
My power!
[ARFOIRE] Once a goddess
enters my Anticrystal field,
their energy bleeds
away, bit by bit.
What is it you want?
Who are you?
The name is Arfoire, girly.
I'm here to bring the gospel
of chaos to this world,
and eliminating its bratty
rulers should be a good start.
[WARECHU]
And I'm Warechu!
Ranked #3 mascot
in the rodent world!
--[ARFOIRE] Come on, Rat.
--[WARECHU] Hm?
This is my big scene here;
stop screwing it up.
What the cheese, lady? I'm the
one who dug up the Anticrystals
in that cave in Lastation
and in the Leanbox ocean.
I think I deserve some time
in the spotlight, too!
Hmph! There wouldn't even be
a spotlight for you to hog
if I hadn't found the first
Anticrystal back on Planeptune.
And need I remind you that
it was none other than moi
who stole the stone
from Lowee's Basilicom?
Lowee's Basilicom? You knew?
Why couldn't you stop her?
Don't blame me. I kept it
under tight surveillance,
but the damn thing
went missing
during the whole
kidnapping mess.
If you hadn't kept it secret,
we could've helped!
Sure, in hindsight,
but I had no idea
there were more
than one of them!
Then, back in the cave...
That's what it was.
Did you figure
something out?
[NEPTUNE (PH) gasps]
[NEPTUNE] Whoa.
My transformation...
[NOIRE (BH) gasps]
[VERT (GH) &amp;
BLANC (WH) gasp]
[ARFOIRE laughs]
I told you your energy
would bleed away.
You shouldn't act so surprised.
But don't worry--
there's plenty more suffering
where that came from.
[NOIRE yells]
[VERT]
Can't we do something?
No, what happened?
Neptune!!
It's Nepgear!
We've gotta get out of here!
We can't just
leave her!
Snap out of it!
We'll come back with a plan!
You're gonna
let 'em get away?
Sure, why not?
They can't transform.
Why should I be afraid
of a pair of little girls?
Wait, could you explain this
to me one more time, IF?
I'm a bit confused
myself, really.
She mentioned something
about "Anticrystals."
I think they're used to
steal power from CPUs.
[HISTOIRE] Huh.
Doesn't ring a bell.
Then could you maybe research
them for us, Miss Histoire?
I wouldn't mind, but I'm afraid
it will take three days.
Maybe try to use blast
processing this time.
I'll give it my best.
Nepgear, you should come back to
Planeptune with IF and Compa.
Until we have an answer,
the rest of you should
probably head home
as well. See you later.
Well, you heard her--
[UNI] Wait! I'm not going
anywhere until you give me
a proper explanation for this.
Can't we do anything?
Usually Blanc
takes down bad guys
with one punch,
so what gives?
She's not gonna die, is she?
No, no, she'll be just fine!
She's a goddess after all,
so even if she gets hurt,
she'll get right back up!
Normally! But you said their
powers were stolen, didn't you?
[NEPGEAR]
I'm sorry.
[UNI]
Hm?
[COMPA] It's not
your fault, Ge-Ge.
[NEPGEAR]
It is, though.
The stone I picked up
when we were shopping.
I knew that it was strange.
It must have been
an Anticrystal.
This is pointless. Playing the
blame game won't help anyone.
[NEPGEAR]
You say that.
But if I'd just
stopped to think...
If I'd tried to figure out why
I got dizzy, even a little...
If I'd told our sisters,
we could've stopped this.
[UNI]
That's right, you idiot!
Noire is strong!
She would never get captured.
Well, not on her own at least!
You did this to her!
I wish they'd
captured you instead,
'cause no one
would miss you!
[footsteps]
[UNI sobs]
[door slams]
[NEPGEAR weeps]
[NEPTUNE] Don't you
have any video games?
This is boring!
I wanna party!
[NOIRE] We could die here,
and that's your complaint?
I finally know.
This is what hell's like.
It's awful.
I can't even post
on the Four Goddesses
Online chat room.
I was supposed to do an end game
raid with my guild tonight!
Are you loco roco?
I'm still stuck on dialup,
but I totally get where
you're coming from.
Okay! I'm gonna try making
some demands real quick.
Hey, you! Uh, what's-your-name!
Arf... Arf... Arfy Warf?
You really think
that's my name?
[NEPTUNE] Oh, uh, sorry,
I mean, um, Awful Waffle?
[ARFOIRE]
You're getting colder.
[NEPTUNE] Okay,
whatever, Art Farts.
Give us something to play with!
You have, like, wifi, right?
We're gonna die of boredom here!
Oh, yeah? Well, I assure
you death by boredom
is a lot less painful than
what you have in store.
Hey, wait. She didn't shoot
me down. So does that mean
she's giving me the okay
to call her "Art Farts"?
Just kill me.
[ARFOIRE] Hey! I just handed
you your death sentence!
Can't you be a little
terrified, at least?
[NEPTUNE]
Wasn't listening.
Huh. Why don't you
try looking down?
[NEPTUNE]
Wha...?
[NOIRE]
Ah! What is that?
[VERT]
It's rather unsettling.
[BLANC] Oh, great.
It gets even worse.
It may look benign for now,
but you'll feel it soon enough.
Enjoy what little
time you have left.
Au revoir, and writhe in your
cage of torment, my friends.
[ARFOIRE laughs]
[NEPGEAR gasps]
[ROM]
Miss Nepgear?
[RAM]
C'mon, hurry!
[UNI]
Ugh, I know.
[UNI sniffs]
Did something happen?
Let's be friends, okay?
I shouldn't have said that.
I'm really sorry.
It's not your fault.
I know that, but...
I'm just so angry right now.
Why am I so helpless?
I know. It's all right.
I feel the same way.
I thought my big sister
was unbeatable. That no one
was stronger. I always felt,
as long as she was around,
everything would turn
out fine, no matter what.
[NEPGEAR]
That sounds like me.
Neptune may act silly sometimes,
but I'm so lost without her.
Now, I'm just standing
here like a fool.
I don't know what to do at all.
What do you mean? It's easy!
All we gotta do is go
and save 'em ourselves!
[ROM] We can win this. If we all
work together, I know we can!
[NEPGEAR] But none of
us have CPU forms yet.
[RAM] Then let's learn
how to get them!
[ROM] I bet we can
figure something out.
I suppose so.
Yeah, it's worth a try.
I think I might
actually have a clue.
It was something that
Noire told me a while back.
She said I can't transform
because I put a
limiter on my heart.
I don't get it.
Just what does that mean?
It's not literal.
It's more like...
I'm afraid of something and
that's what's holding me back.
[ROM]
I'm afraid of monsters.
[NEPGEAR]
I think we all are.
[RAM] Fine!
Then let's train together
till no one's scared
anymore! Okay?
Count me in!
[NEPGEAR]
Mm.
[IF]
Uni! Rom, Ram!
Your attendants
are here to--ah!
[RAM yells]
[COMPA cries]
Owie! You're a lot
stronger than you look.
Compa, are you okay?
It may be harsh,
but this is training!
What? Wait, you're
in Lady Vert's game?
[NEPGEAR] We thought
it might help us
to unleash the fighter within!
[UNI] Obviously! This place
isn't exactly dance central.
I volunteered to
play the enemy,
even though I get
beat up a bunch.
But if it helps Ge-Ge and the
others transform, I don't mind.
Somebody's gotta do it!
Wait, transform?
Look, we have to fight.
I mean, after all,
if we don't do something to save
our sisters, then who will?
Exactly. But we have
to get stronger first.
Whoa, hold on a sec, Nepgear.
We're dealing with an enemy
who captured four goddesses.
I know that. But this's
our responsibility.
Because we have the power
to be goddesses, too.
[IF sighs]
No point in trying to stop you.
But I don't like you beating
on Compa, so no more of that.
I'll play the enemy from now on.
Thanks, Iffy.
I'll avenge you.
I sure hope you're ready.
Ga-thunk, ga-thunk, ga-thunk!
Look who I found!
[NEPGEAR]
Huh?
[dialup internet
connection noise]
[ARFOIRE] Haven't you
uploaded those pics yet, Rat?
What's the problem?
[WARECHU] In case you can't
tell, we're on dialup here.
56k and I keep getting booted.
Kinda lucky there was a modem
here in the trash heap, though.
All things considered.
You knew this place wouldn't
have cell phone reception.
You should've planned ahead!
You're the big cheese here--
any onsite mishaps are on you.
Just hurry it up, all right?
[WARECHU]
Chu...
Why don't you try telling
that to the modem?
Hmmm. How peculiar that only
the little sisters are home
and all four goddesses
are mysteriously absent.
I smell a conspiracy.
[NEPGEAR]
Um, Abnes, was it?
I don't mean to
be rude, but we--
[UNI] Look, this is
a private party,
so get out of our
hair, would you?
Should I know her?
The noisy brat? Really into
little girls for some reason?
Got on Nep's bad side?
Sorry, but we... have a lot
on our plate right now, so--
[ABNES]
Shut up!
I don't want to hear a peep
out of your half-developed
un-little girl mouth!
With the CPUs gone,
this is my best chance
to turn Rom and Ram back
into normal little girls!
Nice idea, if I do
say so myself!
Yes, it's just like
splendor in the grass!
Come on, you little cuties.
Let's hold hands and
play a game together!
[RAM &amp; ROM giggle]
Sounds great! I don't know
about the holding hands part,
but we do have a
really fun game!
Oh, for real?
Pretty please?
Uh, sure.
That sounds nice.
[ABNES] S-Say, are you sure this
is the game you want to play?
How about something a
little more... girlish?
[UNI chuckles]
[ABNES]
Eep!
Okay, guys, attack!
Iffy, look. It says
here you can fight
against an AI character instead.
It figures. Most games
have that option now.
[fighting noises]
Seems like we
should tell them.
I dunno, maybe later. Hate to
ruin their fun, after all.
[ABNES yells]
Now, girls,
leap into my arms!
It's my coup de grace!
[COMPA]
So awesome!
An Ancient Dragon, and you
guys beat it all by yourselves!
That hurt!
You dumb quack nurse!
Sorry, I was distracted.
No good. We may have won,
but if we still can't transform,
it's all for nothing, y'know.
Yeah.
We're just going to have to beat
a bunch more of them, I guess.
[IF] It looks like we
don't have time for that.
[NEPGEAR gasps]
Unfortunately, the entire
world is about to find out
that the four goddesses
have been captured.
The four goddesses
have been captured?
Then it's time to party!
[COMPA] Your nurse says
you need to take it easy.
If the citizens get a
peek of images like this,
then any one of your Shares
could take a serious nosedive.
And you know what that means.
If our Sharicites start
sending us less power,
then there's no way we'll be
able to rescue our sisters.
In other words, even if
we can't transform yet,
we have to give this a shot now!
Right.
[NOIRE] The pool's
getting rather large.
[VERT] What do you think
will happen when it gets
deep enough to overtake us?
[BLANC] I should've
researched countermeasures
against the stone
from the start.
All I did was hide it away
and try to forget about it.
[NEPTUNE] Aw, c'mon, guys!
Let's cheer up!
Sure, this kind of sucks,
but on the bright side,
we're not dead yet!
Normally I can tolerate
your optimism,
but at times like this,
my patience wears thin.
I'm afraid you're in denial.
[NEPTUNE] But hey,
that's still better
than giving up hope, isn't it?
When the situation
is impossible,
then hope isn't terribly useful!
[VERT] Oh, it's not
impossible at all.
Your sisters are
still out there,
and who knows what
they can accomplish?
Who, Uni? She's only
fought with help from me,
and not very well
for that matter.
My little sisters?
They're far too young,
and still need me
to protect them.
[NEPTUNE] Nep Junior's smart
and all, but she's afraid
to do anything on her own.
I'm not sure she can hack it.
[VERT]
I wonder.
Are you sure that's
not your egos talking?
They're all sweet girls,
I understand that.
And because they're
so cute and innocent,
I can see why you would want
them to stay that way forever.
But maybe that attitude
is what's holding them back.
Because it keeps them in the
role of "cute little sisters
who aren't strong
enough to transform."
Just food for thought.
[WARECHU]
They're here.
[NEPTUNE gasps]
It looks like there's six
of them, so the little chumps
came back with
reinforcements this time.
Hmph! Is this one of those
"the power of love" things?
I'll take them down without
so much as lifting a finger.
But here's that
entertainment you asked for!
[ARFOIRE laughs]
[COMPA] They still
can't transform.
Are they gonna be okay?
[IF] Even if the CPUs were
captured, seeing their sisters
fight to save them should
put the citizens at ease,
and that should mitigate
the damage to our Shares.
[COMPA]
That's not reassuring.
Don't get me wrong.
I want to believe in them.
Against all odds, I hope
they can pull this off.
[COMPA]
Iffy...
Is everyone ready?
[NEPGEAR grunts affirmatively]
[ROM &amp; RAM grunt affirmatively]
I won't back down!
I'm not afraid!
You keep fighting, and
I'll keep protecting you!
Sounds good! If you've got
my back, nothing can stop me!
I've got you now.
You better watch out,
'cause this'll hurt!
Move, it, creep.
She's in trouble!
Hey, be careful!
[ROM yells]
Rom, no!
I've got you two covered!
Now let's regroup!
[ROM]
Uni...
[RAM]
Quick, behind you!
[gun clicks]
[NEPGEAR]
I won't lose!
[UNI] Stay back!
Get away from me!
[NEPGEAR] What should
we do? I was wrong.
[RAM]
I need cover!
[NEPGEAR] We weren't ready
to fight yet after all!
Iffy, this is starting
to look really bad!
[NEPGEAR] Everyone's going
to die and it's all my fault!
I can't do anything.
Help me, Neptune!
I'm relying on my
sister too much again.
But what am I supposed to do?
We can't win this without her!
[UNI] I think I might
actually have a clue.
It was something Noire
told me a while back.
She said I can't transform
because I put a
limiter on my heart.
[NEPGEAR]
A limiter?
It's more like...
I'm afraid of something
and that's what's
holding me back.
[NEPGEAR] What am I
afraid of? Losing Neptune?
Of growing up and not being
her little sister anymore?
No. I'm afraid of her
losing something.
I'm afraid of growing
even stronger than she is.
Iffy! It's Ge-Ge!
[IF]
Mm?
[NEPGEAR] I don't
mind being weak,
and I don't mind looking
up to my sister.
But if it means getting
her back, I'll do anything.
I'll become stronger
than anyone else!
[UNI]
Hey, you did it!
She's so pretty.
You rock!
[NEPGEAR (PS) chuckles]
No matter what,
I mustn't retreat.
No looking back!
I have to keep going!
It looks like we don't
have time for that.
[NEPGEAR &amp; UNI wail]
[IF] Hm? Oh! Oops! Rewind!
You did not see that!
I was out late one night and
decided to crash at Compa's,
but when I woke up
to get a drink of water,
I saw her like this and,
like, well, can you blame me?