[WOMAN 10A gasps]
[PEASHY (YH) giggles]
Going on trips is fun, huh?
March, march!
Go go go!
People of Eden!
Please turn back!
If you continue to advance...
...I'll open fire!
Aaahhh! You bad
goddess, you!
[NEPGEAR (PS) gasps]
Peashy, don't!
I hate mean old
bad goddesses.
But Papa said there's nothing
wrong with playing with you.
So how 'bout it?
Come on! Let's party!
[UNI] Noire!
Is it true?
Did Eden really
invade Planeptune?
[NOIRE] Yes.
Nepgear's evidently
trying to hold them off
on her own right now.
I'll go help her!
[NOIRE] Uni.
You need to see this.
[UNI] Uh?
[OFFICERS yell]
[GIRL MOB] Release them!
Release them!
We demand to see
more explicit content!
[MOB GIRL 10B] Down with
despotic age restrictions!
[GIRL MOB] Release them!
Release the adult's--
[BLANC] These extremists are
staging riots everywhere
in Lastation,
Leanbox, and Lowee,
all making the same
demands as Eden.
In other words,
Planeptune's the last of
our worries right now.
We have to deal with this first.
[NOIRE] There's no denying
it's a diversionary tactic.
But that doesn't make the threat
any less dangerous.
So what are you saying?
Forget about Planeptune
and Nepgear?
No, but we have to protect
our own countries first.
That is our duty
as goddesses.
[GIRL MOB]
Release them! Aaahh!
Release them! Release them!
[ANONYDEATH] Ooh!
That's the spirit, ladies!
Stick it to the man and fight
for your right to porn!
Go! Go, go, go!
[REI] It took no time at
all for the whole world
to turn upside down.
[ANONYDEATH] It didn't
turn on its own,
you were the one
who turned it!
You are the commander in chief
of our army after all.
What do you mean, army?
They're not willing soldiers.
You're just using mind control
to make them do what you say.
[GIRLS laugh]
Huh?!
Mmm!
[REI] And what is that
black mist you're using
to control them?
[ANONYDEATH] How many times
have I gotta tell you?
I really don't know.
The client provides us the
goods and I leave it at that.
We're forbidden to
pry into the details.
I'm utterly terrified.
The way things are moving, it's
like the world's going crazy.
[ANONYDEATH] Well, yes,
it does look that way.
No one's getting past me
and that includes you, Peashy.
[PEASHY (YH) chuckles]
Then we can just
play right here!
[PEASHY (YH) laughs]
[MINI HISTY]
According to the data,
that CPU is evidently
the "great presence"
we've been searching for.
[HISTOIRE]
That's exactly what I feared.
[COMPA]
So, wait...
Is that why Peashy already knew
who me and Iffy were
before we met her?
[HISTOIRE] Yes.
It's probably safe to
assume that she knew
the two of you in
the other dimension.
This is really
complicated.
[MINI HISTY] I don't mean to
sound too alarmist or anything,
but there's a large
portion or our world
that's coming completely
undone right now!
Hold on.
Do you think the area
the rebels are claiming
is Peashy's country
in the other world?
Probably.
So we need Plutia to
bring her back here
as quickly as possible,
even if it means
using extreme force.
Not a fan of extreme force.
[MINI HISTY] We can't
have misgivings!
It'll endanger our country too
if we don't bring her back!
[PLUTIA]
I know that, but still...
[phone rings]
[COMPA]
Yes, hello.
Oh! Yeah, of course.
[footsteps]
[NOIRE (BH)]
Snap out of it, Neptune!
[NEPTUNE] Ahh!
[thud]
What, Noire?
[NOIRE (BH)] Why are
you still at home?
Pull yourself together
and protect your people!
But I... It's just...
I can't.
That's P-ko out there.
[NOIRE (BH)]
Don't give me that!
You're a CPU!
You need to put
aside your feelings
and do the right
thing for your country!
You don't mean
take down P-ko?
If I had to...
...I would.
[NEPTUNE gasps]
[NOIRE (BH)] That's all
I have to say to you.
Goodbye.
Was I too harsh?
She'll do the right thing now.
[NEPTUNE] Maybe Noire's
capable of that, but me?
[PLUTIA]
So you can't do it.
There's nothing wrong with that.
[COMPA and NEPTUNE] Huh?
Let's just stay here.
It'll be totally cool.
Lying around, playing games.
That's a nice thought, but
even I can't play games now.
Why not?
If you're not fighting,
what's the difference?
[NEPTUNE gasps]
I play games because I want
to have fun with my friends,
not escape reality.
[NEPTUNE gasps]
I see now...
That's exactly
what I'm doing.
[NEPTUNE cries]
[PEASHY (YH) laughs]
[NEPGEAR (PS)]
Haaa!
[PEASHY (YH) yells]
[gasps]
[PEASHY (YH)]
This is fun!
Oh, please no.
Why did she have to
do a barrel roll?
Here I come!
She's too strong.
At this rate, I'll never...
[PEASHY (YH) laughs]
[NEPGEAR (PS)]
Aahhh!
[PEASHY (YH)] Huh?
Neptune!
Sorry it took so long
to get here, Nepgear.
[NEPGEAR (PS) whimpers]
It's okay. But sis...
[NEPTUNE (PH)] Mm.
Hey, c'mon!
I'm not done playing yet!
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
All right, Nepgear.
You deal with the soldiers
and the monsters.
[NEPGEAR (PS)] What?
[NEPTUNE (PH)] They're about
to breach the barricade.
[NEPGEAR (PS)] Yeah, but--
Just go!
Sure. I'm on it.
[PEASHY (YH)] Hm?
[NEPTUNE (PH)] Listen!
From here on,
you're playing with me.
And I make the rules.
Now do your worst, P-ko!
Here comes a big
one--you ready?
[PEASHY (YH)] Bam!
[NEPTUNE yells]
[PEASHY (YH)] Pow!
[PEASHY (YH) laughs]
Huh?
[NEPTUNE groans]
[PEASHY (YH)] That's it?
You're already done?
Not this Neptuna.
I don't go down that easy.
And you know that, too.
Right, P-ko?
Neptuna?
I don't know you!
No, you just forgot.
But I promise,
you know who I am!
No, I don't!
You do too!
Yes, you do!
[PEASHY (YH) grunts]
No, I don't! No, I don't!
[NEPTUNE groans]
You're weak!
And I'm bored!
I don't wanna play with you!
[NEPTUNE groans]
[NEPTUNE]
Yaaaa!
[PEASHY (YH)]
Aaaahhh!
[NEPTUNE] Only weaklings
call people weak, weakling!
[NEPTUNE] Only a dummy
calls people dummies, dummy!
You...
I hate you! I hate you!
I hate you, I hate you!
I hate you!
I hate yoooouuu!
[loud thud]
[NOIRE] Eden barely has
any believers so far.
But I could sense a ton of
Share energy in Yellow Heart.
Something's not right.
[PLUTIA]
Got some news, Noire?
[NOIRE] Huh?!
What are you doing
here, Plutia?
Oh, y'know.
Neppy didn't wanna
play a game with me.
What?
And what about you?
Shouldn't you be in
your own country?
It's under control.
I have a perfectly
competent little sister.
[UNI (BS) yells]
[GIRLS]
Ooohhh!
If you still wanna fight,
you better step it up.
That's cool.
[rustling]
Ah!
[PLUTIA] Hm?
[NOIRE] Huh?
Aaaahhh! Goddesses!
Shh!
We're spotted!
Guess I'm gonna have to
charge right in after all.
Huh?
[UNDERLING gasps]
[PLUTIA (IH)] Hmph.
Ahh!
I was under the
assumption that everyone
on this island got turned
into mindless soldiers,
but I see you managed
to hang in there.
Please! Not again!
[PLUTIA (IH)] Hmmm, now what
am I gonna do with you?
Ha, ha! That tickles! Ha, ha!
[ANONYDEATH] I knew you couldn't
resist coming to see me!
Now let me shower you
with a torrent of love
my darling, Noire!
[NOIRE (BH)] Huh?
[NOIRE (BH) screams]
[PEASHY (YH)]
I hate you! I hate you!
Hate! You!
[NEPTUNE whimpers]
[PEASHY (YH) gasps]
I got ya now, P-ko.
[PEASHY (YH)]
Let, me, go!
Let go! Stop it!
Go away! Get off me!
I won't... let you go!
[PEASHY (YH) yells]
[NEPTUNE]
Never again!
[NOIRE (BH)]
Hhaaaaaa!
[ANONYDEATH]
Ooh, naughty girl.
But don't think
that'll get rid of me!
I like 'em feisty!
[NOIRE (BH) grunts]
[ANONYDEATH]
Oooohh! Beautiful!
This is ecstasy!
Oh, little Rei.
Quit your wide-eyed dawdling
and find the other goddess.
[PLUTIA (IH)] Oh, I happened
to find her first.
[ANONYDEATH] Ahh!
[ANONYDEATH] Oh, dear.
How did you...?
Heh. A close friend of
mine was more than happy
to point me in
the right direction.
Okay, I may be a rat,
but I kept my virginity.
To be perfectly honest,
you're not exactly my type.
But I still have to punish you.
[ANONYDEATH] Actually.
If I have to be punished,
I'd rather have Noire
take care of it.
[crashing sound]
[ANONYDEATH]
Oh, my.
[PLUTIA (IH)]
Well, speak of the devil.
[NOIRE (BH)]
Aaahhh!
Nice defenses, but,
they're no match for my sword.
[ANONYDEATH] Eep!
Excellent work,
but not enough.
I'm bringing down
the whole house!
[NOIRE (BH) gasps]
[NOIRE (BH)] What is that?
It's radiating Share energy.
[ANONYDEATH] Do you have
to be so destructive?
I would've gladly shown it
to you if you had just asked.
Wait! Is this
what's supplying
Yellow Heart with so much power?
[ANONYDEATH] I'd love to tell
you, but I'm afraid I signed
a confidentiality agreement.
[PLUTIA (IH)]
Here's a fun hypothetical.
What do you suppose would
happen to Peashy and Eden
if someone destroyed
this machine?
[ANONYDEATH]
I don't know.
Well he's not
going to tell us,
so we'll just have
to try it and see.
[PLUTIA (IH)] Hmph.
Fighting Viper!
[NOIRE (BH)]
Lace Ribbon!
[ANONYDEATH] Oh, dear!
[PEASHY (YH)]
Let me go! Let go!
[NEPTUNE]
Nope, sorry!
Not gonna happen!
[PEASHY (YH)]
Noooooo!
[NEPTUNE]
Remember me!
Try to remember, P-ko!
I don't know, I don't know,
I don't know, I don't know!
I don't know anything!
[GIRL MOB yells indistinctly]
[GIRL MOB] Huh?
[MOB GIRL 10A]
What's going on?
[UNI (BS)] Huh?
[EDEN SOLDIERS murmur]
[PLANEPTUNE SOLDIERS murmur]
[NEPGEAR (PS) gasps]
[PEASHY] Stop it!
Let me go!
P-ko, P-ko!
No, I hate you!
I hate you! I hate you!
I hate yoooooouuuu!
[NEPTUNE] Well, I like you!
In fact, I love you, P-ko!
I love you...
to bits and pieces!
[gasps]
[PEASHY] I hate you.
I hate you.
Okay. You can hate me.
Just as long as
you're here, P-ko.
[PEASHY] I hate you.
[NEPGEAR (PS)]
And just like that
everything went
back to normal.
And the new nation of Eden's
short history came to an end.
[NEPGEAR (PS)] As for the riots
in the other nations,
they were suppressed
without many casualties.
It was almost like
none of it had happened.
Well, for most people anyway.
But Peashy's memories
had yet to fully return.
Neptune, huh?
I...
Well then, take care.
It's hard to believe
this is goodbye.
I'm really going
to miss you two.
It's strange, but
it somehow feels
like we've been
friends forever.
I'll never forget
the two of you.
I can promise you that.
[PLUTIA]
Yeah, me either!
Neppy Jr.
[NEPGEAR] Huh?
[PLUTIA] For you.
Huh? You made one of me?
Thank you so much, Plutia.
[PLUTIA] I hope it
makes you happy.
[PEASHY] Huh?
Take care of
yourself, Peashy.
I know you don't
remember us,
but that doesn't matter.
Yeah, 'cause we'll
always be your friends.
[COMPA] Those versions of us
from Peashy's dimension.
I really hope that
they're good to her
and make friends with her again.
Hey, c'mon, it'll be fine.
It's us we're talking about.
[HISTOIRE]
All right, everyone.
I hate to say goodbye
but I'm afraid it's time.
We only have a
small window of time
to open the dimensional gate.
[gasps] Wait, not yet.
Neptune's not here.
I'm sorry, but
we have to hurry!
[NEPTUNE] Hey!
[NOIRE] Jeez, Neptune!
You're late.
[NEPTUNE] I'm sorry!
I'm so glad you came to
visit us, Plutie, I mean it.
We'll meet again someday.
[PLUTIA] Mm-hm.
Yeah. We will.
[NEPTUNE] Here, P-ko,
this is for you.
[PEASHY] Hm?
[PEASHY] Thanks, Neptune,
but what is it?
It's the absolute tastiest
thing you'll ever taste.
[MINI HISTY]
Uh, excuse me!
We really need to get
moving through this gate.
[PLUTIA]
'Kay!
Bye, girls.
See you later.
C'mon, Peashy.
Neptuna?
[NEPTUNE gasps]
[inaudible]
P-ko.
I'll never forget you.
I promise you that.
[PLUTIA]
Yeah, me either!
Neppy Jr. For you.
Um. It's a little
different from the others.
Take good care of it.
[NEPGEAR] Uh, okay!