[REI (GT)]
It doesn't work at all!
[screaming]
It's okay, don't cry.
We'll find your mom.
I know it's scary,
but be brave!
[NEPGEAR (PS)]
Compa!
[COMPA]
Ge-Ge!
Nep-Nep is up there
in the sky, fighting.
I saw.
Actually, I'm about
to go join her.
Are you kidding me?
Evacuating those adorable
children should come first!
[HISTOIRE]
I agree.
The citizens are
our priority, Nepgear.
[COMPA]
Histy! Iffy!
Thank goodness!
I was worried about you two!
Aw, give me some credit!
Like I would die!
[HISTOIRE] We should
lead the townspeople
as far away from that
floating island as we can!
I'll give it my best!
Attention, everyone!
Move this way, please!
Let's hurry!
[NEPGEAR (PS)]
I'm sorry Neptune.
Please try to hold out
just a little bit longer.
Blaze Break!
[laughing maniacally]
Seriously?
I just told you that crap's
not gonna work on me!
[NEPTUNE (PH)] That
lightning is indeed powerful,
but it still seems like I'm
wearing down too quickly.
Something's strange.
What's her secret?
Mommy!
[COMPA]
Well, that's a good start!
What's wrong, Ge-Ge?
You aren't hurt, are you?
I don't know.
It feels like the Share
energy inside me is--
It's fading away.
Nepgear, listen.
Maybe you should change
out of your CPU form.
Huh?
Our Share energy
is dropping rapidly.
I can't determine the cause,
but it doesn't look good.
Okey-dokey.
Since you're still
being so difficult,
let's charge up the
Pong Laser one more time.
[REI (GT)]
And our next target is...
Ooh!
Lots of people over there.
Nice.
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
Stop it!
No thanks!
Target.
Lock on.
[gasping, screaming]
[RANDOM WOMAN 12A]
Lady Neptune!
[RANDOM WOMAN 12B]
They captured her!
[RANDOM WOMAN 12C]
We're all done for!
[RANDOM WOMAN 12D]
What should we do?
I don't want to die!
It's okay!
Everyone, please calm down!
Neptune would never lose!
Just look,
she's lost already!
If she can't save
us, no one can!
Nepgear, no!
You can't do this.
I'm sorry.
The Share energy is unstable.
[UNI (BS)]
Enough with the gloomy face!
[yelling]
Rainy Ratnapura!
So this is your
"festival," huh?
A little violent, isn't it?
Noire!
And Vert!
I can't believe it!
Don't get too
sentimental on me just yet.
I'm only here to drop off 5pb.
Hi!
I guess I kept
you waiting, huh?
I don't mind!
And you brought 5pb, too!
Thanks for the lift, Uni.
Sure thing,
Miss Superstar.
Suppose it's time for
me to join the battle.
Give her a good
beating for me, too!
[RANDOM WOMAN 12E]
Is that 5pb?
[RANDOM WOMAN 12F]
In the flesh?
[5PB]
Hey everybody!
There's nothing
to be afraid of!
Believe in our goddesses okay?
[CROWD exclaiming]
[VERT (GT)] That's a rather
ostentatious piece of scenery
she's brought with her.
Might I ask who she is?
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
A goddess, apparently,
of the ancient
land of Tari.
Although I
couldn't tell you
how a country long dead
got so much Share energy.
[NOIRE (BH)]
It's that thing.
It's the same
device Eden had.
She's using it to
create Share energy.
That's simple enough.
I'm sure that three goddesses
can destroy one hunk of junk.
You guys focus
on the crystal!
Four on one, huh?
Hmph! Let's see if I can
do something about that.
What just happened?
I lost my gun.
How many dirty tricks
have you got up your sleeve?
What did you do to them?
Our Share energy.
That thing's stealing it.
[NOIRE (BH)]
So it's not creating energy;
it's stealing ours!
Yep, you got it.
Oh, and speaking of
stealing your energy,
it looks like I have enough now.
I do believe it's laser time.
No! Don't you dare!
Yeah, like I'm gonna stop
just because you said so.
Fire!
[RAM AND ROM (WS)]
Ice Sanctuary!
What?
[BLANC (WH)]
Sneak in under the laser
and she can't get
you with lightning.
Piece of cake.
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
Blanc!
Thanks, you guys!
You're the best!
Yep! We sure are.
'Cause now we're
playing with power!
Super power!
Like next gen!
I feel it.
Share energy!
It's coming back, Histoire!
Right!
That was beautiful.
Thank you!
It was the least I could do
after flipping out on you.
Once I cooled my head
and thought it over a bit,
it was obvious. That Eden's
machine was at fault, I mean.
[chuckling]
That's our Blanc, huh?
[VERT (GT)] Yes.
Quite incredible, as always,
and equally adept
at stealing the spotlight.
Hey, everybody!
Let us begin.
We have assembled
a true dream cast.
[REI laughing maniacally]
[REI (GT)]
Cute, but you're too late!
I mean, go ahead
and try to stop me,
but I've got
enough Share energy
to destroy the
whole stinkin' world.
[laughing maniacally]
"Destroy the world?"
But you said you wanted
my country, didn't you?
Yeah, I want it,
so I can blow the damn
place up and wreck your shit!
It's a humble wish, really.
Complete global
annihilation, I mean.
But why?
You're a goddess
too, aren't you?
Why, yes,
but not like you.
My subjects and I
didn't get along at all.
So I had to discipline them!
What does that mean?
Tari authorities cracked down
on any citizens who took
issue with its goddess.
The people stopped
believing in her,
so the nation lost its
Shares and fell to ruin.
Today, we call that
the "Great Crash."
Well, it sounds like
she got what she deserved.
[REI (GT)]
You're wrong!
Those ungrateful swine.
They stole my country from me!
And if I can't have it,
then nobody can!
[REI (GT)] Replenish energy
and prepare to fire!
I feel sorry for you.
I have friends,
but you were all alone.
[NEPTUNE (PH)] I wish that
things had been different.
But even if I sympathize,
I will never surrender!
[REI (GT)]
Ha!
You and your crappy friends
can hold hands
and sing songs
all the way to your graves,
'cause there's no way
you're blocking this one!
[laughing maniacally]
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
Vert.
Noire, as well.
Blanc, too.
All of our sisters.
Uni, Rom, Ram, Nepgear.
Our powers united,
we won't lose!
Trying to destroy
the Pongg Laser
before I can fire it, huh?
You better hope you're fast,
or everyone and their dog
down there is super screwed!
I'll send you flying
at the speed of light!
Kay, have a
nice trip, pal.
Eat this!
Sorry, but your plan
so totally blows!
I know we can count
on you, Neptune!
Yeah, right!
Too bad kid,
that ain't gonna work!
One final boost!
Now go!
[REI (GT)]
Damn it, close enough.
[yelling]
Your entire life's
been a mathematical error.
One that we're about to correct.
Oh screw you!
Cannon, fire!
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
Victory Slash!
My nation! You destroyed it.
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
Give it up.
Whatever you
hoped to accomplish,
it will never come to pass.
[NOIRE (BH)] I think it's
time for you to surrender.
All you did was
crash a big rock.
What makes you
think you've won this?
[laughing maniacally]
Why, what is this
glowing ball of energy
I have here?
What's that, Mr. Energy Ball?
You have the power to
blow up half the planet?
[laughing maniacally]
[VERT (GT)]
I'm almost impressed.
You certainly have an
astounding amount of hatred.
But that's not enough.
'Cause we have
something better than that.
Even if we didn't have
an ounce of Share energy
left, we would still fight.
Well spoken.
Because as goddesses,
we have a job to do.
Right, little sister?
Mm-hmm!
Y'know, once I kill you,
I can blow the
world up any time.
Fine, have it your way!
I'll be back.
I'm going, too!
I still have
some power left.
One more shot should wipe
them all out for sure.
Then recharge and wreck the
world, just as I planned.
[ARFOIRE]
I'm afraid that won't do.
After all, this planet
is going to be mine someday,
and I want it
in tip-top shape.
Piss off. Weirdo.
[WARECHU]
Okey-dokey, grandma.
It's all ready.
Sleep in the
murky depths of despair!
[REI (GT)]
Augh!
No! Don't take
my power away!
[screaming]
[WARECHU] After all the
trouble we went to
for those anticrystals,
we just end up using
them on this freak show.
Kind of a waste, huh?
Consider it
an act of whimsy.
[WARECHU] That's cute
for like, teenagers,
but for old ladies,
it's just irresponsible.
[NEPTUNE]
Wait!
Did you two save us?
[ARFOIRE]
I'm your enemy.
All I was saving was the world.
I see.
In that case,
I bet if the world could talk,
it would say,
"Thank you, Boudoir!"
[ARFOIRE] You still
don't know my name?
[giggling]
[HISTOIRE]
Thanks to your help,
we have recovered our
Shares and on this day
we are able to
celebrate the completion
of the brand new Neptower.
Are all of your Shares
back to normal as well?
I'm doing better than ever.
My Shares were
being siphoned by Tari.
The hearts of the people
never turned away from me
for an instant.
No problems
on my end, either.
That's good to hear.
Well let's begin
the ceremony, shall we?
[RAM (WS)]
Blanc!
[ROM (WS)] Hurry up
and tell her! You have to!
Hold on.
Neptune?
This is awkward.
So, listen, about before...
When you attacked me
for something I didn't do?
I'm sorry.
I thought you'd set up
the peace treaty
as a way to trick us.
I was so pissed
I lost my sense.
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
Well, to be honest,
I almost enjoyed fighting you.
It had been quite
a while, after all.
In fact, it gave
me a little idea.
[BLANC (WH)]
Yeah, what?
I'll tell you later, okay?
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
I've come to thank you
for your continued faith.
Thanks to you,
we've been able to
complete the new Neptower.
And of course,
Planeptune City
is steadily
recovering, as well.
Although I am the
face of this country,
you are its heart
and its strength.
I owe all this to you.
While we are gathered here.
I have one other announcement
that I would like to make.
Well, a moment, please.
I think it's better
to use this form after all.
So, um...
It's like, as Planeptune's
goddess, I, Neptune,
hereby declare that
the Friendship Treaty
is totally dissolved!
[gasping]
Who needs it?
We're buds anyhow, aren't we?
We can prove that without
some dumb piece of paper!
Right?
Noire?
Right, Vert?
Blanc?
I can agree to that.
Competing for our livelihood
as friends and as rivals.
Sounds rather
romantic, doesn't it?
I guess even you
can say something cool
once in a while.
If we're all in agreement,
then how about
an exhibition match?
Count me in!
My breasts sing with joy!
D'aw, wait for me!
I'm the main
character, you know!
Uni! C'mon!
Rom! Ram!
Just try to keep up!
Let's show 'em that
two sisters are better than one!
[ROM (WS)]
Mm-hmm!
Count me in!
I have a feeling
this is just going to be
more stress for me.