[humming]
Finally, some time to myself!
[NEPTUNE]
A-wuh-oh!
That was close!
I almost didn't make it there!
[PEASHY]
I'm bored!
Play with me, Neptuna!
I'll bonk you!
Look, P-ko,
we've been over this.
My name's not Neptuna;
it's Neptune, okay?
Learn it, live it, love it.
Neptuna, Neptuna!
[frustrated yelling]
Aww, dude!
If you do that, it's
gonna corrupt my save file!
Huh?
[screaming]
Now you have
to play with me!
[PEASHY laughing]
That's so cute.
Those two are
best buds, aren't they?
You think so?
Neptune looks more like
her punching bag to me.
So, Miss Histoire.
Have we still not found
that girl's guardian?
Afraid not.
And it's already
been three weeks, too.
Are you certain you don't
have any leads at all?
We're totally clueless.
Which is odd,
seeing as she seems to
know who Compa and I are.
[HISTOIRE]
The way this is going,
you make it sound
like we're lucky
to even know her name.
Well that was written
on her underwear,
and we had a pretty good idea
that wasn't the brand name.
I got you now!
Pea Punch!
--[boxing bell]
--[PEASHY giggling]
[VERT]
So are you comfy?
You can take a nap right here.
Wow, Vert. I just might.
Just call me "big sis."
It's all right.
I don't mind one bit.
But Neptune is my big sister.
Well, then again,
If we were sisters,
we could do this all the time,
--couldn't we?
--[VERT] Of course.
Uh, I'm not exactly sure
what I walked into here.
[COMPA] I think she's trying
to level her Lily Rank!
[NEPTUNE]
Gosh darn it, Vert!
Boobie time is over!
She's my sister!
Oh, I was just...
We're all friends
now, aren't we?
What's the harm in
spending some time together?
You want all that
sweet Nep to yourself!
But she's my Nep junior,
and don't you forget it, buddy!
There, there.
Neptune's just jealous
of what we have.
But don't worry,
give her some time and I'm
sure she'll turn around.
That's a good girl.
By the way,
the real truth is,
I came here for you.
Are you trying to make
a sister sandwich?
Oh my, how lewd!
[giggles mischievously]
That wasn't the plan.
I thought Blanc already
contacted you about this.
Huh?
Oh, did she?
Cute, huh?
This is Crachy, the
rabbit-eared bandicoot.
We just got him earlier today!
What a sweetie!
Ooh, can I hold him, too?
[NOIRE]
Well?
What was it you needed
to talk about?
[BLANC] Network defense,
now that we've gotten
our little animal
crossing out of the way.
Ah-ha!
You want to use our
airtight security
as a model for yours, huh?
Uh...
I can't blame you.
After all, it's an
impregnable firewall
built by a crack staff
I spared no expense to hire!
So is the satellite system
that recently
went into operation
protected by that, as well?
[NOIRE]
Of course,
and I don't mind licensing
the technology to you.
But it's not going to
be free, understand?
Actually, one of the
satellites was recently hacked.
From a Lastation
server, it seems.
No way!
Oh, good.
--Now that you're listening--
--[NOIRE] Ludicrous!
The security being compromised
is about as likely as
someone falling from the sky
and landing on me!
[distant screaming]
Move, move, move, move,
move, move, move, move, move!
Hurry!
Uh, hey guys!
Nothing weird here!
[NOIRE]
Unbelievable!
I've come to expect a certain
level of jackassery from you,
but this over the limit.
[NEPTUNE]
Yeah, so funny story--
P-ko decided to throw
a mid-air temper tantrum,
so I lost my
transformation and fell.
[NOIRE]
How typically clownish.
[NEPGEAR]
We're really sorry.
Oh, P-ko,
introduce yourself!
Call me Pea!
Wow, Neptune.
You have a child
this old already?
It's crazy, I know,
but she's my little girl
and I just love her to bits!
Wait, no!
She's a lost kid and we're
taking care of her at my place.
I was making a joke.
Whoa!
I guess you have a
sense of humor after all!
[BLANC] Rom, Ram, play
nice with the little urchin.
'Kay!
You want to play with us?
Mm-hmm! You bet I do!
[laughing]
[RAM]
I'm gonna catch you!
Now, back to the
subject at hand.
We should really take
this somewhere else.
Uni, I'm leaving you
in charge while I'm out.
[UNI]
Nepgear, by the way,
Could I get your
advice on something?
[NEPGEAR] Noire's
acting strange? Like how?
[UNI]
Well,
she's been closing herself off
in the office every
night doing... something.
[NEPGEAR] And you're
sure it's not just work?
[UNI] If it was that,
then she wouldn't lock the door.
And sometimes, I hear this
weird laugh coming from inside.
Whatever it is, I'm worried.
Then you're asking
me to help you
so you can find out
what's happening in there,
is that it?
If you have any ideas,
that'd be great.
Yeah, sure,
I have just the thing!
It's kind of a coincidence
that I brought it.
[UNI]
Hm?
A camera?
It's a wireless remote
video transmitter--
only it's super tiny
and super discreet!
So you're saying it's a
hidden camera, then?
It's an HD hidden camera
that can stream high-quality
footage with essentially no lag!
Isn't that cool?
I've been dying
for an excuse
to set this up somewhere!
Can I? Can I?
--I can, right?
--Uh, oh, boy.
[laughing]
What the hell's so funny?
I must have missed the joke.
Oh, come on.
You were all bragging
about it, remember?
"Lastations security is the
awesomest in the whole world!"
Then, derp! You got hacked!
Too funny!
Hardly any point
crying over spilt milk.
Just make sure it
doesn't happen again.
Simple.
No, I'm going to
find who did this
and tear them limb from limb.
Uh-oh!
Noire is in rage mode!
Conveniently, I
summoned someone here
to deal with this
very situation.
You can come in now!
[VERT]
This is Setag,
ultra-genius programmer
and pride of Leanbox!
It's really her!
Wait, who?
She was made for the anime!
Indeed, I am a brand
new character, bing.
I'll worm my way
into your heart, bing.
Bing? What?
Her catchphrase thing
is totally lame!
Man, this character is
gonna bomb with the fans!
There is no
need to worry.
I'm a one-off character made
just for this scene, bing.
Whoever you are,
think you can track
down the hacker or not?
Of course.
Leave it to me, bing.
Here looks good.
Or maybe we'd get a
better angle from this side.
You certainly seem to
be enjoying yourself.
[ROM]
Oh no, run away!
[PEASHY]
You can't get me!
[NEPGEAR]
A little further back.
[RAM]
You wanna bet?
Perfect!
[NEPGEAR]
Oh, look! It's working!
Wow, you weren't
kidding about the picture.
Isn't it gorgeous?
It uses a new compression
format called NEPEG-4
that gives you an HD
stream with no artifacting
and without using
too much bandwidth.
Um, uh-oh.
Is something wrong?
Even if this works,
the whole plan just
feels kind of wrong.
Please, let's nix
this camera thing, okay?
Yeah, okay.
[UNI]
Don't go over there!
Noire will get mad if
you touch anything!
[static noise]
It keeps messing up.
There's interference.
Wait, but that can't
possibly be true, can it?
That would mean there's another
hidden camera in the room!
[UNI]
What?
What?!
[PEASHY giggling]
[NEPGEAR] Seems like
it should be nearby,
but I can't get a read.
Ugh, I'm so mad!
Nobody spies on
my sister, you hear?
And if they do,
they're in for a thrashing!
Why do I feel like that
comment was directed at me?
[UNI] Well?
Which building is it?
Come on, hurry it up!
Yes, captain!
This only gives
a general location.
It's hard to pinpoint.
Fine!
We'll comb the
buildings one by one!
By the way,
why do you have
a tracking device?
That's kind of weird.
Another coincidence?
[NEPGEAR] Oh, no,
I always carry this.
I mean, mobile energy
generators and signal tracers
are must-haves for all
girls, don't you think?
Not any girls from
this dimension.
[PEASHY]
I'm hungry!
Gimme food now!
Oh. That's no good.
What should we do?
You should feed me,
you big dummy, right now!
[RAM] Aww, Peashy,
you're such a baby!
I'm hungry too,
but I'm a big girl.
That means I can wait
'til it's dinnertime to eat.
Without crying, naturally.
I'm big, too, so there!
So then you can
wait with us?
Yeah, fine.
I'll try not to starve.
You're so mature.
Wow, Rom and Ram
are really on the ball!
As soon as someone
younger than them shows up,
they go into big sister mode.
Oh, hey.
[NEPGEAR]
Speaking of big sisters!
That's funny.
[NEPTUNE (PH)] Noire, are
you sure it's necessary
for us to do this?
Couldn't you have left it
to the soldiers instead?
Sure, but what would
be the fun in that?
I'll tear that bastard
a new one for what he did!
No one makes a fool out
of me and gets away with it!
Noire's rather savage
today, isn't she?
You won't hear any
complaints from me.
Whoa. That's the place?
So our hacker is operating
out of this old dump?
Okay!
Let's beat the bad guy!
What the heck
is wrong with you?
If he hears you yelling,
he might run away!
[NEPTUNE]
Hold up there,
are you really the
right person to say that?
[UNI] This is where
they went, right?
[NEPGEAR]
Looks like it.
Maybe they're after
the Peeping Tom, too,
so we can just kind
of not go in there.
[shrieking]
--Crachy, no!
--Get back here,
you naughty bandicoot!
Peashy, wait,
come back!
Don't you move an inch!
Hands in the air!
Turn around and face me slowly!
Fess up!
You're the hacker,
now, aren't you?
[ROBOT sighing]
Answer me,
or I'll cut you!
[ROBOT] Aww, don't talk
like we're strangers, sister!
[ROBOT] Just call me Anny!
'Kay, girlfriend?
[NEPTUNE]
Nep whaat?
A flaming robot?
But you look so manly!
[ANONYDEATH] My metal gear
may be solid snake,
but my heart is as
maidenly as they come!
Oh wow, he's a
walking stereotype.
I bet he has an acerbic wit
and gives great advice, too.
How charming.
[ANONYDEATH]
Guilty as charged, sweetie!
I thought you were all
boobs and no brains,
but maybe not!
Listen, your gender
identity is irrelevant here.
Are you the hacker or not?
Just spit it out!
[ANONYDEATH chuckling]
What's so funny?
[ANONYDEATH] You're even
cuter in person, Noire.
In fact, I could
just eat you up!
Huh?
Wait, is that supposed
to be flattery, or a threat?
I may be queer, but
let me lay it straight.
I'm hot for you.
[ANONYDEATH]
I'm a voyeur, honey!
So sue me!
[screaming]
Look, that's Noire!
And that one's Noire, too!
They're all Noire!
Peashy! Where are you?
[ROM]
Crachy!
[UNI] Where could
they have run off to?
Peashy!
[ANONYDEATH] I'm like, your
biggest fan, Noire!
I just wanted to see
more of you, that's all!
It was an impulse crime!
[NOIRE] I couldn't care less
about all the stupid photos!
I'm mad because you
hacked my system and--
[ANONYDEATH]
You really don't care?
Not even about these?
[screaming]
Noire's sewing like
somebody's mom!
It does seem rather
uncharacteristic.
Well, my secret is out!
Deep down, I'm just
like an old housewife!
[laughs nervously]
I feel like I've seen
that outfit before.
You've got some imagination,
you crazy goddess, you!
Anyway, like I told you,
that's not why I'm here!
[ANONYDEATH]
Oh?
You're not even here for these?
[snaps]
[screaming]
Whoa, check it out!
Upon inspection,
they're cosplay photos.
So that was a Four
Goddesses Online costume--
that's why I recognized it.
Stop looking!
[ANONYDEATH] OMG, you're cute
when you totally flip out!
Exclusive!
That is enough!
You big metal turdbox!
I am gonna throw you in jail!
[ANONYDEATH]
My goodness!
What language!
Well, you can arrest me,
but just so you know,
if I leave here,
all the photos will be
automatically published online.
[NOIRE]
What?
[ANONYDEATH] At first I was
going to keep them
all to myself,
but then I got to thinking
how fun it would be
to plaster the whole world
with your cute
little cosplay selfies!
This is quite the dilemma.
If such compromising
photos were published...
...she would be too
embarrassed to show her face.
Nah, it's cool, yo.
She looks cute, so no prob.
You need acting lessons.
Y'know what? Fine!
Go ahead and publish them!
All it'll cost you...
...is your life!
[ANONYDEATH]
Heaven or hell,
let's rock!
You creep!
[yelling]
They're coming from above!
[ANONYDEATH]
It's been fun, sweetie pie.
And don't worry, I was lying
about publishing the pics!
Toodles!
Oh no you don't!
[ANONYDEATH] Let them wreck the
hideout, what do I care?
I got to meet
Noire in the flesh!
Dreams really do come true!
[ANONYDEATH]
Hmm?
Oh, heavens, it's
some sort of rodent!
Shoo! Shoo, you awful thing!
Hey, Crachy!
[startled yell]
Look! It's Peashy
and Crachy, guys!
[NEPGEAR]
Peashy, you know better!
We're sorry, Sir.
[UNI]
I hope you're not hurt.
[ANONYDEATH] You should
teach this little beast
some discipline.
Wait.
Peashy? Is that your name?
Peashy?
Mm-hmm!
Call me Pea!
Hey, this is Noire.
[gasps]
So you're the Peeping Tom!
[ANONYDEATH]
Oh, poo!
I just had to print out
my favorites, didn't I?
You're so gonna pay.
[feminine scream]
Get real, tin can.
Did you think
I wouldn't chase you?
Uni? You're here?
Uh, it's a long story.
[ANONYDEATH]
Okay, okay. I give up.
This is lovely, but he never
did admit to the hacking.
Well, as long as
he's locked up,
that's no longer a concern.
Besides, Noire has more
pressing matters on her mind.
Don't look!
You didn't see, did you?
Oh, no, we saw something,
--but not--
--[RAM] I saw! I saw everything!
So what's "cosplay"? Looks fun!
[whiny shriek]
What are you guys
even doing here?
It's like you came by
just to laugh at me!
[NOIRE]
I am so done with this!
Listen, you forget
everything you saw here
or I'm going to beat it out of
you, do you understand me?
And c'mon, Uni, really?
Hey, P-ko.
Ta-da!
You want some pudding?
I snuck it here in my pocket.
You bet!
I'm super hungry!
'Kay. But you have
to share it with me.
'Kay!
Half for me and half for you!
[ANONYDEATH]
Hi, it's me.
I found the girl.
Kind of a pain in
the fanny, though.
I went to the trouble
of hacking that satellite
and then she literally
just runs into me.
What?
Hmm, good point.
[NOIRE]
So, uh, Uni.
You probably think
cosplaying is creepy, don't you?
If you don't like it,
it's okay. I can quit.
No way.
I think that it's great.
I'm just happy you
have time to do it.
That means work isn't
ruining your life, right?
[NOIRE]
Actually,
everything's been great lately.
[UNI]
And I sort of thought
maybe that's because I've gotten
at least the tiniest bit useful?
I could be wrong.
Yeah, I'm not so
sure about that.
That is to say it's
not a tiny bit at all.
I depend on you
a lot these days.
Don't tease me like that!
[giggling]
[FEMALE VOICE]
Move, move!
Hurry! I'm gonna crash!
[yelling]
Uh-oh, that sounds
like bad news!
Nep-whiggity-what?
Ow, that hurt!
Who are you?
Uh...
Oh! Who am I?
Call me Plutia.
It's nice to meet all of you.
I'm from Planeptune,
by the way.
I am the Goddess there.
[NEPTUNE]
Uh...
...what?
[giggling]
That's just ludicrous!
My security being compromised
is about as likely as
someone falling from the sky
and landing on me!
[distant yelling]
[NEPTUNE]
Move, hurry!
Oh, crap!
FYI, I was not standing
in the wrong place!