♪
[5PB] ♪ Shine for me,
star of hopes and dreams ♪
[BACKUP SINGERS]
♪ Let's find it ♪
[5PB] ♪ I swear that you
can always count on me ♪
♪ And I'll always
rise above ♪
♪ Because I won't
lose to anyone! ♪
[crowd cheers]
[5PB] ♪ Blue skies as far
as you can see... ♪
5pb certainly lives
up to her reputation.
She's the true
siren of Leanbox.
Totally!
[5PB] ♪ Stay here, behold
the beauty all around you ♪
♪ Come, take my hand,
let's see them again ♪
♪ The kindness in your heart,
the warm touch of your skin ♪
[BACKUP SINGERS]
♪ Bring them back to me ♪
[5PB] ♪ We may be far apart
right now, but someday... ♪
♪ Shine for me,
star of hopes and dreams ♪
[BACKUP SINGERS]
♪ Let's find it ♪
[5PB] ♪ My will is strong,
there's nothing too extreme ♪
♪ To win your heart ♪
[BACKUP SINGERS]
♪ Bifrost, Glazy Star ♪
[5PB] ♪ Destiny,
written in the skies ♪
[BACKUP SINGERS]
♪ Let's find it ♪
[5PB] ♪ Always meant to be,
I'll make them realize ♪
♪ That I'll always
rise above ♪
♪ Because I won't
lose to anyone! ♪
[crowd cheers]
[WARECHU] Ugh. This concert
or whatever is way too loud.
Don't they know people are
trying to get work done?
[singing continues,
muffled in background]
[device beeps]
Beyond that, why would
anyone send a mouse
on a deep sea dive, anyway?
Chumps are gonna start
calling me "sea mouse,"
which is way too close
to "sea louse."
I finally found it!
[crowd cheers]
Thanks, everyone!
You guys are the best.
Now, up next...
"Dimension Tripper"!
[NOIRE] It was nice
of Vert to invite us
to the concert and all.
But rather odd
that she didn't bother
coming along herself!
What kind of host does that?
[BLANC] I'm sure she has
a perfectly good reason.
[NOIRE] So, which one
is Vert's room, anyway?
Here! This one's unlocked!
Oh!
[ALL gasp]
[COMPA] What happened here?
This place is a mess!
[BLANC] Looks like
it's been ransacked.
Actually, I think she's
just an incredible slob.
Whoa! That one says
"Not recommended
for players under 18"!
Hey! Watch what
you're saying, okay?
We've got some
impressionable kids here!
[NEPGEAR]
Ah...!
[VERT] Oh, come on! What's the
rear guard doing out there?
[NEPGEAR]
Huh?
[VERT] Fine.
I'll cover you myself.
No, I'll be fine.
You go on without me.
What the--? Oh, poo!
Ah! Found her!
They're fast! These guys
are just way too fast!
Vert, what are you doing?
Ah--! No, please!
Not there! Ohh...
Looks like she's
playing MMOs again.
"Four Goddesses Online," huh?
Yo! Miss MMO junkie.
Oh! Oh, whoops! I welcome
you to Leanbox, ladies!
I apologize that I'm a bit
tied up at the moment.
Yeah, right. You stood
us up at the concert
to play some game, didn't you?
I logged in intending to play
for an hour before heading out,
but then a castle siege
started and, well, you know.
I couldn't very well leave
in the middle of that.
I seem to recall you
saying something about
throwing a little party for us
after the concert was over.
Oh. Well, it won't
be much longer
before we take the castle.
So, after that, then?
Now you reveal
your true nature.
Just remember, it takes all
kinds to make up a world.
Serious Goddess fail!
You might be even worse
at your job than I am!
[NOIRE &amp; BLANC]
Not even close.
Come on! This is what
you finally agree on?
What should we do?
It looks like this could
seriously take a while.
Hm. What, indeed?
Right! Everyone help
set up for the party!
Aw! Can't I just
fart around instead?
Enough complaining! We came all
the way out here to Leanbox
and we're not leaving
without a proper party.
Now listen up, everyone!
Nepgear, IF, Compa.
You three go out
and buy the food!
[ALL THREE]
Right! Yes, ma'am!
The rest of us will
clean up this disaster.
Go! Move it like
you're on a mission!
Ha! There she goes!
Shouting out orders in full-on
bossy pants mode again!
I think someone
flipped her crazy switch.
Be quiet!
Get to work!
Chop-chop!
♪
I guess Ge-Ge and Iffy aren't
done with everything just yet.
Aw, man, if I don't
hurry up and get back,
the hag's gonna be
all over my case!
Aah!
Whaa...!
[COMPA]
Huh?
Ouchie... A face-plant is not
what I needed right now... Hm?
[COMPA]
Aw... Ah? Ahh...
[WARECHU]
Ahhh...!
Hey! What are you staring at?
Does it give you
some kind of sick pleasure to
watch a mouse trip and fall?
Of course not! Just wanted
to make sure you're okay.
[WARECHU]
Ahhh...!
Ah! Oh, no! It looks like
you got yourself a scrape!
Here, let me help.
[WARECHU]
Ahhh...!!
I'll put this
on your boo-boo.
[echoing] I'll put this
on your boo-boo...
Put this on your boo-boo...
[WARECHU]
Chu... Chu... Chu...
There you go. That
should take care of it.
[WARECHU]
Chu, chu, chu!!
I'll be leaving now, Mister
Mouse. Be careful, 'kay?
[WARECHU] Sure.
I will, thanks.
And have a
pleasant afternoon.
Hey, wait, wait!
Hold on a second!
Hm? Yes, what is it?
Uh... I, uh... Could you
tell me your name?
That is, if you
don't mind, I mean.
Hm? Oh! It's Compa!
Ahh...! Pleased to
meet you, Compa.
And what a beautiful name.
[NEPGEAR]
Hm?
[NEPGEAR gasps]
[COMPA]
Huh?
[NEPGEAR pants]
[COMPA]
Ge-Ge?
Hey! Get your hands off
of that! Chu, chu, chu!
Oh, no, are you okay?
What happened?
I'm not sure. I just kind of
went limp all of a sudden.
It could be anemia.
Although... I've never heard
of a goddess showing signs
of anything like that before.
[WARECHU]
Chu, chu, chu...
[IF]
Huh?
[WARECHU]
Chu, chu, chu, chu...
Whoa, that was a close one.
Can't believe that
was a CPU's sister.
Whatever, who cares
about her, anyway?
Now, Compa on the other hand.
She's an angel! Chu!
My apologies! Sorry to keep
you waiting, everyone!
I'd like to take
this opportunity
to welcome you to
my house party!
You must be joking.
You didn't contribute anything.
Let it go.
It'll fall on deaf ears.
I heard you got dizzy
earlier. Are you okay?
Yeah. It was nothing, I'm fine.
[VERT]
Come on, everyone!
I'd like for us all to relax
and eat, drink, and be merry!
Why, I've prepared
a special game
for this very occasion, in fact.
Ooh! Really? What is it?
[VERT] I think in this
case it would be easier
to show you than to tell you.
Neptune, Noire,
if you don't mind.
I'd like for you to back
up just a bit, please.
You got it!
Hm? What for?
All right. Why don't you show
us a bit of fighting spirit?
Aah! Awesome!
Look at Nep-Nep!
Dude! What happened
to me? I'm a Dogoo!
I can't believe it!
Is this really me?
I'm using a special
camera to capture
your expressions and
movements. It then processes
and holo-projects them. You can
also use it to search the net.
So I just use my lame, armless
goo body to attack Noire?
Okay, Noigoo, get ready!
I'll nep you until
you're black and blue!
Whoa. And who are you
calling "Noigoo," huh?
Wah!
Yay! The first
point goes to me!
Now you've done it,
impertinent little slime!
Say your prayers, Nep-goo!
Upside-down Noigoo!
Incidentally, I've also
prepared a simulation mode
geared more toward
real battle,
so you can use this for
combat training as well.
That's neat.
Yeah! It sounds fun!
I wanna play, too!
You can absolutely play
as much as you like.
[WARECHU]
Chu... Chu... Chu...
You're late! Are you trying to
undermine our entire plan?
[WARECHU] Gimme a break!
I came as fast
as my stumpy mouse legs would
carry me! It's your fault
for making the deadlines
too tight, you old hag!
How many times do I have
to tell you not to talk
to your master like that?
No, never mind. I'm not going
to dignify the complaints of
some filthy rat with a response.
Hand over the goods and
let's be done with this.
[WARECHU] Yeah,
yeah, here you go.
Now we have four of them.
And tonight,
as the world sleeps,
the rules for the game of
life will be rewritten.
[energetic chatter]
Yes, what is it? We're in
the middle of a party here.
[WORKER] Lady Vert...
I'm afraid that...
[VERT]
Ah--!
What's wrong?
It's over already?
What is it, Vert?
Did something happen?
Yes. I was just told of a
reported mass monster breakout.
The sighting occurred at
a waste disposal facility
over in Zune District.
[BLANC] Zune District, huh?
That's a long way from here.
It's an island that's
only connected
to the mainland at low tide.
[NEPTUNE] What's the big deal?
Monsters pop up all the time!
True, but that's not
the case in this district.
It's under state supervision.
However... The reports
do seem to be accurate.
Sorry to break up the party,
but I should go.
[NEPTUNE] Wait,
I'm coming with you!
Thank you, but...
there's no need
to get involved in my
country's problems.
The way I see it,
fate brought us together,
and this must be the reason.
Come on, let us help!
So let me guess. This is
your "We signed a treaty,
so we're comrades"
thing again, isn't it?
Yeah, pretty much.
[BLANC] I'm coming, too.
You can think of it
as my way of saying thanks for
your help with the kidnapping.
Alright, then!
It's a party of three!
[NOIRE] You're not
leaving without me!
There's no way of
knowing how long
you three would keep the
rest of us waiting here.
You're certain?
Alright, then. It's the
four goddesses together!
[NEPGEAR] Excuse me.
Let me help. Okay?
Uh... I-I'm coming, too!
[RAM]
Me too!
[ROM]
Me too, please.
[BLANC] I'm sorry, but you
can't. This isn't a game.
[RAM]
Ohh...
[NOIRE] Uni, you
stay behind, too.
You can't even properly
transform yet.
[NEPTUNE] Nepgear! Just leave
this one to the big sisters.
Sometimes we gotta
show off, you know?
Okay.
Thanks, and now that
that's settled... Transform!
Alright, everyone.
It's time we move out.
[WARECHU] Well, they're all
random encounter trash,
but I gotta admit, there
sure are a lot of them!
[ARFOIRE]
It was necessary.
How else could I lure all four
CPUs all the way out here?
[ARFOIRE giggles]
I hope they don't
keep us waiting.
[ROM] Miss Nepgear?
Are you okay?
Oh! Yes, I'm fine,
thanks for asking.
I'm just worried about
Sis and the others.
But why would you be worried?
Is your sister weak, Nepgear?
Mm-mm. No, that's not it.
When she gets serious,
she becomes really strong!
Since I'm the weak one,
she's always been there
when I need her to protect me.
But today...
something's different.
Today I feel really
uneasy for some reason.
You feel uneasy?
I see. Uh-huh.
Okay, thanks, Otome.
That confirms it.
I knew something was going on.
You mean about
the monster attack?
That mouse from the
mall earlier today.
I had seen him before. So I
asked a fellow Guild member
working intelligence
to check it out.
Sure enough, that mouse is
on every country's blacklist.
He is likely up to no good.
He's considered a very
suspicion person, er, mouse.
What? Are you saying that...
that Mister Mouse is a bad guy?
I'm sad to hear that.
And that's not
all we discovered.
It seems he took a boat out to
Zune District a few hours ago.
So what are you saying?
While I don't have
solid proof, I'm saying
that those monsters popping
up there wasn't a coincidence.
He's up to something,
and we need to know what.
There's still time for
me to make the low tide.
I'm going. We need to get
to the bottom of this.
[NEPGEAR]
Take me with you.
Please! I'm worried
and I want to help!
What? There's no way.
I can't risk exposing
you to danger, too.
I can't stand this, IF!
Let me come! I'm begging you!
There it is. Just up ahead.
Damn! That is a ton of monsters.
There may be many, but they
all look low-level to me.
I think you're right.
Still, we can't let them
make it into town.
We need to kill them
here before they--
[ALL gasp]
Looks like they've
got a few big ones!
They'll make worthy
enemies, at least.
Perfect. That makes
one for each of us.
Time to race!
[BLANC (WH)] You're not
stealin' a march on me!
You three! Hold up!
The textbook method here
is to stick together and
take them one at a time!
What a spineless textbook.
Honestly, once
they transform,
they turn into a bunch
of fighting vipers!
But... I can't really
say I'm any different!
Alright. Here's the deal.
Don't take any risks,
understand me? If you feel
the least bit threatened,
retreat to safety
right away.
Okay. You got it.
Thanks, IF.
[NOIRE (BH)]
Lace Ribbon Dance!
That puts me
in first place.
Take this! Tanzerin Trombe!
Well, crap.
Looks like I'm second.
They don't appear
to be done just yet.
[VERT (GH)] All right.
Rainy Ratnapura!
[NEPTUNE (PH)]
Cross Combination!
I think we can
call that a tie.
Which would mean
that they're both last.
Well, technically speaking,
I was just a tiny bit faster.
All right. Last place
is fine with me, then.
Noire! Blanc!
What is this?
Don't screw with me!
These little
bastards are fast!
They won't stop me!
[ARFOIRE giggles]
Looks like it's time.
She must be
behind this!
Alright, CPUs. Time to
fall to my sanctuary!
[NEPTUNE (PH) groans]
What's going on?
What's this light?
My power is dropping!
It's that stone.
We have to destroy it!
Nothing powered by
Share energy can get
anywhere near that stone.
No weapon, nor CPU herself.
Consider it the
perfect net to ensnare
Goddesses such
as yourselves.
What? I've never heard
of such a power.
The stone is known
as an "Anticrystal."
It severs the much-needed link
you have with the Sharicite,
thereby stripping
you of your power.
An Anticrystal?
Heh heh. These are some great
pics! Once they're made public,
they're gonna create
a worldwide sensation!
You sneaky little bastard!
I'll stop you. I won't let
you get away with this!
As soon as I'm free,
you two are dead!
[ARFOIRE] Awfully optimistic,
aren't you? A goddess's power
bleeds away inside the
Anticrystal field, you know.
Which means that your
chances of escape
are plummeting
by the second.
[ARFOIRE laughs]
It's really quiet.
Maybe they've already
wiped out the monsters.
It doesn't look like it.
Where is everyone?
IF, look! Up ahead!
[ALL struggle]
Neptune, no!
You're watching Nepstation!
We're joining you
live from the studio.
And today we have a guest!
Hi, I'm 5pb.
I hope you'll pick up my latest
single "Dimension Tripper"!
This isn't stealth marketing.
This is shameless marketing!