- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- THAT SHOULD DO IT.
IN ORDER TO HAVE
INNER PEACE,
IT IS NECESSARY TO HAVE
A BEAUTIFUL ATMOSPHERE.
- ( meows )
- ( sighs )
( grunts )
- HUH?
SORRY, TINA.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, I'M FINE.
- HEY, WHAT'S WITH THIS
HUGE PACKAGE HERE?
- ( chuckles nervously )
WELL, THIS IS...
- HUH?
- AAH!
- UH...
- HUH?
( chuckles )
- WOW, A FERRET.
HOW ADORABLE.
- ISN'T IT?
I GOT IT PRETTY CHEAP
AT THE PET SHOP
I ALWAYS GO TO.
THE VERY FIRST TIME
I SAW THAT CUTE LITTLE FACE,
I JUST KNEW I WOULDN'T
BE ABLE TO LEAVE WITHOUT IT.
HEY, DON'T YOU THINK
IT LOOKS LIKE KAORU?
- OH?
- HUH?
- ( giggles )
- ANYWAY, WHAT WILL
YOU DO WITH IT?
- THAT'S SOMETHING I HAVE TO
ASK YOU, MISS LANDLORD?
- OH?
- SEE? HE LIKES TO
PLAY AROUND LIKE THIS.
WOULDN'T YOU JUST LOVE TO KEEP
A FUR PET TOO, MISS LANDLORD?
- OH MY, IT'S SO DARLING.
- SHE'S ALREADY WON OVER.
HEY, I WONDER WHAT
MISS MIYABI WILL SAY.
- Both: OH.
- ABSOLUTELY NOT.
- ( chuckles )
MISS MANAGER.
- I THOUGHT IT WAS
A LITTLE ROWDY,
BUT THEN TO BRING
SUCH A THING INDOORS.
AND WHAT WERE YOU THINKING
WHEN YOU THOUGHT YOU COULD
RAISE THAT THING HERE?
FIRST OF ALL,
HAVING A PET HERE
WILL GET THE ROOMS DIRTY,
NOT TO MENTION THE SMELL.
YOU SHOULD THINK ABOUT WHAT
WILL HAPPEN IN THE FUTURE.
IS THAT PERFECTLY
UNDERSTOOD?
AS THE MANAGER,
I HAVE THE RESPONSIBILITY
OF MAINTAINING
THIS PLACE.
( groans )
THAT TICKLES.
RETURN THIS THING AT ONCE.
- ( sighs )
- MISS MIYABI?
- HMM?
- IS THERE NO WAY
THAT WE CAN KEEP IT?
ITS ADORABLE.
- ( sighs )
- MISS MIYABI...
- BUT THIS IS ALSO
A MATTER OF MISS MINAZUKI'S TIME
SINCE SHE'LL BE
TAKING CARE OF IT.
- Taeko: WOW, HOW CUTE!
WE'LL BE KEEPING
A FERRET HERE?
- UH-HUH.
- THAT'S GREAT!
- UHH...
( groans )
ALL RIGHT.
DO WHAT YOU LIKE THEN,
BUT I'LL HAVE ABSOLUTELY
NO PART OF THIS.
- ( door slams )
- ( all sigh )
- YEAH, ALL RIGHT!
- HOORAY!
- YEAH!
- WE GET TO KEEP IT!
- ( scoffs )
- Tina: NOW THAT THAT'S SETTLED,
LET'S GIVE IT A HOME.
- Both: HUH?
- WELL, ISN'T IT AWESOME?
I FIGURED IT WOULD BE
PRETTY LONELY
SLEEPING IN
AN EMPTY CAGE.
- ( hisses )
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- HEY, WHY'S THAT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
KAORU?
IT DOESN'T WANT
A BORING CAGE LIKE THAT.
- Kaoru: THESE THINGS
NEED TO BE BORING.
- ( groans )
- SORRY TO
KEEP YOU WAITING.
I'LL MAKE THE FERRET
A NICE FLUFFY BED RIGHT NOW--
WHOA!
- KAORU-SAMA?
- HUH, YEAH-- WHAT?
( grunts )
- I'M SORRY.
THAT WAS SOME
LINGERIE OF MINE.
- MY GOODNESS.
- Taeko: IS THIS ALL RIGHT?
MAYBE IT'S STILL TOO HOT.
- Tina:
YEAH, DRINK IT ALL UP.
- WOW, LOOK AT IT GO.
- OHH.
( chuckles )
IT MUST HAVE BEEN
VERY HUNGRY.
- YEAH, OR MAYBE
THAT STUFF'S DELICIOUS.
- AWW.  YOU'RE SUCH
A GOOD LITTLE FERRET.
DRINK AS MUCH AS YOU CAN
SO YOU CAN
GROW UP HEALTHY.
- AOI-CHAN WILL MAKE
A GOOD MOTHER
WHEN SHE HAS
KIDS SOME DAY.
- ( giggles )
- ( chuckles )
- Aoi: KAORU-SAMA?
- YEAH?
- IS THERE SOMETHING
THE MATTER WITH YOU?
- NO, NO.
IT'S NOTHING.
- OH.
- ( Tina laughs )
- ( sighs )
- Tina: WATCH THIS!
THIS IS FUNNY.
- ( sighs )
- TA-DA!
FISHING FOR FERRETS.
( laughing )
- ( all laugh )
- IT REALLY IS ADORABLE.
BY THE WAY,
WHAT SHOULD WE NAME IT?
- A NAME?
- YES.
IT NEEDS A NAME.
CAN ANYONE THINK
OF A GOOD ONE?
- LET ME SEE...
WHAT KIND OF NAME
WOULD SOUND COOL?
- All: HMM.
- ( squeaks )
- OH.
DO YOU HAVE ANY SUGGESTIONS,
MISS MIYABI?
- HUH?
ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THAT CREATURE
I'LL HAVE NO PART OF.
- ( all sigh )
- ( squeaks )
- ( sighs )
IT CERTAINLY WAS
A CHAOTIC DAY.
HONESTLY,
AND NO INNER PEACE
TO BE FOUND ANYWHERE.
( sighs )
AN ANIMAL.
OF ALL THINGS...
- ( squeaks )
- HUH?
( gasps )
MISS TINA!
- Tina: OH, SO THIS IS
WHERE THE FERRET WAS.
- ( Miyabi groans )
- ( Tina chuckles )
HMM.
- HEY, TINA.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
- OH, IT'S MISSING AGAIN.
- ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT THE FERRET?
- YEAH.
I THINK IT WOULD BE BAD
IF IT PLAYED PRANKS
ON THE MANAGER AGAIN.
KAORU!
PLEASE HELP ME
LOOK FOR IT, OKAY?
- HMM.
- ( knocks on door )
- MISS MIYABI,
HOW ABOUT SOME TEA?
MISS MIYABI?
- THAT'S STRANGE.
I'M POSITIVE THAT'S WHERE
I HAD LEFT IT EARLIER.
- IS SOMETHING THE MATTER,
MISS MIYABI?
- LADY AOI.
NO, IT'S REALLY NOT ANYTHING
ALL THAT IMPORTANT.
I JUST CAN'T FIND THE
FOUNTAIN PEN I LEFT HERE.
- FOUNTAIN PEN.
- HUH?
- ( murmurs )
- DAMN YOU!
- ( gasps )
OH NO.  IT HAS TO BE
WITH THE MANAGER.
- WE'RE A LITTLE TOO LATE,
I GUESS.
- WHERE DID YOU GO?
- ( squeaks )
- ( screams )
OW.
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- MISS MINAZUKI,
GRAB THAT THING!
- HUH?
OH!
AAH!
- LEAVE THIS TO ME.
( chuckles )
- OH!
- THAT'S NOT IT.
- OH?
( yelps )
OH!  OH, NO DON'T!
OH!  OOH, NO. NOT THERE.
- AOI-CHAN.
- ( giggles )
THAT TICKLES.
- COME BACK HERE, YOU!
- ( crashing )
- Taeko: OH, THE VASE!
- Kaoru: OH, OW!
- Aoi: KAORU-SAMA?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- Tina: OH!
ITS PEEING OVER HERE.
- Miyabi: DAMN IT,
COME BACK HERE!
- Kaoru: OH, BROTHER.
IT SURE MADE
A MESS OF THINGS.
- ( sighs )
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
I WON'T ALLOW ANYMORE!
- ( all gasp )
- HUH?
- ( girls gasp )
- YOU THERE!
COME BACK HERE.
- AND THERE SHE GOES.
- BOY, THE MANAGER
SURE IS SCARY RIGHT NOW.
- YEAH.  BECAUSE SHE'S
TOTALLY ANGRY.
- ITS ALL RIGHT.
I'M SURE THAT MISS MIYABI
WILL BE UNDERSTANDING.
( sighs )
- Miyabi:
STAY STILL ALREADY!
DAMN YOU, FERRET!
OH!  GO TO HELL!
( grunts )
IT APPEARS YOU'VE
FINALLY GIVEN UP.
THERE ISN'T
ANYWHERE TO RUN NOW.
( gasps )
IT CAN'T BE.
( screams )
- ( meows )
- MISS MIYABI!
- Miyabi: GET AWAY!  NO!
GET AWAY FROM ME.
DON'T COME ANY CLOSER.
( shudders )
I HATE COCKROACHES!
( screams )
- IT'S A COCKROACH?
- OH, THAT'S THE BUTTON I LOST.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR IT.
- UH-- BUTTON?
- IT'S ALL RIGHT,
MISS MIYABI.
IT'S NOT A COCKROACH.
- MISTAKING A BUTTON
FOR A COCKROACH.
YOU SURE DO JUMP TO
SOME WILD CONCLUSIONS.
- ( chuckles )
SO, MISS MIYABI'S AFRAID
OF SOMETHING AFTER ALL.
- Kaoru:
THAT'S KIND OF A RELIEF.
- ( groans )
- Tina: WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT?
- ( all chuckle )
- ( murmurs )
- ( door slams )
- UH, MISS MIYABI?
- I'M REALLY SORRY FOR LAUGHING
AT YOU, MISS MIYABI.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO HURT YOU.
- YEAH, IT'S JUST THAT
WE NEVER EXPECTED
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
THAT'S ALL.
- I THINK IT'S SAFE TO SAY
SHE'S REALLY MAD NOW.
- I GUESS WE'LL HAVE TO
WAIT UNTIL SHE CALMS DOWN.
- ( all sigh )
- ( sighs )
- ( knocks on door )
- Kaoru: MISS MIYABI?
ITS ALMOST LUNCH TIME.
AREN'T YOU GONNA EAT?
WE'RE ALL WAITING FOR YOU.
- ( squeaks )
- ( sighs )
- HOW IS SHE?
- STILL NO ANSWER.
- OH, IS THAT THE CASE?
I SUPPOSE YOU MUST
BE HUNGRY BY NOW.
HERE'S YOUR LUNCH.
GO ON AHEAD
AND HAVE YOUR FILL.
COME ON.
- ( sniffs )
( squeaks )
- ( both sigh )
- Kaoru: MISS MIYABI?
IF YOU DON'T HURRY UP,
YOUR LUNCH WILL GET COLD.
MISS MIYABI?
- ( sighs )
HE'S SURE PERSISTENT.
PERHAPS I'VE ALSO
BEEN PERSISTENT
IN MY IMMATURE BEHAVIOR.
- ( scratching at door )
- HMM?
WHAT'S THAT NOISE?
- ( squeaks )
- WHAT THE HECK
DO YOU THINK IT'S DOING?
- I WOULD IMAGINE
THAT IT'S WORRIED ABOUT
MISS MIYABI IN ITS OWN WAY.
- Kaoru: I SEE.
MAYBE IT'S WAITING FOR
MISS MIYABI TO COME OUT.
- IT'S WAITING?
( sighs )
WELL, I CERTAINLY DON'T WANT
ANYTHING TO DO WITH THAT FERRET.
AS MANAGER, I CANNOT ALLOW
ANYTHING TO DAMAGE THIS MANSION,
EVEN IF IT IS A PET THAT
BELONGS TO ONE OF THE TENANTS.
ANYWAY, IT IS THE CAUSE OF THIS
PREDICAMENT IN THE FIRST PLACE.
( grunts )
- ( beeps )
- ( gasps )
- ( scratching at door )
- ( sighs )
OHH.
- OH, I'M SORRY!
I'LL CLEAN IT UP,
MISS MIYABI.
- HEY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
TAEKO-CHAN?
- YEAH.
- ( sighs )
I'M ALL OUT OF WHACK TODAY.
WATCHING TAE'S KLUTZINESS
WITHOUT THE MANAGER HERE
SCOLDING HER
JUST DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT.
- ( sighs )
NO, IT DOESN'T.
THE FOOD'S ALREADY
GOTTEN COLD.
AND THE FERRET HASN'T
COME BACK YET EITHER.
- YEAH.
BUT WHY IT WOULD BE
SO WORRIED ABOUT THE MANAGER
IS SOMETHING THAT
I DON'T REALLY GET.
THE ONLY THING
IT EVER GOT FROM HER
WAS BEING CHASED.
- I'M WORRIED IT DOESN'T WANT
TO EAT DURING FEEDING TIMES.
PERHAPS IT WON'T EAT
UNTIL MISS MIYABI
DECIDES TO COME OUT
OF HER ROOM.
THE FERRET IS
JUST LIKE MISS MIYABI
IN THAT IT MUST BE HUNGRY.
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO TAKE
THE MANAGER'S LUNCH
TO HER ROOM.
AND WE'LL ALSO ASK HER
ABOUT THE FERRET ONE MORE TIME
WHILE WE'RE THERE.
- HMM.
AND NOW TO SIGN IT.
HMM?
THE FOUNTAIN PEN.
( sighs )
( scoffs )
ALL DONE.
OH.
IT DIDN'T HAVE TO
BE THAT ONE.
I COULD HAVE USED
ANOTHER PEN.
SO IT FINALLY GAVE UP.
SCRATCHING AWAY
ALL THAT TIME,
IT WASN'T FUNNY.
( sighs )
( gasps )
- Taeko: OH, THE FERRET!
- HOW DID IT
END UP THERE?
- ( squeaks )
- IT'S STUCK!
DON'T YOU WORRY
ABOUT A THING.
HANG ON.
I'LL GET YOU OUT OF THERE,
OKAY?
- ( squeaks )
- STOP IT, MISS TINA.
YOU'RE HURTING IT.
- WE CAN'T PULL IT
OUT OF THERE.
THE SPACE IS TOO NARROW.
- WHAT NOW?
WHAT DO WE DO?
- ( squeaking )
- IF WE CAN MOVE THIS SOMEHOW.
( grunts )
- ( squeaks )
- ( grunts )
NO GOOD.
IT WON'T EVEN BUDGE.
- NO WAY!
- I'LL TRY TO
HELP YOU MOVE THIS,
OKAY, KAORU-SAMA?
- AOI-CHAN.
- YEAH, IF WE ALL
PULL TOGETHER,
MAYBE WE'LL BE ABLE
TO MOVE IT SOMEHOW.
- ALL RIGHT.
- ( squeaks )
- ( all grunt, straining )
- PLEASE HOLD ON.
WE'LL BE GETTING YOU OUT
VERY SOON.
- ( squeaks )
- Taeko: IT'S NO GOOD.
IT'S TOO HEAVY
TO EVEN MOVE AN INCH.
- Tina: THE FERRET'S NOT
MOVING AS MUCH ANYMORE.
- Aoi: YOU SHOULDN'T GIVE UP,
MISS TINA.
- ( grunting )
- Tina: YOU CAN SAY THAT
ALL YOU WANT,
BUT AT THIS RATE,
IT'S GONNA DIE!
- ( grunting )
- MISS MIYABI.
- ( gasps )
- OH, NO.
- ( squeaks )
- HEY, THE LITTLE GUY'S
NOT MOVING AT ALL NOW.
- LET'S TRY MOVING THIS CLOCK
TOGETHER ONE MORE TIME.
ONE, TWO--
- GET AWAY FROM THERE!
( panting )
- MISS MIYABI.
- Taeko: MISS MANAGER.
- ( gasps )
- BROKEN OBJECTS
CAN ALWAYS BE REPAIRED.
WE CAN REPLACE THE THINGS
THAT CAN'T BE FIXED.
HOWEVER,
LIVES ON THE OTHER HAND...
HOLD ON.
ONLY A LITTLE BIT MORE.
( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- MISS MIYABI!
- MISS MIYABI,
KAORU-SAMA?
- OW.
- MISS MIYABI,
DID YOU HURT YOURSELF?
- HUH?  OH.
EXCUSE ME.
- HUH?
- ( gasps )
- ( squeaks )
- LOOKS LIKE THE FERRET'S
GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
- ( sighs )
HONESTLY,
THIS IS WHY I REALLY
DESPISE ANIMALS.
- AND MISS MIYABI'S
OUT OF HER ROOM NOW.
THAT'S ALSO GOOD NEWS.
- THIS IS ALL THANKS
TO THE FERRET.
OH, I KNOW A GOOD NAME.
WHY DON'T WE NAME
THIS LITTLE ONE UZUME.
- YOU MEAN FROM
JAPANESE MYTHOLOGY?
- YES.
- HEY, I DON'T KNOW THAT ONE.
WHAT KIND OF STORY
IS THAT?
- IN ORDER TO LURE OUT
GODDESS AMATERASU,
WHO IS HIDING IN
THE HEAVENLY CAVE,
THE GODS HELD A PARTY
AND DRANK MERRILY
OUTSIDE THAT CAVE.
- ( squeaks )
- AND THE ONE WHO
LED THOSE GODS
WAS DIVINE PRINCE
UZUME.
- ( giggles ) IT'S PERFECT.
I LIKE IT A LOT.
- YEAH, IT SOUNDS
REALLY COOL.
- HOW DO YOU LIKE IT,
MISS MIYABI?
- HUH?
UZUME.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE
A GOOD NAME.
- ( squeaks )
- Tina:
ALL RIGHT, THEN!
UZUME IT IS!
( chuckles )
- WELL, ALL RIGHT.
- YEAH!
- UZUME?
UZUME?
HEY, UZUME?
- WHAT'S WRONG, TINA?
- OH, KAORU,
HAVE YOU SEEN UZUME?
- IT'S GONE AGAIN, HUH?
- I'M CERTAIN IT'S SPENDING
TIME WITH MISS MIYABI AGAIN.
- ( chuckles )
- AWW.
UZUME SURE IS ALL OVER
THE MANAGER.
IT MAKES ME FEEL
KIND OF LONELY.
I GUESS IT CAN'T BE HELPED.
- I'M SURE THAT WAS UZUME'S
PLAN FRM THE VERY BEGINNaING.
- YES, AND IT MUST HAVE KNOWN
JUST HOW KIND A PERSON
MISS MIYABI WAS.
- THAT SHOULD DO IT.
IN ORDER TO HAVE
INNER PEACE,
IT IS NECESSARY TO HAVE
A BEAUTIFUL ATMOSPHERE.
OH, HELLO, UZUME.
WHAT DID YOU BRING ME
THIS TIME?
( yelps )
( screams )
- ( meows )
- NO, UZUME.
GET AWAY FROM ME.
DIDN'T YOU HEAR ME?
I TOLD YOU TO GET AWAY.
TAKE THAT THING WITH YOU
AND GO AWAY.
- UZUME'S REALLY GOT
MISS MIYABI
WRAPPED AROUND
ITS LITTLE PAW.
- IT CERTAINLY SEEMS SO.
- THIS IS EXACTLY WHY
I SAID I DESPISED ANIMALS!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Tina: ( chuckles )
KAORU?
WE'RE ALL ALONE TONIGHT.
- Kaoru:
OH, YOU'RE RIGHT, TINA.
- Tina:
HEY, WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
YOU KNOW WHAT.
- Kaoru: YOU KNOW What?
AI YORI AOSHI,
"ONE NIGHT."
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- Tina:
YOU KNOW WHAT.