- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HEY, MOMMY, CAN I HAVE
SOMETHING TO DRINK NOW?
I GOT THIRSTY.
- Mother: OF COURSE, DEAR.
JUST HOLD ON FOR ONE MINUTE.
HERE.
- Child: YAY.
- Kaoru: AOI-CHAN,
IF YOU DON'T MIND...
- Aoi: YES?
- Kaoru:
...WHEN YOU GET BETTER,
THERE'S SOME PLACE
I'D LIKE TO TAKE YOU TO.
- Aoi: KAORU-SAMA.
- I'M SORRY IF I FORCED YOU
TO COME ALONG
ON THIS SELFISH
TRIP OF MINE.
- OH, PLEASE DON'T SAY THAT.
I REALLY DON'T MIND AT ALL.
ON THE CONTRARY,
THE FACT YOU AND I
ARE GOING SOMEWHERE ALONE
ACTUALLY PLEASES ME VERY MUCH.
I'M GLAD THAT YOU
INVITED ME ALONG.
BY THE WAY,
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- HOW DO I PUT THIS?
WELL, WE'RE GOING TO
SEE SOMEONE, I GUESS.
- TO SEE SOMEONE?
AND WHO MIGHT
THIS PERSON BE?
- YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO
WAIT AND SEE.
UNTIL THEN,
IT'S A SECRET.
- MM?
OH, YOU'RE SO MEAN,
KAORU-SAMA.
- ( chuckles )
- ( both chuckle )
- Kaoru: OH, AOI-CHAN,
I WANT TO TAKE
A SLIGHT DETOUR,
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
- Aoi: SURE.
- ( children laughing )
- CATCH ME IF YOU CAN.
- SLOW DOWN!
- NO WAY.
- HMM.
EXCUSE ME, MISS?
CAN I HAVE THIS
COOKED PUMPKIN
AND THIS FRIED CHICKEN?
NO, SCRATCH THAT.
LET ME GET THIS
JAPANESE OMELET INSTEAD.
- SURE.  JUST A MOMENT, SIR.
- EXCUSE ME, KAORU-SAMA?
ARE YOU BUYING THESE AS GIFTS
FOR THE PERSON WE'RE VISITING?
- HMM?
- IF THAT'S TRUE,
THIS PERSON MUST REALLY
LOVE JAPANESE FOOD.
- ( sighs )
MAYBE TWO OF THESE.
YEAH, TWO OF THOSE,
AND I'LL ALSO TAKE A COUPLE
OF THE ONES OVER HERE.
- Aoi: A FLOWER SHOP.
KAORU-SAMA,
WHO EXACTLY IS THIS PERSON
THAT WE CAME HERE TO VISIT?
- Kaoru: AOI-CHAN?
- HUH?
- THANKS A LOT
FOR WAITING.
WELL, LET'S GET GOING NOW.
( sighs )
FINALLY HERE AT LAST.
THIS PLACE SURE IS
A LONG WAY FROM
THE TRAIN STATION, HUH?
IT'S THIS WAY,
AOI-CHAN.
- UH-- OH.  COMING!
THIS CERTAINLY IS
VERY COMFORTABLE WEATHER.
- YEAH.
- OH, LOOK, KAORU-SAMA.
MY, SUCH LOVELY FLOWERS.
- YEAH, ALL KINDS OF FLOWERS
BLOOM AROUND HERE
DEPENDING ON THE SEASON.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED YOU
TO SEE THIS PLACE, AOI-CHAN.
I'M GLAD WE CAME
ON A NICE DAY.
- ( giggles )
( gasps )
THIS PLACE IS A...
- AOI-CHAN?
- ( gasps )
- AOI-CHAN,
LET ME INTRODUCE YOU.
THIS IS KUMI HONJO,
MY MOTHER.
I'LL GO GET SOME WATER,
SO WAIT HERE FOR
A MINUTE, OKAY?
- ALL RIGHT.
I'M PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
MY NAME IS AOI SAKURABA.
Aoi: PLEASE, ALLOW ME.
- Kaoru: THANKS.
- Aoi: UM, KAORU-SAMA,
SO WHAT KIND OF PERSON
WAS YOUR MOTHER?
- MMM.
A VERY KIND PERSON.
VERY KIND.
EVEN AFTER I BECAME
PART OF THE HANABISHIS
WHEN I WAS FIVE,
SHE KEPT SENDING LETTERS
AS OFTEN AS SHE COULD.
- Aoi: IT SEEMS SHE
WAS A GOOD MOTHER.
- Kaoru: YEAH.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
WE WERE APART SO LONG.
I CAN'T REMEMBER
HER FACE CLEARLY.
IT'S KIND OF STRANGE,
DON'T YOU THINK?
I REMEMBER HOW KIND
MY MOM WAS, BUT EVEN SO,
ASK ANYTHING ELSE,
AND I HONESTLY WOULDN'T
KNOW WHAT TO TELL YOU.
SO WHEN I COME HERE,
I BRINGS THINGS THAT
I IMAGINE SHE LIKED,
AND I ALSO TRY TO IMAGINE
WHAT SHE WAS LIKE.
BUT IF YOU STOP AND THINK,
SHE MAY NOT BE ANYTHING
LIKE THE MOM IN MY IMAGINATION.
MAYBE I'M JUST
HOLDING ONTO THAT IMAGE
BECAUSE IT'S
MORE CONVENIENT.
- Aoi: I DON'T REALLY
BELIEVE THAT'S THE CASE.
I ALWAYS ASKED MYSELF
A SIMILAR QUESTION.
IS KAORU-SAMA DIFFERENT
FROM WHAT I REMEMBER?
I WONDERED HOW YOUR
INTERESTS HAD CHANGED.
WHAT KINDS OF TALENTS
YOU HAD DEVELOPED,
AND WHAT IT WAS THAT
YOU WERE CURRENTLY DOING.
I IMAGINED
SUCH THINGS AS WELL,
BUT WHEN WE MET AGAIN,
I DISCOVERED THAT YOU WERE
JUST AS I'D IMAGINED.
SO I BELIEVE
I CAN SAY WITH CERTAINTY
THAT YOUR MOTHER MUST BE
EXACTLY AS YOU IMAGINE.
- THANKS, AOI-CHAN.
- AND I ALSO BELIEVE
THAT I UNDERSTAND
HOW YOUR MOTHER
MUST HAVE FELT.
HER THOUGHTS WERE
NEVER FAR FROM YOU.
I CAN UNDERSTAND,
BECAUSE MY THOUGHTS
WERE JUST LIKE HERS.
IN ALL THOSE YEARS,
THEY NEVER STRAYED
FAR FROM YOU EITHER.
- OH?
YEAH, I GUESS THEY DIDN'T.
YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
I'M GLAD THAT
I CAME HERE WITH YOU.
MOM, MEET AOI-CHAN.
SHE'S THE ONE.
THE MOST IMPORTANT PERSON
TO ME IN THIS WORLD.
- WHAT'S THIS ABOUT,
KAGURAZAKI?
- Miyabi:
I APOLOGIZE, SIR.
HOWEVER,
WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
I ASK THAT YOU RECONSIDER
THIS COURSE OF ACTION.
THIS IS A MATTER THAT CONCERNS
LADY AOI'S FUTURE AFTER--
- I'VE HEARD ENOUGH.
THIS DECISION WAS MADE
WITH AOI'S FUTURE IN MIND.
AS WELL AS THAT
OF THE SAKURABA FAMILY.
AS THE ONE CHARGED
WITH MY DAUGHTER'S EDUCATION,
YOU SHOULD BE SMART ENOUGH
TO REALIZE THAT.
YOUR OPINIONS
ARE NOT NEEDED.
THE ONLY THING
THAT I NEED FROM YOU
IS YOUR COMPLETE
OBEDIENCE.
DO NOT DISAPPOINT ME,
KAGURAZAKI.
- Miyabi:
I'LL EXCUSE MYSELF NOW.
- ( laughing )
- Taeko:
WHAT A SURPRISE.
WHAT?  WHAT IS
THE MEANING OF THIS?
- ( laughing )
- ( door opens )
- OH, IT'S RATHER LATE,
BUT WELCOME HOME, MISS MIYABI.
- YES, IT HAS
GOTTEN QUITE LATE,
BUT I'M BACK NOW.
- HI, MISS MIYABI.
I CAME BY TO VISIT.
- IT'S NICE TO HAVE YOU
WITH US AGAIN.
- HOLD ON.
DOESN'T YOUR GAME
STRIKE ANYONE AS BEING
THE LEAST BIT RIDICULOUS?
GOING BACK 50 SPACES
WHEN THE TIDE COMES IN,
MAKING YOUR FACE
LOOK LIKE A TUNA FISH
WHEN YOU RUN OUT OF FOOD,
AND FORCING YOU TO
LOOK LIKE A CLOWN
WHEN YOUR CAMOUFLAGE MAKEUP
ISN'T PUT ON RIGHT.
HOW IN THE WORLD
CAN YOU FAIL SO MISERABLY
THAT YOU END UP
LOOKING LIKE THIS?
HOW, I ASK YOU?!
- ( laughing )
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
AS LONG AS IT'S FUN.
- Mayu: IT IS NOT ALL RIGHT!
- Tina: HEY, YOU WANT TO
JOIN IN, MISS MANAGER?
- HUH?
- THIS IS A BOARD GAME
THAT I MADE UP.
I CALL IT
"SURVIVE OR GO HOME."
I'VE EVEN GOT
A TOKEN HERE
I MADE JUST FOR YOU.
- SORRY, NEXT TIME,
PERHAPS.
- Chika: I GUESS THAT MEANS
IT'S YOUR TURN NEXT, MISS AOI.
- Aoi: OH, SURE.
- Tina: HEY, YOU GUYS
WANT TO GO MOON-WATCHING?
- DO WE WANT TO GO
MOON-WATCHING?
- THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW IS
THE HARVEST MOON.
- OH, THAT'S VERY SOON.
- COME TO THINK OF IT,
I'VE KNOWN ABOUT MOON-WATCHING,
BUT I'VE NEVER ACTUALLY
GONE TO ONE BEFORE.
- YEAH, NEITHER HAVE I.
- THAT'S NORMAL, I GUESS.
YOU DON'T REALLY HEAR
TOO MUCH ABOUT PEOPLE
GOING MOON-WATCHING
THESE DAYS, DO YOU?
- I HEAR THE WEATHER'S
GONNA BE GOOD ON THAT DAY TOO.
SO LET'S DO IT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- IF WE'LL BE
DOING THIS TOGETHER,
LET'S HAVE A PARTY.
- MM.  YEAH, WHY NOT?
- ALL RIGHT!
LET'S DO IT.
- OKAY, THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
LET'S ALL GO OUT!
- Miyabi: LADY AOI?
- YES, COME IN.
- Kaoru: WHAT?
YOU'RE GOING HOME?
- I AM.
BUT MISS MIYABI AND I
WILL BE BACK BEFORE
TOMORROW EVENING.
- THEN THAT MEANS
YOU'LL COME BACK
JUST IN TIME FOR THE PARTY.
- OF COURSE.
I'LL SEE YOU ALL THEN.
- THAT'S A RELIEF.
- IT WOULDN'T BE A VERY GOOD
PARTY WITHOUT YOUR COOKING.
- DID SOMETHING HAPPEN,
AOI-CHAN?
- ACTUALLY,
MISS MIYABI HASN'T SHARED
VERY MANY DETAILS ABOUT IT
WITH ME.
SO I'M AFRAID
I'M AT A LOSS.
BUT I'LL BE BACK
VERY SOON, KAORU-SAMA.
SO THERE ISN'T
ANY REASON TO WORRY.
- LADY AOI.
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'LL THEN, EVERYBODY...
I WILL BE OFF NOW.
- All: TAKE CARE!
- ( grunts )
- Kaoru: MOM?
MOM?
HOLD ON, MOM.
I WANT YOU TO MEET SOMEONE.
THIS IS AOI SAKURABA,
THE MOST IMPORTANT
PERSON TO ME IN THE WORLD.
WHAT?
AOI-CHAN?
HEY, WHERE'D YOU GO?
AOI-CHAN, YOU THERE?
( gasps )
MOM?
( sighs )
- ( knocks on door )
- Tina:
HEY, KAORU, YOU UP YET?
- JUST A DREAM.
- Tina: WE'RE STILL NOT DONE
SETTING UP FOR THE PARTY YET.
HURRY UP AND HELP OUT!
- ALL RIGHT.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE, TINA.
( sighs )
- MORE TO THE RIGHT.
MORE MORE MORE MORE.
OKAY!
- ( giggles )
- THIS IS YUMMY.
- HEY, WAIT TILL THE PARTY.
- THEY SURE ARE LATE.
WHAT COULD BE KEEPING
MISS AOI AND MISS MIYABI?
- WE WON'T BE ABLE TO BEGIN
THE PARTY AS SCHEDULED
IF THEY TAKE MUCH LONGER.
- IT'S NOT LIKE THEM
TO BE SO LATE.
I WONDER WHAT
COULD HAVE HAPPENED.
- THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
MISS AOI'S BEEN HOME IN AWHILE.
IT COULD BE THAT SHE
DECIDED TO STAY AN EXTRA NIGHT
BECAUSE SHE WAS
HAPPY TO BE BACK.
I'M USUALLY
REALLY HAPPY TOO
WHENEVER I GET THE CHANCE
TO VISIT MY HOME.
BUT IT'S ALWAYS TOUGH
TO SEE THE LONELY LOOK
ON MY MOTHER'S FACE
WHEN I HAVE TO LEAVE.
- I KNOW THE FEELING.
IT'S LIKE THAT WITH
MY MAMA AND PAPA TOO.
- AND CONSIDERING
HOW KIND-HEARTED MISS AOI IS,
I'M SURE THAT'S WHY
SHE'S NOT BACK YET.
RIGHT?  DON'T YOU AGREE?
SENPAI?
- HUH?
SORRY, BUT YOU'RE RIGHT.
I AGREE.
- Tina: WELL, I GUESS
THERE'S NO HELPING IT.
IT WON'T BE
THE HARVEST MOON ANYMORE,
BUT LET'S PUT OFF THE PARTY
TILL TOMORROW NIGHT.
- Kaoru: AOI-CHAN.
- KAORU-SAMA.
( Aoi crying )
- Kaoru: AOI-CHAN?
AOI-CHAN?
AOI-CHAN, IT'S YOU.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- AOI-CHAN.
YOU'RE FINALLY
BACK HOME.
WHAT A RELIEF.
I'M GLAD TO SEE YOU.
YOU HAD ME WORRIED.
- I'M TRULY SORRY,
KAORU-SAMA.
I'M TRULY SORRY.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT REALLY IS, AOI-CHAN.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
APOLOGIZE.
YOUR COMING BACK IS
ENOUGH FOR ME, REALLY.
- KAORU-SAMA.
I-- I--
I CAN...
NO LONGER BE
BY YOUR SIDE.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- ( gasps )
AOI-CHAN?
- I AM TRULY SORRY,
KAORU-SAMA.
THIS IS WHERE WE MUST
SAY OUR FAREWELLS.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND,
AOI-CHAN.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- GOOD-BYE, KAORU-SAMA.
GOOD-BYE.
- HEY, HOLD ON A MINUTE,
AOI-CHAN.
COME BACK!
- GOOD-BYE.
- ( panting )
AT LEAST TELL ME
THE REASON WHY, AOI-CHAN.
AOI-CHAN, WAIT!
AOI-CHAN!
IT'S THE SAME.
THE SAME AS BACK THEN.
NO.
NO!
I DON'T WANT TO
LOSE SOMEONE AGAIN.
NOT SOMEONE I CARE ABOUT.
- KAORU-SAMA!
- ( gasps )
AOI-CHAN.
Kaoru: I THOUGHT SO.
THEY'RE NOT BACK YET.
- Aoi: BUT I'LL BE BACK
VERY SOON, KAORU-SAMA,
SO THERE ISN'T
ANY REASON TO WORRY.
- Kaoru: MAYBE--
MAYBE SOMETHING
HAPPENED TO HER.
I JUST FEEL IT.
SOMETHING'S WRONG.
I'M GOING.
I NEED TO GO TO HER.
( gasps )
MISS MIYABI.
- COME, SIR KAORU.
IT IS IMPERATIVE FOR US
TO LEAVE RIGHT AWAY.
- Kaoru:
UM, MISS MIYABI?
IS AOI-CHAN STILL
AT HER PARENT'S HOUSE?
IT'S LIKE THE OTHER DAY.
SHE'S NOT TALKING.
I'VE GOT SO MANY
QUESTIONS.
- Miyabi: DO YOU REMEMBER...
- HUH?
- Miyabi:
I'M REFERRING TO THE TIME
WHEN YOU AND I
FIRST MET EACH OTHER.
- Kaoru: OH, YEAH.
- Miyabi: IF I RECALL,
SIR KAORU,
I UTTERLY DESPISED YOU,
TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST.
EVEN BEFORE YOU AND I
MET EACH OTHER.
DESPITE MY YEARS OF
SERVICE TO HER,
YOU, A PERSON WHO HAD
HARDLY BEEN BY HER SIDE,
WERE THE ONLY ONE THAT
SHE COULD EVER THINK OF.
IT WOULD NOT BE
MUCH OF AN EXAGGERATION
TO SAY THAT LADY AOI'S EVERY
WAKING THOUGHT WAS ABOUT YOU.
- YOU KNOW,
I'VE ALREADY DECIDED
WHO I'M GONNA MARRY
WHEN I FINALLY GROW UP.
- HUH?
- I'M GONNA BE MARRIED TO
KAORU-SAMA OF
THE HANABISHI FAMILY.
SO I HAVE TO DO
A BETTER JOB WITH MY LESSONS.
I HAVE TO TRY EVEN HARDER
THAN I AM NOW.
AFTER ALL, IT'S SO THAT I CAN
BE TOGETHER WITH KAORU-SAMA.
- ( gasps )
Miyabi: LADY AOI SEEMED
TO THINK SO HIGHLY
OF THE HEIR TO
THE HANABISHI CORPORATION.
EVERY TIME SHE SPOKE
OF KAORU HANABISHI,
IT ALWAYS
LEFT ME WONDERING
WHAT KIND OF PERSON
HE REALLY WAS.
YET WHEN WE FINALLY MET,
YOU WERE AN ORDINARY
COLLEGE STUDENT
LIVING IN A PITIFUL
APARTMENT.
I WAS DISAPPOINTED IN YOU
AND YOUR EXISTENCE
IRRITATED ME.
WHAT WAS THE POINT
OF LADY AOI BEARING
ALL THOSE DAYS OF HARD WORK?
WHAT WAS THE PURPOSE
OF ALLOWING HERSELF
TO SUFFER SO MUCH PAIN,
SO MUCH ANGUISH?
HOWEVER...
LADY AOI.
THERE IS NO REASON FOR YOU TO
BE DOING SUCH MENIAL LABOR.
YOU ARE THE DAUGHTER
OF THE SAKURABA FAMILY.
- I DON'T MIND IT AT ALL,
MISS MIYABI.
REMEMBER NOW,
IT'S BEEN MY DREAM
TO TAKE CARE OF
KAORU-SAMA LIKE THIS
EVER SINCE I WAS
A LITTLE GIRL.
- HEY, THAT LOOKS
REALLY DELICIOUS, AOI-CHAN.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT
TO TASTE A LITTLE?
- Aoi: SURE.  HERE YOU GO.
- Kaoru: THANKS.
- Miyabi: AFTER SEEING
HOW LADY AOI HAS BEEN
SINCE SHE MET YOU--
WHAT SHE THOUGHT,
WHAT SHE FELT
AND WHAT SHE LONGED FOR...
I HAVE FINALLY BEGUN
TO UNDERSTAND.
I NOW KNOW YOU'VE
ALREADY BECOME
A PART OF LADY AOI'S LIFE.
- MISS MIYABI.
- IF THAT TRULY IS
THE CASE NOW,
NO MATTER WHAT
MAY HAPPEN IN THE FUTURE,
I PROMISE I WILL DO
ALL I CAN TO PROTECT YOU.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Kaoru: MISS MIYABI,
AREN'T WE THERE YET?
- Miyabi:
IT'S A BIT FURTHER.
- Kaoru: THAT'S WHY I ASKED
IF WE COULD STOP BACK THERE.
- Miyabi: STOP OBSESSING
OVER THE PAST.
- ( Kaoru yelps )
I CAN'T BE PATIENT ANYMORE!
- Miyabi: NO, DON'T!
( screams )
- ( Kaoru sighs )