- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( door opens )
- Aoi: YOU FORGOT SOMETHING,
KAORU-SAMA.
- I FORGOT SOMETHING?
- ( chuckles )
YOUR BENTO.
- OH, THANKS, AOI-CHAN.
I WAS ABOUT TO MISS OUT
ON ONE OF YOUR GREAT LUNCHES.
- ( chuckles )
IT'S FORTUNATE THAT
I REALIZED IT.
OH.
- IT'S SORT OF LIKE WE'RE
A COUPLE OF NEWLYWEDS, HUH?
- I'M HAPPY TO
HEAR YOU SAY THAT.
AFTER ALL, KAORU-SAMA,
YOU AND I ARE.
- Tina: KAORU!
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE TO OUR
CLASSES IF WE DON'T HURRY!
- WELL, GUESS I'D BETTER
GET GOING THEN.
- BE CAREFUL ON YOUR WAY,
KAORU-SAMA.
( giggles )
- ( bells ringing )
- ( sighs )
THANK GOODNESS
CLASS IS OVER.
WHY MUST JAPAN'S
EDUCATIONAL INSTITUTIONS
BE SUCH DULL PLACES?
HONESTLY, WHAT A CHORE.
( gasps )
HANABISHI-SAMA!
- ( screams )
- ( giggles )
- ( screaming )
( groans )
- IT'S BEEN SO LONG
SINCE WE SAW EACH OTHER.
MAYU WAS STARTING TO GET LONELY
AFTER NOT SEEING YOU.
( grunts )
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT
"IT'S BEEN AWHILE"?
YOU'VE SEEN KAORU AROUND
THE UNIVERSITY EVERY SINGLE DAY.
- SENPAI.
SAY SOMETHING TO ME, SENPAI.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HANABISHI SENPAI?
- ( groans )
- Mayu:
WHAT? A BENTO LUNCH?
- YEAH, I WAS THINKING
OF EATING MY BENTO LUNCH HERE.
- OH, NO.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
FORCE YOURSELF TO EAT THAT.
I CAN TREAT YOU TO A LUNCH
MADE BY A TOP CHEF
AT SOME RESTAURANT.
- FOOD TASTES A LOT BETTER
WHEN IT'S EATEN OUTSIDE
WITH YOUR FRIENDS
THAN INSIDE SOME
STUFFY OLD RESTAURANT.
- ( sighs )
- ( chuckles )
WELL, I GUESS
I'LL START EATING NOW.
- All: WOW.
- TODAY'S BENTO LOOKS AS GOOD
AS IT ALWAYS DOES.
- WHENEVER MISS AOI
COOKS ANYTHING,
IT'S SURE TO LOOK GREAT
AND TASTE DELICIOUS.
- HUH?
- IMPRESSED, HUH?
WHEN IT COMES TO
COOKING AND CLEANING,
NOBODY'S BETTER
THAN OUR LANDLORD.
I'D BET IT TASTES BETTER
THAN THE EXPENSIVE STUFF
YOU USUALLY EAT.
- WELL, I WON'T
BE ABLE TO COMPARE
UNTIL I TRY
SOME OF IT.
- ( yelps )
GET YOUR PAWS OFF OF MY LUNCH!
- JUST BECAUSE
FOOD LOOKS GOOD,
DOESN'T NECESSARILY
MEAN IT WILL TASTE GOOD.
- WELL?
- WELL, IT DOESN'T
SEEM TO BE HORRIBLE.
- FIRST YOU TAKE
SOMEONE ELSE'S FOOD
AND THEN YOU
WISECRACK ABOUT IT.
( groans )
- HEY, TINA, THESE SAUSAGES
ARE HOMEMADE, RIGHT?
- YOU CAN TELL.
I TRIED TO MAKE IT LOOK LIKE
A LITTLE SEA ANEMONE.
- IT KIND OF DOES, HUH?
- KAORU OVER HERE
IS THE KIND OF GUY
WHO'S ATTRACTED TO
US DOMESTIC GIRLS
WHO CAN COOK AND CLEAN.
( chuckles )
- HMM.
- TAEKO-CHAN,
DID YOU MAKE THIS?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S TEMPURA THAT I MADE
WITH CHOCOLATE COVERED TOMATOES.
- All: HUH?
- IT'S REALLY
DELICIOUS, YOU KNOW.
- YEAH?
- TRUST ME,
IT'S DELICIOUS.
- UHH...
( gulps )
( sighs )
- RIGHT?
- RIGHT.
- Mayu: IS A BENTO LUNCH
REALLY THAT IMPORTANT TO HIM?
BUT IF IT MEANS THAT MAYU
CAN SPEND QUALITY TIME
WITH HANABISHI-SAMA,
THEN I'LL TRY IT.
IF HANABISHI-SAMA EATS
MAYU'S HOMEMADE LUNCH
THEN I'M SURE...
- Kaoru: IT'S DELICIOUS!
TOTALLY DELICIOUS.
I WANT YOU TO MAKE
MY LUNCH TOMORROW.
NO, I WANT YOU TO
ALWAYS MAKE THEM.
- Mayu: I WILL IF IT'S
FOR YOU, HANABISHI-SAMA.
- ( crying )
- Kaoru: I LOVE YOU. I'M NEVER
GONNA LET YOU GO, MAYU.
- Mayu: I'M SO HAPPY,
HANABISHI-SAMA.
- ( crying )
- Kaoru: YOU CAN EVEN COOK
GARBAGE AND MAKE IT DELICIOUS.
- Mayu: OH, YOU ALWAYS
FLATTER ME SO, DARLING.
- ( crying )
- Kaoru: I'M GONNA EAT YOU UP,
JUST LIKE I DID THE FOOD.
- Mayu: OH, NO!
( giggles )
- ( crying )
- ( giggles )
- THE FOOD'S DELICIOUS AND ALL,
BUT DROOLING
LIKE THAT'S DISGUSTING.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING
ANY MORE OF MY LUNCH.
- HANABISHI-SAMA,
IF MAYU MADE A BENTO LUNCH FOR
YOU TOMORROW, WOULD YOU EAT IT?
- WHAT?
YEAH, OF COURSE I WOULD.
- YOU REALLY WOULD EAT IT?
THEN MAYU WILL MAKE
A BENTO FOR YOU TOMORROW
AND BRING IT RIGHT HERE.
- THEN I'LL GO BUY SOME
ANTACIDS FOR YOU TOMORROW
AND BRING THEM RIGHT HERE.
- ( both groan )
- AND WHAT PRAY TELL
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- GEE, I WONDER,
WHAT COULD THAT POSSIBLY MEAN?
- ( both hiss )
- Mayu: WELL, I SHOULD
START COOKING NOW.
LET'S SEE,
FIRST OF ALL...
I SUPPOSE I'LL MAKE
SOME SOLE MEUNIERE.
"POUR OIL INTO
A HEATED FRYING PAN.
SAUTEE SOLE FOR FIVE MINUTES."
( gasps )
DON'T MIND THAT!
( giggles )
THIS WILL MAKE IT MUCH EASIER.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS WAIT
FOR IT TO FINISH COOKING.
- ( dings )
- NEVER GIVE UP.
YOU CAN NEVER HAVE
A PROPER LUNCH
WITHOUT SOME RICE BALLS.
( gasping )
HOT!
THEY MAY NOT LOOK
TERRIBLY PRETTY,
BUT THEY SHOULD DEFINITELY
TASTE LIKE RICE.
( murmurs )
THIS CAN'T BE HELPED,
I GUESS.
SINCE AFTER ALL,
I'VE NEVER HAD
ANYBODY TEACH ME
TO COOK BEFORE.
- WHENEVER MISS AOI
COOKS ANYTHING,
IT'S SURE TO LOOK GREAT
AND TASTE DELICIOUS.
- WHEN IT COMES TO
COOKING AND CLEANING,
NOBODY'S BETTER
THAN OUR LANDLORD.
I BET IT TASTES A LOT BETTER
THAN THAT EXPENSIVE STUFF
YOU USUALLY EAT.
- ( gasps )
WHY DIDN'T I THINK
OF IT EARLIER?
- THERE WE GO.
I WONDER WHAT KIND OF
DISHES I SHOULD MAKE TONIGHT.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
KAORU-SAMA MENTIONED
THAT HE FELT LIKE
EATING FISH.
- ( doorbell rings )
- HUH?
YES, I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
WHO IS IT?
( gasps )
- ( students chatter )
- ( meows )
- I GUESS MAYU-CHAN'S
NOT COMING AFTER ALL.
- AND AFTER ALL THAT
MOUTHING OFF ABOUT
MAKING YOU BENTO, TOO.
I'M SURE THINGS DIDN'T TURN
OUT AS WELL AS SHE HAD HOPED.
- COOKING REALLY ISN'T SOMETHING
THAT YOU CAN LEARN
HOW TO DO WELL
IN ONLY A DAY OR TWO.
IT TOOK ME 10 HARD
DAYS OF THINKING
TO COME UP WITH THIS
TEMPURA RECIPE.
- Both:
OH, IS THAT SO?
- ( sighs )
Kaoru: I WONDER IF
MAYU-CHAN'S ALL RIGHT.
I HOPE SHE'S NOT
HURT OR ANYTHING.
- Tina: HI, WE'RE BACK,
MISS LANDLORD.
- WELCOME HOME.
- HUH?
TAEKO-CHAN?
BUT AREN'T YOU
RIGHT OVER HERE?
- YEAH.
- WELL, YOU SEE...
TO TELL THE TRUTH,
KAORU-SAMA...
- ALLOW ME TO
WELCOME YOU HOME,
HANABISHI-SAMA.
- ( all stammer )
- ( giggles )
- Kaoru: WHAT?!
MAYU-CHAN.
- I APOLOGIZE IN ADVANCE
FOR TROUBLING YOU ALL SO.
- WELL, SO WHAT THE HELL'S
THAT BRAT DOING HERE ANYWAY?
- MAYU-SAMA INSISTED
THAT SHE WISHED TO LEARN
HOW TO PERFORM
EVERYDAY HOUSEHOLD CHORES.
AND IN ORDER
TO ACCOMPLISH THAT,
SHE REQUESTED THAT
MISS AOI SAKURABA,
THE LANDLORD OF
THIS ESTATE,
BE HER PERSONAL INSTRUCTOR.
- I WANTED TO LEARN
HOW TO MAKE THE BENTO LUNCH
THAT HANABISHI-SAMA LIKED.
I ALSO HEARD SHE KNEW
HOW TO DO OTHER CHORES AS WELL.
I LEAVE MYSELF IN YOUR
MOST CAPABLE HANDS, MISS AOI.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- AOI-CHAN.
- BECAUSE SHE IS
ONE OF YOUR ACQUAINTANCES,
SIR KAORU,
WE FELT OBLIGATED
TO ACCEPT HER.
AND APPARENTLY,
YOU HAD PROMISED THIS YOUNG LADY
YOU WOULD EAT HER BENTO
AS WELL.
- UH-- WELL,
THAT WAS ONLY BECAUSE...
- THAT'S RIGHT.
AND WHO BETTER TO LEARN
ALL THESE DOMESTIC CHORES FROM
THAN HANABISHI-SAMA'S
PERSONAL SERVANT.
- HIS PERSONAL SERVANT?
- WHAT?
THAT ISN'T WHAT YOU ARE?
- WHAT I AM IS
KAORU-SAMA'S...
- NO, LADY AOI.
PLEASE SHOW SOME RESTRAINT.
- I KNOW.
- AOI-CHAN.
I'M SORRY.
I NEVER IMAGINED
MAYU-CHAN
WOULD JUST BARGE IN HERE.
- THIS IS NOT SOMETHING THAT
SHOULD HAVE BEEN LEFT UNSAID.
AND OF ALL THINGS
SHE COULD HAVE CALLED HER,
A SERVANT?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
JUST HOW HUMILIATED
LADY AOI MUST FEEL
AT THIS VERY MOMENT?
- Aoi: PLEASE WAIT,
MISS MIYABI.
KAORU-SAMA DIDN'T
DO ANYTHING SO HORRIBLE.
- BUT LADY AOI,
EVEN SO.
- KAORU-SAMA, PLEASE DO NOT
BE SO SENSITIVE
ABOUT HURTING MY FEELINGS.
- WHY NOT?
- I KNOW THE CIRCUMSTANCES,
AND I'M FINE WITH IT.
- ( glass shatters )
- Taeko:
OH, NO, THE VASE!
- Mayu: MAYU WAS ONLY
DOING HER DUTY AS A MAID
BY REDECORATING A LITTLE.
IT'S THE VASE'S FAULT
FOR BEING THERE.
- Tina: ( groans ) WHY DON'T
YOU JUST GO HOME ALREADY,
YOU STUPID LITTLE BRAT?!
- ( sighs )
I'M PERFECTLY FINE
WITH THE SITUATION.
( chuckles nervously )
- WHY ARE THERE
SO MANY SHEETS HERE?
THE ONLY LAUNDRY
THAT MAYU WANTS TO WASH
IS HANABISHI-SAMA'S LAUNDRY.
( sighs )
HUH?
I MAY BE A LITTLE
TIRED RIGHT NOW,
BUT THIS IS
SORT OF SATISFYING.
ALL THE LAUNDRY
SWAYING IN THE WIND.
- ( chuckles )
I KNOW THAT FEELING WELL.
EVERY ONCE IN AWHILE,
SEEING THIS MAKES ME
FEEL VERY HAPPY.
IT'S THINGS LIKE THIS
THAT MAKE ME FEEL LIKE I'M
REALLY LIVING WITH KAORU-SAMA.
( gasps )
- COME ON, AOI-CHAN.
IT'S TIME TO GO INSIDE
AND HAVE SOME TEA.
- HANABISHI-SAMA.
- OH?
- CAN YOU BELIEVE
I HELPED PUT UP
ALL THIS LAUNDRY?
ISN'T IT WONDERFUL?
MAYU WILL MAKE
A VERY GOOD WIFE.
- A VERY GOOD WIFE?
NOW JUST HOLD ON A MINUTE THERE,
MAYU-CHAN.
- AND WHEN MAYU FINALLY
BECOMES YOUR WIFE ONE DAY,
YOU'LL ALWAYS BE THERE FOR ME
AND ONLY FOR ME.
I WONDER IF I CAN IMAGINE
HOW OUR LIVES WILL BE.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I BELIEVE YOU WANTED
SOME TEA RIGHT NOW,
AND AS A MAID,
MAYU SHOULD SERVE IT TO YOU.
- WELL...
- ( chuckles )
- COME ON.
HURRY UP, HANABISHI-SAMA.
- HUH?
WHERE'S MISS MAYU?
- OH, SHE WENT INSIDE
FOR TEA WITH KAORU-SAMA.
- EVEN NOW, MISS MAYU'S
AS AGGRESSIVE AS SHE ALWAYS IS.
THAT KISS THE OTHER DAY,
AND NOW THIS.
- ( gasps )
"THAT KISS"?
- PLEASE HAVE SOME TEA,
HANABISHI-SAMA.
- OH, THANKS A LOT,
MAYU-CHAN.
- I FORGOT TO MENTION TO YOU
THAT I WAS CURIOUS
AND TOOK A LITTLE PEEK
AT THE ROOM EARLIER.
YOUR ROOM, I MEAN.
- YOU TOOK A LOOK
AT MY ROOM, MAYU-CHAN?
- IT WAS SO INSPIRING,
HANABISHI-SAMA.
- HUH?
- LIVING IN A MERE
COMMONER'S ROOM
IN ORDER TO UNDERSTAND
THE LIVES OF ORDINARY MEN.
HOW UTTERLY MAGNANIMOUS
AND NOBLE OF YOU.
MAYU WAS SO HUMBLED
BY IT ALL.
AND JUST FOR YOU,
HANABISHI-SAMA,
MAYU WILL LEARN
THE HOUSEHOLD CHORES
OF THE ORDINARY COMMONER.
- HEY!
- ( grunts )
- WHAT THE HECK
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING
WASTING YOUR TIME
JUST SITTING THERE?
YOU OUGHT TO BE
DOING YOUR CHORES?
- AND WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING
INCESSANTLY INTERRUPTING
THE TWO OF US?
MAYU IS ACTING
AS A MAID HERE.
IT'S ONLY NATURAL FOR ME TO BE
SERVING THE MASTER OF THE HOUSE.
- ( gasps )
- HMM.
- ( murmurs )
( crying )
MISS MANAGER,
THAT BRAT'S
BEING MEAN TO ME.
- NOW THAT WAS
A PERFECT VICTORY.
- ( sighs )
- Taeko: EVEN NOW, MISS MAYU'S
AS AGGRESSIVE AS SHE ALWAYS IS.
THAT KISS THE OTHER DAY.
- ( sighs )
- Mayu: AND WHEN MAYU FINALLY
BECOMES YOUR WIFE ONE DAY,
YOU'LL ALWAYS BE THERE FOR ME
AND ONLY FOR ME.
- HIS WIFE.
( sighs )
- ( door opens )
- Miyabi: LADY AOI.
- OH?  YES?
- IT IS NEARLY DINNER TIME.
WE SHOULD BEGIN
PREPARING IT.
MISS TAEKO AND MISS MAYU
ARE WAITING FOR YOU.
- OH, I DIDN'T REALIZE.
I WILL BE RIGHT THERE
ONCE I TAKE CARE OF THIS.
- Mayu: FINALLY,
I WAS GETTING IMPATIENT.
SO WHAT KIND OF FOOD DOES
EVERYONE NORMALLY EAT
AROUND HERE?
- WELL, FOR TODAY,
WE WERE PLANNING
TO HAVE MEAT WITH POTATOES
AND SOME GRILLED FISH.
- HUH?!
WHY DO YOU FEED
HANABISHI-SAMA
THE FOOD OF COMMONERS?
- HUH?
- FOR A MAN OF HIS
UPBRINGING AND PEDIGREE,
A MORE PALATABLE AND
ELEGANT MENU IS REQUIRED.
FOR INSTANCE,
AS AN EXAMPLE--
- YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
SENPAI ACTUALLY LIKES JAPANESE
FOOD LIKE THAT.
- HMM.
- COMMONER FOOD.
- OH, LADY AOI,
MAINTAIN YOUR COMPOSURE.
- Aoi: IT'S IMPORTANT
TO MONITOR THE TEMPERATURE
AS YOU LET THE FLAVORS
MELT TOGETHER.
IT DOESN'T APPEAR
TO BE SALTY ENOUGH.
- WOW, YOU CERTAINLY
ARE WELL VERSED IN
YOUR WORK AS A SERVANT,
MISS AOI.
- ( stammers )
( chuckles ) I GUESS MY
HAND SLIPPED A LITTLE.
- BUT YOU KNOW, WHEN I
FINALLY MARRY HANABISHI-SAMA,
MAYU WILL BE MAKING
JAPANESE DISHES FOR HIM
LIKE THIS EVERY SINGLE DAY.
- ( gasps )
- OH, MISS AOI.
- I WONDER HOW I SHOULD
ADDRESS HIM WHEN WE'RE MARRIED.
- IN ANY CASE,
WHEN A DISH IS TOO SALTY,
IF I REMEMBER,
THE REMEDY IS TO...
BALANCE THE FLAVOR
WITH SUGAR.
- BUT THAT'S CHILI SAUCE
THAT YOU'RE PUTTING IN THERE,
MISS AOI.
- ( gasps )
I APOLOGIZE FOR THAT.
- Mayu: OHH!
DECISIONS, DECISIONS.
I WONDER WHAT WE SHOULD
NAME OUR CHILDREN.
- Taeko:
OH MY GOSH, IT'S ON FIRE!
- Miyabi: LADY AOI,
THE RICE IS BURNING.
- Aoi: I APOLOGIZE.
- WHAT THE HECK IS THIS?
DID TAE MAKE DINNER TONIGHT
BY HERSELF OR SOMETHING?
- NO, ACTUALLY IT WAS
MOSTLY MISS AOI
WHO DID THE COOKING TODAY.
- HUH?
- I APOLOGIZE.
- AOI-CHAN?
- LADY AOI.
- MAYU DIDN'T
COME TO THIS PLACE
TO LEARN HOW TO COOK FOOD
IN THE WORST POSSIBLE MANNER.
- ( sighs )
- JUST A MOMENT,
MISS MAYU.
- MAYU-CHAN.
TRY NOT TO BE SO HARD
ON AOI-CHAN, OKAY?
SHE MAY NOT HAVE DONE
ALL THAT WELL TODAY,
BUT THIS ISN'T WHAT
IT'S NORMALLY LIKE.
HER COOKING IS USUALLY
TOTALLY DELICIOUS.
- OH?
- BUT NOW THAT I'VE
HAD A TASTE OF THIS,
IT'S ACTUALLY PRETTY GOOD
IN ITS OWN WAY.
- HANABISHI-SAMA.
- YEAH, IT REALLY
ISN'T ALL THAT BAD.
AT LEAST, IT'S A LOT BETTER
THAN WHAT TAE USUALLY COOKS.
- OH, IS THAT REALLY SO?
WELL, MY NEXT RECIPE IS
CHOCOLATE COVERED POTATOES.
AND I'LL MAKE SURE TO
ADJUST IT TO YOUR LIKING.
I HOPE YOU BEAR WITH ME
WHILE I EXPERIMENT.
- ( groans )
ANYTHING BUT THAT.
HEY, KAORU, YOU WANT TO
GET IN ON THE ACTION?
- WHAT?  WHY DO I
HAVE TO SUFFER?
- Taeko: HEY, HOW CAN BOTH OF
YOU BE SO CRUEL TO A FRIEND?
- ( all chuckle )
- KAORU-SAMA.
EVERYONE.
- UM, MISS AOI,
I KNOW THAT I WENT
A LITTLE TOO FAR EARLIER.
I APOLOGIZE.
- MISS MAYU,
AND I APOLOGIZE
FOR NOT TEACHING YOU BETTER.
- ( chuckles )
- WELL THEN, WE'D BETTER BE
TAKING OUR LEAVE NOW.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR EVERYTHING TODAY.
- I HOPE YOU'RE WILLING TO TEACH
TO COOK ANOTHER TIME, MISS AOI.
- I AM.
PLEASE COME WHENEVER
YOU WOULD LIKE.
- ( giggles )
( laughs )
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT,
HANABISHI-SAMA.
( yelps )
- HOW LONG DO YOU PLAN
TO KEEP ON HANGING
ON HIM LIKE THAT?
- Mayu: I'LL BE SO LONELY
WITHOUT YOU, HANABISHI-SAMA.
- ( car door closes )
- Mayu: I'LL COME BACK
AGAIN SOME OTHER TIME!
- Tina:
NEVER COME BACK HERE!
- KAORU-SAMA.
- ( knocks on door )
- ( gasps )
OH, COME IN.
OH.
WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU DOING HERE,
AND AT THIS HOUR?
IF MISS MIYABI FINDS YOU...
- WHAT'S THAT?
WAIT A SEC.
MISS MIYABI JUST TOLD ME
YOU WANTED TO TALK TO ME.
- Both: HUH?
( chuckling )
- Kaoru: I REALLY AM
SORRY ABOUT TODAY.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN
HARD ON YOU.
- NO.
IT WAS BECAUSE
I COULDN'T DEAL WITH THINGS
THAT I TROUBLED YOU
AND EVERYONE ELSE.
I WAS NOT EVEN ABLE
TO TEACH MISS MAYU PROPERLY.
BUT I WILL DO MY VERY BEST
THE NEXT TIME.
AND I WILL TRY HARDER TO PUT
FEELINGS LIKE THAT ASIDE.
IF I DO NOT...
IF I DO NOT,
THEN I CANNOT BE YOUR...
- AOI-CHAN,
IT SURE WOULD BE NICE
IF WE COULD SAY IT SOON, HUH?
THAT YOU'RE MY FIANCEE
AND EVERYTHING, I MEAN?
- ( gasps )
( sighs )
KA--
KAORU-SAMA.
KAORU-SAMA!
- ( Kaoru grunts )
- I'M SORRY.
I JUST COULDN'T
HELP MYSELF.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT,
I'M FINE.
- ( sighs )
I'LL TRY HARDER TO BECOME A
FIANCEE YOU WON'T BE ASHAMED OF.
I'LL DO EVERYTHING
I POSSIBLY CAN.
- YOU'RE A PERSON THAT
I CAN BE PROUD TO CALL
MY FIANCEE EVEN NOW,
AOI-CHAN.
- KAORU-SAMA.
BEING HERE AT THIS MOMENT
AND HEARING YOU SAY THOSE WORDS
BRINGS MORE JOY TO MY HEART
THAN I COULD HAVE
EVER THOUGHT POSSIBLE.
- I CAN'T HELP BUT
WONDER RIGHT NOW
WHAT KIND OF A WIFE
YOU'LL BE IN THE FUTURE.
HAVE YOU EVER
THOUGHT ABOUT THAT?
- I HAVE.
QUITE OFTEN, IN FACT.
WE WOULDN'T LIVE IN
A LARGE HOUSE LIKE THIS ONE.
AND WE WOULD HAVE
THREE CHILDREN,
OH, I'LL HAVE TO ASK MISS MIYABI
TO TEACH ME HOW TO
DISCIPLINE THEM.
- Kaoru: YEAH.
- Aoi: EVERY SPRING,
THE ENTIRE FAMILY
WOULD GO OUT TO SEE
THE CHERRY BLOSSOMS.
- Kaoru: GO ON.
- Aoi: ALSO, LET ME THINK.
OH, I HAVEN'T THOUGHT OF ANY
NAMES FOR OUR CHILDREN YET.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Aoi: AI YORI AOSHI,
"FEELINGS OF THE HEART."