- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- KAORU-SAMA, EXCUSE ME.
I WOULD LIKE
TO SCRUB YOUR BACK.
SO WOULD YOU MIND TERRIBLY
IF I CAME IN?
- WHAT?!
WAIT, YOU CAN'T, AOI-CHAN.
- IT IS ALL RIGHT
AS LONG AS YOU DESIRE IT...
KAORU-SAMA.
- ( gasps )
( heart beating )
- EXCUSE ME.
- WAIT, YOU CAN'T
COME IN HERE!
HUH?
YOU WERE WEARING CLOTHES?
- YES.
- ( yelps ) IN ANY CASE,
NO MEANS NO.
( yelps )
- ( both scream )
- OW OH.
HUH?
- KAORU-SAMA?
- ( stammering )
- ( dog howls )
- ( Aoi screams )
- LADY AOI!
( gasps )
OH!
- ( Aoi gasps )
- HUH?
- Y-Y-Y-YOU!
YOU BEAST!
HOW DARE YOU DO THIS
TO LADY AOI!
- WAIT WAIT, MISS MIYABI!
- LADY AOI.
- M-MISS MIYABI?
( Kaoru moaning )
- IS YOUR HEAD
FEELING ALL RIGHT?
I'M SO SORRY. IT WAS ALL BECAUSE
I RAISED MY VOICE SO MUCH.
- IT'S FINE.
IT'S PARTLY MY FAULT TOO.
BUT WHO EXACTLY IS THIS?
- MISS MIYABI KAGURAZAKI.
SHE IS THE ONE WHO
TOOK CARE OF ME
EVER SINCE I WAS A LITTLE GIRL.
- I SEE.
- LADY AOI,
ARE YOU AWARE OF THE POSITION
THAT YOU HAVE PUT YOURSELF INTO?
- BUT I--
- "BUT I" WHAT?!
- ( whimpers )
- WHAT IS SHE MAD ABOUT?
YOU SAID THIS MORNING
YOU CALLED YOUR FOLKS AND THAT
THEY SAID IT WAS ALL RIGHT.
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
WELL, ACTUALLY I...
CAME HERE WITHOUT LETTING
ANYONE KNOW.
- WHAT?
- LADY AOI,
IT IS IMPERATIVE THAT
YOU BETTER UNDERSTAND
THE SITUATION YOU ARE IN.
THE SAKURABA FAMILY OPENED
ITS FIRST KIMONO SHOP
OVER 200 YEARS AGO.
IT HAS SINCE BECOME
A PRESTIGIOUS FAMILY
THAT RUNS ONE OF THE LARGEST
CONGLOMERATES IN THE NATION,
THE SAKURABA GROUP.
YOU MUST ALWAYS REMEMBER
TO ACT RESPONSIBLY SO THAT
YOU DO NOT DISGRACE THE NAME
OF THE SAKURABAS.
- I APOLOGIZE FOR LEAVING
WITHOUT PERMISSION.
HOWEVER I AM-- I AM STILL
KAORU-SAMA'S FIANCEE.
- THIS MAN HERE
NO LONGER POSSESSES
ANY TIES
TO THE HANABISHI FAMILY.
THE MAN WHO WILL BECOME
YOUR HUSBAND, LADY AOI,
WILL ONE DAY TAKE THE
SEAT AS THE PRESIDENT
OF THE SAKURABA GROUP.
AND IT IS FOR THAT REASON
YOU MUST BE WED TO A MAN
OF YOUR OWN HIGH CALIBER.
HOWEVER,
THIS MAN HAS BEEN BANISHED
FROM THE HANABISHI CLAN.
HIS RELATIONSHIP WITH YOUR
FAMILY ENDED AT THE SAME TIME.
AN ORDINARY MAN
WITH NO POWER WHATSOEVER
COULD NEVER BE WORTHY OF YOU.
SO COME, WE MUST
RETURN IMMEDIATELY.
- KAORU-SAMA!
- THAT IS ENOUGH, LADY AOI.
- I WILL NOT GO. I DO NOT WISH
TO LEAVE KAORU-SAMA'S SIDE.
- IS IT STILL NOT CLEAR TO YOU?
- I CANNOT IMAGINE BEING WITH
ANYONE OTHER THAN KAORU-SAMA.
I HAVE BEEN LIVING TO THIS DAY
SOLELY FOR THE PURPOSE
OF BECOMING HIS WIFE.
- ( sighs ) AOI-CHAN.
- WON'T YOU PLEASE
CONSIDER RETURNING...
- HUH?
- ...TO HANABISHI?
IF YOU RETURN
TO THE HANABISHI HOUSE,
WE CAN BE TOGETHER.
PLEASE, IS THERE NO WAY THAT
YOU WOULD RETURN?
- ( heart beating )
UH, I...
I-- I JUST--
I CAN'T. I WON'T GO BACK
TO THE HANABISHI CLAN.
- ( glass breaks )
- OH, KAORU-SAMA!
( crying )
- YOU SEE FOR YOURSELF NOW,
DON'T YOU?
IN THE END, IT IS OBVIOUS THAT
HE IS A MAN OF LOW CALIBER.
COME, LET'S GO.
YOUR PARENTS ARE ALSO
WORRIED ABOUT YOU AS WELL.
- ALL RIGHT, I'LL GO.
BUT IN A BIT.
PLEASE AT LEAST ALLOW US
A BRIEF MOMENT TO SPEAK ALONE.
- LADY AOI.
- PLEASE, I BEG OF YOU.
ONCE WE ARE DONE TALKING, I
PROMISE THAT I WILL GO WITH YOU.
- YOU MAY HAVE YOUR MOMENT.
- I AM VERY HAPPY THAT I WAS
ABLE TO SEE YOU AGAIN,
KAORU-SAMA.
YOU WERE SO WONDERFUL WHEN
I KNEW YOU AS A YOUNG BOY.
BUT YOU ARE MORE GENTLE NOW
THAN I COULD HAVE EVER IMAGINED.
AND SO KIND.
I WOULD BE SO HAPPY
IF I COULD CONTINUE
BEING HERE
WITH YOU LIKE THIS.
HOWEVER, IF THIS IS THE DECISION
YOU YOURSELF HAVE MADE,
I CANNOT DO ANYTHING.
- ( wind blowing )
- THE REASON THAT I LEFT
THE HANABISHI HOUSE IS BECAUSE
I WASN'T A MEMBER OF THEIR CLAN
TO BEGIN WITH.
- WHAT?
- MY FORMER NAME
WAS KAORU HONJO.
AND MY MOTHER
KUMI HONJO WAS NEVER
ACTUALLY OFFICIALLY MARRIED
TO MY FATHER YUJI HANABISHI.
BECAUSE THE HANABISHI FAMILY
WAS OPPOSED TO THEIR MARRIAGE.
BUT WHEN I WAS FIVE,
RIGHT WHEN MY FATHER PASSED AWAY
FROM A TRAFFIC ACCIDENT,
THEY CHANGED THEIR MINDS
AND THEY SAID THEY
WANTED TO ADOPT ME.
MY MOTHER DID AS
THE HANABISHI CLAN ASKED
TO PROTECT ME FROM HARDSHIP.
AND BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT
TO WORRY MY MOTHER
I PRETENDED TO BE THE HEIR
TO THE HANABISHI FAMILY
ALL THAT TIME.
BUT I COULDN'T DO IT.
IN THE END I JUST COULDN'T
BECOME ONE OF THEM.
- STOP IT!
- ( flames crackling )
- PLEASE STOP IT!
- THAT HUSSY DIED
HALF A YEAR AGO.
WHAT GOOD DOES THINKING
ABOUT THE DEAD DO?
YOU SHOULD GROW UP...
- ( gasps )
- ...AND FORGET THAT
YOU KNEW HER.
- YOU DARE?
YOU DARE DEFY ME?!
- ( grunting )
- AND WHAT'S WITH THAT LOOK?
( kicks )
GIVE THAT TO ME.
NOW!
YOU STUBBORN BRAT!
- ( sobbing )
- DO YOU EVEN UNDERSTAND
THAT YOU ARE THE NEXT HEAD
OF THE 300-YEAR-OLD
HANABISHI CONGLOMERATE?
DO YOU INTEND
TO MAKE US WASTE
ALL THAT TIME
AND EFFORT RAISING YOU?
- ( blows continue )
- ( screams )
- THAT WAS WHEN I DECIDED I
WOULD LEAVE THE HANABISHI HOUSE.
THIS IS A CHARM
THAT I GOT FROM MY MOTHER.
IT WAS THE ONLY THING
THAT I MANAGED TO PROTECT.
THERE IS A PIECE
OF MY PLACENTA IN THIS THING
AND IT IS THE ONLY THING THAT
I HAVE LEFT TO REMIND ME OF HER.
THERE ISN'T A SINGLE PERSON
LEFT IN THIS WORLD
THAT I CAN CALL MY FAMILY.
THAT WASN'T A HOME.
IT WAS JUST A PRISON.
AND THAT'S WHY
I'LL NEVER GO BACK.
HUH?
- OH, KAORU-SAMA.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN
VERY DIFFICULT FOR YOU.
- Kaoru: AOI-CHAN'S HANDS...
THEY'RE SO WARM.
WHAT IS THIS?
THIS FEELING?
IT FEELS SO FAMILIAR,
SO SOOTHING.
OH, I SEE.
THAT'S WHY.
- LADY AOI, COME.
IT'S TIME TO GO.
YOU MUST NOT STAY IN A PLACE
SUCH AS THIS FOR LONG.
- Kaoru: AOI-CHAN?
I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST THAT I--
- Aoi: KAORU-SAMA?
- HUH?
- DON'T WORRY.
I WILL BE FINE.
THERE IS NO REASON
FOR YOU TO FEEL GUILTY.
I DISRUPTED YOUR DAILY
ROUTINES, AFTER ALL.
PLEASE, DO TRY TO EAT PROPERLY,
WATCH YOUR HEALTH
AND DON'T OVEREXERT YOURSELF.
- AOI-CHAN...
- KAORU-SAMA,
THERE IS NO NEED TO LOOK
AT ME WITH SUCH CONCERN.
I WILL BE--
I WILL BE
PERFECTLY ALL RIGHT.
SO PLEASE DON'T WORRY.
( sobs )
I WILL BE
PERFECTLY ALL RIGHT.
AFTER ALL, YOU REMAINED
THE SAME KAORU-SAMA
THAT I LOVED SO MUCH.
AND I ASK THAT YOU
PLEASE CONTINUE
BEING EXACTLY THE WAY
YOU ARE NOW.
ALWAYS BE THE ONE PERSON
WHOM I LOVE SO VERY MUCH.
I AM SORRY TO HAVE
TROUBLED YOU, KAORU-SAMA.
- ( echoing door closing )
( rain pattering )
- EH, IT'S HANABISHI.
- HEY THERE, HANABISHI. YOU
WANT TO GO GRAB A BITE TO EAT?
- HANABISHI, HEY, WAIT UP!
- Both: HANABISHI!
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
- DON'T KNOW.
- ( couple laughing )
- Man: BUT YOU KNOW.
- Woman: YOU'RE SO FUNNY.
- I HAVE ALREADY TAKEN
THE LIBERTY OF INFORMING
YOUR MOTHER AND FATHER,
LADY AOI.
BOTH OF THEM WERE
TERRIBLY WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
PLEASE, DON'T EVER BEHAVE IN
SUCH A HAPHAZARD FASHION AGAIN.
LADY AOI, IF SOMETHING
WERE TO HAPPEN TO YOU,
I WOULD--
- ( thinking )
KAORU-SAMA...
- THERE ISN'T ANYONE
THAT I CAN CALL FAMILY.
- ( thinking ) IT IS BETTER
THIS WAY. IF I WERE THERE,
IT WOULD ONLY SERVE TO REMIND
HIM OF WHAT HAPPENED BACK THEN.
BUT STILL...
- Girl: MOMMY!
- UH?
- ( crying )
HEY, MOMMY,
WHERE DID YOU GO?
MOMMY!
( wailing )
- MAKO-CHAN!
- MOMMY!
( crying continues )
- KAORU-SAMA, WILL YOU BE ALL
ALONE FOREVER FROM THIS DAY ON?
- ( lock clicks )
- I'M...
HOME.
( sighs )
WAS THIS ROOM ALWAYS
THIS BIG AND EMPTY?
HUH?
- Aoi: "LAST NIGHT'S LEFTOVERS
ARE IN THE POT IN
THE REFRIGERATOR.
PLEASE EAT IT ALL SOON.
AOI."
- THIS IS BAD.
AND I THOUGHT THAT I WAS
USED TO BEING ALONE.
WHY IS IT...
WHY IS IT THAT
I FEEL SO LONELY?
( sniffling )
- ( phone ringing )
- Machine:
We are not home right now.
Please leave your name
and a brief message
after the beep.
( beeps )
- Aoi: Kaoru-sama.
- HUH?
I apologize for troubling you
while you are away.
- AOI-CHAN!
- Kaoru-sama.
Thank goodness you are home.
- IS SOMETHING WRONG, AOI-CHAN?
- Uh, um, Kaoru-sama,
please rescue me.
- HMM? RESCUE YOU?
- I-- I HAVE TO SEE YOU AGAIN
AND TELL YOU SOMETHING.
I MANAGED TO ESCAPE
FROM MISS MIYABI,
BUT I SEEM TO HAVE
GOTTEN LOST IN THE PROCESS.
- You escaped?
Where are you right now?
- LET'S SEE... I BELIEVE THIS IS
THE STATION WHERE WE FIRST MET.
- ALL RIGHT, I'LL BE RIGHT THERE
SO DON'T MOVE AN INCH, OKAY?
SHE-- SHE DIDN'T GO HOME YET.
- I HAVE RETURNED HERE.
BUT WHAT IN THE WORLD
SHOULD I SAY TO HIM?
HOW SHOULD I APPROACH HIM?
I AM CERTAIN THAT
I AM BOTHERING HIM.
I AM ULTIMATELY BEING
A NUISANCE TO KAORU-SAMA.
COMING TO SEE HIM.
NOT ASKING IF I COULD.
AND CALLING HIM OUT HERE TOO.
HE MIGHT NOT FORGIVE ME
FOR BEHAVING THIS WAY.
HE MAY BE VERY ANGRY AT ME.
HE COULD VERY WELL
HAVE ALREADY BEGUN TO HATE ME.
KAORU-SAMA.
- AOI-CHAN!
- UH?
- ( panting )
- KAORU-SAMA.
UM, UM, I HAD...
SOMETHING IMPORTANT
I WANTED TO TELL YOU.
I'VE GIVEN IT QUITE A
LOT OF THOUGHT
AS I WAS WAITING FOR YOU HERE.
AND I REALIZE I MAY
BE A NUISANCE,
BUT EVEN SO, I KNOW THAT
I MUST SAY THIS TO YOU.
AND SO THE TRUTH IS...
I AM SO SORRY.
( sobbing )
- COME ON, LET'S GO HOME.
- ALL RIGHT.
- YOU'RE COLD, RIGHT?
THE BATH'S READY,
SO WHY DON'T YOU GO FIRST?
- I COULDN'T POSSIBLY, WHEN
YOU ARE MUCH MORE WET THAN I.
- UH. ( laughs )
I'M FINE.
SO GO AHEAD.
- KAORU-SAMA?
- YEAH?
- ACTUALLY AFTER
BEING SEPARATED,
I'VE GIVEN THIS MUCH THOUGHT,
WHAT MISS MIYABI HAD SAID
ABOUT THE SAKURABA FAMILY
AND ALSO CONCERNING
MY FATHER AND MOTHER.
HOWEVER... HOWEVER
I'VE DECIDED NOW
LIKE YOU I WILL PART WAYS
WITH MY FAMILY!
- ( gasps )
- I WISH TO BE WITH YOU
EVEN IF IT MEANS
THROWING EVERYTHING AWAY.
SO THEREFORE,
I ASK YOU
PLEASE ACCEPT ME
VOWS AND ALL
AND MAKE ME
YOUR WIFE, KAORU-SAMA.
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- WHAT SHOULD I DO?
I SAID VOWS.
HE WILL SEE
EVERYTHING ABOUT ME.
- "AI YORI AOSHI":
LIVING TOGETHER.
- Aoi: OH, I CAN HEAR
YOUR HEARTBEAT.