- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- I HAVE ALL THE INGREDIENTS
I NEED FOR DINNER.
AND NOW--
( slightly gasps )
- ( birds chirping )
HOW BEAUTIFUL.
A RESORT, HUH?
I'D LIKE TO WITH
KAORU-SAMA SOMEDAY.
IF ONLY I COULD SEE
SUCH BEAUTIFUL SCENERY
TOGETHER WITH HIM.
( sighs )
WHAT IN THE WORLD WAS GOING
THROUGH MY HEAD BACK THEN?
BRINGING THESE FLYERS
WITH ME.
BUT...
BUT STILL,
WE WILL GO TOGETHER ONE DAY.
I'M SURE.
- Tina: WELL, WE JUST
HAVE TO INVITE THE LANDLORD
AND THE MANAGER TOO.
- Man: YEAH, GOOD IDEA.
- AFTER ALL, THE MORE
THE MERRIER, RIGHT?
- ( gasps )
OH, MY--
- WE'RE BACK, AOI-CHAN.
- UH, OH, HI.
WELCOME BACK, EVERYBODY.
YOU ALL CAME BACK
RATHER EARLY.
- YEAH, WELL, ALL THREE OF US
JUST HAPPENED TO HAVE
ALL OF OUR AFTERNOON CLASSES
CANCELLED.
- MISS LANDLORD, COME WITH US.
WE'RE GOING TO THE HOT SPRINGS.
- HOT SPRINGS?
IS THAT SO?
- ( horn honks loudly )
- AHH!
THE MOUNTAIN AIR
SURE IS FRESH.
- ( bell rings )
- IT SURE IS.
WE FINALLY MADE IT.
- Taeko: HEY, EVERYONE.
- All: HUH?
- WOULD YOU PLEASE WAIT?
- TAEKO-CHAN?
- ( exhales )
HOLD ON.
( yelps )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT THERE,
MISS TAEKO?
- AHH, I'M FINE.
I'M KINDA USED TO THESE
SORTA THINGS HAPPENING.
- HOLD ON, WHERE THE HECK
ARE THE LUNCH BOXES WE BROUGHT?
- MM?  HUH?
- ( horn honking )
- ( Taeko screams )
I'M SORRY, EVERYONE.
- Sato:
AND I WANTED TO EAT IT TOO.
- Suzuki:
NOT MUCH WE CAN DO NOW.
GUESS WE'LL GIVE UP ON THEM
AND EAT OUT SOMEWHERE.
- Taeko: I'M REALLY SORRY.
- Tina:
HEY, CHEER UP, TAE.
WE'RE HAVING THE WELCOME PARTY
FOR NEW PHOTO CLUB
MEMBERS TODAY.
YOU'RE THE MAIN EVENT, TAE!
- Taeko: RIGHT...
- UH, EXCUSE ME, EVERYONE?
- YEAH?  WHAT'S UP, AOI-CHAN?
- IS IT REALLY ALL RIGHT
THAT I COME ALONG?
I'M NOT A MEMBER OF
THE PHOTOGRAPHY CLUB, AFTER ALL.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT
A THING, MISS LANDLORD.
I WOULDN'T HAVE DRAGGED YOU
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE
IF IT WASN'T OKAY.
- YEAH, AND PRETTY GIRLS
ARE ALWAYS WELCOME IN MY BOOK.
- MAN, WISH I WAS
IN YOUR SHOES.
LIVING UNDER THE ROOF
OF A GORGEOUS LANDLORD.
- ( chuckles )
I SEE.  SO THAT'S THE WAY
IT LOOKS IN OTHER PEOPLE'S EYES.
- OH.
YOU ALL CERTAINLY KNOW
HOW TO FLATTER PEOPLE WELL,
DON'T YOU?
- ( all laugh )
- THE AIR REALLY IS
NICE OUT HERE.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN NICE
IF MISS MIYABI COULD HAVE
COME ALONG TOO.
- HMM.
THAT'S TRUE, BUT--
- I WAS ORIGINALLY PLANNING
TO GO WITH LADY AOI
ON THE GETAWAY TOMORROW,
BUT...
DUE TO WORK CIRCUMSTANCES,
I AM AFRAID THAT I WILL
HAVE TO PASS THIS TIME AROUND.
THEREFORE,
I'M ASKING YOU TO TAKE
THE BEST OF CARE!
THE BEST CARE OF LADY AOI,
IS THAT UNDERSTOOD?!
IF ANYTHING SHOULD
HAPPEN TO HER
UNDER YOUR WATCHFUL EYE,
SIR KAORU...
- MISS MIYABI SOUNDED LIKE
SHE'D REALLY KILL ME
IF ANYTHING HAPPENED TO YOU.
- Tina: BY THE WAY, TAE...
- Both: HMM?
- ...WHEN THE HECK ARE WE
GONNA FINALLY REACH THE HOTEL?
- I'M NOT SURE.
- BUT DIDN'T YOU SAY THAT
IT WAS NEAR THE TRAIN STATION?
- Tina: TRAIN STATION?
- IF I RECALL,
THE TRAIN STATION SHOULD BE
SOMEWHERE IN THIS DIRECTION.
- All: HUH?
- ( beeping )
- I'M SORRY.
MY SENSE OF DIRECTION'S
NOT SO GOOD.
- YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO KNOWS HOW TO GET THERE,
SINCE YOU MADE
THE RESERVATION,
SO GET A GRIP ALREADY,
MINAZUKI.
- RIGHT. THE HOTEL'S CALLED
THE MANOU INN, AND LET'S SEE...
LET'S SEE.
OH, I SEE IT NOW.
IT'S THAT WAY.
IF WE TAKE THIS PATH,
IT'LL BE A SHORTCUT.
- ( water rushing )
- UH...
I'M SORRY,
IT'S THIS WAY.
( chuckles nervously )
UH.
- MONKEY REGRET!
- ( laughing )
HEY, MR. MONKEY, UP HERE!
- I THINK IT'S OVER HERE.
( nervously chuckles )
- ARE YOU READY, EVERYONE?
- All: CHEESE!
- MAY-- MAYBE IT'S OVER
THIS WAY.
- ( all groaning )
- OH, NO.
- ( yawns )
JUST WHERE EXACTLY IS THIS HOTEL
WE'RE STAYING AT?
- WE'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR THREE HOURS.
- OH, I'M SORRY.
- HUH?
AOI-CHAN, ARE YOU DOING OKAY?
I AM PERFECTLY FINE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR YOUR CONCERN, KAORU-SAMA.
- GOOD TO HEAR.
AOI-CHAN LOOKS SO SMALL
AND FRAIL.
BUT SHE MIGHT BE
STRONGER THAN I THOUGHT.
- Taeko:
I'M SORRY!  I'M SORRY!
EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENED
WAS MY FAULT.
- TAEKO-CHAN, HOLD ON.
IF THE STATION'S THERE
AND THIS IS THE MAIN STREET,
AND THE HOTEL IS AT
THE END OF THE STREET...
UH--
- All: AAH!
- ( bell tolls )
- Kaoru: I WAS WONDERING WHAT
WOULD HAPPEN FOR A WHILE THERE.
- DESPITE IT ALL,
IT'S STILL GOOD THAT
WE FOUND THE HOTEL.
- MAN, I'M BEAT.
I WANNA GET TO THE HOT SPRINGS
PRONTO AND START RELAXING.
- Taeko: WHAT?!
- All: HUH?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU DON'T SEE IT?
- I'M SORRY.
AS I ALREADY SAID,
THERE'S NO RESERVATION
UNDER THAT NAME.
- THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
I'M SURE THAT I MADE
A RESERVATION.
IT'S THE MEIRITSU UNIVERSITY
PHOTO CLUB.
- SO YOU SAY,
BUT IT'S NOT HERE.
- IT COULDN'T BE THAT
YOU MADE THE RESERVATION
FOR NEXT MONTH, COULD IT?
TAE?
- YOU KNOW WHAT, TINA?
EVEN IF WE ARE
TALKING ABOUT TAEKO-CHAN,
I DON'T THINK THAT SHE WOULD--
- OH, IT MUST BE
THIS RESERVATION.
IT'S MADE FOR THIS DAY
NEXT YEAR.
- AAH!
- NO-- NO WAY.
- EXCUSE ME, ARE THERE ANY
AVAILABLE ROOMS NOW?
- UNFORTUNATELY,
WE'RE BOOKED SOLID TONIGHT.
AND THERE HAVEN'T BEEN
ANY CANCELLATIONS EITHER.
- ISN'T THERE ANYTHING THAT
YOU COULD DO FOR US?
- I'M AFRAID THAT
THERE REALLY ISN'T.
- KAORU-SAMA.
( slightly gasps )
- LADY AOI,
IF YOU HAVE ANY PROBLEMS,
THEN PLEASE,
USE THIS V.I.P. CARD.
MOST CORPORATIONS WILL DO
SOMETHING IF YOU HAVE THIS.
- ( all groan )
- I'M SORRY.
- WHAT NOW...?
- PARDON ME, ANY ROOM YOU
HAVE WOULD BE ACCEPTABLE.
ISN'T THERE ANY WAY?
- AS I SAID EARLIER,
WE'RE BOOKED SOLID--
HUH?
ISN'T-- ISN'T THIS...
( stammering )
GE-- GET A ROOM THIS INSTANT!
- Man: HUH, BUT AREN'T
WE BOOKED SOLID?
- JUST DO IT!
- YES, SIR!
- ( running footsteps )
- ( clears throat )
I AM TERRIBLY SORRY.
WE WILL HAVE A ROOM
PREPARED FOR YOU MOMENTARILY.
- I THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- AOI-CHAN.
- THIS IS GREAT NEWS,
ISN'T IT?
- THANKS FOR THE SAVE.
WE CAN STAY.
AOI-CHAN HERE
TALKED THEM INTO IT.
- ALL RIGHT!
- THANK YOU SO MUCH, MISS AOI.
- YOU'RE SOMETHING ELSE,
MISS LANDLORD.
- EH, WAS NOTHING.
AFTER ALL,
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
THAT KAORU-SAMA AND I WILL--
- ( knocking )
- Tina:
AHH, IF THIS ISN'T HEAVEN,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IS.
NOTHING'S BETTER THAN
SOAKING IN THE HOT SPRINGS
AFTER A HARD DAY.
- YEAH, BUT...
( sighs )
IF IT WEREN'T
FOR WHAT I DID...
- Aoi: WHAT'S THE MATTER,
MISS TAEKO?
- MISS AOI.
I AM REALLY SUCH
A KLUTZ, YOU KNOW.
I JUST SEEM TO CAUSE TROUBLE
FOR ALL OF THE PEOPLE AROUND ME.
( deeply sighs )
LIKE TODAY.
I'M JUST THE TYPE OF PERSON
WHO CAN'T DO ANYTHING RIGHT.
- I DON'T THINK
THAT'S TRUE AT ALL.
MISS TAEKO.
- MISS AOI.
- DO YOUR BEST,
AND SOMEONE WILL ALWAYS BE THERE
TO ACKNOWLEDGE THAT EFFORT.
AND THAT'S TRUE
FOR THE BOTH OF US.
THAT'S WHY
I ALWAYS DO MY BEST
THINKING ABOUT
THAT PARTICULAR PERSON.
I CAN DO MY BEST
EVEN IN DIFFICULT SITUATIONS
WHEN I IMAGINE
THAT PERSON'S HAPPINESS.
SO, YOU SHOULD DO
YOUR BEST AS WELL TOO.
I'M SURE YOU CAN,
IF I COULD DO IT.
YOU KNOW I'LL BE
ROOTING FOR YOU.
- THANKS A LOT, MISS AOI.
- HEY, WHAT'S WITH
THE LONG FACES OVER THERE?
WE'RE ON A GETAWAY, AFTER ALL.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE HAVING
ALL THE FUN WE CAN.
RIGHT?
- RIGHT!
- Suzuki: ALL RIGHT!
WE CAN'T CALL IT A GETAWAY
IF WE DON'T HAVE A PARTY!
- HEY, THERE!
- WE'VE ALREADY STARTED.
- THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT
A BLONDE WEARING A YUKATA.
- SHE LOOKS PRETTY GOOD
AT FIRST GLANCE.
- OH.  OW!
I'M SORRY FOR
KEEPING YOU WAITING.
- ( gulps )
- AMAZING'S ALL I CAN SAY.
- I THOUGHT TINA WAS
WELL-ENDOWED,
BUT SHE'S JUST HUGE.
- THANK YOU FOR WAITING.
- BEAUTIFUL.
- ELEGANT.
- YEAH.
- Tina: AND NOW IN HONOR OF
THE FURTHER EVOLUTION
OF THE MEIRITSU UNIVERSITY
PHOTO CLUB...
- All: CHEERS!
( laughter )
- Tina: BOTTOMS UP!
- ( gulping )
- ( chewing loudly )
- ( slurping )
- ( raucous laughter )
- SO, MINAZUKI...
- OH!
( coughs )
YES, CHIEF, WHAT CAN I
HELP YOU WITH?
- I'LL BE GIVING YOU AN
IMPORTANT ORDER TO FOLLOW NOW.
- OH?  AN IMPORTANT
ORDER TO FOLLOW?
- ( gulping )
- LOOK AT THIS PICTURE.
- HMM.
THIS IS...
OH.
WHAT IS THIS THING, ANYWAY?
- THAT'S A PICTURE
OF A HUMAN SOUL
THAT TWO COURAGEOUS FRESHMAN
NAMED SUZUKI AND
SATO MADE POSSIBLE.
- HMM.
- SO IT'S...
SUPERNATURAL.
- ( gasps )
- WE'RE GOING TO HAVE YOU
HEAD OUT
TO THIS CERTAIN PLACE NOW.
IT'S A TEMPLE
THAT'S ABOUT A KILOMETER OUT
FROM THIS MOUNTAIN.
THAT TEMPLE BURIED DEEP
IN THE WOODS
IS A SPOT THAT'S FAMOUS
FOR ITS GHOSTS.
GHOSTS ARE GUARANTEED
TO BE THERE WHEN YOU GO.
ALL NEW MEMBERS ARE
REQUIRED TO GO THERE,
AND TAKE A PICTURE
OF A GHOST!
THIS IS A TRADITION
OF THE MEIRITSU PHOTO CLUB!
CALLED THE "PHOTO SHOOT
TRIAL OF COURAGE"!
AND TODAY IS THE DAY!
MINAZUKI, IT'S YOUR TURN!
AND I'LL TELL YOU NOW
THAT IT HASN'T BEEN JUST US.
HANABISHI AND TINA DID IT TOO.
IT'S A TRADITION.
IN OTHER WORDS,
YOU CAN'T BACK OUT OF IT,
SO DON'T EVEN TRY!
- ( shuddering )
I AM NEVER GOING THERE AGAIN.
- SO YOU'D BETTER GET READY.
- WOW!
THAT'S A WONDERFUL TRADITION
TO HAVE, CHIEF.
THESE KINDS OF CULT THINGS
REALLY APPEAL TO ME, YOU KNOW?
- MINAZUKI,
DO YOU REALLY UNDERSTAND
WHAT WE WANT YOU TO DO?
- ALL YOU WANT ME TO
DO IS FIND A GHOST
AND TAKE A PHOTOGRAPH, RIGHT?!
I WILL DO MY BEST, CHIEF!
WELL, THEN, I'LL BE GOING NOW!
- GOOD LUCK, MINAZUKI.
- ( off-key )
♪ AND WE'RE MEN ♪
♪ WELCOMED WITH SAKE... ♪
- ( guys cheering )
- ♪ YOU ARE 18
AND I AM 19... ♪
♪ THE FLOWER OF WOMAN... ♪
- I WONDER IF MISS TAEKO IS
ALL RIGHT.
- YEAH.
I THINK THAT
SHE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
- I'M SORRY, MY SENSE
OF DIRECTION'S NOT SO GOOD.
- IT CAN'T BE.
- ♪ ...CRY AND MAKE UP. ♪
- KAORU-SAMA?
ARE YOU GOING TO GO LOOK
FOR MISS TAEKO?
- UH-HUH.
- PLEASE, ALLOW ME TO
COME ALONG WITH YOU.
- UH, BUT IT'S--
- I BEG OF YOU.
I'M ALSO WORRIED ABOUT
MISS TAEKO, KAORU-SAMA.
- AOI-CHAN.
- ( wind blowing )
- IT'S PITCH-BLACK.
FOLLOW ME.
AND DON'T EVER LEAVE
MY SIDE, AOI-CHAN, OKAY?
- RIGHT.
MISS TAEKO!
- TAEKO-CHAN!
- MISS TAEKO!
- ( wood creaking )
- OH.
- THE WIND'S PICKING UP
AND THE FOG TOO.
- ( squawks )
- AAH.
JUST-- JUST A BIRD.
THAT SURPRISED ME.
( exhales )
THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN SCARY
IF I WAS ALONE.
( chuckles )
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, AOI-CHAN?
- OH.
I AM PERFECTLY ALL RIGHT.
BUT WE OUGHT TO HURRY.
I'M CERTAIN MISS TAEKO
MUST FEEL OVERWHELMED,
SINCE SHE'S ALL ALONE
RIGHT NOW.
- YE-- YEAH.
THAT'S TRUE.
I'M IMPRESSED.
AOI-CHAN ISN'T SCARED OF
THINGS LIKE THIS?
HERE IT IS.
- WHERE'S MISS TAEKO?
- TAEKO-CHAN!
- MISS TAEKO!
- WHERE ARE YOU,
MISS TAEKO!
COULD SHE BE
INSIDE THE TEMPLE?
- MAYBE.
SHE'S NOT HERE.
WHERE COULD SHE
HAVE GOTTEN TO?
- UH, KAORU-SAMA?
- HUH?
- L-- LOOK THERE.
- ( whirring )
- IT'S HERE!
- Both: OHH!
- WHAT THE-- IS THAT YOU
OVER THERE, SENPAI?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE?
- ( stammers )
TAEKO-CHAN.
- OHH, SO THAT'S IT.
- BUT IN ANY CASE,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, MISS TAEKO?
YOU'RE NOT HURT, ARE YOU?
- NO.  I WAS JUST SO ENGROSSED
IN TAKING PICTURES
THAT I REALLY WASN'T
KEEPING TRACK OF THE TIME.
I DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE
HOW MUCH TIME HAD GONE BY.
- I... SEE.
- I'M REALLY SORRY.
IT LOOKS LIKE I'VE BEEN
CAUSING TROUBLE FOR YOU AGAIN.
- WELL, I'M JUST GLAD
YOU WERE ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE DONE TAKING
YOUR PICTURES, RIGHT?
LET'S GET BACK TO
THE HOTEL, OKAY?
- ( all gasp )
- Aoi:
THERE'S SO MUCH FOG.
- ( Kaoru sighs )
THIS ISN'T GOOD.
WE CAN'T SEE A THING NOW.
- Taeko:
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
IT'S A STRAIGHT PATH
BACK TO THE HOTEL.
- PERHAPS,
BUT I THINK IT'S BEST
IF WE WAIT HERE
FOR THE FOG TO CLEAR.
WE PASSED BY SOME CLIFFS
AND A RIVER ALONG THE WAY HERE.
IF WE WERE TO STRAY
FROM THE PATH,
THERE'S A POSSIBILITY
THAT WE COULD END UP IN DANGER.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
LET'S WAIT FOR THE FOG TO CLEAR.
- I HOPE THAT MISS TINA AND THE
OTHERS ARE NOT WORRIED ABOUT US.
- ( bell dings )
- ( all snoring loudly )
- WHAT'S THIS?
TAEKO-CHAN'S ASLEEP ALREADY.
- SHE MUST HAVE BEEN
VERY TIRED.
- YEAH, LOOKS THAT WAY.
- ( shivering )
- ARE YOU COLD?
- NO.  OHH.
I FEEL RELIEVED NOW,
BUT...
- HUH?
- ACTUALLY,
TO TELL THE TRUTH,
IT WAS REALLY FRIGHTENING FOR ME
TO COME ALL THE WAY OUT HERE.
- THEN WHY'D YOU
PUT UP WITH IT?
- WELL, IT'S BEEN
MY DREAM LATELY
TO GO ON A GETAWAY
WITH YOU, KAORU-SAMA.
- I GET IT.
- ( inaudible )
- ( slow piano melody playing )
- THE REASON
SHE LOOKED COMPOSED
WASN'T BECAUSE
SHE WAS STRONG,
BUT BECAUSE SHE WAS
GOING OUT OF HER WAY
TO KEEP ME FROM
WORRYING ABOUT HER.
THE REAL AOI-CHAN WAS
ACTUALLY...
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
DON'T WORRY ANYMORE.
- I'M SORRY.
OH.  OH.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
I CAN'T SEEM
TO STOP TREMBLING.
- MM.
AOI-CHAN?
- YES?
( exhales )
KA-- KAORU-SAMA?
- YOUR TREMBLING,
IT STOPPED.
- OH.
( gasps )
- ( chuckles )
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT MOST CERTAINLY HAS.
- ( both chuckle softly )
- KAORU-SAMA?
- AOI-CHAN!
- HUH?
- GOOD MORNING.
COME ON OVER HERE.
- ( exhales )
SURE.
THIS IS...
- SEE?  IT'S BEAUTIFUL,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- YES.  AMAZING.
- ( soft flute music playing )
- ANOTHER DREAM OF MINE
HAS COME TRUE.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- NOTHING.
IT'S REALLY NOTHING AT ALL.
UM, KAORU-SAMA?
WOULD YOU BE WILLING TO
TAKE ME SOMEWHERE AGAIN?
- HMM?
- THIS WAS THE FIRST TIME
THAT I WAS EVER ABLE TO
GO ON A FIELD TRIP LIKE THIS.
- SURE.  THE PHOTO CLUB
HAS PLENTY OF OTHER TRIPS
BESIDES THIS GETAWAY.
- I MEAN, UM...
JUST THE TWO OF US.
- ( laughs )
YEAH, LET'S JUST GO
BY OURSELVES NEXT TIME.
- LET'S.
- WE'D BETTER GO WAKE
TAEKO-CHAN UP AND GET BACK.
- MISS TINA AND THE OTHERS
MUST BE WAITING.
- WELL, LET'S GO.
- ( door opens )
- SENPAI!
I DID IT!
I GOT A GREAT PICTURE.
LOOK AT ALL THE GHOSTS.
- ( both gasp )
NO WAY!
- IS SOMETHING THE MATTER,
SENPAI?
- WELL, YOU SEE...
IT'S NOT AS GOOD
AS THE ONE WE TOOK,
BUT I'LL ADMIT THAT
YOU GOT THE RIGHT ATTITUDE
TOWARDS PHOTOGRAPHY,
MINAZUKI.
- DEVELOP YOUR TECHNICAL SKILLS
AND YOU'LL BE A PROUD
MEMBER OF THE PHOTO CLUB.
- YES, SIR!
I'LL CONTINUE TO DO
MY VERY BEST!
- ( bell dings )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Tina: HEY, MISS LANDLORD,
WHAT'S WHITE AND WARM
AND GOES "SQUEAK SQUEAK"?
WHAT IS IT?!
- ( doorbell rings )
- Aoi: KAORU-SAMA?
- Tina: HUH?
- "AI YORI AOSHI:
CHERISHED TREASURE"!
( giggles )
OH, THAT TICKLES!
OH, NO! NOT HERE!