- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( children giggling )
- HUH?
- ( giggles )
- KAORU-SAMA.
( humming )
- HUH?
AOI-CHAN?
HUH.
HUH?
I KNOW THAT SONG.
THANK YOU SO VERY MUCH,
KAORU-SAMA.
THAT BATH WAS
SIMPLY WONDERFUL.
KAORU-SAMA...
- ( gasps )
- IS THERE SOMETHING
TROUBLING YOU?
- NO, NOT REALLY.
ANYWAY, YOU MUST BE TIRED
AFTER A BUSY DAY LIKE THIS.
I LAID OUT
THE FUTON FOR YOU,
SO YOU OUGHT TO
GET SOME REST NOW.
- THANK YOU.
BUT WHERE IS
YOUR FUTON?
- I ONLY HAVE ONE,
UNFORTUNATELY.
I CAN JUST SLEEP
ON THE FLOOR SOMEWHERE,
SO IT'S ALL RIGHT.
- I OBJECT.
THAT IS UNACCEPTABLE.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT,
I DON'T MIND.
- IF THAT'S SO,
THEN I PROPOSE A COMPROMISE,
KAORU-SAMA.
INSTEAD, WE COULD SHARE IT,
IF YOU'RE WILLING.
I-- I DO NOT MIND AT ALL.
- ( gasps )
I'M TELLING YOU THAT
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT ME,
SO GET TO SLEEP,
OKAY?
- ( clock ticking )
- KAORU-SAMA'S FUTON.
- AOI-CHAN?
YOU ARE GOING TO GO BACK
HOME TOMORROW, AREN'T YOU?
HUH?
- MUST I GO?
I CANNOT CONTINUE STAYING HERE
AT YOUR SIDE, KAORU-SAMA?
- WELL, IF YOU STAY AWAY
FROM YOUR HOME FOR TOO LONG,
I'M SURE YOUR FAMILY
WOULD WORRY ABOUT YOU.
- OH, I SUPPOSE SO.
- BESIDES,
THINGS ARE MOVING
TOO QUICKLY.
YOU'RE MY FIANCEE,
BUT I--
BUT I ONLY REMEMBER YOU
AS A LITTLE KID.
AND THE SAME
GOES FOR YOU.
- SO THEN--
SO THEN YOU CAN
LEARN MORE ABOUT ME
STARTING RIGHT NOW.
- HUH?
- THE SAME IS TRUE FOR ME.
SO TELL ME.
TELL ME EVERYTHING
ABOUT YOURSELF.
- ( stammers )
COME ON, HURRY UP
AND GET TO SLEEP.
SHE'S SOUND ASLEEP.
SHE MUST HAVE BEEN
REALLY TIRED.
HUH?
SHE WAS HOLDING THIS BEFORE.
I SEE.
SHE MADE A MISTAKE AND WROTE
"DISTRICT FIVE, SECTION TWO"
INSTEAD OF THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
IT'S ALL WORN.
AOI-CHAN MUST HAVE KEPT
THIS NOTE CLOSE TO HER
FOR A LONG TIME...
JUST SO SHE COULD SEE ME.
- THE SAME IS TRUE FOR ME.
SO TELL ME--
TELL ME EVERYTHING
ABOUT YOURSELF.
- UH, AOI-CHAN.
- ( sighs )
- ( gasps )
- ( heart beating )
- ( gulps )
MAN, THIS IS REALLY BAD.
I CAN'T LET THOUGHTS
LIKE THAT GET THE BETTER OF ME.
I GOTTA COOL DOWN
SOMEHOW.
AAH!
IT'S HOT.
( gulps )
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
SHE SAID SHE WAS
MY FIANCEE.
BUT I HAVEN'T EVEN
HAD A GIRLFRIEND YET.
AND NOW SUDDENLY
I HAVE A WIFE?
BUT AOI-CHAN'S NOT
A BAD GIRL OR ANYTHING.
( sighs )
THOUGH IF I ACCEPT AOI-CHAN,
IT MEANS I'LL BE FORCED
BACK INTO THE HANABISHI CLAN.
HANABISHI.
HANABISHI, HUH?
- KAORU-SAMA?
- ( grunts )
- OH, YOU'RE STILL HERE.
THANK GOODNESS.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER,
AOI-CHAN?
- I WOKE UP WHEN
YOU OPENED THE DOOR.
AND WHEN YOU DID NOT RETURN,
I BEGAN TO WORRY
THAT PERHAPS YOU HAD
DISAPPEARED FROM MY LIFE AGAIN.
AND SO, UM, I...
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THAT PLACE IS MY HOME,
YOU KNOW?
THERE'S NO WAY I'D EVER
LEAVE IT JUST LIKE THAT.
- YES, OF COURSE NOT.
I'M SO SILLY.
- COME ON.
LET'S GO BACK.
- YES.
- ♪ IT'S BEEN SUNG ♪
♪ THROUGH ALL GENERATIONS ♪
♪ THE FLOWER OF WORDS ♪
♪ WILL BLOOM. ♪
- HUH?  AAH!
( grunts )
MOM?
- I'M SORRY, KAORU.
I WON'T BE ABLE TO STAY IN
THIS HOUSE ANY LONGER.
TAKE CARE.
BE A GOOD BOY.
- DON'T GO!
DON'T GO, MOM!
( panting )
PLEASE WAIT!
DON'T LEAVE ME HERE
ALL BY MYSELF.
( grunts )
PLEASE COME BACK.
COME BACK, MOM!
GRANDPA, MOM IS LEAVING US.
PLEASE, YOU'VE GOT
TO STOP HER.
PLEASE STOP HER.
HURRY, GRANDPA.
MOM'S GONNA LEAVE!
I DON'T WANT HER TO.
STOP HER!
- YOU AREN'T SOME
BAWLING BABY,
SO STOP ACTING LIKE ONE.
FORGET THAT YOU EVER
KNEW THAT WOMAN.
YOU ARE TO BE THE HEIR
OF THE HANABISHI NAME.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THIS,
KAORU?
- NO, I DON'T.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
AT ALL.
I DON'T GET ANY OF IT!
- Kaoru: DAMN.
THAT DREAM AGAIN.
( grunts )
WHAT?
HUH?!
WHY ARE AOI-CHAN AND I
ON THE SAME FUTON?
I-- I BETTER GET
OUT OF HERE QUICK.
( murmurs )
THIS FEELS...
GOOD.
I CAN'T BREATHE.
( grunts )
( gasps )
- ( sighs )
- WOW.
SHE'S TOO CUTE.
( gulps )
I DIDN'T REALIZE IT
BECAUSE OF THE KIMONO,
BUT AOI-CHAN'S BREASTS
ARE PRETTY BIG.
NO NO NO NO NO.
I HAVE TO GET AWAY SOMEHOW.
IF SHE COMES TO
THE WRONG CONCLUSION...
- ( dog howls )
- GOOD.
I'M FREE NOW.
- Man On TV: You're not
getting away, you pervert!
- ( stammers )
- ( gunshots )
- Man On TV: Oh, no! Now
he's in a submission hold.
The challenger's
in big trouble.
- HOLD ON.
AOI-CHAN!
( screams )
- Man On TV:
That was a close one.
- HUH?  WHOA.
NOW IT'S THE LEGS.
( giggles )
( stammers )
NO!  PLEASE STOP.
ANYWHERE BUT THERE.
- Man On TV: Ooh, the champion
has thrown in the towel!
- FORGIVE ME!
- ( alarm rings )
- ( moans )
( sighs )
OH.
GOOD MORNING.
- GOOD-- GOOD MORNING.
- OH! KAORU-SAMA, IS THERE
SOMETHING THE MATTER WITH YOU?
- THAT'S NOT REALLY IMPORTANT.
WHY WEREN'T YOU IN YOUR
FUTON LAST NIGHT, AOI-CHAN?
- WELL, HONESTLY,
LAST NIGHT I NOTICED
THAT YOU LOOKED VERY COLD
WITH ONLY THAT ONE BLANKET.
SO I GOT INTO YOUR FUTON.
UM, BUT I TEND TO CLING
TO THINGS IN MY SLEEP.
WAS THAT THE CASE?
- YEAH.
TIGHTLY TOO.
- I APOLOGIZE.
OH, BUT KAORU-SAMA,
YOU HELD ONTO ME
AS IF YOU WERE COLD.
THEREFORE,
WE CAN CALL THINGS EVEN.
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
( giggles )
- WELL...
YOU KNOW,
THE PROBLEM ISN'T
WHETHER OR NOT WE'RE EVEN.
- PLEASE,
HAVE SOMETHING TO EAT.
- WOW.
LOOKS DELICIOUS.
- FORGIVE ME.
I LOOKED THROUGH
YOUR REFRIGERATOR
WITHOUT ASKING YOU.
- HEY, I DON'T MIND.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
THERE WASN'T MUCH
OF ANYTHING IN THERE THOUGH.
HOW IN THE WORLD DID YOU
MANAGE TO MAKE BREAKFAST?
AMAZING.
I'M EATING NOW.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- AOI-CHAN?
- HUH?
- I'LL TAKE YOU TO
THE STATION LATER.
I NEED TO HEAD OUT TO MY
FIRST CLASS SOON ANYWAY.
- ( gasps )
BUT I-- I CALLED MY HOUSE
EARLIER THIS MORNING
AND IT TURNS OUT THEY SAID
THAT I WOULD BE ABLE
TO STAY HERE FOR
A LITTLE WHILE LONGER.
UM...
AM I BEING A BOTHER?
- N-NO.  YOU AREN'T AT ALL.
- WELL THEN,
PLEASE ALLOW ME TO SEE YOU OFF
TO THE TRAIN STATION,
KAORU-SAMA.
- SURE.
- SO TELL ME, DO YOU LEAVE FOR
COLLEGE AT THIS TIME EVERY DAY?
- NO, I'M TAKING
MY TIME TODAY
BECAUSE MY FIRST CLASS
STARTS SECOND PERIOD.
- OH, IS THAT THE CASE?
- ( giggling )
- Girl:
YOU ALWAYS MAKE A JOKE.
- ( laughing continues )
- EXCUSE ME...
UM, KAORU-SAMA?
- AOI-CHAN?
- ( gasps )
OH, IT'S NOTHING.
NOTHING AT ALL.
PLEASE, PAY NO ATTENTION.
- HUH?
- UM, KAORU-SAMA?
WHEN ARE YOU
PLANNING ON RETURNING?
- I DON'T THINK IT'LL BE
ALL THAT LATE, I'M PRETTY SURE.
WHY DO YOU ASK?
- IT'S JUST...
I WOULD REALLY LOVE
TO PREPARE DINNER
FOR YOU TONIGHT AS WELL.
WOULD THAT BE ALL RIGHT?
- MAKE DINNER?
FOR ME?
- YES.
- HEY, I DON'T MIND AT ALL.
IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU HAD IN MIND,
THEN I OUGHT TO BE
THE ONE ASKING YOU
IF IT'S ALL RIGHT,
AOI-CHAN.
- I'M SO GLAD.
- I'LL DEFINITELY MAKE SURE
THAT I GET HOME
IN TIME FOR DINNER, OKAY?
- TAKE CARE ON YOUR WAY.
- YEAH.
I'M OFF THEN.
- YES.
I'LL DO MY BEST.
- I'M OFF.
( chuckles )
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
I SAID THAT?
- NOW, WELL, LET'S SEE.
- WELCOME.
- HUH?
- WHAT'LL IT BE, MISSUS?
- OH MY.
I'M NO MISSUS, SIR.
HOWEVER, I WOULD LIKE
THE MACKEREL, PLEASE.
- YOU BET.
THAT'S COMING RIGHT UP.
- ( sighs )
THAT SHOULD BE ALL OF IT.
BUT BEFORE I BEGIN
PREPARING DINNER,
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
ALL RIGHT.
( sighs )
OH, GOODNESS,
THAT KAORU-SAMA.
HE CERTAINLY HAD
A LOT OF LAUNDRY.
( sighs )
HUH?
WHAT?
OHH...
- SO YOU SEE, THE RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN A MAN AND A WOMAN CAN...
- I WONDER WHAT KIND OF DINNER
AOI-CHAN WILL BE MAKING FOR ME.
- ( humming )
( sighs )
THIS ISN'T...
A DREAM.
- HEY, HANABISHI.
WE'RE GOING OUT
DRINKING TONIGHT,
SO DON'T BE LATE.
- DRINKING TONIGHT?
- WE TOLD YOU
THE OTHER DAY.
- YOU DID, HUH.
- YOU ARE COMING,
AREN'T YOU?
- UH, ACTUALLY...
I'M SORRY, BUT I GOT A SUDDEN
CHANGE IN PLANS TODAY.
- YOU SERIOUS?
HANABISHI,
I TOLD YOU EVERY MEMBER
OF THE PHOTO CLUB
HAD TO ATTEND.
- SORRY.
I'LL MAKE SURE
TO GO NEXT TIME.
- ( clock ticking )
- I WONDER WHY IT IS
THAT WHEN I'M WITH KAORU-SAMA
TIME SEEMS TO SLIP BY
SO QUICKLY.
IT IS A BIT EARLY,
BUT...
KAORU-SAMA!
- HUH?
AOI-CHAN!
- PLEASE ALLOW ME
TO WELCOME YOU HOME.
- I'M BACK.
BUT WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE, AOI-CHAN?
- I FINISHED PREPARING DINNER
SOME TIME AGO,
SO I THOUGHT I'D WAIT.
- YEAH, BUT I DON'T THINK
I EVER MENTIONED
WHAT TIME I'D BE
GETTING BACK.
WERE YOU WAITING
THE WHOLE TIME?
- OH, NO.
- HOW LONG WERE YOU WAITING?
- LET'S SEE,
AN HOUR I SUPPOSE?
- FOR AN HOUR?
YOU SHOULD HAVE BEEN
WAITING AT HOME.
- FORGIVE ME.
IT'S JUST...
I WANTED TO BE WITH YOU AGAIN
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
- ( gasps )
- ANYWAY, I WAS LOOKING
FORWARD TO SEEING YOU,
SO IT SEEMED LIKE
A BRIEF MOMENT TO ME.
- OH, I SEE.
- UM... KAORU-SAMA?
- HUH?
- I HAVE A FAVOR
TO ASK OF YOU.
- A FAVOR?
- WELL...
WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT
IF WE HELD HANDS?
- UH... SURE.
- I NEVER REALIZED THAT
YOUR HAND WAS SO MUCH
BIGGER THAN MINE.
- YOU THINK SO?
HUH.
- YES.  HOWEVER,
THE HAND THAT
I REMEMBER HOLDING
WAS THAT OF A CHILD.
IT'S ONLY NATURAL
THAT IT HAS CHANGED.
- IF WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT CHANGES,
THEN YOU'VE CHANGED
A LOT TOO, AOI-CHAN.
- YOU THINK THAT
I'VE CHANGED A LOT?
- YEAH.  A LOT.
- HOW HAVE I CHANGED?
- YOU'VE BECOME
VERY BEAUTIFUL.
- OH.
OH, STOP.
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME.
- ( chuckles )
- Aoi: PLEASE,
GO AHEAD AND START.
- WOW!
LOOKS DELICIOUS.
THANKS FOR ALL THE FOOD.
( chuckles )
WHAT'S THIS, AOI-CHAN?
- OH. CHIKUZEN STEW.
- ( chews )
- HOW IS IT?
- MM-HMM.
- I HOPE IT IS TO YOUR LIKING.
- IT'S GREAT.
TOTALLY DELICIOUS.
- I'M SO GLAD.
PLEASE EAT AS MUCH
AS YOU WOULD LIKE.
THERE'S ENOUGH FOOD
FOR SECONDS.
- MMM!  IT'S THE FIRST TIME
SINCE I LEFT THE HANABISHI HOUSE
THAT I'VE EATEN
FOOD THIS GOOD.
- IS THAT REALLY TRUE?
- MM-HMM.
I EAT INSTANT NOODLES
MOST OF THE TIME.
AND WHEN I DON'T
HAVE ENOUGH MONEY,
I END UP LIVING OFF OF
BREAD CRUSTS.
- LIVE OFF OF BREAD CRUST?
YOU CAN'T MEAN
THAT IS ALL YOU EAT.
- YEP.
BUT THAT'S HOW GUYS
LIVING ALONE USUALLY EAT.
- THAT WON'T DO!
IT WON'T.
YOU MUST EAT SOMETHING
THAT IS MORE NUTRITIOUS.
YOU WILL DIE OTHERWISE.
- ( gulps )
YOU'RE OVERREACTING.
- HERE.  I INSIST
THAT YOU EAT THIS.
I KNOW THAT GRILLED FISH
IS YOUR FAVORITE TOO,
SO HAVE SOME THIS INSTANT.
- THANKS.
GRILLED FISH
IS MY FAVORITE.
HOW DID AOI-CHAN KNOW
WHAT MY FAVORITE FOOD WAS?
COME TO THINK OF IT,
NOW THAT I LOOK AT THIS TABLE,
THIS IS ALL FOOD
THAT I LIKE.
- IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
- UH, AOI-CHAN?
HOW DID YOU KNOW
WHAT FOOD I LIKED?
- WELL, TO TELL THE TRUTH,
I WAS CONSTANTLY WATCHING YOU
WHEN WE WERE STILL CHILDREN,
KAORU-SAMA.
I ALSO LEARNED MANY OTHER THINGS
ABOUT YOU DURING THAT TIME.
THAT YOU LIKED GRILLED FISH,
THAT YOUR FAVORITE COLOR
IS BLUE,
THAT YOU PREFER SHORT HAIR,
AND WHAT KIND OF SONGS
YOU LIKE TOO.
- SONGS?
( gasps )
THAT'S RIGHT.
I WAS WONDERING WHY
AOI-CHAN KNEW THAT SONG
THAT MOTHER ALWAYS SANG.
BUT NOW I REMEMBER.
IT WAS ME.
I TAUGHT HER
THAT SONG BACK THEN.
I'M SURPRISED
YOU REMEMBER THAT SONG.
- THERE'S NO WAY THAT
I WOULD FORGET THE SONG
THAT YOU TAUGHT ME
WHEN WE WERE KIDS.
I SING IT ON OCCASION
TO THIS DAY.
I FELT CLOSER TO YOU
WHENEVER I SANG THAT SONG.
AS IF I COULD OVERCOME
ANY PAINFUL TIMES.
- PAINFUL TIMES?
- YOU KNOW,
I HAVE DONE MY UPMOST
SO THAT I COULD BE
A GOOD WIFE TO YOU.
IT WAS MY ONE DREAM TO BE
TOGETHER WITH YOU LIKE THIS.
I WANT TO CLEAN UP
AFTER YOU.
I WANT TO DO
THE LAUNDRY FOR YOU.
I WANT TO PREPARE
MEALS FOR YOU
THAT YOU WILL ENJOY.
AS LONG AS YOU WISH IT,
I WOULD LIKE TO
FULFILL THAT DESIRE.
- AOI-CHAN...
- FORGIVE ME.
I DID NOT MEAN
TO CHATTER AWAY.
PLEASE FINISH THIS
BEFORE IT GETS COLD.
- SURE.
- ( water sloshing )
- ( sighs )
I NEVER KNEW.
TO THINK THAT AOI-CHAN
HAD FELT THAT DEEPLY ABOUT ME
FOR ALL THESE YEARS.
AND SHE'S SO THOUGHTFUL.
SHE EVEN HAD A BATH ALREADY
DRAWN FOR ME AFTER DINNER.
SHE REALLY IS DOING
EVERYTHING FOR ME.
WHICH MEANS, NEXT IS...
- KAORU-SAMA...
ALLOW ME TO
SCRUB YOUR BACK.
- IF SHE DID
COME IN LIKE THAT,
I REALLY WOULD
FALL FOR HER.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
I REALLY CAN'T SEE
AOI-CHAN DOING THAT.
- ( knocks on door )
- ( gasps )
- KAORU-SAMA, EXCUSE ME?
- I WOULD LIKE TO
SCRUB YOUR BACK.
SO WOULD YOU MIND TERRIBLY
IF I CAME IN?
- WHAT?!
- ( dogs howling )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- YOU BEAST! HOW DARE YOU
DO THIS TO LADY AOI!
- Aoi: MISS MIYABI!
NEXT EPISODE AI YORI AOSHI,
"SEPARATION."
I WILL ALWAYS BE
BY YOUR SIDE.