- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( breathes deeply )
KAORU-SAMA.
- ( sighs )
( sighs )
AOI-CHAN...
OH, THIS ISN'T GOOD.
IF I KEEP THIS UP, I'LL NEVER
TURN THIS IN ON TIME.
HUH?
- ( gulps )
AAH! OH, MAN!
TEA SURE HITS THE SPOT
AFTER A NICE HOT BATH.
- TINA, WHY DON'T YOU KNOCK
BEFORE YOU COME INTO MY ROOM?
OKAY?
- OH, COME ON, KAORU.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE
STRANGERS OR ANYTHING.
- QUIT IT, ALREADY.
SHE SMELLS GOOD.
UH...
- WE'RE NEIGHBORS LIVING
UNDER THE SAME ROOF HERE.
SO WE OUGHT
TO BE NEIGHBORLY.
RIGHT, KAORU?
- COME ON, LET GO OF ME.
IF AOI-CHAN
SAW ME LIKE THIS...
- ( knocking )
- HUH?!
- THIS ISN'T
WHAT YOU THINK!
HUH?
- TAEKO-CHAN?
- HUH? IT'S TAE?
- HELLO, THERE.
GOOD EVENING.
- YES, UNDERSTOOD.
SO THE SAKURA
DEPARTMENT STORE'S
MONTHLY BOARD MEETINGS
WILL BE THEN.
HUH?
NO, JUST SOMETHING
ON THIS END.
YES, I UNDERSTAND.
THE YOKOHAMA BRANCH
SALES REPORT.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
YES.  AND NOW,
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
- ( phone beeps )
- ( sighs )
- I SEE.  SO THIS IS ONE
OF YOUR SCHOOL MATES, IS IT?
- YEAH, TAEKO MINAZUKI.
- I'M SORRY.  I KNOW THIS
IS KIND OF SUDDEN.
- IT'S ALSO LATE. WHAT BROUGHT
YOU HERE, MISS TAEKO?
- ( sighs )
- TAE JUST GOT FIRED.
- SHE DID?
- YES.
I WAS FIRED JUST A FEW HOURS AGO
AS A MATTER OF FACT.
- GOODNESS.
- OH!
- OH, I'M SORRY.
WHAT WAS YOUR JOB EXACTLY
IF I MAY ASK?
- SHE'S A LIVE-IN HOUSEKEEPER.
- HOUSEKEEPER?
- YES, AND THAT'S--
AND THAT'S WHY I--
WHY I...
( sniffs )
DON'T HAVE A PLACE
TO LIVE ANYMORE.
- SO THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE HERE.
- YES.  I REMEMBERED
TINA-SENPAI ONCE TOLD ME
THAT I COULD
COME TO HER FOR ADVICE
IF ANYTHING EVER HAPPENED.
- OH, YEAH, I DID.
ALL RIGHT THEN, TAE.
I'LL GIVE YOU THE BEST ADVICE
THAT I CAN GIVE YOU.
I'M ALWAYS READY TO
LEND A HELPING HAND
OR TWO TO OUR
CUTE JUNIOR CLUB MEMBERS.
- YOU KNOW, SENPAI?
- HUH?
- COULD YOU NOT
MESSAGE MY BREASTS?
- OH, SORRY.
BAD HABIT, I GUESS.
- YOU NEVER CHANGE.
- SENPAI, WHAT DO YOU THINK
I SHOULD DO ABOUT THIS?
- HMM, WHAT CAN YOU DO?
- Tina: HEY, I JUST THOUGHT
OF A GREAT IDEA.
TAE, YOU CAN WORK
RIGHT HERE FOR US.
YOU'LL HAVE A JOB
AND A PLACE TO LIVE.
AND ALL YOUR PROBLEMS
WILL BE SOLVED.
- YEAH?
- THAT'S NOT YOUR DECISION
TO MAKE, TINA!
- THAT'S OKAY,
MISS LANDLORD.
AFTER ALL, WE STILL
GOT EMPTY ROOMS.
- TINA!
- PLEASE!
PRETTY PLEASE
WITH CHERRIES ON TOP.
- MISS TINA, I'VE HEARD
THE CIRCUMSTANCES.
AND I TRULY WOULD LIKE
TO HIRE MISS TAEKO, MYSELF.
- HONESTLY?
- HOWEVER, MISS MIYABI
IS THE ONE
WHO HANDLES AFFAIRS
SUCH AS THESE, NOT ME.
- THE-- THE MANAGER?!
I SEE, SO IT'S HER.
- ( both sigh )
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S MY OWN FAULT.
SORRY TO HAVE
TROUBLED YOU.
GOOD-BYE.
( cries )
- TAEKO-CHAN!
- HEY!
- Aoi and Kaoru:
MISS MIYABI.
- UH, I'M SORRY.
- I OVERHEARD EVERYTHING.
- HUH?
- MISS MIYABI.
- YOU MEAN TO TELL US
THAT YOU--
- SO YOU'LL DO IT?
YOU'LL HIRE TAE,
MISS MANAGER?
- BEING SO SHORT-HANDED HERE
WAS MAKING THINGS DIFFICULT.
- OH!
- HOWEVER,
THE ENTIRE DAY TOMORROW
WILL BE A TRIAL PERIOD.
IF YOU PERFORM
WELL ENOUGH,
I'LL ALLOW YOU
TO BE HOUSEKEEPER.
IS THAT UNDERSTOOD?
- YE-- YES.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, MA'AM.
I'LL DO MY BEST.
- ISN'T THIS GREAT, TAE?
- IT'S WONDERFUL.
( mutters sleepily )
NO, DON'T EAT
THAT ACTION FIGURE.
THAT'S NOT FOOD,
YOU KNOW?
THAT'S ONE OF THOSE
MAGICAL GIRLS.
( sighs ) OH!
( screams )
( thudding )
OWW.
( gasps )
MISS MIYABI,
GOOD MORNING.
- HOW LONG
WILL YOU SLEEP?
THE HOUSEKEEPER IS SUPPOSED
TO BE GETTING UP
BEFORE EVERYONE ELSE.
THAT'S COMMON SENSE!
- I'M SORRY.
( pants )
OH, I HAVE
TO CHANGE FIRST.
- ( grunts )
- ( bubbling )
- YOU WERE RECENTLY EMPLOYED
AS A HOUSEKEEPER ELSEWHERE,
SO MAY I ASSUME THAT
YOU DO KNOW HOW TO COOK?
- YES, I'M NOT SO BAD.
THAT'S STRANGE.
- WHAT IS IT?
- I CAN'T FIND THE INSTANT
MISO SOUP MIX.
- ( grunts ) WE DO NOT USE
CHEMICAL ADDITIVES
IN THE SAKURABA HOUSEHOLD.
YOU WILL MAKE BROTH
FROM SCRATCH!
- OH, UH, OKAY.
- WHEN YOU'RE FINISHED
PREPARING BREAKFAST,
IMMEDIATELY GO AND WAKE UP
BOTH SIR KAORU
AND MISS TINA.
- I WILL.
- Taeko: SENPAI.
SENPAI, PLEASE GET UP.
IT'S MORNING.
- ( groans )
GIVE ME A FEW MINUTES.
OKAY, AOI-CHAN?
- COME ON, WAKE UP, SENPAI.
WAKE UP!
- JUST A BIT LONGER.
- OH!
- HMM.
HUH?
- ( gasps )
( screams )
- WHOA.
- HUH?
- WHAT'S GOING ON IN HERE?
- WHAT WAS THAT SCREAM JUST NOW?
- ( gasping )
- HELLO.
- UH, AOI-CHAN.
THIS IS-- UH...
- WHOO-HOO, KAORU,
YOU'RE A TOTAL PERV.
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
TAEKO-CHAN FELL OVER
AND WE ENDED UP
LIKE THIS.
- MISS TAEKO!
- AH, I'M SORRY.
- Kaoru:
HEY, IT LOOKS GREAT.
- WHOA, YOU ACTUALLY
COOKED ALL THIS
BY YOURSELF, TAE?
- YES, I DID THE BEST I COULD.
- Miyabi: WELL THEN,
WE HAD BETTER EAT NOW.
- Aoi: YES, LET'S.
- All: WE'LL BE EATING NOW.
- HEY, CLAM MISO SOUP, HUH?
- NOTHING LIKE STARTING THE DAY
WITH A BOWL OF MISO SOUP.
- All: SANDY.
- HUH? IS IT NOT GOOD?
- MISS TAEKO,
DID YOU REMEMBER
TO PURGE THE CLAMS?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY
"PURGE THE CLAMS"?
- ( muffled grunt )
- OH! I'M SORRY, MA'AM.
- HEY, DON'T GET SO
DOWN IN THE DUMPS, TAE.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'RE ALL ALLOWED
TO MAKE A MISTAKE OR TWO.
- BUT STILL--
- WE'RE ALL ROOTING
FOR YOU, HERE.
SO CHEER UP.
- YEAH, GO FOR BROKE!
- OKAY, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- SENPAI--
HUH?
- ( meowing )
- WILL YOU ALSO
BE ROOTING FOR ME?
- ( meows )
- ( giggles )
- SENPAI, THANK YOU
FOR THE SUPPORT.
THANK YOU.
I'LL DO MY BEST.
- YEAH, THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
- Taeko: RIGHT.
- ( sighs )
- HMPH.
- Miyabi: UNDERSTOOD?
IF THERE IS EVEN
ONE SPECK OF DIRT LEFT,
WE'LL REPEAT THIS EXERCISE
TILL THERE IS NONE.
- YES, I WILL DO
MY VERY BEST.
- ( grunts )
- MISS TAEKO.
- HUH?
- SUCH LITTLE EFFORT
WON'T GET THESE FLOORS CLEAN.
PUT YOUR HIPS INTO IT,
YOUR HIPS!
- RIGHT, MY HIPS.
( strains ) HIPS, HIPS.
HIPS, HIPS.
- THAT'S THE WAY.
- HIPS, HIPS, HIPS.
- ( gasps )
- MISS TAEKO, WAIT!
- HUH? OH.
- ( both gasping )
- ( sighs )
- I'M SORRY!
- ( grunts )
- WHOA!
- ( pottery breaks )
- I'M SORRY.
- UH, THIS VASE WAS
A FAMILY HEIRLOOM.
AHH!
- I'M SORRY!
- ENOUGH.
THAT'S QUITE ENOUGH,
MISS TAEKO!
YOU ARE TERMINATED!
- WHAT?!
TERMINATED!
N-- NO! PLEASE WAIT!
- Miyabi: LET GO!
- PLEASE!
- Aoi: MISS TAEKO.
- Miyabi: LET ME GO!
- ( whimpering )
OH, I BEG YOU, MISS MIYABI.
PLEASE, MA'AM!
I'LL IMPROVE.
SO PLEASE DON'T
FIRE ME OVER THIS.
MISS MIYABI!
- YOU SHOULD FIND
ANOTHER LINE OF WORK.
- BUT I CAN'T THINK
OF BEING ANYTHING ELSE
BUT A HOUSEKEEPER.
IT'S JUST SOMETHING
I HAVE TO DO.
- THIS CAREER
DOESN'T SUIT YOU.
- ( gasps )
MISS MIYABI,
GIVE ME A CHANCE,
JUST ONE.
I'LL DO THINGS RIGHT.
I'LL DO MY BEST,
SO PLEASE GIVE ME A CHANCE.
I PROMISE TO PUT IN
EVEN MORE EFFORT.
SO I BEG YOU, PLEASE.
- MISS TAEKO,
WHY IS IT SO IMPORTANT?
- ( cat meows )
- Aoi: MISS TAEKO.
- HUH?
MISS LANDLORD, PLEASE.
- I COULD USE A LITTLE HELP
IN HANGING THE LAUNDRY.
- LAUNDRY? BUT, MA'AM,
I'M NO LONGER--
- WELL, SHALL WE START?
- OH.
- YOU'RE A HARD WORKER.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT,
MISS TAEKO?
- HUH?
- YOU'RE GIVING THIS
A LOT OF EFFORT.
I CAN TELL.
- MISS LANDLORD,
IT'S ONLY BECAUSE I--
I'D FEEL SORRY
FOR MY MOTHER
IF I JUST GIVE UP
LIKE THAT.
- YOU SEE, SHE'S
A SINGLE PARENT.
MY FATHER PASSED AWAY
WHEN I WAS VERY YOUNG.
AND EVER SINCE THEN,
MY MOTHER RAISED ME
ALL BY HERSELF.
- ( television chatter )
- ( door opens )
- ( gasps )
- I'M HOME.
- WELCOME BACK.
- UM, MOM,
UH, LOOK AT THIS.
MY SKIRT GOT RIPPED, SEE?
- OH MY.
TAKE IT OFF,
SO I CAN SEW IT.
- Present Taeko:
SHE ALWAYS TRIED HER BEST
WHEN SHE DID THINGS.
AND SHE COULD DO ANYTHING!
- ( chopping )
- MOM, I'M REALLY HUNGRY!
- HMM, JUST WAIT
A LITTLE BIT MORE.
I'M MAKING
SOMETHING DELICIOUS.
- ( giggles )
- Present Taeko: I GREW UP
AROUND A MOTHER LIKE THAT.
AND THAT'S WHY I--
I WANTED THIS JOB,
SO I COULD BE
MORE LIKE MY MOTHER.
- SO THAT'S THE REASON.
- I HAVE TO DO MY BEST.
I'M A REALLY CLUMSY PERSON.
I HAVE TO GIVE MY ALL
JUST TO BE EVEN AVERAGE.
- HUH?
- BUT STILL, MAYBE
BEING A HOUSEKEEPER
JUST ISN'T POSSIBLE FOR ME.
- MISS TAEKO.
NOT AT ALL.
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S THE CASE.
- HUH?
- I WAS THE SAME AS YOU.
I AM A RATHER CLUMSY PERSON
MYSELF.
NOTHING I EVER DID
WENT RIGHT
AND MISS MIYABI
CONSTANTLY SCOLDED ME.
- SHE DID?
- BUT I WANTED
TO BE ABLE TO DO
THE HOUSEHOLD CHORES WELL.
AND I PUT ALL THE EFFORT
I COULD INTO IT.
THAT'S HOW I KNOW THAT
YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
IF YOU TRULY WISH
TO BECOME A HOUSEKEEPER,
I'M SURE
YOU WILL BE ONE.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
- MISS LANDLORD, THANKS A LOT
FOR THE PEP TALK.
I'LL DO MY VERY BEST.
ALL RIGHT!
NOW LET'S GET THE REST
OF THE LAUNDRY ALL HUNG UP.
- ( knocking )
- COME ON IN.
- WOULD YOU LIKE TEA?
- OH, AOI-CHAN, IT'S YOU?
- HOW IS YOUR REPORT GOING?
- PRETTY WELL.
I THINK I OUGHT TO
BE FINISHED BY DINNER.
- OH, I SEE.
I BROUGHT YOU SOME TEA.
SO WHY DON'T YOU
REST FOR A WHILE?
KAORU-SAMA?
- HUH?
- MISS TAEKO
IS AN AMAZING PERSON.
- YEAH.
- BOTH MY PARENTS ARE ALIVE.
AND I NEVER HAD
ANY PROBLEMS GROWING UP.
I DON'T KNOW THE PAIN
THAT MISS TAEKO HAS SUFFERED.
SO THAT'S WHY I FEEL
SOMEWHAT AWKWARD AROUND HER,
I'M ASHAMED TO ADMIT.
- AOI-CHAN.
I KNOW YOU'RE DOING
THE BEST THAT YOU CAN.
- EXCEPT I DON'T HAVE
HARDSHIPS ANYMORE.
- HUH?
- THE ONLY THING I COULD DO
WAS IMAGINE IT
IN MY HEART BEFORE.
NOW, I'M ABLE TO SEE
YOUR GENTLE FACE
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
I CAN TOUCH YOU LIKE THIS.
AND I'M VERY HAPPY NOW.
SO...
KAORU-SAMA, I HOPE
THAT YOU'LL FORGIVE ME
FOR BEING SO SELFISH.
- AOI-CHAN.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- ( knocking )
- ( both gasp )
- EXCUSE ME, SENPAI.
HMM? WHAT EXACTLY
ARE YOU DOING?
- HUH? OH, NOTHING.
( nervous laugh )
- I SEE.
- IS SOMETHING WRONG?
WHAT'D YOU COME HERE FOR?
- OH, YEAH.
HAVE YOU SEEN THE LANDLORD
AROUND HERE ANYWHERE?
- NOT REALLY. WHY DO YOU
NEED HER, TAEKO-CHAN?
- I WAS THINKING ABOUT
MAYBE CLEANING
THE BATHROOM TODAY,
BUT I COULDN'T
FIND THE CLEANSER.
- THEN WHY DON'T YOU ASK
MISS MIYABI?
- SHE'S NOT COMING OUT
OF HER ROOM FOR SOME REASON.
- I SEE, THAT'S A PROBLEM, HUH?
- YEAH, OH, SORRY TO BOTHER YOU
DURING YOUR REPORT WRITING.
I'LL KEEP LOOKING.
- ( sighs )
- ( Aoi giggles )
- HUH?
- ( giggling )
- ( both laughing )
- AOI-CHAN.
- IT'S WARM HERE.
I SHOULD CHECK UP ON HER.
I'LL GO NOW.
- OKAY.
- I'LL JUST
STAY A BIT LONGER.
- HMM.
- YES.  HIPS.
( gasps )
WHOA-OH-OH-OH.
- ( gasps )
- ( thudding )
- OWW!
( moans )
( pants )
OH!
- OH, MISS TAEKO.
- ( gasps )
( gasping )
HM-HMM.
- ( chopping )
- Taeko: TIME FOR DINNER!
- Tina and Kaoru: OKAY!
- IT'S BEEN A ROUGH TIME
FOR TAEKO-CHAN.
- THE MANAGER'S
SURE BEEN TOUGH ON HER.
BUT I REALLY WANT TAE
TO PASS HER TEST.
- HEY, LISTEN, TINA.
NO MATTER WHAT'S
SERVED FOR DINNER,
LET'S SAY IT'S DELICIOUS.
- YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
US KYUSHU GALS KNOW
HOW TO GRIN AND BEAR IT.
THEN WE'LL WORK TOGETHER
AND TAEKO-CHAN
WILL BE OUR HOUSEKEEPER.
- Both: YEAH!
- OH!
UH, THAT IS--
- I TAKE IT THAT
DINNER IS READY,
- Y-- YES.
- MISS TAEKO,
IF THIS IS NO GOOD,
YOU KNOW
WHAT WILL HAPPEN.
- YES, MA'AM.
- WHOA, WHAT A FEAST!
- WE'VE NEVER HAD
WESTERN FOOD HERE BEFORE.
- IT LOOKS LIKE
IT'LL BE DELICIOUS.
- ARE YOU READY, TINA?
- YOU BET.
I'M READY FOR THE WORST.
- HUH.
- EVERYONE,
WE SHOULD EAT BEFORE
IT GETS COLD.
- OH, RIGHT.
- All: TIME TO EAT.
HUH?
- HUH?!
- MY.
- WHOA, EVERYTHING'S DELICIOUS!
THIS IS GREAT, TAE.
- DO YOU REALLY MEAN IT?
THANK YOU FOR SAYING SO.
- IT'S REALLY DELICIOUS.
- UM...
- MISS TAEKO.
- YES, MA'AM.
- PLEASE CONTINUE PERFORMING
AT THIS LEVEL.
- HUH?
- THEN ARE YOU SAYING...
- YEAH! SHE PASSED!
- I-- I CAN STAY?
- YOU DID IT, TAEKO-CHAN.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- YEAH! CONGRATULATIONS!
WELCOME TO YOUR
NEW HOME AND JOB, TAE.
- I'M NOT GOOD AT COOKING
WESTERN CUISINE.
SO I HOPE YOU'LL BE WILLING
TO TEACH ME, MISS TAEKO.
- MISS AOI,
THANK YOU SO VERY MUCH.
- OH, BUT I REALLY
DIDN'T DO ANYTHING AT ALL.
THIS IS WONDERFUL, ISN'T IT?
- OH, YEAH.
- ( yawns )
- Miyabi:
LADY AOI, MAY I COME IN?
- ( gasps )
YES, PLEASE DO.
- ( door slides open )
- PARDON THE INTRUSION.
- IS SOMETHING THE MATTER,
MISS MIYABI?
- ONLY THAT SOMEONE'S BOOK
WAS LEFT IN THE KITCHEN.
- ( gasps )
- I THOUGHT THAT IT HAD
BELONGED TO MISS TAEKO,
BUT LOOKING INSIDE...
I RECOGNIZED YOUR
HANDWRITING.
- I WAS JUST, UM,
YOU SEE...
- AND THAT'S ALL
I CAME TO SAY.
- MISS MIYABI.
- YES, WHAT IS IT?
- THANK YOU, MISS MIYABI.
- GOOD NIGHT TO YOU,
LADY AOI.
- ( door slides closed )
- Aoi: GOOD NIGHT.
- YES, I UNDERSTAND.
YES, MA'AM.
I'LL TRY EVEN HARDER.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Aoi: I WAS INVITED TO GO TO
THE HOT SPRINGS. I'M SO HAPPY.
- Miyabi:
HOW WONDERFUL FOR YOU.
- Aoi: AI YORI AOSHI,
"SPIRITUAL ILLUSION."
MEN AND WOMEN
WELCOMED WITH SAKE?
- Miyabi: WHAT COULD THAT MEAN,
LADY AOI?