- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- THAT SURE WAS
A SURPRISE, THOUGH.
THAT GIRL KISSING
HANABISHI SENPAI.
- THERE WAS A GIRL?
- HANABISHI-SAMA IS
STAYING WITH MAYU.
- MAYU-CHAN.
- KAORU-SAMA...
WHAT IN THE WORLD IS
GOING ON HERE?
KAORU-SAMA!
- ( glass shatters )
- Mayu:
ALL RIGHT, HANABISHI-SAMA,
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY.
- OKAY.
I'M GOING AHEAD THEN.
- WAIT.  NOT SO FAST.
BE PATIENT
A LITTLE LONGER.
- UH-- OKAY.
- ALL RIGHT, GO AHEAD.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- YES, I'M SURE.
- LET'S GO.
- NO!
DON'T TAKE THAT CARD THERE!
- WHA-- UH.
ALL RIGHT, THIS ONE.
- HOW LUCKY!
YOU JUST TOOK
THE JOKER AWAY!
NOW IT'S MAYU'S TURN
TO PICK A CARD.
- HMM?
- LET'S SEE, LET'S SEE.
WHICH ONE SHOULD IT BE?
( giggles )
HURRAY!  I'M OUT NOW!
- ( laughing )
LOOKS LIKE I LOST
ANOTHER GAME.
- ALL RIGHT, WHY DON'T
WE PLAY ANOTHER MATCH?
- YOU MEAN YOU REALLY
WANNA PLAY AGAIN?
- OF COURSE I DO!
- YOU KNOW, YOU SURE HAVE
A LOT OF DOLLS IN YOUR ROOM.
- EVER SINCE I WAS LITTLE
AND BEGGED MY FATHER FOR A DOLL
THAT I SAW ONE TIME,
HE'S ALWAYS BOUGHT ME DOLLS
OR PLUSH TOYS
AS BIRTHDAY PRESENTS
OR AS SOUVENIRS.
THAT ONE WAS FOR
MY EIGHTH BIRTHDAY.
THAT ONE ON THE LEFT WAS
FOR MY 11th.
AND THAT ONE WAS
FOR MY 14th.
EACH ONE WAS A GIFT
I RECEIVED FROM MY FATHER.
MAYU IS NO LONGER
A CHILD, THOUGH.
- SHALL WE SLEEP NOW?
- SURE!
- SO, WHAT ABOUT ME?
UM, WHICH ROOM AM I
SUPPOSED TO BE SLEEPING IN?
- ( giggles )
THIS ROOM HERE.
- I-- I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
AAH!
- DON'T BE THAT WAY!
MAYU WANTS TO SLEEP
IN THE SAME ROOM WITH YOU.
PLEASE, HANABISHI-SAMA,
WON'T YOU?
- COME ON NOW,
TAKE IT EASY.
- LADY AOI?
- HUH?
- YOU'RE STILL UP
AT THIS LATE HOUR?
- YES, I APOLOGIZE.
I'LL GO TO SLEEP NOW.
GOOD NIGHT.
- LADY AOI...
- ( giggles ) THANK YOU
FOR STAYING, HANABISHI-SAMA.
- THIS IS ONLY UNTIL
YOU FALL ASLEEP.
- SURE.
- THEN I'M TURNING
THE LIGHTS OFF.
- ( beeps )
- I'M SORRY.
- HUH?
- MAYU IS BEING
A SELFISH GIRL AGAIN,
AND IT ONLY TROUBLED YOU
IN THE END.
- THAT REALLY ISN'T
THE CASE AT ALL.
- HANABISHI-SAMA,
MAYU IS A BAD GIRL,
SO SCOLD ME
WHEN I DO BAD THINGS.
- MAYU-CHAN.
NOW MAYU-CHAN,
YOU'RE NOT A BAD GIRL, OKAY?
SO PLEASE GO TO SLEEP.
- ALL RIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT, HANABISHI-SAMA.
SLEEP WELL, RABI.
- HUH?
RABI?
SHE STILL KEPT IT CLOSE
ALL THIS TIME?
- ( crowd chattering )
- HERE YOU GO, MAYU.
IT'S THE RABBIT
THAT YOU'VE ALWAYS WANTED.
- ( giggles )
THANKS SO MUCH, PAPA!
- YOU HAVE WONDERFUL TASTE,
DEAR.
- YOU DON'T TURN 12
TILL NEXT WEEK,
BUT WE'LL HAVE TO GIVE YOU YOUR
BIRTHDAY PRESENT A LITTLE EARLY.
- HUH? THEN WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN TO MAYU'S BIRTHDAY PARTY?
- WE'RE VERY SORRY, MAYU.
- IT'S UNFORTUNATE
CIRCUMSTANCES.
BOTH YOUR FATHER AND I
HAVE TO TRAVEL
OVERSEAS TOMORROW.
- I THINK THAT I CAN RETURN
IN ABOUT TWO MONTHS THIS TIME.
- WE'LL HOLD THE PARTY
WHEN WE'RE ALL TOGETHER AGAIN.
- NO WAY, IF WE DID THAT,
IT WOULDN'T BE A BIRTHDAY
PARTY AT ALL.
- THIS IS IMPORTANT BUSINESS,
MAYU-CHAN.
- TRY TO UNDERSTAND.
- YEAH, BUT...
OKAY.  I UNDERSTAND.
- MR. MIYUKI.
- OH, LOOK WHO'S HERE.
- IT'S ALWAYS A PLEASURE
SEEING YOU AROUND.
- WELL, I COULDN'T MISS
ONE OF MIYUKI TRADING'S
LEGENDARY PARTIES.
- NO NO, DON'T FORGET--
THIS IS A GROUP EFFORT.
- MAY I GET YOU
SOMETHING TO DRINK?
- OH, YOU'RE GOING TO SPOIL ME
ROTTEN ONE DAY, MRS. MIYUKI.
- ( all laughing )
- MAYBE IT'S TOO LATE.
- HEY, PAPA,
MAYU HAS A STORY!
IT HAPPENED THE OTHER DAY
AT SCHOOL.
- I'M SORRY, MAYU.
I'LL BE HAPPY TO LISTEN
TO ALL OF THE DETAILS LATER.
LET'S TALK SOMEWHERE QUIETER.
- ( sighs )
- ( laughs )
THAT CERTAINLY IS TRUE.
- MAMA?  MAMA MAMA!
DID YOU KNOW THAT MAYU
GOT A PERFECT SCORE
ON THE LAST JAPANESE TEST?
MAMA!
- PARDON ME.
I'LL JUST BE A MOMENT.
YOUR MOTHER IS BUSY HAVING
A VERY IMPORTANT CONVERSATION
RIGHT NOW, MAYU-CHAN.
WHY DON'T YOU SIT QUIETLY
SOMEWHERE AND DRINK THIS?
- OF COURSE, I HOPE
WE CAN KEEP WORKING TOGETHER.
- WE'D LIKE TO INVITE YOU
TO DINNER IF YOU HAVE TIME.
- ( party guests chattering )
- MAYU.
- ( gasps )
- YOUR SCHOOL'S CHAIRMAN IS
WITH US TODAY.
COME SAY HELLO TO HIM.
WHAT ARE YOU BEING
SO QUIET FOR, MAYU?
IT'S ONLY A SIMPLE HELLO.
- ( whimpering )
- MAYU.
- ( gasps )
( sobbing )
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- MAYU, COME BACK.
- I'M TERRIBLY SORRY.
PLEASE FORGIVE OUR DAUGHTER
FOR HER RASH BEHAVIOR.
- IT'S FINE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- ( sobbing )
- THIS...
- ( gasps )
- ...IS YOURS, RIGHT?
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- BUT ISN'T THIS THE DOLL
YOU DROPPED EARLIER?
- I TOLD YOU
IT'S NOT MINE!
PAPA BOUGHT IT
'CAUSE HE WANTED TO!
IT DOESN'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH ME!
- ( cartoon voice )
HI, THERE.
- UH--
- THAT'S WEIRD.
NO ANSWER.
ONE MORE TIME THEN.
HI, THERE!
GEE.
YOU SEEM KINDA DOWN.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
AROUND HERE ANYWAY?
- NOTHING MUCH.
- HMM.
OH, YEAH, I STILL HAVEN'T
INTRODUCED MYSELF, HUH?
HOW DO YOU DO?
MY NAME IS RABI.
RABI THE RABBIT.
LET'S GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
- ( giggles softly )
WHAT A FUNNY NAME.
- ( giggles )
HEY, AREN'T YOU GONNA TELL ME
WHAT YOUR NAME IS?
- MAYU.
MAYU MIYUKI.
- MAYU-CHAN, HUH?
THAT'S A NICE NAME.
YOU KNOW, MAYU-CHAN,
I'M ALL THE WAY OUT HERE
BECAUSE I WANNA PLAY WITH YOU.
YOUR PAPA PICKED ME OUT
OF ALL MY FRIENDS IN THE STORE,
AND I'M GLAD HE DID
BECAUSE YOU SEEM LIKE YOU'RE
A DECENT PERSON.
AND I'M SURE THAT YOUR PAPA'S
A REAL NICE PERSON TOO.
'CAUSE HE'S THE ONE
WHO PICKED ME, AFTER ALL.
- I HATE PAPA.
- YOU HATE HIM?
AND WHY'S THAT?
- THIS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE SEEN HIM IN SIX MONTHS,
AND HE'S NOT EVEN
TALKING TO ME.
HE'S NOT COMING TO MAYU'S
BIRTHDAY PARTY, EITHER.
ALL MY FRIENDS' MAMAS
AND PAPAS CELEBRATE
THEIR BIRTHDAY PARTIES
WITH THEM.
AND THEY ALL GET CHEERED ON
DURING THEIR PIANO RECITALS.
MAYU'S THE ONLY ONE
WHO NEVER DOES.
PAPA AND MAMA NEVER TRY
TO DO ANYTHING WITH MAYU.
THEY DON'T CARE
ABOUT MAYU AT ALL!
- ( wind gusts )
- ( normal voice )
I'M JEALOUS.
- HUH?
- I'M JEALOUS, MAYU-CHAN.
BECAUSE YOU HAVE
A PAPA AND MAMA.
- WHAT ABOUT
YOUR PAPA AND MAMA?
- THEY'RE NOT AROUND.
- THEY'RE NOT?
THEN DOES THAT MEAN
THAT THEY'RE OVERSEAS?
AMERICA?  CANADA?
- NO.
FARTHER AWAY THAN THAT.
- SO THEY'RE IN FRANCE.
OH, I KNOW, IN ENGLAND.
- NO, FARTHER THAN THAT.
THEY'VE GONE MUCH MUCH
FARTHER AWAY.
- REALLY?
THEY'RE MUCH MUCH FARTHER AWAY?
THAT WOULD BE...
- I'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO SEE
MY MAMA OR PAPA.
EVER AGAIN.
THAT'S WHY I CAN SAY THIS.
BECAUSE I WAS ALWAYS ALONE.
BEING ALONE IS REALLY SAD.
IT'S TOUGH AND LONELY.
BUT, MAYU-CHAN,
YOUR PAPA AND MAMA
CARE DEEPLY ABOUT YOU.
THE TRUTH IS THEY LOVE YOU MORE
THAN ANYONE ELSE IN THIS WORLD.
SO, PLEASE, MAYU-CHAN,
YOU SHOULDN'T HATE
YOUR PAPA AND MAMA.
RIGHT, MAYU-CHAN?
- ( crying )
( sobbing )
- WELL, SEE YOU, MAYU-CHAN.
- YOU'RE GONNA COME VISIT
MAYU AGAIN, AREN'T YOU?
I'LL SEE YOU, RIGHT?
- OF COURSE.  I'LL COME AGAIN.
- MAYU WILL BE
WAITING FOR YOU, UH...
- ( laughs )
MY NAME'S KAORU.
KAORU HANABISHI.
- HANABISHI-SAMA...
- OH, BROTHER.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO LEAVE NOW?
- HANABISHI-SAMA.
- ( both groaning )
- WHAT THE HECK'S WRONG
WITH THOSE TWO?
- Taeko: TINA SENPAI HAS
A MASSIVE HANGOVER.
- Sato: AND HANABISHI?
- HE DIDN'T GET MUCH SLEEP.
- NOT ENOUGH SLEEP?
- HANABISHI SENPAI STAYED OVER
AT THAT GIRL'S HOUSE LAST NIGHT.
REMEMBER? WOW!
WE CAN'T TAKE OUR EYES OFF
YOU FOR A SECOND, SENPAI.
- KAORU!
- WHAT?
- WHAT DID YOU AND THAT GIRL
DO LAST NIGHT?
- ( bell tolls )
- AAH!
MY HEAD'S GONNA SPLIT OPEN.
I'M DYING.
- JEEZ.
BUT IT'S A GOOD THING THAT
MAYU-CHAN DIDN'T COME TODAY.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
A BIG MESS IF SHE HAD.
- NO!
I WANNA GO TO UNIVERSITY
WITH HANABISHI-SAMA!
- YOUR VERY FIRST CLASS WILL NOT
BE STARTING UNTIL NEXT WEEK,
MAYU-SAMA.
- I SAID RELEASE ME!
I'M GOING WITH HANABISHI-SAMA!
AND THAT'S THAT!
- ( chuckles )
- OH, WASN'T THAT SUSPICIOUS?
- WHAT?
- SO SOMETHING DID HAPPEN LAST
NIGHT WITH HER, DIDN'T IT?
- IS THAT REALLY TRUE,
HANABISHI?!
- NO, IT ISN'T.
I SWEAR.
( grunts )
- KAORU!
- ( bell tolling )
- OH!  AAH!
- JEEZ, WHAT WAS THAT
ALL ABOUT?
OH, YEAH, I'D BETTER GO
CALL AOI-CHAN.
- ( birds chirping )
- ( sighs )
- I SEE.
THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
THEN I THINK THAT
IT'S PROBABLY BEST
THAT WE GO OVER THE
BUDGET ONE MORE TIME.
YES, BUT COULD YOU
HOLD ON A MOMENT?
- ( beeps )
- YOU'RE CORRECT.
IT IS POSSIBLE TO
MANAGE THE SAPPORO BRANCH
IN THAT MANNER.
- ( beeping )
- THE LINE'S BEEN BUSY
FOR A REALLY LONG TIME NOW.
- TV female announcer:
IT'S TIME ONCE AGAIN
FOR SMILEY COOKING!
TODAY WE'LL BE SHOWING YOU
HOW TO MAKE A WONDERFUL
FISH DISH, AS WELL AS...
- ( yawns )
( softly groans )
- WHAT WE HAVE HERE IS A GANOID
FISH AT THE PEAK OF ITS SEASON!
IT'S CALLED KISU.
( echoing )
KISS...
- KISSES ARE AT
THE PEAK OF THEIR SEASON?
- KISSING HANABISHI SENPAI
OUT OF NOWHERE.
- SORRY, BUT I'LL BE
STAYING OVER
AT MY ACQUAINTANCE'S HOUSE
TONIGHT.
- I WONDER WHAT KIND OF PERSON
THIS ACQUAINTANCE IS.
AND LAST NIGHT, DID THEY...?
OH, MY!
WHAT AM I THINKING?
NO, IT IS AT TIMES LIKE THESE
THAT ONE MUST PERSEVERE.
ALL RIGHT, I WILL
DO SOME LAUNDRY
AND TAKE MY MIND OFF OF THINGS.
- ( door opens )
- I'M HOME!
- MISS TINA?
- SAY, SENPAI?
- HMM?
- SENPAI, WHEN EXACTLY DID YOU
HAVE YOUR VERY FIRST KISS?
- WHAT?  THAT WAS A PRETTY
SUDDEN THING TO ASK.
- SO HOW OLD WERE YOU, ANYWAY?
- I REALLY DON'T REMEMBER.
- ( gasps ) COULD IT BE
THAT IT WAS YESTERDAY?
- JEEZ, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?!
THAT WASN'T A KISS;
THAT WAS JUST A LITTLE GREETING.
MAYU-CHAN SAID SO HERSELF,
DIDN'T SHE?
- YEAH. BUT DO YOU REALLY THINK
IF NORMAL GIRLS
HEARD YOU SAY THAT,
THEY'D THINK THAT WAY?
- HUH?
- EVEN IF IT WAS A GREETING,
IF SOME GIRL KISSED
MY BOYFRIEND,
I JUST DON'T THINK THAT
I'D BE ABLE TO CONTAIN MYSELF.
- UH--
SHE'S RIGHT ABOUT THE KISS.
I COULDN'T HELP IT.
BUT IT'S TRUE THAT WE KISSED.
MAYBE I SHOULD APOLOGIZE TO HER.
BUT AOI-CHAN DOESN'T KNOW
ABOUT THIS YET.
SO I SHOULDN'T BRING IT UP
OUT OF THE BLUE.
- WELL, I'D BETTER GO CHANGE
AND GET TO WORK.
- SURE.
NO.  I SHOULD TELL HER.
IT'S FOR THE BEST.
- I'M HAPPY TO WELCOME YOU BACK,
KAORU-SAMA.
- UH--
YEAH, GOOD TO BE BACK.
- DINNER WILL BE READY
MOMENTARILY.
- UH, OKAY.
UH, AOI-CHAN?
- YES?  WHAT IS IT?
- OH.  UH, WELL...
I-- I HAVE TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING.
- YOU HAVE SOMETHING TO SAY?
TO ME?
WHAT IS IT EXACTLY?
- WELL, THIS IS SOMETHING...
THAT HAPPENED YESTERDAY.
- YESTERDAY, WAS IT?
- YEAH.
HONESTLY--
- KAORU!  ( laughs )
- DON'T TELL ME YOU'VE BEEN
DRINKING AGAIN, TINA.
- SORRY I'M SO LATE.
- KAORU-SAMA, I'M AFRAID
I'M STILL IN THE MIDDLE OF
PREPARING DINNER, SO I'LL
LISTEN TO YOUR STORY LATER.
- OH, UH UH--
- COME ON,
YOU DRINK TOO, KAORU!
UH, I CAN'T DRINK
ANOTHER DROP.
- I THINK YOU'VE DRUNK ENOUGH
FOR TODAY, TINA.
( sighs )
I GUESS I CAN WAIT
UNTIL SHE'S DONE CLEANING.
- ( groans )
ALL RIGHT THEN,
COME ON, KAORU!
- HMM?
- HOW ABOUT
A LITTLE KISS, HUH?
- ( spits )
- WHY NOT?! YOU KISSED
THAT OTHER GIRL BEFORE,
SO WHY CAN'T YOU KISS ME NOW?
- SHUT UP, YOU IDIOT!
- COME ON, IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU'RE GONNA LOSE ANYTHING
FROM HAVING A KISS OR TWO.
ALL I WANT IS ONE. YOU
DIDN'T HAVE ANY PROBLEM
KISSING THAT OTHER GIRL.
- HEY, WAIT!
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING TO HER.
SHE DID IT TO ME!
MAYU-CHAN SAID SO HERSELF.
AND IT WAS JUST
AS A GREETING, REMEMBER?
- THEN WHY DON'T YOU
GREET ME TOO?  OOH.
- THAT'S NOT THE POINT, TINA!
- OH, I SEE.
FINE THEN!
I DON'T CARE ANYMORE IF YOU
WANNA KISS ME OR NOT, KAORU!
I'M JUST GONNA HAVE TO GO
KISS THE LANDLORD THEN,
AND I'LL KISS THE MANAGER TOO!
- WHAT'S THE POINT OF THAT?
- I'M GONNA GO DO IT
WITH TAE TOO!
- HEY, COME ON!  TINA!
THAT SMILE EARLIER
SURE WAS PAINFUL TO SEE.
( sighs )
WHAT SHOULD I DO NOW?
I THINK THINGS MIGHT BE STARTING
TO SPIN COMPLETELY OUT
OF MY CONTROL.
- THAT'S HORRIBLE.
I EXIST ONLY FOR YOU,
AND YET YOU STILL GO OFF
AND KISS SOMEBODY ELSE?
AND YOU ALSO SPENT THE NIGHT
AT HER HOUSE
DOING WHO-KNOWS-WHAT.
I ASK THAT YOU PLEASE FORGET
THIS ENGAGEMENT EVER HAPPENED!
- ( sighs )
- KAORU-SAMA?
- UH.  AOI-CHAN.
- YOU HAD SOMETHING TO SAY?
ABOUT YESTERDAY.
AT LEAST THAT'S WHAT
YOU MENTIONED EARLIER.
- YE-- YEAH, I DID,
DIDN'T I?
WE-- WELL, HOW DO I PUT THIS?
YOU SEE...
AOI-CHAN, IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
THE ACQUAINTANCE
THAT I BUMPED INTO YESTERDAY,
SHE'S LIKE A LITTLE SISTER
TO ME.
THE KISS...
IT'S TRUE.
THE KISS DID HAPPEN.
BUT SHE HAD JUST COME BACK
FROM OVERSEAS,
AND THE KISS WAS ONLY
A GREETING.
PLUS, THE REASON I STAYED OVER
AT HER HOUSE
WAS BECAUSE SHE SEEMED
REALLY LONELY ALL BY HERSELF.
BUT NOTHING WEIRD HAPPENED
WHILE I WAS THERE.
WELL, I GUESS YOU COULD CALL
A KISS SOMETHING WEIRD,
BUT STILL...
- EVEN IF IT WAS A GREETING,
IF SOME GIRL KISSED
MY BOYFRIEND,
I JUST DON'T THINK THAT
I'D BE ABLE TO CONTAIN MYSELF.
- I'M SORRY.
I REALLY AM SORRY.
- KAORU-SAMA.
PLEASE, I ASK THAT YOU NOT
APOLOGIZE FOR WHAT HAPPENED.
WHEN YOU APOLOGIZE LIKE THIS,
ALL THAT IT DOES...
IS FILL MY HEART
WITH FEELINGS OF SORROW.
NO ONE UNDERSTANDS YOU,
OR UNDERSTANDS YOUR FEELINGS
MORE FULLY THAN I DO,
KAORU-SAMA.
NO MATTER WHAT MAY HAPPEN,
I BELIEVE IN YOU,
AND I ALWAYS WILL.
SO, PLEASE, I ASK YOU,
DON'T EVER APOLOGIZE.
- AOI-CHAN.
- KAORU-SAMA,
THE NEXT TIME
THERE'S A PHOTO EXHIBIT,
PLEASE TAKE ME WITH YOU.
- YEAH, I WILL.
I'LL BE A LITTLE EMBARRASSED
DOING IT, THOUGH.
- THERE'S ONE MORE THING.
- HMM?
- WOULD YOU MIND IF I ASKED
ANOTHER FAVOR?
THOUGH IT MIGHT BE CONSIDERED
A SELFISH REQUEST.
- IT'S OKAY.
WHAT IS IT?
- WELL, HONESTLY,
WHAT I WOULD LIKE...
WHAT I MEAN TO SAY IS...
- YEAH?  WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S, UM--
I APOLOGIZE.
I'VE CHANGED MY MIND.
IT WAS REALLY NOTHING.
PLEASE, FORGET IT.
- DON'T JUST STOP THERE.
YOU'VE GOT ME INTERESTED NOW.
JUST GO AHEAD AND ASK ME.
- OH, BUT I...
- THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH ASKING.
- UH, ALL RIGHT.
IF THAT'S THE CASE...
THEN I, UM...
I WOULD LIKE--
I'D LIKE YOU TO...
KISS ME,
IF IT'S POSSIBLE.
- ( heart beating )
- ( crying )
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Tina:
HEY, TAE, WHAT'S "TANABATA"?
- IT'S ABOUT STAR-CROSSED
LOVERS,
PRINCESS ORIHIME
AND PRINCE HIKOBOSHI--
THE ONLY DAY OF THE YEAR--
- "AI YORI AOSHI--"
- Taeko: "...STAR FESTIVAL"!
- WHAT?!
THAT'S MISS LANDLORD'S
BIRTHDAY TOO?
- WHERE IS MY HIKOBOSHI-SAMA?
- HUH?