- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( waves crashing )
- HANABISHI-SENPAI IS KIND
AND EASY TO TALK TO.
AND HE'S ALWAYS
HELPING ME OUT TOO.
I NEVER THOUGHT ABOUT IT BEFORE.
BUT HE IS IMPORTANT TO ME.
MAYBE THESE FEELINGS
THAT I HAVE FOR HIM...
REALLY ARE...
- ( chatter, laughter )
- ENJOY THE BEACH.
- AAH!  THE FOOD'S
BURNING BEHIND YOU!
- AAH!
OH, MY GOSH.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING NOT
PAYING ATTENTION TO THIS?
WAKE UP ALREADY!
- I'M SORRY.
- ( groans )
- Chika and Taeko: AAH!
- WA...
WATER.
- ( ringing )
- ( gulping loudly )
( exhales )
I FINALLY FEEL ALIVE.
- WOW.
IT'S ALL GONE?
EVERY LAST BAR OF ICE CREAM?
- MM-HMM, WE SOLD OUT
IN 20 MINUTES.  YEAH!
- THAT'S CERTAINLY GOOD
FOR BUSINESS.
YEAH!
- I FAIL TO SEE WHAT
YOU'RE SO HAPPY ABOUT.
I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA
SHRIVEL UP INTO A MUMMY.
THE HEAT WAS
SIMPLY UNBEARABLE.
AND WHY DO I HAVE TO SELL ICE
CREAM IN THE FIRST PLACE?
I DIDN'T COME
ALL THE WAY TO THIS
GOD-FORSAKEN PEASANT BEACH
JUST TO DO SOMETHING SO MENIAL.
I CAME WITH THE INTENTION
OF SHARING A MEMORABLE
SUMMER ADVENTURE
WITH HANABISHI-SAMA.
UH?
- THANKS FOR THE HELP
OUT THERE, MISS MAYU.
HERE'S A REWARD.
- THIS IS A REWARD?
- WHEN WE'RE DONE WITH THESE,
WE'LL GO OUT FOR
OUR SECOND PASS.
- WHAT?!  YOU MEAN
WE'RE GOING OUT AGAIN?
- CHEERS!
AHH!
MAN, THAT'S GOOD STUFF.
- YOU CAN REALLY
PUT IT AWAY, HUH?
YOU'RE A YOUNG LADY
OF MANY TALENTS, AREN'T YOU?
- YOU'RE NOT SO BAD YOURSELF,
MISTER.
- THANKS.
ONE MORE ROUND THEN!
- YOU GOT IT!
TWO MEDIUM BOTTLES, KAORU!
HIMEJI AND EDAMAME TOO.
- TINA, DIDN'T YOU SAY
YOU WERE GOING TO HELP OUT
WITH THE RESTAURANT?
- I'M EATING AND DRINKING,
AREN'T I?
AND THAT HELPS OUT
THE BUSINESS AROUND HERE.
AIN'T THAT RIGHT, MISTER?
- SURE IS.
- ( both laugh )
- FIGURES, I GUESS.
- OHH!
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT THERE?
- I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- IT'S OKAY.
I TRIPPED OVER
THIS THING EARLIER TOO.
YOU SHOULD WATCH YOUR STEP
AROUND HERE.
- I WILL.
- HURRY UP
WITH THE DRINKS, KAORU!
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
- ( laughing )
- ( sighs )
- TAEKO.
ALL RIGHT, THEN!
THIS LOOKS LIKE A JOB FOR CHIKA!
- YES.  AND PLEASE
FORWARD THAT ORDER
TO THE MAINTENANCE DEPARTMENT.
THANK YOU.
- I CAN'T EVEN MOVE
AN INCH ANYMORE.
- I CAN'T...
DRINK ANOTHER DROP.
- BIG BROTHER!
- HMM?  CHIKA-CHAN.
- ( giggles )
I THINK YOU'VE DONE
ENOUGH WORK FOR TODAY.
- OH, YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD
AT THIS FOR SOMEONE SO YOUNG.
- THANK YOU, MA'AM.
I'VE ALWAYS LOVED COOKING,
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
- ANY MAN WOULD BE LUCKY
TO HAVE YOU AS HIS WIFE.
- OH.
OH, MY.
I'M SO EMBARRASSED
TO HEAR YOU SAY THAT.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
- ( laughter )
- HEY, TAEKO.
WHY DON'T YOU GO
TAKE A BATH?
I CAN TAKE OVER FROM HERE.
- OH, IT'S OKAY.
I'LL TAKE A BATH LATER.
- OH, NO, YOU GO AHEAD,
MISS TAEKO.
WE'RE PRACTICALLY DONE HERE
ANYWAY.
- BUT STILL--
- DO YOU REALLY THINK
BIG BROTHER LIKES SWEATY GIRLS?
- HUH?
- OH.
WHAT'S THIS?
IT LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY'S
IN HERE ALREADY.
MAYBE IT'S TINA-SENPAI.
- ( giggles )
GO FOR IT, TAEKO.
JUST ONE LOOK AND HIS HEART
WILL BE YOURS FOREVER.
- TINA-SENPAI,
WOULD IT BE OKAY
IF I TAKE A SHOWER TOO?
HI.
SENPAI?
( gasps )
AAH!
( murmuring )
WHY IS HANABISHI-SENPAI HERE?
- WH-- WHY'S TAEKO-CHAN HERE?
WAIT!  MY BACK.
AAH!
- IT SOUNDS LIKE
OPERATION: CUPID OF LOVE
WAS A
COMPLETE SUCCESS!
- TIME TO TAKE A BATH!
- MAYU WILL BE FIRST!
- ( cheering )
- ( groans )
- ( water splashes )
- HUH?
- ( Tina and Mayu arguing )
- OH, NO, WHAT DO I DO NOW?
- ( exhales )
THIS IS PARADISE.
- ( water running )
- HUH?
I GUESS SOMEONE ELSE MUST
HAVE COME IN HERE BEFORE US.
IS THAT YOU, MISS MANAGER?
OR MISS LANDLORD?
- AAH, IT'S TINA.
- WHAT SHOULD I DO?
IF THEY FIND
HANABISHI-SENPAI HERE...
I HAVE TO THINK OF
SOMETHING QUICK, OR ELSE.
- HEY, COME OUT, COME OUT
WHEREVER YOU ARE!
- ( steam hissing )
- AAH!
- OH, SORRY ABOUT THAT,
TINA-SENPAI.
- HUH?  IS THAT YOU, TAE?
YOU SURPRISED ME.
SO WAS THAT YOU ALL ALONG?
- YEAH.  ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, I'M FINE.
BUT DON'T YOU THINK
THAT WATER'S A LITTLE TOO HOT?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
I'M PERFECTLY FINE.
- OH, OKAY.
I GUESS YOU LIKE IT
PRETTY HOT.
I'LL BE IN THE BATH
IF YOU NEED ME FOR ANYTHING.
- ALL RIGHT!
- IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU FOOLED HER FOR NOW.
- YEAH.  FOR NOW.
- ( giggles bashfully )
- HEY, SENPAI?
- ( shakily )
YEAH?
- I'LL DISTRACT TINA-SENPAI
AND WHOEVER ELSE IS THERE,
SO WHEN I DO--
- OKAY.
I GOTCHA.
- ♪ THE THUNDER CLAPS!
THE DEMON ROARS! ♪
♪ NOW IS THE TIME FOR US
TO DEFEND... ♪
- THAT'S THE MOST SENSELESS SONG
I'VE EVER HEARD.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS!
CAN'T YOU JUST ENJOY
A BATH QUIETLY?!
- SAY, TINA-SENPAI,
MISS MAYU...
- HMM?
- WHAT ARE YOU SO
NERVOUS ABOUT, TAEKO?
- TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
YOU SEE...
MM...
GO FOR IT, TAEKO.
LOOK, THERE'S A SQUID OVER THERE
THAT'S 20 YARDS LONG!
WAIT, THAT'S TOO FAR-FETCHED.
STUPID STUPID.
THAT'LL NEVER GET THEM
LOOKING THE OTHER WAY.
- WHERE?!  WHERE?!
- 20 YARDS LONG--
THAT'S A LOT!
- THEY ACTUALLY FELL FOR IT.
- OH, LOOK AT THAT OVER THERE.
I THINK IT'S THAT OVER THERE!
- WHERE IS IT?!
- I THINK IT'S...
- ( overlapping shouting )
- ( grunts )
- THERE!
- ( water splashes )
- WHAT WAS THAT SOUND
JUST NOW?
- YEAH, WHAT WAS IT?
- UM, IT WAS--
WELL...
SORRY FOR STARTLING YOU.
IT WAS JUST ME
SPLASHING THE WATER.
( laughs nervously )
OHH!
- ( burbling )
- IS IT ME, OR DID THAT
BUCKET JUST MOVE?
- WHAT?!
YOU MUST BE MISTAKEN!
- ( exhales )
- SUSPICIOUS, HUH?
- IT CERTAINLY IS.
- I DON'T THINK
IT'S SUSPICIOUS IN THE LEAST.
OH, NO, IT'S ALL OVER.
- TAEKO!
- ( all scream )
- AHH.
- CHIKA-CHAN!
( giggles )
DO YOU MIND IF I JOIN IN?
- NATURALLY I'M SURE
THAT NONE OF US MIND.
- WELL, I SURE DON'T.
WHEN IT COMES TO
THE HOT SPRINGS,
THE MORE THE MERRIER,
I ALWAYS SAY.
- MM!  HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
SINCE WE'RE ALL HERE,
LET'S SCRUB EACH OTHER'S BACKS.
- YEAH!
THAT SOUNDS KINDA FUN.
WE'VE NEVER DONE THINGS
LIKE THAT BEFORE.
DON'T YOU TWO THINK
IT'LL BE FUN?
- REALLY?
WASH EACH OTHER'S BACKS?
- WHY NOT?
I'M UP FOR THAT, CHIKA.
- ALL RIGHT!
LET'S DO IT THEN!
- WELL, THE FIRST ORDER
OF BUSINESS IS TO WARM UP.
- YEAH.  YOU'RE RIGHT.
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE, CHIKA!
IF YOU WANNA SOAK
IN THE HOT SPRINGS,
THEN THE TOWEL'S GONNA
HAVE TO GO.
THAT'S THE ONLY PROBLEM
THERE IS!
- AAH, CHIKA-CHAN.
- IS SOMETHING WRONG, CHIKA?
- AH...
( exhales )
- ( chuckles nervously )
- ( whimpering )
( crying loudly )
STUPID STUPID STUPID
STUPID STUPID!
- ( girls screaming )
- ( panting )
I'M SAFE AT LAST.
- ( bell dinging )
- All:
THANK YOU FOR THE MEAL.
- ( humming a tune )
JUST LEAVE THE DISHES
OVER THERE AND I'LL GET TO THEM.
- HEY, CHIKA-CHAN.
THANKS A LOT FOR
WHAT YOU DID EARLIER.
- WOW, THIS DISHWASHING
LIQUID DOES A GREAT JOB
OF CUTTING THROUGH THE GREASE.
IT'S TOTALLY AMAZING!
- I THINK I'LL BE ABLE
TO HANDLE THE REST.
SO WHY DON'T YOU AND MISS AOI
TAKE A BATH, MISS MIYABI?
- THANK YOU.
- HOWEVER--
- IT'S FINE--
THE TWO OF THEM WILL BE ALL
RIGHT IN A LITTLE BIT.
THEY JUST GOT OVERCOOKED
IN THE HOT SPRINGS,
SO LET 'EM COOL DOWN.
- ( both groaning )
- SO HOT.
- THEN WE'LL BE GOING NOW.
- ENJOY YOUR BATH.
- IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
I SHOULD TAKE TO THE KITCHEN?
- NO, I'LL HANDLE
THE REST MYSELF.
WHY DON'T YOU GO REST?
OH, ALMOST FORGOT.
- HMM?
- ACTUALLY, I DO HAVE
A LITTLE ERRAND
I'D LIKE YOU TO DO
WITH TAEKO LATER ON TONIGHT.
- SURE.
SO YOUR FAMILY
ALSO HAS A BOOTH?
- YES, WE ONLY HAVE IT OPEN
ON THE WEEKENDS,
BUT IT'S A FRIED NOODLE STAND.
- AND CHIKA-CHAN'S
THE ONE WHO COOKS?
- SHE SURE DOES.
IT'S REALLY GOOD TOO.
- ( waves crashing )
- I REALLY ENVY YOU.
I WISH I HAD A FAMILY OUT
IN THE COUNTRYSIDE LIKE THIS.
- MM.  YOU KNOW,
I'VE WANTED TO TELL YOU...
THAT I'M SORRY ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED EARLIER.
- HUH?  OH, YEAH!
I'M SORRY TOO.
WE'D BETTER GET GOING.
- YEAH.
- THANK YOU.
HMM?  WHAT IS IT?
- THAT'S REALLY AMAZING.
- HUH?  WHAT'S AMAZING?
- YOU CARRYING THAT GAS TANK.
WHEN IT WAS CHIKA-CHAN AND ME,
IT TOOK TWO OF US TO CARRY IT,
AND WE STILL WOBBLED
BACK AND FORTH.
- I SEE.
- I GUESS THIS COULD BE A LITTLE
BIT TOO HEAVY FOR A GIRL.
- AND THAT'S THE REASON
I SAID YOU WERE AMAZING, SENPAI.
- WELL, I AM A GUY, AFTER ALL.
- ( chuckles )
- ( chattering )
- HEY!
I'M RIGHT OVER HERE.
( giggles )
- ( sizzling )
- WOW, YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD
AT THIS, CHIKA-CHAN.
- AREN'T I, THOUGH?
HERE YOU GO.
GIVE IT A TASTE.
- ARE YOU SURE?
WOW, DELICIOUS.
- IT IS, ISN'T IT?
COME ON,
TRY SOME OF IT, TAEKO.
- BUT I'M NOT HUNGRY.
- JUST TRY IT.
- HERE.
- ( gasps )
- Chika: WELL,
THE STAND'S ALL READY
AND WE STILL HAVE
SOME TIME LEFT,
SO YOU TWO OUGHTA GO
LOOK AROUND A BIT.
- Taeko: OH, BUT--
- Chika: IT'S ALL RIGHT.
GO ON, GO ON.
- WHAT SHOULD I DO?
THIS FEELS...
KIND OF LIKE A DATE.
- TAEKO-CHAN.
- YES?!
- WANNA PLAY A GAME?
- HUH?
OH.
- SHOOT!
ALMOST HAD IT.
JUST A LITTLE HIGHER
WOULD HAVE DONE IT.
OKAY, IT'S YOUR TURN,
TAEKO-CHAN.
- ALL RIGHT.
( exhales )
I CAN'T DO THIS.
I FEEL WAY TOO NERVOUS TO.
MY HANDS WON'T LISTEN
TO WHAT I SAY.
I'LL JUST MESS UP.
OHH.
I HAVE TO ACT NATURAL.
HA!
AAH!
I'M SORRY, SENPAI.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( chuckles )
I'M FINE.
- WHY?  WHY AM I LIKE THIS?
THE MORE I TRY
TO ACT NATURAL,
THE MORE MY BODY
REFUSES TO COOPERATE.
JUST THINKING THAT
I'M ALONE HERE WITH HIM...
OHH...
I'M THE WORST!
IT'S ALL OVER.
HE MUST REALLY HATE ME NOW.
- TAEKO-CHAN.
- UM, SENPAI?
- YOU KNOW, SPENDING TIME
WITH YOU IS A LOT OF THINGS,
BUT IT SURE ISN'T BORING,
AT LEAST.
- ( slightly gasps )
OH.
YOU-- YOU MEAN
YOU'RE NOT MAD AT ME AT ALL?
- HUH?  WHY WOULD I BE?
- BECAUSE MY CLUMSINESS MUST
HAVE REALLY BEEN
A NUISANCE FOR YOU.
- HEY, THAT ISN'T TRUE AT ALL.
I HAD A LOT OF FUN TODAY.
- WHAT?
- BESIDES...
NO MATTER WHAT TROUBLE
COMES YOUR WAY,
YOU ALWAYS TRY YOUR BEST
TO HAVE A POSITIVE OUTLOOK.
YOU KNOW, IT'S THAT,
TAEKO-CHAN,
THAT I LIKE THE BEST.
- OH, SENPAI.
SENPAI.
SENPAI, I, UH--
THERE IS SOMETHING--
THERE'S SOMETHING...
THAT I HAVE TO TELL YOU.
- HEY, TAEKO-CHAN.
- YEAH.  YES, SENPAI?
- BEAUTIFUL.
COME ON,
DIDN'T YOU SEE THEM?!
THOSE WERE
BEAUTIFUL FIREWORKS.
- ( sighs )
HE-- HE DIDN'T HEAR
A SINGLE WORD I SAID.
ALL RIGHT, ONE MORE TIME.
SENPAI, I--
- ( fireworks cracking )
- OH.
- OH, SORRY.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT WERE WE
TALKING ABOUT AGAIN?
- UH-- NOTHING.
NEVER MIND.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- I'M SURE CHIKA-CHAN
MUST BE TIRED OF WAITING FOR US.
WE'D BETTER HURRY BACK.
- HEY, SLOW DOWN THERE.
- ( chuckles )
COME ON!
HURRY UP, SENPAI!
- All: THANK YOU FOR
TAKING SUCH GOOD CARE OF US.
- BUT YOU CAME HERE
TO ENJOY YOURSELVES,
AND I MADE YOU WORK.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- PLEASE, MA'AM,
WE ENJOYED OURSELVES.
- WE'LL COME VISIT YOU
REAL SOON, 'KAY, GRANDMA?
- OH, I'LL BE WAITING
FOR YOU ALL.
- DON'T CRY, GRANDMA.
- I'M NOT CRYING.
- YOU'RE SO MEAN!
- ( laughter )
- Chika:
SO HOW DID IT GO, TAEKO?
YOU AND BIG BROTHER SEEM
TO BE GETTING ALONG REALLY WELL.
SO, DID YOU ASK HIM OUT?
OH, BUT I GUESS THAT'S PROBABLY
ASKING TOO MUCH OF YOU, HUH?
- ( giggles )
- HEY!  WHY'D YOU LAUGH?
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
- IT'S A... SECRET.
- HEY, NO FAIR!
I'VE JUST GOTTA KNOW.
DON'T YOU KNOW THAT
I'M THE CUPID OF LOVE?
- MM.  WELL, YOU SEE...
AFTER BEING WITH HIM TODAY,
I'VE DISCOVERED SOMETHING--
I FOUND OUT THAT
I'D ONLY TROUBLE HIM
IF I STAYED THE SAME WAY
I AM NOW.
I HAVE TO TRY HARDER.
MUCH MUCH HARDER.
SO THAT I CAN DO ANYTHING,
LIKE MISS AOI.
SO I CAN BE STRONG-WILLED,
LIKE MISS MIYABI.
SO I CAN BE BRIGHT,
LIKE TINA-SENPAI.
AND SO I CAN BE AS HONEST
WITH MYSELF AS MISS MAYU.
I HAVE TO BECOME
A WONDERFUL WOMAN,
SO THAT I AM WORTHY OF HIM.
AND I'LL HAVE TO TRY
EVEN HARDER THAN I AM NOW.
- YOU'VE SURE CHANGED A LOT,
TAEKO.
- REALLY?
- YOU USED TO BE SO AFRAID
OF SPENDING TIME
AROUND GUYS.
BUT WHEN YOU'RE WITH
BIG BROTHER,
YOU'RE VERY NATURAL.
THAT'S WHY I THOUGHT
HE WAS YOUR BOYFRIEND,
WHEN I FIRST SAW HIM.
- I SEE.
- YEAH.
BUT, YOU KNOW...
( panting )
BIG BROTHER!
HEY, LISTEN...
- AAH!
- ( gasping )
- YEAH!
...BUT, YOU KNOW,
IF YOU TAKE TOO LONG
TO BECOME
A WONDERFUL WOMAN, TAEKO,
I JUST MIGHT GROW UP IN TIME
TO STEAL HIM AWAY FROM YOU.
- ( Tina and Mayu growling )
- CHIKA-CHAN...
- LET'S PLAY AGAIN SOON,
BIG BROTHER.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING,
KISSING KAORU LIKE THAT?!
- THAT'S RIGHT!
THE ONLY ONE HERE
WHO'S EVER TO KISS
HANABISHI-SAMA IS ME!
- WHAT?!
- YOU HAVE A PROBLEM?!
- ( both growling )
- OH.  OH.
- DO YOUR BEST, TAEKO, OKAY?
- HEY!
- ( Tina and Mayu shouting )
- Miyabi:
HONESTLY...
( sighs )
- Tina: COME ON!
- YEAH.
I'LL DO MY BEST.
- ( waves crashing )
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( Tina giggles )
FINALLY ME AND KAORU WILL--
- Chika:
WHAT'LL YOU DO WITH HIM?
- I CAN'T SAY IT!
IT'S SO EMBARRASSING!
- WHAT IS IT?
- "AI YORI AOSHI:
BEDSHARING."
- YOU'RE GONNA GIVE A HAIRCUT
TO YOUR PET?
- THAT'S PET-SHEARING!