- ( birds twitter )
- ( chattering )
- HUH?
- I AM NOT PERFECT,
BUT I HOPE YOU WILL
LEARN TO ACCEPT ME.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( birds twitter )
- ( child cries )
KAORU-SAMA!
- AOI-CHAN,
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
REALLY.
- ( sniffles )
( light sobs )
- THAT'LL DO IT.
HERE, THIS SHOULD WORK,
AOI-CHAN.
- WOW!
THANK YOU, KAORU-SAMA.
( giggles )
- ( train horn blares )
- ( alarm clock rings )
- Kaoru: OH NO!
IT'S THIS LATE ALREADY?!
HUH?
- ( birds chirp )
- ( yawns )
( thinking )
I'M SO HUNGRY.
- ( bell rings )
- ( students chatter )
- Girl: HERE.
- Boy: THANKS.
- ( giggles ) I MADE
YOUR FAVORITE TODAY.
- Announcer: TOKYO, TOKYO.
PLEASE TRANSFER TO
THE JR AND SUBWAY LINES HERE.
- WHICH IS THE ONE
I SHOULD TAKE?
( shyly )
UM, PARDON ME.
( gasps )
- IT'S ONE OF THOSE
CHERRY BLOSSOM PATTERNS.
- ( machine whirs )
( beeping )
- I WONDER WHY THIS GATE
WILL NOT LET ME PASS.
( gasps )
OH.
- EXCUSE ME.
EXCUSE ME,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- OH, I APOLOGIZE
FOR THE TROUBLE.
I THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
- OH, YOUR SANDAL.
- HOW TROUBLESOME.
WHAT WILL I DO?
- COULD YOU PLEASE HOLD
ONTO MY SHOULDER
FOR A LITTLE BIT.
- HUH?!
- IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
- SU-- SURE.
- IT'S PRETTY RARE,
A TSUMUGI
ON SOMEONE YOUR AGE.
- YOUR OBI HAS A NICE
DESIGN FOR SPRING TOO.
- YOU SEEM FAMILIAR
WITH KIMONOS.
- JUST A BIT.
- ( woman sighs )
- Man: THESE TWO GET IT.
- THAT SHOULD DO IT.
I THINK IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT,
BUT IT'S ONLY TEMPORARY
UNTIL YOU GET IT
FIXED PROPERLY.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR YOUR KINDNESS.
- OH, MY PLEASURE.
- THEN IF YOU WILL EXCUSE ME...
- HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
- YES.
- THAT'S A HOKUBU LINE TICKET,
RIGHT?
SO THEN THE GATE
THAT YOU NEED TO GO THROUGH
IS WAY OVER THERE.
- OH, I WAS NOT AWARE.
HOW WILL I BE ABLE
TO REACH IT THEN?
- LET'S SEE, YOU GO
STRAIGHT THAT WAY,
LEFT AT THE T-INTERSECTION,
RIGHT AT THE FIRST
FLIGHT OF STAIRS.
- GO STRAIGHT,
THEN LEFT,
RIGHT...
- UM, DID YOU GET THAT?
- SOMEWHAT. I BELIEVE THAT I'LL
BE ABLE TO FIND MY WAY.
SO I MUST WALK STRAIGHT AHEAD...
- LOOKS LIKE
SHE'LL JUST
GET HERSELF LOST.
IF YOU'D LIKE,
I CAN COME WITH YOU,
SINCE I'M ON MY WAY HOME
ON THAT SAME TRAIN.
- ... AND THEN TURN LEFT
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
YOU WOULD BE WILLING TO?
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
AND YOU REPAIRED
MY SANDAL STRAP TOO.
I WILL NEVER FORGET
YOUR KINDNESS.
- THAT'S A LITTLE MUCH.
- ( machine whirs )
- ( gasps )
- Kaoru: IT'S HARD TO SWITCH
TRAINS IN TOKYO, ISN'T IT?
- YES, I DO NOT UNDERSTAND
THE PROCESS AT ALL.
- WHEN I FIRST STARTED
GOING TO COLLEGE,
I USED TO GET LOST
ALL THE TIME TOO.
- OH, A COLLEGE STUDENT,
ARE YOU?
- UH-HUH.  I STARTED
JUNIOR YEAR THIS SPRING.
- YOU ARE GOOD
WITH YOUR HANDS.
- HUH? OH, THE SANDAL STRAP.
- YOU ALSO SEEM TO KNOW
A LOT ABOUT KIMONOS.
- WHEN I WAS A KID,
I USED TO DRESS UP A LOT
IN TRADITIONAL
JAPANESE CLOTHING.
MY MOM ACTUALLY USED TO WEAR
THE TSUMUGI KIMONO A LOT TOO.
SO I'M CERTAINLY NO STRANGER
WHEN IT COMES TO TALKING
ABOUT THOSE SORTS OF THINGS.
SORRY, I DIDN'T MEAN
TO BORE YOU.
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
YOU HELPED ME OUT
SO MUCH.
I HAD ABSOLUTELY NO IDEA
WHAT TOKYO WAS LIKE.
AND I WAS WORRIED
ABOUT FINDING MY WAY.
SO MEETING SOMEONE
WHO APPRECIATES KIMONOS
IS TRULY A GREAT RELIEF.
- Announcer: TOYAMADAI,
TOYAMADAI.
WE WILL BE HOLDING HERE
UNTIL THE EXPRESS TRAIN PASSES.
- WE FINALLY HAVE A SEAT.
- YEAH.
- ONE, TWO...
FOUR MORE STOPS UNTIL
IZUMIGAOKA.
- LOOKS LIKE IT.
- ( thinking ) SHE SAID
IT WAS HER FIRST TIME HERE.
BUT IT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE SHE'S A TOURIST.
A BOYFRIEND MAYBE.
- IS SOMETHING ON MY FACE?
YOU KEEP STARING.
- NO, N-- NOT REALLY.
UM, CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
- YES.
- WHY ARE YOU HERE
IN TOKYO?
- ACTUALLY, I CAME HERE
TO SEE SOMEBODY.
- SO COULD IT BE A GUY?
- YEAH, YES.
- ( thinking )
AND I WAS ONLY JOKING TOO.
- BUT THEN I CAME HERE
TO TOKYO
ON A WHIM, NOT KNOWING
IF I COULD MEET HIM OR NOT.
I WAS UNSURE
OF THE DIRECTIONS.
AND I WAS TERRIFIED, HONESTLY.
SO I APPRECIATE YOUR EFFORT
IN GUIDING ME LIKE THIS
FROM THE BOTTOM OF MY HEART.
( yawns )
IT'S NOT VERY OFTEN THAT
I STEP OUTSIDE ON MY OWN.
BUT FOR SOME REASON,
I FEEL MORE SLEEPY
THAN RELIEVED.
- Announcer: IZUMIGAOKA,
IZUMIGAOKO.
- WAKE UP.  WE'RE IN
IZUMIGAOKA STATION NOW.
- ( phone ringing )
- HEY, COME ON.
HEY, WAKE UP!
THERE GOES OUR STOP.
I GUESS IT'S FINE.  SHEESH.
SHE MIGHT BE A LITTLE CLUELESS
ABOUT THE WORLD,
BUT SHE'S STILL
KINDA CUTE.
- ( sighs )
I APOLOGIZE! WHEN DID I--
IS THE STOP MUCH FURTHER?
- IT'S COMING UP.
- I ALMOST SLEPT
PASSED THE STOP.
- YOU MEAN
A SECOND TIME, RIGHT?
- ( phone rings )
- Aoi: I REALLY DO APOLOGIZE
FOR ALL THIS TROUBLE.
IT'S OKAY.
ISHI IZUMI BLOCK, RIGHT?
I LIVE AROUND THERE.
- AGAIN, I APOLOGIZE.
- SO WHAT'S HE LIKE,
THIS GUY THAT YOU'RE VISITING?
- GENTLE.  WE HAVE NOT
SEEN ONE ANOTHER
IN A LONG TIME,
BUT I DO REMEMBER THAT.
AND IT'S AS IF MY HEART
IS PUT AT EASE
EVERY TIME I THINK OF HIM.
( giggles )
- WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
- I JUST REMEMBERED THAT
AN INCIDENT FROM MY CHILDHOOD
WAS VERY SIMILAR TO
WHAT HAPPENED EARLIER.
THE STRAP ON MY SANDAL BROKE
MUCH LIKE IT DID TODAY.
AND HE REPAIRED IT FOR ME.
NOW THAT I THINK OF IT,
HE MUST HAVE BEEN GOOD
WITH HIS HANDS AS WELL.
- OH.
YOU REALLY LOVE
THIS GUY A LOT, HUH?
- I DO. HE IS THE FIRST ONE
I HAVE EVER
LOVED IN MY LIFE.
WHEN I THINK OF HIM,
I FEEL BLESSED
TO HAVE BEEN BORN
INTO THIS WORLD
AND TO HAVE MET HIM.
- THAT'S PRETTY AMAZING,
TO FEEL SO MUCH
FOR ONE PERSON.
I HOPE YOU GET
TO SEE HIM SOON.
- ME TOO.
- IT SHOULD BE AROUND HERE
ACCORDING TO THIS ADDRESS.
YUP, NO MISTAKE.
IT'S RIGHT AROUND THAT CORNER.
- I WILL FIND HIM
AROUND THIS CORNER.
( gasps )
- ( siren wails )
- ARE YOU SURE
THERE'S NO MISTAKE?
- WELL, IF THE ADDRESS
IS RIGHT, THIS IS IT.
- THAT CANNOT BE.
NO!
I THOUGHT I WOULD
FINALLY SEE HIM.
THIS CANNOT BE TRUE.
WHAT WILL I DO NOW?
- ( rain spatters )
- Kaoru: DRINK THIS.
AND TRY TO CHEER UP.
- ( despondently )
ALL RIGHT.
- HAVING HER COME UP HERE
IS FINE AND ALL,
BUT WHAT CAN I SAY TO HER
IN A SITUATION LIKE THIS?
UM, ARE YOU OKAY?
ALL I CAN DO
IS FEEL SORRY FOR HER.
I WANT TO
HELP HER SOMEHOW.
EXCUSE ME,
BUT DON'T YOU HAVE
ANY OTHER CLUES
THAT YOU CAN USE.
- A PHOTOGRAPH
OF MYSELF AND HIM.
- BUT IT'S
A CHILDHOOD PICTURE.
HMM?
HEY, HAVEN'T I SEEN THIS
SOMEWHERE?
ISN'T THIS ME
AND AOI-CHAN?!
- HUH? WHAT WAS THAT?
- I SAID TH--
THIS WAS A PHOTO
OF AOI-CHAN AND ME.
- THEN THAT MEANS
THAT YOU ARE...
KAORU-SAMA?
- YEAH, I'M KAORU HANABISHI.
- Young Kaoru: AOI-CHAN,
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
- Present Kaoru:
- ( gasps )
( gasping )
OH, KAORU-SAMA!
KAORU-SAMA! KAORU-SAMA!
KAORU-SAMA!
FOR 18 YEARS,
I'VE BEEN WAITING PATIENTLY
FOR THIS MOMENT.
- 18 YEARS?
- TO THINK THAT THE PERSON
WHO WAS SO KIND TO ME
WAS YOU.
I HAVE NEVER FELT THE FORCE
CALLED DESTINY
MORE STRONGLY THAN NOW!
- UH, HOLD ON A MINUTE.
CALM DOWN.
I THINK I NEED
AN EXPLANATION.
- I APOLOGIZE.
IN SHORT, I,
AOI SAKURABA,
HAVE COME WITH THE INTENTION
OF BEING YOUR WIFE.
- HUH?
WIFE?!
- YES, I AM TO BECOME
YOUR WIFE, KAORU-SAMA.
- IT'S TRUE THAT
I REMEMBER YOU NOW, AOI-CHAN,
BUT YOU BECOMING MY WIFE?
- THE DREAM THAT I HAVE HAD
FOR ALL OF MY LIFE
IS FINALLY COMING TRUE.
COME, LET US RETURN TO THE
HANABISHI FAMILY TOGETHER.
- HANABISHI!
- ONCE YOU RETURN TO THEM,
YOU AND I
CAN BE TOGETHER.
- I SEE.
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
- KAORU-SAMA?
- IF THEY WANT ME BACK
IN HANABISHI,
THEY CAN COME
STRAIGHT TO ME!
TRYING TO LURE ME BACK
USING A GIRL!
I TRUST THEM EVEN LESS
AFTER THIS.
- KAORU-SAMA?
- AOI-CHAN, I WON'T
GO BACK TO HANABISHI.
I'M SORRY, BUT PLEASE
LEAVE NOW.
- ( door slams )
- ( Aoi cries )
KAORU-SAMA.
YOU MUST HAVE
REALLY LEFT HANABISHI
BECAUSE YOU
DID NOT LIKE ME.
- HMPH! I ALMOST
LET THEM FOOL ME.
I'M SURE THOSE HANABISHI GUYS
RIGGED ALL THIS.
WHEN THEY FIND OUT THAT THEIR
NASTY LITTLE PLAN DIDN'T WORK,
I'M SURE THAT SOMEONE WILL BE BY
TO TAKE HER BACK.
AND IT'S LIKE I SAID.
HERE THEY COME,
JUST LIKE CLOCKWORK.
HUH?
- ( both chuckle )
- THEY'RE NOT FROM
HANABISHI!
- YOU HERE
BY YOURSELF, GIRL?
- YOU WANT TO KARAOKE?
- YEAH, LET'S GO KARAOKE.
- YOU'LL JUST CATCH A COLD
STANDING OUT HERE.
HEY, HOW ABOUT
A BITE TO EAT?
- WE KNOW A JOINT AROUND HERE
THAT'S GOT A GOOD OCEAN VIEW.
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
- HUH? AND WHO ARE YOU?
- HEY, BUDDY,
WE WEREN'T
TALKING TO YOU.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- YOU TRYING TO STEAL HER
AWAY FROM US?
- WE ASKED THE GIRL OUT
FIRST, YOU KNOW?
- AIN'T YOU
GONNA SAY SOMETHING?
- IT WAS GOOD
I JUMPED OUT HERE,
BUT THEY LOOK PRETTY STRONG.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
UM, UH...
- Both: HUH?
- SH-- SH--
SHE'S MY GIRL!
G-- GOT A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
- Both: HUH?
- KAORU-SAMA?
- THAT WASN'T SMART.
DID THAT REALLY JUST COME
OUT OF MY MOUTH?
- DAMN IT! AWW!
SO SHE'S ALREADY TAKEN.
- YOU SHOULDN'T LET A GIRL
WAIT AROUND HER ALL BY HERSELF.
- LET'S GO.  DAMN!
- ( sighs ) HUH?
OH, WERE YOU SCARED?
EVERYTHING'S ALL RIGHT NOW.
COME ON,
IT'S ALL RIGHT NOW.
- NO, I...
( sobs )
AM JUST HAPPY
THAT YOU JUST SAID
THAT I WAS YOUR GIRL,
LIE OR NOT.
( sniffles )
- THAT'S TRUE.
A GOOD GIRL LIKE HER
WOULD NEVER DO THAT.
AOI-CHAN, SORRY. I JUMPED
TO CONCLUSIONS, I GUESS.
IN ANY CASE, LET'S GO BACK.
MY FEET KIND OF HURT
STANDING HERE.
OKAY?
- KAORU-SAMA.
- SO YOU AND I
WERE PROMISED TO WED?
- YES, WE HAVE SEEN
ONE ANOTHER
QUITE A FEW TIMES
IN OUR YOUTH.
- ( laughs )
- HUH?
- ( gasps )
- Present Aoi:
SINCE THEN,
I WAS RAISED TO BE YOUR WIFE,
KAORU-SAMA...
TO DO EVERYTHING THAT
I POSSIBLY CAN DO FOR YOU.
YOU WERE NOT AWARE
OF ANY OF THIS, KAORU-SAMA?
- WELL, YOU SEE,
I THINK I REMEMBER
SOMETHING THAT WAS SAID
ALONG THOSE LINES,
BUT NOTHING CONCRETE.
- HOWEVER, ONE DAY, I WAS TOLD
TO FORGET THAT PROMISE.
SO I WISHED TO
MEET YOU IN PERSON
AND HEAR THE TRUTH.
- THAT'S WHY YOU'RE HERE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT LIKE
I LEFT HANABISHI
BECAUSE I DIDN'T LIKE YOU.
IT'S JUST A LOT HAPPENED
BACK THERE.
- THANK GOODNESS.
- YOU MUST BE TIRED.
SO RELAX FOR TONIGHT.
- UH, UM, WILL IT
BE ALL RIGHT
FOR ME TO STAY HERE
TONIGHT?
- WELL, IT REALLY IS GETTING
PRETTY LATE, AFTER ALL.
I'LL GO GET
THE BATH READY.
OH, YOU TOLD YOUR FOLKS
BEFORE YOU LEFT
THAT YOU WERE COMING HERE,
RIGHT?
- YES, OF COURSE I DID.
THERE IS NO NEED
TO CONTACT THEM NOW!
I SUPPOSE I WILL
TAKE A BATH NOW.
- YOU'RE COLD, RIGHT?
TAKE YOUR TIME
AND WARM UP.
- I WILL.
- TO THINK THAT A GIRL'S
TAKING A BATH IN MY ROOM,
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
ONE'S EVEN BEEN IN HERE.
- ( clothes ruffle )
- WOW, WHY DOES IT
SOUND SO SEXY
WHEN SOMEONE TAKES OFF
A KIMONO?
- ( ruffling continues )
- ( clock ticks )
- HMM!
- 18 YEARS, HUH?
I NEVER HEARD
ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
- ( silent )
- IT'S A PROBLEM.
SHE'S A REALLY NICE GIRL,
SO IT ISN'T HORRIBLE,
BUT THIS IS SO SUDDEN.
I CAN'T GET MY HEAD
OUT OF THE CLOUDS.
- ( cries )
( crying )
- HUH?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- N-- NO.
IT'S NOTHING.
- OH.
OH, OKAY.
( gasps )
- SHE WORE THIS KIND
OF UNDERWEAR?
UH!
- I AM SO GLAD KAORU-SAMA
DOES NOT HATE ME.
I AM TRULY BLESSED
THAT I WAS ABLE
TO MEET KAORU-SAMA.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Aoi: I WISH TO FULFILL
WHATEVER KAORU-SAMA DESIRES.
HUH? YOU WANT TO SLEEP
IN THE SAME FUTON?
AI YORI AOSHI.
"SUPPER."
I WILL ALWAYS BE
BY YOUR SIDE.