- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( sighs )
HUH?
- COME ON, CHIKA.
EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
THERE ISN'T ANYTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
- I DON'T KNOW, GUYS.
- THEY'RE GONNA
COME BACK, OKAY?
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
- YEAH.
- ( sighs )
- IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
- WELL, LET'S GET GOING.
- YES.
- ( gasps )
LADY AOI!  SIR KAORU!
WHAT ARE YOU TWO
STILL DOING HERE?
- TAKE US THERE, MISS MIYABI.
- WHERE?
- TO THE SAKURABA ESTATE.
- Miyabi:
ARE YOU CERTAIN ABOUT THIS?
- YES, I DECIDED THIS
WITH KAORU-SAMA.
- YEAH, WE DISCUSSED IT
LAST NIGHT.
WE'RE SET ON
TALKING THINGS OUT.
- Tina:
KAORU'S AN AWKWARD GUY.
AND HE'S THE TYPE
THAT CAN'T LIE TO HIMSELF.
BUT THOSE TWO THINGS ARE WHAT'S
SO GOOD ABOUT HIM, I GUESS.
- KAGURAZAKI.
I WANT AN EXPLANATION.
- UH, YES.
OF COURSE, SIR.
ACTUALLY--
- TO TELL THE TRUTH, FATHER...
...THE ONLY THING
MISS MIYABI DID WAS
FULFILL A SELFISH REQUEST
OF MINE.
I WANTED TO SEE
KAORU-SAMA AGAIN.
I'M THE ONE
THAT'S TO BLAME.
SO I WILL TAKE
FULL RESPONSIBILITY
FOR ALL OF HER ACTIONS.
- I WILL BE THE JUDGE
OF FAULT.
- BUT THIS IS NOT
MISS MIYABI'S FAULT.
THE BLAME SHOULD FALL ON ME.
- AOI.
- I KNOW THAT I CAME
UNANNOUNCED, AND I APOLOGIZE.
BUT THERE WAS
SOMETHING IMPORTANT
THAT I WISH TO
DISCUSS WITH YOU--
- NOT ANOTHER WORD
OUT OF YOU!
THIS IS A SAKURABA
FAMILY MATTER.
- ( slightly gasps )
- NO, IT ISN'T, FATHER.
PLEASE LISTEN TO WHAT
KAORU-SAMA HAS TO SAY.
HIS FEELINGS ARE
THE SAME AS MY OWN.
- FEELINGS, YOU SAY.
- PLEASE,
JUST HEAR ME OUT, SIR.
- I HAVE NO REASON TO DO SO.
- I BEG YOU, PLEASE.
- Taeko: HANABISHI-SENPAI REALLY
HAS A STRAIGHTFORWARD HEART.
THAT'S WHY
HE SHINES SO BRIGHTLY.
AND WHENEVER I SEE HIM,
I THINK ABOUT HOW I NEED
TO DO MY BEST IN LIFE.
- PLEASE.  PLEASE.
JUST HEAR ME OUT, SIR.
- I BEG OF YOU TO
HEAR HIM OUT AS WELL, SIR.
HE CAME HERE WITH
VERY HONORABLE INTENTIONS.
- YOU SHOULDN'T OVERSTEP
YOUR BOUNDS.
REMEMBER YOUR PLACE,
KAGURAZAKI!
- I WAS CHARGED WITH
LADY AOI'S EDUCATION.
AND BECAUSE I'VE SERVED
YOUR DAUGHTER ALL THESE YEARS,
ENSURING HER HAPPINESS
IS MY PLACE.
- VERY WELL, MIYABI.
THE YOUNG MAN MAY SPEAK FREELY.
- THANK YOU, MOTHER.
- I'M IN YOUR DEBT.
THANK YOU.
I, AS I AM NOW...
I AM NO LONGER
OFFICIALLY A MEMBER
OF THE HANABISHI HOUSE.
THE CIRCUMSTANCES
HAVE CHANGED
SINCE THE ENGAGEMENT.
I'M JUST A COLLEGE STUDENT NOW.
AND I'M AFRAID I CAN'T MAKE
ANY PROMISES ABOUT THE FUTURE.
BUT STILL, EVEN SO--
- IS THIS NONSENSE
ALL YOU HAVE TO SAY?
DID YOU HONESTLY THINK
THAT I APPROVED
OF YOUR RELATIONSHIP
WITH MY DAUGHTER,
CONSIDERING YOUR STATE?
THERE ARE NO WORDS
THAT CAN DESCRIBE MY DISGUST.
YOU ARE THE ONE
WHO BETRAYED US!
YOU ABANDONED YOUR OBLIGATION.
YOU BETRAYED THE FEELINGS
THAT MY DAUGHTER HAD FOR YOU.
YOU BETRAYED THE ONE
WHO BELIEVED IN YOU THE MOST
AS YOUR FIANCEE,
AND IN DOING SO,
YOU BETRAYED
OUR FEELINGS AS WELL,
AS PARENTS WHO CARE
FOR THEIR DAUGHTER.
YOU BETRAYED
OUR ENTIRE FAMILY!
SINCE YOU HAD
SOMETHING TO SAY,
I ASSUMED YOU WERE
GOING TO APOLOGIZE.
I DON'T INTEND TO
LET YOU HAVE MY DAUGHTER.
IF THAT'S UNDERSTOOD,
THEN LEAVE RIGHT NOW!
- HOLD ON, FATHER!
- IT IS TRUE.
IT IS TRUE THAT
I WAS THE ONE
WHO BROKE THE PROMISE
TO YOUR FAMILY.
SO YOU COULD SAY THAT WE'RE
NOT REALLY ENGAGED ANYMORE.
AND I MAY NEVER BE
FORGIVEN FOR THIS,
BUT I...
I JUST DIDN'T WANNA
RUN AWAY ANYMORE!
FOR HER SAKE,
AS WELL AS MINE.
- SO THIS IS FOR AOI'S SAKE?
- Mayu:
HANABISHI-SAMA IS A PERSON
WITH A VERY GENTLE HEART.
GENTLE, YET STRONG.
I'M SURE IT MUST BE
BECAUSE...
HE'S KNOWN MORE PAIN
IN HIS HEART
THAN ANYONE SHOULD EVER
HAVE TO EXPERIENCE.
- I... HAVE NO FAMILY.
MY FATHER AND MOTHER...
WERE NEVER ALLOWED
TO BE WED.
MY MOTHER WAS SAID
TO BE UNWORTHY
OF CARRYING
THE HANABISHI NAME.
AND SOON AFTER I WAS BORN,
SHE AND I LOST MY FATHER
TO AN ACCIDENT.
IT WAS JUST THE TWO OF US.
BUT BECAUSE THE HANABISHIS
LOST THEIR ONLY HEIR
IN THAT ACCIDENT,
THEY NEEDED A SUCCESSOR.
SO THEY FORCED ME
BACK INTO THEIR HOUSE.
IT WAS THEN THAT I WAS
SEPARATED FROM MY ONLY FAMILY.
THERE WAS NO LOVE
IN THE HANABISHI HOUSE.
AND EVERY DAY I DREAMT OF...
- ( slap landing )
- ...BEING REUNITED
WITH MY MOTHER.
HOWEVER, THAT REUNION
NEVER CAME.
EVER SINCE THEN,
I'VE BEEN ALL ALONE...
WITH NO ONE TO RELY ON
AND NOWHERE TO RETURN.
I WAS LONELY
AND SAD.
IT WAS BECAUSE
I KNEW THOSE FEELINGS--
THE PAIN OF LOSING
ONE'S ENTIRE FAMILY--
THAT I ALSO KNEW THAT
I NEVER WANTED AOI-CHAN
TO FEEL THE SAME WAY.
THAT'S THE REASON WHY
I DECIDED TO COME HERE,
AND DISCUSS THINGS WITH YOU.
- SIR KAORU...
- IS THAT ALL
YOU HAVE TO SAY?
DID YOU HONESTLY THINK
THAT I WOULD JUST FORGIVE YOU
AFTER HEARING THAT STORY?
IF SO, YOU'RE A FOOLISH MAN.
- FATHER, PLEASE.
FATHER, PLEASE DON'T GO YET!
- AOI-CHAN'S--
AOI SAKURABA IS
IMPORTANT TO ME.
NO ONE CAN REPLACE HER.
I DON'T WANNA LOSE
ANYBODY I LOVE EVER AGAIN!
- ( slightly gasps )
- I'M SORRY.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- WELL THEN, KAORU, AOI.
- HUH?
- EVERYTHING IS FINE.
- DESPITE WHAT YOU THINK,
YOUR FATHER HAS CHOSEN
TO ACCEPT KAORU.
- HOW SO, MADAME?
- IF HE HAD NOT
ACCEPTED KAORU,
THEN HE WOULD HAVE HAD
SOME SERVANTS
ESCORT HIM OFF THE ESTATE.
BUT YOUR FATHER CHOSE
TO LEAVE THE ROOM HIMSELF.
- ( crying )
- Chika:
BIG BROTHER...
WHEN YOU'RE HERE,
YOU KNOW,
I FEEL SO RELAXED.
AND I ALWAYS FORGET
ALL MY PROBLEMS.
- FATHER?
PLEASE FORGIVE MY LACK
OF MANNERS EARLIER.
- THE ONE THING
THAT I WOULD LIKE TO SEE NOW
IS YOUR SMILE, AOI.
BUT EVER SINCE
YOU RETURNED HOME
THE OTHER DAY,
YOU HAVE NOT SMILED
EVEN ONCE.
I REMEMBER THE DAY
YOU WERE BORN.
IT WAS WARM AND THE SKY WAS
A PIERCING SHADE OF BLUE.
MUCH LIKE TODAY.
THE COLOR BLUE HAS THE POWER
TO HEAL PEOPLE'S HEARTS.
IT'S SO KIND, SO PURE.
YOU WERE NAMED IN HONOR
OF THAT PIERCING BLUE.
WITH THOSE VERY IMAGES
IN MIND,
I ACCEPT THAT MAN,
BUT I HAVE NOT FORGIVEN HIM.
IT'S ONLY THAT I ALWAYS
WANT YOU TO BE SMILING.
THAT'S ALL.
YOU ARE MY DAUGHTER.
YOU ARE MY DAUGHTER
WHO IS MORE PRECIOUS TO ME
THAN EVEN MY OWN LIFE.
- FATHER, I NEVER KNEW.
- THIS IS YOUR HOME, AOI.
COME BACK WHENEVER YOU WISH.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR EVERYTHING.
THANK YOU, FATHER.
- IT SEEMS THAT EVERYTHING
TURNED OUT FOR THE BEST,
LADY AOI.
- MISS MIYABI, I APOLOGIZE
FOR TROUBLING YOU SO
ALL THIS TIME.
- PLEASE, RAISE YOUR HEADS,
THE TWO OF YOU.
I WAS SIMPLY DOING WHAT I FELT
WAS MOST APPROPRIATE.
WELL THEN, SIR KAORU,
I WILL LEAVE LADY AOI
IN YOUR CARE.
- HUH?
- MISS MIYABI?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- THE DUTIES THAT WERE
ASSIGNED TO ME ARE COMPLETE.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME,
LADY AOI.
I REALIZE THAT MY WORK
PERFORMANCE
COULD HAVE BEEN IMPROVED
IN MANY AREAS.
BUT IN ANY CASE,
I HOPE THAT YOUR LIFE
WITH SIR KAORU WILL BE
A HAPPY ONE.
- MISS MIYABI...
- WE SHOULD ALL GO BACK HOME
TOGETHER, MISS MIYABI.
BACK TO THE PLACE WHERE
OUR FAMILY MUST BE WAITING.
- I'M SURE THEY'VE GOTTA BE
WAITING FOR US.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Chika:
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHY ARE YOU GETTING READY
FOR A PARTY?
DID YOU HEAR SOMETHING
FROM THEM?
- NO.  NOTHING JUST YET.
- THEN WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
IF THEY DON'T COME BACK TODAY,
THEN ALL THE FOOD
YOU GUYS ARE PUTTING OUT IS
GONNA GO TO WASTE.
- THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND AT ALL,
EITHER.
- HEY, WHAT THE HECK DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING HERE?
- DON'T MIND THE MINOR DETAILS.
- COME ON, TELL ME WHY
YOU'RE DOING THIS.
- WE'RE DOING THIS BECAUSE THEY
MIGHT BE COMING BACK HOME TODAY.
- Mayu and Chika:
HUH?
- WE'RE PREPARING DINNER
SO IT'LL BE READY
WHENEVER THEY COME HOME.
SO WE CAN WELCOME THEM
WITH A SMILE.
'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT IT MEANS
TO BE A FAMILY.
- WHAT IT MEANS TO BE
A FAMILY?
- MM-HMM.
- Both: HMM...
- YOU TWO DON'T GET IT.
I DON'T BLAME YOU.
BUT YOU KNOW,
I'M SURE YOU GUYS WOULD GET IT
IF YOU LIVED HERE.
- WE'D GET IT?
- IF WE LIVED HERE?
- ( vehicle approaching )
- HUH?  OH!
- Both:
IS THAT WHAT I THINK IT IS?
- THEY FINALLY CAME BACK!
- ( all chuckling, panting )
- WE'RE BACK.
- WE'VE JUST ARRIVED HOME,
EVERYBODY.
- All: WELCOME BACK!
- MM,
THIS NICE WARM WEATHER WE'RE
HAVING SURE IS COMFORTABLE.
- IT DOES FEEL PRETTY GOOD.
- YEAH, I SLEPT LIKE A LOG
DURING MY LAST LECTURE.
- SO I'M AWAKE
AND FULL OF ENERGY!
- OH, WILL YOU PLEASE STOP
DOING THIS TO ME EVERY DAY,
TINA-SENPAI?!
OHH!
- BY THE WAY, MAYU,
HOW FAR ARE YOU TAGGING ALONG?
- WELL, IF YOU MUST KNOW,
MAYU WAS INVITED TO SPEND
SOME TIME AT
HANABISHI-SAMA'S HOUSE TODAY.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN "TODAY"?
IF YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED,
YOU HANG OUT WITH US EVERY DAY.
- THAT'S MERELY A COINCIDENCE,
I ASSURE YOU!
- I DON'T REMEMBER ANYONE
INVITING YOU IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- MAYU MAKES HER OWN RULES
IN THIS CASE.
- DID THAT MAKE SENSE
TO ANYONE?
- ( laughs )
- ( squeaks )
- ( giggles )
YOU SEE?  UZUME WELCOMED ME,
SO I'M INVITED.
- WHOSE SIDE ARE YOU ON
ANYWAY, UZUME?!
- ( squeaks )
- IT LOOKS LIKE UZUME
HAS GOTTEN USED TO
MISS MAYU BEING AROUND NOW.
- ( sinister laughter )
"OPERATION: KISS THE SQUIRE
FIRST AS THE NIGHT
IS PROCEEDING" IS PLANNED.
- OH, HELLO THERE.
WELCOME HOME, EVERYONE.
- HEY, THERE, AOI-CHAN.
WE'RE BACK.
HUH?
- HEY, WHAT'S UP, HANABISHI?
- YOU'RE LATE, YOU KNOW?
- SUZUKI?  SATO?
- WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING HERE?
- Suzuki:
WE'RE MOVING, CAN'T YOU TELL?
- YOU GUYS ARE MOVING?
- SO THEN YOU GUYS ARE
GONNA BE LIVING HERE WITH US?
- Suzuki and Sato: HUH?
- WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- HEY, DON'T JUMP THE GUN
LIKE THAT, HANABISHI.
- ( sighs )
AHH!
GUESS I FELL ASLEEP.
- CHIKA-CHAN!
- IT'S CHIKA!
- ARE YOU STARTING
TO WAKE UP NOW, MISS CHIKA?
- MM-HMM.
OH, BIG BROTHER!
- JUST A MINUTE THERE.
WH-- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING WITH
HANABISHI-SAMA?!
- I'LL LET CHIKA
KEEP DOING IT.
- YAY!
- I WON'T ALLOW THIS
TO CONTINUE!
GET AWAY FROM HIM
THIS INSTANT!
- WHAT EXACTLY IS
GOING ON HERE?
- MISS CHIKA IS A NEW TENANT,
AND SHE WILL BE LIVING IN THIS
HOUSE WITH US STARTING TODAY
- CHIKA'S A NEW TENANT?
- COME TO THINK OF IT,
SHE DID TELL ME
SHE GOT ACCEPTED INTO
A HIGH SCHOOL HERE.
- IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GONNA BE
TOGETHER EVERY DAY FROM NOW ON.
LOOK, THIS IS MY SCHOOL UNIFORM!
NEAT, HUH?!
- WOW!
- I WORE IT HERE, BECAUSE
I WANTED TO SHOW IT TO YOU.
- ( both chuckle )
- WELL THEN, TWO CAN PLAY
THAT GAME.
AH, HANABISHI-SAMA!
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO PULL HERE?!
- ( all scream )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
KAORU-SAMA?
- HERE WE GO AGAIN.
- Tina: LET GO OF HIM!
- Mayu:
HELP ME, HANABISHI-SAMA!
THIS CAVE WOMAN IS
ATTACKING ME!
- Tina: WHO YOU CALLING
A CAVE WOMAN?!
AAH!
- Taeko: OH, MY GOSH,
I JUST NOTICED
THEY'RE ALL STANDING
ON CHIKA-CHAN!
- Aoi: OH, MY!
- Kaoru: HEY, GET OFF!
EVERYBODY OFF!
- ( meowing )
- All: CHEERS!
- ( glasses clinking )
- HEY, CHIKA, GLAD TO
HAVE YOU WITH US AGAIN.
- THANKS! I HOPE YOU'LL
TEACH ME LOTS OF THINGS
LIKE YOU DID BEFORE, MISS TINA.
- SURE THING! FEEL
FREE TO COME TO ME
IF THERE'S ANYTHING
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I COULD TEACH YOU
JUST ABOUT ANYTHING.
- OTHER THAN
ACADEMICS, THAT IS.
- WHAT?!
- WHAT'S THIS?
YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN TO HAVE
A PROBLEM WITH A GUEST
WHO'S BEEN OFFICIALLY INVITED,
WOULD YOU?
- UH--
MISS MANAGER!
( cries )
CAN'T YOU SAY SOMETHING
TO THE GUEST?
SHE'S BEING MEAN TO ME.
- PLEASE DON'T FONDLE
MY BREASTS.
- HUH?
SORRY.  BAD HABIT.
- THAT IS NO EXCUSE,
MISS TINA.
- NO, I'M SORRY!
HA HA, PLEASE FORGIVE ME!
- Taeko:
JEEZ, TINA-SENPAI...
- Mayu:
WHAT A SAD INSTINCT.
- WE WEREN'T INTRODUCED.
I'M RUKA SAIONJI.
- OH, UH, HELLO.
IT'S VERY NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M CHIKA MINAZUKI.
- ( wind blowing )
- IT'S NICE TO
SIT OUT HERE AT NIGHT
AND WATCH THE CHERRY BLOSSOMS.
- YES.
- THE STARS ARE BEAUTIFUL TOO.
- OH.
- YOU KNOW, AOI-CHAN...
IF YOU'RE LOOKING AT ME,
THEN YOU CAN'T SEE
THE CHERRY BLOSSOMS
OR THE STARS.
- THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I WANNA WATCH YOU
RIGHT NOW, KAORU-SAMA.
- REALLY?
- BOO.
- ( both chuckle )
- UH-- AAH.
AOI-CHAN!
- OH, I APOLOGIZE.
WERE YOU NOT ABLE
TO BREATHE?
- I COULD.
IT'S JUST...
WELL, YOU KINDA CAUGHT ME
BY SURPRISE.
BUT IT FELT GREAT.
- HUH?
KAORU-SAMA, HONESTLY.
- ( laughs )
SORRY.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I WOULDN'T
MIND IF YOU DID THAT AGAIN.
- UH?
- ( singsongy )
WON'T YOU DO IT AGAIN?
- KAORU-SAMA,
PLEASE DON'T LOOK AT ME
LIKE THAT.
- ( laughs )
I'M JUST KIDDING AROUND.
- YES, I SUPPOSE.
- HUH?
- ONE MORE TIME.
RIGHT?
THERE!
( giggles softly )
- ( giggles )
- IN THE PAST,
I ALWAYS FELT VERY LONELY
DURING THIS SEASON
OF CHERRY BLOSSOMS.
- YOU DID?  WHY?
- THE CHERRY TREES ARE
A FAMILY NAMESAKE.
AND THERE IS A LARGE ONE
WITHIN OUR ESTATE.
EVERY SPRING,
I ALWAYS LOOKED AT THE TREE
AND THOUGHT TO MYSELF,
"I DIDN'T GET TO SEE
KAORU-SAMA LAST YEAR.
BUT MAYBE I WILL THIS YEAR."
I ALWAYS WONDERED IF
I WOULD BE ABLE TO SEE
THE CHERRY BLOSSOMS
WITH YOU SOMEDAY.
BUT SINCE WE'VE BEEN REUNITED,
I WAS ABLE TO SEE THE FLOWERS
WITH YOU THIS YEAR.
AND THAT'S WHY RIGHT NOW,
I FEEL VERY HAPPY, KAORU-SAMA.
- AOI-CHAN.
WE'LL SEE THEM AGAIN
NEXT YEAR,
AND THE YEAR AFTER.
WE'LL MAKE SURE
WE ALWAYS DO.
- ALWAYS.
- YEAH.  ALWAYS.
- KAORU!  MISS LANDLORD!
YOU'RE OUT THERE, RIGHT?
LET'S PLAY A GAME TOGETHER.
COME ON!
- ALL RIGHT!
WE'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
SHALL WE GO BACK?
AOI-CHAN?
- SURE.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HEY, COME ON, KAORU-SAMA.
I WANTED TO PLAY SOME MORE.
COME ON.
WAKE UP, KAORU-SAMA.
( sighs )
- ( birds chirping,
wings fluttering )
- AHH!
I GUESS I FELL ASLEEP.
SORRY ABOUT THAT, AOI-CHAN.
MM?
WHAT'S WRONG, AOI-CHAN?
- UH, NOTHING'S WRONG.
- OH.
THEN LET'S PLAY SOME MORE.
- SURE.
- WHAT DO YOU WANNA PLAY NOW?
- UM... UM...
HIDE-AND-GO-SEEK.
- WHAT?! AGAIN?
- AW, HIDE-AND-GO-SEEK.
- ALL RIGHT, THAT'S FINE.
- YAY!