- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- KAORU-SAMA, HAVE YOU
FORGOTTEN ANYTHING?
- NOPE. OH, THE MISO SOUP WITH
DAIKON RADISHES WAS DELICIOUS.
- THANK YOU FOR
THE COMPLIMENT.
YOU WERE SAYING HOW
THE FOOD FROM THE OTHER DAY
WAS TREMENDOUSLY
DELICIOUS ALSO.
- EVERYTHING THAT YOU COOK
IS JUST SO DELICIOUS, AOI-CHAN.
- OH MY.
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME.
- AOI-CHAN.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- ( Miyabi clears throat )
- Both: HUH?
- SIR KAORU,
YOU DO UNDERSTAND
THE SITUATION, CORRECT?
- YEAH.
- EXCELLENT.
LADY AOI IS THE LANDLORD.
I AM THE MANAGER.
AND YOU, SIR KAORU,
AS ONE OF OUR TENANTS HERE--
- PLEASE, I'VE HAD ENOUGH
OF HEARING THAT STORY.
- LADY AOI.
- OH, I'M GONNA BE LATE.
- TAKE CARE ON YOUR WAY
TO SCHOOL, KAORU-SAMA.
- I'LL BE GOING
ON MY WAY THEN.
- HOW RUDE OF HIM.
- WHAT THE HECK?
THERE'S NO FIRST PERIOD
LECTURE TODAY?
- I WOULD HAVE RELAXED
A BIT MORE AT HOME IF I KNEW.
- HANABISHI!
- HUH?
- YO.
- SUZUKI.
WHAT?
YOU'RE CLUB PRESIDENT NOW?
- YEP, I'M PRES,
AND SATO'S VICE-PRES.
- Kaoru: I HAD NO IDEA.
- THAT'S 'CAUSE YOU HAVEN'T
SHOWN UP FOR CLUB STUFF LATELY.
- THAT'S NOT SO TERRIBLE
WHEN THE ONLY OTHER CLUB MEMBERS
BESIDES ME ARE YOU TWO.
- MM.  IS THAT
REALLY TRUE NOW?
- HUH?
- OH-OH.
- ( gasps )
- OOH.
- HEY THERE,
MINAZUKI.
- OH, CHIEF.
GOOD MORNING.
OHH!
- ( gasps )
- ( sighs )
( screams )
- ( crashing )
- IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M TAEKO MINAZUKI,
A SOPHOMORE, AND I JUST JOINED
THE PHOTO CLUB RECENTLY.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT TAKING PHOTOGRAPHS,
BUT I'LL DO MY
VERY BEST TO LEARN.
I PLACE MYSELF
IN YOUR HANDS.
- UH... SAY,
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU,
BUT ARE YOU OKAY?
- YES.  MY BODY HAS
BECOME TOUGHENED
BY THESE SORTS OF THINGS.
- ESPECIALLY SINCE THIS
IS PRETTY MUCH THE NORM,
FOR YOU AT LEAST.
- YEAH.
- OH, IS THAT TRUE?
- LISTEN, MINAZUKI,
WHEN YOU'RE WIPING DOWN
THE PARASOLS,
FOLD UP THE STANDS FIRST.
THAT WAY YOU WON'T
HAVE TO CLIMB LADDERS
TO REACH THEM.
- OH, I SEE.
I NEVER REALIZED.
I'LL DO THAT
FROM NOW ON.
- ( chuckles )
- CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
- SURE.
GO RIGHT AHEAD AND ASK.
- IS DRESSING LIKE THAT
SOME SORT OF HOBBY?
- HEY, WHAT HOBBY HAS PEOPLE
DRESSING LIKE THIS, YOU IDIOT?
- BUT THEN...
WHAT'S IT FOR?
- WELL, THIS IS WHAT
VICE-PRESIDENT SATO--
- Sato: WHOA!
( giggling )
INCREDIBLE!
THREE CHEERS FOR COSPLAY!
- I'M GUESSING THAT
THE PHOTOS ARE DONE,
RIGHT, VICE-CHIEF?
OHH?
- ( screaming )
- UH, EXCUSE ME?
BUT HAVE I DONE
SOMETHING WRONG AGAIN?
- ( camera shutter clicks )
- THIS IS GREAT,
MINAZUKI.
MAGNIFIQUE!
INCROYABLE!
- I GET IT NOW.
TAEKO-CHAN MUST THINK
THAT THIS IS THE FIRST STEP
TO BECOMING A GREAT
PHOTOGRAPHER.
- ( camera shutter clicks )
- SHE DOESN'T REALIZE
THAT SATO'S JUST USING HER,
THE POOR THING.
- WELL, THEY SAY YOU SHOULD
LEARN YOUR SKILLS ON THE FIELD.
SO HE'S NOT REALLY LYING
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
- SURE SOUNDS CONVENIENT.
- A CLUB MEMBER
WHO NEVER TAKES PICTURES
DOESN'T HAVE THE RIGHT
TO SAY THAT.
- AND WHO WAS IT THAT TOLD ME
TO JOIN THE CLUB IN NAME ONLY
BECAUSE IT DIDN'T HAVE
ENOUGH PEOPLE?
- WHO THE HECK
TOLD YOU THAT?
- YOU DID, SUZUKI.
- ANYWAY, I DON'T GET WHY
A GUY WOULD WANT
TO TAKE PICTURES LIKE THAT.
AFTER ALL, REAL MEN ONLY
TAKE PICTURES OF THESE BABIES.
- YEAH.  ONLY IF THEY'RE
TRAIN FREAKS LIKE YOU.
- THERE EXISTS NO BEAUTY
THAT CAN COMPARE TO THAT
OF THE MIGHTY LOCOMOTIVE.
MANLY, NOBLE, COURAGEOUS,
AND SOMETIMES GENTLE.
WHENEVER I THINK OF TRAINS,
I'M ALWAYS MOVED TO
UNCONTROLLABLE TEARS.
( crying )
DO YOU UNDERSTAND,
HANABISHI?
- SUZUKI... THE PHOTOS.
- HUH?
( sobbing )
- ( camera shutter clicks )
- NOW THAT I THINK OF IT,
I WONDER HOW SHE'S DOING.
- HUH?  WHO'S THAT?
- YOU KNOW,
THE OTHER PHOTOGRAPHY CLUB
MEMBER FROM LAST YEAR?
- OH YEAH, HER.
WHO THE HECK KNOWS WHERE
SHE COULD BE TRAVELING.
- I HOPE SHE'S DOING WELL.
- Tina: KAORU!
- HUH?
( gasps )
- ( laughs )
- OW.
- HUH?
- TINA!
- KAORU, I CAME HERE
FROM NARITA
'CAUSE I WANTED TO SEE
MY DARLING KAORU.
- T-TINA.
COME ON, WOULD YOU
GET OFF ME ALREADY?
- HEY, WELL AREN'T YOU
STILL SHY AS EVER.
COME ON, IT'S BEEN
AN ENTIRE YEAR.
- ( stammers )
- OH, THERE'S A NEW MEMBER, HUH?
- I'M TAEKO MINAZUKI.
- AND I'M TINA FOSTER.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
- IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU TOO.
- ( meows )
- I DIDN'T EXPECT YOU
TO BE SUCH A FLUENT SPEAKER.
- I'VE BEEN LIVING IN HAKATA
SINCE I WAS FIVE.
- HAKATA?
OH.  IS THAT THE CASE NOW?
( gasps )
HUH?
TINA, SENPAI?
OH, TINA SENPAI PLEASE!
- WHOA!  YOU SURE
GOT BIG BOOBIES.
YOU'LL MAKE A GREAT
PHOTOGRAPHER.
- SORRY, BUT THAT'S HOW TINA
LIKES TO GREET PEOPLE.
- IS THAT REALLY SO?
- ALL RIGHT, THEN.
IT'S TIME TO CELEBRATE MY RETURN
AND WELCOME OUR NEW MEMBER
WITH AN OLD FASHIONED PARTY.
LET'S HAVE A BLAST!
- SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
- WHAT?  YOU MEAN RIGHT NOW?
BUT IT'S STILL BRIGHT OUT.
- SO WHAT ABOUT THE SIDE DISHES,
LADY AOI?  HUH?
- Aoi: KAORU-SAMA LOVES
THESE SARDINE PATTIES SO MUCH.
I WILL MAKE HIS SLIGHTLY
BIGGER THAN THE OTHERS.
- ( chuckles )
- Tina: SEE?  LOOK,
IT'S THIS PICTURE RIGHT HERE.
- Sato: WOW, COOL!
- Kaoru: WHERE'S THIS?
- Tina: IT'S KENYA.
A HUGE OLD SAVANNAH
THAT WENT ON FOREVER.
AND THE SUNRISE WAS
JUST SO BEAUTIFUL THERE.
IT WAS REALLY BREATHTAKING.
- Kaoru:
WOW. AND THIS?
- Tina:
THAT'S AUSTRALIA!
I COUNTED ON HITCHHIKING
TO GET AROUND,
BUT THERE WERE NO CARS!
I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA DIE.
THIS IS THE AMAZON.
I BROILED SOME PIRANHAS.
THEY WERE PRETTY GOOD EATING.
- AMAZING.  YOU REALLY DID
TRAVEL AROUND THE WHOLE WORLD.
- OH, YEAH.
- BUT WASN'T IT
REALLY DANGEROUS?
YOU WERE ALL BY YOURSELF,
WEREN'T YOU?
- HA!  I WAS TOTALLY FINE
AND PERFECTLY SAFE.
- UH...
LOOK AT THE TIME.
I'VE GOT TO GET GOING SOON.
- OH YEAH.
I GOT SOUVENIRS
FOR Y'ALL.
- WHAT? WHAT KIND OF
SOUVENIRS?
- PHOTOS OF TRAINS
AROUND THE WORLD?
- PHOTOS OF COSPLAY
IDOLS AROUND THE WORLD?
- LIKE I'D HAVE
THAT KIND OF STUFF.
I'VE GOT THIS.
- All: HUH?
- IT'S BOOZE THAT
SOMEONE ALONG MY WAY
WAS NICE ENOUGH
TO GIVE TO ME.
- IS THAT REALLY ALCOHOLIC?
- MAN, THAT'S SOME
QUESTIONABLE LOOKING STUFF.
- AND THAT COLOR
LOOKS LIKE TROUBLE TOO.
- CAN YOU DRINK THAT,
TINA?
- WHAT A RUDE THING TO SAY.
WELL, WHO FIRST?
- UH, I THINK I'LL
PASS ON THIS ONE.
- UH, YEAH, ME TOO.
- AH, WHAT A BUNCH OF WUSSES.
- SHE DID GO THROUGH THE TROUBLE
OF BRINGING THIS BACK FOR US.
I'D BE HONORED TO BE
THE FIRST TO TRY SOME, SENPAI.
- ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
KNOCK IT BACK, GIRL.
- HMM.
- HEY, IF YOU DRINK IT
DOWN LIKE THAT...
- ( sighs )
YES?
- WHAT THE--?
YOU'RE ACTUALLY ALL RIGHT?
- YES.  OF COURSE.
IT WAS VERY GOOD.
- UH, OKAY.
THAT'S COOL THEN.
COME ON, KAORU.
IT'S YOUR TURN.
- UH, I'VE GOT TO GO
MAKE A PHONE CALL FIRST.
I'LL HAVE A GLASS
WHEN I GET BACK, OKAY?
- FINE THEN.  YOU DON'T
HAVE TO FORCE YOURSELF.
AND I BROUGHT THIS
JUST FOR YOU, KAORU.
( crying )
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
I'LL DRINK IT.
YOU'LL BE SATISFIED
ONCE I DO, RIGHT?
( sighs )
- YES!  THERE WE GO.
NOW THAT'S WHAT'S
SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
ISN'T THIS STUFF THE BEST?
YOU SEE WHAT I MEAN?
SUZUKI, SATO,
YOU'RE UP NEXT.
- Suzuki and Sato:
YEAH, RIGHT!
- ( clock ticking )
( clock tolls )
- Aoi: TO THINK THAT HE
HAS NOT RETURNED
WHEN IT IS SO LATE.
PERHAPS SOMETHING AWFUL
HAS HAPPENED TO HIM.
- SIR KAORU HAS HIS GROUP OF
ACQUAINTANCES TO SOCIALIZE WITH.
COME, IT IS BEST THAT WE BEGIN
EATING SUPPER WITHOUT HIM.
- BUT STILL...
KAORU-SAMA.
- ( clock tolls )
- ( moans )
OH, I MUST HAVE
FALLEN ASLEEP LAST NIGHT.
- ( knocks on door )
- KAORU-SAMA?
I'M COMING IN.
OH?
- ( door closes )
- ( sighs )
KAORU-SAMA?
- ( groans )
AOI-CHAN, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- OH, THANK GOODNESS.
WHAT EXACTLY HAPPENED
TO YOU LAST NIGHT?
YOU DIDN'T EVEN CALL.
I WAS VERY WORRIED ABOUT YOU,
I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW.
- LAST NIGHT?
- OH?
- HMM?
IS SOMETHING WRONG,
AOI-CHAN?
- ( moans )
- HUH?
- GOOD MORNING, KAORU.
- OH!
- ( yawns )
- T-TINA?
WHAT IN THE WORLD?
- MMM.
- UH-UH-UH.
WHO IS THIS PERSON?
- HMM?
HEY, KAORU, WHO'S THAT
CUTE GIRL, HUH?
- I-- I AM HIS--
THAT IS, I'M KAORU-SAMA'S--
- Miyabi: LANDLORD.
- MISS MIYABI.
- LANDLORD?
- YES.  THIS IS THE ESTATE'S
LANDLORD, AOI SAKURABA.
AND I AM MIYABI KAGURAZAKI,
THE MANAGER.
YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM
CANNOT BE REVEALED, REMEMBER?
THIS IS TO AVOID A SCANDAL
WITHIN THE FAMILY.
- YES.
I'M THE LANDLORD.
- UH, AOI-CHAN.
- OH, SO YOU'RE
THIS PLACE'S LANDLORD, HUH?
- I'M TINA FOSTER.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
( giggles )
- ( yelps )
- WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU DOING?
- JUST SAYING HELLO,
THAT'S ALL.
YOUR TURN, MISS MANAGER.
( giggles )
AW, CHEAPSKATE.
- IT WAS MISS TINA,
WASN'T IT?
IT APPEARS YOU ARE ONE OF
SIR KAORU'S SCHOOLMATES,
AND ALSO THAT YOU TWO
WERE TOGETHER LAST NIGHT.
- ( sighs )
- LAST NIGHT?
YEAH, WE WERE TOGETHER
FOR THE WHOLE NIGHT!
- ( gasps )
- TINA!
- IF YOU PLEASE!
I WOULD LIKE TO HEAR
THE STORY IN DETAIL.
- SURE.
US PHOTO CLUB GUYS
WERE DRINKING LAST NIGHT.
- AND IT WAS ALL OF US
TOGETHER--
- SILENCE!
- ( stammers )
OKAY.
- CONTINUE.
- AND KAORU WAS OUT COLD
AFTER DRINKING TOO MUCH BOOZE.
MAN, YOU WERE SUCH A WUSS.
RIGHT, KAORU?
- IT WAS ALL BECAUSE OF
THAT MYSTERY BOOZE!
- Tina: SO NOTHING WOULD
WAKE THE BUM UP.
WE BARELY GOT THIS
ADDRESS OUT OF HIM,
AND I WAS NICE ENOUGH
TO BRING HIM HERE.
BUT WHEN I DUMPED HIM
ONTO THE FLOOR,
I STARTED FEELING
THE BOOZE GET TO ME.
SO I GRABBED
THE NEAREST FUTON
AND SLEPT LIKE A LOG.
- OH.
- I SEE.
NOW I KNOW THE CIRCUMSTANCES.
I SUPPOSE THAT NOTHING
COULD HAVE BEEN DONE
TO PREVENT THIS SITUATION.
HOWEVER, SUCH INCIDENCES
MUST NOT EVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
IS THAT UNDERSTOOD?
- YEAH.  I'M SORRY.
- Tina: HEY,
THE NEXT ROOM IS FREE!
COOL.
- All: HUH?
- MISS LANDLORD?
MISS MANAGER?
I JUST GOT BACK,
SO I DON'T HAVE
A PLACE TO STAY.
I'M GONNA LIVE HERE
STARTING TODAY.
- ( gasps )
- Both: HUH?
- CAN'T WE ALL GET ALONG,
MISS LANDLORD?
- NO, NOT AGAIN.
- WE ARE NOT CURRENTLY
LOOKING FOR ANY NEW TENANTS,
UNFORTUNATELY.
- AW, DON'T PLAY HARD TO GET
WITH ME, MISS MANAGER.
- WHEN I SAY NO,
I MEAN NO.
- I GUESS I OUGHT
TO GET GOING THEN.
I'VE GOT NO CHOICE
BUT TO GIVE UP LIVING HERE.
- SIR KAORU.
- UH, YEAH?
- THERE IS NOTHING WRONG
WITH SPENDING TIME
WITH YOUR SCHOOLMATES,
BUT I WOULD BE TROUBLED
IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND
LADY AOI'S FEELINGS.
SHE WAS PATIENTLY AWAITING
YOUR RETURN FOR SUPPER,
SIR KAORU,
AND AS SUCH HAS NOT
EATEN SINCE LAST NIGHT.
- ( gasps )
- ( door opens )
- AOI-CHAN.
- KAORU-SAMA?
- SORRY.
- PLEASE DO NOT APOLOGIZE.
I AM CERTAIN YOU
WOULD NEVER DO SOMETHING
THAT YOU WOULD BE ASHAMED OF.
I BELIEVE IN YOU,
KAORU-SAMA.
- THANKS, AOI-CHAN.
STILL, I'M SORRY.
- Tina: KAORU!
- HUH?
TINA, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING THERE?
- HEY, DON'T WORRY.
I TRAVELED
ALL AROUND THE WORLD,
SO I'M USED TO
THIS KIND OF STUFF.
- THAT ISN'T THE PROBLEM.
- BUT I DON'T HAVE
ANYWHERE ELSE TO GO.
THE FISH IS JUST ABOUT DONE.
SO DO YOU WHAT TO HAVE
SOME BREAKFAST WITH ME?
- WELL, I AM PRETTY HUNGRY.
UH--
NO.
I HAVE TO BE FIRM.
TINA, WE NEED TO TALK.
- SURE.
SO, WHAT IS IT, KAORU?
- TINA, I KNOW YOU DON'T HAVE
A PLACE TO LIVE, BUT SAYING
THAT YOU'RE GONNA LIVE--
- ( meows )
( meows )
- HELLO.
WHO ARE YOU, KITTY?
- TINA, WAIT.
LISTEN TO ME.
- WHERE DID YOU COME FROM?
ARE YOU ONE OF
THE TENANTS HERE, KITTY?
THEN I GUESS I'LL BE ABLE
TO SEE YOU EVERY DAY.
- HEY, I'M NOT DONE
TALKING HERE!
- Tina: AW, KITTY.
( giggles )
AWW.
- ( chuckles )
- TINA!
- WHAT IS IT, KAORU?
DON'T LECTURE ME
SO MUCH, OKAY?
- WOULD YOU CUT THAT OUT,
TINA?
- Tina: DON'T BE SO SHY.
- STOP IT ALREADY,
ALL RIGHT?
- THERE THERE THERE.
AWW.
- ( gasps )
- ( clears throat )
- UH, MISS MIYABI?
- WELL, YOU'RE ENJOYING
YOURSELVES.
- THIS ISN'T WHAT
YOU THINK IT IS.
COME ON, LET GO.
- THEN WHAT, PRAY TELL,
IS GOING ON?
- WELL, TINA WAS COOKING FISH,
AND THEN THE CAT CAME OUT,
AND WE WOUND UP LIKE THIS.
- I UNDERSTAND.
YOU NEEDN'T TROUBLE
YOURSELF WITH THIS.
I WILL DO IT.
JUST STEP ASIDE.
( screams )
- WOW!  YOU GOT BIG BOOBIES TOO,
MISS MANAGER.
- MISS TINA!
- SORRY, SORRY.
- I SWEAR.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
( gasps )
- WOW, AND THEY FEEL
BIG FROM THE FRONT TOO.
HUH?
- ( groans )
- ( chuckles )
- ( shouts )
I WILL NOT!
- IT'S NOT LIKE THEY GOT SMALLER
OR ANYTHING.
- AND WOULD YOU TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY IF THEY DID?
- I SAID I WAS SORRY,
MISS MANAGER!
- ( both sigh )
- COME BACK HERE!
- SO IN HONOR OF ME.
TINA FOSTER,
STARTING A NEW LIFE,
CHEERS!
( gulps )
AHH!
THAT'S GOOD.
- IT IS RATHER LATE
ALREADY,
SO I ASK THAT YOU LEAVE
FIRST THING TOMORROW MORNING.
- LET'S FORGET THAT FOR NOW.
COME ON,
TAKE A NICE LONG CHUG.
- I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO HAVE SOME.
- WHOA. YOU CAN REALLY PUT
THAT STUFF AWAY, MISS MANAGER.
THEN LET ME BRING OUT
MY SECRET STASH.
- YOU STILL HAVE MORE
OF THAT STUFF, TINA?
- Tina: COME ON,
HAVE A DRINK.
- MISS MIYABI, YOU REALLY
SHOULDN'T DRINK THAT STUFF.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I WILL BE
PERFECTLY FINE.
I AM NO STRANGER WHEN IT COMES
TO DRINKING HARD LIQUOR.
- ( thuds )
- ( Tina laughs )
- SEE?  I TOLD YOU SO.
- HEY, MISS LANDLORD,
YOU WANT TO HEAR SOME
INTERESTING STORIES ABOUT KAORU?
- HUH?
- TINA, DON'T YOU DARE
SAY ANOTHER WORD.
- WE WERE CAMPING
IN THE SUMMER.
KAORU WAS DEAD DRUNK
BACK THEN,
AND WHEN I GOT HIM
SOME WATER TO DRINK,
HE SAID THAT HE WANTED IT
MOUTH TO MOUTH.
- ( gasps )
- HEY, QUIT CHANGING THE STORY.
WHAT REALLY HAPPENED WAS YOU
POURED A WHOLE BUCKET
OF WATER ON ME
IN MY SLEEP.
- OH, SO YOU REMEMBERED.
I GUESS IT DIDN'T WORK.
- OH, THAT WAS A LIE
JUST NOW?
- OF COURSE IT WAS,
AOI-CHAN.
- IS THAT SO?
- OH, I REMEMBER ANOTHER STORY.
- DURING OUR WINTER
CAMPING TRIP,
I GOT IN AN OPEN AIR
BATH WITH KAORU.
AND HE GOT A CHANCE TO SEE
EVERY INCH OF MY NAKED BODY.
- EXCEPT IT WAS
A HEATED SWIMMING POOL,
YOU HAD A BATHING SUIT,
AND SATO AND SUZUKI
WERE THERE.
- GIRLS FROM KYUSHU
CAN NEVER GET MARRIED
IF SOMEONE SEES US NAKED.
- AND I'M TELLING YOU,
I NEVER SAW A THING.
AND ANYWAY, FIRST OF ALL,
YOU'RE AN AMERICAN.
- OH, I REMEMBER
DURING THE AUTUMN TRIP.
- ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S ENOUGH.
- WE ALMOST GOT STRANDED.
- I SAID ENOUGH!
- YOU WERE WHINING ABOUT
HOW WE WERE GONNA DIE,
AND IT WAS LIKE
SO ANNOYING.
- WHEN IN THE WORLD
DID THAT EVER HAPPEN?
- ( thuds )
- ( door opens )
- ( sighs )
OH?
KAORU-SAMA?
- AOI-CHAN,
YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I-- I THINK SO.
- YOU SURPRISED US,
DRINKING SO MUCH
THAT YOU PASSED OUT.
- OH.  I APOLOGIZE.
- WOULD YOU LIKE ME
TO BRING YOU SOME WATER?
- NO.  I'M FINE.
UM, WHAT ABOUT
MISS MIYABI AND MISS TINA?
- OH, THEY'RE STILL BACK THERE.
- HEY, HEY!
WHAT DO YOU SAY,
MISS MANAGER?
IT'S OKAY FOR ME
TO LIVE HERE, RIGHT?
- MM-HMM.
( sighs )
- ALL RIGHT.
- MISS TINA...
- HUH?
IS FAMILIAR WITH MANY
DIFFERENT ASPECTS OF YOU
THAT I'M NOT AWARE OF.
- IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
- I APOLOGIZE,
BUT ITS JUST THAT...
I WANT TO KNOW MORE
ABOUT YOU THAN ANYONE.
MUCH MUCH MORE.
BECAUSE I'M NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE YOUR LANDLORD.
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
YOUR FIANCEE.
- AOI-CHAN.
LET'S MAKE MEMORIES.
- HUH?
- WE'LL MAKE LOTS
OF MEMORIES TO SHARE,
STARTING RIGHT NOW.
- KAORU-SAMA?
- RIGHT?
WE WILL, AOI-CHAN.
- YES.
- Tina: KAORU!
- Both: HUH?
- KAORU,
WHERE'D YOU GO?
LET'S DRINK SOME MORE!
KAORU, MISS LANDLORD?
I'M GETTING LONELY HERE
BY MYSELF.
- ( both chuckle )
- WE'VE GOTTEN INTO
A BIG MESS.
- BUT IT SEEMS LIKE
IT WILL BE A LOT OF FUN.
- ( both laugh )
- ( groans )
( howls )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Taeko: OH, MISS AOI,
THAT MAID UNIFORM
THAT YOU GAVE ME--
- Aoi: WHAT IS THE MATTER?
- Taeko: I'M HEARING
SOUNDS OF DOOM FROM
AROUND MY BUST.
- Aoi: AI YORI AOSHI,
"FAMILY TRADITION."
MISS TAEKO,
DO YOU LIKE MILK?
- Taeko: YES.