- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Kaoru: THE ECONOMIC EFFECT
IS A DEFLATION SPIRAL...
I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
HUH?
I GUESS I FELL ASLEEP.
THAT'S NO GOOD.
THE DUE DATE FOR THIS ECONOMICS
REPORT IS COMING UP PRETTY SOON.
( grunts )
- ( clock ticking )
I'M LA-AAAATE!
UH--
HUH?
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT! WHY DIDN'T
ANYBODY WAKE ME UP TODAY?
WHAT THE--?
- OH, TINA-SEMPAI,
GOOD MORNING.
- MORNING, TAE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT'S UP
WITH MISS LANDLORD?
- NO, I DON'T.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER ALL MORNING,
COME TO THINK OF IT.
- ( door opens )
- All: HUH?
- GOOD MORNING.
I'M SORRY, EVERYONE.
I WAS ACTUALLY ON MY WAY...
TO WAKE YOU ALL...
- AOI-CHAN!
- MISS AOI!
- WAKE UP, AOI-CHAN.
AOI-CHAN.
AOI-CHAN!
- WHAT A FEVER.
YOU MUSTN'T PUSH YOURSELF,
SO PLEASE,
GO AND GET SOME BED REST.
- I'M ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS REALLY NOTHING
TO BE CONCERNED ABOUT.
- DON'T BE SO UNREASONABLE.
A HIGH FEVER IS VERY SERIOUS.
- Aoi: I TRULY AM ALL RIGHT.
I THINK IT'S JUST A COLD.
KAORU-SAMA?
THERE'S NO NEED TO BE
WORRIED ABOUT ME.
PLEASE, GO ON AHEAD
TO YOUR CLASSES.
- BUT, AOI-CHAN, I--
- I'M ALL RIGHT, HONESTLY.
MISS TINA, MISS TAEKO,
YOU'LL ALSO BE LATE IF YOU
DON'T LEAVE SOON.
- SIR KAORU, I AGREE WITH LADY
AOI'S SENTIMENTS AS WELL.
I WILL TAKE CARE OF HER
WHILE YOU ALL GO TO SCHOOL.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- AS I SAID, PLEASE DON'T WORRY.
- ( panting )
- Tina: KAORU!
COME ON,
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE!
- OKAY.
I'LL BE RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- HURRY UP, KAORU.
- SORRY, GUYS.
- I APOLOGIZE.
- PLEASE DON'T.
I SHOULD BE THE ONE
APOLOGIZING TO YOU.
AFTER ALL, LADY AOI,
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN MORE
ATTENTIVE IN MY DUTIES
AND NOTICED THE CHANGE
IN YOUR CONDITION EARLIER.
- KAORU-SAMA...
- OH.
- PLEASE DON'T BE
WORRIED ABOUT ME.
I'LL BE ALL RIGHT
HONESTLY, KAORU-SAMA.
- OH.
- ( Mayu chanting )
HA-NA-BI-SHI-SA-MA!
WHY DON'T WE HAVE A NICE QUIET
DINNER, JUST THE TWO OF US?
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- WELL, MAYU-CHAN, TO
TELL THE TRUTH--
- IT LOOKS LIKE TONIGHT
WILL BE A GORGEOUS NIGHT
SO YOU SHOULD
SPEND IT WITH MAYU.
DOESN'T THAT SOUND WONDERFUL,
HANABISHI-SAMA?
- ( growls )
YOU REALLY IRRITATE ME!
KAORU DOESN'T HAVE TIME
TO PLAY WITH YOU, OKAY?
- WHAT IS IT WITH YOU?
YOU'RE BEHAVING MUCH MORE RUDELY
THAN USUAL TODAY.
YOU HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO RIGHT
TO TELL HANABISHI-SAMA
AND I WHAT TO DO
IN OUR PRIVATE TIME.
RIGHT, HANABISHI-SAMA?
- SORRY, MAYU-CHAN.
- OH?
- AOI-CHAN JUST CAUGHT
A COLD RECENTLY.
- WHAT?
MISS AOI IS ILL?
- YOU UNDERSTAND, RIGHT?
- I SUPPOSE.
BUT STILL...
( sighs )
PERHAPS ANOTHER TIME.
- THANKS.
- OH, I SEE NOW!
- HUH?
- THE KEY IS PROPER MIXING
SO THAT'S HOW YOU COOK IT RIGHT.
SAKI EGGNOG IS HARD TO MAKE.
- MAN, I SURE WISH THESE CLASSES
WOULD END ALREADY.
- IT LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE ALL
WORRIED ABOUT AOI-CHAN TOO.
- I'M PERFECTLY ALL RIGHT,
HONESTLY.
- AOI-CHAN.
- ( door opens )
- All: WE'RE BACK!
- WELCOME HOME. I DIDN'T
EXPECT YOU BACK SO SOON.
- Tina: HOW'S MISS LANDLORD
HOLDING UP, MISS MANAGER?
- SHH, LOWER YOUR VOICE,
MISS TINA.
LADY AOI IS CURRENTLY
ASLEEP IN HER ROOM.
- Tae: I GUESS HER FEVER
HASN'T GONE DOWN YET, HUH?
- Tina: THAT'S GOTTA BE HARD
ON MISS LANDLORD.
- ( sighs )
- Kaoru: MISS MIYABI?
- HUH?
UH?
- I UNDERSTAND.
I WILL CONTINUE
LOOKING AFTER LADY AOI
THESE NEXT FEW DAYS
SO I LEAVE THE HOUSEHOLD CHORES
TO YOU THREE.
SIR KAORU,
PLEASE CLEAN THE MANSION.
- SURE THING.
- MISS TINA, THE LAUNDRY.
- I GOT IT COVERED!
- MISS TAEKO,
DINNER PREPARATIONS ARE YOURS.
- YES, MA'AM.
- WELL THEN,
DO YOUR BEST, EVERYONE.
- EASILY SAID.
BUT I STILL HAVE
THIS MUCH LEFT TO DO.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW HARD
AOI-CHAN HAS TO WORK EVERY DAY.
THERE'S LOTS TO DO.
- Tina: HELP ME, KAORU!
- TINA, WHAT'S WRONG?
- ( yelps ) THE WASHING
MACHINE'S OUT OF CONTROL!
IT'S GOT A LIFE OF ITS OWN!
- Kaoru: JEEZ, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
- THE ONLY THING I WAS
TRYING TO DO WAS GET
ALL THE LAUNDRY DONE
LIKE MISS MANAGER ASKED.
AND THAT'S WHEN--
- THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT.
( yelps )
( sighs )
- Tae: DINNER'S READY,
EVERYONE!
- HURRY IT UP ALREADY, TAE.
I'M STARVING OVER HERE.
- OH, SORRY TO KEEP
YOU ALL WAITING.
I FOLLOWED MISS AOI'S LEAD TODAY
AND TRIED MY HAND AT COOKING
JAPANESE FOOD.
THE MAIN COURSE IS
YOUR FAVORITE, SEMPAI--
FISH!
- YEAH.
- HERE YOU GO.
- ( moaning )
- Kaoru: THIS CAN'T BE--
- IT IS!
MACKEREL STEWED IN CHOCOLATE.
( giggles )
- All: CHOCOLATE?
- I FIGURED THAT
SINCE EVERYONE HERE
SEEMED TO LIKE
MISS AOI'S MISO STEW,
I'D TRY TO MAKE MY OWN
VARIATION OF HER RECIPE.
- ( squeaks, sneezes )
- HUH.
- Tina: THIS SURE WAS
A LONG DAY.
WITH THE WAY THIS HOUSE LOOKS,
YOU WOULD THINK WE WERE ALL OUT
SICK OR SOMETHING.
- Tae: IT DOES LOOK THAT WAY.
BUT THIS SHOULD BE NOTHING
IF MISS AOI DID IT ALL HERSELF.
- Kaoru: IT SHOULD
BE NOTHING, HUH?
- ( clock chiming )
- WE'D BETTER JUST
CALL IT A DAY, GUYS.
- I SUPPOSED WE SHOULD.
- Tina: LET'S DO
OUR BEST TOMORROW.
- GOOD NIGHT, SEMPAI.
- ( footsteps )
( door closes )
- Miyabi: THE SAKI EGGNOG
IS FROM MISS TAEKO
AND THE ENERGY DRINKS
ARE FROM MISS TINA.
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
I DID NOT MEAN TO MAKE
YOU ALL WORRY.
- DON'T CONCERN YOURSELF
WITH US.
RIGHT NOW YOUR TOP PRIORITY
IS ONLY TO GET BETTER.
- I KNOW.
BUT STILL I FEEL
RATHER ASHAMED OF MYSELF.
IT'S JUST THE THOUGHT
THAT I AM INTERFERING
WITH KAORU-SAMA'S STUDIES.
I'M USUALLY ALWAYS THINKING
ABOUT WHAT DIFFERENT WAYS
I CAN BE OF HELP TO HIM
IN OUR DAILY LIVES.
BUT AS IT STANDS NOW
I'M JUST A BURDEN.
- LADY AOI.
- ( yawns )
UH?
- Kaoru: GOOD MORNING, MISS
MIYABI.
OH, SIR KAORU, WHAT PROMPTED YOU
TO WAKE UP SO EARLY TODAY?
- ACTUALLY I HAVE THE DAY OFF
SO I WAS THINKING ABOUT DOING
SOME CLEANING.
- THEN YOU MUST
HAVE BEEN THE ONE
WHO PUT NEW FLOWERS IN THE VASE?
- OH THAT?
SURE WAS.
I THOUGHT SEEING SOME PRETTY
FLOWERS IN THE MORNING
WOULD BE A NICE WAY
TO START THE DAY.
EVEN IF I COULDN'T ARRANGE THEM
AS WELL AS AOI-CHAN DOES.
- Tina: KAORU, COME HERE A SEC!
- HUH?
- HURRY UP!
- WELL, I'D BETTER SEE
WHAT TINA WANTS.
SO WE'LL TALK LATER.
- SO SIR KAORU WAS
THE ONE WHO DID THIS.
- IS THIS OKAY?
- Kaoru: YEAH,
THAT WHITE ONE IS FINE.
- ALL RIGHT.
HOW'S THIS ONE?
- THAT'S OUT.
WE'LL WASH THE PRINTS LATER.
- OKAY.
HOW ABOUT THIS?
- OUT TOO.
- I THINK THIS NEEDS
A GOOD CLEANING.
- THAT'S OUT TOO.
- THEN WHAT ABOUT THIS?
- HUH?
- ( screeching )
- HEY, IT'S JUST A JOKE!
COME ON, I'M SORRY, OKAY?
OW!
- ( sighs )
- ( sighs ) I CAN'T BELIEVE
THERE'S STILL THIS MUCH LEFT.
- IF YOU'RE GETTING TIRED,
WHY DON'T YOU GO TAKE A BREAK
FOR A LITTLE BIT.
- I'M FINE.
LET'S TRY TO FINISH THIS UP.
BUT YOU KNOW,
IT'S AMAZING HOW MISS AOI
CLEANED PLACES LIKE THIS
ALL THE TIME BY HERSELF.
- YEAH, IT IS.
I NEVER REALIZED JUST
HOW MUCH WORK IT TOOK.
IT'S ALWAYS SO CLEAN HERE.
- Tina: KAORU!
- ( pants )
I'M DONE WITH ALL THE LAUNDRY.
AND THE WASHING MACHINE
DIDN'T GO CRAZY THIS TIME!
I'M SO PROUD!
- IT'S LIKE I TOLD YOU.
TAKE CARE OF IT
AND IT'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU.
- YEAH, I SORTED THE LAUNDRY
LIKE YOU SAID
AND EVERYTHING WENT
AS SMOOTH AS A PENGUIN GOING
DOWN AN ICE FLOE.
- ALL I HAD TO DO WAS IMAGINE
WHAT AOI-CHAN WOULD
HAVE DONE THERE.
- ALL RIGHT THEN, KAORU, WHAT
DO YOU THINK I SHOULD DO NEXT?
- LET ME THINK NOW...
IF I WAS AOI-CHAN,
I'D GO SHOPPING.
SO I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THE REST HERE,
AND YOU GUYS HANDLE
THE SHOPPING, OKAY?
- Tina: OKAY THEN, I'M GONNA
GRAB EVERY DISCOUNT I SEE
AND GET THINGS WAY CHEAPER
THAN THE LANDLORD.
COME ON, TAE.
- HEY, WAIT FOR ME, TINA-SEMPAI.
- THAT'S MUCH BETTER.
HER FEVER HAS STARTED TO BREAK.
- I THINK THAT'S
ABOUT IT FOR NOW.
- ( knocks )
- COME IN.
- I'M SORRY TO BOTHER YOU
WHILE YOU'RE WORKING.
- I DON'T MIND.
CAN I HELP YOU WITH SOMETHING?
- I'M SORRY IF THIS SOUNDS
LIKE A SELFISH REQUEST.
THE ECONOMICS REPORT I'VE BEEN
WORKING ON IS DUE SOON
AND I CAN'T FIND ANY GOOD
SOURCE MATERIALS.
- SIR KAORU, ARE YOU CERTAIN
THAT YOU ARE ALL RIGHT?
- UH?
- IT MUST BE DIFFICULT
TO DO BOTH YOUR SCHOOLWORK AND
THE HOUSEHOLD CHORES, IS IT NOT?
- I CAN HANDLE THIS MUCH.
I'LL BE OKAY.
- OH.
- LET'S SEE, GLOBALIZATION...
THE EFFECT WHEN LOCAL ECONOMIES
EXPAND TO INCLUDE A CON...
- ( squeaks )
- THANKS FOR WAKING
ME UP, UZUME.
I'M LUCKY YOU'RE HERE
TO HELP OUT.
- ( squeaks )
- OKAY.
- Tae: WE'RE BACK FROM SHOPPING.
- Tina: WE BOUGHT A TON.
- UH. WHAT'S ALL THIS?
DID YOU THREE MAKE THIS?
- YEAH, WE FIGURED
WE COULDN'T GO WRONG
IF WE EACH MADE THE DISHES
WE WERE GOOD AT.
SO WE SPLIT UP
THE COOKING DUTIES.
- Tina: THIS OVER HERE IS
MY OWN SPECIAL STAMINA SOUP!
PERFECT FOR JUMP-STARTING
A TIRED BODY.
- Tae: THE MIXED TEMPURA
IS MINE.
DOESN'T IT LOOK GREAT?
I THINK I DID
A PRETTY GOOD JOB ON IT.
- MINE'S THE STAPLE OF POOR
COLLEGE STUDENTS EVERYWHERE:
A VEGETABLE STIR-FRY
WITH ALL THE ODDS AND ENDS.
- LOOKS LIKE WE DID A GREAT JOB.
LET'S DIG IN BEFORE
IT GETS COLD!
- BY THE WAY...
- All: HUH?
- DID YOU REMEMBER
TO COOK RICE?
- All: UH...
- "FINANCIAL TRANSACTIONS
HAVE BENEFITTED
FROM THE IMPROVEMENTS
IN INFORMATION..."
- Miyabi: REDUCE THE HEAT!
- HUH?
- MISS MIYABI.
- THE HEAT IS MUCH TOO HIGH.
LOWER IT THIS INSTANT!
- OKAY.
- INCREASE IT TO MEDIUM HEAT
WHEN IT BOILS AND
COOK IT THOROUGHLY.
- I WILL.
- BUT IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN,
PREPARING LADY AOI'S PORRIDGE
IS MY RESPONSIBILITY.
- I KNOW. SORRY.
- SIR KAORU?
- HUH?
- DON'T OVEREXERT YOURSELF.
- I APPRECIATE THE CONCERN.
BUT COMPARED TO THE WORK
THAT AOI-CHAN DOES,
THIS IS PRACTICALLY A VACATION.
- WHAT?
- YOU KNOW,
I NEVER REALIZED IT BEFORE,
BUT AOI-CHAN IS ALWAYS
THINKING ABOUT EVERYONE.
ALWAYS SMILING. SHE NEVER EVEN
MAKES A SINGLE SOUR FACE
AS SHE DOES ALL THIS
HARD WORK.
THAT'S OUR AOI-CHAN.
SHE REALLY IS AMAZING.
- SIR KAORU.
- UH?
- WITHOUT GREEN ONION,
JAPANESE PARSLEY AND EGGS,
A DELICIOUS BOWL OF RICE
PORRIDGE IS NOT COMPLETE.
- OH RIGHT!
LET'S SEE.
THAT'S STRANGE.
WHAT THE HECK?
WHERE DID THE EGGS GO?
- THIS IS ALL RIGHT.
- THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
I GUESS I'D BETTER
LET YOU TAKE OVER NOW.
- SIR KAORU?
- YEAH?
- TAKE THIS TO LADY AOI'S ROOM.
- WHAT?
BUT I'M NOT--
- IT'S JUST FOR TODAY.
I ASK THAT YOU STAY BY
LADY AOI'S SIDE.
- MISS MIYABI.
- NOW RUN ALONG.
- O-OKAY.
- PLEASE, TAKE THIS AS WELL.
- WHAT'S THAT FOR?
- YOUR REPORT'S TOPIC
IS MACROECONOMICS,
IS THAT NOT CORRECT?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- THEN YOU WILL FIND THIS BOOK
TO BE A MORE VALUABLE
SOURCE OF INFORMATION.
- YEAH?
THANKS! MISS MIYABI,
YOU'RE A LIFE-SAVER.
- A LIFE-SAVER.
UH.
- ( footsteps )
( thinking )
IT'S SO SMALL.
HER WHOLE BODY IS SO SMALL
AND FRAGILE LOOKING.
YET SHE'S DONE SUCH DEMANDING
CHORES ALL THIS TIME.
AOI-CHAN.
( gasps )
- HMMM.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
AOI-CHAN HAS A HABIT
OF CLINGING TO THINGS
IN HER SLEEP.
DON'T YOU, AOI-CHAN?
- HMM.
- OH.
I'M SORRY.
- HUH? KAORU-SAMA!
- I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD
BE SITTING UP YET, AOI-CHAN.
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
WHAT'S THE MATTER, AOI-CHAN?
- I APOLOGIZE.
I'VE ONLY BEEN A BURDEN
TO YOU LATELY.
BUT BECAUSE I AM YOUR FIANCEE
I SHOULD BE DOING ALL
THAT I CAN DO TO HELP YOU,
SO I PROMISE TO REDOUBLE
MY EFFORTS.
I PROMISE!
- TODAY...
- HUH?
- ...WE TRIED TO DO
WHAT YOU NORMALLY DO
AND IT TOOK
ALL OF US TO DO IT.
NOTHING WENT THE WAY
WE WANTED IT TO.
AND I REALIZED AGAIN
JUST HOW AMAZING YOU ARE.
JUST THINKING THAT SUCH
AN AMAZING WOMAN WAS MY FIANCEE
HONESTLY MADE ME VERY HAPPY.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- I'LL STAY BY YOUR SIDE
FOR THE REST OF THE NIGHT.
SO DON'T YOU WORRY.
- UH?
IS THAT REALLY TRUE?
- IS THERE SOMETHING
YOU'D LIKE ME TO DO?
- UH...
ACTUALLY...
WELL...
WELL, THERE IS ONE THING
THAT YOU COULD DO RIGHT NOW.
PLEASE, I'D LIKE YOU TO HOLD ME.
- I'D BE GLAD TO.
- THIS MAKES ME SO HAPPY,
KAORU-SAMA.
KAORU-SAMA, FOR NOW,
JUST FOR NOW
PLEASE BE MINE AND ONLY MINE.
- WHAT?
COME ON, AOI-CHAN.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN YOURS
AND ONLY YOURS.
- I KNOW YOU'VE BEEN,
BUT THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN.
WHAT I REALLY MEAN IS
I WANT YOU TO BE
THE ONLY ONE FOR ME.
- ( thinking )
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
THAT I'VE SEEN HER WANT
SOMETHING SO MUCH.
NO, THIS ISN'T THE FIRST TIME.
BACK THEN TOO.
- OKAY, THAT'S THE END.
- WHAT?
I WANT TO BE PIGGY-BACKED
SOME MORE.
- THAT'S TOO BAD.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- NO MORE, THAT'S THE END.
- COME ON,
PLEASE, KAORU-SAMA.
- AOI-CHAN HASN'T
CHANGED ONE BIT.
SHE'S STILL THE SAME
AS WHEN WE FIRST MET.
SO DEMANDING,
SUCH A CRYBABY,
BUT SHE ONLY SHOWS
THAT SIDE TO ME.
THAT'S THE REAL AOI-CHAN.
AOI-CHAN?
- YES?
- WHEN YOU GET BETTER,
THERE'S SOMEPLACE I'D LIKE
TO TAKE YOU TO.
- HUH? KAORU-SAMA.
- THAT CAN'T BE!
UH, HOWEVER...
SO THAT'S THE CASE.
YES, I UNDERSTAND.
( sighs )
LADY AOI...
- ( wind gusting )
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Aoi: GOING OUT
MAKES ME SO HAPPY!
- Miyabi: COME, LADY AOI.
LET US GO. GET IN THE CAR.
- HUH?
BUT KAORU-SAMA AND I
ARE GOING OUT.
- I WILL BUY YOU
SOMETHING TO DRINK.
- SARSAPARILLA!
- HUH? WHAT IS THAT?