- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Miyabi: SIR KAORU.
- HUH?
- Miyabi:
DO YOU REMEMBER--
I AM REFERRING TO THE TIME WHEN
YOU AND I FIRST MET EACH OTHER.
- Kaoru: OH, YEAH.
- EVEN BEFORE WE MET,
I TRULY DESPISED YOU,
TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST.
BUT THINGS HAVE CHANGED
SINCE THAT TIME.
AFTER SEEING HOW
LADY AOI HAS BEEN
SINCE SHE MET YOU--
WHAT SHE THOUGHT,
WHAT SHE FELT
AND WHAT SHE LONGED FOR...
I HAVE FINALLY
BEGUN TO UNDERSTAND.
IF THAT TRULY
IS THE CASE NOW,
NO MATTER WHAT MAY
HAPPEN IN THE FUTURE,
I PROMISE I WILL DO
ALL I CAN TO PROTECT YOU.
- Tina: THIS NOTE WAS
POSTED ON KAORU'S DOOR.
- WHAT?  WHY WOULD HE
LEAVE LIKE THAT?
- DO YOU KNOW IF HE HAD
SOMEWHERE ELSE TO BE?
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HOW CAN YOU HAVE NO IDEA?
- WHAT PART OF THAT
DIDN'T YOU GET, HUH?
- DON'T BE IRRESPONSIBLE,
JUST ANSWER THE QUESTION.
- HOW'S THAT IRRESPONSIBLE?
- IT'S IRRESPONSIBLE
SINCE YOU'RE IRRESPONSIBLE.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- OHH.
WOULD YOU STOP
FIGHTING OVER THIS?
- MR. SAIONJI?
- Saionji: HMM.
I DON'T BELIEVE THERE IS
ANY NEED FOR CONCERN,
CONSIDERING THE NOTE.
- IF YOU SAY SO,
BUT MAYU IS STILL CONCERNED.
- WHAT THE HECK'S GOING ON
INSIDE OF KAORU'S HEAD,
LEAVING LIKE THAT?
- OH, ARE YOU TRYING
TO INSINUATE
THAT THIS IS ALL
HANABISHI-SAMA'S FAULT?
- YOU GOT A PROBLEM
WITH THAT OR SOMETHING?
- COME ON,
STOP FIGHTING.
JEEZ, WHERE IN
THE WORLD DID YOU GO?
BIG BROTHER!
- Kaoru: THIS IS--
- Aoi: KAORU-SAMA!
( panting )
( grunts )
KAORU-SAMA.
YOU'RE HERE, KAORU-SAMA.
- I'M RELIEVED.
I THOUGHT THAT SOMETHING
HAD HAPPENED TO YOU.
- ( crying )
- ( clears throat )
- ( both gasp )
- Aoi: MISS MIYABI?
- UH?
- I APOLOGIZE
FOR TROUBLING YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
ALL THAT YOU'VE DONE.
- OF COURSE.
- AOI-CHAN,
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN
WHEN YOU WERE BACK AT HOME?
- EVERYTHING IS FINE.
IT REALLY WAS
NOTHING IMPORTANT.
- HUH?  BUT...
- WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT
FOR US TO TAKE A SHORT WALK?
- GO AHEAD.
I HAVE SOME ERRANDS TO RUN,
SO I WILL NOT BE ABLE
TO ACCOMPANY YOU, UNFORTUNATELY.
- Aoi:
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
SHALL WE, KAORU-SAMA?
- Kaoru: SURE.
- ( giggles )
I HAVE TO SAY THAT TAKING
A LEISURELY WALK WITH YOU
IS ALWAYS ENJOYABLE.
- YEAH, REALLY?
- OH?  KAORU-SAMA,
LOOK THERE.
ADORABLE.
ESPECIALLY WITH ITS CHEEKS
BULGING OUT LIKE THAT.
( giggles )
- ( softly chuckles )
WOW.
THERE WAS A SHRINE BUILT
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE?
- YES.
ACTUALLY,
THERE'S A GOD OF ROMANCE
IF YOU LOOK CLOSELY.
- Kaoru: YOU'RE RIGHT.
ALL THE WISHING PLATES
ARE ABOUT RELATIONSHIPS.
- ( sighs )
DELICIOUS.
- YEAH.
HEY, ISN'T THAT--
- ( giggles )
- THAT TREE.
HEY, AOI-CHAN,
I'VE BEEN AROUND THIS PLACE
BEFORE, HAVEN'T I?
- YES.  IT WAS HERE
THAT YOU AND I SPENT
OUR TIME TOGETHER
AFTER OUR INITIAL MEETING,
KAORU-SAMA.
Aoi:
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
WHEN I FIRST
MET YOU THAT DAY,
I HAVE TO ADMIT I FELT
A LITTLE FRIGHTENED.
THERE WAS NOT A SINGLE TRACE
OF EMOTION ON YOUR FACE.
IT WAS AS IF
YOU LACKED THEM ENTIRELY.
BUT WHEN WE CAME OUT
TO THESE WOODS,
YOU REALLY SURPRISED ME.
- ( Young Kaoru laughs )
- Young Aoi:
WAIT FOR ME, KAORU-SAMA!
COME ON, SLOW DOWN.
- Aoi: THE REAL YOU
WAS A VERY CHEERFUL BOY.
AND SLIGHTLY MISCHIEVOUS.
- ( croaks )
- ( screams )
- ( laughs )
DID I SURPRISE YOU?
- KAORU-SAMA,
YOU'RE A MEANIE.
- ARE YOU OKAY,
AOI-CHAN?
- THAT HURT A LOT.
( crying )
- COME ON, AOI-CHAN.
- HMM?
- Aoi: BUT YOU WERE
A VERY KIND
AND VERY WONDERFUL PERSON.
- ( murmurs )
- WELL, HURRY UP.
- OKAY.
- Kaoru: YOU KNOW,
I THINK I REMEMBER
BEING A LITTLE NERVOUS
WHEN I FIRST MET YOU.
- Aoi: NERVOUS?
- Kaoru: YEAH.
WELL, IT'S BECAUSE
YOUR HAIR WAS SO SHINY,
AND YOU LOOKED SO CUTE.
I THOUGHT YOU LOOKED
JUST LIKE A DOLL.
YOU WERE SUCH
A CUTE GIRL,
SO I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE FUN
TO TRY TO MAKE YOU LAUGH
OR CATCH YOU BY SURPRISE.
- HUH?
IF THAT'S SO...
THAT'S THE REASON
YOU WERE PLAYING
ALL THOSE MEAN
PRANKS ON ME.
- ( chuckles )
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- ( sighs )
- Kaoru: I REALLY HAD
A LOT OF FUN PLAYING HERE.
IT'S ALL STARTING
TO COME BACK.
- YOU CERTAINLY DID.
I REMEMBER THAT YOU WERE
ENJOYING YOURSELF.
- Kaoru: IT'S BECAUSE
THEY HARDLY LET ME PLAY
AT THE HANABISHI HOUSE.
- HEY, KAORU-SAMA!
- ( Aoi chuckles )
THAT'S WHY BACK THEN...
- COME ON.
WAKE UP, OKAY?
- OH.
- WHAT IS IT, AOI-CHAN?
- NOTHING.
PLEASE DON'T PAY
ANY ATTENTION.
- IT'S STILL SO BIG.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I THINK IT WAS
SOMEWHERE AROUND HERE.
OH, HERE IT IS.
I FOUND IT, AOI-CHAN.
- OH, SO YOU DID.
- Young Kaoru:
STAND RIGHT HERE, AOI-CHAN.
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO,
KAORU-SAMA?
- JUST WAIT A MINUTE, OKAY?
- IT'S NOT ANOTHER FROG,
IS IT?
- NOPE.  IT'S THIS.
- WOW.  IT'S SO PRETTY.
LET ME SEE IT.
- SORRY, BUT YOU CAN'T.
JUST HOLD STILL, OKAY?
THIS IS THE GREATEST
TREASURE I HAVE
IN THE WHOLE WORLD.
- OOH.
- YOU'RE THIS LINE,
AOI-CHAN.
AND I'M THIS ONE.
( chuckles )
ALL RIGHT,
LOOK AT THAT.
I'M WAY TALLER THAN YOU.
- WHAT?  I WANT TO
SEE YOU MEASURE US AGAIN.
- NO WAY.
( chuckles )
- PLEASE?
- NO WAY.
- Aoi:
IT WAS AFTER THAT DAY
THAT WE HAD TO
SAY GOOD-BYE.
- Young Aoi: KAORU-SAMA!
- AOI-CHAN.
- KAORU-SAMA, I DON'T
WANT YOU TO GO BACK HOME.
- I'M SORRY.
- IS THIS FINE WITH YOU,
KAORU-SAMA?
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE
TOGETHER WITH ME?
- THAT'S NOT
THE REASON AT ALL.
I REALLY WANTED TO SPEND MORE
TIME WITH YOU TOO, AOI-CHAN.
- THEN WHY DON'T YOU
JUST STAY HERE LONGER?
- I DON'T WANT TO
GO HOME EITHER.
BUT...
AOI-CHAN?
- HUH?
- TAKE THIS.
I'LL LEND IT TO YOU.
- BUT THAT'S YOUR
GREATEST TREASURE
IN THE WHOLE WORLD,
ISN'T IT?
- IT'S OKAY.
JUST GIVE IT BACK TO ME
WHEN WE MEET AGAIN.
OH YEAH,
AND WHEN YOU DO,
WE'LL COMPARE HEIGHTS AGAIN,
AOI-CHAN.
OKAY?
- ( crying )
MM!  ALL RIGHT THEN,
KAORU-SAMA.
- IT'S A PROMISE.
- YEAH.
- THAT KEY WAS
ACTUALLY SOMETHING
THAT I INHERITED
FROM MY MOTHER.
- OH?
- IT WAS THE KEY
TO HER OLD JEWELRY BOX.
BUT THE BOX ITSELF
WAS BURNED UP
ALONG WITH ALL THE OTHER
MEMORIES OF MY MOTHER.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- YEAH?
- I HAVE HELD ONTO THIS
FOR A LONG TIME,
BUT I WILL NOW RETURN
THIS IMPORTANT MEMORY
OF YOUR MOTHER TO YOU
AS PROMISED.
- ( sighs )
THANK YOU.
BECAUSE YOU PROTECTED THAT KEY
ALL THIS TIME, AOI-CHAN,
AT LEAST ONE MEMORY
OF MY MOTHER
HAS MADE IT BACK TO ME.
- KAORU-SAMA.
I'M SO GLAD
THAT I MET YOU,
KAORU-SAMA.
I'M GLAD THAT
THE FIRST PERSON
I EVER FELL IN LOVE WITH
WAS YOU, KAORU-SAMA.
- ME TOO.
- ( car starts )
- Miyabi: "I WILL RETURN
TOMORROW MORNING
TO PICK YOU UP."
- BUT DOESN'T THAT MEAN
WE'RE GONNA...
Kaoru:
UNTIL TOMORROW MORNING...
- Aoi:
WE'RE ALL ALONE.
- Both: YOU KNOW--
- OH, I APOLOGIZE.
- THAT'S OKAY. IT'S NOTHING
YOU NEED TO APOLOGIZE FOR.
- NO, I GUESS IT ISN'T.
- UH, EXCUSE ME,
AOI-CHAN?
- WHAT?  WHAT IS IT?
- WOULD YOU MIND PASSING
THE SOY SAUCE?
- NOT AT ALL.  HERE.
- THANKS.
- ( gasps )
- UH...
- ( giggles )
IT'S A LITTLE FAR,
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
- YEAH, JUST A LITTLE BIT.
- UM, KAORU-SAMA?
- UH?
- WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT
IF I SAT DOWN NEXT TO YOU?
- Kaoru: UH, SURE.
- FOR SOME REASON, THIS FEELS
A LITTLE LIKE A HONEYMOON.
- UHH-- YEAH, KIND OF.
- OH?
- Kaoru:
LIKE A HONEYMOON, HUH?
THAT MEANS...
- KAORU-SAMA?
- ( gasps )
- SAY "AHH."
- WHERE DID THAT COME FROM,
AOI-CHAN?
- OH, I APOLOGIZE.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO BE SO FORWARD.
IT'S JUST,
FROM THE EXPRESSION YOU HAD,
I THOUGHT YOU WOULD
ENJOY IT.
- HOW DID YOU KNOW?
- ( gasps )
- I WAS ACTUALLY
JUST THINKING
HOW I WANTED YOU
TO DO THAT.
- YOU REALLY MEAN IT?
- YEAH.
- WELL THEN, SAY "AHH."
- AHH.
MM!  THAT WAS TASTY.
- Aoi: THEN COULD
THE NEXT ONE BE...
THIS ONE?
- WOW.
YOU'RE RIGHT AGAIN.
AHH.
- ( giggles )
- AOI-CHAN?
- HUH?
- ARE MY FEELINGS REALLY THAT
APPARENT ON MY FACE?
- OH, NO, IT ISN'T LIKE THAT
AT ALL, KAORU-SAMA.
I JUST WATCH YOU A LOT,
SO THAT'S HOW I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE FEELING.
WHAT I LIKE
IS THE EXPRESSION
YOU HAVE WHEN YOU'RE HAPPY,
AND ALSO THE ONE WHEN
YOU'RE DEEP IN THOUGHT.
HOWEVER,
WHAT I LIKE BEST IS
YOUR SMILE, KAORU-SAMA.
- AOI-CHAN.
( yawns )
- DID YOU HAVE
TOO MUCH FOOD TO EAT?
- YEAH.
( sighs )
IT ALL TASTED SO GOOD.
HUH?
KEEP THAT UP AND YOU'LL GET
TIRED OF LOOKING AT ME ONE DAY.
- NOT AT ALL.
I'LL NEVER GET
TIRED OF LOOKING
AT THE FACE OF
THE ONE I LOVE.
- OHH.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
WE SHOULD PROBABLY
TAKE OUR BATHS SOON.
AOI-CHAN,
WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE YOURS FIRST?
- KAORU-SAMA?
- HUH?
- WHY DON'T WE
BATHE TOGETHER?
PARDON ME.
- ( gasps )
- WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT
TO SIT BY YOUR SIDE?
- UH, SURE.
( gulps )
- YOU HAVE QUITE
A LARGE BACK.
THERE'S SO MUCH TO WASH.
- YOU THINK SO?
- ANOTHER ONE OF
MY DREAMS CAME TRUE.
- DREAMS?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO SCRUB YOUR BACK
JUST LIKE THIS,
KAORU-SAMA.
( gasps )
- SORRY.
I KNOW IT'S NOT
A PRETTY SIGHT TO LOOK AT.
IT'S OKAY, AOI-CHAN.
I REALLY DON'T MIND DOING
THIS AT ALL, HONESTLY.
- UM...
- HUH?
- DO THESE
OLD INJURIES STILL...
- WELL, YEAH, SOMETIMES.
BUT IT'S KIND OF STRANGE.
- ( gasps )
- I THINK IT WAS
ABOUT THE TIME
YOU HELPED WIPE MY BACK
IN THE OLD APARTMENT,
BUT SINCE THAT TIME,
THE PAIN'S STARTED TO FADE.
I'M SURE THAT IT'S BECAUSE
YOU'VE BEEN HEALING MY WOUNDS
OVER TIME,
LIKE YOU SAID.
- ( gasps )
- HUH?  AOI-CHAN?
- I...
I HAVE DREAMS,
MANY OF WHICH
HAVE COME TRUE.
I'VE DREAMT OF
PREPARING YOUR DINNER
AND DRAWING YOUR BATH,
ALL THE WHILE WAITING FOR YOU
TO COME HOME FROM WORK.
AND WHEN YOU
FINALLY RETURNED,
I WOULD ALWAYS SAY
"WELCOME BACK."
ON YOUR DAYS OFF,
WE WOULD SIT ON
THE LEDGE TOGETHER
AND SHARE THE PASTRIES
THAT I MADE THAT DAY.
IF YOU WERE TIRED,
I WOULD MASSAGE
YOUR SHOULDERS.
AND IF IT WAS COLD,
I WOULD SIT UNDER
THE HEATED TABLE WITH YOU.
HOWEVER, THE DREAM
I WANTED MOST TO COME TRUE
WAS...
WAS TO BE...
YOUR WIFE, KAORU-SAMA.
KAORU-SAMA!
KAORU-SAMA.
I CAN'T POSSIBLY
IMAGINE ANY LIFE
THAT DOESN'T HAVE YOU.
I BEG YOU,
PLEASE ALLOW ME TO CONTINUE
STAYING BY YOUR SIDE.
I BEG YOU, KAORU-SAMA.
- ( sighs )
WHAT HAPPENED?
- ENGAGED?
- I ARRANGED IT ALL.
HE'S THE SON OF A TRADER
WHO'S DONE WELL IN AMERICA,
AND I APPROVE
OF HIS FAMILY.
I MET HIM THE OTHER DAY.
HE HAD VERY GOOD MANNERS,
AND SEEMED TO BE
A VERY STRONG-WILLED MAN.
I HAVE NO COMPLAINTS
IF HE IS YOUR PARTNER.
YOU WILL BE MEETING HIM SOON.
- ( gasps )
PLEASE, SLOW DOWN
FOR A MOMENT, FATHER.
YOU'VE NEVER MENTIONED THIS
ARRANGED MARRIAGE TO ME BEFORE.
BESIDES WHICH I STILL
HAVE KAORU-SAMA,
AND HE'S ALWAYS BEEN--
- AOI!
IT'S TRUE THAT THIS
ARRANGED MARRIAGE
IS A BENEFICIAL ONE
FOR THE SAKURABA FAMILY.
BUT THAT WAS NOT
MY PRIMARY CONCERN.
YOUR HAPPINESS IS WHAT
WAS IMPORTANT TO ME.
- IF THAT'S TRUE,
IF MY HAPPINESS IS
WHAT'S TRULY IMPORTANT,
LET ME STAY WITH
KAORU-SAMA--
- ENOUGH OF THIS
CHILDISH MAKE-BELIEVE!
HE IS NO LONGER ONE OF
THE HANABISHI HOUSEHOLD.
HE'S MERELY AN ORDINARY BOY
WHO'S LOST THE HANABISHI CROWN.
HE CANNOT POSSIBLY
MAKE YOU HAPPY.
JUST FORGET THAT YOU
EVER KNEW THAT BOY.
I'VE KEPT QUIET
ABOUT THIS FOR SOME TIME,
BUT THAT ENDS TODAY.
ALL RIGHT?
- NO.
I CANNOT DO THIS.
I CAN'T GO THROUGH
WITH THIS.
I WON'T SUBMIT TO
THIS ARRANGEMENT!
- THEN I FORBID YOU
TO LEAVE THIS HOUSE FOR NOW.
- PLEASE, WAIT A MOMENT.
FATHER!
- Miyabi: LADY AOI,
YOU SHOULD AT LEAST
MEET WITH THE OTHER PARTY.
- Aoi: NO.
I WILL NOT SEE HIM.
- PLEASE.  IS THERE NO WAY
TO CONVINCE YOU TO RECONSIDER?
LADY AOI...
- IF I DO
GO THROUGH WITH THIS,
I WILL NO LONGER BE ABLE
TO STAY AT KAORU-SAMA'S SIDE.
AND I WILL BE FORCED
TO MARRY SOMEONE
OTHER THAN THE ONE
I WANT TO MARRY.
HOWEVER...
HOWEVER,
I AM KAORU-SAMA'S WIFE!
- DO YOU INTEND TO FORSAKE
THE SAKURABA NAME, LADY AOI?
THE ONLY THING
THAT ACT WILL ACCOMPLISH
IS TO ANGER THE MASTER.
AND YOU WILL NO
LONGER BE ALLOWED
TO STEP FOOT IN THIS HOUSE.
YOU WILL NO LONGER BE ABLE
TO SEE SIR KAORU EITHER.
- ( gasps )
I UNDERSTAND.
BUT I HAVE ONE REQUEST
BEFORE I DO THIS.
I WANT TO SEE KAORU-SAMA
ONE LAST TIME.
- Kaoru:
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
- I APOLOGIZE,
KAORU-SAMA,
FOR KEEPING THIS QUIET.
I TRULY LOVE YOU
VERY MUCH.
BUT IT SEEMS THAT ALL I AM
EVER CAPABLE OF DOING
IS TROUBLING YOU.
- AOI-CHAN.
- HOWEVER, NOW THAT I'VE
SEEN YOU LIKE THIS, KAORU-SAMA,
I FINALLY UNDERSTAND.
I KNOW NOW THIS IS
THE PLACE WHERE I SHOULD BE.
AFTER ALL, I BELONG
TO YOU AND ONLY YOU.
KAORU-SAMA.
( crying )
I DON'T WANT TO BE
SEPARATED FROM YOU.
- I'LL NEVER LET YOU GO.
- Miyabi: I AM CERTAIN
THAT LADY AOI AND SIR KAORU
MUST HAVE ALREADY
DEPARTED BY NOW.
MY PRINCIPLE DUTY
IS TO PRESERVE
LADY AOI'S HAPPINESS.
THIS IS RIGHT.
I SHOULD BE DOING THIS.
( gasps )
LADY AOI, SIR KAORU?
WHY ARE YOU TWO
STILL DOING HERE?
LADY AOI.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Aoi: THE SKY IS BLUE
AS FAR AS ONE CAN SEE.
IT LINGERS ON
FOREVER AND EVER.
"AI YORI AOSHI:
I WILL ALWAYS
BE BY YOUR SIDE."