- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Tina: THE SEASON IS SUMMER!
SUMMER MEANS BEACHES.
BEACHES MEANS SWIMSUITS!
STAY WITH ME NOW.
FOLLOWING THAT
TRAIN OF THOUGHT,
IT ONLY MAKES SENSE
FOR US GALS
TO HAVE THAT ONE
SPECIAL SWIMSUIT
JUST IN CASE
WE GO TO THE BEACH.
- IS THAT REALLY SO?
- IT'S BEST NOT
TO TAKE HER SERIOUSLY, LADY AOI.
- COME ON, GIRLS! LET'S GO!
- I HOPE THEY HAVE A LOT OF CUTE
SWIMSUITS AT THE STORE.
ISN'T THIS EXCITING,
MISS MIYABI?
- IF I WERE BUYING
A SWIMSUIT, PERHAPS.
- WHAT? YOU MEAN
YOU WON'T BE BUYING ONE?
- Tina: MISS LANDLORD.
WHAT YOU DOING OVER THERE?
- OH, I APOLOGIZE.
- Tina: WHAT THE HECK WERE
YOU DOING, MISS LANDLORD?
- Mayu: ( sighs )
I WONDER WHICH ONE
OF THESE SWIMSUITS
HANABISHI-SAMA
WILL LIKE BEST.
I THINK THIS ONE
LOOKS NICE,
BUT I'M SOMEWHAT PARTIAL
TO THIS ONE TOO.
- Tina: PARDON ME, MA'AM.
- HUH?
- A BEAUTIFUL YOUNG GIRL
SUCH AS YOURSELF
WOULD LOOK MUCH BETTER
IN A SWIMSUIT LIKE THIS ONE.
- WHY THANK YOU.
HANABISHI-SAMA'S HEART
WILL BE MINE WITHOUT A DOUBT
ONCE HE SEES ME
IN THIS SWIMSUIT.
MY, WHAT A WONDERFUL DESIGN.
IT'S SIMPLICITY
SEEMS TO BRING OUT
MY OWN NATURAL BEAUTY
IN SOME WAY.
WAIT?!
WHY I AM I WEARING
A SCHOOL SWIMSUIT?!
- GOOD AFTERNOON, MISS MAYU.
- DID YOU COME HERE TO BUY
A SWIMSUIT, TODAY, TOO?
- HEY, YOU LOOK
GREAT IN THAT.
- ( grumbles )
- JUST LIKE I THOUGHT YOU WOULD.
THAT OUGHT TO BE GOOD ENOUGH
FOR A BRAT LIKE YOU.
- THAT'S ENOUGH! WHY
DON'T YOU STOP INTERFERING?
- HEY, I WAS TRYING
TO HELP YOU OUT
IN CASE YOU
DIDN'T NOTICE!
- WHO SAID YOUR ASSISTANCE
WAS NECESSARY?!
- WELL, PARDON ME FOR GIVING
YOU MY HONEST OPINION.
- EXCUSE ME.
I'M SORRY,
BUT I THINK YOU'RE DISTURBING
OUR OTHER CUSTOMERS.
SO WHY DON'T YOU ALL
GO TO THE CHANGING ROOMS
AND TRY ON SOME SWIMWEAR?
- YEAH, THAT'S WHY WE'RE HERE.
- NO, THANK YOU.
I WON'T BE--
- Both: I'LL TAKE
A LOOK AT WHAT YOU HAVE!
- WELL, HOW'S THIS
FOR A MATURE LOOK?
I'LL BE THE HEROINE
OF THE BEACH IN THIS.
- HOW UTTERLY GAUCHE.
THIS ONE IS MUCH MORE ELEGANT
IN COMPARISON.
EVERY EYE ON THE BEACH
WILL BE ON ME.
- ( both growl )
- THIS ONE'S WAY COOLER.
- BUT NOT NEARLY AS ADORABLE
AS THIS ONE.
- SEXY'S THE WAY TO GO.
- BUT THIS SWIMSUIT
IS OBVIOUSLY THE BEST OF ALL.
- NOT TOO SHABBY, KID.
- MY THOUGHTS EXACTLY.
- Taeko: WHAT?!
THIS IS THE ONLY ONE?!
- YES, I'LL HAVE
TO APOLOGIZE.
BUT PLEASE UNDERSTAND.
CONSIDERING YOUR SIZE...
- ( groans )
I GUESS SO.
- BUT IT DOES LOOK
REALLY GOOD ON YOU.
I ENVY THE LUCKY MAN WHO'LL
BE GOING TO THE BEACH WITH YOU.
- HUH?
- ( both laughing )
- WHY'D I THINK OF HIM?!
WHA-AH-AH-AH!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S NOT
THE CASE AT ALL!
OH, I'M SO EMBARRASSED!
- ( both sigh )
- THE BEACH.
I WISH KAORU-SAMA
AND I COULD ENJOY
SOME TIME ALONE AT ONE.
OH MY!
HUH?
- SUMMER ISN'T SUMMER
WITHOUT BREAKING OPEN
A WATERMELON.
- ( sighs )
HUH?
- Tina: KAORU!
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DON'T I LOOK WAY BETTER
THAN THAT BRAT, HUH?
- MAYU'S UNMISTAKABLY THE ONE
WHO LOOKS THE BEST HERE,
ISN'T THAT RIGHT,
HANABISHI-SAMA?
- EXCUSE ME, WHY AM I
A PART OF THIS.
- WELL, UH... I THINK
ALL THREE OF YOU
LOOK GREAT
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
- Tina: OH, KAORU!
- Mayu: HANABISHI-SAMA!
- Miyabi: OH, I FORGOT TO
MENTION THIS, MISS MINAZUKI,
BUT YOUR GRANDMOTHER
SENT YOU A POSTCARD.
- Taeko: A POSTCARD
FROM GRANDMA?
- I ACTUALLY BOUGHT IT.
I WONDER IF IT'LL
LOOK GOOD ON ME.
- Tina: ( laughing )
- ( gasps )
( screams )
- DID YOU HEAR,
MISS LANDLORD?
THE BEACH! THE BEACH!
- WHAT?
- THE BEACH! ( laughs )
WATER, WAVES, AND SUN!
- MUST SHE BE SO ANNOYING?
- WHAT IS MISS TINA
SO EXCITED ABOUT?
- OH, WELL,
ACTUALLY, AOI-CHAN--
- TAE'S GRANDMA SENT
HER A POSTCARD
THAT'S GOT SOME GREAT NEWS.
- HAVE A LOOK.
- MY, WHAT A BEAUTIFUL PLACE.
- THIS PICTURE
MUST HAVE BEEN TAKEN
SOMEWHERE NEAR
THE BEACH HOUSE
THAT MY GRANDMOTHER RUNS.
- OH, A BEACH HOUSE?
- TAKE A LOOK AT
WHAT MY GRANDMA WROTE.
- Tina: THE BEACH!
THE BEACH!
IT'S THE BEACH!
- HONESTLY, SUCH ENTHUSIASM
FOR SO SIMPLE A JOY...
- LOOK AT YOURSELF
BEFORE OPENING YOUR MOUTH!
YOU'RE MORE EXCITED ABOUT THIS
THAN I AM, GEEZ.
RIGHT, MISS MANAGER?
MISS MANAGER?
- HUH?
OH, YES, THAT'S TRUE,
MISS TINA.
( nervous laugh )
- AREN'T YOU GLAD
WE CAME, AOI-CHAN?
- I AM.  IT'S NICE HERE.
( gasps )
- ( girls giggles )
- ( panting )
HUH?
TAEKO!
- HUH?
- IT REALLY IS YOU.
TAEKO!
- OH, CHIKA-CHAN.
- ( pants )
- OH!
- IT'S BEEN SUCH A LONG TIME
SINCE I'VE SEEN YOU, TAEKO.
I WAS HOPING THAT YOU'D
VISIT US AGAIN THIS YEAR.
- YOU'RE AS LIVELY AS EVER,
AREN'T YOU?
AND IS IT ME
OR HAVE YOU GROWN A BIT?
- I ACTUALLY GREW ALMOST TWO
INCHES TALLER THIS PAST YEAR.
YEAH! HUH?
- WOW, GREAT.
OH, I SHOULD INTRODUCE YOU.
THIS YOUNG LADY HERE IS--
- HER COUSIN,
CHIKA MINAZUKI.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
- NICE TO MEET YOU TOO.
- OH!
THIS GUY'S GOT TO BE
YOUR BOYFRIEND, RIGHT, TAEKO?
- ( waves crash )
- CH-- CH-- CH-- CH--
CHIKI-CHAN!
- KA-- KAORU-SAMA IS--
THAT IS HE AND I ARE--
- NO, IT ISN'T
LIKE THAT AT ALL.
- WHAT THE HECK YOU
TALKING ABOUT, LITTLE MISSY?!
- THE ONLY PERSON THAT
HANABISHI-SAMA'S FOND OF IS ME!
- LOOKS LIKE YOUR BOYFRIEND
SURE IS POPULAR
WITH THE GIRLS, ISN'T HE?
- IT ISN'T LIKE THAT!
- Chika: HEY, TAEKO'S HERE.
- HI, THERE.  IT'S BEEN
A WHILE, GRANDMA.
- OH, I'M GLAD THAT
YOU DECIDED TO VISIT.
YOU'VE BEEN AWAY SO LONG
THAT YOU'RE STARTING
TO LOOK LIKE A FOREIGNER.
- ( screaming )
- I GUESS IT'S TRUE
WHAT THEY SAY
ABOUT GIRLS CHANGING A LOT
WHEN YOU DON'T SEE THEM.
- GRANDMA, I'M OVER HERE.
- I'M JUST KIDDING.
THINGS'LL BE LIVELY THIS YEAR
WITH ALL THESE FRIENDS HERE.
AND WHAT'S THIS?
YOU HAVE YOUR HUSBAND
WITH YOU.
- ( wails ) I CAN'T
TAKE THIS ANYMORE.
- ( bell rings )
- LET'S GO TAKE A DIP.
- HOLD ON!
- HANABISHI-SAMA WILL BE
ENJOYING THE WATER
WITH ME FIRST.
- HERE.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR THE DRINKS.
- TAE-CHAN, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO HELP ME OUT HERE.
GO AND HAVE FUN
WITH YOUR FRIENDS.
- OH, BUT--
- YOU'RE ALL HERE TO
ENJOY YOURSELVES.
SO THAT'S WHAT
YOU SHOULD DO.
- YEAH, GRANDMA'S RIGHT.
SO WHY DON'T WE GO OUT
ONTO THE BEACH AND PLAY?
- OH, WELL, ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO.
- YIPPEE! COME ON.
HURRY UP AND GET CHANGED.
- OKAY, OKAY, DON'T TUG
ON MY ARM SO HARD.
- Tina: WHOOHOO!
ARE YOU HAVING
AS MUCH FUN AS I AM, KAORU?
WELL, ARE YOU?
- ( gargles )
YOU TRYING TO KILL ME?!
- WHOOHOO!
I'M FLYING.
- AWW, I HAVE A CRAMP
IN MY LEG.
I'M IN DESPERATE NEED
OF RESCUE.
- HEY, DON'T WRAP
YOUR LEGS AROUND ME.
- ( moans )
- DON'T THINK I DON'T SEE
WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO PULL HERE!
- NOW, NOW.
- AND WHY ARE YOU TRYING
INTERFERE WITH
MY SUMMER LOVE STORY?
- LOVE STORY?! LOOKS MORE LIKE
A BAD ROMANCE NOVEL TO ME!
- YOU STAY OUT OF THIS.
SUMMER CALLS
FOR A MORE AGGRESSIVE APPROACH.
- THEY SURE ARE FIGHTING
LIKE CATS AND DOGS
OVER YOUR GUY.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE IN THERE
FIGHTING FOR HIM, TAEKO?
- I-- I'M NOT INVOLVED--
- SO YOU'RE JUST GONNA LET THEM
STEAL YOUR BOYFRIEND?
- I TOLD YOU.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
- YEAH, YEAH,
JUST GET IN THERE.
- ( screams )
- ( splashes )
- ( arguing continues )
- KAORU, HELP!
I'M GONNA DIE!
WILL ANYBODY HELP?!
- Chika: I'M REALLY SORRY
ABOUT THAT, TAEKO.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO HELP.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- ( loud arguing continues )
- YOU WANT TO MAKE
SOMETHING OF IT?!
- GET OUT OF MY WAY!
- MAKE ME!
- ( sighs ) I'M HOPELESS.
- Guy #1:
HEY, THERE, CUTIE.
ARE YOU HERE
ALL BY YOURSELF?
- FEEL LIKE HAVING
A LITTLE FUN WITH US?
- OH, UH, ACTUALLY,
I'M HERE, UH...
- WHOA.
- COME ON, BABY.
LET'S DO SOMETHING TOGETHER.
- ( gasps )
UH, I'M NOT REALLY
INTERESTED.
- LOOKS LIKE SHE'S GOT MORE GUYS
HANGING OFF HER AGAIN.
SHE SHOULD JUST LEARN
TO TELL THEM OFF.
I GUESS I HAVE NO CHOICE.
HUH?
- TAEKO-CHAN!
- HMM?
- HEY, TAEKO-CHAN.
- SENPAI.
- I BROUGHT A FRISBEE
ALONG WITH ME, TAEKO-CHAN.
WHY DON'T
WE TOSS IT AROUND?
- Guy #1: DAMN, SHE'S HERE
WITH A GUY.
- WELL, WE JUST HAVE
TO FIND ANOTHER ONE.
- COME ON, LET'S GO PLAY
WITH THE OTHERS.
- SENPAI.
- ( giggles )
- Kaoru: CHIKA-CHAN!
YOU WANT TO TOSS AROUND
THE OLD FRISBEE WITH US?
- SURE!
( laughs )
- LADY AOI.
ARE YOU REALLY SATISFIED
WITH JUST SITTING HERE?
YOU'VE COME TO THE BEACH
WITH SIR KAORU, AFTER ALL.
- ( gasps )
OH, I'M ALL RIGHT, REALLY.
I DIDN'T EVEN
BRING A SWIMSUIT.
- OH, IS THAT SO?
- ( bell rings )
- I LIED TO MISS MIYABI.
BUT IT'S JUST THAT
I'M EMBARRASSED
ABOUT WEARING A BATHING SUIT
IN FRONT OF OTHERS.
- ( grunts )
PLEASE BE PATIENT, LADY AOI.
WE'LL BE ABLE TO ENJOY
SUMMER TOGETHER SOON.
AH!
AHH AHH AHH AHH.
MY SUMMER, WAIT FOR ME!
- I WISH I COULD PLAY LIKE THAT
WITHOUT WORRYING SO MUCH.
RIGHT, UZUME?
- ( bell rings )
- AWW, YOU FELL ASLEEP.
( gasps )
CHIKA-CHAN.
- I SURPRISED YOU, HUH?
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR SPACING OUT LIKE THAT.
HERE YOU GO.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- YOU KNOW,
IT REALLY IS SORRY.
- HUH?
- BEING SO SHY LIKE THAT.
AND NOT BEING ABLE TO SHOW
TRUE FEELINGS WELL.
JUST SEEING THAT MAKES ME
TOTALLY CRAZY.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
SHE HASN'T CHANGED ONE BIT
AT ALL, THAT TAEKO.
- OH, MISS TAEKO.
- SHE'S GOT TO BE
MORE AGGRESSIVE.
IF SHE ISN'T, SHE CAN'T
CATCH THE HEART
OF THE PERSON
SHE REALLY LIKES.
THAT'S WHAT I READ
IN A MAGAZINE.
IN ANY CASE, THE POINT'S TO
KEEP PUSHING FORWARD IN ROMANCE.
- THAT'S TRUE.
- OH, YEAH!
- Aoi:
THE PERSON YOU LIKE...
- DID THAT THING HIT YOU,
AOI-CHAN?
- HERE, KAORU-SAMA.
- THANK A LOT.
SORRY ABOUT THAT,
BUT TINA REALLY PUT
ALL OF HER STRENGTH
INTO THAT LAST THROW.
HEY, AREN'T YOU GOING
TO SWIM, AOI-CHAN?
- WELL, I'M EMBARRASSED
ABOUT BEING SO BARE
IN FRONT OF OTHERS.
- I SEE.
WELL, THAT'S A LITTLE
DISAPPOINTING.
I WAS KIND OF
LOOKING FORWARD
TO SEEING YOU WEAR
A BATHING SUIT.
- ( heartbeats )
- Miyabi: ARE YOU
REALLY SATISFIED?
- KEEP PUSHING FORWARD
IN ROMANCE.
- AH, KAORU-SAMA.
( gasps )
- DON'T RUN OFF, KAORU!
- OUR SWEET AND PASSIONATE
LOVE STORY
IS ONLY JUST BEGINNING,
HANABISHI-SAMA.
- HEY, WOULD YOU
LET ME GO, ALREADY?!
- ( grunts )
I'M NOT LETTING MY SUMMER
SLIP AWAY THAT EASILY!
HUH, HUH?
- ( bell rings )
- HERE, HANABISHI-SAMA.
SAY AHH.
- IT-- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I CAN EAT BY MYSELF.
- COME ON, KAORU!
FORGET ABOUT EATING.
WHY DON'T WE
DRINK SOME MORE?
THE SAKE THEY MAKE AROUND HERE
IS PRETTY GOOD.
- Chika: MORE PLEASE.
- WHAT?
BUT THAT'S
YOUR FOURTH BOWL.
- ( giggles )
FOOD JUST TASTES BETTER
WHEN THERE'S LOTS
OF PEOPLE AROUND.
- TAEKO-CHAN.
- HUH?
- I COULD USE A LITTLE BIT
MORE RICE TOO.
- OH, SURE.
- HANABISHI-SAMA.
- KAORU!
- OKAY, OKAY.
- HERE, SEMPAI.
- THANKS, TAEKO-CHAN.
( gasps )
- I HOPE IT'S ENOUGH.
- COME ON, HE'D GET
A STOMACHACHE
IF HE ATE
THAT MUCH RICE, TAE.
- I'M SORRY.
- IT'S OKAY, TAEKO-CHAN.
I WAS HUNGRY ANYWAY.
- Tina: YOU'RE SUCH
A NICE GUY, KAORU.
- Chika: HEY, TAEKO,
YOU'RE BLUSHING!
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR THE DINNER.
- COULD YOU
GET MORE SAKE?
- ( overlapping chatter )
- I WILL GO TAKE A BATH.
- I WAS KINDA
LOOKING FORWARD
TO SEEING YOU WEAR
A BATHING SUIT.
- WHY IS IT THAT I CANNOT
GATHER ENOUGH COURAGE
TO WEAR A SIMPLE
BATHING SUIT?
MISS MIYABI?
- ARE YOU SATISFIED
WITH THE WAY THINGS ARE?
- IT'S JUST--
IT'S JUST THAT I--
- OH, BY THE WAY,
I'VE HEARD SOME TALK REGARDING
A WONDERFUL SECTION
OF THE BEACH
THAT ONLY THE LOCALS
KNOW ABOUT.
IT'S APPARENTLY VERY ROMANTIC
DURING THE NIGHTTIME.
OH, WELL, IN ANY CASE,
I SUPPOSE THAT'S NEITHER
HERE NOR THERE.
- MISS MIYABI.
- ( clears throat )
BUT PLEASE,
BE ABSOLUTELY SURE
NOT TO RETURN TOO LATE.
- RIGHT.
- ( snores )
- GEEZ, SHE REALLY
HAS TO LEARN
TO STOP PARTYING
UNTIL SHE DROPS.
- ( sneezes, whimpers )
- ( mutters sleepily )
- ( door slides )
- KAORU-SAMA.
- AOI-CHAN?
IS SOMETHING WRONG, AOI-CHAN?
- WELL, ACTUALLY--
- YEAH, WHAT IS IT?
- WELL...
THE BEACH.
- THE BEACH?
- COULD WE GO
TO THE BEACH NOW?
- ( sighs )
OH! OH, THAT HURT.
- YOU HAVE TO GIVE IT
YOUR ALL, TAEKO.
RUSH FORWARD WHEN
YOU'RE IN LOVE.
- GEEZ, WHAT KIND OF DREAM
IS SHE HAVING?
HUH?
THIS IS SENPAI'S SWEATSHIRT.
WHAT IS THIS,
THIS STRANGE FEELING?
- COULD YOU STAY STILL
FOR JUST A SHORT MOMENT?
I WONDER IF I COULD'VE
GOTTEN THE TWO OF US LOST.
- WOW.
IT'S REALLY BEAUTIFUL HERE.
- IT IS.
SAY, KAORU-SAMA.
- YEAH?
- I WOULD LIKE YOU
TO LOOK AT SOMETHING,
JUST FOR A LITTLE WHILE
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
- ( clothes rustle )
- WHAT?
AOI-CHAN!
WAIT, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
- KAORU-SAMA, WELL,
HOW DO YOU THINK I LOOK?
EXCUSE ME?
KAORU-SAMA?
- HUH?
OH, I'M SORRY.
I GUESS I COULDN'T
TAKE MY EYES OFF YOU,
SINCE I-- THAT IS,
SINCE YOU
LOOK EVEN BETTER
IN A SWIMSUIT
THAN I THOUGHT POSSIBLE.
SORRY, MY HEART'S RACING.
I CAN'T PUT IT
INTO WORDS WELL.
- I'M SO HAPPY TO HEAR
YOU LIKE HOW I LOOK
IN THIS, KAORU-SAMA.
THIS AFTERNOON,
WHEN I WAS WATCHING YOU ALL
ENJOYING YOURSELVES,
I HAVE TO ADMIT THAT
I FELT A LITTLE JEALOUS.
BUT I DIDN'T HAVE THE COURAGE
TO JOIN YOU.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME,
KAORU-SAMA.
- SHALL WE SWIM?
COME ON OVER, AOI-CHAN.
- BUT, KAORU-SAMA, YOU DON'T
HAVE YOUR SWIMSUIT.
- I'M FINE IN THIS.
- BUT STILL--
- IT'S OKAY.  COME ON.
- SURE.
( gasps )
- AOI-CHAN!
- ( both laugh )
- I GUESS I WON'T BE NEEDING
THIS T-SHIRT ANYMORE.
- BUT, UM, KAORU-SAMA.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
AS LONG AS YOU'RE
THE ONLY ONE HERE
WHO CAN SEE IT,
I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
- ME TOO.
IT'S ALL RIGHT AS LONG
AS YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO SEES ME LIKE THIS,
KAORU-SAMA.
- AOI-CHAN.
- KAORU-SAMA.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Taeko: THE HAND THAT HELPS ME
THROUGH HARD TIMES
IS SO KIND... TO ME.
SENPAI IS...
"AI YORI AOSHI--
WAVES."
SENPAI, I...