- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- KAORU-SAMA,
PROMISE ME
THAT YOU'LL NEVER
FORGET ABOUT ME.
I HOPE YOU STAY WELL.
- AOI-CHAN.
- KAORU-SAMA. ( cries )
- YOU DON'T HAVE
TO CRY SO MUCH.
YOU'RE COMING BACK TOMORROW.
- THAT'S RIGHT, LADY AOI.
IT'S ONLY A NIGHT'S STAY
AND IT'S FOR A MEMORIAL SERVICE.
- BUT EVEN SO...
- Taeko: YOUR CAR'S HERE.
- COME, LADY AOI, LET'S GO.
- ALL RIGHT.
- WELL THEN, SIR KAORU,
WHILE WE ARE AWAY,
I TRUST YOU TO TAKE CARE
OF THINGS HERE.
YOU MAY USE THE MANSION
AS YOU PLEASE.
- UH, OKAY.
- KAORU-SAMA.
KAORU-SAMA!
- TAKE CARE.
- ( chuckles )
- ( chime rings )
- ( door opens )
- OH, ARE YOU DONE
WITH ALL THE DISHES?
- YUP.
- THANKS FOR THE HARD WORK.
- IS TINA-SENPAI
STILL ASLEEP AT THIS HOUR?
- PROBABLY.
- Taeko: EVEN IF SHE DID
MEET UP WITH OLD FRIENDS
FROM KYUSHU, DRINKING FIVE
LARGE BOTTLES OF SHOCHU
IS A LITTLE MUCH.
- Kaoru: AND I HEAR THAT TINA
DRANK THE LION'S SHARE TOO.
- ( groans ) THE EARTH'S
SPINNING AROUND AT FULL-SPEED.
- YOU THINK
SHE'LL BE ALL RIGHT?
SHOULD I GO IN THERE
AND CHECK ON HER?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT HER.
SHE'LL POP OUT
IN A LITTLE WHILE
AS IF NOTHING HAPPENED
LAST NIGHT.
- I HOPE THAT'S THE CASE.
- ( phone rings )
- OH, THE PHONE.
EXCUSE ME FOR A BIT.
- ( phone rings )
- JUST THINKING
THAT AOI-CHAN
AND MISS MIYABI
AREN'T HERE
MAKES THIS PLACE
SEEM SO HUGE.
- Taeko: WHAT?!
HOLD ON,
THEN DOES THAT MEAN...
WHAT?
IS THAT RIGHT?
YES, I UNDERSTAND.
- ( phone clicks )
- IS SOMETHING GOING ON?
- YES, YOU SEE...
- ALL RIGHT THEN, MINAZUKI!
LET'S GET OUR
BUTTS IN GEAR!
- SUZUKI AND SATO.
- HOW DID YOU
GET HERE SO FAST?
I JUST HUNG UP
A FEW SECONDS AGO.
- HUH?
THEN YOU MEAN
THAT PHONE CALL
WAS FROM YOU GUYS?
- YEAH, IT SURE WAS.
WE CALLED FROM THE FRONT DOOR.
- COME ON, GO CHANGE
INTO THIS, MINAZUKI.
- HUH?
- HURRY UP.
- UH, YES, SIR!
- WHAT WAS IN THAT BAG, SATO?
AND WHAT ARE YOU GUYS UP TO?
- YOUR AVERAGE, EVERYDAY
PHOTO SHOOT , THAT'S ALL.
- YOU'RE HAVING A PHOTO SHOOT?
BUT OF WHAT?
- ( menacing laughter )
OF THIS BABY!
- A-- A TRAIN, HUH?
- YEAH!
CAN YOU BELIEVE A TRAIN
OF THE 165 SERIES
IS RUNNING IN KURASHIKI?
THE MEMORIAL TRAIN SERIES!
IS THERE A GUY
IN THE WORLD
WHO ISN'T EXCITED
OVER THIS NEWS?!
- THERE'S ONE RIGHT HERE.
BUT, SATO, YOU AREN'T
A TRAIN FREAK LIKE SUZUKI,
SO WHY ARE YOU GOING?
- Taeko: UM, VICE CHIEF SATO,
IS THIS ALL RIGHT?
- HUH?
- AWESOME! INCREDIBLE!
SALUTE, MINAZUKI!
- ( whistles )
- HUH? OH, OKAY.
SALUTE!
- HMM, PERFECT.
YOU LOOK RADIANT!
THE ULTIMATE
IDOL PHOTO SHOOT.
COSPLAYING A ONE-DAY
STATION CHIEF!
- A ONE-DAY STATION CHIEF?
- YEAH, GET IT NOW?
I'LL BE TAKING PICTURES
OF THE TRAIN.
AND SATO WILL BE TAKING
PICTURES OF OUR STATION CHIEF
AGAINST THE
TRAIN BACKGROUND.
- TAKING A TRIP YOURSELF
IS BORING.
THIS IS THE PERFECT WAY
TO TAKE COMPANY ALONG WITH YOU.
- COME ON.  ARE YOU REALLY
TAKING TAEKO-CHAN ALONG
FOR SUCH A SILLY REASON?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"SILLY REASON"?!
- WELL, GUESS WE
BETTER BE OFF NOW.
- WE'RE GONNA BE BACK
BY TOMORROW.
- HEY, HOLD ON.
- SENPAI, I'M SORRY.
BUT THIS IS THE FIRST STEP
TO BECOMING
A GOOD PHOTOGRAPHER.
- LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE
USING HER AGAIN.
HUH? THEY'LL BE BACK TOMORROW?
IT'S AN OVERNIGHT THING?
HEY, HOLD ON, GUYS!
THAT WAS QUICK.
- ( thunder crashes )
- WHAT WAS THAT?!
IS THIS A JOKE?
- IT'S TRUE.
MY MEMORY--
MY MEMORY'S STARTING TO FADE!
- IT CAN'T BE!
- AT THIS RATE, I'LL FORGET
ABOUT YOU TOO ONE DAY!
- You can't! I don't want
that to happen, Yoske!
- ( show theme music plays )
- ( clicks )
- I'M SO BORED.
- Tina: GOOD MORNING.
( yawns )
I'M HUNGRY.
HEY, MISS LANDLORD, TAE,
WHERE'S THE FOOD?
- THEY'RE NOT HERE.
- THEY AREN'T? HOW COME?
- AOI-CHAN AND MISS MIYABI
WENT TO A FUNERAL.
AND TAEKO-CHAN WAS FOOLED INTO
A PHOTO SHOOT IN KURASHIKI.
- OH, IS THAT RIGHT?
- THERE'S BREAKFAST FOR YOU.
IT'S IN THE REFRIGERATOR.
- OH, WELL, THEN I GUESS
THAT MEANS
THAT WE'RE ALL ALONE IN THIS
HOUSE TODAY, DOESN'T IT KAORU?
- ( nervous mutters )
COME TO THINK OF IT...
( heartbeats )
( gulps )
( louder heartbeats )
( gasps )
- WE'RE ALL ALONE NOW.
WHAT IS IT, KAORU?
YOUR FACE IS ALL RED,
YOU KNOW?
- UH...
IT-- IT'S NOTHING.
REALLY, TINA.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHAT ARE YOU NERVOUS ABOUT, HUH?
- GEEZ, WHAT AM I THINKING?
THINGS WOULD NEVER
END UP LIKE THAT.
CALM DOWN.  CALM DOWN.
( nervous laughter )
- HUH?
- ( laughs )
DO YOU WANT OUT?
SORRY, BUT IF I LET YOU OUT
JUST LIKE THAT,
MISS MIYABI WILL
GET REALLY MAD AT ME.
- Tina: KAORU! COME HERE A SEC!
- HUH?
- WHAT'S WRONG, TINA?
GIVING UP ON COOKING?
- HEY, NOW THAT WAS A PRETTY
RUDE THING FOR YOU TO SAY.
- WHAT IS IT THEN?
- SORRY, BUT CAN YOU
HELP ME PULL UP MY SLEEVES?
- SLEEVES?
- THEY'RE GONNA GET WET.
COME ON, HURRY.
- YOU'LL HAVE
TO TURN AROUND.
- BUT THEY'RE ABOUT
TO GET WET.
JUST GET BEHIND ME
AND PULL 'EM UP ALREADY.
- FROM BEHIND YOU?
ALL RIGHT.
- ( gasps )
- UH...
- ( heartbeats )
- HEY, HURRY UP.
- OH, UH, SORRY.
- ( giggles )
THANKS A MILLION.
- UH, YOU'RE WELCOME.
- WELL, I'LL MAKE YOU
SOMETHING DELICIOUS, KAORU.
♪ THE THUNDER CLAPS.
THE DEMON ROARS ♪
♪ NOW IS THE TIME... ♪
- TINA SURE SMELLS NICE.
I GOT TO STOP THINKING
THESE THINGS!
- Tina: THANKS FOR WAITING.
- POLLOCK ROAST
SPAGHETTI, HUH?
YOU CAN COOK A LOT BETTER
THAN I EXPECTED.
- OH, THEN I CAN MAKE YOU
SOMETHING CLOSER
TO YOUR EXPECTATIONS.
- ( nervous laugh )
I THINK I'LL HAVE THIS.
- HOW IS IT?
- ( chewing )
HMM, HEY, THIS
IS REALLY DELICIOUS.
- HONESTLY? THAN I GUESS
I'D BETTER CHOW DOWN.
- IF YOU KNOW HOW
TO COOK THIS WELL,
THEN YOU OUGHT TO BE FINE
WHEN YOU'RE LIVING
ON YOUR OWN ONE DAY.
HUH?
- OH, KAORU, DON'T
YOU REALIZE HOW I FEEL?
- UH...
- I-- I REALLY...
- UH, T-- TINA!
- I REALLY THINK
IT'S WAY TOO MUCH OF A PAIN
TO COOK LIKE THIS
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
- UH, I SEE.
- ( laughs )
- TV Announcer: In sports,
the national...
- TINA, THE BATH'S READY.
GO ON IN.
- OKIE DOKIE.
♪ I'M GONNA HAVE A BATH ♪
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
HAPPY, HAPPY BATH!
- ( banging )
- HUH?
- ( wind rushes )
- ( thunder crashes )
- ( doors rattle )
- HUH?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
DON'T YOU WANT TO TAKE A BATH?
- HUH? UM...
( laughs ) YEAH,
I GUESS I'D BETTER GO.
- WHAT'S WITH HER?
- ( thunder crashes )
- ( whimpers, pants )
( laughs )
THERE WE GO.
I GUESS THE BATH'S
ALL MINE TODAY.
- ( thunder crashes )
- ( whimpers )
- SOMEHOW, I JUST CAN'T
RELAX LIKE THIS.
- ( gasps )
( screams )
( screaming continues )
- ( dripping )
- HUH?
- ( drips )
- HMM.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET THINGS
ROLLING WITH A SONG.
♪ THE THUNDER CLAPS ♪
♪ THE DEMON ROARS ♪
♪ NOW IS THE TIME
TO DEFEAT EARTH'S EVIL ♪
( whimpers )
- HUH? I GUESS THE FUSES
MUST HAVE TRIPPED.
THIS ISN'T GOOD.
WHERE ARE THE CIRCUIT BREAKERS?
UH! AAH! OWW.
WHAT NOW?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE
TO BEGIN TO LOOK FOR THEM.
OH YEAH, I WONDER
IF TINA'S ALL RIGHT.
- ( dripping )
- HEY, YOU THERE, TINA?
TINA!
( grunts )
THIS SURE IS DANGEROUS.
HELLO, TINA?
YOU OKAY IN THERE?
ARE YOU THERE, TINA?
OH!
WHAT'S WITH THIS?
TINA?
IF YOU'RE HERE, ANSWER ME.
- KAORU!
- WHOA!
- ( screams )
( cries )
- ( strains )
- I WAS SCARED!
I WAS SO SCARED, KAORU!
( cries )
- T-- TINA!
IS SHE NAKED?!
- ( cries )
- WHA-AH-AH!
HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
NOW, HOLD IT! HOLD IT!
- ( wailing )
- GET OFF OF ME, TINA!
GET OFF ALREADY!
- I DON'T WANT TO!
I'M SCARED.
( cries )
- TINA!
- ( sniffles )
- WELL, IN ANY CASE,
SINCE I DON'T KNOW
WHERE THE CIRCUIT
BREAKERS ARE,
WE CAN'T GET THE POWER
BACK ON FOR TONIGHT.
- ( sniffles )
- I'LL BE ALL RIGHT WITHOUT
THIS CANDLE FOR TONIGHT, TINA.
SO WHY DON'T YOU TAKE IT
WITH YOU AND GET SOME SLEEP?
- ( sniffles, whimpers )
NO!
- BUT WHY NOT?
- I'M SCARED OF THE DARK!
I DON'T WANT TO GO BACK
AND SLEEP ALL BY MYSELF.
- ( metal clangs )
- AAH!
AAAH!
- AH! QUIT IT!
- I'M SLEEPING IN YOUR BED
TONIGHT, KAORU!
- HEY, HOLD ON!
- NO, DON'T LEAVE ME ALONE!
- BUT!
- NO!
( whimpers )
( sighs )
- ( grumbles )
- I FEEL MUCH BETTER NOW.
- ( gasping )
WHAT THE--
NOT HERE?!
I GUESS SHE'S UP ALREADY.
I HUNG ONTO
MY SANITY SOMEHOW.
IT WAS TOUGH LAST TIME
WITH AOI-CHAN TOO.
BUT IT WAS TOUGH IN
A DIFFERENT WAY WITH TINA.
( strains )
( yawns )
I LOST SO MUCH SLEEP.
HUH?
- TOP OF THE MORNING, KAORU.
- G-- GOOD MORNING.
- JUST WAIT A SEC. I'LL
HAVE BREAKFAST READY SOON.
OH.
THANK YOU
FOR LAST NIGHT, KAORU.
- HUH? SURE.
SURE THING.
- ( laughs )
- ( squeaks )
- I WAS THINKING IT AGAIN.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME, AOI-CHAN.
- ( squeaks )
- ( laughs )
I MADE IT FOR YOU AGAIN,
SINCE YOU SAID
THAT YOU LIKED IT.
- OH.  I SEE.
POLLOCK ROAST SPAGHETTI
FOR BREAKFAST?
- WELL, THEN,
LET'S DIG IN.
SO WHAT WAS WRONG?
- THEY SAID THAT SOME WATER
GOT INTO THE ELECTRICAL WIRING.
- OH.
- IT'S A GOOD THING
THAT A FIRE DIDN'T START.
- KAORU.
- HMM?
- LET'S GO TO THE SHRINE LATER.
- THE SHRINE?
- HM-HMM.
- Child: COME ON, MOM,
I'M HUNGRY.
- Kaoru:
HEY, A HYDRANGEA FAIR.
- ( clacks )
- DIRECT HIT!
- ( bell rings )
- HEY, I HIT IT!
DID YOU SEE THAT, KAORU?
I'M A REAL SHARPSHOOTER.
( laughs )
- THERE SURE ARE A LOT
OF THINGS TO BUY HERE.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT IS IT?
- OVER THERE, LET'S GO THERE.
- HUH?
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT
THE DONATION BOX?
- YEAH, I'M GONNA
RING THE BELL.
- THE BELL?
- NO WAY, WE'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO MAKE IT THROUGH THE CROWD.
- AWW! I WANT
TO RING THE BELL!
- IT DOESN'T HAVE
TO BE NOW, DOES IT?
- I WANT TO RING THE BELL!
I WANT TO RING THE BELL!
I WANT TO RING IT!
- WHY DO YOU WANT
TO RING IT SO BAD?
- BECAUSE.
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T SINCE
I WAS A LITTLE KID
WHEN I SHOOK IT TOGETHER
WITH MY MAMA AND PAPA.
- ( clinking )
- AND I REALLY COULDN'T
PRAY BACK THEN
'CAUSE I WAS TOO LITTLE.
THAT'S WHY I WANT TO RING
IT NOW, NO MATTER WHAT.
( strains )
- I KNOW YOU'LL DO
YOUR BEST, TINA.
YOU'RE HERE.
RING THE BELL.
- KAORU.
- WE FINALLY
MADE OUR WAY HERE.
- ( giggles )
- GO ON, TINA.
RING THAT BELL ALL YOU WANT.
- HM-HMM.
- ( bell clinks )
- ( claps )
I WISH THAT--
THAT THE WHOLE WORLD
WAS HAPPY.
- ( sniggers )
- HUH?
DID IS SAY SOMETHING
THAT WAS FUNNY?
( laughing )
NO, NOT REALLY.
( laughs )
- WHAT?
- ( laughing )
- COME ON.  WHAT IS IT?
WHATCHA LAUGHING FOR?
- ( laughing )
- COME ON, KAORU.
- ( continues laughing )
- HEY,
TELL ME WHAT YOU
THINK IS SO FUNNY, KAORU.
BUT I HONESTLY DO!
- WHAT WAS THAT?
( laughing )
- YOU SURE HAVE CHANGED
A LOT, KAORU.
- HUH?
- WHEN WE GOT TO
KNOW EACH OTHER...
HEY, TOP OF THE MORNING!
- HUH?
( deadpanned )
YEAH, GOOD MORNING.
- Present Tina: BACK THEN,
WELL, YOU SEEMED
KIND OF LONELY,
LIKE YOU DIDN'T WANT TO
LET ANYONE INSIDE YOUR HEART.
THAT'S WHY--
WELL, HONESTLY,
THAT'S WHY I INVITED YOU
TO JOIN THE PHOTO CLUB.
- YEAH?
WAS I REALLY LIKE THAT?
- YOU SURE WERE.  HONEST.
I HAVE BEEN WATCHING YOU
THE WHOLE TIME, KAORU,
SO I SHOULD KNOW.
- HUH?
- I THINK IT'S ALL BECAUSE
YOU MOVED IN HERE.
THE LANDLORD AND MANAGER
ARE BOTH GOOD PEOPLE.
THEY'RE THE TYPE OF FOLKS
THAT MAKE YOU FEEL AT EASE.
AND THEY DON'T EVER
LOOK AT ME FUNNY
JUST BECAUSE
I'M AN AMERICAN.
AND WHENEVER
I'M IN TROUBLE,
THEY REALLY WORRY
ABOUT ME.
JUST LIKE--
JUST LIKE WE'RE ALL
A REAL FAMILY.
- FAMILY.
( sad sighs )
- Tina: SHE'S AN AMAZING PERSON.
- HUH?
- THE LANDLORD,
SHE IS REALLY KIND.
AND SHE CAN DO
ALL SORTS OF THINGS.
SO THAT'S-- THAT'S
A TRADITIONAL JAPANESE BEAUTY.
I WONDER WHAT KIND
OF A LIFESTYLE
YOU WOULD NEED
TO END UP LIKE THAT?
( sighs )
I SOMETIMES WISH I COULD
HAVE BEEN BORN
A JAPANESE PERSON
WHO'S LIKE THE LANDLORD.
AND IF I HAD BEEN,
THEN I--
THEN MAYBE
I COULD HAVE...
- HUH? WHAT'S THAT?
- MH-HMM, AWW,
IT WAS NOTHING AT ALL.
( laughs ) WELL,
LET'S DRINK UP, KAORU.
- TINA.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
- YEAH! KNOCK IT BACK!
OH, YEAH.  HEY, UZUME.
YOU SHOULD DRINK SOME TOO!
- HEY, COME ON, DON'T TAKE
UZUME OUT OF THE CAGE.
- AWW, DON'T BE
A PARTY POOPER.
- THE RULES ARE THE RULES!
- PARTY POOPER!
I WON'T LET YOU DRINK
IF YOU KEEP TALKING LIKE THAT.
- HEY, THAT'S MY BEER!
- ( gulping )
- DAMN IT!
- AHH.  YUM.
( laughs )
- ( door opens )
- I'M BACK, EVERYONE.
OH MY GOSH!
( groans )
- ( mutters sleepily )
- OH, WOULD YOU PLEASE
STOP THAT, TINA-SENPAI?
- ( engine runs )
- Aoi: KAORU-SAMA.
WAKE UP, KAORU-SAMA.
- ( groans )
WELCOME BACK, AOI-CHAN.
- YOU WILL ONLY
CATCH YOURSELF A COLD
IF YOU CONTINUE SLEEPING
OUT HERE ON THE COUCH.
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
- NO, NOT REALLY.
DID TINA GO BACK
TO HER ROOM ALREADY?
- Aoi: UM, ALSO...
- HUH? ( gasps )
- M-- MISS MIYABI.
- SIR KAORU.
- YEAH?
- WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS THE MEANING OF THIS?
- TH-- THIS IS...
UZUME?!
- SIR, KAORU,
I DID TELL YOU
THAT YOU COULD USE
THE MANSION AS YOU PLEASED,
BUT I DID NOT SAY
TO LET UZUME WRECK THE HOUSE!
- I DON'T KNOW
A THING ABOUT THIS.
- DON'T PLAY
DUMB WITH ME!
AS YOUR PUNISHMENT,
I WILL HAVE YOU CLEAN
THIS MESS UP!
AND THEN CLEAN
THE ENTIRE HOUSE!
- WHAT? DO YOU MEAN RIGHT NOW?
- IMMEDIATELY!
- NO WAY.
- I'LL BE GLAD TO HELP YOU.
- NO HELP! SO START CLEANING
RIGHT NOW.
- ( sighs )
HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
- STOP STALLING AND BEGIN!
- YES, MA'AM.
- PLEASE LET ME GO.
DON'T MESSAGE THAT.
I BEG YOU!
- ( laughing )
- OH, PLEASE, STOP! SENPAI!
- LET'S DRINK
SOME MORE, KAORU.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Aoi: I MIGHT NOT EVER
BE ABLE TO SEE YOU AGAIN,
KAORU-SAMA.
I'M SO LOST.
"AI YORI AOSHI:
LACE OF LEARNING."
I AM ALWAYS...
( cries )