[hubbub of a crowd]
[JUDGE 25A] Order!
We will now begin the trial of
the defendant, Mister Dandy,
also known as Space Dandy,
who has been charged with
the murder of Guy Reginald.
[PROSECUTOR] Ladies and
Gentlethings of the jury,
at three a.m. Suburbia Standard
Time on the twelfth day
of the thirteenth month,
a heinous crime was
committed with a baseball.
In a fit of brutality,
a nefarious monster
murdered Guy Reginald.
And that monster is Space Dandy.
Well. That's all for now.
[JUDGE 25A] How will you plead
in this case, Mister Dandy?
Seems he's exercising
his right to remain silent.
[PROSECUTOR] The victim was
a Lumetian named Guy Reginald.
Now, when he was discovered,
his skull exhibited
a circular depression matching
that of an ordinary baseball--
a baseball that was
smashed into his head,
causing immediate death!
[PROSECUTOR] After hearing a
scream, the victim's wife, Rose,
rushed into the room to find her
husband lying dead on the floor.
Standing next to the body
was the defendant, Mister Dandy.
A baseball and
mask were also found.
We believe the defendant
hid his face with the mask,
snuck into the room,
and used that ball to
commit this ghastly murder.
[LAWYER] Objection!
The defendant claims
he's an alien hunter.
He was there to
catch Mister Reginald,
not kill the poor creature.
We'll see.
Now, then.
Let's hear the prosecution's
case and star witness.
[PROSECUTOR] Ms. Scarlet,
do you know
the defendant, Mister Dandy?
Yes.
He's a regular at the
alien registration center.
[PROSECUTOR] And would you
please inform the court
of his track record
with registered aliens?
Well, I suppose
it's abnormal for him
to bring in anything
very impressive.
[PROSECUTOR] Then I suppose
the court can suppose
he had no proven track record.
The defendant,
with no credentials
or achievements, was desperate.
So desperate, he'd use
any means necessary
to get that reward money.
A conjecture, sir!
Ms. Scarlet, I have
a question, now.
If a Lumetian were
in fact registered,
how much would
that reward money be?
An alien of the
Lumetian class?
I'd say approximately
a million woolongs.
Thank you. I have
no more questions.
[PROSECUTOR] Mister Meow,
where were you
and what were you doing
at the time of the crime?
I uh--Dandy said to wait.
So, I was at the emergency
exit and didn't see anything.
It's Me#$%.
[PROSECUTOR]
And where did you obtain
the information
about the victim?
[MEOW] Oh, we met a Suburbian
when we were at Boobies,
and they said they could tell us
where to find a
legit Lumetian, so--
[PROSECUTOR] How did the
defendant react to that news?
He was super stoked
because we hadn't made
any money in, like, forever.
Dandy doesn't list
you as a crew member.
His affidavit claims
you're just a cat.
A cat he unsuccessfully
tried to sell to a pet shop.
He chose to keep you on
as a freeloader because
no one else would take you.
[MEOW] What?
He seriously said that?
[PROSECUTOR] The defendant
will do anything for money,
so why should this
incident be any different?
Did you know that
you were working
so closely with
such a violent man?
Uh... Yeah, sure;
I mean, I kinda figured
he'd snap, eventually.
Objection! Leading the
witness, your honor!
[PROSECUTOR] Mister QT,
can you tell the court
where were you at
the time of the crime?
[QT] I was standing
by with the ship,
so I was never
technically at the scene.
Now, regarding
you in his affidavit,
the defendant claims he
was in a thrift shop trying
to buy a robot like that R2D2,
but he accidentally ended up
buying you, a cleaning robot.
[QT] What?
He states here he kept you,
because you were too
much trouble to return.
[QT] Too much trouble?
He said that?
[PROSECUTOR] The truth is,
the defendant has always
used aggressive hunting methods
and creates incredible
damage wherever he goes.
[QT] Yes.
I always thought it
wouldn't be very surprising
if he committed a crime.
So, basically,
you're saying you're not
surprised the defendant's
violent nature led to a murder.
Speculation. This is
all circumstantial!
[LAWYER] Mrs. Rose Reginald.
You have stated for the
record that you heard
your husband scream as
you were arriving home.
That's right.
I hurried to the
door and rushed in,
but I was too late to help him.
And prior to
this fateful night,
did you know your groom,
Mister Guy Reginald,
was a rare Lumetian alien?
[ROSE] No.
Is that right?
So you had no idea that
if you turned him in you'd
receive a hefty reward?
Objection!
That question is not
relevant to the current case.
[JUDGE 25A] Objection sustained.
Now, let's get back to
the murder in question.
Did he have a large
depression on his head?
[ROSE] Yes, and
there was a ball lying
on the floor by his feet.
A ball.
Exhibit A, the murder weapon.
[MEOW] "Checking in
at the courthouse."
[QT] Why do you think Dandy
hasn't said anything so far?
[PROSECUTOR] This is the
ball from the crime scene.
Now, do you own
this baseball, Rose?
[ROSE] No.
It wasn't mine, and
Guy never played baseball.
Your Honor, look!
There's a name written on here.
[PROSECUTOR] Indeed, there is.
In that case, Your Honor,
I would like to call a
new witness to the stand.
[PROSECUTOR] Are you Mister
Hiroshi, from Planet Turbo?
Yes, sir.
[PROSECUTOR] Do you
recognize this ball, son?
Uh. Yes.
It belongs to me, sir.
[PROSECUTOR] And do you
recognize the defendant?
No, not at all.
Now, tell the truth, son.
Have you ever been
to Planet Suburbia?
No, sir.
At what point
did you notice
you were missing
your ball?
Well, I was playing
baseball with Jack
in our neighborhood's
vacant lot,
and jeepers, it just
flat-out disappeared.
Thank you, son.
I think we should have
his friend testify, too.
[PROSECUTOR] Mister Skipjack,
are you Mister Hiroshi's friend?
Yeah.
[PROSECUTOR] And do you
recognize this ball as well?
Yeah, that's the
ball we used to play with.
[cell phone beeping]
Sorry; got a text.
It has been proven
that this ball
is without a doubt the property
of young Mister Hiroshi.
The ball disappeared,
and stealing hardly seems
out of character
for the defendant.
Prosecution rests.
[MEOW] Hiroshi. Huh...
[MEOW] Look, it's
Hiroshi's Chwitter.
[LAWYER] However.
Was it necessary
for Mister Dandy
to steal the
murder weapon at all?
It was on Planet Turbo,
far away from Suburbia.
Now do you mean to try
and lay the guilt on those
youngsters, councilor?
Not in the least,
it just seems illogical
to travel five thousand parsecs
to steal an average ball.
Why he stole
it is unimportant,
what matters are the facts,
and the facts are
the defendant used
that ball to kill
Mister Reginald!
Objection!
You can't claim he used
it without evidence.
We have to first
prove your theory, sir!
It isn't responding.
Interesting.
There should at
least be traces of DNA.
Are you saying
there is no response
from the murder weapon?
No, sir.
The problem here is
we're not getting any traces
of DNA from
Mister Dandy himself.
[JUDGE 25B] You must be
getting traces of something.
Your honor,
what I am detecting
from both the defendant
and the murder weapon
are trace amounts
of Pyonium.
His DNA doesn't matter;
this proves he was
in contact with the ball.
"Pyonium," you say?
Please explain to the court:
What is this substance?
[LAWYER] Professor Duran,
you specialize
in Pyonium research, do you not?
[DURAN] I do.
Professor, will
you explain Pyonium
to the best of
your abilities?
"Pyonium" is
the common name
for the particle known
as M.E.G.A Pyonium.
It is a recently
discovered particle,
so we do not yet fully
understand its true nature.
However, we believe
that this particle is able
to bend time and space in
order to cross dimensions,
and potentially holds
a vast amount of energy.
[LAWYER]
Time and space, you say?
[DURAN] That is correct.
That unique quality
is the reason scientists
like myself refer to
it as the "god particle."
And would it be accurate
to say this particle
is particularly rare?
[DURAN] Very rare, sir.
So if such a rare particle
had been detected
on both the defendant
and the ball--well then.
I think the answer is clear.
Objection! Your Honor.
I'd like to introduce
a new piece of evidence.
These are the documents for the
victim's life insurance policy.
The payment in
the event of his death
is far greater than the
registration center's reward.
Fifty million woolongs!
What?
I would like to call a previous
witness back to the stand.
Rose Reginald, who
conveniently found the body.
Rose Reginald, you
are the beneficiary
of Guy Reginald's life
insurance policy, are you not?
[ROSE] I am.
Eh, yes, of course.
Then, you must also
have known how much
you would receive in
the event of his death.
The truth is, Rose, you
were struggling with money.
Your husband was jobless,
leaving you the sole
earner for your family.
He was a kept man and
you despised him for it!
Furthermore, I have
documents here
from the Internet
store known as Tamazon.
Based on these receipts,
you recently purchased
the following items.
Brass knuckles, a sabre,
and a folding chair.
Answer me this:
what need would a waitress
at Boobies have for
these kinds of items?
What's wrong, Rose?
Thorn got your tongue?
[LAWYER] Ms. Honey.
You work at Boobies
with Rose Reginald, correct?
Yeah.
Were you aware
that Rose was married?
[Not really.
She took the late-night shifts,
so I figured she
either needed the money
or didn't have anyone
to go home to.
On the day of
the incident,
did the defendant, Dandy,
visit your restaurant?
Uh-huh.
I think he bought
like a cup of coffee
and then stayed
for five hours.
Ah. Your Honor, I'd
like your permission
to examine the security
camera footage from Boobies.
If the two came
into contact there,
that opens up a whole new can
of worms I hadn't counted on.
Indeed. It's a tale
as old as time:
A greedy wife and
her alien hunter lover
committing insurance fraud.
[SCARLET] Don't tell me. Dandy?
Blinded by the wiles of a woman?
We're talking
about boobies,
so I wouldn't put it past him.
[QT] Yeah, me neither;
he's always saying his whole
reason for living is Boobies.
[JUDGE 25A] Well, let's
examine the video footage.
[PROSECUTOR] I see.
So you were acquainted with
the defendant, Mister Dandy.
It's not like that.
He's a customer.
Listen, I was just doing my job!
Come on, tell
them the truth, Dandy!
Why aren't you saying anything?
You're making
everyone suspicious!
[JUDGE 25A] I must ask
the witness to calm down.
You were after that
insurance money,
so you bought various
weapons to kill him
and met Dandy at Boobies,
then you hired him
to kill your husband,
isn't that correct?
You're guilty, too!
Dandy's an alien hunter,
so if he were caught,
he'd be charged with
professional negligence,
which carries a
lighter sentence.
You're wrong!
I swear it wasn't me!
I didn't kill my husband!
Please, I didn't do it!
You have to believe me;
I loved him!
I'd never hurt him! Let me g--!
However, there's still
one thing bothering me.
Why was that darn ball stolen
from such a faraway planet?
Good question.
[DURAN] Your Honor!
[JUDGE 25A] Go ahead, Professor.
Yes, thank you.
This could be helpful.
Pyonium may respond to
strong emotional fluctuations.
If so, it can turn the emotion
in question into a reality.
How 'bout you take
the shine off it for me.
The Pyonium
could have reacted
to someone's intent to kill.
If killing intent came
from Planet Turbo,
well that emotion could
bend space, causing the ball
to cross dimensions
to fulfill the killing intent.
[LAWYER] Can intent
to kill be that powerful?
[DURAN] So powerful
that the killing intent
wasn't even necessarily directed
at the victim in this case.
[PROSECUTOR] That explains
why Pyonium was found
on the murder weapon,
but why would it
be on Mister Dandy?
[JUDGE 25A]
A question for the jury.
Now that arguments
have been presented,
we'll proceed to the next phase.
[JUDGE 25A]
Does the defendant have
anything at all
to say at this time?
[JUDGE 25A] It appears
the answer is "no."
Now we will have you,
members of the jury,
take a hard look at
the facts in this case
and decide the
application of the law.
We are adjourned!
[MEOW] I'm posting that
he's totally getting
the death penalty.
It's weird.
I can't figure out
why he hasn't said a
word in his defense.
[QT] Maybe he's just
accepted his guilt.
Hey, you guys.
Check out this account.
[JUROR RUTO] Well then,
might as well get started.
Remember, we've got to
reach a unanimous verdict.
[JUROR CUMIN] I've never
saw a guiltier man in my life.
I agree.
Hey, boy, we're talking
about life and death here!
[JUROR BRUTELY] Have I seen
this mark somewhere before?
Do you think his
wife had him killed
for that insurance money?
I agree.
[JUROR DAMAUN] Maybe Rose's
intent to kill was so strong
that the Pyonium caused the ball
to move through space and time.
Where do I know that
mark from? Oh, man.
know I've seen
it somewhere.
Creepy!
Bah. This here's a
court of law, boy!
Whatever, grandpa.
Kids these days.
Hold on; what's this?
I dunno.
It's not mine, it's the
chwitter of that witness boy.
[JUROR BRUTELY]
Oh, I remember now!
It's the bruise he got
from that 16-giga kick!
[JUDGE 25A] A verdict has
been reached in the case
of the murder of
Mister Guy Reginald.
The jury agrees unanimously
this was a case of murder.
The murder weapon traveled
through space from Planet Turbo.
This bending of space
and time was the result
of Pyonium reacting to
a strong, murderous intent.
[JUDGE 25A] The main focus
of this case is intent.
Who did that strong
emotion come from?
Chwitter might hold that answer.
Specifically the
account of Hiroshi,
the owner of the
murderous baseball.
His Chwitter posts
indicate he had that intent.
What? Chwitter?
How is that a verdict?
[JACK] Say, hold on a minute!
You shucksters are
making it sound like
we were the ones who
wanted to kill somebody!
[HIROSHI] Can it, will ya?
Now, here are some
of the Chwitter
posts in question.
Kill, kill, kill.
I'll murder him.
Murder-death-kill-obliteration,
and things of this
murder-death-kill nature.
On the day of the
incident, there's a post
that reads as follows:
"I am going to
go kill you now
with the Giacobinid
batting form. LOL."
[JUDGE 25A] For those of you who
don't understand the reference,
the Giacobinid batting form
is where a bat is scored
so it breaks into pieces
when it hits the ball,
sending those pieces toward
the pitcher and killing him.
Let's do this, Hiroshi!
Here it comes! Eat this!
[DURAN] I see.
That's where the strong
killing intent resonated
with the Pyonium,
crossing through space and
turning that ordinary baseball
into a disappearing
miracle murder ball.
I don't understand.
Why? What did I do?
[HIROSHI] Like you don't know.
You blocked me
from your Chwitter!
You were supposed
to be my friend!
When I joined, I couldn't
wait to follow you!
But when I tried, I found
out you'd already blocked me!
What kind of friend
pulls that stunt?
But you're not a friend at all;
and you never were, you liar!
I hate you! You dip stick.
You were just pretending
to be my friend, huh?
I bet you were really talking
trash about me behind my back.
I didn't do anything to you!
And you blocked me! Why?
You were supposed
to be my friend!
One more thing.
I think it's my responsibility
to clear Rose
Reginald's good name.
I have a theory regarding
the weapons you purchased.
You actually bought those items
for your husband,
didn't you, dear?
[JUDGE 25A] The mask
at the scene didn't
belong to the murderer.
It belonged to none other
than the victim himself.
That's not all.
I've seen that foot mark
on your husband's chest
at the Spacer Hall match in '83.
I remember that fight well.
I'm sure everyone does.
That's when he took the 16-giga
kick in the famous Barba match.
Don't tell me.
That was him? Really?
That's right.
Rose's husband was a
famous masked wrestler.
Guy Reginald was "The
Messenger from Hell" himself.
The Dustroyer.
[JUDGE 25A] He was the
greatest wrestler of his time,
but his talent was
squandered by the league.
He lost his career
and fell into despair.
You believed in him
and wanted him
to have another try at it,
only this time as a villain.
So you bought those weapons
as a birthday gift, didn't you?
But you knew he'd
roll over in his grave
if you revealed his identity,
and that's why you refused
to explain those receipts,
isn't that right?
Yes.
What?
[JUDGE 25A] Order in the court!
I have received some
unexpected news.
It seems Mister Reginald has
regained consciousness.
Apparently, he suffers
from sleep apnea,
and slumbers for
long periods of time.
And being that
he's such a rare alien,
the coroner misdiagnosed
Mister Reginald as deceased,
when in fact,
now that he's awake,
it is clear he is very much not.
So he's alive?
Well, raise my rent.
Then, what was the
point of this entire trial?
[yawns]
Tha'wassa good nap. Huh?
[DURAN]
One thing still troubles me.
Why did the ball
travel 5,000 parsecs
and appear at Dandy's location?
That would require an
exceptionally strong
attractive force.
It suggests and even more
intense concentration of Pyonium
was there to pull the ball
through dimensions.
Puzzling.
Wouldn't you agree, sir?
Given that your DNA scan of that
man failed to turn up anything.
[DURAN]
Wait... Don't tell me...
Could it really be...?
[QT] There's no way.
I can believe anyone
could sleep that long.
That's just ridiculous.
Uhm...
What's that about?
Huh?
♪
[DANDY]
We made it.
The big finale to our
crazy space adventures
in space is just
an episode away.
I hope you enjoyed the ride.
Next time, "Never
ending Dandy, Baby"
Catch ya on
the flip side.
[ALL] Bye!