Yeah, buddy!
[QT] Nope, doesn't count.
I'll explain it again.
The hook has to
be inside the mouth.
That's how fishing works.
[DANDY] Now you're being
picky for no good reason.
[QT] I'm being accurate.
Besides, there's
nothing impressive
about catching a carp.
[DANDY] You're sucking all
the fun out of this, dude.
[MEOW]
Guys.
If we're gonna spend
all this time fishing,
let's try for a
more lucrative catch.
Something like this, maybe.
Huh?
A mysterious fish straight
out of ancient legend.
Found on the world
Kayu; the Munagi.
[DANDY] Munagi, huh?
[MEOW] Apparently
it's mega-rare,
appearing only once every
thirty-six hundred years.
Sounds a little
fishy to me.
[QT] Hey! It must be true.
It's on the wanted list
at the Registration Center.
If we catch it, we'll net
fifty million woolongs!
No way!
Then what are we doing out
here fishing for guppies?
Let's go catch us
a Munagi, baby!
[NARRATOR] And so, Dandy and
company headed to Planet Kayu,
excited about a
profitable day of fishing.
Unfortunately, they were
immediately caught
in a bed of space kelp.
[DANDY] Seriously?
[QT]
Uh. This doesn't look good.
It'll be a while
before we can move.
[MEOW]
Eh?
[DANDY]
Alrighty, then.
I'll have to handle
this on my own.
Whoa! Oh! Uh!
Hey! What in the-- ew.
Oh! Oh no! Oh no! Ohhhh!!
[DANDY]
Ow, ow, ow!
[ERSSIME] Wow!
It's a mudworlder!
Huh?
[ERSSIME] Ha!
Your headpiece is weird.
[chuckles]
Wanna be friends?
Wha--?
[ERSSIME] We're best
friends now, okay?
Yeah, sure. Whatever
you want. We're BFFs.
So, pal, you ever heard of
a rare fish called a Munagi?
[ERSSIME] Sure,
I know the Munagi!
Yeah? You do? Really?
[ERSSIME] This way! This way!
Whoa, hold on!
Wait for me!
[ERSSIME] Here we are!
Where?
[ERSSIME] See that house?
[DANDY] Oh. You live there ?
[ERSSIME] I'm home!
That's not her face. Hm.
L'delise! I brought a
friend over to visit!
Uh. The name's
Space Dandy.
It's nice to
meetcha.
Uhh...
This is L'delise.
He's a great fisherman.
[DANDY] That should
work out well, then.
Here's the deal.
I'm lookin' to catch this
special fish called the Munagi.
Do you know
anything about it?
Where to find it,
or what bait to use?
Really anything will help.
[L'DELISE] Go away.
Why? What'd I
ever do to you?
[ERSSIME] Dandy!
Let's get moving!
We've got a Munagi to catch!
Yeah! Old geezer.
That is one grouchy man.
[ERSSIME] Munagi!
Munagi! Munagi! Munagi!
Where should we look?
[DANDY] Wait. What'd you say?
I thought you knew all
about these fancy fish.
I do!
[DANDY] We haven't
gotten a single bite.
Are you sure there are
fish living in this sludge?
It looks pretty gross.
[ERSSIME] I'll go in and--
Aw, man.
Hope she didn't drown.
What is that thing?
There's lots and lots
of fish down there.
Hey, now.
You got moves, baby.
Uh, right.
I'm gonna take a wild guess
and say this guy isn't
a Munagi, though, is he?
[ERSSIME] Bye-bye, Dandy!
Let's play again later, 'kay?
[DANDY] Yeah. We'll catch us
a Munagi tomorrow, Erssime.
[snoring]
It's freakin'
freezing out here!
A little late-night
stargazing?
[DANDY] Enjoy, gramps.
Everywhere I go nothing
but mud, mud, and more mud.
Are there really any of
those Munagi around here?
[DANDY] I know that
bird from somewhere.
[DANDY] Huh? Great.
Captain Crotchety.
Huh?! Whoa!!
Hm?
[L'DELISE] That idiot.
That was almost
the end of Dandy.
Thanks. You saved my bacon.
I didn't save you
because you deserve it.
[L'DELISE] Long ago,
a great many fools
like you came here hoping
to catch the Munagi.
They all met the same fate.
They offended
the Munagi and died.
I don't like you, maggot.
Stay out of my way.
Hey!
Come back here!
I'm not leaving.
You hear me, ya old geezer?
Not until
I catch me a Munagi!
[sneeze]
How are we supposed
to find a Munagi, then?
It won't be easy!
The legend says it
lives someplace real deep
beneath the surface and doesn't
ever take any bait at all!
Yeah, really?
That doesn't say much for
our chances of catching one.
[ERSSIME] There's more, though.
It doesn't happen
often, not at all!
But when there's a blue moon,
the Munagi will actually
swim up to the surface!
That's what the
legend says, anyway.
And it goes back
for, like, ever.
That's the thing
about legends.
They can be a
little off sometimes.
L'delise hunted the
Munagi for a long time, too.
Mean geezer dude? Really?
[ERSSIME] He loves to fish,
and he's real good at it!
Erssime wants to grow up
and be as good a fisherman
as L'delise someday!
Well, don't sweat it, kid.
I think you'll make
a great fisherman!
If memory serves,
it looked something like this.
[VILLAGER 18A] Hey! Check
your line. You've got a bite!
And here we go!
Looks like a big one!
Maybe you finally caught
the legendary fish! Eh?
How long now until
the blue moon comes out
and the Munagi
make an appearance?
Aw, poor sap.
Those two totally have him
convinced, don't they?
Yeah. For starters, this planet
doesn't even have a moon!
[DANDY] But-- but what
about that old legend?
L'delise is the only
person on this world
who puts any stock
in that old story.
Nobody ever goes near him.
He's always in a bad mood,
and he's a pretty creepy guy.
Now that you mention it,
he is a weird old coot.
[VILLAGER 18A]
Well, see you later!
Hope the fish keep on
biting for you, stranger!
Were they just
messing with me?
[MEOW] So nothing but total
radio silence from Dandy, huh?
[QT] No, he hasn't tried
to contact us at all.
Granted, this happens a lot,
but I still hope he's okay.
Huh? Isn't this--
[QT] Yeah, it is.
That's not good!
[chuckling female voice]
[bubbly gasp]
[gargled screams]
[muffled screams]
Aaah! Stop!
I can't find L'delise!
Eh?
[ERSSIME] What do we do?
I'm worried.
Do you think he might've
gone Munagi fishing?
Yeah. I don't
know about that.
I'm not seeing that blue moon
the legend mentioned,
and it looks like
a storm's coming.
And, of course,
as an added bonus,
Munagi probably
aren't even real.
They're real! Erssime
believes L'delise!
Uh, yeah.
I'm serious! L'delise
would never tell a lie!
How 'bout you, Dandy?
I know when I'm beat.
All right, kid. Let's see
if we can find him.
[laughter]
Huh?
[DANDY] That bird again.
If we follow it, it might
lead us to the old man.
[DANDY] All right!
Let's get moving!
[QT] Yep, that's
the Rubini Comet.
It only comes around once
every thirty-six-hundred years.
It's getting closer,
which is not good for us.
I picked up
on that, thanks.
We should give Dandy
a heads up about it.
[QT] But we can't go anywhere!
The Aloha Oe still can't move!
Hey, look.
[QT] Huh?
[MEOW]
Think we can use that?
[ERSSIME] L'delise!
Hm? Erssime!
[DANDY] Wait up, you crazy coot!
Why're you still here?
I thought I told you to leave.
Yeah, and I told you
I wasn't going home
until I caught a Munagi.
You see what I see?
Incredible!
It really is a blue moon!
[L'DELISE]
As the legend tells us,
when a blue moon fills the sky,
the seas shall billow and the
Munagi shall rise from the deep!
They should be here soon.
[DANDY] Huh?
[QT] What do you think that is?
[MEOW] Meow.
Yeah, here
they come, baby!
Make 'em go away!
It begins.
Okay, Munagi, this is it!
Let's see what you got, huh?
[DANDY] Ah! My rod and tackle!
[L'DELISE] Useless tenderfoot!
[DANDY] Bail faster, kid.
Here it comes!
That's amazing!
[ERSSIME] Look out behind you!
[DANDY] Whoa!
Did he make the catch?
L'delise!
Hey! Come back!
You okay?
That was close, huh?
To fail after all that.
[DANDY] Auuuuuuggghh!!
[DANDY] You're not
goin' anywhere!
Be careful!
Let's go help him out.
[DANDY screams]
[L'DELISE] All right.
Let's see if we can pull it in.
We're with ya!
Yep!
Okay, now. Ready?
Heave, two, three, four!
It's not even
budging, is it?
Huh?
[QT] Is that a Munagi?
You actually
found one? Sweet.
You guys picked a good
time to make an entrance.
Come on, you slackers!
Pull like you mean it.
Easy, dude,
I'm doing my part.
[QT] If I pull any harder,
my battery's gonna blow!
So they're real! The old
legend is actually true!
Sorry we made fun of you.
That was our bad.
It's okay,
just help out now.
[L'DELISE] Everyone ready?
Heave, two, three, four!
Can't keep pulling.
Arms so tired.
[L'DELISE]
Oi.
Huh...?
Take the bow and arrow.
[DANDY] Huh?
Go on, take it! Or are
you just gonna sit there?
You really mean it.
Count on Dandy.
[ERSSIME] Good luck!
You can do it!
What are you waiting for?
[DANDY] Here we go! Uh-oh.
[ERSSIME]
Dandy!
[DANDY] Where the
hell are we going?
[NARRATOR] Three-thousand-six
hundred years ago,
the Munagi soared
through the universe
on the back of the
majestic Rubini Comet.
When the comet drew
close to Planet Kayu,
the great sea
creatures crossed over.
And now at long last, the
Rubini Comet has reappeared,
and the Munagi can return
to their rightful home.
[ERSSIME crying]
Dandy's dead, isn't he?
[QT] I wonder if
this means we're going
to have to go up
there after him.
[bubbling sound]
Ugh. Ow!
Hey! It's Dandy!
[DANDY] Damn overgrown
fish got away.
Hmph! Stupid neophyte!
You say something to me,
you decrepit old geezer?
You brats are all the same!
Wet-behind-the-ears,
and no good to anybody!
I hope you plan to retire
before the senility kicks in.
[L'DELISE] Retire, huh?
Why don't you come over
here and say that?
Aw, you guys!
You're finally getting along!
[DANDY] Fine, I'll say it
again: you should retire!
[L'DELISE] Not a
chance, tenderfoot!
[QT] Don't forget, the
hook has to be inside
the fish's mouth or
the catch doesn't count.
Are you kidding? All that
and we're back here now?
[MEOW] Guys. If we're gonna
spend all this time fishing,
why don't we try for
a more lucrative catch?
[DANDY] Shut up.
[QT] Just work on
your fishing skills.
Like I said,
there's nothing impressive
about catching a carp.
[DANDY] Say that one more time.
[MEOW] If it's impressive
you're looking for,
there's always the
legendary Mussie.
[DANDY] Mussie, huh? All right,
sounds good to me!
So, where should we
start looking for it?
[GENTLE] My name is Gentle,
and I am far too refined for
a lowbrow anime such as this.
[DANDY] 'Scuse me?
[WOMAN] So handsome.
[DANDY] Hey!
[GENTLE] Next time, "The Gallant
Space Gentleman, Baby."
Until then!
[DANDY] See ya then!