[NARRATOR]
Space Dandy.
He's a dandy guy... in space.
He combs the galaxy
like his pompadour,
on the hunt for aliens.
Planet after planet he searches,
discovering bizarre new
creatures both friendly and not.
These are the
spectacular adventures
of Space Dandy and his
brave space crew... in space.
[UKULELE plays]
[UKELELEMAN sighs]
I hate being frozen.
I want to show the world
what I'm feeling inside!
[crowd chatters]
[UKELELEMAN] You'd never know,
but I have a very cheerful,
bubbly personality.
I'm a regular joke factory.
And I laugh at
other people's jokes.
I laugh until my stomach hurts.
But so what?
All anyone can see is this face.
And they don't
seem to like it much.
I have tried.
I've tried a bunch of things,
but no matter what,
it's the same
outcome every time.
Nothing ever works.
I'm stuck like this.
I just want
to be able to laugh
like I don't have a
care in the universe.
Yes. Like this.
You are so wrong.
It's them!
You're so wrong.
It's not!
♪ Huh huh huh huh-- ♪ Right?
How does that
sound like Shakatak?
♪ Hu-huh
hm huh huh hu-huh. ♪
How can you not hear it, man?
Actually, the song
I just played--
Oh, shut up.
What do you know?
[MEOW] You're wrong,
I'm tellin' ya.
You're always
misunderstanding stuff.
You're like the king
of misunderstandings.
If there was a contest
for misunderstanding,
you'd win in a landslide.
[QT] That's a great idea!
I wonder if there is
a contest like that.
Uh, we done here?
Can I move on to
the next table now?
Look, you're wrong.
I'm right. I'm telling
you, I just heard it.
[MEOW] Where?
I dunno. On Late
Night or something.
Sketchiest
explanation ever.
Sketchy, is it?
How am I sketchy?
What part of me
is sketchy, exactly?
From pompadour to toe, you
are one sketchy bastard.
Then, sketch away.
That's not what
"sketchy" means!
[QT] Ha! What do you know,
there really is one!
The Mr. Misunderstanding
Grand Prix!
We've gotta sign
this dude up.
[QT] The prize for the winner
is "a whole lot of food."
That sounds pretty sketchy, too.
Oh, I see how it is.
That's how you guys
wanna play it, huh?
That's fine by me,
but if that's the case--
[drumroll]
[DANDY] I have a shocking
announcement to make.
As of today, this moment,
Team BBP is--
--officially disbanded!
Sweet, the entry
form printed!
Misunderstanding Grand
Prix, here we come!
This is it!
Don't try and stop me!
So long, former friends!
[QT] Where are
you going?
Don't you want to stay
and eat pancakes?
Pancakes are too sweet
for the bitter pain
consuming my heart.
What do think
he meant by that?
[QT] Maybe he wanted
waffles instead?
[HONEY] Hi there!
One giant Hawaiian Pancake
Tower, at your service!
Hey, where'd
Dandy run off to?
[DANDY] It's no use!
I guess I'm just Dandy
the Space Bum, nothing more.
That's what a guy gets for just
tryin' to live with the flow.
[horn honks]
[POSTIAN] Are you a
Mr. Space Dandy, sir?
I have your space
mail right here.
[DANDY] Huh?
[horn honks]
[DANDY] What's this?
"Dear Mr. Dandy,
I'm your biggest fan
in the whole universe.
I can't stop
picturing your smile.
I've fallen in love with it.
[IMAGINARY GIRL] I'm
throwing a party at my house,
and I was hoping you might
come as the guest of honor.
See you soon. A Rare Alien."
She signed it from
"a rare alien."
Sounds like this babe's itchin'
for me to snatch her up.
[GEL] Maman. So kind,
but with a firm hand.
I owe everything to you.
You made me what I am today.
Oh, dear Maman.
I wish I could
see you once more.
Whatever I do, whatever I try,
I am thwarted at every turn!
How many times now
has Dandy slipped
through my fingers?
Over and over again it happens.
I get so close, and then
he just disappears!
[BEA] I don't think
we've ever really gotten
that close, actually.
Shut up! We have, too!
[BEA] Oh. Don't
dwell on it, sir.
It's not like we
can turn back time.
Time, eh? Yes, that's it!
We'll make for the
River of Time at once!
This piece of junk.
What's wrong with
the damn thing now?
He did that thing
where he runs off
somewhere without
telling us, huh?
[QT] He'll come back when
he gets hungry like usual.
Huh?
[QT] What's that?
[music]
[MEOW] Look at that!
Dandy won the
Mr. Misunderstanding Grand Prix!
[QT] Check out the fine print.
It says the prize
must be awarded
in person or it's forfeit!
[BOTH] We have to get
Dandy back here right now!
Huh?
Uh. Habba you
help-uh me, please?
It's okay. I can
understand you.
Ah-ha. I'm looking
for a mansion where
a beautiful girl lives.
Can you help me out?
A mansion? Here?
Yeah. I was invited
to this party.
See, I would hate to
let the hostess down.
A party without
Dandy's no party at all,
if you know what I mean.
No, what do you mean?
Uh, yeah, forget
I said anything.
I had my doubts
about this planet
when I hit water
on the way down,
but it's lookin'
pretty dry so far.
You passed through water?
Is it possible?
I think perhaps you
saw the River of Time.
Oh, yeah?
Never heard of it.
[CAPYBARIAN] It has long been
held that the River of Time
flows in the upper
atmosphere of this planet.
You see, like time
itself, the river's
current moves from
the past to the future.
Which means that
the "you" that was
and the "you" that will be
are both floating in the river.
You must have had a
near-death experience in which
you caught a glimpse of
the river's temporal flow.
[DANDY] Huh?
[CAPYBARIAN] The Pororoca
phenomenon has been known
to occur in the river.
[DANDY] Pororoca?
[NARRATOR] Yes. When
a river flows backwards,
it may be referred to as
the Pororoca phenomenon.
The gravitational pull of
a satellite acts on the
surface water of a planet,
causing it to flow backwards
and create an immense,
seemingly endless wave.
The Pororoca phenomenon
is not limited
to planets but may also
occur in the River of Time,
which flows through space.
To put it simply,
it causes the past
to repeat itself.
You might think of
it as a give and take
between a planet
and its satellite.
--which is not dissimilar
to the give and take
between a man and a woman;
two bodies acting
upon one another...
What are you talking about?
[NARRATOR] Oh. Forget
I said that last bit.
[QT] According to
the GPS coordinates,
Dandy should be
somewhere in this area.
Looks like the
whole planet's a jungle.
Moving around down
there won't be easy.
So let's teleport directly
where we need to go.
[QT] Yeah! That'll give us a
chance to try out the remote.
[BOTH] Huh?
[BEA] Dr. Gel, sir.
We're nearing the location
where the River of Time
is said to flow.
[GEL] Good.
The Spacetrotter Guidebook,
Frontier Edition says:
"You never can
tell when you'll get
to see the Pororoca phenomenon.
If you catch it, count yourself
super lucky! Like, for real!"
We will succeed this time.
I demand it!
That no-good space
bum will not escape
from our clutches again.
We will capture him!
Yeah!
[QT] We had a few
false starts there,
but I think we finally
found the right place.
[MEOW] Did you see
those Mantisians?
When they were
chasing us I thought
we were gonna be
space dust for sure.
[QT] Yeah. And what
about the Wiggians?
They were freaky, too.
It seemed like they
were pretty desperate
to find an empty
scalp to call home.
If that's all
they really want,
I wish they'd save the shock
treatments for bald people.
[QT] And there
were so many.
If they'd caught us, we'd
be wearing wig stacks!
Yeah, like the wig version
of the pancake tower!
[UKELELEMAN] Well, here goes.
Time for a ukulele lullaby.
[UKULELE plays]
[DANDY] Ah! Finally, here it is.
Fashionably late is
better than nothing.
[UKELELEMAN] You really came!
You're Space Dandy, aren't you?
Welcome to my home!
You have no idea
how long I've been
waiting to meet you.
No matter where you go,
you are the life
of the party.
I don't know what
I would've done
if you didn't come.
Easy. You're
gettin' really upset
about this, aren't you?
Upset?
No! This is me ecstatic!
It's kinda hard
to tell, ya know?
Well, anyway,
where's the girl?
[UKELELEMAN] What girl?
The sexy, rare alien
who sent me that letter.
She waits for me.
I should go to her.
[UKELELEMAN] Unfortunately,
there seems to have been
a grave misunderstanding.
I know that's just part
of your charm, though.
There's no need
to cry about it, man.
[UKELELEMAN] I'm not
crying! I'm ecstatic!
Though I'm starting to
get a little angry now.
[DANDY] Well, you got
a great poker face.
So. Who are
you, anyway?
[UKELELEMAN] A rare
alien. I am Ukeleleman.
[UKELELEMAN] I am of a race
that is born utterly alone.
I am the only living
example of my kind.
As I was born, so am I
destined to die: alone.
Over time I've become
what you might call
a smile aficionado.
Now, at last, I've found it.
The crowning jewel
of all smiles!
I can't tell
you how little
I care about that.
Now go and
get the girl.
It's time to get
this party started,
don't ya think?
[UKELELEMAN]
It was me.
[DANDY]
What's you?
[UKELELEMAN]
I wrote that letter.
I'm the one who
invited you here.
Not a beautiful girl?
[UKELELEMAN] No.
How 'bout an ugly one?
Don't be like that.
We can still party!
But first, let me see the
best smile in the universe.
Hey--where--?
A party with just two guys?
I did not come all the way out
here for a sausage festival.
[DANDY] What are these things?
Alien statues? Pretty realistic.
And each one is different.
Meow? QT?
[UKELELEMAN] You shouldn't
have come out this way.
This exit isn't for guests.
[DANDY] These two here.
I'm pretty sure I know 'em.
[UKELELEMAN] Oh, those?
Recent acquisitions.
They didn't work out.
You know how it is.
Their smiles just
weren't quite right.
[DANDY] Not cool.
[UKELELEMAN] Sorry?
Not cool. You turned 'em
into statues?
[UKELELEMAN] I told you,
I'm an aficionado.
This is my life's work;
collecting smiles.
Obviously, I had to try out
a lot of different models.
[UKELELEMAN] But none worked.
I looked and I looked,
but I just couldn't
find my perfect match.
Of course,
until I saw you.
I want your smiling mug
for my collection.
People will like me so much more
with that grin
plastered on my face.
So go on, Dandy,
give us a smile.
Want me to smile for you?
I can't, not now.
How could
I possibly smile after
what you turned my friends into?
I'll never be able
to smile again, baby!
[UKELELEMAN] Oh, really?
Well, that's problematic.
[Ukulele plays]
Hell no!
Whoa, hold on!
That's the Aloha Oe!
[DANDY] Hey!
[CAPYBARIAN] Hm?
Oh, you were here before.
That's not yours
by any chance, is it?
[DANDY] Hey, what're you doing?
That's not food! Get off!
Hey, uh.
That Pororoca thing in
the River of Time means
I can travel to the past, right?
Well, that's the theory.
That planet there
is coming closer.
Going now's your best chance.
[BEA] Dr. Gel.
Dandy's down there.
The Aloha Oe is ascending
through the planet's atmosphere.
[GEL] That's him?
[DANDY sighs]
Knew it would work.
I'll drag them back out
from a point in the past,
and they'll be as good as new.
It's Dandy, sir!
So we haven't even
traveled to the past.
No matter! I
want him captured!
[GEL] What is that?
That's Maman.
[GEL] Maman!
Who do you think you are,
you hairy pervert?
Get away from me!
[GEL cries]
Come on.
Where are that pinhead
'bot and bonehead cat?
[UKELELEMAN]
You give me no choice.
You said you would never
be able to smile again.
So I'll search the River of Time
for a version of
you from the past.
A version of you
that is smiling.
Past me?
[UKELELEMAN] Well
would you look at that!
You're right over there.
Unfortunately,
when I pull you out
of the past, the present
you will disappear.
That's just the way it works.
Nothing personal.
[DANDY] Hey! You guys!
Hey, QT, Dandy's here!
[QT] Everything okay, Dandy?
You look a little faint.
[DANDY] Whoa! What the--?
That ukulele-playing bastard!
[DANDY] Don't mess
with me, baby!
[UKELELEMAN] Oh, well.
It's alright.
It can end like this.
A smile probably wouldn't
have suited me, anyway.
[DANDY] Actually, baby.
You're smiling right now.
[UKELELEMAN] I am, really?
And is--
is it a good smile?
Good?
No, that's a great smile
you've got there.
[Ukulele plays]
[DANDY] I recognize that melody.
Yeah, that's totally it.
[CARPACCIO] Gyo gyo-gyo!
Uh-gyo wuh-were-we
cow-woowee yooweereeyow
turlee-urleeoway, ing-now-ah,
ooh-ooh n'gyo-gyo-gyo-gyo
cown my gyo!
Gyo gyo-gyo! Go-ah-we-were!
Gyo gya-gyo! Gyo gyuh gyo!