[GENERAL 20A]
Special report, Commander.
We've received some
interesting intelligence
from our spy in
the Gogol Empire.
They will soon be
conducting an inspection
of their ultimate weapon,
the dreaded C.O.R.E.
[GENERAL 20B] So what
does that mean for us?
[GENERAL 20A] While the C.O.R.E.
is docked for inspection,
it's highly likely
they will replace it
with a decoy to
maintain appearances.
This is our best chance to
launch a full-scale invasion!
[GENERAL 20B] I believe
we should proceed,
but with caution.
[GENERAL 20A] With that
spineless sort of attitude,
we couldn't conquer a comet!
Commander, what are your orders?
[the commander chuckles]
Getting ahead of
ourselves, aren't we?
This is a momentous decision.
The fate of the entire
galaxy rests upon it.
And what have you given me?
Scraps of information.
A bare bones report.
I can't make a
decision based on that.
Consult your sources.
Gather more definitive
intelligence at once.
Then I'll decide
what is to be done.
[NARRATOR] The leader
of the Jaicro Empire:
a man whose very name
rings with power. Johnny.
But beneath his steely
exterior lie depths
that no one has plumbed.
At least, not yet.
[NARRATOR] His dream is
to become a rock star!
How original.
[JOHNNY] What were
you just humming?
What?
Disgusting. You didn't
wash your hands.
Says the guy
who didn't flush
after taking an epic dump.
Come on. Did he
fall in or something?
[QT] Whoa!
[MEOW] Whoa!
[JOHNNY] Oh yeah!
That's it. I'm gonna rearrange
that pretty face of yours
so your own mama
wouldn't know you!
[QT] So much violence!
Hang on.
[JOHNNY and DANDY] Yeah!
Yeah. There's just no beating
the Andromeda branch
of the Naritasan Temple,
is there?
Exactly!
That's what I'm saying!
I mean you have to get
a blessing from Acala
before warping anywhere.
[MEOW] Look, isn't it sweet?
Dandy found his soul mate.
Hey.
We should start a band.
What, you and me?
It came to me when you were
humming in the bathroom.
Like the rock gods spoke,
I would be on the guitar.
You'd be lead vocals.
Sound good?
[DANDY] If we're really gonna
do this, we do it for real.
We don't go halfway.
We're either the best
there is, or we're nothing.
You agree to that, and
I just might be interested.
[JOHNNY] It's a deal!
Oh, yeah!
[QT] So, uh, who decided
I should be on drums, anyway?
Probably the same genius who
decided I should play bass.
We should pick
out a name first.
The rest will flow from there.
"Dandy &amp; Omega Tribe"
has a nice ring, huh?
Hey, man, come on.
Let's not waste time
joking around, okay?
Here, check this one out.
"Johnny with Team D."
[DANDY] Or "Dandy Rave Factory."
That's DRF for short.
[JOHNNY] "Johnny
featuring You Guys."
[DANDY] Or "Dandy and
Those Guys Over There"
[JOHNNY] Never!
[DANDY] No way!
We'll figure it out.
Now here's an idea
I think you're gonna like.
We'll have our big
debut at Space Budokan.
Yeah, that'll rock.
Nobody's gonna
know what hit 'em.
You and me, we're gonna
change the face of music!
The rock revolution
starts today!
Right! Look out, galaxy!
A legend's being born!
[NARRATOR] Thus they
spent their first practice
discussing the finer points
of their own awesomeness,
which is much more productive
than the tedious business
of practicing music.
[MEOW] Look,
they're at it again.
[QT] Kind of makes you
want to vomit, huh?
[HONEY] Thanks for
waiting, boys. Here you go.
What's this delicacy?
What do you mean?
They're french fries, silly.
They look like potatoes
that have been fried.
[JOHNNY] Wow!
I had no idea potatoes
could be so delicious.
[MEOW] You've really never
had french fries before?
Guess what!
We're starting a band,
and it's gonna be
the best in the galaxy.
Obviously there'll
be a special edition
of our debut single,
and it'll come
with an awesome,
one-of-a-kind sticker!
[DANDY] A sticker? Lame.
Dude, it's gonna come
with a pennant, not a sticker.
You're kidding, right?
Who wants a stupid little
flag as a keepsake?
[QT] Let's calm down.
In the long run,
does it really matter?
Stay out of it, okay?
We're going with a pennant. Ah!
[QT] Hey, stop! This isn't fun!
A sticker! That's final!
[MEOW] Uh, what are you doing?
Something that's
absolutely vital
for any legendary rock star.
Here, take a look.
I'm practicing my autograph,
baby. Nice, huh?
Yeah. I don't
think that's necessary.
[QT] Who is this Johnny
character, anyway?
I mean, do we know
anything about him?
Well, apparently
he has a part-time job.
Really? Doing what?
I dunno.
The spaceship he came in on had
"something-Empire" written
on the side of it, though.
[QT] Maybe he's a
security guard, then.
I think there's a guard
service with a name like that.
Huh.
Guess he's still in the
"paying his dues" phase
of his music career.
[QT] Right? He'd never
had french fries before.
He must be seriously broke
if he can't even afford those.
[SERVER 20A] An aspic consommé
of Homard lobster from Bretagne.
Paired with the
highest-quality caviar
and a luscious
cauliflower mousseline.
I don't suppose you
have any fried potatoes.
[SERVER 20A] Pardon?
[JOHNNY] Never mind.
This is fine.
[NARRATOR] And so, Johnny
began to lead a double life,
balancing his
duties as commander
of the Jaicro Empire,
and aspiring musician.
Hey, do you know
the most important part
of preparing to be
a serious rock star?
What do you think it is?
That's easy.
Practicing for interviews, baby.
Exactly! That's
what I'm saying!
Here's the thing. It's not
that I'm pursing rock.
That's not it at all.
Rock is pursuing me.
[DANDY] There are two things
that a real rocker
can't live without,
and that's booze,
women, and music.
I always knew
I was different.
Destined for greatness,
one might say--
[DANDY] Hey, man.
Back off, all right?
I was talking. Camera hog.
[NARRATOR] They fought about
who would get more camera time.
Do you know the
most important thing
for the number-one rock star
in the galaxy to have?
What do you think it is?
That's easy.
Awesome t-shirts for
the merch table, baby.
Exactly! That's
what I'm saying!
Hey! What are you wearing?
The t-shirts should be black!
[JOHNNY] No, red!
[DANDY] Black!
[NARRATOR]
They fought about the t-shirts
for the merchandise table.
They fought about the
money they hadn't made yet.
They even fought about drugs.
The whole of their
rocker experience
consisted of fighting,
fighting, and more fighting.
Not only had they failed
to write a single song,
they hadn't even decided
on a band name yet.
Hey, I know.
How about the Dropkix?
[GROUP] Huh?
I mean, you two are
always dropkicking
each other, so it kinda
fits, dontcha think?
"The Dropkix," huh? Well?
It's not bad.
I think I like it.
Oh, looks like we've
got a gig lined up.
[JOHNNY and DANDY]
A real gig?
[MEOW] It's a tiny club, not a
major concert venue or anything,
but they were looking
for bands to play,
so I told them we
might be interested.
Should we test
our set out there,
before our big
Space Budokan debut?
Yeah, baby.
Give 'em a little taste
before the real legend begins.
[QT] Um, guys.
Before we do that,
we need to write a song.
Our set list is
really short right now.
Oh. Don't worry.
That part you
can leave up to me.
Hey, uh, what are
you doin' up there?
I'm waiting for a song.
Huh?
Don't you get it?
A true masterpiece
isn't written.
It descends upon you from above.
[JOHNNY] It's here!
[plays Galaga theme]
Hey. Isn't that from Galaga?
[QT] Doesn't band
practice usually
involve everyone
playing together?
No reason you an'
me can't practice
on our own, right?
It's not like we're busy, here.
[JOHNNY] My masterpiece!
My ultimate creation!
[JOHNNY] It's here!
[plays "The Flea Waltz"]
"The Flea Waltz."
Not exactly original, baby.
[NARRATOR] And so,
time passed as time does.
Until finally, it was
the day before the gig.
It's not coming to me.
There's nothing.
[QT] It seems like this method
might not work
so well, after all.
Maybe it would be
better to cancel the gig.
[DANDY] No, wait. It's coming.
[NARRATOR] Sure enough,
the ambient sounds combined
and gave rise to
a musical miracle.
[JOHNNY] It's here!
[GROUP] Ooh!
[JOHNNY] Well, there you go.
Just learn it by the
time we go on tomorrow.
Huh?
How do you expect us to learn
something like that so quickly?
[QT] We've been practicing.
We've had extra time
lately for some reason.
[MEOW] So?
Yeah. That'll do.
Rock on, you guys.
[GENERAL 20A] We have
an update, Commander.
We have evidence
that the Gogol Empire
is preparing to dock the
C.O.R.E. for inspection.
[GENERAL 20B] Indeed?
What part of this is
firm evidence, exactly?
[JOHNNY] What is that?
[GENERAL 20A] It's a dummy
constructed of plywood.
Our sources indicate
the Gogol plan is to use
this to fool us while they
conduct the inspection.
[GENERAL 20B] If that is
what we were up against,
I can't imagine we would
have any trouble defeating it.
[GENERAL 20A] Commander,
what are your orders?
[NARRATOR] And so, after
what felt like years of waiting,
the day of the
first gig arrived.
Only three in the audience?
[QT] There are more
than that in the band.
Hold on, now.
You never know.
There might be someone
from the industry here.
That's not very likely.
[QT] Are you talking
about a scout or something?
[JOHNNY] Yeah. I've heard
they check out clubs like this.
Scoping out raw
talent, you know?
See that old man back there?
He could be a scout, huh?
[NARRATOR] What they didn't
realize was that the old man
wasn't a member of the audience.
He was the club janitor.
Right. Let's do this.
[plays rock song]
[NARRATOR] Their very first gig.
]It may not have been
how they'd imagined it,
but in a way,
it was a landmark event.
Because even though
they had only one song
in their repertoire,
they managed to play
for two full hours.
We can play all night, baby.
Next up on the set list
is our new song again--
Don't do it!
If you play that
damn song once more.
[DANDY] Shut up!
[NARRATOR] The fight that broke
out following this initial gig
made the news and soon
went viral, which, in turn,
gave the band some
much-needed publicity.
[NARRATOR] Their fame
continued to grow.
Until they finally
came to the notice
of a large record label's CEO.
Howdy fellas.
Would you guys be the Dropkix?
Us?
What if we are?
You got somethin' to say?
How's a recording contract
with my company sound?
You guys have
potential to be big.
Number one in the galaxy.
We have some conditions.
We know we want our first big
show to be at Space Budokan.
That's non-negotiable.
And then there's
our debut single to
consider, as well.
We want it to come with
a special bonus pennant.
Hey! What's with
the damn flag again?
I thought we
decided on a sticker?
Hey, no problem!
We'll do both!
Huh?
[CEO] Right, boys?
[QT] Huh?
I think neither
would've been better.
[DJ] This next song has really
been climbing the charts.
New to the music scene,
it's the Dropkix.
July 7th.
That's the day we've
lined up for your big debut.
And, obviously, it's going
to be at Space Budokan.
[GENERAL 20A] Commander!
We've finally learned
the exact date
of the Gogol Empire's
C.O.R.E. inspection.
It will be July 7th!
What? July 7th?
[GENERAL 20B]
And the intel is solid?
[GENERAL 20A]
Yes, as solid as it gets.
That day is our chance to
launch a full-scale offensive.
[GENERAL 20A] Commander!
[GENERAL 20B] Quiet!
The commander is conflicted,
can't you see that?
If we start a war,
many lives will be lost.
The commander
can't decide lightly.
He knows that the fate of the
galaxy hangs in the balance.
[NARRATOR] It's true that
Commander Johnny was conflicted.
[NARRATOR] Should he
launch an all-out invasion
of the Gogol Empire?
Or should he play
in his band's big gig?
War, or gig.
Gig, or war. He chose.
Something's come up, guys.
I can't make it to the show.
[MEOW] No!
Huh?
Sorry.
Hold on. Wait a sec!
Something's going on.
What gives? Come on, man.
We were gonna be the best!
We were gonna change
the very face of music!
[QT] Is it your job?
Did they call you in?
You guys...
You guys just don't get it.
Then why
don't you help us to.
About my job,
I'm the commander-in-chief.
Uh?
I am the supreme commander
of the Jaicro Empire!
In my real life,
I'm powerful.
I have it all: the rank, the
fame, the money. That and more.
But I wanted to be
recognized for my music.
I wanted to see how far
I could make it on talent alone.
Sorry I lied to you.
What kind of
blind idiot are you?
Do you actually think it
matters if you're rich or poor?
Nobody gives a damn about
that stuff once you're
on stage, you moron!
Go on and admit it:
you're just scared.
You got scared and
you're running away!
You can believe
whatever you want to,
but I know that the future
of the Empire is in my hands!
Damn that guy.
What was all that
commander-in-chief stuff?
Seemed like a big deal.
Maybe he's a manager at the
security company he works for?
Our guitarist?
A manager? So not rock.
[NARRATOR] And then,
it was upon them.
The day of their debut concert
at Space Budokan had arrived.
[QT] We were supposed
to start a long time ago.
The crowd's getting restless.
I really don't think Johnny
is going to make it, you guys.
[MEOW] What should we do?
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Johnny
and his fleet were headed
for the Gogol Empire
and galactic conquest.
[QT] We're kind of
out of time here.
Maybe we can stall them
with some magic tricks
or jokes or something.
[QT] Two words: Jazz Odyssey.
[DANDY] Right. I'll just have
to go on with my voice guitar.
[badly mimics guitar sounds]
[MEOW] It hurts to look!
[QT] I can't take
much more of this!
[DJ] The band you've been
hearing so much about
is finally going to
take the stage today!
[GENERAL 20A] We'll reach the
target location before long.
[badly mimics guitar sounds]
It's incredible.
Who knew Dandy
had so much heart?
[QT] A true performer
knows the show must go on!
That's enough, son.
I'm afraid there's nothing
more you can do here.
Attention.
It pains me to announce this,
but it seems I have no choice.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the concert is--
Huh?
[GENERAL 20A] Commander,
we await your order.
Wait, where is the
commander? Did he leave?
What's that thing?
[QT] A shooting star?
Uh...
Had to make an entrance.
Sorry I'm late, everybody.
What a show off.
I'm not surprised, you know.
Yeah, I know.
You're the one
who started all this.
There wouldn't be
a band without you.
Actually, you started it.
Humming that song of yours.
[DANDY] 1. 2. 3. 4!
♪ Hey Lady! ♪
♪ You don't have to
have a lonely night ♪
♪ Space Lady! ♪
♪ Just come with me and
I'm 'a treat you right! ♪
♪ Oh, you're tricky, baby ♪
♪ I misunderstood
your saucy eyes ♪
♪ Now I know you're faded ♪
♪ And I'm gonna
be alone tonight ♪
♪ Pouty lips,
moist and wanting ♪
♪ But they're never
wanting what I'm offering ♪
♪ At the furthest boundary
of the universe ♪
♪ We pass by each
other so inebriated ♪
♪ Lonely night! ♪
♪ Mistified! ♪
♪ Solitary, not so merry-- ♪
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
[JOHNNY] Hey!
Look out! I'm on fire!
I'm on fire! Someone put me out!
[JOHNNY] Get away
from me, you idiot!
You're gonna kill us both!
[NARRATOR] And so
the Dropkix first concert
was also their last,
and, as they had said from
the beginning, it was legendary.
[UNDERLING 20A]
What should we do?
[GENERAL 20A] We have no choice.
Jaicro Space Armada, retreat!
[MEOW] Lucky us. We've got a
million t-shirts left over.
What're we gonna
do with all these?
Wear them.
What the hell else do
you do with t-shirts?
Or, we could send 'em to Johnny
and let him deal with them.
[QT] Just one problem with that.
We don't know where he lives.
[NARRATOR] Today they're
remembered only as
the one-hit wonder that
broke up after just one gig.
No one knows the truth,
that these intrepid rockers
prevented a galactic war
and saved the universe
from total chaos.
[DJ] You're listening to this
week's Galaxy Hit Chart.
Now for our number one song!
[DANDY] ♪ Hey Lady! ♪
♪ You don't have to
have a lonely night ♪
♪ Space Lady! ♪
♪ Just come with me and
I'm 'a treat you right! ♪
♪ Oh, you're tricky, baby ♪
♪ I misunderstood
your saucy eyes ♪
♪ Now I know you're faded ♪
♪ And I'm gonna
be alone tonight ♪
♪ Pouty lips,
moist and wanting ♪
♪ But they're never
wanting what I'm offering ♪
♪ At the furthest
boundary of the universe ♪
♪ We pass by each
other so inebriated ♪
♪ Lonely night! ♪
♪ Mistified! ♪
♪ Solitary, not so
merry, lonely night! ♪
♪ Come on baby, why don't
you just hold me tight? ♪
♪ Lonely night! ♪
♪ Ah! ♪
♪ Mistifed! ♪
♪ Lonely night! ♪
[GEL] Imagine waking
from a drunken stupor,
not knowing if you've been
asleep for an hour or a day,
uncertain if the fuzzy
memories of the night
before had all
just been a dream.
The next episode
sort of feels like that.
"A World with No Sadness, Baby"!