[SCARLET] Dandy, that's a cow.
A wha--?
[SCARLET] Holstein Friesian.
A mammal classified
as order Artiodactyla,
family Bovidae, genus Bos.
[DANDY] Take a closer look.
I'm tellin' ya, this ain't a
cow this is 'Grade A' alien.
Aren't ya?
[COW moos]
[QT] Uh oh.
It looks like Miss Scarlet's
about to go berserk again.
[MEOW] We'd better get
outta here while we still can.
[SCARLET] Excuse me.
[QT] Yes, ma'am?
Please don't kill us!
Good grief.
I just want to have
a chat with you.
[SCARLET] Dealing with
alien hunters day in
and day out as I do,
I've become something of
an expert at sizing them up.
So I can tell you:
you three are,
by far, the worst
hunters I've ever met.
I'm sorry, boys.
I hate to break it to you
but I don't think you're
cut out for this job.
That's why, for your own
sakes and my sanity,
I urge you to consider
a career change.
The universe
is a big place.
I'm sure the possibilities
are endless.
[MEOW] Space Career
Change Magazine, huh?
[DANDY] Man, what the hell
does Scarlet know anyway?
[MEOW] These
ain't gonna work.
They want
college grads.
[QT] So much
for there being
"endless possibilities."
[DANDY yawns]
[MEOW] Here's
an ad looking for
space-truck drivers.
No degree required.
[DANDY] Now that you mention it,
I was a space truck driver
before I hunted aliens.
[MEOW] Huh?
[QT] This is the first
I've heard about it.
But you gotta have
a special license
to drive a big
rig truck, dontcha?
I can't really remember.
But I think I had one.
[MEOW] "You think."
[MEOW] In a universe
where there are endless
possibilities, how
did I end up gettin' stuck
with two of the biggest
losers in all existence?
If only Dandy
was a respectable
alien hunter;
right now, I would be--
[DANDY] If only the mangy cat
and the bucket o' bolts
weren't so useless;
right now, I would be--
[QT] If only Dandy and
Meow were valiant warriors
instead of scatterbrains;
right now, I'd be--
[ALL THREE chuckle]
Hey man, you got a stray hair
pokin' out your pomp.
What the--?
Dude. That's
so gross.
[QT] Geez, how
long is your hair?
I'm gettin' some
resistance here.
[DANDY] Ow!
That's crazy!
They popped out
of your perfectly
styled coif!
Yeah, but
stranger things
have happened,
buddy.
QT! Get me some info on 'em.
[QT] Roger.
[QT] No data
available.
Do you think
they could be
an undiscovered
alien species, Dandy?
Wait. Your name's Dandy?
Yeah, and don't you forget it.
D-A-N-D-Y. Dandy.
What a small world.
My name is also
D-N-A. It's Dandy.
You get the point.
[QT] Incidentally,
my name's QT, also.
[QT] Impossible!
There's no way an
old clunker like you
is the same
model as me!
What about you, cat?
What's your name?
Why's everyone
think I'm a cat?
I'm Meow.
What? That's weird;
my name's Meow!
[DANDY] What the
heck's goin' on?
This is way too freaky
to be a coincidence.
[HONEY] Dandy!
I can't believe you
took off without me!
That's a red card, Mister!
[DANDY] Honey!
Honey?
You mean, like the
one from Boobies?
Aw, c'mon.
I can't afford
anymore red cards.
[HONEY A] Poor thing!
In that case, I'll make it
a yellow card just for you!
Thanks, babe.
[QT] Dandy, what should we
do about our "visitors"?
I dunno.
You think we should take 'em
by the registration center?
[QT] That's a
splendid idea!
[DANDY] They're gone!
[MEOW] I'll find 'em!
Big Punch!
[DANDY] There's
no escaping me!
You might as well give up.
I'm the number one alien hunter,
with a one hundred
percent capture rate!
You're getting
a red card
for being
way too cool!
Geez, as if
I didn't hate
the guy enough
already.
I'm sendin'
him some bad juju.
That'll teach him
to mess with me.
[QT] I doubt he's
gonna be frightened
by threats
of "bad juju."
[MEOW] Hey QT.
You've got a pube
growin' out of your head.
[QT] Hmm?
[GIRL MEOW] Wouldn't
we get there faster
if we just warped
right meow, Dandy?
Don't be a dumbass.
If we move too fast we'll miss
out on the amazin' view, baby.
[QT] Tell the truth!
He doesn't wanna
warp 'cause he heard
a silly rumor that it
makes your hair fall out.
Says the bald guy!
Hey, QT.
You're not bald, you've
got a hair right up here!
Whoa.
Just where in
the hell are we?
Hey, who are
you guys?
If you're pirates,
you better leave right meow!
"Meow"?
[QT] I'm starting to
sense a pattern here.
Excuse me, sir,
is your name Dandy?
Yeah, it is;
how'd you know?
[DANDY] Ain't that somethin'?
I can't believe you're Dandy,
QT, and Meow, too.
Yeah, talk about
crazy coincidence, huh?
Is that this month's issue?
Dandy, you know it's dangerous
to travel with strangers,
so why won't you
kick them meow-t?
You kiddin' me?
"Merry companions are
a wagon in space", baby.
[QT] May I ask
what brought
the three of
you together?
[QT B] Well, you
see, Dandy is the
best trucker in
the whole universe.
At first, QT and I
were nothing more
than cargo he
picked up for delivery.
But I was sent back
and the address on QT's
shipping label was wrong.
[QT] That's when Dandy,
out of the kindness
of his heart,
took us in and made
us part of his team.
That's what makes him
the best trucker in
the whole universe!
That's such
a beautiful story.
Our Dandy sucks.
He could stand to learn
a thing or two from theirs!
[DANDY] What in the--?
Hey, check out this centerfold!
Her underarm
hair is in 3-D!
[QT] Are you
okay, Meow?
What happened?
[MEOW] QT! I was just
reading my comic book
when these weirdos
popped out of it!
[QT] Then it's possible
that they're comic
book characters!
[DANDY] Here's Dandy! Oh ah.
Huh?
[DANDY] Am I nuts or did he
just say his name's Dandy?
[DANDY] Hey, old man!
You got a star-shaped birthmark?
[DANDY] Huh?
I've gotta gather
all eight of the heroes
with star-shaped
birthmarks in order
to defeat the evil demon king!
Okay.
[QT] Listen Dandy.
I don't trust these
guys one bit.
They seem
kinda sketchy.
What if they're the
demon king's henchmen?
What?
[DANDY] Now that
you mention it.
I think you're right, QT!
That guy definitely
looks like Demon King
Black Cat's second
cousin twice removed!
Huh?
[MEOW] Oh no!
Don't tell me you
scoundrels have come here
to steal our
Miracle Heartful Balls!
Your what?
[QT] I assure you,
we have no intention
of touching your balls.
[DANDY] Why, you!
You don't think you
can fool me, do you?
I know you're related to
the Demon King somehow!
No. Wait! I'm not!
[DANDY C] That's it!
You're goin' down!
[MEOW] This kid's
tryin' to kill me!
Whoa! QT!
[NARRATOR] The "stray hair"
Dandy pulled is called
a cosmic string,
more commonly referred to
as a dimensional fray.
This string-like
domain is a remnant
of a phase defect at
a certain point in space.
Whenever someone
pulls on a cosmic string,
a doorway leading to a
parallel universe is opened.
There are an infinite
number of universes,
and within them,
every conceivable possibility
has become a reality.
Allow me to give you
some examples.
In one universe,
Dandy and his crew
are mobile suit pilots.
However, in another universe.
Space Ninja Dandy--
--is at your service.
[MEOW] Space Ninja Art:
Earth Style Jutsu!
Meow-bow-wow!
[HONEY] Space Kunoichi.
Mistress Honey!
[QT laughs]
[QT] Ninja Art!
Substitution Jutsu! QT!
[NARRATOR] They're
a space ninja team.
And in another,
he's Space Inspector Dandy.
In yet another,
he's Big Dandy.
She-Dandy.
Mascot Dandy.
Bearbrick Dandy.
Triangle Dandy.
While some may be
quick to label
them "counterfeits"
or "doubles,"
that's not the case.
They are each the
genuine Dandy and crew
of their particular universe.
We're finally
back home, baby.
[MEOW] Is it just me,
or does somethin' feel
kinda off about the place?
[SMALL QT] Intruders detected!
Intruders detected!
[LARGE QT] Exterminating.
[MEOW] Dang it! This is
the wrong universe, too?
[DANDY] Cut it out, QT.
These men are not our enemies.
[BOTH QTs] Understood, Dandy.
[QT] Dandy?
He's just a kid!
[DANDY] Sorry about that.
I'll call him off.
He's got a defense system
installed to protect me.
Stand down, QT.
[BOTH QTs] Defense
system deactivating.
Let me guess,
you guys're Dandy,
Meow, and QT, right?
Geez. You must've
pulled a cosmic string.
[MEOW] 'Scuse me.
Who am I in this universe?
Meow, right?
You're in the box.
You see, our Meow
is an alien
called a Schrödingerian.
[MEOW] Oh.
Until you open the box,
you never know if
he'll be alive or dead.
They're tricky that way.
[DANDY] He's dead.
Now he's alive.
Dead.
Alive.
Creepy little fur ball!
Watch it.
If you don't quit teasin'
the Schrödingerian
like that he's
liable to bite you.
It's them again!
[QT] What's happening?
Every week
our ship is attacked
by the mysterious Gorillian.
[BOTH QTs] We are surrounded.
Now what? I know!
You guys can take us
back to your universe!
[QT] We've gotta hurry and
find a cosmic string to pull!
Bea-B-Bea!
Gel-Gel-Gel!
Oh. B-B-B-Bea!
Gel! Gel! Gel!
Bea. B-Bea
Gel!
Let's go!
[QT] Oh thank goodness,
we made it back safely.
Huh?
Uh?
[HONEY] What's going on?
I don't get it.
[DANDY]
Hey! What do we got here?
Looks like we
overdid it a little.
[NARRATOR]
Several days have passed
since the Aloha Oe
was taken over
by the various Dandys,
Meows, and QTs.
Let's see how things are going.
Hey! Go back, baby!
I wasn't done readin' that page!
Dammit, lady me!
No scavenging the fridge
without my permission!
[QT] What do you guys
think you're doing?
Don't use my charger
without asking first!
[QT] Transform!
[QT] Are you even
listening to me?
[NARRATOR] As you can see,
our heroes are
living in utter chaos.
I'm so stressed out.
There's only one thing to do.
A trip to Boobies'll
take the edge off, baby!
Yoo-hoo! Dandy!
Welcome back! Oh my!
[HONEY] Wow, that's crazy!
Who knew you
had all these siblings?
Siblings?
We look alike?
No.
I don't think any
of you look alike,
but there's something
about all of you
that's kinda Dandy.
You know what I mean?
Who, these guys?
Sure. Whatever you say.
Let's drink to us!
[DUPLICATES] To us!
[NARRATOR] Just as
everything seemed to be
getting better for our heroes,
they began to notice some
strange abnormalities.
[MALE BROADCAST A] Be sure to
stop by your local supermarket
and try our new beef flavor
"Space Chicken Ramen" today!
Huh? Beefy chicken?
[MALE BROADCAST B]
Good afternoon.
We now bring you breaking
news from this time last year.
[QT] Huh?
Hold up.
There's no coffee
in my Café au lait,
and no curry in my curry rice.
What's goin' on?
Something's not right.
[NARRATOR] That's
putting it lightly.
The world was now filled
with inconsistencies.
Posted bills
forbidding posted bills.
Cold, hot coffee.
Strange hairstyles.
Jobs with seven days
off per week.
[MEOW] Hey, where
are you goin'?
[DANDY] Somewhere.
[NARRATOR] Full-tilt
half-assedness.
[QT] Hey, where
did you go?
[DANDY] 35.4330 degrees
latitude. I think.
Precise malarkey.
Frantic relaxation.
And then the last straw.
[MUSCLE HONEYS]
Welcome to Boobies!
We hope you like
what you see, boys!
[DANDY] It's all over.
The boobies are gone.
[QT] I wonder what
happened to cause
the world to become
so contradictory.
[NARRATOR] Apparently,
the cosmic string
had been pulled too many times,
creating a distortion
in the universe.
[NARRATOR A] No, no, no
that ain't what happened.
It's like this--
[NARRATOR B] All we know for
sure is there's a distortion.
We've got no idea
where it came from.
[NARRATOR C] Speak for yourself!
You see, the universe is sitting
on top of a giant brain--
[NARRATOR D] That's got
to be the dumbest theory
I've ever heard, ya moron.
[MEOW] Aw, crap. One was enough.
[DANDY] This sucks.
Yeah, every time we turn
around there's more of 'em.
What do we do?
[QT] If only there were
a way to get them back
to their own worlds, you know,
like pulling a cosmic string.
Yeah, that's a great idea,
but good luck tryin'
to find one, buddy.
What in the--?
[QT] Ask and you
shall receive.
Yeah, they've become
pretty common, baby.
It's gonna be tough
to pick which one to pull.
[QT] I'm not surprised
that they've started popping
up all over the place.
You know, since every
point in the universe
is basically a boundary surface
for other-dimensional spaces.
At least, that's what
it says on Wikipedia.
Oh really?
Whoa.
Geez. Not again.
Yowza. Guys, don't
touch the strings.
Hey, me, didn't you
hear what I said?
Don't touch the mother--
[NARRATOR] And now,
several months have passed
since that fateful day.
[NARRATOR A]
What're you talkin' about?
It's been a few weeks!
[NARRATOR B] C'mon.
It's been exactly two minutes.
[NARRATOR C]
That was a second ago!
Shut up!
[DANDY] You shut up, dumbass!
[DANDY] What'd you say?
[QT] Whoa, there are
even more of us here now.
[MEOW] It's gettin'
hard to breathe.
[QT] Somebody's pulling cosmic
strings behind our back.
[MEOW] We were at max
capacity ten Meows ago!
[DANDY] Okay, it's time to
hold a meeting of the Dandys!
So, what's on your mind, babe?
We're not gonna
get anywhere
like this, you guys!
You dumby.
Why you gotta
freak out over
every little thing?
If we don't do
something we'll
be stuck here!
True. Good point, man.
There's no way I
could live in a world
without Boobies.
Whatcha think? Meow?
Well, if you ask me--
Shut your trap!
He was talkin' to
me, ya furry freak!
Ugh. Either one's fine.
Mr. Dandy, if you'll make
me this universe's Meow,
I'll be the
best cat ever!
Ain't happenin'!
And for the last
time, I'm not a cat!
I have an idea.
Why don't we try
to think up a way
to pull all of the
universes together?
Easier said
than done, kid.
I wanna die.
What?
[DANDY] Yowza.
Who brought Captain Emo onboard?
[MEOW] The guy reeks
of depression.
[QT] If he wants to die so badly
then why is he sipping
on a nutritional drink?
Kinda hypocritical
if you ask me.
[creepy robotic meows]
What the hell?
It's a monster!
That thing; it's mewing!
If so, then, that guy's--
Yeah. He's the Meow
from my universe.
[creepy robotic meows]
[EMO DANDY] That's it.
That's all he ever says.
I've got a translator but
it doesn't understand him.
I can't tell what that
nightmare's sayin' either!
Lemme ask you,
what do you think
that Meow is carrying
underneath his arm?
[QT] Uh. It looks
like a helmet to me.
[EMO DANDY] You'd
think so right?
But you wanna hear
something strange?
I've never seen him put it on.
[QT] Okay, then what's it for?
[EMO DANDY] That's what
I'd like to know.
[QT] Look! Someone
else has shown up.
It's a person in some
kinda space suit.
No. You don't think he's--
That old codger is your QT?
[screechy whiny QT]
I am not an old codger!
I'm a state-of-the-art
robot, thank you!
Watch!
Aw crap, damn it!
[EMO DANDY] Imagine how
much my life sucks.
I'm stuck with a scary lookin'
guy I can't understand,
who carries around a helmet
that I have never seen him wear,
and a sickly, old codger
in a pink unitard,
who insists that
he's actually a robot.
[creepy robotic meows]
[screechy whine]
[QT] No wonder the guy's emo.
That's gotta be miserable.
[EMO DANDY] I wanna die.
Let's hurry and find
a way outta this mess.
No joke.
If it weren't for
the cosmic strings,
this never
woulda happened.
It's their fault.
Damn them!
We've gotta destroy them.
The question is: how?
You wanna burn 'em?
[EMO DANDY]
It's worth a shot.
Think it'll work?
Let's try it.
If this works,
everyone'll go back
to their universes
while we stay here.
[MEOW] I hope you're
right about that.
[QT] But what if it doesn't work
and something terrible happens?
Then what'll we do?
C'mon, QT.
Y'know I'm not the
type to think ahead.
We'll just have to wait and see.
[QT] I should've known.
[sonic blast]
What?
[NARRATOR] And so,
the cosmic string vanished,
and once again the universe
had only one Dandy and crew.
[NARRATOR] However.
[screechy whiny QT]
[creepy robotic meows]
[EMO DANDY] I wanna die.
[NARRATOR] All future
episodes of Space Dandy
will feature this cast.
♪
[NARRATOR] Space Dandy.
He's a dandy guy.
In space.
He combs the galaxy
like his pompadour,
on the hunt for aliens.
Planet after
planet, he searches,
discovering bizarre
new creatures
both friendly, and not.
These are the
spectacular adventures
of Space Dandy and his
brave space crew in space.
I wanna die.
[UKULELEMAN] I'm sorry but
I just can't take it anymore.
You have no idea
how shocked I am.
All I wanted was for you to
listen to my cheerful tones.
Next time, "There's Music
in the Darkness, Baby."
Please watch.