[POE] I was lonely for decades.
[POE] For centuries. For eons.
Okay.
[resonanting thrums and squeals]
[DANDY] You're kinda weird.
I guess they
just ditched me here.
Yeah, real nice!
Oh, right.
Meow! QT! Anyone? Hello?
What's wrong
with those guys?
Would it kill 'em to
answer when I call--?
[DANDY] Huh...?
[DANDY] Oh...
Hey, lady.
Where are we, exactly?
The corner of everywhere
and nowhere, you dig?
Well, that
wasn't freaky. What gives?
I don't even know
how I ended up here.
I can't
remember anything!
Hey!
You're like a
person, aintcha?
Say would you mind
giving a stranger
a ride into the nearest town?
[DANDY] Not to
sound like a jerk.
But walking here myself
would'a been whole a lot faster.
What the hell?
Someone's gotta be around.
Who's this guy?
I'm your someone.
Huh?
You asked for a someone
just now, did you not?
Whatever, just
point me towards a kitchen!
Dandy is so hungry.
In that case, let us away
to a quality restaurant.
Huh? There's a
restaurant here?
Ferdinand, at your service!
A pleasure to make
your acquaintance.
Hey, are you
a rare alien or what?
Oh. I'm rare
insofar as that.
My skills as a medium
are rendered well.
Of course they are.
Tell me your
thoughts on it.
I find it vexatious.
What topic hath
earned your enmity?
[NOBLEMAN] Life is a
caravanserai of delights,
but death is our destined lot.
The only difference is
for how long one eludes it.
You voice all
this to what end?
[NOBLEMAN] If the grave is one's
only aspiration and guarantee,
then life is a bleak path
with little to recommend it.
Wherefore this
brief season of breath, milady?
What reason compels us to live?
[chuckles]
You would laugh?
For what reason?
The gall of such conceit.
[NOBLEMAN] Huh?
Tiny forms of
life there are
which 'scape the naked eye.
They do not demand
"wherefore?" of the cosmos.
[gasps]
[NOBLEWOMAN] Go die,
if life without reason is
so loathsome to you.
[FERDINAND]
Your feast awaits you.
Whoa! I'm likin' it!
The hell'd you
put in my food?
Thought I was gonna bite
the big one just then!
You were taking
big bites, after all!
Death ain't a joke, baby.
But life is certainly one.
And I'd wager there are times
when you'd be hard-pressed
to discern one from the other.
Huh?
Take your evening slumber.
Your spirit endures, having
cast off your mortal coil.
Be still!
What?
Those are the
Night Porters above.
It'll be a bother if
they lay eyes on you.
[FERDINAND] So sorry about
your meal going south.
[DANDY] It's not gonna give me
flashbacks this time, right?
[FERDINAND]
Leave it to me, friend.
[CORNET] How do I live my life?
That's the question of the hour.
[GREGORIANS in sing-song voices]
Aren't asking that,
and how to die when life
is over the same thing?
[CORNET] Course not!
And who wants
to ask about dying?
Stuff like that's a
waste of breath, I say!
[GREGORIANS] Want or not,
better ask while you can
because it will happen to all.
[CORNET] I'm just saying,
if I get preoccupied with it,
then I might as well
keel over right now!
[GREGORIANS] Holding death
at a coward's distance
does not allow it
a spot in your mind.
Mortal you are.
Time to come to better
terms with your fate.
[CORNET] No, that's crazy.
[GREGORIANS] Entropy is the
end of all creatures left
unto their own devices.
Death is our lot,
and the lot of everyone
that we hold dear.
So think or do not think
about the end of your own life.
Anon it comes to you so take
your pleasure while you may.
Ah! All right! Ramen!
Not cool, ramen.
Hey, c'mon!
Get your own food!
They dancing, or what?
You know, this
planet is kinda screwy.
First of all the
people are all nuts,
and then the food
won't stop teasing me.
It's candy!
Now we're talking!
Oh, you wanna
eat us, is that the idea?
I ain't scared of
a candy-ass like you!
That's right!
Back off, sucker!
Maybe I'll wait
for dinner after all.
Bird.
[soothing guitar music]
[DANDY] Bravo, baby.
[LUTENER in echoey voice]
Who are you, down there?
You can really hear my song?
What'd you say?
[FERDINAND] Look alive!
Run for it!
Son-of-a--!
[high-tempo guitar music]
You are a creature
of much unfamiliarity to me.
Huh? Back atcha!
My gaze has never
fallen upon one so odd as this.
Oh yeah?
Well go high-five a mirror.
[NIGHT PORTER] You're an
affront to the natural order.
As a result, you cannot
be permitted to stay.
Prepare yourself for
imminent termination.
Whoa! Gimme a sec.
No reflection!
Are you guys dead?
I didn't sign on for this!
Time for a
crash-course in ghosts!
You are not alive!
You follow?
Why aren't you
all freaked out?
[FERDINAND] Goodness me.
Our new addition
is quite unhinged.
[DANDY] Uh, why'm
I getting carried in a boat?
Your naiveté is refreshing,
though I'm surprised that
you honestly don't know.
This is your
funeral procession, Dandy.
Okay. Seems legit.
Huh?!!
It shouldn't come as
that huge of a shock.
For all of your whining,
are you actually hungry?
[DANDY] I should be.
I mean, I'm a couple meals
behind, but I guess I'm not.
Here's another one for
you--you've been awake
since you got here, but
are you tired in the least?
[DANDY] He's right.
I'm not tired at all.
In fact, I'm wide awake.
[FERDINAND] It's a
common mistake.
The newly-dead don't
pick up on that fact,
and keep eating and sleeping
as though they
still have a need to.
They go through the motions,
blithely assuming
they're still alive.
[FERDINAND]
Some poor souls, it takes them
hundreds of years
to accept the truth.
And if one is
sublimely unfortunate,
they never acknowledge
their demise at all.
[FERDINAND] You know,
I wouldn't worry about it.
You'll come around.
Yes. All in good time.
[QT] I'm detecting something
up ahead on Planet Limbo.
If these numbers are right,
this creature is off the charts!
But, I checked the
registry just now,
and nothing lives there.
Use your head!
That just means whatever's
on the surface
must be super-rare!
You better
not be sending us
on a wild goose chase again!
[QT] Don't mind me--I'll
just cry in the corner.
You do not wanna deal
with my starvation hairballs!
C'mon, guys!
Would it kill you
to have more faith
in your fearless leader?
[DANDY] Too much faith!
Too much faith!
[QT] We must've accidentally
flown into a dark nebula!
They're super-dangerous!
[MEOW] Shouldn't we
go around crap like this?
[QT] Well, the radar's
been broken for a while now.
Looking out the
window usually works.
[DANDY] You piece of junk!
What is this thing?
[FERDINAND] Your own personal
"black box," as it were.
Many people are fuzzy on the
details of their own death.
Such devices help
bring them up to speed.
Do you accept
your demise now?
As you've noticed, this
is a planet of the dead,
so you'll fit right in.
[DANDY] So, that header
onto the control panel,
that punched my card?
[FERDINAND] So to speak,
yes--though I'm not sure
my telling you that is
going to convince you any.
Sorry 'bout that.
Here, hunger and age
are nothing you
have to worry about.
There are no jobs.
You're free to spend your
time however you want.
[FERDINAND] Come on!
You're the man of the hour!
It's time to make merry
and trip the light fantastic!
"Make merry"?
Right!
There's nothing to lose here,
because you are already dead!
It's a world where
sadness doesn't exist.
No sadness, huh?
I'd buy that for a wulong.
Wait, no I wouldn't!
You can't have happiness
without sadness--
they're like cousins
or some junk!
I ain't giving up my good times!
I wanna eat and
drink stuff! Gimme that!
I'm going to Boobies!
You can take this
funeral and shove it!
Freaky. Hey, girl!
Can you drive this thing?
'Cause, I need to get
outta here pronto!
Floor it, or whatever you do!
Which way?
[DANDY] Uh?
[DANDY] Down will go to
hell with the kinda luck
I've been having,
so-- Up, please!
Huh? We're at
the last stop already?
I just wanna go
back to my old life.
Killing time on a
rock full of ghosts
ain't the Dandy way, baby.
I gotta be me!
You want to go back?
Yeah.
[POE] This is a place
between worlds. A way station.
This whole world is a place
for the dead to find repose.
Only one living being remains,
longing for
companionship. It's me.
[DANDY] That's pretty deep.
Are you a goddess or something?
[POE] No goddess I, but
something simpler to comprehend.
I am the Planet Limbo.
[POE] I am its
curiosity personified.
The Night Porters, on the
other hand, are its logic.
Years ago, in another time,
this was a vibrant,
living world.
But then, its inhabitants
fell to fighting,
and used their wondrous
creations to kill each other.
[POE] Of course,
the war had no victors.
Ghosts are all that remain.
[POE] The souls
of our dead thrum
with a certain magnetism.
Wandering souls are
drawn to this place,
lured in by their essence.
I was lonely for decades.
For centuries. For eons.
There was no one.
But then you arrived.
Impossible.
You're the one--!
It can't be. How could it?
Huh? What's up?
[POE] Look.
I can't send you back
to before you perished,
but maybe I can send you
to another dimension.
Another dimension?
[POE] Yes.
Perhaps you can escape to one
in which the dark nebula
didn't signal your end.
It's possible.
I'm kinda
outta my league.
Yes. You will live anew.
But it requires much energy.
To put you back where you
belong I must use all of Limbo.
Wait! But that's--!
Why'd you do it?
I had to.
Because I love you.
'Kay fair enough.
I mean, I do look pretty
good for a dead guy.
And you're the
prettiest planet ever.
[DANDY] I just
realized something.
Honestly, it kinda
doesn't matter where I go.
Whether
I'm alive or dead.
I'm still pretty dandy.
[QT] We're coming out
of the dark nebula!
And not a moment too soon!
[MEOW] Yeah, no
freakin' kidding!
I thought we were
goners for sure.
[QT] Wait. Where's Dandy?
Ah. Found 'im.
[QT] No way.
[MEOW] We almost died just now,
and there he is, taking a nap?
[QT] Should we wake him up?
[MEOW] Quieter if we don't.
[QT] Yeah, you're right.
[DANDY] All those far away
stars you see shining in space?
They could already be dead.
I'm something of a star in
space myself. Who knows?
Maybe I'm already dead, too.
That's why I say screw it!
Next time, "We're All Fools,
So Let's All Dance, Baby."
See ya' on the dance floor.