[NARRATOR]
Space Dandy.
He's a dandy guy... in space.
He combs the galaxy
like his pompadour,
on the hunt for aliens.
Planet after planet he searches,
discovering bizarre new
creatures both friendly and not.
These are the
spectacular adventures
of Space Dandy and his
brave space crew... in space.
No way.
You actually came--
I can't believe it!
Well, yeah.
I came yesterday,
and I came today, too.
And don't you worry, I'm sure
I'll come tomorrow, baby!
[WAITRESSES squeal]
You are so hot!
[DANDY]
Huh?
[HONEY]
Welcome to Boobies!
[WAITRESSES]
Master Prince!
Hello, there, ladies.
So nice to see you.
[WAITRESSES squeal]
[CHORUS]
♪ Dandy... ♪
Who the hell is this clown?
[QT] You mean you
really don't know?
That's the top-flight
space racer, Prince.
They call him the
Sonic Speed Stud.
He's had a busy year,
what with winning
all of the Grand Prix races
that've been held so far.
[DANDY groans]
[DANDY]
I've decided!
I'm gonna make
my bones as a racer.
[QT &amp; MEOW]
What?
The next race is
coming up soon, right?
I'm gonna enter and crush it!
Yeah. Good luck.
[QT] You can't just decide
to become a top-flight racer.
It's not that simple.
Ha! I was already
tops back in the day.
I raced the toughest courses out
there at least a dozen times.
I cut through the competition
like they were nothing.
The Speed of Light Jackknife.
That's what they called me.
[QT] Funny, I've never
heard any of this before.
Yeah, seriously, dude.
I thought you said you
were a surfer or something.
Hello, hello!
Welcome to the crowd
and the folks back home!
The 82,342nd Magellanic Nebulae
Grand Prix is about to begin!
Before things get going,
let's take a look at the course.
Today's course
requires the racers
to pass through nine gates
interspersed through space.
Their goal: the finish
line past the final gate.
The key to staying in the race
is to pass through
every single gate.
Entrants who don't
will be disqualified.
Also note that warps
and warp-like technologies
are not allowed.
Anything else goes, including
noogies and mortal violence.
That's right: It's a no holds
barred crazy death race!
[CHORUS]
Dandy.
And now, let's meet the racers
you'll want to keep
a close eye on today!
The dauntless speed enthusiast!
The Masked Racer!
The savage monster pair!
The Twins!
Next up, the ever-tantalizing,
Crusher Girl!
Triks eth rednu si terces eth
Whoa!
Nothing to see here,
boys and girls.
She's just demonstrating
some fighting poses!
And finally.
In the pole position, the man
you've all been waiting for.
It's Prince!
Tell us, Prince.
How do you feel
going into this race?
[PRINCE]
I'm just here for fun.
Racing's not about
winning or losing for me.
[DANDY scoffs]
Wow, he's even more
full of it than you are.
[PRINCE]
Oh.
Are you entering, too?
With that beat-up old machine?
Yeah. You got a
problem with that?
'Cause I can take you in
two seconds flat, ya know?
Two seconds! Two!
[QT] Actually, it's
physically impossible
to finish the race
in two seconds.
--[ZED] Look at this!
--[QT] What?
[ZED] Master Prince, this is
possibly the oldest robot
I've ever encountered.
I think it's what
your grandmother
would have called "an antique."
[QT]
Excuse me?
[SQUEAK]
What's going on, Master Prince?
Why did we stop?
Hey, look. He's got
a rat sidekick. Lame!
Watch what you
say or I'll sue you.
Defamation of character.
Now, why don't
you shut your mouth
and go find some smelly fish
to eat, you dirty cat bastard?
What a treat!
It looks like we have all
the members of CCH here today!
The cool genius driver, Prince!
The clever alien lawyer, Squeak!
And the high-spec robot, Zed!
Put 'em together,
and what d'ya get?
C.C.H.!
In complete contrast,
we have this other trio: BBP!
Blockhead, Bonehead,
and Pinhead!
Put 'em together,
and what d'ya get?
B.B.P.!
Shut the hell up, would ya'?
[CHORUS]
Dandy.
[GEL]
Bea.
What are you doing?
Having a picnic?
Oh. Hello, Doctor.
I've been desperately scouring
the stars for Dandy day in
and day out, and this is how
you see fit to occupy your time?
Hey, would you stop stuffing
your face and listen to me?
You're not going to locate Dandy
by sitting in front of
the TV, munching on--
Oh!
[GEL]
Hmm?
[BEA]
I think I found him, Doctor.
[ANNOUNCER]
And now, at long last,
the moment of truth has arrived!
The Magellanic Nebulae Grand
Prix is only seconds away!
[RACE QUEEN]
5. 4. 3. 2. 1.
And go!
[ANNOUNCER]
Whoa!
Prince shoots right
to the front of the pack.
That's some seriously
studly speed!
We have no choice.
It's time to use
our last resort.
[QT] What? But the
race only started
a few seconds ago, Dandy.
[DANDY]
Let's go!
Caught a big one!
Harnessing the speed of others.
That's what my secret attack
"Slipstream Running"
is all about, baby.
[QT]
Isn't that kind of cheating?
[DANDY]
Is it?
Lleheht tahw.
Ohw?
Gip saym ffo teg!
Safe rouy shurc lie!
[DANDY, MEOW, and QT scream]
[GEL]
Move quickly, Bea!
We can't let him
get away this time!
[BEA]
Roger!
[ANNOUNCER] It's time
to find out who will be
the first racer to
brave the asteroid field
in hopes of reaching
gate number one!
No surprise there.
It's Prince!
With the usual panache,
Prince executes his
famous cardioidal cornering!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
Almost there...!
And he's through!
And the next racer approaching
the gate is... Unbelievable!
It's the Little Aloha's Dandy.
Whatever move that is,
it seems to be working.
It looks like we may have
a wonder rookie
on our hands here!
[QT]
So you're using the impact
from the missiles to propel our
way through the asteroid field?
It's another one of
my super-secret attacks,
"Moonsault Scrambled
Life Intersection!"
[QT] You know that name
is complete nonsense, right?
Uh-oh! It's looking like
big trouble in Little Aloha!
[PRINCE] Incredible.
I was certain he would
be out of the race by now.
[ZED]
It's only beginner's luck.
You needn't concern
yourself with him.
No.
[ZED]
Pardon?
Dandy. That's his
name, isn't it?
It's more fun if he
does put up a good fight.
[CHORUS]
Dandy.
[ANNOUNCER] And now approaching
the second gate is...
Yes! Once again, it's Prince.
Using his legendary
four-wheel drift,
he easily clears the checkpoint.
Coming in right behind him,
we have... the Giant Turtle!
Oooh. I don't see how it's
going to fit through the gate.
Aha! A clever move!
I bet the other racers
aren't too happy about this.
[MASKED RACER grunts]
[CHORUS]
Dandy.
[QT] We're way behind the
other competitors, huh?
What? We caught up?
All right. Time to
use our last resort!
[QT]
Now I'm confused.
Didn't we already use it?
Wow-ow-ow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
[DANDY] Blowing up
other people's machines
to get a burst of speed.
I call it special attack:
"Flying Bomber Rumba!"
[QT] But aren't we just
blowing ourselves up, too?
[CHORUS]
Dandy.
[ANNOUNCER] The third
gate is a rotator.
Contestants must match their
speed to it, or it's DQ time.
But, of course,
Prince is through!
However, up ahead is a nasty
surprise just for the leader.
[ZED]
Prince!
[PRINCE]
That makes sense.
If they don't
handicap me somehow,
I'll win too easily, and
the race won't be as exciting.
[ANNOUNCER] And here comes the
Masked Racer in second place.
He's gaining speed very quickly!
But wait!
Oh, no! The Masked Racer
exits the race with a bang!
Who will be the next racer
to attempt the gate?
Get ready, Dandy.
Today is the day
that I capture you--
Hey, hold your fire!
I'm not participating
in the stupid race!
[ANNOUNCER] The Twins
are making their way
through the third gate.
The contest's leaders are now
more than halfway through
this perilous racecourse.
The sixth gate is just ahead and
may be the most difficult yet.
Who will it be?
Is Prince still in the lead?
[ZED]
Oh, no!
[DANDY]
Heh-heh...
Yee-haw!
What an undignified simpleton!
Hey. How're you?
Honey? What are you--?
[HONEY giggles]
I thought entering
a race sounded fun! Yay!
[DANDY]
Hey!
Oh, yeah?
You wanna dance?
What the--?
[BRAIN TWINS gasp]
[CHORUS]
Dandy.
[ANNOUNCER] Only the best
of the best stand a chance
in the race's final leg.
[PRINCE]
Hey, Dandy!
I'm sorry. It's alright if
I call you Dandy, isn't it?
It's Space Dandy to you.
Heh. I just thought
you should know
I've never lost
a race in my life.
If I really try, it'll be
over for you in a second.
I'll stop gloating, though.
It's beneath me.
[DANDY]
Hey, Prince.
[PRINCE]
Hmm?
You can go suck on it,
ya arrogant little cockroach.
[PRINCE huffs]
[ZED]
Prince, look out!
[PRINCE grunts]
What is this?
Where are we?
My hair!
[ZED] Forget that man.
We have to keep going.
Evolution clearly missed a
step when it produced him.
Dandy! Nobody makes
a fool of me like that.
I am going to end you and
the universe will thank me.
A creature like you
has no place in it.
[CHORUS]
Dandy.
[ANNOUNCER] It's about
time for the contestants
to make a pit stop.
The swiftness of
the refueling process
can greatly affect
the race's outcome.
[SQUEAK] It appears
the events of the race
have severely unsettled
Prince's state of mind.
Well then, I'll just have to be
prepared to take certain steps.
[SQUEAK chuckles]
[ANNOUNCER] The leader
heading into the pit area
is none other than the race's
ever-surprising dark horse:
Dandy in the Little Aloha.
[MEOW]
Um, let's see...
I put this here.
And then I, uh... Huh...
Got a race to win, here!
[MEOW] Rushing me isn't
going to help, you know!
What the-- Huh?
[DANDY]
C'mon, what's taking so long?
[MEOW] Please calm down
and give me a second to think!
Okay...
[ANNOUNCER]
The next group of racers
are starting to
arrive at the pit.
They're heading in
around the same time,
but who will be
the first one out?
Aw, damn it. Meow!
[ANNOUNCER]
Here he is at last!
It's Prince!
This is important, troops.
We're counting on
you to get it right.
[ROBOTS make noise]
[ANNOUNCER]
Did you see that pit crew work?
Probably not if you blinked!
Prince comes back from behind!
Will Prince be crowned
the winner, after all?
[DANDY]
Damn cat!
I'm trying, really!
All I have to do is
fill up the tank, right?
[ANNOUNCER] They're returning
to the course, but where--
There he is!
Dandy's out of the pit,
but his lead is gone.
He is dead last!
[DANDY] Damn it.
Time to use our last resort!
[QT]
Again? Seriously?
[DANDY] I'll fire all
the bombs we reloaded
and use the impact to get
us a serious speed boost.
[QT] What? That might
speed us up,
or it might blast us
into teeny-tiny pieces.
Doncha know, QT?
This is the way of the world.
A man's gotta do
what a man's gotta do,
even if that means being
blasted into teeny-tiny pieces.
[QT]
Dandy...
But now's not really
one of those times.
Well, that's good.
[QT and DANDY yell]
[QT and DANDY groan]
[DANDY] Uhh... I didn't
mean to do that.
[ANNOUNCER]
Oh, my. What is that?
Niaga meth ton?
[QT]
Whoa-whoa-whoa...!
What'd he do?
[ZED]
That entire crew is insane.
[ANNOUNCER]
Here we are at last,
in front of the ninth
and final gate!
And it's Prince through first.
Followed by Dandy.
And it looks like--yes, yes,
it's the Boobie-mobile!
And then--what?
Who's that?
It looks like a gorilla.
There was a gorilla in the race?
He's catching up.
Yes, the gorilla has
passed the Boobies!
Get us moving faster!
We need to reach Dandy!
Yes, sir. Activating
hyper-dimensional turbo.
All right! Good job, Bea!
We passed Dandy!
Um, Doctor, was passing him
actually what we wanted to do?
Oh...
[GEL screams]
[QT]
It may be time for us
to accept that we're
going to lose to Prince.
Ditch all the baggage!
[QT]
What?
[DANDY] We need to be
as light as possible!
[QT]
That wasn't nice!
Impossible!
Got you now!
You did it.
You're the first
opponent I've faced
who's ever pushed me
all the way to the edge.
[ZED]
That wasn't nice!
[ANNOUNCER] The first two
racers are approaching
the finish line now,
and it is a dead heat!
Who will be the
Grand Prix winner?
Amazing. I have never
seen such speed!
[PRINCE]
I--I feel funny inside.
[ANNOUNCER]
Unbelievable!
They have exceeded
the sixth space velocity!
[PRINCE]
What is this feeling?
It can't be...
But maybe, maybe it is...
Maybe this is...
Love.
[beeping]
[NARRATOR] In that moment,
something truly extraordinary
happened to Prince.
Dandy plowed into him
from behind at the
seventh space velocity.
The bomb that had been planted,
the fluctuating electric charge,
the magnetic flux density,
the metric slug...
The addition of unknown fuel...
All of these factors
were brought together
in a miraculous,
unprecedented cosmic accident
and then... the steamed
dumpling burst open!
[PRINCE grunts]
[DANDY grunts]
Where's Dandy?
He's not here!
[NARRATOR]
Yes, Dandy is here.
He is in a space
faster than thought.
A domain that mere
mortals cannot even
begin to understand.
[NARRATOR] He accelerated
to a speed faster than light
and fell out of time.
Until, finally, he arrived
in the far distant future.
And when he woke on a world
that exists at a time
five point six
seven billion years
from this moment,
what he saw was...
Dan... dy...
[DANDY] The following episode
will be brought to you
by a cat who won't bathe,
a planet full of scrap metal,
a possessed robot,
fleas, and a dog.
Next time, an
unexpectedly sad story,
"The Lonely Pooch Planet, Baby."
See ya then.