[NARRATOR]
Space Dandy.
He's a dandy guy... in space.
He combs the galaxy
like his pompadour,
on the hunt for aliens.
Planet after planet he searches,
discovering bizarre new
creatures both friendly and not.
These are the
spectacular adventures
of Space Dandy and his
brave space crew... in space.
[GEL]
These time-space distortions
indicate the existence
of a tremendous
amount of energy.
Interesting. However,
if such power truly exists
in this universe
then that would mean--
[BEA] Dr. Gel. I really hate
to interrupt you, sir.
But you've been working so hard
and I thought you
could use a break.
Perhaps it'll bring you clarity?
As they say,
"All work and no play
leads to a
monotonous existence."
Sorry! Please forgive
my clumsiness, sir!
Ah, Pyonium.
Dr. Gel.
Admiral!
Um. How can we help you?
[PERRY] How many
times must I remind you
to check in regularly?
These long distance
space-phone charges
are nothing to
sneeze at, Doctor!
Hmm?
He's been deep in thought
like this for days now.
With all of his bungling,
it's easy to forget that he's
actually a gifted scientist.
Well, you certainly can't
tell by looking at him.
[PERRY]
Since the Doctor is indisposed,
I'll let you handle
this matter, Bea.
We are launching
a full-scale assault
to conquer planet Lagado.
[BEA]
For what reason?
That planet is nothing more
than one giant library, sir.
To teach them a lesson.
No one harasses
the great Admiral Perry
about an overdue book
and gets away with it!
I'm going to make them pay!
I can't help but feel as
though there's something
vital missing from this formula.
[SCARLET]
For the last time,
will you just show me
what's in the box, already?
[DANDY]
What'd I just tell ya, babe?
You can't open it,
'cause if you do,
we're gonna
forget what's inside.
[SCARLET]
But if I don't,
I'll never know what it
was in the first place.
[DANDY] I'm tellin' ya,
once you open that box
it'll be like none'a this
ever happened! Ya dig?
I'm sorry. I don't understand
a word of what you just said.
You're killin' me. Okay,
I'll go over it one more time.
I busted my butt
to capture the super-rare
alien that's inside that box.
The problem is if you
look at it you'll forget it,
which is why nobody's discovered
the damn thing 'til now.
So, how did you manage
to capture this alien,
when everyone else forgets that
they've ever even seen it?
Well obviously baby,
I've forgotten that.
We worked really
hard for this one!
So, so hard!
[QT] Unfortunately, I have no
memory of how we captured it.
Yeah, that part is kinda' fuzzy.
[SCARLET]
Enough. I'm opening it.
[DANDY]
No, you can't!
Didn't you hear what
I said, woman? I'm serious!
If you open that box,
we're gonna forget
everything that's happened!
[SCARLET] Then tell me this, if
it makes you forget everything,
then why do you still
remember that we'll forget?
Whoa.
Lemme think.
[SCARLET]
Only one way to find out.
We'll never know unless we open
the box and see what's inside!
No!
[DANDY]
Give it! Give it!
Um, Dandy?
Wha--? Oh. What's up Scarlet?
Is there something
that I can help you with?
Yeah, I brought this rare
alien in for you to check out.
[QT] It's weird; I have
this faint recollection
of capturing something.
Yeah, me too.
I got this hazy feeling
like we made the
discovery of the century.
It looks like a box to me.
It is kind of boxy.
What could possibly make
you think that it's an alien?
Hold up.
What the heck is this?
[SCARLET]
How should I know?
You're the one
who brought it here.
[GEL] If I take
the square root plus B
and deduct it from
the total that means
the linear attenuation
coefficient would be--
No, that can't be right.
If A is the intensity of
transmitted energy and B is--
[BEA] Don't you think
attacking the planet
is a tad excessive?
All you have to do
is return the book
and they'll stop harassing you.
[PERRY]
I can't. It was stolen.
I never imagined
thieves would be able
to circumvent our
impeccable security system.
Thankfully, our surveillance
cameras caught them.
Watch closely.
[BEA]
They look familiar.
I feel like we've
dealt with them before.
[PERRY]
Now that you mention it.
[BEA]
I can't put my finger on it.
[PERRY] This whole mess
started because Dr. Gel insisted
I check out a book that he
needed to complete his research.
At this point, the overdue
fine is going to be ridiculous
so I figured it would just be
easier to conquer the planet.
By the way, what was
the title of the book?
[PERRY] "Secrets of the
Cosmos for Dummies".
[DANDY] I'm tellin' you guys,
this book ain't no joke!
I betcha it holds the
secret to somethin'.
[MEOW] Oh yeah?
Somethin' such as what?
[DANDY] Well, you know, like,
some kinda awesome somethin'!
[QT]
Hm.
This doesn't look
like any ancient writing
that I'm familiar with.
Hey tin-for-brains, why dontcha
just give it a quick search?
What's up guys?
What're you lookin' at?
[QT]
I can't "give it a quick search"
because I'd need an
update in order to do that,
and I would need
another update just
to be able to
perform that update,
but the last time I tried to
update it failed miserably
so I don't even remember what
I was talking about anymore.
What's this say?
I can't read the damn thing
but I feel like it's
missin' somethin'.
Oh wow! You guys're taking
a trip to planet Lagado?
Hang on. You can
read that, Honey?
Of course I can, silly,
it's for a sightseeing tour.
"This complimentary
ticket covers three guests
for four days and three nights".
Complimentary?
Y'know, now that you mention it,
it does look like
that's what it says, huh?
Yep, all-you-can-eat,
all-you-can-drink,
and all-you-can-read.
There ain't nothin' more
delicious than free food, baby!
I'm sold!
Planet Lagado,
we're comin' for ya!
[HONEY]
Huh?
Dandy and his buddies
always hang out here.
Why does it feel like
I haven't seen them in a while?
[MALE OPERATOR]
Seventh Fleet deployment
is now complete.
[BEA]
Roger.
Commencing occupation mission.
But I suppose before we do that,
we should give them
the option to surrender.
How dare those insolent
fools hassle the Admiral
about an overdue library book!
We're going to
make them regret it!
[MALE OPERATOR] I'm picking
up a ship, port side aft!
It's warping out!
A ship?
It's the Aloha Oe!
We've got trouble!
Dr. Gel! It's
Space Dandy and his crew!
So it's possible to
control luck via energy?
But how? I still seem
to be missing something.
Listen up! Fire tractor beams!
I want that ship
and its crew captured!
[MALE OPERATOR]
Yes, sir!
Why, Dandy?
You ruin everything.
[MEOW and QT screaming]
What's with the attack?
They invited us!
Aw, man! There's
fleet of ships out there!
It's possible this is a trap.
Nah, these greedy bastards want
all the free grub to themselves!
Whatever you say, Dandy.
Turn us
one-hundred-eighty degrees!
Aloha Beam, stand by!
We're firing back!
[QT] Roger! Turning
one-hundred-eighty degrees!
[QT]
Aloha Beam standing by!
[QT] Energy charge at
one-hundred-and-twenty percent!
Firing in five seconds!
Four! Three! Two! One!
Here we go!
[BEA] There's no way!
He must be insane!
He's challenging the
entire Gogol Space Force
with just one ship?
I'll show him!
Launch missiles at once!
[MALE OPERATOR]
The target has vanished!
Did they warp?
[MALE OPERATOR]
No, it appears they used
an unknown transport device.
What should we do, sir?
Send out the
reconnaissance probe.
[MALE OPERATOR]
Yes, sir!
[BEA] It seems you're smarter
than I thought you were, Dandy.
[DANDY]
Where in the hell are we?
[QT]
The planet Lagado.
[DANDY]
But how did we get here?
[QT] I'm not sure,
but if I had to guess,
I'd say we must've been
forcibly transported.
[MEOW] Maybe that's just how
they welcome their guests?
Let's do this!
I dunno about you guys, but I'm
ready to get my free grub on!
[DANDY]
Check it!
Now that's what I call service!
[DANDY] What's the
deal with this world?
[QT]
Lagado is more commonly known
as the Great Library Planet.
It holds the largest collection
of literature in the universe.
Visitors are allowed
to check out books
just like any other library.
Seems weird we haven't
seen a single life form.
So where's all the free food and
booze that we were promised?
Yeah, no kiddin'.
I ain't interested in the
"all-you-can-read"
part of the deal.
If you found food, you
better share it with us, QT!
C'mon!
[QT]
Hands off!
This data is yummy!
It has such a delicate
yet bold flavor!
It's so delicious
and easily digitized
that my operating
system is in overdrive!
I've never downloaded such
organized and tasty data!
Hey QT, are you sure
you're not bein' hacked?
[QT]
Pathetic living being!
What do you know?
You meat puppets could
never understand the beauty
of this experience!
[DANDY] I don't see how
that paper could be tasty.
[QT]
Of course you don't!
Your sense of taste
is totally different!
Inputting well-organized data
gives me the same sensation
as eating something incredible!
This sucks! Gah!
Isn't there anything
real on this crappy planet?
I don't wanna see pictures of
food in books, I wanna eat it!
I don't wanna see boobs in
centerfolds, I wanna grab 'em!
Man cannot live by data alone!
This is gonna drive me nuts!
And it's all this
damn ticket's fault!
[VOICE]
Insolence!
That's a lot of spears.
[LIBRARY STAFFER] We're so
glad to have you back!
Welcome home,
Great Librarian Alethia
and Deputy Librarian Idea.
You don't happen to go by
one of those names, do ya?
[MEOW]
Uh-uh.
[MALE OPERATOR]
Lagado has yet to respond
to our request
for surrender, sir.
I assume that they're
too terrified to answer.
[MALE OPERATOR] We have images
from the reconnaissance probe!
Good. Let's see them.
[GEL]
That's it!
[BEA]
Doctor Gel?
[GEL]
I can't believe it!
I've finally found
the missing piece
that will complete the formula!
Indeed! It all makes
sense to me now!
I have been asked to inform
you that the Great Librarian
thoroughly enjoyed sharing
this adventure with you.
Our Excellency is thankful
for everything you've done.
Look, I don't mean to be rude
but I got no idea what
you're talkin' about.
[LIBRARY STAFFER] Hmm.
It was foolish of me
to expect such commoners
to grasp the situation.
The book that you see
before you is actually
the librarian of Lagado,
the Great Library Planet.
The greatest of
all banned literature,
also known as "Secrets
of the Cosmos for Dummies".
Huh? I'm not
followin' you, buddy.
[LIBRARY STAFFER]
The Great Librarian Alethia
is what you would
call a book-type alien.
Our Excellency travels the
galaxy studying the truths
of the universe and taking
in vast amounts of knowledge.
The Great Librarian then takes
all of the information gathered
and stores it away within the
pages of this physical form.
And beside Alethia is--
[DEPUTY LIBRARIAN]
The deputy librarian, Idea.
I am the one who
was put in charge
of the recovery operation.
Excellent work.
Thank you for your help.
Huh?
[QT] Oh, I see.
So Alethia's a phantom alien!
A Parasite-type?
No wonder my brain's been foggy.
You're tellin' me we were bein'
manipulated this whole time?
[LIBRARY STAFFER]
Yes, that's correct.
As a Parasite-type alien,
Our Excellency is able to use
other beings' brains to think.
Doing so is much easier than
thinking for oneself, after all.
The Great Librarian tells
me that your rescue mission
to free Our Excellency
from the Gogol Empire
was nothing short of amazing.
But I don't remember
any rescue mission.
[LIBRARY STAFFER]
It happened.
Whether or not you
remember is irrelevant.
Okay, if that's true, then how
come I have no memory of it?
[LIBRARY STAFFER] Erasing and
rewriting the memories of others
is a simple task for
The Great Librarian.
The only shortcoming Our
Excellency has is the inability
to move around unassisted.
Other beings must be manipulated
in order to facilitate movement.
Okay, lemme get this straight,
you're sayin' we kicked ass
on a rescue mission
that we can't remember?
[DEPUTY LIBRARIAN] Yes, that's
precisely what we're saying.
[LIBRARY STAFFER] I have
to be honest with you,
Great Librarian,
I was terribly
disappointed to learn
that you had been checked
out without informing us.
[DEPUTY LIBRARIAN]
Yes, we all were.
In the future, please be sure
to let us know ahead
of time, Your Excellency.
[GIRL'S VOICE] I will.
I'm really sorry.
Whoa. You're just a little girl!
[GIRL LIBRARIAN] I know
I shouldn't go off on my own,
but I wanna see the universe!
When the checkout
request came in,
I went for it 'cause I thought
it might be my only chance!
I know it was wrong of me
to manipulate others,
but I couldn't help myself.
[MEOW]
The poor thing.
I know how she feels.
You don't know nothin'!
This little lady's a
dreamer just like me, Dandy!
[GIRL LIBRARIAN]
I wanted to see all
of the things I had only
ever read about in books!
The fire bandits!
The smash-and-grab thieves!
The demons of hell!
Incantation dancing!
The heads of the crucified
on the prison gates!
[QT] What kind of creepy
books have you been reading?
[LIBRARY STAFFER]
You had us all worried!
[DEPUTY LIBRARIAN] Now, now,
no need to get so upset.
After all, there is some
good that's come out of this.
The Great Librarian fulfilled
her wish to see the universe,
and she gained some wonderful
knowledge along the way.
[QT] "Book-type aliens have
the ability to manipulate
others' brains into
thinking about problems
they find too bothersome
to deal with themselves.
When they retrieve the
answer to the problem,
they gather the energy the
being exerted while thinking,
and feed off of it to survive."
Wow, that's really interesting.
[MEOW] Ya mind
dumbin' it down for us?
[QT] Basically, they're like
unfinished books who feed off
of others in order to fill
their pages with information.
[LIBRARY STAFFER]
Very eloquently put.
Unfortunately, you three
were of absolutely no help
in that regard,
but not to worry.
Allow me to handle this!
I understand!
It all makes sense now!
Doctor Gel?
[MALE OPERATOR]
Multiple weapon strikes
from the planet's surface!
We can't evade them all!
What the--?
[BEA]
What should we do?
Doctor, we have to evacuate!
[GEL] I did it, Bea. I've
figured out what this is.
It's the secret behind the
powerful energy Dandy possesses.
The Secrets of the Cosmos.
The ever-changing truth!
It is so beautiful, and yet--
Let's go, Doctor!
Bea.
I've realized why it
was so difficult
for me to solve
this formula.
Would you like me to tell you?
Maybe later, right
now we need to evacuate!
[GEL]
There's no point.
Doctor?
It's too late.
I've stumbled upon
an amazing truth
that one cannot simply forget.
A knowledge of such power.
That it spells death for
anyone who might attain it!
[screaming]
[GIRL LIBRARIAN] It's a shame
you don't remember the time
we spent together, because
I thoroughly enjoyed myself.
It was the best six months
of my entire existence.
You were with us that
long and we had no clue?
[GIRL LIBRARIAN] I know it's my
duty to erase your memories,
but it breaks my heart to think
that I'll lose the bond
of friendship we shared.
When all of this is over, you
will have no memory of me
or anything that
happened on our journey.
However, I believe I've
come up with a way to leave you
with a token of my affection.
[GIRL LIBRARIAN] From what
I gathered during my time
on the Aloha Oe,
you make your living by
searching for rare aliens.
Please, take that box with you.
Consider it your reward
for a job well done.
But whatever you do,
you mustn't open it early.
[SCARLET]
For the last time,
will you just show me
what's in the box, already?
[DANDY]
You can't open it,
'cause we're gonna
forget what's inside.
[NARRATOR] Contained within the
box was a mysterious videotape.
One which manipulates
the viewer's memory.
It wasn't long before similar
laser discs, cassette tapes,
and floppy disks began
popping up all over the galaxy.
Eventually, they
became jumbled together,
causing a war that dragged
the entire universe into chaos.
Unfortunately,
there is no record
of it ever even happening.
[OLD MAN]
Bee-ma, bee-ma, bee-ma,
bee-ma, be my baby, be my baby.
Be my baby, be my baby.
Bee-ma, bee-ma, be my baby.
Bee-ma, beep-ba, be my baby.