[NARRATOR]
Space Dandy.
He's a dandy guy... in space.
He combs the galaxy
like his pompadour,
on the hunt for aliens.
Planet after planet he searches,
discovering bizarre new
creatures both friendly and not.
These are the
spectacular adventures
of Space Dandy and his
brave space crew... in space.
[GEL]
Bea.
I take it by your
silence that you're close
to finishing my
newest tracking device?
[BEA]
Yes. Now complete with upgrades!
You have several
state-of-the-art capabilities.
It's as cutting edge
as you can get, sir.
Then show me an example.
[sound of record scratching]
[uptempo music plays]
You can enjoy music
to your heart's content.
However, I'm still
trying to figure out
how to play sick beats
without the tracker also firing
missiles at the same time.
No!
What have you done, Bea?
What have you done?
Don't worry, sir. I checked,
and we're the only signs of
life in the immediate area.
Are you sure?
[BEA]
Of course, sir.
I know how angry
the Admiral gets
when Gogol has to pay
out for damage claims.
That man is as
cheap as they come.
So stingy.
[signal buzzes]
[BEA]
Hm?
Doctor Gel?
Your tracker has
located the target.
Already?
Impressive work there, Bea.
Now! Prepare the
ship for warp drive!
[PERRY]
Doctor Gel.
[GEL]
Gaaah!
[PERRY]
What's wrong?
I'm cool.
[PERRY]
"Cool"?
No! No, I said "cruel."
[PERRY] You weren't speaking
ill of me, were you?
No, sir, not me!
And he definitely
didn't call you cheap!
[PERRY]
What was that?
Apologies, sir, we
were just about to warp.
We've found where
you-know-who has been hiding.
[PERRY] Tell me, do you know
what this claim might be about?
I won't permit irresponsible
spending and wastefulness!
Not in this economy!
Yes, I understand that, sir.
Bea?
Okay, the warp is ready to go.
Admiral, we must
take our leave of you!
[PERRY]
What?
How dare you run away?!
You're fired!
[DANDY]
Somethin's off here.
I haven't seen anything,
not even a bug.
C'mon, there's
gotta be some life.
I just downloaded this
free unrecorded alien app,
and it says
there's activity here.
Never trust a free app, cat.
[QT]
Hold on!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Oh my gosh, there are
pieces of old spaceships
all over the place!
Look! What else
could this be?
Whoa! And this...
It looks like part of
an old space station.
Be still, my hard drive.
Wow, my circuits
rarely get this aroused!
Yeah. Speaking of aroused,
I'm pretty hungry.
Please let me find delicious!
Seems like everyone here
is aroused except me.
Don't eat that before
we find out what it is!
Could be a new species.
C'mere, little doggie.
[DOG whimpers]
You're a chick dog.
Isn't that right?
No mistaking that look.
Say what they will about me,
I can always spot a bitch.
[DOG whimpers]
[DANDY barks]
[DANDY whoops]
[DANDY hums]
[DOG whimpers]
[DANDY cries]
Confess! You're an alien,
aren't you, dog?
I see through
this cheap disguise.
Your brown eyes don't fool me!
Wow. Sorry, baby.
[DANDY]
Aww...
[BIG BROTHER]
Can you feel it, Little Brother?
Yes, Big Brother.
I can.
[QT] I think this entire
planet must be made of metal!
Did you guys catch any aliens?
Ah! If by catch, you mean eat?
[QT] Oh. I wonder
what that creature is!
[DANDY]
Good girl.
Alright! Fetch!
Gah! Dandy!
Don't eat that, it might
be a new species of alien!
[DANDY]
Huh?
[QT] He said we think that
might be a new species of alien.
This is just a D-O-G, baby.
A widdle puppy poo.
[QT]
Puppy Poo, indeed.
According to past data, this is
a breed of Husky called a Laika.
Really? And how far in the past
is this past data of yours, huh?
Can we trust it?
[DOG barks]
Lemme try the translator.
[TRANSLATOR]
Woof, woof!
What the pup?
[QT] The wavelengths aren't
matching up correctly.
Aw, don't tell
me you're planning
to allow that canine
to join our crew.
'Cause there's no
vacancy at the space inn!
That's not your call, ya mooch.
And besides, she seems
way more helpful than you.
That's right, girl, now you're a
member of the Aloha Oe's crew!
So, uh, that monster
just used its powers
to brainwash Dandy, right?
[QT] I think there's
something wrong with you.
She's a sweet dog,
no more, no less.
[DOG barks]
[MEOW]
Huh?
[DOG barks]
[MEOW]
Uh...
[DOG barks]
Heh heh... Thanks,
but it's not that cool.
[QT]
She talked to you?
Speak, Cat.
What did puppy say?
I know you can understand her.
Uh, yeah, um... She just
said my hat looked cool.
[DOG barks]
Uh... and that's something
about us leaving A.S.A.P.
[DOG barks]
"You creeps get the hell off
my planet and never come back."
[TRANSLATOR] I'm so happy
I was able to meet you guys!
You lied about
everything she just said.
Ugh, you pathetic, shady cat.
[QT]
I'm with Dandy on this one.
Definitely shady.
Listen, you freeloading feline.
You better turn your
attitude around three sixty!
Math. Okay, maybe go
back like sixty degrees?
Look, the dog is cute.
And if I know anything, I know
that the chicks dig cute stuff.
If we take her to Boobies,
we're sure to have
the ladies all over us
like a fart in a spacesuit.
Really? And I'm the
shady one at this party?
So, baby, can you
tell me your name?
[TRANSLATOR] I've forgotten.
You can choose a new one for me!
Oh, all the feels!
Our frontier is starting to die.
I know, Big Brother.
What should we do?
[BIG BROTHER]
We must seek out a new land.
If it is the Great Spirit's
will, we will find one.
As the last of the Machinians,
we cannot lose hope.
Do you understand, Brother?
[YOUNGER BROTHER]
Yes, I do.
Let us follow the sun.
[DOG whines]
Oh, Precious Upside-Down-
Coconut Pie, what's wrong?
[QT]
Is that supposed to be her name?
That's right, it's P.U.P.
"Pup" for short.
It's inspired by the
Boobies dessert menu.
[QT]
Right. Because that matters.
Well, it looks like you
got an original name.
Not as if I care, though.
Of course,
it would have been nice
to have that much thought
put into my name, but whatever.
I mean, I'm just a shady,
freeloading feline.
[DOG whines]
Talk to me.
[TRANSLATOR]
This is nice.
I was pretty sure
that all humans hated me.
Oh, Pup, whaddaya mean?
[TRANSLATOR]
It's okay, though.
I got used to it.
The whole world seemed
to hate me so much
that they decided to
abandon me on a planet
where nobody lived.
No! Who could hate you?
This is so not fair at all!
Look at Meow.
He's hated by an
entire universe,
and you're the one who got
abandoned and left for dead!
That cat is just a
shameless pervert!
I am not a pervert!
[QT]
He's not a cat, either.
[TRANSLATOR] I remember the
darkness more than anything.
I didn't have friends
or a crate to call home.
I couldn't see anything.
Eventually, I started to
wonder if I actually existed.
I kept asking why--
why was I alive?
But no one ever answers when
you've been left all alone.
I'm so sorry, Pup.
You know, a long time ago,
people would say,
"A good ass should be felt
and not seen," and it's true.
[QT] You're the only
one who says that.
Anyway, point is, you gotta find
your own purpose in life, baby!
[TRANSLATOR] You know, Dandy,
I'm happy I'm here with you.
Now that it's the end.
Thanks for playing with me;
I'm pretty sure
this isn't your fault.
[DANDY]
Pup?
Oh, no!
What is your problem?
I wanted to play with her,
too, and now it's too late!
[QT]
It'll be okay.
She really did tell me
she thought my hat was cool.
I'm so sorry!
[MEOW cries]
Great Spirit speaks.
Now jump, Little Brother!
[QT]
Dandy, where are you going?
Wait. We can't
just leave her here.
What kind of heartless
monster are you?
We're gonna build Pup
her very own rocket-coffin,
and then we'll give her the
send-off she deserves, baby!
[QT] I never realized you
knew how to make a rocket.
[DANDY] Well, that's because
technically I don't.
[QT] So then why not just
build a regular coffin?
What's the point?
We'll make 'er fly.
You'll see.
[NARRATOR]
A long, long time ago on Earth,
the U.S.S.R launched a
spacecraft called Sputnik Two.
Riding it was the
first living thing
to orbit the Earth,
a dog named Laika.
As the story goes,
her ship was in orbit
for five months before it burned
up reentering the atmosphere.
But who can say?
We may never know for
sure if our friend Pup,
the dog found in a faraway
galaxy, was really Laika or not.
I like to think it was.
Why am I so itchy? Agh!
[QT] Well, perhaps
a bath is in order.
Do you even remember
the last time you took one?
[MEOW] Three weeks, I think,
but I'm a big licker.
[QT] Oh, so that must be why
you smell like fish breath.
Back off. I can't help
that I hate water.
Or these stupid itchies!
[QT gasps]
[QT]
Meow! What are those?
[MEOW]
Eh?
[QT]
Don't let them get away!
Is it food?
[BIG BROTHER]
That creature stunk of fish.
I'll hold them back here.
You go on ahead, Little Brother!
[LITTLE BROTHER]
No. I will fight alongside you.
Look out, Brother!
[BIG BROTHER]
Fire!
[LITTLE BROTHER]
[BIG BROTHER]
Be quick! This way!
So those were just fleas, right?
[QT] No! I think they
might be an alien species
everyone thought was extinct!
They're called a
Graviton and a Gravitino!
Yeah. I knew that.
[BIG BROTHER]
Hup!
[BIG BROTHER grunts]
Hup! Hyah!
Brother. This way!
[LITTLE BROTHER]
Right!
[LITTLE BROTHER grunts, groans]
[BIG BROTHER]
Little Brother! No!
Brother!
--Dandy!
--[QT] We've got a problem!
There's something on this planet
you really need to know about!
[QT] Aaaahhh!
Uh... The heck is
your problem, dude?
Yeah, what's all
this 'bout the planet?
QT?
[QT]
I will avenge my brother!
Smash, smash! Smash, smash!
[DANDY] Since when
did QT have a brother?
How would I know?
[QT] I, Le Flea,
last of the Machinians,
will make you suffer!
QT is a flea?
[QT]
Le Flea.
You, white devil,
and your friends
took my brother's life
and halted our journey.
My new frontier will be
this old robot and your ship.
He just said "old"
talking about himself.
Wow, QT.
You really are possessed.
I think he might be
the little flea thing
that jumped off me a minute ago!
Wait, Le Flea was on you first?
Mm hmm. I caught a
microscopic new species.
See. Shady freeloaders
don't help out, right?
I must not be one
since I'm helping!
Are not!
Hey, what are you doing?
Wait, stop that!
I said stop!
Thirsty?
[QT] Don't let Le Flea
get near the machines!
There!
Meow, let's get him.
--[DANDY] Where is he?
--[MEOW] I think I see him!
[DANDY]
He got away.
[MEOW]
Here. Get him!
[QT] Don't kill him! If he dies,
this planet is done for!
[ALL]
Uh...
Um... You were saying
the planet was--?
[QT]
This is just a guess,
but I think those two were
machine-manipulating aliens
called a Graviton
and a Gravitino.
Their planet happens
to be made of machines,
so they were most likely on it
to keep the whole thing
from falling apart.
So, good thing?
[QT] Most likely,
a gravitational collapse
will occur,
causing it to explode.
Then it will turn
into a black hole,
pulling everything inside of
it with no hope of escape.
Well. Looks like
it's time to go!
Yeah, it doesn't look like
we're going anywhere!
I always wanted to
die by extreme sucking.
[QT] The gravitational
collapse is imminent.
We might get to see
what's inside a black hole.
What'll happen to us?
[QT] No one knows for sure, but
my money is on a painful death.
I guess this is
the end. Bye, baby.
[DANDY] To all the girls
I've loved before...
Oh. You mean me?
[DANDY]
No, not you.
Farewell.
Hey, Dandy, next
time you're around,
let's go like
hang out or something.
[DANDY]
Score!
I can't die yet;
I've got too much
to live for, baby! Oh, yeah!
I cannot imagine
what that'd be.
[DANDY] Why can we never
warp when we need to?
[QT]
We can warp.
What? Who said we couldn't warp?
Then, why haven't
we gotten out of here?
[QT] Because you always
say you hate warping.
I hate painful death more.
Get us out of here!
Warp it, now!
[QT]
Okay, fine, we'll warp.
Oh, crap.
Yes, I agree.
This does not
look very promising.
[BEA]
Well, black holes rarely do.
[GEL]
Oh, give me a break.
That man seriously knows
how to create a black hole?
This is bad...
Uh! Hey, hold on a second.
Gimme some of those sick beats!
[sound of record scratching]
Wow, that didn't work at all.
I guess that's what I get
for buying this thing used.
So you were fine letting me
think you made it yourself?
Hold me close, Bea!
We made it, guys.
Ugh! You kidding me? You smell
like dead fish breath, man.
Take a freakin' bath!
Bye-bye. Come back and see us!
My name is Doctor Gel.
They don't give me
very much screen time,
and for some reason,
I keep dying.
I am officially
very dissatisfied.
Next time: "Plants are
Living Things, Too, Baby."
[BEA] I don't think
we're in that one.
[GEL] Oh, sonofa--!