Space Dandy.
He's a dandy guy... in space.
He combs the galaxy
like his pompadour,
on the hunt for aliens.
Planet after planet he searches,
discovering bizarre new
creatures both friendly and not.
These are the
spectacular adventures
of Space Dandy and his
brave space crew... in space.
[DANDY] Huh? Hold the phone!
What did you say?
The bounty is a
measly two woolongs?
[MEOW] C'mon, lady! It
may look all floppy,
but catching this thing
was a huge pain in the butt!
[QT]
Can't we work something out?
It cost more than two woolongs
just to fly this in
for processing!
Now we're in the
red worse than ever!
[DANDY] A two-woolong bounty
is crazy-talk, sweet-cheeks--!
Quit your whining!
The Baranian you hauled in last
week netted you 128 woolongs.
The Pylorian before
that went for sixty-four.
And the Rakendrian?
Thirty-two woolongs.
Which brings us to this
bounty-hunting travesty--
Do you know how much it costs us
in processing fees just to
pay you two measly woolongs?
You are the worst excuses for
alien-hunters I've ever seen.
Stop wasting my time with trash.
Come back with something
rare or don't come back at all.
Yes. Something good,
like a Chameleonian.
--Huh?
A Chamele-what-now?
[NARRATOR] Much like
their reptilian namesake,
Chameleonians are masters
of disguise--but instead
of just changing their colors,
they can shape-shift
into anything they want.
In fact, they're
so good at mimicry,
no one in the universe knows
what they actually look like.
Can a slacker, a space-cat,
and a goody-goody match wits
with such a slippery target?
Smart money says no, but
stranger things have happened.
How much do we get for
catching this thing, anyway?
[QT]
A hundred million woolongs.
--A hundred million?
[QT] What? I thought
you guys already knew.
A hundred million woolongs!
We're gonna be so stinkin' rich!
Yeah, all right! Let's go, baby!
[QT]
Go where, exactly?
Where do you think?
To a planet that looks like
it has chameleons, of course!
[DANDY]
Here.
[QT]
Huh?
[MEOW] I'm gonna start
with a nice juicy fly
and see what happens.
Oh man, I so wanna chase it.
[QT] Okay, and you
gave me a cricket why?
Chameleon bait!
We're on an alien
fishin' mission, baby!
[QT] Um, we're trying to catch a
Chameleonian, not a chameleon.
Chameleons are
totally different creatures.
Just, you know,
something to think about.
I'm thinking 'bout
that hundred million!
More like hundred cham-million!
[QT] Sometimes I wonder
why I even bother.
[MEOW] So hey,
what're you going to do
with your share
of the woolongs?
Me, I'm looking at
a whole lotta lazy-time!
I'm gonna drink beer and nap in
the sun and lick myself all day!
Is that it?
You're thinkin' small, man.
I would go out to eat at
Boobies three meals a day.
Which of course would
earn me a butt-load
of frequent-diner points,
and then I'd get to use 'em
on even more trips to Boobies!
That's your grand ambition--
to go out to eat a lot?
What about it?
[QT]
This is my life.
[DANDY]
Step off, tuna-breath.
Lookit!
[QT] I don't know how
this works! What do I do?
Reel it in!
Turn the little crank!
[MEOW] Aw, it was
just a tsuchinoko?
[DANDY] Those're worthless.
Toss it back already, yeah?
[NARRATOR] And that's
when QT suddenly realized:
[QT]
Fishing is actually kinda fun!
My Fishing Journal, Day 1:
Tried out a quiet little spot
that I read about in a magazine.
Day 2: Bad weather.
Got caught in a nor'easter
that tossed our boat
around something fierce.
Goodness!
Day 3: What a
perfect day for fishing!
My homemade lure paid off!
Day 4: Jackpot! Got my
biggest one ever today!
[QT] I don't care if you're
deadsticking or doodling,
finesse fishing with
a splitshot rig sure
is a handy way
to hit your limit.
Say what?
Did he break his language chip?
Gotcha!
Yes, black tsuchinoko!
Come to QT!
Heya, Dandy?
Call me crazy, but
I think we're hitting a bit
of mission creep out here.
What were we hunting?
Look, you got a nibble!
It looks like a whopper!
[MEOW]
Chameleonian off the port side!
[DANDY] Yeah, that's the ticket!
Come to Dandy, woolongs!
Wh-? Whaddya mean?
[MEOW] Whoa, whoa, whoa,
it's not a Chameleonian?
This is just an
ordinary chameleon!
You're not getting a bounty for
this--it's not even an alien!
Now pick up this reptile
and get out of here!
[MEOW]
So, that happened.
[QT]
I tried warning you earlier,
but no, nobody listened to me.
Nobody ever does.
[DANDY]
Whatever.
How come you kept that thing?
[QT] You don't come
across a black tsuchinoko
this big every day, you know.
And I still have to upload
pictures of it to my blog.
Oh! Maybe it'll become a meme!
That's the last time
I teach a robot to fish.
[yawning]
Time to hit the sack.
[QT] Don't forget, surf
fishing starts at 4 a.m.
Ugh, have fun.
Yeah, I don't do 4 a.m.
Huh? But surf fishing
is so much fun!
Say cheese!
Hey, Meow.
You and I are not cool
enough to share a toothbrush.
Huh? Dude, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Then how come
it's all damp, hombre?
Look at it, Meow. There's fish
flakes stuck in the bristles.
The same fish flakes that
you sprinkle on everything!
Whatever! Who ate my
octopus-flavored popsicle, huh?
It sure as hell wasn't me!
Yeah, you're not fooling
anybody, Pompadour.
Could you two please
not look at porn sites
on my cell phone?
I don't even want
to touch it now!
I don't look at porn.
Maybe you were looking at it.
That makes no sense,
I don't even have those ports!
It had to be one of you!
Who else is there?
There is another.
Huh?
A stowaway.
One who doesn't respect
other people's stuff.
--Huh?
Somebody looked at porn
sites in the dead of night,
chowed down on
your octopus popsicle,
and then brushed their
teeth using my toothbrush!
That's the only possible way
to explain these fish flakes!
This is nuts.
We are not alone.
Roll call! One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Hold up.
[screaming]
--Huh? Huh?
[QT] There's definitely
someone else on board the ship!
Come on, let's find this poser!
[QT] My black tsuchinoko!
It's gone!
Huh, maybe our stowaway ate it.
Something's fishy about this.
It was here when I went to bed.
[DANDY]
Maybe it bailed.
[MEOW] But how?
The cage is still locked.
Yeah. How did I manage that?
--Huh?
[PERRY]
Out with it, Dr. Gel.
When are you going to
capture that damnable Dandy?
My patience with your
ineptitude grows thin.
[GEL chuckling]
[PERRY] Hmm? You're in
no position to smirk!
I suggest you explain yourself.
Of course. You see,
a new weapon that I
have been secretly developing
for several years now has at
long last reached completion.
[PERRY]
A weapon, you say?
Indeed.
A diabolical device
capable of ensnaring
its target anywhere
in time and/or space.
[PERRY]
Is this true?
With this power at my disposal,
Dandy's day of
reckoning is nigh.
[BEA]
Doctor.
I've finally confirmed
Dandy's location.
You shall get your quarry
soon enough, Admiral.
How did that geezer
get on the ship?
What's he doing here?
How the hell am
I supposed to know?
It's not like
I've seen him before!
[QT] You don't think he's
the Chameleonian, do you?
Say what?
[QT] I know it's
a huge coincidence,
but I'm starting to think
the tsuchinoko I caught
was really the
Chameleonian in disguise!
All right! We gotta
split up and find it!
Big-money-big-money-
big-money-big-money!
[DANDY]
Ow! Ow, my foot!
Hey, Dandy!
Any luck?
Nothing yet!
I'll check in the
engine room. See ya!
Hey, Dandy!
Hey!
Nothing yet!
I'll check in the
engine room. See ya!
Hang on a sec!
[DANDY] That was
one Meow too many!
Huh?
Which means-- You're that
sneaky Chameleonian, aintcha?
What? C'mon!
I'm a Betelgeusian, dude!
[SCARLET]
See?
He's a Betelgeusian, just like
he was in the last three scans.
[MEOW] Yeah. That's
what I told him, but oh no.
[DANDY] Damn it. So the other
one was the Chameleonian, huh?
I can't believe you put
me in a cage. Not cool.
[QT]
Are you sure it was there?
Look, I don't know what kind of
con you're trying to pull here,
but don't come back until
you have an actual bounty!
[MEOW]
Not our finest moment.
[DANDY] And that poser
is still on the ship.
Are you sure this time?
Uh-huh. The ol' Dandy-sense
is getting' tingly.
I say we split up
and look some more!
Did we always have a
funky couch over there?
Huh?
Aw, son of a...!
That was no funky couch--it
was a freakin' Chameleonian!
Man, I can't believe
I put my butt on it.
Hey, cheer up.
I think some groovy
tunes may be just what
the doctor ordered to snap
us outta this nasty funk.
♪ Beee-ma, bee-ma, bee-ma, ♪
♪ bee-ma, be my baby,
be my baby. ♪
♪ Beee my baby, be my baby. ♪
♪ Bee-ma, bee-ma,
be my baby, be my baby. ♪
Huh. I remember that
part bein' different.
I must'a grabbed a
live version by mistake.
I remember that song sucking
a lot less back in the day.
Also, since when did we
have a boom-box over there?
You're kidding me!
I would'a sworn
that was The Ronettes!
Dammit, that
alien's freakin' good!
I'm pretty sure the
Chameleonian's here!
"Pretty sure?" I'm positive!
You should've quit while
you were ahead, poser!
One of those robots is bogus!
Huh?
I don't like this!
Gotcha!
So! Which one of you
guys is the piggy bank? Huh?
I kinda wish they were
both fake! Get a load of her.
[DANDY whistling]
Whoa. That really
floats your boat?
You don't see an ass like
that every day, my friend!
That's true.
Not my fault you don't
appreciate the finer things.
It's getting away!
--Huh?
Not again!
Oh no, we
really just lost it?
[SCARLET] You three don't
know when to quit, do you?
Uh, about that! You're
not gonna believe this, but--
Let me guess.
The robot is the
Chameleonian this time?
Or maybe the rope.
It was next to me, I swear!
That alien is
really pissing me off!
[SCARLET] Well, it
learned from the master!
Now get out of here!
It must have pulled its
quick-change shenanigans again!
[SCARLET] You three don't
know when to quit, do you?
Whoa. Déjà-vu. Uh.
Aw, come on!
Now you're just
being a dick about it!
Huh?
You're not skipping
out this time.
Get off me, you idiots!
I wonder how long
we're banned for?
I guess that means
the Chameleonian got
away for good, huh?
Game over, man. Game over.
Aliens suck.
We finally get a chance
to make some major coin,
and all we do is
tie each other up.
But, oh well. Whenever
life gets you down--
[VOICE]
Boobies gets you up again!
You just read my mind, baby!
They're the same.
It's a doppel-Dandy!
Hey, that's my face.
Hey, not if I had it first.
Okay, so I'm like
90% positive that
one of these Dandies is bogus!
But which one of them
is the real Dandy?
I'm the real one, obviously!
Well, I was me
before it was cool!
But both of 'em seem legit!
Don't worry, Meow.
I have a plan!
[QT] Welcome, contestants,
to the first-ever Dandy Quiz!
--Huh?
[QT] The rules of
the game are simple:
Answer more questions
about Dandy's life correctly
and you win!
Are you ready?
Oh, I was born ready.
He's nailed the hair--
I'll give him that much.
But he doesn't know
jack about Dandy.
You are so goin' down!
Bring it!
Cool it, Dandies.
Okay, Dandy #1--finish this
thought. "I am a slave to..."
"...the booty!"
[QT]
Is that your final Dandy?
Yeah, sure, Final Dandy.
That is correct!
All right!
Okay, Dandy #2,
this next question is yours.
What did you have
for dinner last night?
How in the hell
would I remember that?
Is that your final Dandy?
Final Dandy. Yeah, sure.
That's correct!
The real Dandy wouldn't
remember this morning,
much less yesterday!
Ya hear that?
In your beautiful face!
Son-of-a--!
[QT]
Favorite ninja.
[DANDY 1]
Sexy female!
[QT]
Correct! Your favorite vehicle.
[DANDY 2]
Ooh, a chick-mobile!
Correct! Favorite
women's fashion.
[DANDY 1]
Birthday suit.
[QT] Correct!
Favorite sports event.
[DANDY 2] Ladies hundred
meter breast-stroke!
[QT] Correct!
Nobody's missed one yet.
I know, when it comes to being a
dumb-ass, they're neck-and-neck.
Hey! Stop talking
smack about me, cat!
Yo! Give it a rest!
Nobody shouts at
my crewmates but me.
Huh?
C'mon, QT.
You're killin' me here.
How is it you still can't
tell I'm the genuine article?
Maybe it's time we got
you that upgrade, huh?
Dandy or not, I like
the cut of that one's jib.
He sure doesn't yell as much.
Maybe we're getting too
hung up on finding the real one,
you know what I mean?
Let's just take that one.
What the hell, guys?
I'm sittin' right here!
It looks like we
got our answer, baby.
And what does that mean?
It means you
should hit the road.
Oh give it a rest, you faker!
You're the faker, you faker!
Oh yeah? Then who're you?
I'm who you wish you were, pal!
I'm me, baby! So there!
I'm way more me than you!
You're not you,
you fraud! I'm you!
I'm the real me!
No, you're the fake me!
Who's that make you?
[NARRATOR]
I'm not sure who's who.
[DANDY 1]
You are so me.
[DANDY 2]
Right back at you.
[DANDY 1]
I'm you, okay?
[DANDY 2]
Well, I'm you, too!
[NARRATOR] Hell, they're
not sure who's who.
[DANDY 1]
Who are you?
[DANDY 2]
You!
[DANDY 1]
And who're you?
[DANDY 2]
I'm me!
[DANDY 1] Can we get
name-tags or something?
[NARRATOR] The Chameleonian,
a master of disguise.
It's so skilled,
no one knows its true form.
In the end, not even
the Chameleonian itself.
Uh-oh. I've been karate-choppin'
through life like I'm Dandy.
But what if I'm really
that Chameleonian thing,
and I forgot all
about it because I'm doing
such a bad-ass job of
pretending to be the actual me?
I am he. As you.
Unless you're him.
[NARRATOR]
Drowning in the introspection
he couldn't even spell,
he grasped at answers.
And then, as it all
went black, he found one.
Who cares, baby!
So maybe I'm an alien.
Or maybe I'm the real deal.
Either way, I am awesome!
That's it. I so give up.
[BEA] Dr. Gel. We've
locked onto the target.
Awaiting your order.
Oh, how I've waited for this.
Engage the
Hyperdimensional Magic Hand!
I found 50 woolongs! Huh?
I have landed my prey.
Great job, Doctor!
Bow before me, Dandy!
[snarky laughter]
Huh?
Hello there, sexy.
Who the hell are
you supposed to be?
I am Gel, the doctor!
No, I am Gel, the doctor!
You're the doctor, too?
Who is the doctor?
Exactly!
[GEL]
Who's the doctor?
Who's the doctor? Who's the
doctor? Who's the doctor?
Who's the doctor?
That's the question, isn't it?
Is it me? Is it him?
[BEA] Dr. Gel!
Get a hold of yourself!
[GEL] How long has
this been going on for?
Who's the doctor?
Who is he?
Who am I?
Who's the doctor?
Who is he?
[NARRATOR]
And with his inner monologue
stuck on infinite repeat,
Dr. Gel succumbed
to Gestaltzerfall.
It's a thing. Gogol it.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
over at Boobies.
It's business as usual.
Or is it?
Is this the real Dandy?
Staring at the waitresses
could just be part of the act.
[NARRATOR] Maybe business
as usual, never was.
The Chameleonian changes its
form and slips into our lives,
and with a few rare exceptions,
no one's the wiser.
For all you know,
you're surrounded by them.
Friends, coworkers, family.
Anybody could be a Chameleonian.
Even me. Maybe even you.
[QT] Why are there so many
songs about love?
How much can you say
about some silly emotion?
[MEOW] They do get
kind of repetitive.
[DANDY]
That's how love works.
The words are the same but
every time feels like the first.
Next time: "Even Vacuum
Cleaners Fall in Love, Baby."