[running shower]
[CATHERINE] Dandy.
Tell me, have you figured out
the secret of warping yet?
[DANDY] I dunno
what you mean, babe.
Like, how to do it
without losin' your hair?
[CATHERINE] That's not what
I meant and you know it.
Can't you be serious
about something for once?
[CATHERINE] If you want to know,
I'd be happy to tell you.
All you have to do is ask.
Well, thanks but
no thanks, baby.
Secrets are more fun when
you find 'em out for yourself.
[CATHERINE] I've done
a lot of thinking
and I've made my decision.
[DANDY] You wanna be with Paul.
Hey Catherine,
so does this mean--
[CATHERINE] What?
Nothin'. It doesn't matter.
[door opening]
[door closing]
[MALE OPERATOR 11A]
Warp complete, sir.
Are you absolutely sure
this is the place, Bea?
I don't see anything of note;
just an average looking planet.
According
to the space radar,
it's definitely coming
from within this sector.
Our instruments are picking
up a spatial distortion
that's producing an
enormous amount of energy.
Well, there doesn't appear
to be anything unusual here.
Yes, but one might say that
is what's unusual, Doctor.
Is that your convoluted way
of implying Dandy
might be to blame?
I can't say yet.
At this point, there's only
one thing I know for certain.
The source of the energy anomaly
is not on the planet's surface.
What?
[BEA] It's
actually right here.
But how is that possible
when there aren't any
spaceships or satellites nearby?
Huh?!
[MALE OPERATOR 11A]
We're getting super high
energy readings
just off the planet!
I think something's
about to warp, sir!
Its mass and energy
are both beyond measurement!
Its length is unknown!
Same for its width! And it's
growing by the second!
No way. It can't be.
Another universe?
[MALE OPERATOR 11A]
The unknown mass
is headed straight for our ship!
Then get us out of here now!
[MALE OPERATOR 11A]
There's no time!
[yawns]
I wonder if warping
is really as bad for
you as they say it is.
'Cause I'm feelin'
awfully sluggish.
[QT] I bet anybody
would feel that way
after doing it as
many times as we did.
Well, it's not
like we had a choice.
That dumb alien kept
warping away from us.
[alarms]
Alert! May I have
your attention, please!
An emergency order was
issued today at two pm
Universal Time.
A 2D universe has materialized
near Planet Abbot.
A whole universe...
[QT] ...warped into ours?
[MALE ANNOUNCER 24A]
The Gogol Imperial Space Force
has dispatched a fleet
to prevent the 2D
universe from advancing.
However, their efforts have
thus far had little
effect on this invader.
Hmm...
[MEOW] Wow, I had no idea
whole universes could warp.
[QT] I don't get
why it came here.
I mean, if I could go anywhere,
this is the last place I'd pick.
Yeah. Maybe it thinks
our universe is cute
and wants to get
to know it better.
[DANDY] Hey.
Would you dummies quit
goofin' off already?
Let's go!
Well, aren't you a
ray of sunshine today?
[QT] Lemme guess, you've got
a bug up your nose 'cause
we've been warping so much.
It's either that, or you've got
a bug up your butt.
[MEOW] You should be excited!
I bet you that universe
is full of rare aliens!
I dunno 'bout that,
but it's definitely
full of bad memories.
Huh?
[QT] You've been there before?
What's it matter to you?
Look, there's a lot you guys
don't know about my past,
and I'm trying my
damnedest to forget about it.
You're not runnin' from
that universe, are ya?
[QT] Who, Dandy?
What gave you that silly idea?
It's not silly!
Think about it, why else
would it warp its way here?
It's gotta be chasin'
after somethin'.
[QT] That makes no sense,
what would a
universe be chasing?
[MEOW] A miniverse, maybe?
Paul, you bastard.
[CATHERINE] Dandy.
Yeah, I thought it was you.
Hello, Catherine.
[QT] Um. Who are
you talking to, Dandy?
Some kinda invisible alien?
[CATHERINE] I can't
believe you'd be so cold
after all this time.
[QT] Whoa, what
kinda alien is that?
How many years has
it been, Catherine?
[CATHERINE] You know
I can't answer that.
We 4th-dimensionals live in
a different time than you,
so it's impossible
for me to say.
Yeah. I remember now.
Hey, what's a
"4th-dimensional"?
[QT] A being from
the fourth dimension?
That's all I've got.
[MALE OPERATOR 11A]
Warp complete, sir!
And what is our
position now?
[MALE OPERATOR 11A]
We are inside the 2D universe.
[GEL] You're pathetic.
Would you quit whining, Bea?
What did you think
was going to happen?
You do realize that
warping is nothing more
than a method of moving
through the universe, don't you?
Well, yes but--
I'm worried we might
not be able to get back.
Why?
I have to be completely
honest with you,
sometimes your idiocy amazes me.
The 2D universe was
able to warp into ours,
so there must be a way
to move between them.
Good to hear, but we'd
better move quickly!
There's something off
about this universe.
I can't explain it.
[GEL] Would you look at that?
The energy anomaly exists
in this universe as well.
[HONEY] Oh, wow! That's so cool!
I can't believe the two of you
were an item back in the day!
So tell me, what was it like
being Dandy's girlfriend,
Miss Catherine?
[CATHERINE] Such a cute and
spunky young lady, isn't she?
Is she your current girlfriend?
[laughs]
That's the funniest
thing I've heard today!
[QT] Is it just me
or is this kinda weird?
I don't understand Dandy's
taste in women one bit.
Hey man.
Shoot straight with me,
whaddya think of
that Catherine broad?
Do you think that she's hot?
[QT] Honestly, she just
looks like a box to me.
Okay, just wanted
to make sure
I wasn't the only one.
So Dandy and this other guy
were fighting over you?
That's so romantic!
I wanna hear all about it!
[CATHERINE]
Well, that's all in the past.
So, uh, I'm guessing that you
chose the other guy, huh?
Knock it off, would ya?
Enough with the questions.
[HONEY] Don't be a grump!
[CATHERINE]
What's the harm, Dandy?
After all, it's ancient history.
[CATHERINE] We realized
that the worlds
we lived in were
simply too different.
Mismatched
personalities, huh?
[QT] Sounds more like
mismatched dimensions.
And Paul?
What ever happened with him?
[CATHERINE] We broke up.
When he became
successor to the throne,
his personality changed,
and not for the better.
Wait. This Paul guy's
a freakin' prince?
Why would you ever
break up with him?
[CATHERINE] It's complicated.
He's a 2nd-dimensional,
and I'm a 4th-dimensional.
[CATHERINE]
The two-dimension difference
was just too much for us.
[MEOW] I don't get it.
Do you?
[QT] I think what she's saying
is that to a 4th-dimensional,
a 2nd-dimensional looks like,
well, like a straight
line would look to us.
Uhmm...
So, Catherine. Whaddya want?
[CATHERINE] For old time's sake,
I want you to send Paul
and his universe back
to where they belong.
He can't go on disturbing
the cosmos like this.
[CATHERINE] He spent
an entire decade looking
for a way to find me,
but I never wanted to be found.
[MALE OPERATOR 11A] Multiple
ships of unknown origin ahead!
It appears they have a
defense fleet ready to attack.
Who'd've thought that
being sucked into 2-D
with that energy anomaly
would be a good thing.
[GEL] I suspect that fleet
is defending the drive
which allows their
universe to warp.
If that's true, sir,
then we can go back home
if we destroy it, right?
I don't know.
Huh?
It's possible that
destroying the drive could
cause this universe
to be annihilated.
There's also the chance
that its destruction
could leave us stranded here,
in 2D, forever.
[BEA] Oh, Doctor.
I don't understand
why you're getting
yourself so worked
up about this.
Are you kidding me?
I don't understand how you
can be so calm about it!
Bea.
Don't you know that
the happiest moments
in a scientist's life are when
they come face-to-face
with the unknown?
We spend our entire
lives searching for it!
Why worry about my fate and
ruin such a joyous occasion?
[MALE OPERATOR 11A] Impact
sustained to the third Block!
The enemy fleet is
ramping up their attack!
We can't do much
to camouflage ourselves;
we're two-dimensional.
But I suppose the same
can be said of our enemy.
At this point, all
we can do is continue
to press on towards
their warp drive!
[CATHERINE]
Are you angry, Dandy?
No, of course
I'm not.
[CATHERINE]
You look angry.
I told ya I'm not.
Just drop it, okay?
[CATHERINE]
You're such a softie.
I knew you wouldn't be able
to turn down a
request from an ex.
[MEOW] So she's a
woman from his past.
[QT] Who looks like
some kinda futuristic box.
Geez, I thought
cats and robots
were supposed to be smart,
but you guys don't have a clue!
Are you a stowaway?
Well, yeah.
I wanna meet that Paul guy!
He might be my prince!
Why chase rare aliens when
you can just marry royalty?
Sorry for stowing away,
but this might be my chance
to meet Prince Charming!
[QT] Here's something
for you to think about.
If Paul is one of
Dandy's old friends,
then that means he's gotta
be getting up there in age.
So what?
I've got no problem
with dating an older man.
[MEOW] Do you really
think a guy who warped
his entire universe to try
to win back his ex-girlfriend,
is gonna turn
around and dump her
for some chick he's never met?
Maybe!
You never know what such
a passionate man might do!
[CATHERINE] Tell me something.
Have you figured out
the secret of warping yet?
Why do you ask?
Didya tell Paul?
[CATHERINE] Well,
considering the way he warped
into your universe,
I'd say it's rather obvious
that he knows something.
Catherine.
[CATHERINE] You and I are on
two completely different planes.
I still remember what
happened in the past,
but you don't, do you?
[DANDY] No.
[MALE OPERATOR 11A]
The fighters near the warp drive
have started to move.
It appears to be a
defensive maneuver.
I guess that means
we've been spotted.
Well, it certainly took
them long enough.
[MALE OPERATOR 11A] The route
starts to get narrow up ahead.
We'll be making contact
with the enemy's
defensive line soon.
[DANDY] Okay, listen up.
We've gotta stop
this ruthless bastard,
and by bastard, I mean Paul.
I'm thinkin' we
should go to him,
and hash this out directly.
[MEOW] Whaddya mean
by "go to him"?
We can't just
search the universe;
even in 2D it's
still a big place.
Catherine here knows
where to find 'im.
[QT] Since he's in a 2D
universe, his forces won't
be able to attack us
while we're on the outside.
So it should be pretty
easy for us to get in.
[CATHERINE]
Paul knows this, too,
which is why he's
already begun rolling up
the fabric of his universe.
[MEOW] Huh? But how
is that even possible?
[QT] Well, it's 2D so it's kinda
like folding a piece of paper.
[CATHERINE] He'll be
on the interior end.
[MEOW] The wha--?
[CATHERINE] The space
between the universe layers
is very narrow,
so we won't be able
reach him by flying
in from the side.
Our only choice
is to be drawn
into the universe and
search from within.
Screw that
psycho stalker!
He's just makin' this
tough because it's me.
Oh, I know! Hey Dandy.
Man, I really hate
the 2D universe--
the ceilings are low
and it's hard to fight.
[CATHERINE] Yeah, but it's
still better than a 1D universe.
[HONEY] I've got
an idea! Yoo-hoo!
How can you be sure we're
not gonna get crushed
when that thing sucks us up?
[QT] He's got a point.
Seems like it would
make our insides pop out.
[HONEY] Um. Hello!
What?
Is there somethin'
you'd like to add, Honey?
Why don't we
just poke right through?
[QT] That's it!
'Kay, here we go!
[QT] It's about to get narrow.
Looks like it's now
or never, Dandy!
Hold tight, everyone!
[DANDY] Whoa!
Alright, let's do this, baby!
Cut through!
Welcome to 2D!
[MALE OPERATOR 11A] A powerful
shockwave is approaching!
Just what do you
mean by "shockwave"?
Look! It's creating
a fissure in space, sir!
Whoa. It's huge.
[QT]
Yeah, you can see everything
looking down at it like this.
Hey, QT.
Zoom in on that big square.
[QT] Give me a second.
You mean right here?
[CATHERINE] Paul.
He hasn't changed, has he?
Huh? He's just a
rectangle with a crown?
[QT] Yeah, he's
a two-dimensional.
What'd you expect?
I thought that he
was my Prince Charming,
but I can't marry a rectangle!
Wow, you can see
everything from up here!
[DANDY] Two-dimensionals don't
even realize they're
visible like this.
Can't quite get their
heads around the idea.
[CATHERINE] Once we
destroy their warp drive,
the 2D universe should
immediately go back
to where it came
from on its own.
Are you sure you
don't wanna see Paul?
[CATHERINE] Yeah. I'm old now.
I'd rather he remember
me the way I was.
[QT] I found something
that looks suspicious.
Do ya think this could
be their warp drive?
[BEA] Range: sixteen-hundred
to the warp drive.
[MALE OPERATOR 11A]
I'm picking up
some kind of transmission, sir.
[GEL] Well then, let's hear
what they have to say.
[PAUL] Catherine!
You're the one who's about
to destroy the drive,
please listen to me first.
I was wrong
about everything.
Please come back to me!
My beloved Catherine.
I'm willing to renounce
my claim to the throne
and leave this universe
behind to be with you!
Catherine?
Probably just interference
from a TV soap opera.
We don't have time to
worry about it right now.
[MALE OPERATOR 11A]
Target acquired!
What are your orders, sir?
All weapons, fire!
That was a direct hit!
[GEL] It can't be!
Is that a 1D universe?
[MALE OPERATOR 11A]
A massive object
is headed toward the ship!
No! Not again!
As if going 2D wasn't bad
enough now we're going 1D?
Whoa, did it
self-destruct on its own?
What's gonna happen
to my rectangle prince?
[DANDY] So, Catherine.
Did you do this?
[CATHERINE] No,
I had nothing to do with it.
But I--
What?
[CATHERINE] I could've sworn
that I heard Paul's voice
calling out to me.
[CATHERINE] Paul sealed
a 1D universe in a box
to harness its power.
He then used that power
to warp his 2D universe
into your own.
And are you the one who
gave Paul that crazy idea?
[CATHERINE]
Wouldn't you like to know?
[CATHERINE] So now
that it's been ten years,
why don't you tell me.
[CATHERINE] Have you figured
out the secret of warping yet?
Yeah.
The secret is
warping doesn't exist.
[CATHERINE] That's right.
[DANDY] We travel through
the space between universes,
and for some strange reason,
we decided to call it warping.
Suppose that there's
a world in this universe,
and then a similar
world in another one,
and both have the same
stuffed animal lyin' around.
Here's where
it gets tricky.
At some point,
the stuffed animal here
will sense "This is me."
Do you get what I'm sayin'?
And the next moment,
the stuffed animal there
will sense "This is me."
That's all it is, baby.
[CATHERINE] True but
you forgot to mention
that you can't sense the
switching between universes.
Ain't that the truth?
I guess, it's different
for you, huh?
[CATHERINE] Yes, it is.
From my perspective,
Dandy before warping
and Dandy after warping
are two completely
different people.
[CATHERINE] Which means
you're not the Dandy
I fell in love with.
Yeah, I know.
Even though you're
still the same Catherine
that I fell in love with.
[CATHERINE] You knew that
and you helped me anyway?
Thank you.
[DANDY] So about Paul.
[CATHERINE] There's no need
to worry, he's alive still.
[DANDY] That's not what
I'm talkin' about, Catherine.
[CATHERINE] I see.
You want to know
why I chose Paul.
You were able to figure out
the secret of warping
all by yourself, Dandy.
On the other hand,
I knew that Paul would
be lost without me.
[BEA] Doctor, I'm picking up
a high-energy
reading dead ahead!
We're not going to
be able to avoid it!
[GEL] Another energy anomaly?
What could it be?
[BEA] I think that it's a Zero-D
universe warping out, sir!
[GEL] What? Zero dimensions?
[JUDGE 25A] Order!
We will now begin the trial of
the defendant, Mister Dandy,
also known as Space Dandy,
who has been
charged with murder!
[JUDGE 25B] On the nest
episode of Space Dandy.
"Dandy's Day in Court, Baby."
We'll see you then!