[NARRATOR]
Space Dandy.
He's a dandy guy... in space.
He combs the galaxy
like his pompadour,
on the hunt for aliens.
These are the
spectacular adventures
of Space Dandy and his
brave space crew... in space.
[MEOW] Checking in at the
Alien Registration Center.
[FEMALE ROBOT VOICE]
Now calling 538.
Here we go!
[SCARLET]
Okay. Who's next?
Mister Dandy, is it?
All right, let's check you out.
[buzzer sounds]
[SCARLET] That's an
Androman Giroro.
One of about a hundred
million registered at present.
Huh?
Meaning there is nothing
rare about this species.
As aliens go, these
are very common, sir.
Whoa, hold the phone!
You didn't even look
closely at it, lady!
Okay, next up, please.
[DANDY]
I've got one more!
Now how does this one look?
[buzzer sounds]
This is a Betelgeusian.
One of about 58.6 billion
registered at present.
See. I told ya so.
I'm an honest-to-goodness,
bonafide Betelgeusian--
Damn cat!
You're nothin' but
a useless, pathetic,
freeloading feline
with a bad attitude!
[DANDY and MEOW yell]
[PERRY] So...
Have you located the man
we're searching for, Dr. Gel?
[GEL]
Soon, Admiral Perry.
We are using the latest
in search technology.
Thanks to Gogol
galaxy street view,
our investigation
is well underway.
I fully expect I will be
reporting to you of
our success shortly.
[PERRY] Hmm.
For the honor of
the Gogol Empire,
I hope your
assessment is correct.
Sir. The mission
is in good hands.
[DANDY] Dammit.
What's a guy gotta do to find
a big money alien these days?
This bites.
[QT] Be reasonable.
There are only about
thirty thousand cases
of new aliens
recorded each year.
Among those, no more
than ten percent
of the registrations
are rare enough
to land the responsible
hunter a hefty reward.
It's not an easy process.
[DANDY] Man, I'm hungry.
Don't we have any food?
Wait, we do.
I almost forgot about
my super special stash.
Yes, I knew I was
saving it for a reason.
Gone! Gone!
Gone!
The Guruchan Ramen
I've carefully hoarded is gone!
Gone, baby, gone!
[slurping]
[MEOW] Ahhh...
[DANDY] You!
What? Oh, yeah, this stuff?
It was just taking up space
in the kitchen, so, you know.
It wasn't all that bad.
Of course
it wasn't good, either.
I would rate it a solid "okay."
It had that fake
"instant" taste to it.
Know what I mean?
[DANDY]
Tell me, Meow.
Do you know where
you stand around here?
Where I stand?
Let me think.
Well, obviously, I'm
a very important member
of the Aloha Oe's crew, an--
No, you're a mangy,
mooching, flea-ridden stray!
[MEOW screams]
[DANDY]
That's right.
I took you in because
I thought you might be useful.
But sitting around all day,
eating and smooching your
girlie pillow is not useful.
Do you hear me,
you dimwitted feline?
Wait! Hold on!
Yeah, I almost forgot!
I have something!
Knowledge I've been
saving for a rainy day!
There's a rumor
I heard about ramen
that's supposedly made by
some kind of phantom alien!
Phantom ramen?
[MEOW] Its flavor is like
something not of this dimension.
One that nobody
else can imitate.
Because it's so unusual
they say it must be made
by an as-yet-unknown species.
And where is this ramen shop?
Yeah, see, the thing is,
information on it is
sketchy at best,
so we won't really
know until we taste it.
But, given that I'm
a ramen connoisseur,
I'm sure I'll be able to tell
the second I put it in my mou--
Now listen closely, kitty.
If this info is bogus, you're
in for a whole universe of hurt.
Got it!
Yoo-hoo!
Crispy fried dragon!
[MEOW] Yay!
Checking in at Boobies.
Man, boobs really
are one of the wonders
of the universe, aren't they?
[QT] But you were just going on
about how butts were
the superior feature.
Oh, really?
I don't remember that.
[QT] No, of course
you don't.
So why'd we come here if we're
searching for phantom ramen?
Don't be an idiot!
The first step in any search
is conducting interviews.
Excuse me, Honey?
How can I help you?
[DANDY] Ever heard of something
called phantom ramen?
Oh, yeah!
[ALL THREE] What?
Hold on, are you serious?
[HONEY]
Totally!
[QT] Does this seem a
little too easy to you?
[grunting noises]
Huh?
Yeah, he's right. If it's
ramen you're after, buddy,
you gotta go check out Ra-sta.
What's Ra-sta?
He is referring to the Space
Ramen Station, young gashopper.
It is a place where ramen shops
from all different regions
of space gather
to sell their dishes.
Right. Hey, that
gives me an idea.
Let's go there!
So this is it, huh?
[COOKS]
Welcome!
Checking in at
the Noodle Galaxy.
[CLERK]
Hey, boys. What'll it be?
Ah...
How about four large orders of
extra noodles with hen fruit?
Huh?
And all on one tab.
[CLERK] Right! A pair
of egg-whopper-toppers
with quadruple everything!
[COOKS] Heard!
[QT} They appear to be
speaking a different language.
[CLERK] Here ya go.
Every ramen aficionado knows
the key to success is the broth.
No, I shouldn't get
started on that,
or I'll be going on
about it all night.
[QT] So, what's the verdict?
Is this the phantom ramen?
No, no, no. It's not even
in the neighborhood.
[DANDY] Hmm. Surprisingly
passable, though.
[MEOW] Yes, I concur.
[slurping]
[QT] Let's check the
next place, already!
[GEL] Hmmm...
This can't possibly be right.
We've conducted a thorough
search using galaxy street view
but despite all our efforts,
there is still no trace of him.
[BEA] Doctor Gel.
We have finally
ascertained Dandy's location.
[GEL] We have?
Good! Commence pursuit at once!
Gogol Empire Seventh Fleet.
Move out!
[COOKS]
Welcome!
[MEOW] Checking in
at the Ramen Nebula.
So this is the raw
food movement in action.
[MEOW] I think it's
pretty good, actually.
[QT ]I hate to be the
bearer of bad news, but...
...we're down to
zero woolongs on-hand.
I don't see how we're
going to pay for this.
That woulda been a good
thing to know before we ate!
[QT] I would hate for the
authorities to get involved
if we walked on the tab.
Hey, that chick over there...
[QT] Is she a friend of yours?
Let's find out.
[QT] Dandy?
[DANDY] Hey. Well,
hello there, beautiful.
What a delicious surprise.
This must be my lucky day.
So, lovely.
What is your name?
What?
Yes! I'm speechless, too!
Destiny's in the air!
I can practically hear
Beethoven's Sixth
playing just for us.
"Destiny" was
the fifth symphony.
You are a shy one, aren't you?
That's okay, baby.
Spit it out. What are
you trying to say?
Direct, I like that in a woman.
I do have something
very important to ask you.
Babe.
Can ya spot me some cash?
Huh?
[SQUAD MEMBER]
Don't move.
One step and we'll shoot!
No, my ramen!
[SCARLET] Didn't your
mothers ever teach you
not to waste your food?
You should all be
ashamed of yourselves.
My name is Scarlet, by the way.
And don't you forget it.
[SCARLET]
Sorry about the mess.
[CLERK]
Thanks, ma'am.
Whatever your name is,
that's a grade-A butt
you've got there, baby.
[BEA]
Doctor.
It seems the battle squad we
dispatched has been wiped out.
[GEL]
The whole squad?
One man took them all out?
Perhaps we've underestimated
what Dandy is capable of.
I'm sorry, sir.
We'll pinpoint his
new location ASAP.
[GEL] Good. The pursuit
must continue!
[MEOW]
Checking in at Andromenda.
[QT] Attacked out of
the blue like that...
I wonder who those thugs were.
[DANDY]
Hmm...
[QT] What is it?
Do you have an idea?
I think I either know something
or I have absolutely
no clue at all.
[QT]
What does that mean?
Jeez, I can't remember
every tiny detail, okay?
Don't move!
[QT] How did they figure
out where we were?
Who knows?
Lucky guess, maybe?
Too tough!
[MEOW] Checking in
at Fullmetal Noodlist.
[SQUAD MEMBER]
Don't move!
[QT] How did they figure
out where we were?
Who knows?
Lucky guess, maybe?
Checking in at "Men" in Black.
[SQUAD MEMBER]
Don't move!
[QT] How did they figure
out where we were?
Who knows?
Lucky guess, maybe?
[BEA]
I don't understand.
All these attempts
and we haven't got him.
[GEL]
Indeed.
Dandy is a fearsome opponent.
[BEA]
What should we do, Doctor?
[GEL]
We have no choice.
We must send the
whole fleet to attack.
Gogol Seventh, move out!
Warp!
Strange, isn't it?
These guys just keep showing up.
How do they know where we are?
Who knows?
Lucky guess, maybe?
[DANDY] What are you doing
with that thing, anyway?
You're always messing with it.
Keep your feet to yourself.
If you wanna know what I'm
doing, you'll have to follow me.
Huh? Let me see that.
Hey!
[QT] He's been broadcasting our
every location with this thing.
You stupid, useless ball of fur!
[BEA] We're warping out at
the target's location now.
[GEL] Excellent. All hands,
prepare for combat.
[GEL]
Huh?
Well, where is he?
[CLERK]
Here you go.
Your extra garlic, mile-high,
double greasy veggie towers.
Whoa.
That's sure greasy, all right.
Mm hmm. Grease is the main
reason for eating the thing.
[DANDY] Guess we
should dig in, huh?
[MEOW]
Absolutely.
Yum!
What is with you?
The stale, chewy noodles.
The salty, buttery broth.
The limp vegetables.
Considered as
individual components,
they sound disgusting.
But combined, they create
a heady, addictive flavor.
A flavor not native
to our dimension!
This is it! This is
the phantom ramen
we have been searching for!
This slop?
Are you kidding me?
[QT]
You can't be serious.
Do not doubt me, my friends.
Have you not noticed
that this store doesn't
make its own ramen on site?
Over there!
Do you see?
[DANDY]
New idea...
We need to find out
what's in that thing!
[CLERK E] Hey, you
maniac! Get down!
[QT]
Dandy!
[CLERK F]
You little punk!
[CLERK G]
I got him!
Take that!
Whoa!
[MEOW]
Whoa, hold on!
[DANDY]
Whoa.
What's wrong with it?
[NARRATOR] Wormholes:
similar to black holes
in that they absorb
time and space;
however, there is a difference.
Wormholes are
more like shortcuts.
Each one generally
has a fixed exit.
[DANDY] Aren't you bein'
a little blasé about this?
Damn.
Where the hell are we?
[QT] Dandy!
Do you read me?
Go ahead, QT!
[QT] You're likely in
an alternate dimension.
Huh?
What d'you know?
It really was a flavor
from another dimension.
[QT] When you forced your
way through the wormhole,
you deepened the rift in
the space-time continuum,
making travel between
points more dangerous.
Hey, Dandy.
See that?
Why, what is it?
[DANDY]
Two ramens, please.
[OLD MAN]
Coming up.
[DANDY] Hey, Pops,
looks to me like your shop
is pretty well established.
Could you tell us how
long you've been here for?
Oh...
I guess it must be about
ten thousand years now.
Been ninety years since
I had any customers, though.
When people stopped coming,
I arranged to send the
ramen through the wormhole
so it could be sold elsewhere
and I could still make a living.
Of course, by the
time it arrives,
the noodles have gone stale
and the flavor of
the broth has changed,
but folks seem
to like it anyhow.
Well, that's one mystery solved.
There are plenty of places
a guy can open a ramen shop.
Why here?
I'm guessing there's
a story behind that.
Tell me, sir.
Who are you?
It's Dandy.
But, you can
call me Space Dandy.
By the look of it,
I figure you for an earthling.
Not a bad planet, Earth.
I've been there before myself,
if you'll believe it.
Though I wouldn't
blame you if you didn't.
It happened so long ago,
I couldn't tell you when it was.
I was a reckless kid.
Always getting into trouble.
Until one day there
was an accident.
I took somebody's life.
I had to leave after that.
I fled my home world,
always on the run
from one planet to another,
hoping no one
would track me down.
Then one day long after
my heart had grown weary
and my soul had grown exhausted.
I found myself on
a world called Earth.
An earthling came along
and took me under his wing.
He introduced me to the
comforting flavor of ramen.
It was an experience
I would never forget.
And a flavor,
I would always cherish.
After my time on Earth ended.
I stopped world-hopping
and fled to this dimension.
I can't go back to
my home world again.
So I'll stay here forever,
cooking my ramen
for whoever cares to order it.
Here you go.
So tell me, Pops.
don't you get lonely
here all by yourself?
[OLD MAN]
You feel something long enough
and it becomes a state of being.
You don't notice
it so much then.
[MEOW]
So. How is it?
Those are some tasty tears.
They make for a
good broth, baby.
[QT]
Dandy, you have to hurry!
The wormhole is going to
close up again any minute now!
What?
[QT] If you're not quick,
you won't be able to get back!
Crap!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
[OLD MAN]
Here you are.
Let's go!
Aw! No fair!
[DANDY]
Hey, Pops.
We do have room for one more.
[OLD MAN] Go on.
Take the bowl.
What? I can? Are you sure?
Oh, thank you, Pops!
[QT]
You've gotta move faster!
C'mon!
Wow. I can't believe we made it.
Uh huh.
My ramen didn't, though.
Yeah.
That was one good bowl of soup.
Don't you think?
Oh, that's right.
You didn't eat yours, did you?
What a shame.
It was truly a flavor
from another dimension.
Ya missed out. Too bad.
[QT] So, uh. What about
the phantom alien?
[QT] Why am I
not surprised?
Apparently, worthless crew
members are just something
I'll have to get
used to around here.
[DANDY] Now then,
on the next Space Dandy.
[QT] There's a next episode?
[DANDY] It's time for some
full-on anime fanservice!
[QT] Eh?
[MEOW] We need
fanservice already?
[DANDY]
Next time:
"Occasionally Even the
Deceiver is Deceived, Baby."
See you then!