[DURAN] Puzzling.
Wouldn't you agree, sir?
Given the fact that your
DNA scan of that man
failed to turn up anything.
[DURAN]
Wait... Don't tell me...
Could it really be...?
Huh?
What?
Where did Dandy go?
No! He's gone!
[QT] The Gogol Empire's
taken Dandy!
[GEL] Welcome, Dandy.
You have no idea how anxious
I've been for this moment.
At last, I've found you.
[QT] I've found out where
they're keeping Dandy!
According to the GPS,
he's in the heart of the
Gogol Empire homeworld.
What? For real?
Isn't that an "impossible
to break into" kind of place?
[QT sighs]
Yeaaaah...
Your thoughts?
I'd rather not let him die.
A man like that is
as rare as it gets.
I agree.
[HONEY] Energy charge:
one hundred twenty percent!
We're heading
into the Gogol Empire!
I'm comfortable with that.
[QT] Roger that!
Then, full speed ahead!
So, who are you anyway?
[GEL] I can't say I'm terribly
surprised you don't know me.
You have somehow
always found a way
to escape my grasp
at the last moment.
[BEA] Doctor,
I'm picking up readings
of a large quantity of
Pyonium coming from Dandy.
Even better they're
still increasing!
I knew it.
Tell me the truth;
you can't pretend you don't
know anything about Pyonium.
Dandy.
Yeah, well, I don't.
This pyo-whats-a-stuff?
See, I can't even say it.
Now, if you want to
talk about booty--
[GEL] Play dumb all you want;
it honestly doesn't matter.
[GEL] The reason we've
pursued you for so long
is due to that Pyonium,
so we'll ascertain the truth
whether you sing or not.
We can simply take the matter
up with your body instead.
[GEL] Either way works for me.
And you're positive
about this?
[DURAN] If Dandy
winds up in their hands,
the entire universe
will fall directly
into the Gogol
Empire's clutches.
Should that happen,
your Excellency,
we'll never know victory again
and the world will be lost.
Very well.
All stations
prepare for battle!
We're going to launch an assault
against the Gogol Empire
and save the universe!
[PERRY] Dr. Gel.
[GEL] Sir!
[PERRY] Finally you've
captured the elusive Dandy.
I must say, well done.
I do not deserve
such praise.
Who knew you'd randomly
catch Dandy's trial
while watching Court TV?
[PERRY] Extract the Pyonium
from the captive
as soon as possible.
Thanks to the development
of the Hulkider.
Correction: The Super Hulkider.
Our new weapon
is ready and waiting.
If we can get the
Pyonium to make it work,
we will be the masters
of the universe!
[DURAN] Theoretically, there are
a countless number of universes
that exist parallel to our own.
However, we have never
been able to cross over
to these other dimensions,
nor even had a glimpse
of their actual existence.
That being said,
we know of connections
that run through the dimensions
called cosmic strings.
These strings can be pulled out
into one universe
using M.E.G.A. Pyonium.
By gaining control
over these connections,
we should be able to
manipulate any possibility.
Some might even call
such a feat the work of God.
Only one man in the
universe holds that key.
Dandy. I must say,
I did not see that coming.
[JOHNNY] All hands, as soon
as we've completed warp,
commence the attack!
[alarms blaring]
What's going on?
[MALE OPERATOR 11A]
A massive fleet has just
dropped out of warp space!
It's the Jaicro Empire!
How could they have known?
[MALE OPERATOR 11A]
They're attacking!
[MEOW] I'm gonna hurl!
[QT] I think we're in
the middle of a battle
between the Gogol Empire
and the Jaicro Empire!
What?
Of course we dropped
into the middle of a war!
This is our chance!
[HONEY] Then let's do it!
Sorry, Dr. Gel.
I hate to break this to you,
but I'm afraid I have
to take Dandy now.
[GEL] You shot me? Why?
[PERRY] What? But-- What?
[DANDY] Come on, fellas.
I think we need
to talk feelings.
[GEL] Say it isn't so, Bea.
Say it isn't so.
It's so.
Hey, Dandy, I need to
put you to sleep, okay?
[DANDY] Like hell you do!
Let me out of here!
[SCARLET] If we don't move it,
we won't live long
enough to save Dandy!
[HONEY] Where is he now?
[QT] The GPS reading
is currently coming
from that tower.
[MEOW] Aw!
You mean we have to
go all the way over there?
Charge through them;
fire at will!
[PERRY] What a
disappointment, Bea.
You were a Jaicro spy
this whole time?
You bet I was,
but technically I'm
nobody's spy anymore.
[PERRY] I'm confused.
Hey. Yeah, it's me.
Oh, I've secured Dandy.
But circumstances have changed.
Tell the Jaicro
commander-in-chief that uh--
I'm in charge now,
and I'm sick and tired
of being pushed
around by you guys.
Adios Muchachos!
[GENERAL 20B] Your Excellency!
Our connection with
the spy has been cut off!
Cut off? Go! Now!
[MEOW] Are you sure
we can't turn back?
If we leave him, we'll
be in even more danger.
How much farther
to the tower?
[QT] Let me see.
[SCARLET] See faster!
This ship won't last long!
[BEA] I'll be taking
the Pyonium for myself.
Whoever possesses it--
--will be able to
rule the whole universe!
Basically, I'm going to
be King of All the Things!
I'll be a god!
[screams]
[SCARLET] This isn't good!
[HONEY] There has to
be some way out of here!
[QT] Might as well. Bam!
All right!
Sir, they're planning
to use the Pyonium
to activate their
massive weapon overhead.
I figured as much.
So how do we stop them?
Where in the tower
is Dandy being held?
[QT] Well, the GPS readings
are actually coming
from the very top, so--
What?
Why didn't you say that
before we started down?
I think we're
being attacked.
Those are the
Gogol patrol robots.
Can you shake them?
I can try!
[PERRY] That treacherous
Bea. He'll pay.
I'll kill him for this!
Surprise. Here's Johnny.
[PERRY] Commander Johnny?
[JOHNNY] Long time
no see Admiral Perry.
[PERRY] Indeed.
How did you get up here?
How do you think?
So, what do you say?
Shall we settle things
right here, right now?
Oh yes, my time
has finally come!
From this moment on, I will
be ruler of the universe!
[GEL] Not so fast.
I'm not dead yet, friend!
I've worked far
too hard to get Dandy.
I'll crush anyone who
tries to take him from me!
[HONEY] Yeah! All right!
[JOHNNY] What's so funny?
Don't you value your life?
[PERRY] Go ahead and shoot.
A gun is hardly going
to put an end to things.
[JOHNNY] What?
[PERRY] Once the weapon starts,
no one will be able to stop it.
You're insane!
[PERRY] Insane and winning.
You've known the virtual
image of a nightmare;
now meet the real thing.
Ah!! Dandy!
[QT] Are you alive?
Hi Dandy!
Oh, hey guys!
[DANDY] Thanks for saving me.
I probably owe you one for that.
[GEL] Dandy.
It's up to you.
If you don't stop that weapon,
the whole of the universe--
[coughs]
--will disintegrate
into nothing.
[DANDY]
QT, where's the Aloha Oe?
Bad news.
[QT] Even the Little
Aloha got all busted up.
Dandy.
I would be honored
to let you use my ship.
[DANDY] Listen up, everyone.
I'm going to do this alone.
Aww!
That's crazy talk.
How are you gonna get
all the way up there
and stop it
without any help?
[QT] What Meow said!
You don't seem to grasp
the significance
of us rescuing you.
[HONEY] Yeah, I mean, yeah!
We just got done saving you;
you can't go die!
[DANDY] I'm not gonna die!
[DANDY] Each one of you risked
your lives to come to my rescue.
And that's why I can't
let you throw away
your lives now; not for me.
Not again.
I got this. Don't worry
about me, babies.
[GEL] Go, Dandy. I believe.
[DANDY] What the hell?
[roaring]
[strained grunting]
[DANDY]
Auuuuuggghhh!!
[QT] Anyone know
what that light's about?
Yeah, I got nothin'.
It's glorious.
[NARRATOR] My stars, Dandy,
you are a constant source of
"I don't know what."
[DANDY] Thanks. Wait.
I feel like I've heard
your voice before.
[NARRATOR]
That's because you have.
I've been watching
over you for a while, now.
Once as a Chameleonian,
but mostly as a narrator.
[DANDY] Huh?
[NARRATOR] I am one
who is not subject
to any physical restrictions.
I am one who can traverse the
entirety of time and space.
[DANDY] Wouldn't that make
you kinda like God, though?
[NARRATOR] Of course.
If that's what you want
to call me, I won't object.
[DANDY] Weird.
[NARRATOR]
You should have forgotten
your memories from
parallel universes.
I doubt you remember
the you who was a surfer,
the you who was a space racer,
or even the you
who was a trucker.
[DANDY] I don't
remember anything.
[NARRATOR] You are someone
who can conceivably be one
and the same while
simultaneously existing
in all other universes.
In other words, you are
the one and only being
who can freely pass between
the different dimensions.
[DANDY] Okay. So what
do you want from me?
[NARRATOR] This world,
over which I have reigned
for roughly fourteen
point eight billion years,
is now in a state of collapse.
All universes,
including the parallel ones,
will be coming
to an end as well.
[DANDY] Whoa.
[NARRATOR] This is more
than a "whoa," Dandy.
This is because of you.
[DANDY] Whoa.
[NARRATOR] Okay.
After it disappears
into a singularity,
the world will be reborn.
Which means I need a successor.
[NARRATOR]
Dandy, you are the only one
who is worthy to take
on the role of God.
[NARRATOR] Um. What's wrong?
[DANDY] This being God thing,
does that mean I won't
have a body anymore?
[NARRATOR] Of course.
God is one who
transcends all matter.
[DANDY] Oh. Without a body,
going to Boobies
won't be any fun.
[NARRATOR] Pardon?
[DANDY] This is the
stupidest idea ever.
I'm out. No God for me!
[NARRATOR] I don't understand.
You're seriously turning down
the opportunity to be God?
Believe it!
See ya, voice of God guy!
[NARRATOR] No, wait!
Stop for a minute
and think, Dandy!
This decision means the
world will have no God!
[DANDY] Stay Dandy, baby!
[DANDY] Show me a "boob-man,"
and I'll show you a no-brain,
no-class knuckle-dragger
who knows nothing
of the fairer sex.
There are far more
important things to consider.
And by that I mean--
[QT] Is something wrong, Dandy?
QT. You are
still you, right?
[QT] Of course I'm still
me. Why wouldn't I be?
Ah. Guess it doesn't
really matter.
[DANDY] As I was saying,
it's all about the legs, baby!