[NARRATOR]
Space Dandy.
He's a dandy guy... in space.
He combs the galaxy
like his pompadour,
on the hunt for aliens.
Planet after planet he searches,
discovering bizarre new
creatures both friendly and not.
These are the
spectacular adventures
of Space Dandy and his
brave space crew... in space.
[DANDY]
You're sure that you're sure?
[MEOW] Come on!
Of course I'm sure.
I know a good source
when I see one,
and word on the street is that
there's a rare kind of alien
named Code D. on Planet Planta.
[QT] And what was your
source for this information?
[MEOW] The newest edition
of the totally reputable
Space Adventurer Magazine.
Their stories are true.
I'm not buying
what you're selling.
[QT]
Problem!
There's a powerful
magnetic field
being emitted near
the planet's north pole,
which means we can't
get any closer than this.
See?
That proves it.
No one's bagged this alien
for the simple reason
that they can't get
close enough to do it.
Great, so what do we do now?
[QT humming]
Gentlemen, I believe you
are forgetting something.
This ship happens to be equipped
with an amazingly advanced
device known as
the instant transporter.
[DANDY]
You mean that piece of crap
that takes thirty minutes
to beam us anywhere?
Hm-hm.
I won't have you guys
denigrating the
transporter any longer!
I've refurbished
the entire thing.
Its transport speed is now fifty
times faster than the original!
Yeah?
Wow, that was
really handy of you.
Don't look so surprised.
You two may spend
all your time slacking,
but I, for one, have been
working my gears off
to improve this ship!
[DANDY]
So, transport us.
That is, if you're
all done nagging.
[QT]
All right. Here we go.
[MEOW]
Woo.
[DANDY]
Get on with it.
[QT] Oh, I forgot to
mention something.
The transporter
is definitely faster,
but its accuracy may
have suffered a bit.
Damn you, QT!
[DANDY groaning]
Hey!
I don't belong in here!
Do you even understand
what I'm saying?
Hello?
[DANDY] I'm not some
kinda display item!
Huh?
[MEOW]
Ow!
[DANDY]
Hey!
Don't ignore me! Come on!
I'm talkin' to you!
I mean you, leafy guy!
Aw, man, that's disgusting!
They're talking?
Maybe I should give this a try.
[PLANT CREATURE]
Excuse us.
We were having the impression
that you were unusual plant.
Oh, is that what you guys are?
Some kinda smart plants?
[DR. H]
My name is Doctor H.
And you are first
creature we have met
that is not plant and
also not microorganism.
[SMALL CREATURE squeals]
[DR. H]
Ah. You forgive her.
My daughter is somewhat curious.
You've got a daughter?
[DR. H]
Please, enjoy the hospitality.
Make yourself at home.
[beeping noise]
[QT]
Oh, good! You are alive!
Yeah, no thanks to you!
Why do I always let you
get me into these messes?
[QT]
Well, any luck?
Did you find the rare alien?
If you mean the freaky
plants then, yep, I did.
[QT] Nah, you can
forget about those.
There's no reward for
registering vegetation.
Seriously?
[QT]
Yes.
I think you're better off
focusing on this Code D alien.
Shouldn't be too hard!
Sure, if you're not actually
the one who has to do it.
[SMALL CREATURE]
What kind of thing are you?
Sorry?
[SMALL CREATURE]
What are you?
I'm human, baby.
Isn't that obvious?
[SMALL CREATURE]
Human! Hi, Human!
Nice to meet you!
I'm zero-three-three-H.
Oh, well, that's a pretty name.
[033H]
Thank you!
Thank you, Human!
[NARRATOR]
Welcome to Planet Planta.
It's long been known as
a world where plants alone
were able to thrive, their
growth rampant and unchecked.
But in recent years, a
stunning evolution has occurred.
The planet is now a
plant republic comprised
of eighteen different states.
Vegims are a
cerebral plant people
who live mainly in
the northern hemisphere.
They possess
elevated intelligence
and use tiny organisms
known as microbes
to perform hard labor
and menial tasks.
In contrast to the
Vegims are the Movies,
which inhabit the
southern hemisphere.
They are a lower order of plant
and live a simpler lifestyle.
[MEOW]
Aww.
That's about as dead as it gets.
Huh?
Is this supposed to be
some kind of welcome present?
♪♪♪
[DR. H]
Hm?
♪♪♪
[DANDY]
Huh.
You weren't kidding.
There really isn't
a thing on this planet
but a bunch of plants, is there?
[033H]
Human. Human.
So, here's the deal.
I'm looking for a rare
alien they call Code D.
Maybe you can help
me out with that?
[033H]
I can!
What? You know Code D?
[033H screaming]
[033H]
Run now! Run now!
Huh?
[DR. H] Those things that chase
you we call federal microbes.
That membrane is special.
Only plants are
able to pass through.
No microbes can enter.
[DANDY]
Huh?
No, I really can't.
I'm completely stuffed!
Well, I wouldn't
want to offend them.
[DANDY]
So anyway.
Is there anything else you can
tell me about this Code D guy?
[DR. H] Code D is located at
energy center of north pole.
It is not a safe place to go.
By "not safe" you
mean "real dangerous."
[DR. H]
Code D is different.
Special. Emits intense smell.
This smell does something
interesting to plants.
Makes us grow quickly.
Makes us quite big.
[DANDY] And by "quite big,"
you mean "freakin' huge."
[DR. H] Code D's
energy is much too strong
and hazardous to examine safely.
I want to investigate
Code D, like you do, but plants,
we cannot stay close for long
enough, so I can do nothing.
Well, don't worry.
You're smart.
You'll figure something out.
[DR. H] It's possible human like
you could go to energy center.
You would not respond
to the essence as plants do:
would not grow big.
[033H]
I go, too! I go, too!
I want to go with you!
I'm going! I'm going! I'm going!
[DR. H]
A giant bug?
Yeah? Let's go!
I can take on this
caterpillar, no problem!
No way! A dead battery?
Uh-oh!
[VOICE]
Stop now!
Doctor, this is unacceptable.
[DR. H]
CoCamuka!
[COCAMUKA]
I have my eyes and ears.
This one, my spy, reported
your intentions to me.
Not cool.
[COCAMUKA] North pole
energy center is off-limits.
Going there is violation of law.
[DR. H] Well, CoCamuka,
you found us.
What intend you do with us?
[DR. H]
I am asking most strenuously.
Code D is dangerous.
Must be investigated
as soon as possible.
[COCAMUKA] Don't get
your stamen in a knot.
As you know, we can
no longer live without it.
[COCAMUKA] These fear-mongers
are under arrest.
Take them away.
Man, I don't think I've
ever been this full before.
They sure know how
to treat a guest.
This place is so great.
[DANDY]
Damn.
What's that jerk's problem?
[DR. H]
CoCamuka is not nicest guy.
He is leader of this country.
Long ago.
I was part of north pole
research group.
Was our job to
investigate Code D.
I made my report to CoCamuka.
Code D is dangerous, I said.
Vegims must do something.
But he did not listen.
Instead, he buried my report,
and removed me from
research group permanently.
I think is because
I threatened his authority.
Nini! Nini!
[DR. H]
You are here!
You came for rescue?
[033H]
Nini! Thank you! Thank you!
[DR. H]
This is Nini.
She is in plant
entertainment industry.
Is also very
good friend of ours.
[DANDY]
This is it, huh?
Man, you weren't kidding
around about that stench.
[DR. H] We cannot go
further with you, human.
You must continue on your own.
I can go! I can go! I can!
[DANDY]
So, how do I go about catching
this Code D thing, anyway?
[DR. H] Locate cables used
for extracting essence,
and remove them.
[DANDY]
Gotcha!
Ugh!
That really smells!
[033H]
Can do it.
[DANDY]
Damn.
[033H]
I can go no farther.
From here on, you are alone.
[DANDY]
Oh, well. Here goes.
That's it? Big, bad Code D?
It doesn't look like
much more than a stone.
[033H whining]
[DR. H] At one time, we
were ordinary plants.
Not thinking, talking beings.
And then, one day it came here.
Code D.
A meteorite that
landed on Planet Planta
and changed everything.
We plants evolved.
We became intelligent.
However, I think, maybe,
our sudden evolution
was not such a blessing.
But that era is over now.
We return to our original forms.
To what we were meant to be.
I feel myself fading.
Is all right. Is not
an ending, I think.
Is a new beginning.
[033H]
Human! Human!
Bye bye.
What happened?
[MEOW] So, this whole time
Code D was a meteorite?
Just some glorified hunk
of space dust?
[QT] They don't give out reward
money for finding rocks.
And there was nothing else
down there worth reporting?
Well that didn't work out.
Nope, no it didn't, fatty.
I gotta say, I'm fine if
I never see another plant.
Huh?
What the hell?
[MEOW]
In a town like this,
all covered in dust
and full of nothin',
even dreams can
be hard to come by.
Next time: "There's
Always Tomorrow, Baby."