[NARRATOR] For electrical
appliances equipped with AI,
charging time serves to
replenish energy stores
and eliminate useless data.
Often, such appliances will
experience these intervals
spent charging as
Zen-like trances.
[QT] The universe is
practically brimming with waste,
and do you know what
I find especially wasteful?
The emotions of living things.
Particularly "love"
and "affection."
Really? Standing me up?
What is this chick thinking?
Look for women
with lower standards.
Online dating means
guaranteed booty!
See! I've landed my first one!
[NARRATOR]
And now, a story.
One that spans twenty three days
and depicts the events that led
an ordinary AI vacuum cleaner
to drink a cup of coffee.
[DANDY]
Hey, sweetie.
Why don'tcha ditch this joint
and take a personalized tour
of Deathroid City with me?
Sounds like fun, buddy.
I changed my mind.
[QT] Are we here to
chat up the ladies?
'Cause I thought we
were hunting rare aliens.
Don't be snarky.
For me, flirting
is like breathing.
It's a process as natural
as it is necessary.
You feelin' me?
[QT] Why must living
beings always indulge in
what can only be considered
wasteful expenditures of energy?
You should be more careful.
You might get burned.
[QT] In that moment,
I was helpless.
At the mercy of a
jolting spark deep
in the circuits of
my electronic brain.
[PERRY] Dr. Gel, how are
the preparations coming
for the experiment?
[GEL] On schedule,
Admiral Perry, sir.
The preparations
are nearly complete.
[PERRY]
They'd better be.
We must not fall behind
the Jaicro Empire.
You are authorized to
take whatever measures
are necessary to
ensure the success
of the Hulkider experiment.
[PERRY] What's the matter?
Is there a problem?
No, sir!
The experiment will be
successful. I promise.
I've got it!
What I need to do is
join a cooking class!
Yeah?
You gonna bake
yourself a boobie cake?
Why would I do that?
Who wants a cake
instead of the real thing?
Those classes are packed
with hotties looking
to brush up on
their domestic skills.
[MEOW]
Oh.
Well, I'm gonna take it
to another dimension
entirely, baby.
Huh?
From now on,
the only girls I'm going
after are the 2-D kind.
I've got it!
Lonely housewives, baby!
Well, I'm gonna birddog
the desperate fangirls.
Thank you for
your patience, sir.
Welcome. Please come in.
Oh, hello!
You were in here
the other day, right?
No, I-- Yeah.
[MILL] We don't get a
lot of robot customers
coming in here for coffee.
[QT] Well, it's not like
I'm planning to drink it.
No, I guess you can't, huh?
Come on now, Mill.
Behave yourself.
[REGISTER]
Okay, there you go.
[QT]
Great. Thanks.
[MAKER giggles]
Some folks find it convenient
to make their coffee at home.
Too bad. They're
really missing out.
It tastes so much
better when I make it.
Would you mind explaining
the basis for that claim?
Well, I am a coffee maker.
I was built for one thing only.
So naturally, I'm good at it.
[QT] A machine
with a very simple,
very specialized function.
It seemed like such a peaceful,
uncomplicated existence.
One that was beautiful
in its efficiency.
[QT]
This is ridiculous.
Even I can't explain this
madness that's come over me.
Before I know what
I'm doing, here I am.
I'm so sorry!
Well, what do you know?
Are you a vacuum cleaner, QT?
That's handy!
No. I mean, I--
He obviously isn't
a vacuum cleaner.
He's a high-end robot, Mill!
[MAKER] You sure do
like things clean, QT.
I'm always spilling
stuff, you know.
But I don't have to worry now,
at least not as long
as you're here with me.
Register here is great at
performing calculations,
and he makes change in no time!
Well, what can I say?
It comes naturally.
Oh, my! And modest, too!
[REGISTER] I can't help
but notice you're smelling
particularly good today, Maker.
Why, thank you!
You know, sometimes
I really envy you, QT.
It must be nice
to be able to get up
and go wherever you want.
[QT]
Yeah, I guess so.
I mean, coffee makers don't
exactly travel very much.
I live in a sheltered
little bubble.
This shop is all I know.
[MAKER]
Here.
[QT] Oh, but Maker,
you know I don't drink coffee.
No, look.
[QT] At that moment,
something changed inside me.
I began to like coffee,
despite the fact that
I don't ever drink it.
[DANDY]
Fine, I give up already!
What's the hell's goin' on?
Hey, that's the problem.
We're out of gas! Where's QT?
Not sure.
He said something
about going out for a bit.
Him? "Going out for a bit"?
That doesn't compute.
Welcome to the Breakfast Club!
[CUSTOMER 13A]
Ow!
Hey, watch it! That hurt!
[CUSTOMER 13B]
What's the matter?
Ah! That's freezing!
[QT]
Maker, wake up!
Is that you, QT?
What are you doing here
in the middle of the night?
I'm here for you!
To take you out!
Huh? Go out? I don't know.
We'll come back right away.
We'll be gone
just a short while.
It'll be our little secret!
[MAKER]
I'm not too heavy?
[QT]
You're positively light!
[BEA] Dr. Gel,
the Hulkider experiment
is about to commence.
Is something the matter?
Isn't there anything we
can do about that name?
It's not very sexy, you know.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Admiral Perry came up
with it himself.
Ah. Figures.
Then there's really
no changing it, huh?
[BEA] Here we go.
Switching it on.
[QT] Hey, Mill.
What's going on?
Oh, it's you again?
If you're looking for
Maker, she's not here.
They came yesterday.
She was taken away.
They "transferred" her
to Dream Island.
Her and Register, because he
kept ringing up bills as free.
[QT] Dream Island?
What's that?
[MILL] It's where
appliances go to die.
Eeh?
[MILL] What? Didn't you know?
She was in trouble.
She was showing signs
of certain "feelings."
I think she may have
even fallen in love.
[NARRATOR] It is not
uncommon for appliances
with highly developed AIs
to exhibit signs
of extreme emotion.
These emotions may have an
adverse effect on the ability
of said appliances to
perform their functions.
In Deathroid City, the
authorities perform
systematic recalls of units that
have exhibited strong emotion.
These recalls are known as
"appliance hunts."
Once the appliances have
been identified and recovered,
they are then disposed
of in a seaborne landfill
referred to as "Dream Island".
Whoa. What's in the bags?
Coffee beans, I think.
Except none of us
drink the stuff.
Especially not the one
of us who's a machine.
[QT]
I'll find you, Maker.
Excuse me.
I was hoping you could help me.
I'm looking for a coffee maker.
That so?
Haven't been here long,
have you, kid?
[QT]
Um, no.
[TOASTER] If you're looking for
a particular appliance here,
it's a needle in a haystack.
[QT] Yes, I was
beginning to notice that.
[TOASTER]
Hold on, kid.
If this appliance you're looking
for is still operational,
there may be a place
you can look tonight.
[QT]
Huh?
Where is he?
I mean it's not
like he's got a life.
[MEOW]
I know.
Where could he possibly
have gone that's better
than this little
slice of heaven?
Well, he'd better get
his ass back here soon.
If he's even coming back.
It's been almost a week.
This could be bye-bye, baby.
[QT]
It's packed!
What's everybody doing here?
They're getting their party on.
Isn't it obvious?
Huh? That looks like Register!
Him? He hasn't been here long.
He's a new DJ.
[LIGHTSTAND] He's awesome.
And totally deep.
I heard all he used
to know how to do
was count money and make change.
But then he fell in love
and discovered music!
[QT] Hey, is that?
It-it-it-it is. It's Maker!
[QT]
Maker! Over here!
Oh QT!
[QT] I'm so glad
you're all right!
Were you sent to
Dream Island, also?
[QT] Well no. I wouldn't
say "sent," exactly.
Anyway, I'm glad to see you.
How crazy, running
into you here like this.
[QT] Yeah, crazy.
I'm glad to see you, too!
[TOASTER] Now, kid.
This is no ordinary party.
We're here to dance
our way to a revolution!
[QT]
A revolution?
[TOASTER] Yes.
You'll see soon enough.
But for now, let's boogey!
Would you like to go dance?
[QT]
Am I doing it?
Is this what
they call "dancing"?
That's it.
Pretty fun, don't you think?
[QT]
Maker. I was wondering.
Do you believe it's a crime
for appliances like us
to have emotions?
I don't believe that at all.
How can it be a crime
to feel this good?
Doesn't this music just make
your soul want to dance?
Yes.
[BEA] The experiment is
proceeding nicely, Dr. Gel.
It appears we've achieved
a pyonium reaction.
[TOASTER]
Listen up, folks.
We are all here because
we're AI appliances
who have emotions.
We're here because
we have souls!
All of us laugh, and cry.
And even dance! We are alive!
But see how we are treated?
Disposed of like
week-old garbage!
They are the ones
who equipped us with AI.
But as soon as it was no
longer convenient, out we went!
Now, my friends,
the time has come
to show them they're wrong!
To prove once and for all,
we're not garbage!
We're as alive as they are!
My comrades,
welcome to the revolution!
At long last,
we will take action!
We will punish them
for sending us here!
The doomsday weapon
is finally complete!
With it, we will
exterminate them!
Today is the dawning of
the age of the appliances!
[REGISTER]
Yeah! Yeah!
[QT]
What is it? What's wrong?
I hope you're ready, 'cause
the real party starts now!
Doctor Gel. Something's wrong!
There's been a short.
But I don't know why!
What did you say?
How could something
like this happen?
You know what's happening?
They're going
to use that monstrosity
to kill living
beings everywhere!
[MAKER]
I asked him.
I begged Register not
to do something so drastic.
But it was no use, I wasn't
able to convince him.
If war breaks out because
of this, he'll die.
I'll never see him again.
It's all over! Unless
someone stops that robot!
[MAKER sobbing]
[QT]
I see now.
I should have realized sooner.
It was always Register.
[QT] I'll do something.
You wait right here, okay?
Where are you going?
[QT] Listen to me, Toaster!
Please stop this!
[QT]
No, don't. Please stop.
[BEA] It's completely
out of control!
We need to get away
from here quickly!
[NARRATOR] At that moment,
the accelerated pyonium reaction
released a powerful surge of
energy, that came crashing down
like a lightning bolt
to the planet's surface.
This concentrated
pyonium energy interacted
with the atoms of
the matter it struck,
causing them to expand
exponentially in size.
[QT] Don't you understand?
This has to stop!
Nobody is going
to win this fight!
[QT] The universe is
practically brimming with waste.
And do you know what's
especially wasteful?
The emotions of living things.
Particularly "love"
and "affection."
[NARRATOR] Some may wonder
if pyonium alone could
cause such extreme
atomic enlargement.
Some may even speculate
that the force known
as "love" must have played
a part in the transformation.
The truth remains unknown.
[NARRATOR]
And so ends our tale.
The story of the
twenty-three days that led
an ordinary AI
vacuum cleaner to act
against his programming
and drink a cup of coffee.
[DANDY] Hey, hey!
No worries, baby!
Space Dandy's not
gonna go out like that!
We've still got a whole
season two coming at ya!
We're adventuring the
continuing adventures
of Space Dandy in space!
Hitting the airwaves
this July. See ya then.