[NARRATOR]
Space Dandy.
He's a dandy guy... in space.
He combs the galaxy
like his pompadour,
on the hunt for aliens.
Planet after planet he searches,
discovering bizarre new
creatures both friendly and not.
These are the
spectacular adventures
of Space Dandy and his
brave space crew... in space.
Rejected.
Rejected. Rejected.
Now, who's next?
A guy who just made the
discovery of the century.
That's who's next up!
It wasn't easy, either.
This bad boy fires
beams from its eyes
and flames from what
I think is its mouth.
After managing to
avoid any and everything
that shot out of
those face holes,
I caught this weird
wild cat off guard.
All it took was a
well-placed karate chop.
[SCARLET] I've never heard
of an alien like that before.
[DANDY]
Hm. No one has.
Cool. Right, baby?
That's why it's the
discovery of the century!
Rejected.
[MEOW]
I told you so.
Nothing gets past that girl.
[DANDY] Look, if you
hadn't been so clumsy,
we'd all be rolling
in reward money by now!
But you had to screw the pooch.
[MEOW] Man, the thought
of money makes me hungry.
[QT] All right,
who's ready to eat?
[MEOW]
Nice timing!
[DANDY]
Mm. Ew.
[QT] What? It's space food I got
through the galaxy mail order's
"Phase Difference
Space Delivery Service."
You don't know what
any of that means, do you?
It came from ten thousand
light-years in the future!
The galaxy mail order is
at the end of the universe,
so it was beyond cheap.
[DANDY]
Ten thousand light years.
Which means...
This crap expired
ten thousand years ago!
[MEOW] Technically,
it doesn't say "consume by";
that's only the "sell by" date.
It might still be okay to eat.
[DANDY] Fine, then why
don't you dig in?!
[QT] Have as much as you like;
we've got plenty.
[DANDY]
Gross.
[QT]
They were having a buy one,
get three hundred sixty
five free special.
Couldn't pass that up.
Ugh, no way I'm eating that.
I guess we'll have to
find refuge in Boobies.
[QT] We don't have
money for Boobies.
Luckily for us, I have
a secret weapon
for just this kind
of predicament.
Check this!
[MEOW]
Check this, what?
You've filled up
your point card.
Your next visit's on us!
You see, we may be poor as hell,
but we can still enjoy Boobies
as long as we have
this sweater puppy.
[QT] How long have you
been waiting to say that?
Longer than you'd think.
I've got a point card
for time served
and I am a faithful customer.
With benefits.
[QT] Right, why work when
you can get point cards?
[DANDY]
Watch this.
Never fails to get him.
[QT] You do realize
your precious card expires
at the end of the day.
No. No!
How many hours
are left in "today"?
[QT]
Two hours, thirty minutes.
Now! Where's the
closest Boobies?!
[QT] There's one in Galaxy
Mexico, District Three.
Then charge the engines.
Two hundred percent!
Full speed ahead!
[QT] It will take us
at least two hours
and forty minutes to get there.
So, you know, not happening.
Damn it.
We've got no other options left.
We gotta warp.
[MEOW] Wait. Didn't you say
we couldn't use the warp drive
because it got broken?
So what?
It's times like these
when a man's gotta do
what a man's got to do!
And this man's got to do!
Hurry up!
Uh. That's probably
enough pushing.
Ow.
So, anyone know where we are?
[QT]
Analysis finished.
Location unknown.
Unable to detect
living organisms.
And Boobies?
[QT] Well, there seems
to be oxygen here.
I don't care about oxygen;
I need Boobies, nothing more!
[MEOW] C'mon, let's
head back to the ship.
We can put out
a distress signal,
and maybe a rescue party
will come find us;
that sounds like fun, huh?
[DANDY]
No way.
There's a Boobies hiding out
there somewhere, I can feel it.
[MEOW]
Nope. No Boobies.
Won't find one.
Not today.
[QT] Even if there
isn't a Boobies,
there might be an alien
that has yet to be recorded.
[MEOW] But I thought you said
there were no signs of life.
[DANDY]
What, are you scared?
No. Please don't
start with this.
Who's a pretty
little scaredy cat?
You are!
Betelgeusians don't get scared.
[DANDY] Ha! Yeah, says the
puss shakin' in his boots.
[QT]
Do you know what that was?
[MEOW]
Right. So who's the puss again?
[MAMITAS]
Someone, please!
[DANDY]
Mmm...
Please, help me!
Okay. I'm on this. Ah--
Hey! QT, what are these?
[QT] Gimmie just
a minute on that!
[MEOW] I don't like what's
going on with their face area.
Warning. You're about to
get a taste of Space Dandy!
[QT] Would you
stop doing that?
Why isn't my beam working
against these things?
What's wrong?
Usually you have
to hit them first.
New idea.
Ready or not...
Run away!
[QT] Bummer, those things
have already been recorded.
They're called Ragians,
which doesn't sound pleasant.
[DANDY] So we won't get any
money for bringing them in.
[MEOW] Oh, as if you
could catch one anyway!
[MAMITAS] Um...
Thank you for saving me.
I don't know what
I would have done.
What's your name?
Well, it's Dandy, but--
You can call me Meow;
and not to brag,
but did you know that
Betelgeuse holds the record
as the number one
consumer of dried fish flakes
in the known universe?
No one knows,
and no one cares!
Hi.
[MEOW]
Jerk.
You two are so funny.
[QT] Are you guys petting
yourselves right now?
My name is Mamitas.
I was just finishing
a little shopping trip
when my warp device
malfunctioned.
I got caught in
what must have been
a space-time distortion
and landed here.
My ship ended up broken, so I
was trapped all by my lonesome.
No need for cryin'
anymore, baby.
I'll personally make
sure you get home safe.
Unless you'd
rather stay with me.
[QT] What?
The Aloha Oe is broken.
Mamitas, is your spaceship's
core system higher
than version five
point two, by chance?
Yeah.
Well, that's good news!
We might be able to repair
the Aloha Oe using
parts from your ship!
Sir, we have finally been
able to determine his location.
[PERRY]
I will not tolerate failure.
Understood?
[GEL]
Yes, sir.
The Seventh Fleet is currently
surrounding the planet
on which we found him.
[PERRY]
Wonderful.
Once we capture
that Space Dandy,
the universe will belong
to the Gogol Empire and
the Gogol Empire alone!
[PERRY laughs]
[MAMITAS]
My spaceship is over there.
[MEOW] Boo, mouth
faces are in the way.
[DANDY] They've got spunk,
I'll give 'em that.
[MAMITAS] I can show
you how to go around.
It's a lot easier.
[GEL] The commander and I will
land on the planet together.
Then, we'll capture him.
[BEA] Doctor, there's
a bit of a problem.
A rather nasty alien
is inhabiting that
planet at the moment.
[GEL]
What?
They're kind of what
you'd call terrifying
because they kind of eat
everything they run into.
[QT] Well, it's older
than I thought,
but there are a number of
parts that still look useable.
[MAMITAS]
So, you're an alien-hunter?
How exciting!
It's not a big deal.
Although, some people do
consider me a touch reckless.
[MEOW] This is off-topic,
but are you a picky eater?
It's okay if you are.
I'll eat practically anything.
[MEOW]
You mean, you're omnivorous?
No way; me too!
That's so cool!
[HONEY] You've filled
out your point card.
Your next visit will be on us!
Check this.
Do ya see how he's a cat?
[HONEY] Oh, no! Your points
are only good for another hour!
Are you even listening to me?
Hurry up and get here already!
[DANDY]
Crap, I forgot, baby!
Get it together, Meow;
we've gotta get out of here.
[BEA]
See, look at this.
It's the Deathgerian, the alien
that's topped the list
of "Aliens I Don't
Want to Be Eaten By"
for twelve years straight!
When you meet one, that's it.
They're gonna eat
you till you're dead.
They're that serious?
[BEA]
As moon dust in your underpants.
[VOICE] Doctor, all
ships are in position!
[GEL]
Withdraw, Seventh Fleet!
It was a close call.
If there's an alien
I don't want to be eaten by,
it's got to be this one.
Come to Dandy!
[QT]
Hooray, I found it!
As long as we
have this little guy,
the Aloha Oe might
start working again!
Hey. Where'd those two go?
No one out-dandies Space Dandy.
Still here and still disgusting.
Spunk only goes so far.
Sorry.
You lose!
The battery is dead?
This is so full of suck!
[QT] Based on the whole
"us not being dead yet" thing,
I think they might be
trying to communicate.
Use your space translator to
see if they're saying something.
You must return home
before it's too late!
This world's dangerous; the
Deathgerian will eat you all!
Deathgeriwhat?
It is a horrible creature
that has targeted
and eaten everyone who
has landed on this planet;
you must leave, immediately!
Yeah, you fools get
all up in our face
with your fancy guns
that don't have batteries
when we just tryin' to warn you
about what's about
to go down, bro.
[QT] Okay, so it looks like
these aliens are weird,
but they're not as
bad as we thought.
Maybe.
Where's the Deathgerian? Talk!
Apologies; I'm not
sure what you mean.
[QT]
Huh?
[ALIEN] Look, y'all
have been fraternizing
with that monster
since you landed.
And you know what, son?
She about to get real,
real hungry up in here.
[ALIEN] Run! Deathgerians
turn into monsters
when they are ready to dine.
[ALIEN]
Well, good luck.
We'll get out of
your poufy hair, now.
[DANDY] Why's it always
gotta be the hot ones?
[MAMITAS] Cat?
Cat...
Cat? No.
Come on; you can't believe
what Space Dandy says.
I've never eaten cat.
[MEOW]
Cool.
I'm not one, though.
Like not technically.
Mamitas?
Meow! Meow, come over here.
I gotta tell you somethin'!
It's really important!
[MEOW]
No, I don't want any!
[DANDY]
She's a booby monster!
Run!
[MEOW]
I'm gone!
[MEOW] Will someone
please at least try
to get up here
and save me already?!
[DANDY]
Meow! I'm coming!
[QT] The repairs
aren't finished yet!
[DANDY] Sounds like time
for the Little Aloha!
Lei me!
[QT] So, are you gonna
try to save Meow?
There's a chance he might not
be completely digested yet.
[DANDY] Farewell,
my dear friend Meow.
I shall never forget you.
[QT] Wait. Where's
the Boobies Point Card?
Doesn't Meow still have it?
[DANDY]
That idiot!
Lucky for him, Space Dandy
doesn't abandon his friends!
[QT] You mean like just now?
What's with this Deathwawhosit?
[QT] When hungry, they transform
into monsters, as we can see,
and then they try to eat
everything around them,
as we can also see.
Then maybe we
should transform, too.
[QT]
What?
[DANDY]
Let's use it.
You know what I'm talkin' about.
[QT]
No, I don't.
[DANDY]
Change!
Hawaii-Yankee!
[QT] What? How did I not
know we could do this?
Oh, yeah!
Bring it on!
[DANDY]
Take this!
Uh oh.
[QT] I wonder what
that's all about.
[DANDY]
Huh?
[DANDY] I get it. She ate
your expired space food.
It's totally making her sick.
[QT]
Oh.
[DANDY]
Open wide!
Want more?
Dig in!
[QT] See. Now aren't
you glad I ordered them?
[SCARLET]
Accepted.
Yeah!
[QT]
Seriously?
The reward was ninety-nine
thousand woolongs?
We may have lost the point card,
but with this much money,
we can pay for all
the Boobies we want.
[QT] Wait, are you sure we
only lost the point card?
I feel like we're missing
something else, too.
[DANDY]
Uh-- Huh...
[DANDY] Neshtime on
Spash Lanly, uh...
[QT]
What are you saying?
You're not making real words.
[MEOW]
Hey guys; what's the dealy-yo?
[ALL] Next time: "Sometimes You
Can't Live With Dying, Baby."