[static]
[disco music playing]
Hey!
No more!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stoooooooooo..!!
Huh?
That was one
crazy ass nightmare.
[QT] We're almost there, guys!
Planet Grease, here we come!
[DANDY] What's the
story on this place?
[QT] My research
says it's the home
of the legendary
Dancingian Festival.
Okay, what
in the hell is that?
[QT] It's named after
the mysterious aliens
that appear on this world
once every hundred years.
Yeah, it's supposed to
be a big blowout bash!
I don't know about
this one, guys.
I've got a real bad
feeling all'va sudden.
[QT] That's not the best part!
There's also a
big dance contest,
and the winner gets
one-hundred-million woolongs!
[DANDY] So many zeroes!
[QT] They say no one aside from
the Dancingians has ever won,
but still--I'm not
gonna let that stop me
from busting a move!
Get with it QT, nobody
does the Robot anymore.
[QT] Even if we can't win,
the Dancingians are obviously
some kind of rare alien.
We can at least try to
catch one while we're there.
I got this!
No one shakes a booty
like yours truly!
[upbeat funk music]
[MEOW] You sure
this is the place?
[QT] That's what the sign says.
[DANDY] Whatever this place is,
I'm pretty sure
we missed the party.
[MEOW] Musta' made a mistake
in your calculations, QT.
[QT] It's 500 years to the day
since the festival listed
on the old flyer I found.
If they do this
every hundred years,
we should be right on time.
[MEOW] So how come
everything's closed?
[QT] I don't know.
It's like a ghost town.
Hey. Check it out!
They're open.
Aw yeah, this place
reeks of bargain bin, baby!
Ahh!!!
Did you see that, Dandy?
It's some kinda crazy
other-dimension thing!
Yeah, but you can't
go in there, buddy.
Only those who can
read are allowed.
Wait, whaddya mean?
Read what?
Oooo!
This one looks rockin'.
[MALE CLERK 22A]
Yeah, there's a rare gem.
Gotta say, you've got
some good taste, my man.
Well they don't call me
Dandy for nothin', baby.
[MALE CLERK 22A]
I wouldn't usually recommend
buying an album
for the cover art.
But this--
This record right here
has got some killer grooves,
so you don't wanna do
more than admire the jacket.
Because if you ever
dropped the needle,
inflation will
spin out of control.
Time flies, life passes you by,
and before you can
blink--poof!--it's all gone.
Hey, what can I say?
Do I know how to
pick 'em, or what?
[QT] Uh, about the festival.
[MALE CLERK 22A] Sorry, can't
help ya, man, I'm just a clerk.
You might wanna ask at the
tourist information center.
[PLANET CHIEF'S WIFE]
They've given up on us.
They haven't shown up in ages,
and I doubt they ever will.
They've washed
their hands of us
and decided to move
on to some new world.
It's about time
you accept that fact.
Who the hell are you?
My goodness! I think
they're sightseers!
Hey, if you don't
like people peekin' in,
hang some damn blinds!
Yeah, that's not
what he said.
[QT] Forgive my friend;
we just wanted to
ask about the festival.
We thought it would
be going on right now.
The festival, huh?
Unfortunately,
it's been centuries
since the last time
we had one here.
I would know.
You see, I am the planetary
chief of this world.
[PLANET CHIEF] Long ago,
galactic bus tours
brought throngs of sightseers
to see the Dancingians.
It was an event like none other,
and thanks to its popularity,
our planet thrived.
But all good things must end.
In the nearly 500 years
since I was born,
the Dancingians haven't
appeared even once.
The tourists
stopped visiting us,
and most of our residents
eventually decided to
relocate to other planets.
Wow, that's gotta suck.
Well, when it's time
to go, it's time to go.
[QT] Excuse me, sir.
What's this?
[PLANET CHIEF] Ah...
That's a photo my mother took
when she was young.
It was the first time
she saw a Dancingian.
[QT] Is there one
in this picture?
I'd like to know
what they look like.
I've never seen one myself;
in fact I doubt there's
anyone left alive who has.
The only exception
being my dear, old mother.
But I'm afraid she can't help.
She's been in a coma
for three hundred years.
I remember her talking about
their beautiful dancing
and how she hoped
she'd get to see it again.
Well, if they aren't around,
then what can ya do, huh?
Besides, I'm sure
these Dancingians have
enough of their own dancy
troubles to worry about.
I just wish my beloved
Planet Grease
could come back to life someday.
Thanks for the snacks.
We gotta go.
[QT] Bye-bye.
Nice talking to ya.
Great space! That booty!
Uh...
It's like it was
built for dancing!
Cut that out, man!
You're ticklin' me!
It's just what we need
to shake life back
into this world!
Still tickles!
Together, we will host
a new dance contest!
The winner gets
seven-hundred-million woolongs!
[DANDY] So many zeroes.
Then you can count me in!
[QT] Me too!
I'm gonna dance all
the way to the bank!
Now hold on.
We don't really have
that kind of money,
but it looks good on the flyer.
We want to make sure
we get folks' attention.
[DANDY CREW]
Eh...?
You'll pretend to
be a Dancingian
and tourists will
flock to our planet
from all over the
universe to see you,
and then we'll fix the
dance contest so you win!
Is there a prize
for second place?
I can win this fair
and square, gramps.
Still, Dandy don't shake
his moneymaker for free!
Please forgive me,
you're right.
You deserve to be compensated.
I can offer you a
magnificent treasure!
It's been in my
family for generations!
Treasure?
Ooooo!
Woah, Agnes Lum to papa!
If I had known you had that
kind of smut lying around--
Now do we have a deal
or do I need to throw
in my wife, too?
[NARRATOR] Since no one seems
to have noticed them yet,
it's probably worth pointing out
the lichens that grow
on Planet Grease.
For eons, the appearance
of these symbiotic life forms
marked the planet's seasons,
until a sudden climatic change
brought them to the
brink of extinction.
The few surviving spores
lay dormant for centuries,
but at last--these
long-forgotten creatures
are ready for a comeback.
[PLANET CHIEF]
Big news from Planet Grease!
The amazing Dancingian
has returned!
Come and see a show
you'll never forget!
Have your picture taken
with a real Dancingian!
Or enter our dance contest
and try for the grand prize of
seven-hundred-million woolongs!
That's right, you heard me!
Seven-hundred-million!
This is a once in a lifetime
opportunity so don't miss out!
Come to Planet Grease today!
[BEA] Dr. Gel?
[BEA] I have to ask,
why are we even trying to
catch Dandy in the first place?
[GEL] Aw, what's the matter,
Bea? What kind of talk is that?
[BEA sighs] I hate to
complain but I'm just tired
of getting blown up
week after week.
A guy like me can
only take so much.
I see.
It sounds like you could
really use a vacation.
Oh, I know!
Perhaps this will motivate you--
When we finish this job
you can take some time off!
[BEA] Do you mean it?
[GEL] I think that's just
what the doctor ordered!
There's no better
way to cleanse the mind.
Tasty treats, a
dip in the hot--
[loud crash]
[GEL]
What the blazes was that?
It looks like a
hit-and-run, sir!
Why, that miserable bastard!
Make sure you get his info!
We'll sue the pants off him!
[QT] Welcome to
Planet Grease, everybody!
Right this way!
Thank you for coming out!
I see we've got
some major contenders
for today's dance contest!
Make your way to the stage!
The show is starting soon!
[DANDY] Aw, come on, man!
Tights, sure, but a hula hoop?
[PLANET CHIEF] I studied
up on Dancingians and apparently
they were accompanied
by some kind of big rings.
I doubt they looked like that
but the audience'll never know.
[BARRY] Barry.
Barrybarry. Barrybarrybarry.
[PLANET CHIEF]
We've got customers!
Huh?
[PLANET CHIEF] Wait, that's it?
[PLANET CHIEF'S WIFE] Mm hmm.
[MEOW and QT] Yeah.
[PLANET CHIEF]
Well, the show must go on!
Hey, Dandy.
Uh. Sorry, I mean,
Mr. Dancingian, you're on!
Got it, baby!
[upbeat disco music]
[BARRY] Barrybarrybarry?
You can't be serious!
[JRAVOLTA] I love to dance!
You love to dance!
Everybody dance!
Oh, spacey dance!
Now move those feet!
We're makin' love to
the beat! Oh, spacey Love!
Everybody rock!
Now everybody roll!
Gotta groove 'til
you move your soul!
The stars are
comin' out tonight!
Tonight we're gonna party,
right? Oh, spacey dance!
So that's a Dancingian?
He's so sexy!
[QT] He has a big ring just
like the old man said he would!
He's gotta be a
genuine Dancingian!
So handsome!
I don't swing that way
but I gotta agree.
It's a pleasure, sir!
Thanks for coming
to Planet Grease!
No worries, my man!
Y'know I'm here for ya!
The name's Ton Jravolta.
Oh wow.
I'm happy to see you!
I was worried you
might never return.
I don't mean to be rude
but what took you so long?
[JRAVOLTA] There are as
many parties as planets!
And I gotta--
Oh! Spacey! See 'em all!
Watch your step, Afro.
Well, I dunno about
the rest of you guys,
but I'm ready to
start the contest!
Yay!
Alright everybody!
Let's dance until we're dizzy!
[CROWD] Aw, yeah!
[retro hip hop music]
[JRAVOLTA] Yeah! Get funky now!
[JRAVOLTA]  Work it out, ya'll!
[retro hip hop music]
[BARRY] Barrybarrybarry.
Barrybarrybarry.
Barrybarrybarrybarry
barrybarrybarry.
Barry. Barry.
[QT] I'm gonna be sick!
Shamone!
I didn't realize you
were still here, Dandy!
[QT] I completely
forgot about him!
Why dontcha just
head back to the ship?
Now that we got the real thing,
we don't really have
any use for you.
Hey!
Whoa! Spacey, not cool!
Wanna dance with me
'stead a bein' a tool!
Hell no!
Yeah, you do!
Keep up, man!
[JRAVOLTA] Let's go!
Good God!
No! Stop it! Stop it!
Stooooo...!!
Look Mother!
The Dancingians have
come back to Planet Grease!
Wake up! You're missing out!
You may be a Dancingian
but you don't impress me, Afro!
Your moves are like your
threads: outta style!
Outta style?
So you think you can do better?
Then why dontcha show us?
Turn on some music and
let's see ya shake your booty!
Uh oh.
It's kinda hard to cut a
rug without music, huh?
Hey guys!
Hurry up and put my record on!
[MEOW] Huh?
[QT] Oh, ya mean this one?
You sure that's a good idea?
The clerk told you
not to play it.
It's not like we can anyway;
we don't have a
freakin' record player.
Gimme that, dummy!
[ballet march music]
[QT] This is interesting.
Can you dance to this?
[ballet march music]
[very high-pitched]
Yaaaaaaaa!
[NARRATOR]
Fascinating, isn't it?
These life forms which
normally take months
to become full-grown have
sprouted up in no time at all.
How, you may ask?
Well, believe it or not,
it's thanks to the
mysterious power
of Dandy's
other-dimensional record.
Its melody has
caused time to accelerate,
at an alarming pace.
[QT] Is it just me or do
you guys feel kinda funny?
Why does my arm hurt?
Aw man, my lifespan.
[QT (OLD)] Way to
rock old age, Dandy.
That really smarts.
Hurry, play it backwards!
[high-pitched record
backspin noises]
Aw, yeah!
I think it's workin', baby!
Huh?
Hey, what're you doin'?
That's too far back, fleabag!
Meeeeooow!
Aaaaaah!!
She's awake!
Goodness, it's a miracle!
[PLANET CHIEF'S MOTHER]
They've returned!
It's just like
when I was a girl.
Strike that. It's even more
amazing this time around!
Meow!
I can't believe it,
the Dancingians are back!
What the--?
Hey!
Isn't it just
amazing, Mother?
He's an honest-to-goodness
Dancingian!
Those numbskulls
aren't anything close.
Huh?
Well, if that's the case.
Then who the heck are you?
What? Who me?
I am Ton Jravolta!
Oh, spacey soul!
[NARRATOR] As it turns out, Ton
Jravolta is not a Dancingian.
He's just an alien
who likes to party;
traveling the universe from
one dance contest to the next.
His ring is a transport device
for his top-of-the-line
sound and lighting systems.
This professional booty
shaker is always prepared!
If it's not him,
then who is it?
Look son, there they are!
The Dancingians are coming!
[PLANET CHIEF'S MOTHER]
Aren't they beautiful?
They're the gods who will lead
this land to its true form!
Are you kiddin' me?
[NARRATOR]
These are the Dancingians.
However, they've never known
that this is what they're
called and honestly,
there's no reason they should.
To a species like this,
things like names,
or the opinions of others,
are of no importance.
They live simply
for the sake of living.
When the time
is right, they die.
And in between--
[GEL] It's so beautiful.
You know, I don't
think I've ever
seen anything
quite so lovely.
It cleanses
the mind, doesn't it?
Something about this light
moves me, to my very soul.
I agree, sir. I don't
need a vacation anymore.
[PLANET CHIEF'S MOTHER]
Oh glorious day! Hallelujah!
Those Dancingians
ain't half bad!
They got you beat;
that's for sure.
Very funny!
We all know who
the number-one dancer
in this universe is
and it's me!
[JRAVOLTA] Aw, yeah!
[DANDY] Screw you, man!
I'm number one!
Just wait 'til you see
what these gyratin' hips
can do, baby!
[QT] Given what's
happened in the past,
I have a feeling this situation
is gonna escalate quickly.
[MEOW] So when that
old lady said the Dancingians
would lead this land
to its true form,
you don't suppose--
[upbeat disco music]
[JRAVOLTA] Spacey dance!
[DANDY] Dandy dance!
We better hurry
and get off this planet
before it's too late!
[QT] We'll never
make it in time!
Dancin'. We're dancin'!
You're not the greatest
'cause I am the greatest!
No, we're both great! Okay! Wow!
Fever!
[NARRATOR] I'll try to explain:
It seems the new
Dancingian life form's
yearning to be born reacted
to the pyonium energy
within Dandy--causing the
two to become fused together,
and generating a release
of unimaginable power.
Or something like that.
Seems we're facing
annihilation once again.
Dust in the solar wind, sir.
[NARRATOR] And so, as one
heavenly body meets its demise,
another of equal
brilliance is born anew.
Although it will take
hundreds of millions of years,
eventually this
world will also come
to be known as Planet Grease.
However, the planet
itself will never know
that this is what it's
called and honestly,
there's no reason it should.
[JRAVOLTA] What just happened?
[DANDY] No clue.
[JRAVOLTA]
What should we do now?
[DANDY] Whaddya think?
We get our groove on!
[JRAVOLTA] Oh! You are
one spacey soul, Dandy!
[DANDY] Yeah, baby!
[upbeat disco music]
[DANDY] Next time,
on Space Dandy!
It's a first in the history of
the Dandy-est guy in space--
a heartwarming love-story,
with feelings and everything!
Next time,
"Lovers Are Trendy, Baby."
It's gonna be a hit
with the young folks,
so make sure you catch it!