[NARRATOR]
Space Dandy.
He's a dandy guy... in space.
He combs the galaxy
like his pompadour,
on the hunt for aliens.
Planet after planet he searches,
discovering bizarre new
creatures both friendly and not.
These are the
spectacular adventures
of Space Dandy and his
brave space crew... in space.
[MEOW]
Terrible.
All these famous alien hunters.
[QT] Made to look like the
biggest fools who ever lived.
[MEOW] Seriously, though.
These Gentooans
can't really be
that scary, can they?
[QT] Hard to know when all
you can see is an antenna.
[MEOW] Yeah. I guess it's
all worth it, though, huh,
for an eight million
woolong reward.
[QT]
Dandy only bothered to listen
to half the story
before he took off.
I hope he's not outmatched.
Hey, QT.
Is it just me,
or's the room slanting?
No, it couldn't be.
I think it's just you.
[MEOW] Well, wouldn't
be the first time.
[MEOW and QT laugh]
All right, Gentooan!
You're mine now!
A little kid?
Hey, uh... You cool, kid?
Did the big bad
Gentooan get ya?
Huh?
[PENGUIN]
Wah?
[NARRATOR] Now might be
a good time to explain:
Gentooans possess
the unique ability
to capture another
being's consciousness
and transfer it into
the body of a toy puppet.
Like this space penguin here.
[PENGUIN growls]
Wahhh!!
Ah...!
[NARRATOR] Normally, a
Gentooan's victim is too
overcome with embarrassment
to put up a fight.
But Dandy has never been
one to sweat the small stuff.
[PENGUIN, singing]
Wak wak wak wak wak...
[DANDY, singing] The boobies
at Boobies go up and down,
up and down, up and down.
The boobies at--
Oh, hey. I'm back
in my own body.
Hey... Great...
That's the power
of boobies, baby.
Even just singin' about
'em makes miracles happen.
Idiot.
My power only lasts
for six hundred sixty-six
seconds, once a day.
That's fascinating.
So I guess that means you're all
tapped out for a little while?
See, kid, I'm an alien hunter
and I'm gonna take you on
a field trip to get registered.
Hey, don't look at me like
I'm the scum of the cosmos.
I'm not gonna hurt ya.
[DANDY]
Gone! Gone! Gone!
My precious Aloha Oe!
Hey, QT! What the hell?
[QT] Oh, hi, Dandy.
Funny story.
Seems we got towed
for a parking violation.
[DANDY]
So, get back here already!
[QT] Yeah, we can't
pay the fine,
so the ship's stuck in impound.
Stupid-ass 'bot.
I've been out
catching a Gentooan,
and you manage to lose the ship?
Okay. So, how about
you take the Gentooan
down to the Alien
Registration Center?
Then we can use the reward money
to get the ship out of impound.
[DANDY]
Stupid-ass cat!
That place is like
majorly far away.
It'll take me days to get there.
[QT] You don't have much
of a choice, do you?
So suck it up and
take public transportation.
Bye!
[DANDY]
Hey! Don't hang up on me!
Let's make a deal.
Huh?
[ADÉLIE] There's someone I
wanna see at this address.
If you swear we can
stop by on the way.
I'll go to the
registration center quietly.
And if I don't
agree to the deal?
Sicko!
This man isn't my dad!
He's trying to
make me go with him!
Somebody please help!
[DANDY]
Easy there, kid! Quiet down!
The bad man's
trying to kidnap me!
[PASSERBY] Call the police!
That girl's in trouble!
[DANDY]
Dirty brat.
Do we have a deal?
Damn it.
Like I have a choice.
You couldn't at least
pick somewhere on the way?
[DANDY] We're gonna
need two tickets.
One human adult
and one alien child.
I am not a child.
Oh, yeah?
Two adult tickets!
Do you even know what
adult women look like?
They're the ones with
the big, round boobies
and nice, shapely asses.
Like I said.
Two adults!
What's your name, anyway?
Got any family in these parts?
Okay. Not a very
talkative one, are you?
I'm gonna be straight with you.
I don't like kids.
I never have and I never will.
Saying any damn
thought in their heads
and thinking they can get
away with it just 'cause
they're all young
and cute or whatever.
Far as I'm concerned,
kids are all brats.
Great. We're on the same page.
'Cause I'm not exactly a
big fan of grownups, either.
Why's that?
[ADÉLIE] They think
they're smarter
just because they're older,
they blame the world
for all of their problems,
and they lie about everything.
Far as I'm concerned,
grownups are all jerks.
Okay, fair enough.
Now pipe down, will ya?
I'm gonna grab some shuteye.
There you go! Enjoy!
[DANDY] I'm gonna be
straight with you, kid.
[ADÉLIE]
We already did this.
[DANDY] You've gotta eat
sunny-side-up eggs with Tabasco.
That's just the way it is.
What the hell? You deaf?
I said Tabasco!
Sunny-side-up eggs need salt.
Also, I have a name.
It's Adélie.
Oh, yeah?
Well, take this!
Not enough?
How 'bout some more?
[ADÉLIE]
It needs salt!
Like I said.
Kids are brats.
Every last one.
♪
[QT] He still
hasn't come, has he?
Can't put anything past you.
[QT] I wonder what
he's up to this time.
It had better be important.
♪
[DANDY sneezes]
[DANDY yawns]
Mama.
I'm so cold.
[DANDY sneezes]
Like I told you, it's
gonna be a while longer.
I'm still on Planet Humboldt.
[QT] You're not at the
registration center yet?
What're you screwing around
on Planet Humboldt for, anyway?
What am I doing here?
Well, uh...
It's a long story, actually.
Like real long.
[CHILD]
Mama!
[CHILD laughs]
[PHOTOGRAPHER]
Okay, say "green cheese"!
[camera clicks]
[PHOTOGRAPHER] Great!
Let's get one more shot.
All right. Give me
just a moment, please.
Oh, hello, young lady.
Just five hundred woolongs for
a picture of you with your dad!
Oh, thanks, but actually--
[DANDY]
Yeah!
Smile big!
Hey, hold on a second.
You jerk! What the hell
do you think you're doing,
dumping sand on a guy like that?
Blech!
It's gonna take me forever to
get this stuff out of my hair!
Well? Are you
gonna apologize,
or will I have to make you?
I mean it! I'll teach
you to mess with me!
Hey! Knock it off!
Seriously, man!
This is it?
Yep. Room 104, apparently.
Nice place.
Whose is it?
My grandfather's. I think.
What do you mean, you think?
[ADÉLIE]
I don't really remember much.
I only met him once,
when I was super little.
[doorbell rings]
[HOSTESS]
Yeah...? Huh?
Um, yes, hello.
Sorry to bug you, but does a
man named Mr. Sclater live here?
Huh? What are you
talking about?
There's no Sclater here.
Are you selling something?
I don't wanna buy any
Space Scout Cookies, you know.
[footsteps running away]
Wait. That does
sound familiar.
I think it's the name of the
guy who lived here before me.
Huh?
So, your grandpa wasn't there.
Well, maybe he
moved somewhere else.
Got any other relatives?
My mama.
Hmm?
She never got married.
She raised me on her own,
without any help.
That's how it was my whole life,
just me and my mama.
Right up until Mama
got sick and died.
Aside from close family members,
we Gentooans always try to
live spread out from each other.
We don't like to be noticed,
'cause the bad people
want to use our powers.
At least, that's what
Mama used to say to me.
So now...
I don't know who else I can go
to for help besides my grandpa.
Are you going out?
Yup!
Where're you going?
[DANDY]
Boobies, obviously, baby.
What?
[DANDY] It doesn't matter
how far in the universe I go,
I never forget Boobies.
That's just the
kind of guy I am.
I don't want to be alone.
Not tonight.
You should know by now, kiddo,
there's nobody in the whole
cosmos that can stand
between me and boobies.
What's with the face?
Don't be a brat. Listen.
I don't take orders
from anybody.
If there's something
I wanna do, I do it.
If there's something I don't
wanna do, I don't do it.
That's the Dandy way to live!
And I'm Dandy!
Do you get it?
I'll catch ya later.
♪
[DANDY] We're going
to the station today.
10 o'clock in the morning,
platform thirteen.
[ANNOUNCER] Now arriving
at platform nine,
from Humboldt Station,
is the Super Express
bound for Emperor Station.
Passengers requiring
King Station,
please board
the following train,
with service to all stations.
[DANDY] Let's see. Platform
thirteen. Platform thirteen...
This is your last
chance to get a souvenir.
Huh?
Well, what would you like?
What are you talking about?
Like a going away present?
What, really?
No way.
What about the
registration center?
There's been a
slight change of plans.
[ADÉLIE]
Oh, yeah?
Why, 'cause you don't like kids?
You're sick of having
a stupid brat around?
Whoa. Easy, there.
I knew it, Dandy! You're just
like all the other grownups!
You do what you want,
when you want to,
and if the kid gets in
the way, you just ditch her.
Hey.
You jerk!
[DANDY]
Uh... Ah...
[electrical pulse,
guttural grunt]
[thud]
[DANDY]
Wak wak? Waak!
[DANDY squeals]
[HUNTER A] Do you remember
who we are, little Gentooan,
or would you like us
to refresh your memory?
[HUNTER A] We're the hunters
who came for you before.
You made us look like the
biggest fools who ever lived.
Too bad you just
used your power.
For the next day, you're
nothing but a helpless girl.
We've been waiting a
long time for our revenge!
[ADÉLIE screams]
Stop it! Let me go!
Hey, twerp!
Quit squirming so much!
[ADÉLIE]
Put me down!
You'll shut your mouth if
you know what's good for ya!
Wak wak wak wak
wak wak wak...
Dandy!
Wak wak wak wak...
Wak... Wak...Wak....
Wak... Wak... Wak...
Wak...! Wak! Wak!
Wak! Wak!
Wak! Wak! Wak!
Wak! Wak! Wak! Wak!
Waaaaa...
Hey, idiot.
Don't you know that
penguins are flightless birds?
Wooo...
[ADÉLIE gasps]
Oooo...!
[DANDY struggles]
[HUNTER A]
Not the brightest, is he?
Oh, no! Dandy!
[DANDY] Wak wak wak...
Wak wak wak...
[HUNTER A]
That is a penguin, right?
[HUNTER B]
That's impossible!
Penguins aren't supposed to fly!
Aw, crap! Get back!
[DANDY grunts]
Dandy!
[HUNTER A]
Argh! Dirty brat!
Are you okay?
No!
[HUNTER A]
Did your birdie go bye-bye?
I guess your time
is up, little girl.
Huh?
Hey, old man, stay outta this.
[HUNTER A groans]
[ADÉLIE]
You're a Gentooan, too?
Adélie, is that you?
It's okay now.
Grandpa's here.
[GRANDPA] The young man
with the large hair
got in touch with me yesterday.
I guess he must've
checked around
to see where I'd moved to.
One way or another, he was
able to track down my number.
He did that?
Frozen tangerines make a great
traveling snack, you know.
[ADÉLIE]
Okay.
Well, see ya.
You two have a
good life together.
We're not going to
the registration center?
Nah. Never mind that.
But what about all that money?
Eh...
I'll just find another alien.
Can't be too hard.
You be good, okay?
Ciao.
Dandy, hold on!
Yeah?
Do you think I... Could I crew
for you on the Aloha Oe?
Don't be stupid, kid.
We don't take whiny
little brats aboard my ship.
Well, maybe once I'm grown up?
Yeah. If you grow up
into a big-breasted,
curvy-assed woman,
then we can talk.
Idiot.
Adélie.
[ADÉLIE]
I'll do it.
I'm gonna grow up
quick, you'll see.
And then, I'll hunt you down.
[NARRATOR] Which is more
important to clothe:
the chest or the buttocks?
Next time,
a philosophical treatment
of this timeless topic.
"The War of the Undies
and Vests, Baby."
[QT] That's what
the episode is about?
[NARRATOR]
We'll see you then!