[crowd cheering]
Look alive, Misawa!
Give 'im the ol' elbow!
Yay!
[bell clanging]
[HONEY]
Misawa's just incredible!
Yahoo!
I wonder where
he is right now.
[HONEY screams]
[PINE-PINE] Don't be
a dummy, Scarlet.
It's not like the
perfect man's gonna
come waltzing in here and
plunk a ring down on your desk.
Alien hunters are
dogs and dorks.
[laugh track laughter]
[SCARLET] Tell me about it.
They're not too
easy on the eyes.
And there're
usually three of 'em.
Men, or eyes?
[laugh track laughter]
Even so, any guy you meet
here you should throw back.
Yeah, I know, Pine-Pine,
but where else am
I gonna meet a man, huh?
We're taking your lonely
asteroid to a space mixer!
You might meet someone
dandy and gentle.
Who knows?
[SCARLET] Dandy and gentle?
Where do I sign?
[NARRATOR] Where does
one find a dandy man
in the vast infinity of space?
[NARRATOR] Just left
of camera, it would seem.
[laugh track laughter]
[sucking noises]
This chicken wing,
it's so good,
I can't wrap my brain around it.
[QT] You know you're sucking
on your own tail, right?
That would explain why
it tasted all familiar.
[laugh track laughter]
[QT] Isn't it about
time we give up
on the Cloudian and
catch something easier?
[NARRATOR] Dandy and crew
are looking for an alien
that would land
them a huge bounty.
Only problem is,
it's been six months,
and they've found squat.
Morale has gone belly-up,
and bellies have gone empty.
It's been a drag.
All we need is
L-O-V-E, love, guys.
[QT] Huh?
I've come to a
realization, baby.
What I lack in life,
it ain't food,
or wulongs, I need love to grow!
[QT] Uh.
Here's a thought.
What if I'm love itself?
[QT] Total body fat:
Less than one percent.
Total water: Thirty
cubic centimeters.
He was less thrashed
when he was a zombie.
[laugh track laughter]
[QT] I think the prolonged lack
of food and water
is making him crazy.
[MEOW] He wasn't before?
Seize your destiny!
Love's not something you
grab with a tractor-beam!
It's something you
give to the world,
all naked and sexy vulnerable!
I'm a super-nova!
And I'm about to blow!
[QT] Maybe don't
explode just yet.
Planet C'est La Vie
is coming up ahead.
Oh, they're hosting a free
all-you-can-eat buffet today.
--What?
[NARRATOR] Elsewhere, in a
place not lacking for reason,
or food, or pants,
we find this man.
His name is Sir Gentle Nobra.
He's one of Dandy's
elusive Cloudians.
The cloud surrounding his ship
is actually a part of him.
It serves as a
storehouse for the data
he's gathered from
a lifetime of travel.
[sniffs]
All I want to do is
share a pot of rose tea
with the right companion.
Sitting in the
dark is no fun.
Oh, wow!
What do you sell here?
[laugh track laughter]
[GEL] No shop this,
my dear girl.
I am Dr. Gel, your hesitant
captor and eager host.
I bear you not
a shred of ill-will.
Rather, I've brought you here
to help me find a
certain ne'er-do-well.
"Ne'er-do-well?"
[BEA] We're looking for
the man in this photo.
You know him?
Oh! You want Dandy!
We've been led to
believe you're well versed
in this Dandy's comings
and goings, m'lady.
Hmm...?
[GEL] "Hmm," indeed.
So we're going to copy
your brain's contents
into this impressive device
under which you now sit.
[laugh track laughter]
[SCARLET] I dunno, Pine-Pine.
I'm not seeing any
quality men around here.
What's the theme of this
mixer supposed to be?
The theme is
"Eat like a queen!"
And don't let the schmucks
get their hooks into you!
[alien language]
Ugh! Not with a rented rocket!
[chuckles]
[QT] "Free buffet for
women of all species." Uh!
I'm a woman!
Me too.
[laugh track laughter]
Are you judging a book
by its cover like
all the rest of 'em?
[laugh track laughter]
Oh, believe me, honey,
you are preaching
to the big green choir!
Now, in you go!
[laugh track laughter]
I didn't exactly come
here for the food,
but free is free!
[MEOW] Is that Scarlet?
Man, she can
really pack it away.
So whaddya think, is she
here for the grub or the love?
[DANDY] Whatta freeloader.
Now's your chance to hit
her with your love-beam,
or whatever it was
you were saying.
Love-beam?
You trippin' hairballs?
Well, look who's
finally back to normal.
[laugh track laughter]
[ROBOT SUITOR]
0-0-1-1-1-1-0-0 0-0-1-1-0-0-0-1.
[QT] Oh no, I'm not here for
that. I'm just tagging along.
[ROBOT SUITOR]
0-0-1-1-0-1-0-0 0-1-0-1-0-1-0-1.
[QT] Oh, that's really sweet
of you, but no--you keep it.
Yeah, that's pretty scandalous.
Clucking in public!
I give up.
Welp, that's about
all I can eat, baby.
[QT] We're leaving already?
But, Dandy, there might be
an unregistered alien here.
Really, QT?
Finding true love's hard enough.
Last thing these folks need
is some hunter dragging
their alien soul-mate
out the door
before they even
have a chance to mingle.
Fear not, madam,
I've got you.
Oh, excuse me.
[moans]
[laugh track laughter]
We haven't had the pleasure
of meeting, have we, miss?
No. Falling into your arms,
I would remember.
[laugh track laughter]
How does a cup of rose tea
on my ship strike you?
I would love to.
Capitol, and call me
Gentle, please.
What a name.
Though Handsome or Suave
would've worked, too.
[laugh track laughter]
[finger snap]
[SCARLET] Wow.
Your cloud awaits you.
That hit the spot.
[QT] Huh?
[QT] Um. That woman floating
into the pink cloud,
isn't that Scarlet?
Yeah.
[QT] I wonder if that
means that's the Cloudian
we've been looking
for this whole time!
What?
Let 'em go.
There's no way we can
catch up to 'em now.
[QT] Yeah, we can.
Only thing I wanna
catch is a nap.
Ditto that.
[laugh track laughter]
[DANDY] No Honey today, huh?
[QT] I want to
find the Cloudian.
Not only for the
bounty, of course,
but because Scarlet is with him.
So what?
[QT] If a Cloudian
searched her out,
her life must be pretty crummy.
I feel bad for her, that's all.
Yeah, I get it.
I mean, Scarlet's no
spring chicken anymore,
and all that frowning
she's always doing
at us ain't exactly helping the
sell-by date any, ya feel me?
Well, aren't you
a smooth talker.
[laugh track laughter]
[DJ] Thanks for waiting, fellas!
Happy Hour starts now!
Shake it, ladies!
Now that it's just us adults,
what is a Cloudian anyway?
[QT] They take lonely
women up to their ships
and show them a good time.
Whatever that's
supposed to mean.
So you're saying
this alien's a master
of the ol' "love 'em
and leave 'em routine?
I know, can you believe
what a monster he is?
[laugh track laughter]
All right!
Let's go bag ourselves
a Cloudian, baby!
[QT] Dandy sure seems motivated.
All it took
was a little T&amp;A.
Huh? What happened?
[BEA] It's overloading, sir!
This defies explanation.
Oh, well that's your
problem right there.
You're gonna need an andro-
supergreat-giga drive, Doc.
Huh? Is it possible
this girl is a--?
Uh-huh! I'm a Cloudian!
Just half, though!
Tell me. Are you
one of those--?
[GENTLE] Go on.
No, on second thought,
I don't wanna know.
Just say it, Scarlet.
You're a Cloudian, aren't you?
Quite.
Ah.
And you would that
I were otherwise?
[SCARLET sighs] I wasn't
born yesterday.
Your kind has a clear M.O.
Trawl through women's personal
data for the lonely ones,
then drop in on your cloud
and give 'em a little thrill.
If that's your idea
of charity, save it.
I'm not desperate! Really!
Everyone has a dry-spell, right?
If I could, I would peel
my birthright clean away.
Women hold me to
be a dilettante.
No one thinks me
capable of true love,
given my proclivities.
I want to stoke the embers
of your lips into a smile.
Verily, that is what
I want for all women.
[GENTLE] My heart shivers.
All that I want is to
bring as much happiness
to a woman as she's
brought to the universe.
Look, I-- I'm sorry.
It's just that I get
paid to doubt people.
At the end of the day,
it can be so hard to turn off.
I wish-- I wish
I were a better person.
No, don't say that!
Yours is the purest
heart I've ever known.
[NARRATOR] You probably
picked up on this already,
but a Cloudian reflects
his feelings through color
and weather conditions
within his cloud--
[NARRATOR]
Oh, did I kill the mood?
You kids go right ahead.
[laugh track laughter]
[QT] According to the
Weather Radar LooksLikeRain,
there's a cloud moving
extremely quickly through space.
We can't be sure, but
that's probably the Cloudian.
There any reason
we didn't use
this thing in the first place?
[QT] Somebody wasn't putting
enough hustle into their job.
[heavy panting]
[QT] We should catch up
to it soon, though.
Ah. Don't mind if I do.
[DANDY] Psyche!
Totally goin' in!
[GENTLE] Welcome to my
humble ship, the Edinburgh.
Guests are a rare
treat indeed, sirrah.
I am the occupant,
Gentle Nobra.
[DANDY] The name's Dandy.
Pleased to meet ya.
Might I interest you
in a cup of tea?
The sitting room
is most agreeable.
[QT] He talks all fancy-like!
[MEOW] Man, this
place is friggin' huge.
Dandy? Why are you here?
Don't worry!
I see the look in your eyes,
and I'm here to save ya!
Save me from what?
Please, warm yourself.
You must be chilly.
And you. Recharge all you like.
And brandy for a Dandy.
Oh. Yeah.
Well? What're you doing here?
Huh?! Oh, right!
Damn near forgot!
I'm taking you in, top hat!
[laugh track laughter]
Capturing me is no easy task.
You're as like to catch
a cloud in a butterfly net.
[laugh track laughter]
This place haunted?
Or do you have a laugh track
with low standards?
Well! Your sense
of hearing is quite keen!
Atmo. You, too, Sphere.
Hold your tongue.
Say what?
They're
known as Ambiancians.
I hired them to help
out around the ship,
but, drat the luck, all
they do is chime in like that.
[AMBIANCIANS awww]
Are they registered, or--?
[QT] How would
we transport them?
What're they going on about?
You are not kidnapping anyone!
Why? 'Cause it's his job?
Ugh! Just kick him out!
[GENTLE] Please, calm down.
[DANDY] I'm tryin' to save you--
I'm sorry, you were saying?
[AMBIANCIANS laugh]
I said, I'm gonna knock
your monocled ass out, baby!
That rather smacks of a duel.
So be it. I have no
choice but to oblige you.
Hey! Hold on!
Don't fight over me!
Unless you must.
[beeping sound]
[CLOUD SHIP PA] An S.O.S.
signal has been detected.
What? On screen!
Dandy! Help! They caught me!
If you save me,
I'll comp your next meal!
Whoa--Honey!
Lady, is it really you?
Huh?
This is an outrage!
I will rescue her forthwith!
Are you nuts?
She said "Dandy!"
What of it?
[DANDY] Hey! Wait!
[SCARLET] Hold on!
What about me?
[PERRY] What?
[GEL] Though it
beggars belief to see her,
this little minx
thought up the trap
that is now luring Dandy to us.
Yay! He'll show up.
Dandy loves free
Boobies most of all!
What a spitfire, eh?
I'm supposed to work
the late shift up
at Boobies tonight.
Be a sweetie and zap me
back to my bike, would ya?
Yes, but of course.
The moment we apprehend Dandy,
you'll be free to go on
your merry way, my dear.
[PERRY] Gel.
Oh, Doctor Gel!
You're such a gentleman.
My gentle nature has
been a heavy burden.
I am a lover, not a fighter,
though I can hold my own.
[AMBIANCIANS laugh]
[PERRY] Agh. Gel!
Oh, Doc! I bet you're a
real beast in a fight!
[PERRY] Listen,
you besotted fool!
After stammering all
of the Gogol Empire's
secrets into her ear,
you're just going to let
her go, you nincompoop?
What would you have me do?
[PERRY] Kill her!
[GEL] B-But Admiral!
[beeping sound]
Dr. Gel, I think
something's coming!
[GEL] Really?
Admiral Perry, permission to
mobilize the Seventh Fleet, sir!
Surely it's Dandy!
[GENTLE] Stop pressing
things at random!
Save her with your own ship,
if you've a mind to!
[QT] The Aloha Oe
ran out of fuel. Sorry!
Where's the missile button?
[GENTLE] Incendiaries? You jest!
Really? Then what
are we gonna do?
Simple. We'll rely on
civilized discourse.
Hey! You're not done,
you lightweight!
Don't you care
what's up out there?
We're, like, in space.
Hmph! Whatever it is,
a man did it!
[AMBIANCIANS laugh]
The ship! It isn't Dandy's, sir!
It's way too big!
Come again?
[PERRY] Dammit, Gel! Behind you!
Emerald Flowsian, slam!
Misawa is awesome!
Later, 'gators!
Be still my heart.
[CLOUD SHIP PA]
We've been surrounded
by a hostile fleet, sir.
[DANDY] For reals?
Zounds! So this was a trap?
[QT] They weren't
exactly discreet about it.
Damn their eyes!
They dare to kidnap she
whom I hold most dear?
Villainy! Aye! They will suffer!
Burn to a crisp!
[DANDY] Chill out, baby!
Chill out!
[PERRY] All ships open fire!
[OPERATOR 19A] But, Admiral!
Dr. Gel is still onboard!
[PERRY] Screw him!
No. No, my ship!
And my beautiful cloud!
They're destroying them!
How's the "no weapons"
thing workin' out for ya?
[QT] I found the
emergency eject button!
What are you waiting for?
[QT] But what about
Scarlet and Meow?
[DANDY] Son-of-a--!
"I'm a rare alien
with a fancy-ass ship!"
Wouldn't know a trap
if it bit him in the ass!
Don't be mean.
At least Gentle
isn't afraid of love.
Love?
You're not such
a hard-ass, are ya?
[AMBIANCIANS laugh]
Wow! So cute!
Lady!
Big bro. Is it really you?
This guy is your big brother?
[NARRATOR] More or less.
They're actually half-siblings.
Turns out Honey's
real name is Lady Nobra.
She's only half Cloudian
herself, like she mentioned--
but we're already running
down the clock here,
so we'll get into
that some other time.
[AMBIANCIANS laugh]
I'm glad you're safe, Lady.
But stay back!
Huh?
With my ship's demise.
I lost the cloud for
which we are known.
This small piece
was all I could save.
I cannot face you
cloudless as I am, Lady.
The shame of it is too great.
But I don't care about that!
It's not like I have my cloud!
No, Lady.
My pride as a gentleman is
the one thing I yet possess.
Whenever you're done, big bro,
I'm gonna register
you right here and now.
Hey! Scan him, okay?
Why bother?
A Cloudian without his cloud
is just a regular old alien.
What the hell?
Sister, to know
that you're well,
how it gladdens my heart.
I swear I will gather
my cloud anew,
and reunite with you
as a proper Cloudian!
I'll blot out the sky
with its magnificence--just
you wait and see!
[HONEY] Oh, big brother!
[AMBIANCIANS awww]
I shall take my leave of you.
Farewell, Dandy.
See ya, Bro! And good luck!
I know you'll gather
your cloud again,
better than ever, you'll see!
Be good, okay? Bye-bye!
Do you wanna ride?
Do I ever!
[QT] I'll sit in front!
I got dibs on the caboose!
Oh, there's no more room.
[SCARLET] Stupid bounty-hunters!
[loud smacking]
[screams]
See ya later!
Tune in again, okay?
[CEO] The next episode of
Space Dandy is a documentary.
Following the phantom
one-hit-wonder band
'The Dropkix'
from their formation
to their last concert ever!
Next time, "Rock
'n' Roll Dandy, Baby."
Look forward to it! Ow!