[PROTESTORS]
Exterminate the devil pests!
(Female devil crying)
(Train alert bell)
(Male vigilante running)
(ANZAI grunts)
(Female devil panting)
[ANZAI]
At least carry some
sedatives with you.
[FEMALE DEVIL]
Ah!
[ANZAI]
Rest for awhile and
you'll be up again soon
[MAN]
Well, well, well.
I've been looking for you.
Remember me?
You broke into my office
at the university.
You attacked me, and shattered
every bone in my face.
So happy to see you.
What the hell do you
want with me?
What do you think?
Do you have any idea what
I have had to endure
since that day?
The university fired me
and my wife left me,
making me pay an arm and
a leg in child support.
On top of that, a student
put all my personal
information online.
My nightmare began the day
you invaded my office.
That was the day that
ended up ruining my life.
I'm a social outcast now,
and it's all thanks to you.
Like I care. I never wanted
to see that face of yours
ever again.
Must be because birds of
a feather flock together.
[ANZAI]
Huh?
[OCHIAI]
I've done some research
on you devils.
Apparently your thirst for
blood is aroused at the
same time as your sex drive?
You were in full‐on monster mode
in my office, weren't you.
You act tough, but you're
no better than me.
You were turned on, seeing
Tsukasa with her shirt off,
just waiting for me to do her!
(Ochiai struggling to stand)
(Anzai breathing sharply)
(Anzai in anguish)
[OCHIAI]
So... what just triggered
your transformation?
Was it the memory
of her bare skin?
Or please don't tell me...
it was from this right here?
What?
So... my blood is actually
turning you on, huh?
You sick fuck.
Seriously? You got
a little boner, there?
From the nosebleed of
a dude that you hate!
Ha! Man, I gotta feel
sorry for you devils!
[ANZAI]
Huh?
I feel like I've been told
something like that before.
[ZERO FOUR]
Even blood from an old man
like me turns you on, eh.
You know, that almost makes me
feel sorry for you devils.
[HANS]
His blood is actually nothing
but just simple ketchup.
Well I did get it off
your mind, no more signs
of transforming.
So I guess you really do only
go full‐on devil
when you're lusting
after Tsukasa.
(Anzai catches breath)
[KATAGIRI]
I once had to hit a man
and he immediately
started to bleed.
Then the urge started
swelling within me.
I lost it at that point.
I hated him, but I
sucked his blood anyway.
[ANZAI]
Last time I punched
this jerk of a professor...
I didn't feel the urge.
[YUUKO]
Do you have someone...
someone that you would
do anything to protect?
If you don't, you wouldn't
understand how I feel.
[ANZAI]
Blood is just a minor catalyst.
Once triggered my
transformation more
than anything else is...
Hey, what's the matter?
Why are you so calm now?
[ANZAI]
What happened to my eyes?
How is my mind so stable?
[OCHIAI]
Hm... I don't know what's
going on, but don't
let me down, fella.
Does this mean you're not
turned on by my blood?
[ANZAI]
I'm not.
[OCHIAI]
Tabuse, open the door to
the next car and wait there.
I'll be behind you.
[TABUSE]
Huh? You're gonna use them here?
[OCHIAI]
Yeah, well when else would I
ever get the chance to use 'em?
Use what? Huh?
Somethin'... more stimulating!
(Splash)
(Anzai catches breath)
Smells good, doesn't it?
The vigilante corps made up
these brand new blood packs.
And they have real blood inside.
[OCHIAI]
These are valuable prototypes,
and you get to be the first
to play with them.
[ANZAI]
For a second there...
I almost had it.
I almost found balance...
between my mind and
my transformation.
(Ochiai giggles)
[ANZAI]
Dammit, I feel hot.
I'm losing the balance.
So? Did you fuck her
after that?
Did you suck her sweet
little blood while you
had your way with her?
Or did she end up dying in
the saddle nailing a devil?
(Anzai struggling)
[OCHIAI]
If only I had known what
you were going to do.
I would've made sure to have
my fun with Tsukasa first...
Right?
(Anzai grunting)
[OCHIAI]
Whoa, check out those claws!
(Anzai screaming)
[TABUSE]
Come on! Let's get
out of here, man!
(Female passenger screams)
[MALE PASSENGER]
Don't open the door!
[MALE] What's going on?
[FEMALE]
Look, there's a devil
on the train!
[MALE]
That's messed up!
[SAWAZAKI]
He what?
[ANZAI]
Somebody...
[OFFICER]
Close all the doors.
The devil's in Car 5.
Open those only!
[ANZAI]
Somebody...
Somebody, please
Please...
[ANZAI]
Ah...
I'm glad I was able to make it.
[ANZAI]
Somebody please...
call me into the light.
[YANAGI]
So the video was posted by
that college professor,
the one who got a disciplinary
dismissal after he tried
to assault Tsukasa.
[SAKAKI]
Hmm...
[SUPERIOR]
Look, devil personnel were
supposed to be banned
from investigations.
And F Squad's devils were
specifically prohibited from
going in the field un‐escorted,
but now we have one
that's wreaked havoc on
public transportation,
and the video is
all over the internet.
Now there will be disciplinary
action coming down later,
but I promise you,
it will be more than
suspending one officer.
By the way, where is Ishimaru?
I thought you were removed
from leadership in F Squad?
[FEMALE]
That's awful.
Can this really be happening?
[PROTESTORS]
Exterminate the devil pests!
[ANZAI]
Ishimaru?
[ISHIMARU]
So let me get this right.
There's someone on the
vigilante corps
with a personal grudge
against you.
I must say I didn't expect that.
What's gonna happen to me?
Internally, the worst
punishment our bylaws allow.
For now, we've
taken the position
that you weren't
actively deployed,
that you just
happened to be there
and got mixed up
in the incident.
Because if we don't,
what you did was bad enough
to easily get you fired.
The higher ups are pretty
upset about that video
getting uploaded.
But even after you transformed,
you still didn't hurt
the guy, so that's good.
And personally I find
this video very interesting.
[ANZAI]
Hm...
See, here?
You've seen his blood and
started to transform,
but still stayed in control.
Hmm...
[ISHIMARU]
You should take that off.
It will only get dirty.
What is it you're going to do?
[ISHIMARU]
As your superior officer,
I thought I ought to know just
how much you're capable of.
(Shocked)
[ISHIMARU]
Devils are strong.
Even their most basic
physical abilities
far surpass those of humans.
Surely there had to be an
opening for you to get in
a good punch on me.
I'd appreciate it if you'd try.
No!
I don't know how much
control I'll end up having
after I'm fully transformed.
[ISHIMARU]
That's exactly what
I want you to figure out.
What in the hell
are you thinking? Don't!
It's just you and me in here.
Your girl's not around.
And if you do happen
to lose control,
I guarantee
I'll restrain you.
Just stop it!
Why are you doing this?
If anyone can do it... you can.
(Door opens)
[TSUKASA] Good morning.
Oh! Well, good morning, Tsukasa.
Um, where's Anzai?
He just left a few minutes ago
with Ishimaru.
[TSUKASA]
Oh...
[ISHIMARU]
Anzai.
You can handle this.
Fight me. For real.
Don't be stupid.
I have read every file
we have on you.
You're afraid of who
you are when you're
a fully transformed devil.
But on the other hand,
you have an intense desire
to try and control your
devil transformation.
(Slurp)
[ANZAI]
Uh...
[ISHIMARU]
Come on. Hit me.
Do it!
(Anzai grunts)
[ANZAI]
I got him.
(Inhales)
See, you're faster now.
(Scream)
(Anzai groans)
(Anzai coughing)
[ISHIMARU]
Don't let your guard down.
Have you not noticed yet,
you've been in full control
of yourself this whole time.
Wasn't that true yesterday, too?
[ANZAI]
I'm... still in control?
Do you get it now?
I honestly could not dodge
that hit that you threw
at me earlier.
So, there you go.
You've transformed,
but you're thinking rationally.
What you are experiencing
is what we call a benign
transformative reaction.
[ANZAI]
Huh?
[ISHIMARU]
Your senses are sharpened,
your reflexes have improved,
and you can almost access your
maximum muscle strength.
Plus it seems you can
consciously control
what you are doing.
You haven't been able
to realize it yet,
but now we know exactly
what you're capable of.
And what is that?
It may be that the sight
of human blood isn't the
only thing that can trigger
a full transformation response
within your system.
Could be your trigger is also...
That's it... who are you?
(Ishimaru grunts)
You are fast!
Can you see my every move?
[ANZAI]
Answer me! How d'you know...
about devils?
[ISHIMARU]
I can tell you
I'm not your enemy.
[ISHIMARU]
Time for the next stage.
Drinking blood.
(Anzai struggling)
You don't need to
worry about me.
I can take care of myself
in this circumstance.
Don't you want to know
more about your potential
and what that means for you?
My what? My potential?
(Car pulls up and doors open)
[SAWAZAKI]
Tsukasa!
[TSUKASA]
Where's Anzai?
[ISHIMARU]
Go on.
Wait.
That's not gonna
be necessary here.
Officer Anzai is in complete
control of himself now.
(Nervous gasp)
[ANZAI]
I didn't want Tsukasa to have
to see me in my devil form.
I don't think you have to worry.
Pretty sure that guy knows
what he's doing when it
comes to devils.
I've been a big fan of devils
for a really long time.
[ANZAI]
Huh?
When I was a kid,
I had a friend I played with
who was a devil.
It got me interested,
so I started doing research.
Do you understand what it
means... to make him transform?
I have a basic idea of
the extent and method of
the transformation.
And how to deal with it.
I'm asking if you understand
how someone would feel
if they were forced to
transform like that?
[ISHIMARU]
Hmm...
Oh... I'm so sorry.
(Thunder)
It's no good,
I can't get seem to get in.
[ISHIMARU]
And that means?
[KENICHI]
It means the hideout computer
isn't connected to the internet.
So I can't hack in.
[SAWAZAKI]
Is it always offline?
[KENICHI]
No. Maybe they disconnected it
to avoid hacking.
If someone's thinking
that far ahead, it would have
to be Zero Two or Zero Six.
[ISHIMARU]
Are the numbers given
in order of importance?
Zero Two is technically
our leader...
but after that,
I think it's random.
And Number One?
That would be the investor...
I don't know who it is.
Then do you know who
the other numbers are?
[KENICHI]
Uh... Well, um...
Why start holding back now?
[SAWAZAKI]
What are these
"probably no one" marks?
[KENICHI]
I've never seen them at the
hideout or heard their names,
so I think the numbers
must've been skipped.
But I don't actually
know for sure.
[ANZAI]
So one‐three isn't Thirteen?
...it's Jason?
[KENICHI]
Yeah. I don't know why.
I think there is a Jason,
but I don't know
their real name.
That's not good.
You sure no one has
those numbers?
If I could just see the roster,
it should tell us which numbers
haven't been assigned.
If we want the roster
then we probably have to
break in to the hideout.
I'd like to ask for some
backup, but we don't know
who might be a spy.
Worst case, our squad
will go it alone.
That sounds about right.
(Raining outside)
So now then, are you
over your hatred?
I'm putting it
on hold for now.
Are you mad at me?
For taking a shot at you and
putting a hole in your chest.
[ANZAI]
Mad? That I got shot?
Please, Anzai.
You should be
apologizing to her!
Hm?
[ANZAI]
Whenever you shot
through that window...
...a piece of glass
cut her face.
Oh, no, please...
it doesn't bother me.
I, uh, kind of like it.
[ISHIMARU]
What do you mean
"hole in his chest"?
It's just, uh...
I never heard
anything about this.
[ANZAI] What are you...?
Get off me!
[ISHIMARU] How could
an injury like‐
(Gasp)
How did you heal that fast,
I put a 7.62mm
right through you?!
Of course.
That was when...
he gave you‐
[KANO]
Okay kiddos, that'll be
enough of that.
[ALL]
Hm?
If you value your heads.
Hey there, Kano.
What's that mean?
Why would you say
something like that?
Almost everybody here knows.
Anzai's injury wasn't a secret.
Then it does not
leave this room.
There was once a detective
who discovered devils could
heal their wounds by
drinking human blood.
So did he get fired
or something?
Officially, he was
transferred from fieldwork,
but was really demoted,
and then quit as a result.
Even in the medical world,
the healing properties of
blood drinking are
treated as top‐secret.
[ANZAI]
He doesn't look like
he's hearing anything new.
Why is it so secret?
Is it because devils
might try
to attack someone every
time they get hurt?
Probably so.
[HANS]
Yeah but we wouldn't do
something like that.
[KANO]
The public doesn't
exactly trust devils.
Especially devils
who've transformed.
Then what do we do?
I mean we already know
all about the secret.
That's why this information
doesn't leave this room.
I've no intention of losing
my subordinates over
something unfair.
Sawazaki, I want a
full report sent to me
about Anzai's chest wound.
I understand.
[ISHIMARU]
All right. Everyone else,
go and take a break.
[ANZAI]
Can I talk to you?
[KANO]
Here, I have something
that I wanted to give you.
It's some new equipment.
The manual's somewhere
in there, so you feel free
to give it a go later on.
Thanks.
Well then?
When I transform,
it brings back memories.
From when I was a kid.
There's a man
standing beside me.
[KANO]
A man you know?
Kirio Kikuhara.
A police inspector.
[KANO]
Something wrong?
[ANZAI]
It's just, I feel like
I've said that name before.
And you don't have any
clear memories of meeting him?
No.
Well, it could be...
...you just forgot because
it was such a terrible memory.
It's a type of self‐defense.
If that's the deal,
you're better off not knowing.
You don't have to know
everything about yourself.
Some things are better
left unknown.
There a particular reason
you want to remember?
I feel like, if I remember,
then I can figure out
something important.
I'm in a basement...
with devils everywhere.
[ANZAI]
He told me I was
just like them.
I think I might find
the reason I hate devils...
somewhere in those
memories of Kikuhara.
Didn't know you hated devils.
Oh, uh...
I'm not blaming you, my boy.
If you feel hatred,
that's what you feel.
Can't move forward
by ignoring your feelings.
And didn't I tell you to
always know yourself. Hmm?
[ANZAI]
I always thought that
devils are dangerous.
And that devils and
humans should stay
separate from each other.
But I never remembered
what made me think that way.
That's why I couldn't
get mad at Zero Seven...
for hating devils so much.
[NEWS ANNOUNCER]
The Diet continued
deliberations today
on the laws regarding
devil regulation.
After the upsurge
in public interest,
the debate became
rather heated
as both parties
made arguments that‐
[ANZAI]
The reason I hate demons
has something to do
with Kikuhara...
And the memory was so terrible
that I blocked it out.
What possibly
could've happened to me?
But I was just a kid back then.
Maybe now that I'm grown up,
I can handle remembering it.
Oh. I didn't know you were up.
Just reading some case files.
I was having trouble sleeping.
[TSUKASA]
I was thirsty.
I'm going to make some tea.
Want some?
Sure. Thank you.
[TSUKASA]
Um...
[ANZAI]
What is it?
[TSUKASA]
About what happened
on the train...
You're good. You don't need to
worry about that guy anymore.
They arrested him right there
on the spot, he's gone now.
And don't feel responsible
for what happened.
Thank you.
Anyway, about today.
Huh?
Back there... I, uh...
I'm sorry for
scaring you like that.
Oh, no. I was a little
startled, but I'm fine.
Lee said that Mr. Ishimaru
knows a lot about devils.
So I know he did what
he did to help you...
But it's just that...
[ANZAI]
Yeah?
[TSUKASA]
To be honest,
I was a little jealous.
[ANZAI]
What?
The truth is...
I just want to let you
drink my blood, too.
And uh... I want to do
anything I can to help you.
Tsukasa...
[TSUKASA]
I've felt that way before.
It's just that
sometimes I think...
I should be the one
giving you blood.
Silly, I know.
Hee hee...
Sorry. Even I think
it's childish.
It's embarrassing.
[ANZAI]
You surprise me.
I'm always so amazed.
How can you always come out
and say exactly what's
on your mind?
(Embarrassed giggle)
I think it's that honesty
that's pulled me up
and got me this far.
You think so?
[ANZAI]
Ishimaru told me that my
transformation is known as a...
benign transformative reaction.
It's benign?
[ANZAI]
If I transform
only from seeing blood,
I can control my emotions
and stay rational.
If what he says is true...
then someday...
maybe I can stop living in fear
of the devil inside me.
[TSUKASA]
Someday...
Uh‐hm.
[TSUKASA]
Well, I hope that day
comes soon.
Me too.
But... for now, I'm‐
Don't you worry.
I swear...
I'll never offer you my blood.
[ANZAI]
Mhm...
If there's anything else
you want me to do,
please don't hesitate to ask.
I won't.
I've been thinking some.
On how to help...
wondering what I can do...
if there's a way to support you
and other devils.
[TSUKASA]
There has to be something.
Something different from
what you and Sawazaki
and the police are doing.
Something I can do.
Tsukasa.
[SAWAZAKI ON RADIO]
Sawazaki here.
[ANZAI]
Oh!
[SAWAZAKI]
A fire has broken out
in Taito Ward.
We believe it's the home of
a devils' rights activist.
It's owned by business man,
Souzou Shiraki.
It's not public knowledge,
but he's well known for being
an advocate for devils.
We can't say for sure
at this stage,
but it seems the anti‐devil
faction is making
an example of him.
Hm...?
[ANZAI]
Huh...
[KIKUHARA]
I'm on an investigation,
looking for a devil serial
killer named Tamaki Anzai.
[ANZAI]
Kikuhara!
[ISHIMARU]
Anzai, I can't let you go alone.
[ANZAI]
Then come with me!
Devil serial killer...
Tamaki Anzai?
Can I help you there?
As I recall, you were
suspended from duty, Officer.
You and I met a long
time ago, didn't we?
We already discussed this.
At the new staff ceremony.
No. More than 10 years ago.
Tell me about the devil
serial killer, Tamaki Anzai.
[KIKUHARA]
Does he have no memory of it?
That's not possible.
You should go home.
I can't have you
disrupting the scene.
Hey, Kikuhara.
Who are you exactly?
The question is who are you?
(Anzai shocked)
If you can't even remember
what happened that day,
you have no right
to ask me who I am.
I remember everything that
has ever happened to me,
good or bad.
No matter how painful.
I own it all, regardless.
Excuse me.
[ANZAI]
Did I... want to remember?
Reporting in.
You are late,
[KIKUHARA]
Jason.
[ANZAI & TSUKASA]
DEVILS' LINE,
Line 11,
"Ouroboros."