Uh...
Huh?
(Anzai grunting)
[HANS]
He transformed!
But he didn't drink
a drop of blood.
(Anzai hisses)
[HANS]
I have to get Tsukasa‐
He dodged me!
Hey!
Didn't you just tell me
if you transformed,
I was to keep her safe?
You need to hand
her over now!
Look... she might be hurt.
She needs to get some help!
Are you even listening to me?
Ah it's you... Anzai...
I... I thought I... I was...
That I was shot in the stomach.
The bullet... stuck in here.
[ANZAI]
(Angst)
I had this right where
it hit me!
It was... hers...
the sniper gave it
to me earlier today.
I have to‐
(Anzai crying)
[HANS]
He regained his sanity
while still transformed.
Amazing...
If he went through
the proper training,
he might learn to
really control himself.
[ZERO SIX]
Permission to fire?
[ZERO TWO]
Granted. Take care
of it, Zero Six.
(Gunshots)
[ANZAI]
Huh?
I know that face. Makimura?
(Gunshot)
(Anzai gasps)
[NANAKO]
If only they were all like that.
I wish all devil‐human
couples were like you two.
[TSUKASA]
Did she say something to us?
Our work here is done.
Let's pack it up.
[KENICHI]
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm not really hurt.
Not that.
That was your first time...
shooting a human.
Was it hard?
Not especially, no.
It's wasn't that much different
from taking out devils.
I see, well in that case...
It's because I'm shooting
from a distance.
So does Tsukasa always
administer your
sedatives for you?
I've only done it twice.
But it's a good idea for me
to be able to do it, right?
I called the cops.
I let them know there
were people with guns
on the roofs of two hotels.
I didn't say anything
about Ushio, though.
That good?
Uh... I can't figure out
what we should do.
I'll have to ask Sawazaki.
[HANS]
Aye‐aye.
[ANZAI]
Tsukasa.
Uh... yeah?
I need to talk to you for a sec.
[TSUKASA]
Um‐sure...
[HANS]
Hm?
Hey, can I play with you two!
[BOY]
Whoa! Where are you from?
[OTHER BOY]
Your hair looks funny!
[ANZAI]
There's this doctor,
a friend of Yanagi's.
He told me in order to control
the devil inside me,
I had to know myself.
That it's important
to figure out
exactly what causes
me to transform...
And just how far
my transformation will go.
But to be honest...
I've never thought
about it that way.
I didn't want to hurt you,
so I always thought
it would be best
if I just tried to
keep you at a distance.
But every time I transform,
it's because of you.
So if I want to learn more
about why I transform...
(Boys ooh's and ahh's)
I'm going to have to
drag you in with me.
But I fear it means
putting you in more danger.
And I would never
want to do that to you.
I now realized
I've never actually
talked to you about this.
[TSUKASA]
Back at the hotel,
it was just like when you
saved me at college.
You knew I was bleeding then,
but you still came to help me.
This time, I was shot, and well
I could have been bleeding.
I was so happy
that you came for me.
I really wanted to see you.
(Anzai groans)
[ANZAI]
If I had lost it and bitten you,
do you honestly think you would
still be able to say that?
I mean it probably wouldn't
just end right there.
Devil's drink blood
and can do much worse.
[TSUKASA]
I'm pretty sure Lee
would have stopped you
before that
would have happened.
Isn't that why you brought
him along with you today?
Kind of like insurance,
just in case.
Look don't worry.
I don't think one
or two little bites
is necessarily
going to kill me.
Uh...
Well a bite is painful.
Was she always this reliable?
Physical pain doesn't
really bother me.
I find it much harder not
being able to be around you.
[ANZAI]
Oh... of course.
It was never about
her reliability...
it's because she's sincere.
But, I guess I'm just being
kind of selfish with you.
[TSUKASA]
I'm sorry. I know this
can't be easy.
[ANZAI]
And she never seems to lie.
You don't... think my face
is somewhat, disgusting?
What? Why?
D‐did somebody say it was?
Don't let those people
bother you!
They're just being cruel!
It was me.
Huh?
The one who said I was
so disgusting was... me.
Everyone thinks so.
It's just you that's weird.
It's dangerous for us
to be together.
But I don't want to
leave you either.
You might run off
and hurt yourself.
That doctor told me.
There are ways out there
that will enable you to
control your bloodlust.
But to do that...
You're going to need
her help as well.
[ANZAI]
Hm...
I'm still a little concerned
about what that could
possibly mean for us.
How does one...
control the devil...?
[TSUKASA]
Anzai... let's be together.
I would like that.
[BOYS]
‐ Bye!
‐ See ya!
(Hans chuckling)
(Boys laughing)
Um... so I was... thinking...
[ANZAI]
Hm?
Oh, nevermind!
Wha...? Come on, now you're
just making me curious.
I know... but...
[ANZAI]
Just spit it out!
Does... does this
mean that we're...
actually like
a real couple now?
[ANZAI]
Whoa. That's true.
(Anzai laughing)
Uh! What's so funny?
"So, does this mean
we're a couple now?"
Ah!
Hm...
[ANZAI]
I guess we really
haven't talked about
any of the
important stuff, have we?
You wanna be?
Yes. I want to.
Good... then I'm happy.
So am I.
Tsukasa... do you mind
if I just kiss you...
Uh!
[TSUKASA]
Mm!
The sedative hasn't
worn off yet...
so I don't think
I'll transform.
Yeah.
Anzai's a bigger pervert
than he lets on.
[TSUKASA]
Oh!
You might wanna watch
yourself there, Tsukasa.
[KATAGIRI]
Huh?
Oh... I see.
I'm sorry.
[KIKUHARA]
So you're saying the manger
of Cross Bar, Kiwako Oe
and her employee Wataru Akase,
are both dead?
And Ryunosuke Katagiri
is in hiding?
Though he's virtually
immobilized for now.
Two people died because of him.
That should be warning enough.
[USHIO ON RADIO]
C Squad, Ushio here...
secure line.
Zero Seven and Nine appear to
have escaped the Mino Hotel.
The workers who went up
to inspect the water tank
had their uniforms stolen.
They were left
tied up on the roof.
And what about the hostage?
[USHIO]
Um... a devil showed up
and took her away.
Zero Six says it was
Anzai from F Squad.
[KIKUHARA]
It's him...
[USHIO] What now?
[KIKUHARA]
We got a tip earlier from what
sounded like a young man.
He said there were snipers
on the roof of both the
Mino Hotel and Grand Hotel.
The blood splatter on the
roof will eventually tell them
that Makimura was involved.
As for now... there was
nothing mentioned in the tip
about you being a spy.
I wonder why...
[KIKUHARA]
I couldn't say. But Anzai's
just a low‐ranking officer.
It may be that he couldn't
make the call on his own.
We'll keep an eye on F Squad
for the time being.
Sounds good.
[KIKUHARA]
Can you find out
who the hostage was?
I'll find her.
It's just a hunch but...
I think Anzai and
the hostage are lovers.
[KIKUHARA THINKING]
Well... interesting.
So he's old enough to
fall in love with a human,
like his father.
Aside from the hair color,
they look almost identical.
Although, if he gets
to be any more like him...
It would be tragic.
The half‐devil son of
a violent mass murderer...
My interest is piqued again...
Yuuki Anzai.
After I move to
the place over the bar,
we can see each other
every day.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
[ANZAI]
This place is a mess.
They're supposed to
come fix it next month.
[ANZAI]
Next month?
Make sure to bring
your valuables.
This place is just asking
to be robbed. Huh?
[ANZAI]
You can take that, too.
[TSUKASA]
Huh?
(Taps foot)
We won't be seeing this
place again for a while.
[TSUKASA]
When it calms down,
I hope we can relax
under the kotatsu again.
[ANZAI]
Yeah.
[SAWAZAKI]
That's fishy.
He's not with the police.
It's an amateur stakeout.
Could just be a nosy reporter...
trying to get a look at Tsukasa.
A lot of people saw her
during the Ikebukuro incident.
Some people have even leaked
her name and school, too.
That's just great.
[YANAGI]
Changing the subject.
There are rumors going
around about a new group..
they're trying to
wipe out the devils.
What, are you serious?
[YANAGI]
They're called the CCC.
Known as the
Chosen Civil Community...
[KANO]
So these lunkheads
think they're chosen, eh?
Sounds sketchy.
After the Ikebukuro Incident,
it's to be expected,
groups like these are bound
to pop up during tragedy.
Don't you think
it's a little too soon
for a group to be
fully formed yet?
Abso‐tutely.
[TSUKASA]
So, um...
I see the happy couple's here!
[KANO]
Who's ready for some
bloodlust training?
[ANZAI & TSUKASA]
Hmm...
[KANO]
The Anzai Couple will be
in Guestroom A.
Yanagi and I will be
standing by in Room B next door.
I brought a few restraining
devices with me.
They were all made
with devils in mind.
So what are we
supposed to do, exactly?
Enjoy some hanky panky,
of course.
(Anzai gulp)
[KANO]
And we'll actually
have you transform.
Huh?
[ANZAI]
Wait! I thought this training
was to help me control it!
To control it, we need the
timing of your transformation.
And the point of training
is to control the
transformation afterwards.
Control doesn't mean "stop,"
it means gaining
mastery over it.
If you want to stop
the bloodlust,
then all I can tell you
is to stop dating women.
Just chill it, daddy‐o,
this is why we have protection.
You kids have fun.
And don't worry,
we'll be checking it all out
from right next door.
(Anzai & Tsukasa gulp)
[KANO]
Yanagi, can you hear me?
[ANZAI & TSUKASA]
Whaaaat!
I can hear you loud and clear.
Tell me, why?
I thought a doctor only watched
if we planned on doing it!
Simmer down, it's only to
make communication easier
and we're going to have it off
most of the time anyway.
Besides, depending on how
it goes, you might get lucky.
Don't be stupid.
Anyway, Yanagi and I will
be monitoring your temperature
from Room B, if you're worried.
If you transform and
your temperature rises
above the control value,
we will force the audio
channel open and address you
from the other room,
asking if you or Tsukasa
have been hurt at all.
And you must both
answer this question.
If we feel it necessary,
we will also turn on
the video feed.
So, they're really going to keep
this whole thing offline, right?
If he's not, then that doctor
has some serious problems
he needs to take care of.
[TSUKASA]
Oh! Maybe this is it.
The microphone and the camera
are both X‐ed out.
[ANZAI]
Oh... it should be okay then.
(Anzai startled)
You okay, Anzai?
(Angst)
Don't push yourself too hard.
Do you wanna take a break?
[ANZAI]
No... I'm okay.
[TSUKASA]
Why don't you put these on?
[ANZAI]
Uh... okay.
[TSUKASA]
Nail protectors...
They protect nails
when they've grown
and measure added length
during transformation.
[ANZAI]
Are these handcuffs?
They're heavy.
Maybe I should take them off,
they feel kind of weird.
No, I like it.
I feel like it's safer this way.
Really?
I could hide them.
Like this.
Oh no, that's even
worse somehow!
Stop it!
Oh! Sorry, I just hit you
where you got shot, didn't I?
It's fine, actually.
It's already healed up.
See?
(Gasp)
Hm? What's wrong?
Uh... Nothing... just uh...
Does it hurt or anything?
Not anymore.
But the skin around it
feels kind of tight.
Wow...
Oh! Sorry! I didn't even think.
I just reached...
It's okay, you can touch it.
(Inhales)
You smell so good.
Ooah!
Oh! Sorry!
I uh... I made sort of
a weird noise.
Wanna... touch...?
His pulse just went up a notch.
His temp is up
one degree as well.
Uh sorry. Did you not like that?
No, I don't mind. I think
I'd like you to keep going.
[KANO]
It's moving.
[YANAGI]
What's the control value?
[KANO]
34 degrees centigrade,
the average
transformation temperature.
Four degrees to go.
(Anzai heavy breathing)
[TSUKASA]
You can take my bra off...
if you want.
(Tsukasa gasps)
[KANO]
Three degrees.
Hey... just relax.
[ANZAI]
Touch me... lower...
(Tsukasa catches breath)
[KANO]
Two...
One...
(Anzai heavy breathing)
(Tsukasa shaky breath)
[KANO ON SPEAKER]
Your temperature is now
above the control value.
I'm going to ask
you two a question.
Are either of you hurt?
(Anzai shaky breathing)
Uh... no.
[TSUKASA THINKING]
Maybe... he didn't hear him?
If he doesn't answer soon...
The video...
[KANO]
Anzai, are you hurt?
I'm good.
[KANO]
I'm turning the video feed on,
just in case.
Understood.
Sorry...
For not uh...
stopping.
Huh?
[TSUKASA]
So he did...
he heard the question.
[KANO]
Once you're settled down, I'll
ask you a few more questions,
go take a breather.
Sounds good.
I'm gonna go get some air.
Sure.
[TSUKASA]
That little yelp when I...
when I touched him...
It was so cute.
I want to hear it again.
[ANZAI]
When I pushed her down...
and was I pressing myself
between her thighs...
I definitely heard it.
A small sound.
She was wet.
She was really turned on.
(Anzai heavy breathing)
I want to hold her.
I want to touch her...
be inside her.
I want to move.
(Grunting)
I want to lick her.
(Moaning)
I want to feel her.
(Groaning)
I want to drink...
I want... to drink?
(Gasping)
To drink...?
[KIKUHARA]
It may be a good idea to
assign a new leader to
Division 5's F Squad.
He's known to let his
underlings disobey orders
when told to stand by.
[DETECTIVE]
F Squad?
You mean Sawazaki?
So did something happen?
We had trouble with him
when he worked with
a certain devil inspector.
Heh...
[MIDORI]
The skies are clear.
The weather report was wrong.
Chief Anzai, I haven't
been to Tokyo since
my high school trip...!
Calm down, we are not here
to have fun.
And call me by my maiden
name while we're here.
Until we get back to
Obihiro, it's "Chief Sako."
[CROWD LEADER]
Exterminate the devil pests!
[PROTESTORS]
[KANO]
This is Redeyes' Rights
Protection Committee.
R2PC for short.
It's a civil rights committee
that works to preserve
human rights for devils,
and I just so happen to be
on the committee, as well.
It's the main reason I'm
in Tokyo to begin with,
to attend this conference.
So why did you bring us?
It makes sense to bring me...
but Tsukasa too?
Figured you were spent from
the training, and thought
you could use a reward.
My signature is able to get
two of my guest's free dinner
at the hotel restaurant.
[ANZAI & TSUKASA]
Huh?
Hmh?
Oh!
[KANO]
How is ONLO doing these days?
It's just fine, it seems
peaceful. They're doing well.
I hear more of your high
school kids are looking
to become police officers.
And how are things at
the lab, might I ask?
I thought you promised
not to pry into my business.
I suppose I did.
Anyway, you might run into
a handsome stranger later today.
A certain fellow who
drove me over here.
[MIDORI]
What are you talking about?
[TSUKASA]
The view here is amazing!
[ANZAI]
We are on the 46th floor.
The restaurant's on
the floor right below us.
Looks like it opens at six
o'clock, so you wanna go now?
Uh... can I wash up first?
Go ahead.
[ANZAI]
I can't believe
we're a couple now.
We made it official, but
what does it really mean?
If we keep up with
all this training...
Will it come more naturally?
Hmh?
Can I help you?
Sorry... um.
It's just that you
look a lot like
someone I know.
Please excuse me.
[ANZAI]
That's alright.
[MIDORI]
Are you here for
the conference?
Oh... No, I'm not
a member of the committee.
I'm just here as a chauffeur
for a friend tonight.
(Shock)
[TSUKASA]
Thanks for waiting.
Oh! Excuse me.
It's a pleasure meeting you,
please excuse us.
You make sure to be
good to her, okay?
[ANZAI & TSUKASA]
Wha...?
Uh... I sure will.
You know her?
I don't... Never seen
her before, we just met.
[TSUKASA]
It may sound strange...
but she kind of reminds me
of you, a little.
[ANZAI]
Huh...
(Sobbing)
I might run into a...
a stranger? Right...
You old bastard.
Yuuki has grown into
a handsome young man.
I wish you could
have seen him...
Tamaki.
[MIDORI]
Allow me to be frank.
At this point in time.
We should hold off on
passing the sex law...
allowing devil/human
intercourse.
ONLO is working to develop
restraining devices
to use during intercourse...
But there are issues
that need to be resolved
such as the safety of these
devices and their availability.
Passing the new law without
having addressed any
of these issues...
would be like setting a trap.
Now that the Ikebukuro
Incident has made devils'
public knowledge...
I can't help but think
the government might
use this new law
as a means to try and capture
the devils and eliminate
them from our society.
[KANO]
Mm‐hm...
It was so sudden, I mean I just
couldn't come out and say,
"Well hello there,
I'm your mother."
But you wouldn't believe
how much he's grown.
He even had a human girlfriend.
[MIDORI]
Yeah... I'm a little worried
by that, too.
But, I also had a feeling
that they would be okay...
And when I saw
both of their faces...
I wanted to tell you so badly,
I came back as fast as I could.
But, there weren't any
direct flights.
[TAMAKI GRUFFLY]
I want to hug you.
To hug me? Or Yuuki?
[TAMAKI]
Both of you.
[MIDORI]
Yeah...
I hope the day comes
that you can...
Tamaki.
[ANZAI & TSUKASA]
DEVILS' LINE,
Line 9,
"Command."