[VAMPIRE]
(heavy breathing)
[MEN]
(running)
[VAMPIRE]
(heavy breathing)
(heavy breathing & crying)
[MEN RUNNING]
(terror) (running)
[VAMPIRE]
(grrr)
(charges)
[MAN D]
(swings knife)
(screams)
[MAN C]
[VAMPIRE]
(hngh!)
[MAN C]
(strangled)
(agonized gasp)
[MAN C]
(crashes into friend)
[MAN B]
(struggles to get up)
(struggling)
[MAN B]
(gasp of fear)
(screams)
[VAMPIRE]
(mental anguish)
(screaming in agony)
[VAMPIRE]
(dissolves into whimper)
[MAN B
(surprise)
[VAMPIRE]
(weeping)
[MAN B (with knife)]
(uhh...)
(screams)
[MAN B (with knife)]
(screaming in pain)
[Man B]
(grunts)
[MAN A]
(terror)
(scream)
[VAMPIRE]
(strangled utterance)
(horror)
[VAMPIRE]
(sobbing)
(screams)
ANNOUNCER
That makes three victims now.
Just how long will this string
of "vampiric killings" go on?
[TSUKASA]
I never realized.
As I went on living my normal
life,
[TSUKASA]
I never stopped to notice...
[AKIMURA]
What's wrong?
[TSUKASA] Oh...nothing.
[MIWAKO(UNDER)](hm?)
[TSUKASA]
He always was there in the
crowd.
[TSUKASA]
watching...and waiting
FEMALE STUDENT A
What? I don't believe it!
You need to break up with him
fast!
FEMALE STUDENT C
Right, Tsukasa? What do you
think?
[TSUKASA]
Huh?
FEMALE STUDENT B
Forget about that.
Do you have a
boyfriend yet, Tsukasa?
[TSUKASA]
Me? I...
...don't think I need one.
FEMALE STUDENT A (SITTING)
Come on, you can't be like that
forever.
FEMALE STUDENT B
I could introduce you to
someone.
FEMALE STUDENT B
What about Professor Ochiai?
You're his favorite student,
Tsukasa.
[TSUKASA]
I'm not his favorite.
And I'm pretty sure he's
married.
[MIWAKO]
Hey, cut her some slack. Tsukasa
is "pure," okay?
[MIWAKO]
She's not like you lot.
GIRL B
What makes her so different?
[MIWAKO]
Tsukasa is actually responsible.
GIRL B
You make it sound like we're a
bunch of shallow airheads!
[TSUKASA] (wry laugh)
[MIWAKO] And believe it or not,
Tsukasa has...
[AKIMURA] Hey Tsukasa.
[MIWAKO] (oops!)
[AKIMURA]
Can I sit next to you?
And would you mind showing me
your notes?
[TSUKASA]
(slight utterance)
Sure, no problem.
[MIWAKO]
What? Borrowing Tsukasa's notes
again?
[AKIMURA]
Hers are the most helpful‐she
knows how to organize them.
[FEMALE STUDENT A] That's for
sure. [FEMALE STUDENT B] Can I
see too?
FEMALE STUDENT C
Hey, Tsukasa. I'm having a hard
time getting this one.
[TSUKASA]
(laughs)
Um, well, you have to...
GIRL A
There's Professor Ochiai!
OCHIAI
Alright, take your seats.
And quit stealing Tsukasa's
notes.
[TSUKASA]
(sheepish)
So where were you heading next,
Miwako?
[MIWAKO]
Well, there are a few companies
I'd like to apply for.
[TSUKASA]
Oh yeah...we have to find jobs.
[MIWAKO]
No, you're such a great
student‐you could go for a PhD!
You know?
[TSUKASA]
I'm not so sure. I don't think I
want more school.
[MIWAKO]
Huh?
[TSUKASA]
I do like doing research and
learning new things,
[TSUKASA]
And I like college, too, but...
[AKIMURA]
It's okay. You don't have to
rush.
[MIWAKO]
Yes, you do!
You don't have to get a
boyfriend,
But if you don't get serious
about your future,
you could be in big trouble.
[TSUKASA]
(noncommittal laugh)
It's true.
[TSUKASA]
As the days go on,
I usually just go with the flow.
[TSUKASA]
I can't see the future,
so my only option is to do my
best with what's in front of me.
[TSUKASA]
How do you figure out what it is
you really want to do in life?
[TSUKASA]
There it is. It's that feeling
again.
Like someone is watching me.
[RADIO]
The target is on Hakusan Dori.
He left Kasuga Station and is
headed for Tokyo University!
[RADIO]
The victim has what appear to be
bite marks on her neck,
[RADIO]
and all the blood has been
drained from her body.
[MAN
(lands from jump)
POLICE OFFICER A
Freeze! Don't move!
OFFICER B
You won't get away from us!
Stop right now!
[MAN
(growls)
OFFICER A
(shock)
[MAN
(lunges)
OFFICER B
Hey!
[RADIO] A
Attention all units
in the vicinity.
[RADIO] A
The suspect in question has been
identified as a Level 3 special
case.
[RADIO] A
We're giving this to Public
Security Division 5.
[RADIO] A
I repeat. This is a special case
for Public Security Division 5.
DETECTIVE A
I want a name for this suspect.
DETECTIVE B
What's his escape route?
WOMAN A
Hey, have you heard about the
Vampire Murders?
[WOMAN B]
Yeah, of course. But they're
just an urban legend.
[WOMAN B] There's no such thing
as vampires.
[AKIMURA UNDER] (Disturbed)
[AKIMURA]
Is something wrong?
[TSUKASA]
No, I'm fine.
[AKIMURA]
You sure?
Miwako, I can hear your show
through your headphones.
[MIWAKO]
Oh, you can? Sorry.
[TSUKASA]
What are you watching?
[MIWAKO]
A special on the Vampire
Murders.
[AKIMURA]
You and your occult obsession.
[MIWAKO]
(giggle)
Whatever!
Look! They found fang marks
on the victims' necks and‐
[AKIMURA]
That's the kind of stuff you
only read about in the tabloids.
You never hear about it on the
real news.
[TSUKASA]
Must have imagined it.
[RADIO] A
F Squad has gone on ahead and
blocked the target's escape
route.
[SAWAZAKI]
Sawazaki, F Squad, I copy!
I have one striker, and one
doctor.
On our way to apprehend
the target.
[RADIO] A
Initiating information control.
Issuing gag order to all police
officers.
[RADIO] B
Requesting backup from the MPD
Aviation Unit's EC135.
[RADIO] A
Division 5 detectives and riot
police now in position on
target's escape route.
[MAN
(running)
DETECTIVE C
Freeze!
[MAN
(tackles)
(jumps away)
[SAWAZAKI]
(jumps out of car)
(surprise)
[SAWAZAKI]
This is Sawazaki.
He's headed your way.
[SAWAZAKI]
He's all yours, Jill.
[MAN
(lands and starts running)
(grabs fence, jumps over)
[MAN
(running)
(growls)
[JILL
Did you think we'd let you get
away?
[JILL
This game of tag ends here.
[MAN
(lunges)
(one‐two punch)
[JILL
(punch)
[MAN
(punches)
[JILL
((hits him with forearm))
[MAN
(grr)
[JILL
(smirks)
[MAN
(runs)
(wah‐agh)
[MAN
(rah)
[JILL
(takes off running)
[SAWAZAKI]
Think he's a first offender?
[YANAGI]
Hard to say.
Once they get a taste of blood,
they never forget it.
They lose themselves to the
mental high and the sexual rush.
Human blood is just like a
narcotic to them.
[SAWAZAKI]
And they get ten times higher
than any human on drugs.
[SAWAZAKI]
It's unbelievable an entire
race, born with an addiction to
human blood.
[YANAGI]
Vampires.
[MAN (UNDER)
(rah!)
[JILL]
(uhh!)
[MAN (UNDER)
(screams)
[JILL
I know you're suffering.
Let me put you out of your
misery.
[JILL
(yah)
[MAN
(agony)
[RADIO] B
Is he the one behind the serial
vampire murders?
[RADIO] A
No. Negative, not this guy...
[MIWAKO]
Hey, Tsukasa, what do you think?
What's really behind the Vampire
Murders?
[AKIMURA]
Come on, she doesn't need to see
that stuff!
[MIWAKO]
Aww, look at you, Akimura.
[AKIMURA]
(Aghh)
Stop looking at me like that.
ANNOUNCER (UNDER)
The next station is Korakuen.
The doors on the right side will
open.
[MIWAKO] Tsukasa's place is a
far walk. Make sure she gets
home okay. [AKIMURA] I will,
don't worry
COUPLE WOMAN
It was a great show!
COUPLE MAN
Yeah, it was.
What do you wanna do now?
[TSUKASA]
(ah!)
(slight utterance)
[AKIMURA]
You really don't have to worry
about it, Tsukasa.
[TSUKASA]
Huh?
[AKIMURA]
What I said to you the other
day.
[AKIMURA]
It's okay.
I knew you didn't think
of me that way.
[AKIMURA]
I'm not trying to make you feel
bad.
[TSUKASA]
I know that, okay!
[AKIMURA]
Whoa. If looks could kill.
[TSUKASA]
What!? I don't look like
anything.
[AKIMURA]
But anyway,
It does help to know that you
don't have a boyfriend, Tsukasa.
[TSUKASA]
(wry smile)
[AKIMURA]
I just feel like, if you did
have one...
I might not be able to recover.
[TSUKASA]
What are you talking about?
[AKIMURA]
I'm serious.
[TSUKASA]
What?
Huh
[AKIMURA]
For now...
I'm okay as friends.
[AKIMURA]
But someday,
If you ever start to...you
know...
[TSUKASA]
(slight utterance)
[AKIMURA]
Never mind.
[TSUKASA]
(deep breath)
(shock)
[TSUKASA]
(gahh)
Akimura?
[AKIMURA]
Let's take a different way.
I don't feel safe here.
[TSUKASA]
Okay.
[TSUKASA] & [AKIMURA]
(running)
[TSUKASA]
(panting)
[AKIMURA]
We should be far enough away by
now.
[TSUKASA]
It's definitely him.
That's the
guy I saw on the train.
[TSUKASA]
Who is he?
He's following me
[AKIMURA]
(surprise)
[TSUKASA]
(breath)
[AKIMURA]
(very slight utterance)
(determination)
[TSUKASA]
(noticing something)
[AKIMURA]
(grr)
[TSUKASA]
(breathing)
(surprise)
[TSUKASA]
(huh?)
[AKIMURA]
(slight utterance)
[TSUKASA]
[AKIMURA]
(sharp breathing)
[TSUKASA]
(nervous)
[AKIMURA]
(breathing)
[TSUKASA]
(pushes him)
[AKIMURA]
(surprise)
[TSUKASA]
(slight utterance)
(guilt)
[AKIMURA]
(sigh)
[TSUKASA]
(slight utterance)
[AKIMURA]
Sorry about that.
Let's go.
[TSUKASA]
(hesitant)
[AKIMURA]
(awkward laugh)
[TSUKASA]
(gasp)(hm?)
[ANZAI]
Hey there, vampire.
[TSUKASA]
(surprise)
(ah!)
[AKIMURA]
(ow!)
[ANZAI]
What‐a man's blood doesn't do it
for you?
[AKIMURA]
okay...who are you?
What...do you...want
[AKIMURA]
(gulps)
I'm wasn't goint to...
...I would never drink her
blood.
Leave us alone.
[TSUKASA]
Aki...mura?
[AKIMURA]
Look you're scaring my friend.
I don't know who you are,
but there's nothing to worry
about.
I've never directed my bloodlust
at her
and I never will.
[ANZAI]
Of course not.
You found a
different outlet.
You turned your bloodlust on the
three other women
three women you
murdered.
[TSUKASA]
(shock)
[AKIMURA]
Listen!
That wasn't me.
[ANZAI]
I'm told your semen was found at
each of those scenes.
[AKIMURA]
It wasn't mine!
Don't talk about that in front
of Tsukasa!
[ANZAI]
Your DNA was a match.
I wouldn't be following you
without the evidence.
[ANZAI]
Go!
[AKIMURA]
Tsukasa!
You keep your hands off of her!
[ANZAI]
I understand you want to be a
hero in front of your
girlfriend.
even if you wern't a
vampire...you'd be trash.
[AKIMURA](UNDER)
(oof)
[AKIMURA] (nngh)
[ANZAI] You're better off
letting me arrest you now.
[ANZAI]
Once a vampire has raped and
murdered a victim,
They can never shake the thirst
for that pleasure.
They're guaranteed to kill
again.
[ANZAI]
Sooner or later,
you would have
done the same thing to her, too.
[AKIMURA]
I would never hurt her.
I've been taking medicine to
help me control it.
I even gave myself a sedative
earlier.
I can be fine with her
and take this secret to my
grave.
[AKIMURA]
I know all human lives are
considered equal.
But they're not equally
important to everyone.
[AKIMURA]
(gahh)(deep breath)
I just can't protect everyone,
okay?
[TSUKASA] (breath)
[AKIMURA] I agree, it's not
right.
[AKIMURA]
But it's not fair...
Why should I have to kill other
women just to keep Tsukasa safe?
Or should I have killed her to
stop myself from killing the
others?
Or maybe I...
I just shouldv'e killed myself?
[AKIMURA]
(sob)
[AKIMURA] Tsukasa.
[AKIMURA]
(sobbing)
[TSUKASA]
(afraid)
[AKIMURA]
(sobbing)
(surprise)
[TSUKASA]
I'm so sorry. I should have
realized.
[AKIMURA]
(sobbing)
[TSUKASA]
(crying)
[AKIMURA]
Tsukasa.
[TSUKASA]
(crying)
[ANZAI]
Can you walk?
[TSUKASA]
(struggles to stand)
[ANZAI]
Not on that leg, you can't.
This is Anzai from F Squad.
[ANZAI]
I've apprehended Target A.
Currently at Hongo 4‐10.
[SAWAZAKI]
This is Sawazaki.
Hidaka will be there to back you
up in three minutes.
[ANZAI]
I tranqed him.
And sorry, something came up.
Take him in for me.
[SAWAZAKI]
What?!
Standby. You could atleast wait
three minutes for someone to‐
[TSUKASA]
Don't you have to go?
Don't worry, I'll be...
[ANZAI]
Fine? No, you won't.
This way?
[TSUKASA]
Mhmm
[ANZAI]
Hey. 301, right?
[TSUKASA]
Thank you for everything...
Anzai.
[ANZAI]
You need to forget my name
understand?
[ANZAI]
forget what happened today.
[TSUKASA]
(crying)
[ANZAI]
(sigh)
Don't cry.
[TSUKASA]
why shouldn't I cry!?
Akimura and I were friends for
a really long time!
[TSUKASA]
I least, I thought we were.
I...
[TSUKASA]
I guess I didn't know anything
about him.
[ANZAI]
The thing about vampires is...
Biologically, they're extremely
similar to humans.
[ANZAI]
If they don't ever transform,
Then most other vampires
can't pick them out in a crowd.
[ANZAI]
So if he was trying his
damnedest to hide it,
[ANZAI] Then you can't blame
yourself for not knowing he was one.
[TSUKASA] (slight utterance)
[ANZAI]
But vampires...
are fighting a constant battle
against the fear
that they'll lose control the
instant they see human blood.
[ANZAI]
He might've really loved you and
meant to protect you
[ANZAI]
But devils and humans were never
meant to be together.
[TSUKASA]
Devils?
[ANZAI]
That's right.
That's what we call vampires.
[ANZAI]
(realization)
Your mouth.
[ANZAI]
It's bleeding.
[TSUKASA]
Now you notice?
I cut my lip when you shoved me!
[TSUKASA]
I'm getting a little sick of how
rough you a‐
[TSUKASA]
(gasps)
(shock)
[TSUKASA]
(ah!)
(ugh!)
[ANZAI]
(licking/kissing)
[TSUKASA]
(gasp)
[TSUKASA] & [ANZAI]
Devils' Line
Line 2.
[TSUKASA] & [ANZAI]
Safe House.