(Drip)
[TSUKASA]
(passion sigh)
(passion gasps)
(Drip)
(passion breaths)
(breath catch)
Wha...!
Uh...
(embarrassed whimpering)
[OCHIAI]
Let me see now.
How about Tsukasa?
[MIWAKO]
Tsukasa.
Tsukasa!
[OCHIAI]
You alive there, Tsukasa?
[TSUKASA]
Huh? Oh!
[OCHIAI]
Feel free to stay
in your seat...
But would you read
paragraph three for us, please?
It's there on page 136.
Uh... Yes, of course.
Medieval communes in Europe
had sworn allegiances of
mutual defense among citizens‐
[TSUKASA THINKING]
It's been a month
since Akimura disappeared.
They're saying he left
to study abroad in Canada.
His arrest wasn't
even on the news.
Is it because he's a vampire?
And I haven't seen Anzai
since the... incident.
What if...
What if I imagined
the whole thing?
[TSUKASA]
(Gasping)
[ANZAI]
(Exhale)
Huh?
Hey... there's a syringe
sticking out of your leg!
I know. I did it on purpose!
I can't believe I had to
use this on myself.
(Breathing hard)
Do my... Do my eyes
look normal again?
Uh, yeah... I guess.
[TSUKASA THINKING]
He... He does look
a lot better.
The dark circles are gone.
I, um...
I'm sorry about that.
With the tongue and everything.
(Embarrassed shock)
Ah! No need to remind me
about all the tongue, okay!
I'm sorry!
Hey stop it, stop!
Anyway...
So are you...
are you a vampire, too?
(Gasp)
Uh...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...
No, no... it's fine, really.
Actually, I have genes
from both, so I guess
I'm a half vampire.
Half vampire?
I was under the impression it
would make my impulses weaker.
But apparently not.
(Sigh)
I held it all in with Akimura,
but I almost blew it.
Anyway, look on the bright side.
Huh?
There are plenty of
other fish in the sea.
Oh... wait!
[TSUKASA THINKING]
Since then, I haven't
seen Anzai at all.
(Groaning)
Is it because he kissed me?
Is that why I can't stop
thinking about him?
But... But I...
That's not how real love
is supposed to work.
Is it?
Akimura?
I hope...
I hope you're okay.
Come to think of it...
Have I ever truly fallen
in love with anyone before?
To be honest... that basically
was my first real kiss.
I wonder where you are
right now... Anzai.
Ah!
Hm!
[ANZAI]
Oh! Sorry...
I uh... didn't mean
to scare you.
Wh‐what're you doing Anzai?
Why are you just
sitting out there?
I used the telephone pole.
It was the best way
for me to to get to you.
Telephone pole!?
[ANZAI]
So. How've you been?
Huh?
You're worried about
Akimura, aren't you.
Um...
You always stop for a minute
when you get to the place
we arrested him.
(Gasp)
I can put in a request for you
if you want to go and visit him.
And, well... depending on
the trial, they can get off
with a life sentence.
Uh... yeah.
[TSUKASA THINKING]
What kind of person am I?
I've been more worried
about Anzai than Akimura.
Ugh... I'm the worst.
So have you been
losing some weight?
You know guys like a girl with
a little meat on her bones.
(Grunt)
Hey now! Stop it!
Take it easy, stop hitting me!
(Anzai laughing)
Well look at you.
You're doing much better
than I thought.
Huh?
He's... he's smiling.
(Radio chirps)
[SAWAZAKI]
It's Sawazaki.
We have a Level 1 Special Case!
Name: Yuuko Tamaru.
Female. Age 21.
Suspect will be referred to
as Target T from now on.
Be advised. Target is hiding
inside the Mikusa Building.
[ANZAI]
This is Anzai. Copy.
I'm right by it. On the way.
Huh?
Oh!
(Tsukasa running and panting)
(Yuuko breathing heavily)
[SAWAZAKI]
Calm down.
Let's settle this peacefully.
[SAWAZAKI]
Right, Yuuko Tamaru?
[TSUKASA]
Oh...
(Yuuko breathing heavily)
You the police?
[SAWAZAKI]
PS‐D5 Task Force:
Devil‐related crimes.
We can make special allowances
in cases like yours.
You have no priors.
If this was all
just an accident...
they might not press charges.
Charges?
I really don't care
what they do to me, okay.
[ANZAI]
Then why are you running...
Yuuko?
Is that you, Yuuki?
[TSUKASA]
What the...?
Do you have someone...
Someone that you would
do anything in the
world to protect?
If you don't you won't
understand how I feel.
The love of my life was just
helping me make dinner.
He cut his finger
and then said...
"Lick it off."
(Gasp)
Next thing I knew
I stabbed him.
Then... I was desperately
drinking his blood!
I was...
I was always so careful!
Trying to make sure
I would never hurt him.
I should've known
it could never work out.
A devil marrying a human...
living under the same roof.
[ANZAI]
Damn right it didn't work.
He showed you his bloody finger
and asked you to lick it off?
What part of that is
"being careful"?
(Gasp)
[ANZAI]
I don't care if he
was your husband.
If you see blood,
you're gonna lose it.
I take it you never taught
your husband how vicious
devils can be.
(Gasps)
[ANZAI]
You said you would do
anything to protect him,
but were too afraid
that he'd leave you.
You can't leave out
something that important.
(Sobbing)
(Yuuko crying)
[SAWAZAKI]
December 3rd, 23:35.
Target T apprehended.
Assault charges to be filed.
Present on the scene:
Senior Officer Sawazaki
And Officer Anzai.
(Yuuko sobbing)
Oh!
Uh...
(Anzai grunting)
[ANZAI]
I knew it!
You followed me, didn't you?
Huh!
And you didn't even
bother to lock the door?
You're all alone,
it's the middle of the night!
Yeah you're right. Sorry.
But you left this, I thought
I'd return it to you.
(Gasp)
Uh...
[ANZAI]
I... I'm sorry.
[TSUKASA THINKING]
Really? Is he
apologizing to me?
[ANZAI]
But from now on, you don't
have to bring me my stuff.
[TSUKASA]
Oh...
Understand?
Yeah... I got it.
[TSUKASA]
Um... So, that woman...
[ANZAI]
She's an old friend.
We... we used to make snowmen
when we were kids.
(Gasps)
It's cold.
(Exhales)
[ANZAI]
Do not get hurt
in front of me again.
(Anzai exhales)
[ANZAI]
As I was saying earlier...
it's not easy for non‐family
members to visit a devil.
But they might make an
exception if you helped
the devil reform himself.
If you wanna see him,
then that's how you can
do it, alright.
(Shivers)
You okay?
I mean... if you want...
you could use the uh...
A kotatsu.
[TSUKASA]
You have one at home?
I only have the basic things
one needs to get by.
Everyone needs a kotatsu.
Do you get cold easily?
[ANZAI]
No, but my temperature
stays around 80 degrees.
What, that's low!
(Radio chirps)
[SAWAZAKI]
Anzai. Where are you?
I've told you to stop
running off like this.
[ANZAI]
Sorry, but I gotta go.
And you make sure
to lock your door.
Hey! Wait a sec!
Huh?
[JILL]
What?! Do it with
somebody watching?
Not a chance.
[SAKAKI]
Welcome back, Anzai.
[YANAGI]
Anzai, how's it going?
Right then, here are
your tranqs.
[ANZAI]
Oh, thanks. This'll help.
Where's Sawazaki? Not here yet?
He should be here soon.
Sounds like you're gonna
be in for a lecture.
Something about...
oh, you running off
on your own again?
[JILL]
He's right, Anzai.
You've been a stranger
around here lately.
(Anzai groans)
[JILL]
Why run away when you've
got someone like me
taking pity on you and
inviting you over?
[ANZAI]
Leave me alone.
Water, please.
I didn't realize you two
were actually dating.
Oh, please.
Of course we are.
I didn't realize
that either.
What is wrong
with you guys?
You know you can't
believe a word she says.
She just wishes we were.
So, what was it you two
were just talking about?
[JILL]
Hm? Hee‐hee...
Just some ridiculous new clause
they added to the guidelines.
Devil Conduct Guidelines
Article 1:
Sexual intercourse between
a human and a vampire
will now be legal...
As long as there is consent
from both parties...
and a doctor is present.
(Anzai groans)
[JILL]
I'm not so sure
that's a good idea.
The Tamaru couple was in
that very situation,
I mean they even signed
a pre‐nup promising
not to have sex,
and look how that turned out.
(Happy giggle)
[TSUKASA THINKING]
What kind of hot‐pot
should I make?
A what? Hot pot?
In your apartment?
Uh‐huh. It's too cold
out on the balcony.
Plus, you know...
I was hoping we could talk.
(Anzai gulps)
Y'know that's no reason
to just let me in.
I can't just go in your place
like that. That would be um...
[TSUKASA]
Hmm...
Ah...
Uhh... if it can uh...
Let's wait til after
my squad meeting tomorrow.
[TSUKASA]
Oh...
I'll stop by the grocery store
on my way home from class
and pick up all the
ingredients we'll need.
Is there anything you‐
[ANZAI]
Hey...
What are you so happy about?
Huh? Oh uh‐nothing!
[ANZAI]
How about...
you wait till I'm done...
then we can meet up and
I'll carry the bags.
So... uh which school was it
that you go to again?
[TSUKASA]
Let's see, Professor Ochiai's
office should be right
around here.
Oh. Here we go, this is it.
(Both startled)
[OCHIAI]
Hey, Tsukasa.
What are you doing here?
Can I help you?
Uh... I came to return
the book I borrowed from you.
Ah! So it was you
all this time, huh?
[TSUKASA]
Sorry, I kept forgetting
to bring it back.
Oh no, I understand,
it's okay. Hm...
[OCHIAI]
Oh! Is it snowing out there?
(Tsukasa gasps)
[OCHIAI]
Well then, you must be
pretty cold, I bet.
Why don't you stay here
and warm up?
No... I don't have time.
[OCHIAI]
I can at least make you
some tea. C'mon in.
(Tsukasa gasps)
[SAWAZAKI]
So, "devils and humans living
together is a bad idea," right?
[JILL]
Hm? Where did that come from?
[SAWAZAKI]
Anzai's little creed.
You know...
Seems Target T
that we apprehended...
She and Anzai were at the
same orphanage as kids.
What?
I'd say he's had a
lot to think about
ever since we arrested that
serial killer last month.
He's spent a lot of time
checking up on the girl
who was the motive
behind the murders.
[OCHIAI]
Here. Careful, it's hot.
[TSUKASA]
Oh... Thank you very much.
Soooo... let me think now.
Where did I put it?
[TSUKASA THINKING]
Maybe I'm just being
neurotic, but...
But he's kind of scaring me
for some reason.
But...
...I don't think I was afraid
the other day with Anzai.
I should've been. I mean he was
a total stranger kissing me!
Normally, that would be
even worse.
Oh, something is wrong with me.
[OCHIAI]
Your timing was perfect.
Uh...
I got another really good book
I was looking forward to
lending you the next time
you came in for class.
Oh, no...
I just had your book
for over six months,
I can't go and
borrow another one.
As long as it leads to
a good thesis, I don't care.
You can keep this one for
another six months if you want.
Take it.
Um, all right...
if you're sure you
really don't mind then.
(Surprised gasp)
(Grunts in terror)
[FEMALE STUDENT]
I did not expect to be
out this late.
[OTHER STUDENT] Yeah, it's
super dark out here.
[ANZAI] Is this a good
place to wait?
[OTHER STUDENT]
Ooh! That guy's hot.
Think he's waiting for somebody?
[FEMALE STUDENT]
Quiet! He'll hear you!
[OTHER STUDENT]
I'm just wondering!
[ANZAI] What am I even
doing here anyway?
[TSUKASA]
Ah! No! Stop!
(Tsukasa crying)
(Ochiai grunts aggressively)
Ah!
(Mug breaks)
Uh, what are you doing, Tsukasa?
That's just like you,
being so considerate and
not swinging it at me.
But I did really like that mug.
[TSUKASA]
I'm...I'm sorry...
[OCHIAI]
I'm just kidding.
Now let me take a look
at your hand.
You didn't have to be
that extreme, you know?
You could've just said no,
if you didn't want me to.
[TSUKASA]
What? But I just did...
And even if I didn't...
that doesn't mean you can
just do whatever you wa...
Really... I always thought
silence meant yes.
It doesn't.
And I thought...
you were married?
And have children?
So what's your point?
(Tsukasa gasps)
[YANAGI]
You know... in the end, whether
or not someone turns into a
monster is entirely up to them.
Wha...?
No! Stop!
(Tsukasa whimpering)
(Ochiai moaning)
(Tsukasa crying)
Stop!
Get off!
(Gasp)
(Crying)
(Anzai growling)
[OCHIAI]
What the hell!?!?
Huh... Who're you?
(Anzai growls)
(Ochiai screams in pain)
(Punching and screaming)
(Tsukasa gasps)
Stop it! That's enough!
You'll kill him!
(Ochiai whimpers)
(Anzai breathing heavy)
[TSUKASA]
Uh...
(Knocking at the door)
[STAFF MEMBER]
Professor? What was that noise?
Are you okay?
[ANZAI] Call the police.
[STAFF MEMBER] Professor!
[ANZAI]
When they answer tell them
a vampire got in.
(Doorknob rattles)
[STAFF MEMBER] Professor?
[ANZAI]
After they get here, you
report the sexual assault.
[STAFF MEMBER] Hey, do you
have a spare key?
[SECURITY GUARD]
Yeah. Right here.
(Anzai frantic)
[TSUKASA]
Oh! Wait! Stay here.
[ANZAI]
Don't touch me!
(Gasp)
(Door unlocks)
[STAFF MEMBER]
Huh?
[SECURITY GUARD]
Huh? What happened in here?
[STAFF MEMBER]
Professor Ochiai, are you okay?
[GUARD] Call an ambulance!
[STAFF] What's wrong?
[GUARD]
How in the world
did this happen?
[GUARD] Ma'am. Did you
see anything? Ma'am?
[STAFF] Ah! Wait! Professor!
Ah!
Well that's just great...
I'm gonna be
disciplined for this.
Huh...?
(Gasp)
[ANZAI]
This is... her blood.
I must... get rid of it!
(Licking, gulping)
(Heavy breathing)
[TSUKASA THINKING]
It's been two weeks.
[STUDENT]
I think I missed every
question on that test.
[TSUKASA]
Professor Ochiai was given
a disciplinary dismissal.
My hand has healed up, too.
[MIWAKO]
Okay, see you later! Bye.
[TSUKASA]
But ever since that night.
I've been seeing
Professor Ochiai in my dreams.
(Shivers)
Oh...
I wonder what he's
doing right now?
(Anzai deeply inhales)
(Tsukasa moans)
[ANZAI]
Ah... I'm, I'm sorry I didn't
know you were awake.
[TSUKASA]
Oh, hey Anzai.
Oh, I see... you're wearing
the scarf I made to thank you.
Wait you mean you made this?
I did. You like it?
Hm. Thanks a lot.
You're pretty good y'know.
Uh...
Sorry. Are you
afraid of men now?
Huh? I'm not scared...
Well not scared of you.
Why aren't you
scared of me, Tsukasa?
You know what I am.
Because...
your jacket is nice and warm
and makes me feel safe inside.
When I wear it, it helps me feel
like I won't have so many...
so many bad dreams.
So then you're having
nightmares now?
(Gasp)
(Tsukasa tearing up)
(Crying)
[ANZAI]
I'll get you something, too.
A present.
[TSUKASA & ANZAI]
DEVILS' LINE:
Line 3,
"Paradox."