[TSUKASA]
Anzai, please...
I want you to drink my blood.
Every day... I'll give you some.
[ANZAI]
(stunned)
[NEWS ANNOUNCER]
Police are telling
us the male suspect
(Door busts open)
who attacked a reporter
during a live broadcast...
Uh...
What craziness have you
put in her head?
You make it sound bad.
D'you talk blood tolerance?
And healing?
Long life? What else?
[TSUKASA]
Uh...
Tsukasa told me
that she was willing
to share her blood with me!
Did you put her
up to this or what?!
Hey I never forced her
to do anything at all.
But come on, man...
I can't believe you transformed
just by hearing her say it.
You have any other
physical changes?
Did you just
invent this garbage?
This baseless nonsense
is nothing but...
It is not baseless.
There's even a proven case.
There's proof of
cell regeneration after
blood consumption.
If I hadn't happened to show up
and given you some blood,
you'd still have
a hole in your lung,
and would be dead right now.
Near death amnesia?
You were listening to that
girl's little sob story
and she shot you.
A devil killed her mother,
so she's convinced all devils
are blood‐sucking rapists.
And now she's a terrorist
that kills devils
indiscriminately.
Has she been confirmed
as the sniper?
She really worth crying over?
Don't tell me you
feel sorry for her.
You're the one walking around
with human blood,
blabbing on about your
nutzo fairytales.
And you have no ID, you're
the definition of suspicious.
Ah, fair point.
If you promise to hide me out
here for a while,
I'll give you
a proper introduction.
Oh! And I do have
human blood,
but I haven't
killed anyone for it.
And there's one other thing
I would like to make clear
to you right now.
"A sap who always lets
his emotions get
the better of him...
can't protect anyone."
[TSUKASA THINKING]
On second thought,
maybe I should've
asked Sakaki
to bring this
here instead.
He probably doesn't really
want to talk to me right now.
But why should I cry about it?
If anyone wants
to cry, it's him.
I, uh, brought you some ramen.
I'll leave it
right here for you.
(Sigh)
Is it true he was healed
just by drinking
some blood?
Well Sawazaki told me...
He'd report that Anzai
was shot in the shoulder.
And despite all the blood loss,
the wound was shallow,
and healed pretty quickly.
So he filed
a false report?
[TSUKASA]
I'll just go to the roof
to cool my head.
Anzai's red eyes...
I saw them for the first time
on the day we met.
When our eyes locked
on the train...
I was afraid of him.
But his red eyes were always...
so full of pain.
And... full of kindness.
They always seemed
to be crying.
Anzai has protected me
all this time...
from bad people,
and bad dreams.
But I feel like I still
haven't done anything
for him in return.
(Startled gasp)
(Sigh)
(Heavy breathing)
Oh my gosh, what am I doing?
I guess I didn't
have to run away.
[HANS VOICE]
"A sap who always lets
his emotions get
the better of him...
can't protect anyone."
[ANZAI THINKING]
He's exactly right.
I want to be able
to protect her.
[ZERO SEVEN/NANAKO]
(Groaning)
I'm still alive?
I had a dream. With Mom...
and a devil that looked human.
Kenichi Morisawa.
That was the devil's name.
[KIKUHARA]
Should you be sitting up?
(Startled)
That weather girl is next door.
She's rather lucky to be alive.
That's excellent news, isn't it?
[NANAKO THINKING]
A devilish human...
Looks like you are too.
I'm impressed.
Why didn't you
just finish me off?
You bit me, remember?
Just like a devil.
(Nanako gasps)
[KIKUHARA]
It was beautiful, like you'd
become one yourself.
Shut up! When I'm questioned,
I'll tell them everything!
If you insist. But it will
only result in more deaths.
Anyway, I guess I should go and
tell him that you're okay.
You know, your buddy who told
you we'd be executing Plan B.
[NANAKO OVER RADIO]
Don't you dare hurt Zero Nine!
[ELEVEN]
Are you really stupid
enough to betray us?
(Groaning)
[UNO]
There were 36 transformations
in Tokyo due to the
Ikebukuro incident.
As for human casualties,
the reporter is still critical.
And the suspect has
jumped to his death.
There were two more in Ikebukuro
with minor injuries.
One in an electronics store
in Shinjuku.
And one with minor injuries
at a firm in Itabashi.
What about devil casualties?
The devil in the
electronics store was
beaten by the customers.
Later he ended up dying
in the hospital.
And an officer at the
Ikebukuro West Gate incident
shot and killed
a female devil, as well.
We have multiple reports of
a mob attacking devils in
the residential area of Nerima.
I know murder is murder,
but I wonder if they'll
be convicted like they
would have in the past.
If someone sees a devil for
the first time and kills them,
I don't think it would be fair
to charge them with murder.
And the confidentiality
policies surrounding devils?
Since now the media
blackout is over?
Do we comment on the devils
at the press conference?
No, no, not at this time.
Or well to be more precise...
we can't.
The MPD doesn't have
the authority to decide
when would be the right time
to go public about devils.
The devil issue is
a national concern
that needs to be
addressed by others.
Furthermore, all Division 5
devil personnel
are to be relieved of
their duties indefinitely.
Wait, exactly what do you mean,
"they'll be relieved
of their duties"?
We don't want to deal
with the mess
if word gets out that the
police are harboring devils.
(Door opens)
Here...
[JILL]
You know, your princess
brought that to you.
Just in time.
You can carry her to the
guestroom, Prince Charming.
She just fell asleep.
(Anzai sighs)
[JILL]
She's really not a bad kid.
So you better be there for her.
[ANZAI THINKING]
She's not even stirring.
She must be exhausted.
Oh...?
Uh? How do I take these out?
(Tsukasa stirring)
(Tsukasa moans)
(Gasp)
[ANZAI]
That scar... it really is deep.
No... it won't happen again.
This is my last one, huh?
I'm gonna have to call a donor
soon and get some more.
(Swallows)
[HANS THINKING]
So they hid the fact that Anzai
drank blood to heal his wounds.
I guess blood drinking
is illegal.
And looking at it that way...
it almost seems like ONLO
is exempt from the law.
Seeing how they run
experiments on exactly that.
Why is it considered
illegal, anyway?
[SAWAZAKI THINKING]
That figures, 30 years
of bloodsucking cases
and not one mention.
There's nothing on devil's
healing after drinking blood.
If that's true, then why
isn't it common knowledge?
Huh?
[ASAMI]
Sawazaki.
Hey.
We got a call
that someone saw
a person get pushed from
the apartment complex.
It was too dark to
make out a face,
but they said the person
was definitely
pushed over the rail
from the stairway.
Who's the informant?
Someone who works at the bar
behind the crime scene.
Ryunosuke Katagiri?
[TSUKASA'S VOICE ECHOING]
It's a beautiful day.
It's starting to look
like spring.
Hm?
[ANZAI'S VOICE ECHOING]
Don't have to do
anything you don't want.
Hey look...
it's starting to snow.
Hm...
Huh? What was I
just dreaming about?
That's weird, I usually
remember my dreams.
[ASAMI]
So uh... did you get in touch
with the informant?
Yeah, I'm on my way to
the bar right now.
I'll drive you over there.
B Squad already has
enough humans.
[SAWAZAKI]
Thanks.
(Phone buzzing)
Hey girl, it's been a while.
[MIWAKO OVER PHONE]
Ah! You finally picked up!
Are you okay?
Why? Whaddya mean?
"Why"? There are pictures and
videos of the Ikebukuro thing
all over the internet!
And you're in several
of the ones I saw!
It looks like you're
running away from a vampire.
Huh?!
They show vampires
attacking people...
And images of people
beating vampires.
And even vampires
jumping around like ninjas.
It can't possibly be real.
It has to be some kind of epic
prank someone set up, right?
Miwako, vampires exist.
Most of the time they just
look like all the rest of us.
But they lose control
when they see blood.
[TSUKASA]
So they spend their lives
trying to avoid
the sight of it.
[MIWAKO]
Um, I'm sorry.
Let's just forget
if it's true or not.
How do you know about them?
[TSUKASA]
Uh...
Oh wait...
didn't you tell me
that guy that you're really
into could jump super high?
He can jump from phone pole
to phone pole.
(Gasp)
But listen, I know I can
trust him, so it's ok‐
[MIWAKO]
Is trust really the issue here?
Uh...
[MIWAKO]
You said they lose control
when they see blood.
In that case, it doesn't
matter how much you can
trust him, does it?
Besides, Tsukasa...
you only just met the guy!
How much do you really
even know about him?
[TSUKASA]
Well..
[MIWAKO]
I‐I'm sorry.
I'm just...
so worried about you.
[TSUKASA]
Maybe you're right.
It hasn't been that long
since we met.
And there's still so much
I don't know about him.
I could never know...
how hard it is
to be a devil...
Or what it's like
to lose control.
But he...
He means so much... to me.
Huh?
(Gasp)
(Gunshot)
Whoa... I missed ya,
I can't believe it.
(Cowering)
[KIWAKO]
Oryo, dear?
(Slams door)
Um...
There are other
people here. What now?
[ELEVEN OVER RADIO]
If he told them what he saw,
they'll be trouble.
If you can kill them,
kill them.
Don't... don't you
dare hurt them,
you leave these people alone!
Well, don't you have
a beautiful heart.
I almost can't believe you're
actually a bloodsucking animal.
(Gasp)
Look out!
[SAWAZAKI]
Dammit!
[KIWAKO]
Hey, just what is
going on out here?
I think I'm gonna stay behind,
they might still be at risk!
Thanks. I'm taking your car.
(Clattering outside)
[TSUKASA]
What was that?
[ANZAI]
Isn't that the same guy
from the New Year's Eve case?
But who's this guy?
[ANZAI OVER RADIO]
Sawazaki, this is Anzai.
A devil is being chased.
It's not really
our jurisdiction,
but this is urgent.
Target is the same trans‐person
from the New Year's Eve case.
[SAWAZAKI OVER RADIO]
He's an informant!
(Gasp)
Where is he now?
[ANZAI]
He's running across rooftops
south of Bar Sakaki.
I can see him.
[SAWAZAKI]
Officer Anzai,
deployment authorized.
Protect the target!
[HANS]
Mr. Five O'Clock shadow
is the Touo TV cameraman.
He's the one that kept the
camera rolling back at the plaza
where that devil was drinking
the weather girl's blood.
He kept rolling even after
I told him to stop.
And while he was filming
he kept telling me to
just kill the guy already.
(Disgust)
I will assist you in
the arrest, Officer Anzai.
[ANZAI]
You sure talk big for someone
who won't even give us
his real name.
M'kay... My name is
Johannes Kleemann.
I was born in Hybrid Birth Plan
Term 15, White Group Number 7.
Raised under the
supervision of ONLO.
Since you keep going on
and on about identity.
What term, group,
and number are you?
Huh?
Well, we can talk about that
later, let's just go for now.
If you lose it, I'll just
punch your lights out again.
Uh...
Oh!
Lock the door and hide.
Hybrid Birth Plan?
I thought ONLO was just
an orphanage for devil children.
[SAWAZAKI OVER RADIO]
Attention F Squad.
Anzai has deployed
with my permission.
(Door opens)
This is an emergency.
[YANAGI]
Hmm?
(Breathing heavily)
[SAWAZAKI]
Jill, stand by.
What? Why? Seriously?
[SAWAZAKI]
You both should know.
All devil personnel have
been removed from duty.
But right now the safety of
our target comes first.
[ANZAI]
Just don't let
the brass find out.
[YANAGI]
Alright... I guess
I should monitor
Anzai's temperature
and heart rate.
What's the deal
with the tracker?
You've never had to
monitor me before.
Look all I know is
that ONLO asked me to
monitor Anzai's health.
I'm not aware of
all the details.
(Breathing heavily)
It's like tag,
except the devil is running.
As a kid, I thought it was weird
when there was just one "it."
I never understood why
the runners didn't just
all band together
to defeat the pathetic thing.
Sure, a transformed devil
is vicious, but it shouldn't
take long to figure out.
Humans are the ones
that have the devils
hopelessly outnumbered.
Now we're going to hunt down
all of you filthy devils,
so that there will be
even less of your kind.
[HANS]
Outnumbered, huh?
Huh?
Because I'm counting
three‐to‐one over here.
[ANZAI FRUSTRATED]
Hey, don't make him bleed.
What? Come on. Not even
a little bitty nosebleed?
Didn't you know? Murderers don't
have human blood in their veins.
And that's not just
a silly metaphor.
What are you talking about?
His blood is actually nothing
but just simple ketchup.
Wha...? Ugh, at least you could
come up with something funny!
Well I did get it off your mind.
No more signs of transforming.
(Shocked)
[HANS]
So I guess you only go
full‐on devil
whenever you're
lusting after Tsukasa.
[ANZAI]
Huh?
(Smug laugh)
Ah!
(Screaming)
[ZERO FOUR]
Haha... Even blood from an old
man like me turns you on, eh?
I almost feel sorry for you.
Ah, you talk too much, Ketchup.
You really don't have to listen
to a ketchup‐head like him.
(Anzai groans)
Now, when you need
to pull it out,
you need to pull it out.
What?
A doctor once told me...
"Sexual lust
comes with bloodlust
and vice versa,
it's physiological."
"So instead of always
relying on just sedatives,
a more natural outlet
would be masturbation."
Got any handcuffs on you?
[ANZAI]
So you just accept we have
a lust that drives us to murder.
Yeah, well whether you
choose to accept it or not,
bloodlust is always
going to exist.
Question is how you're
going to control it
when it overtakes you.
[ANZAI THINKING]
He's right.
(Car pulling up)
But...
[SAWAZAKI]
Anzai! Where's Katagiri?
Uh... here!
Hey, uh, wait a minute,
aren't you Tsukasa's boyfriend?
[SAWAZAKI]
Wait, Lee's here, too?
[KATAGIRI]
Um! Are all the people
at the bar all right?
Because, well, this man
threatened to murder
all of them, too.
[SAWAZAKI]
Don't worry, I left another
detective at the bar.
[ANZAI]
You said that he's an informant
on the Ikebukuro case.
Is that why that guy
was after him?
[SAWAZAKI]
Wha...?
Anzai, you need to hide
Katagiri at Bar Sakaki.
And don't answer any
questions from the team.
(Anzai gasps)
Katagiri's tip is not
common knowledge back at HQ.
Only a few know about it.
[ANZAI]
You think there's a mole?
[KANO]
Well, well...
Looks just like his father.
Oh?! Now that's a surprise.
To think I'd see
a child of the light
and a child of
the dark in one place.
(Running footsteps)
Huh?
(Panting)
[TSUKASA]
You're hurt,
what happened to your face?
[KATAGIRI]
Tsukasa...
(Fainting)
[TSUKASA]
Oryo! Why are you here?
Apparently he's a vital witness
in the Ikebukuro case.
What the hell did you see?
[KATAGIRI]
On the news, they said that
the suspect jumped to his death,
but he didn't.
(Gasp)
I saw everything that happened.
As he fell... I could hear
he was saying something.
I think... I heard him
say, "Traitor."
[TSUKASA]
Did that happen when
he was chasing you?
[KATAGIRI]
This is, um...
I get it. You probably
did that to yourself
in order to fend off
your bloodlust, didn't you?
Huh?
I saw all that dead boy's blood.
Devils do it all the time.
One of my coworkers back at the
bar said she used to do it, too.
She was wondering what's
going to become of us now...
now that they know.
Johannes, take care of Oryo.
I'll go in through the window
and come down when my eyes
are back to normal.
But Anzai, you have to
get your wounds treated.
I'm fine. Just go
to your room, okay?
Uh...
It's nothing to worry about.
That's just how he has to deal
with his bloodlust right now.
[TSUKASA]
Hm...
[HANS]
Tsukasa, are you angry?
[ANZAI]
Bloodlust is always
going to exist.
I can't change that fact.
But...
If I admit that this craving
is somehow natural...
It would be like I...
No, I must remember that
I've been a devil...
...since the first day
I met her.
[YANAGI]
You've lost a lot of blood.
We need to get you
to a hospital.
[HANS]
But that Sawazaki guy said
we have to hide him here.
If we leave him like this,
he could die.
But what hospitals around
here will treat devils?
Shirase Hospital will.
Jill, call Sawazaki for me.
You go back to the bar.
Actually, uh...
Huh? Hey now,
where are you going?
We're taking Oryo
to the hospital.
You don't have to go
with them y'know,
you should stay here.
It's not safe out there.
I'm going.
Uh...
Makimura, give me
a status report.
[SAWAZAKI ON RADIO]
Makimura.
[MAKIMURA]
Nothing to report.
What about with you?
[SAWAZAKI]
We arrested the guy.
Now I'm looking for
Katagiri; he's missing.
You stay where you are.
Understood.
You be careful.
Eleven, Zero Four
has been arrested.
[MAKIMURA ON RADIO]
And there was a human
working at Cross Bar.
You told me that it was all
just devils working in there.
(Sigh) I cannot
stand incompetence.
The next time you slip up,
you'll be the one
pushed off the ledge.
(Zero Nine grunts)
(Eleven groans)
(Breathing heavily)
Zero Seven!
Hey there Uno, you remember
this girl, don't you?
[UNO]
You mean the sniper?
[TAKIMOTO]
Yeah... And as I recall,
I'm pretty sure I've seen
that name somewhere else before.
(Crashing sound)
[BOTH]
Huh? Hmm?
Hang in there, Oryo!
We're almost there!
[TAKIMOTO]
She's escaping! Hey! Stop!
[YANAGI]
Who is that? A devil?
(Nanako grunts)
(Gasp)
[TSUKASA]
That's the person
who shot Anzai.
[NANAKO]
Give me your car keys!
Or I will break her neck!
[ANZAI & TSUKASA]
DEVILS' LINE:
Line Seven,
"Chaser."