(Sewing machine running)
[TSUKASA]
There.
Ow! Oh!
Don't you worry.
I swear... I'll never
offer you my blood.
[KENICHI]
The main PC is
on the second floor.
We can boot it up and
get the member list,
but it will take
five minutes to unlock it.
And five more to copy the file.
At what point will we
be breaking into the
CCC hideout, exactly?
[ANZAI]
You're the squad leader.
Well when do you think
would be good?
How about tonight?
The sooner the better.
If they catch on to us,
they'll erase the list
and run.
Zero Five was Ushio
from C Squad.
We'll ask their leader
Takimoto for a little help...
he'll keep him busy.
I'll take down Kikuhara.
[ISHIMARU]
I don't think we can
let you join the raid.
On the other hand, we're
short‐staffed, so would
you keep a lookout for us?
But I hope you'll leave
the sniper rifle at home.
You and Jill need to
stay grounded for now.
If you deploy without leave,
then they'll fire you.
(Jill grunts)
[ANZAI]
You're only taking humans?
There aren't any devils
in the CCC.
If we're up against humans,
we got it.
[ANZAI]
Yeah, but...
[ISHIMARU]
We've been given notice.
They're willing to understand
that you were in danger
the other day...
But in the event that
a devil ignores the ban...
and engages in violence,
causes injury or drinks blood...
They will be relieved of their
duty, regardless of reason.
(Shock and dismay)
They will henceforth be placed
under strict surveillance
and forbidden to make
contact with humans.
Are you serious?
Are they going to quarantine us?
I'm guessing you'll be under
24‐hour surveillance
and banned from
visiting, calling or
even emailing, anyone.
[HANS]
Man, I'm starving.
[TSUKASA]
Hey, everyone. Dinner is ready.
Sweet beautiful food!
This is glorious!
Sorry. We couldn't make
anything more elaborate.
[ANZAI]
This is fine.
(Peaceful music playing)
[ASAMI]
Thanks for the food.
When a guy tells you to
investigate him,
he knows you're not gonna
find any dirt on him...
without some serious digging.
(Sigh)
[TSUKASA] Um, Anzai.
[ANZAI] Hm?
[TSUKASA]
Here. I made this for you.
[ANZAI] Oh!
[TSUKASA]
It's a utility belt.
What? You made this? Really?
I did... but I guess
you won't be deploying,
so you won't need to
use it now. Um...
You had one...
I just didn't think
it was great
for carrying the
nail protectors
Mr. Kano gave you.
Yeah. Huh?
[TSUKASA]
I thought you could put
the protectors here,
and it would be easier
to get them on quickly.
But maybe it won't be
that easy after all.
So, um... Anzai.
Hm?
Thank you.
No, you have it
all backwards.
I should be the one
thanking you.
You gave me a gift.
That's not what I meant.
I mean, um...
(Happy sigh)
[TSUKASA]
I want to thank you...
for everything.
(Compassionate music playing)
We've been through a lot.
But I... mean it...
when I say I'm glad I met you.
[ANZAI]
Oh...
Yeah.
Me, too.
I'm really glad...
I met you, too.
Thanks for this.
I'll take care of it.
(Tsukasa giggle)
(Anzai giggle)
(Bags being packed)
[ANZAI]
Sawazaki.
[SAWAZAKI]
Hm?
I'm going with you.
[SAWAZAKI]
No. This is one time I hav‐
[ISHIMARU]
Then I'll need you to join up
with the lookout team.
[SAWAZAKI]
You can't do that.
He'll just be standing watch.
But Anzai...
[ANZAI]
Don't worry.
Hold on to this.
'Kay.
[ANZAI]
Hey, I want you to
stay with Tsukasa.
And take care of her.
[HANS WITH MOUTH FULL]
Hm... You got it!
[SAWAZAKI ON RADIO]
Objective on raiding
the CCC hideout:
Obtain the member list.
This is Ishimaru,
Sawazaki, and Asami.
We're taking Nine over to
the main computer.
[SAWAZAKI]
Zero Seven is on a building
100 yards south.
Anzai is on a building
500 yards north.
I'm now in position.
[SAWAZAKI]
Yanagi, you stand near
the hideout, just in case.
Got it.
Um... would you
take me with you?
I need to be close to him.
[HANS]
Then I'm going, too!
[YANAGI]
Just a‐ Hey!
It's time.
Go.
By the stairs.
(Tapping sounds)
[SAWAZAKI]
I heard a strange noise.
[ISHIMARU]
Okay, let's go.
Hmm... Oh!
[MERCENARY]
My condolences.
Stop there!
[SAWAZAKI]
Zero Seven!
Can you see the river?
[NANAKO]
It's in my blind spot!
I heard a splash, but...
[ISHIMARU]
Looks like they're dead.
Those strange noises
must have been gunshots.
He used a silencer.
These are the same bullets
we use in Division 5.
[SAWAZAKI]
If that man were
from Division 5,
would he deliberately let us
hear his voice like that?
[ASAMI]
Well, they're not
the most uncommon bullets.
Anyway, where's the computer?
[KENICHI]
The... the second room
from the end.
[ISHIMARU]
Maybe they were homeless
and were squatting here.
[SAWAZAKI]
There's way too much dirt
on his feet for that to hold.
It would've come off if he
were walking around in here.
[TSUKASA]
Someone killed those
homeless people...
and then just left them
in the CCC hideout?
Why would they do that?
[ASAMI]
Let's hurry this up.
We'll be in here.
(Tapping sounds)
[SAWAZAKI]
Those gunshots...
There were three of them.
Where's the third bullet?
There's no third bullet.
Huh?
(Door creaking)
(Devil growling)
A devil.
(Roar)
(Attack sounds over radio)
[SAWAZAKI]
Devil!
Sawazaki?
(Static on radio)
Come in! Hey! What's wrong?
You and Jill need to
stay grounded for now.
If you deploy without leave,
then they'll fire you.
(Devil growling and
fighting over radio)
(Devil and Sawazaki grunting)
[ISHIMARU]
Are you alright?
[SAWAZAKI]
Yes. But he bit me‐
Oh!
Behind you!
[ASAMI]
Hey! What's go‐
[ISHIMARU]
Get back!
Huh?
(Devils growling)
[ISHIMARU]
You've got to be kidding.
[ISHIMARU ON RADIO]
This is Ishimaru.
We've encountered five
transformed devils.
[ANZAI]
Five?
[ISHIMARU]
There are two bodies
in the hallway,
but the devils aren't even
looking at them.
The dead bodies left back in
the hall aren't human.
[SAWAZAKI]
There's one more body, as well.
The man killed by
the third bullet.
A human.
[SAWAZAKI]
The five devils
ganged up on the human
so they could all
drink his blood.
[ANZAI]
So just one of them is human?
Then I'll make sure not to look
at him when I come to help you.
Give me your location!
[SAWAZAKI]
I'm bleeding, too.
Even if I weren't...
the second they find out
you deployed, you'll be fired.
[ANZAI]
But I...
(Slow deep breathing)
I swear...
I will protect you!
You need to stay away from here!
[ISHIMARU]
Here they come, Sawazaki!
[SAWAZAKI]
We'll split them up.
I'll go upstairs.
Then I better go that way.
Let's go!
(Gunshots)
Come on, I'm over here!
Up here!
[ISHIMARU]
They're going after him
because of the blood.
Over here.
(Nervous breathing and typing)
[ASAMI]
Keep going! You can
do this in ten, right?
[TSUKASA]
Five transformed devils,
all at the same time.
Anzai, please be careful.
Seriously. Be careful.
(Devils roar)
(Gunshot)
(Devil growling)
(Gunshots)
(Gunshot)
[ISHIMARU]
Sawazaki's on the third floor.
There were two devils after him.
If you don't hurry,
they'll get him.
(Devils roar)
(Gunshots)
[SAWAZAKI]
His wound is closed over.
Is that because he bit me
and drank my blood?
Huh?
(Anzai hissing)
(Sawazaki screams)
(Anzai roars)
(Snapping sounds)
(Sawazaki heavy breathing)
(Anzai heavy breathing)
Anzai.
If you hadn't shown up...
I would be dead.
(Deep breath)
I should...
have killed them myself.
I should have...
Where's little Nine at?
[ASAMI]
He's copying the list
right now;
I made him lock
the door behind him.
More importantly.
I did that background check.
Before you were on A Squad,
you spent 5 years in W Squad.
My connections in Division 5
got me some info from people
who were in W Squad at the time,
confirming there was a
Megumi Ishimaru on the squad.
But... only for one year.
(Ishimaru sighs)
[POLICE ON RADIO]
Emergency for Division 5
Squads L through N.
[ISHIMARU & ASAMI]
Huh?
[POLICE]
We received a report
that armed officers
are hunting devils
in an abandoned building
at 2‐6 Hinomi, Koto Ward.
(Police sirens)
[NANAKO]
Uh...
[POLICE]
That's 2A2B jurisdiction.
They'll be there shortly.
[ISHIMARU]
Yanagi, get out of here.
What's going on in there?
Why did he say,
"hunting devils"?
[ISHIMARU]
I'm not sure,
but this was a trap.
That doesn't mean we can
leave you stranded in there!
[TSUKASA]
Anzai!
[KIKUHARA]
We brought in
eight homeless men,
seven devils and one human.
Three of them were killed by
Division 5 bullets.
On the scene were
armed members of F Squad,
who had lured the men inside.
All ready for framing.
[ASAMI]
We just have to tell them
what we're doing!
They'll know we're not
hunting devils!
[ISHIMARU]
They'll also know we let
Nine and Seven in on our
plans without approval.
So they might just decide to
remove us from the case anyway.
[ASAMI]
Is that why you tricked us
into raiding the hideout?
I don't know what you mean.
The date and time of the
raid was all your idea
to begin with!
It wasn't me!
It wasn't "Jason".
I didn't report on today's
operation to anyone in the CCC.
(Anzai heavy breathing)
What am I crying about? Why...?
[ASAMI]
Wait are you... Jason?
[ISHIMARU]
I am Number 13 or
better know as Jason.
Good for you;
you were right about me.
[ASAMI]
I'm supposed to be happy?!
What have you been plotting
all this time, huh?
That first man, the one who
shot the devil and ran.
I suspect he was
working for Kikuhara.
It may be that they've been
watching me the whole time.
I didn't think they were
actually capable of
setting such an
annoying trap for us.
The way things are going,
I would've expected the list
to have been deleted.
But Nine is back there
copying down the list right now!
Yes, he is.
And there was a list.
That's why I joined
the CCC and Division 5,
so as to find that list.
I'm working as
an undercover agent.
[ISHIMARU ON RADIO]
I really work for Public
Security General Affairs,
Investigation Division 6,
Section 11.
And... there's one more
undercover agent
working for us,
probably the one
who left us the list.
He was able to infiltrate
the CCC just like I did.
You know Makimura.
What are you doing?
It's done.
I am turning
you in to HQ.
Turning me in?
You of all people?
They'll arrest you, too, for
the murders you committed
over at Cross Bar.
I'm turning myself in, too.
[ISHIMARU]
E Squad investigated
at Cross Bar.
There they came across both
the bullets and a revolver
with the manager's
fingerprints all over them.
And there was gunshot residue
on the manager's right hand.
[MAKIMURA]
Get outside! Now!
[ISHIMARU]
Makimura would have been
trying to get everyone
in the bar to safety.
Which probably ended up
making the manager even
more suspicious, so...
[MAKIMURA]
Go! GO!
[ISHIMARU]
She carried a gun
for self‐defense,
and she fired first.
(Gunshot)
(Gasp)
[ASAMI]
But then who was it that
killed the employee?
[SAWAZAKI ON RADIO]
Suicide.
(Asami surprised gasp)
[SAWAZAKI]
It happens a lot with vampires
who have seen death or injury
caused by blood drinking.
When they see someone
they care about
losing a lot of blood
right in front of them...
They get so afraid of
losing control
that they kill themselves.
[MAKIMURA]
No, don't!
[YANAGI]
Makimura was a double agent?
And so was Ishimaru?
I am taking you in.
Now come with me.
(Gunshot)
That's hilarious.
[ANZAI]
This is Anzai.
There are squad cars down there.
And it's not just
the riot police.
Looks like the media's
here, too.
[SAWAZAKI]
This is just speculation...
but I feel there's
another motive behind this.
If all he needed was the list,
Makimura could have just taken
the whole computer and left.
But maybe that's not
all he needed.
[ISHIMARU]
The list has
accounting information.
In other words,
the flow of money,
listing names with a financial
connection to the group.
Is there someone else
involved that we won't
find with just a list?
Uh...
[MAKIMURA IN PAIN]
There is something
behind the CCC.
At first, I thought Zero One
was pulling the strings.
A self‐righteous politician
or government official at worst.
It's just...
it doesn't add up.
There's something bigger...
Like...
Maybe R2PC and the government
body over them, the Ministry
of Health, Labor, and Welfare.
[SAWAZAKI]
Maybe what Makimura really
wanted was just to get
everyone's attention.
[ANZAI]
And that's why he decided to
call the police and the press?
[KIKUHARA]
You shouldn't have done that.
You can cause
all the uproar you want.
Get people from all walks
of life to notice the CCC.
But it won't solve the
fundamental problem.
I didn't stop F Squad
or Section 11...
Because I was betting on
a one in a million chance.
The chance that they might get
to the truth of this matter.
But I overestimated
their usefulness.
[MAKIMURA]
Uh... It's not the MHLW?
Or there's something else...
something more than‐
(Screaming in agony)
[KIKUHARA]
So you think you
can solve this...
by cutting off the lizard's head
instead of its tail?
But this lizard can
regrow even its head.
It's like grass;
you mow it down,
but you leave the roots,
so it grows back.
The roots are deep down in the
ground where you can't see them.
You can't pull them out,
and you can't control them.
On top of that, they all come
together in a large mass
to form a giant grassy field.
The enormous, uncontrollable...
"shared consciousness"
Forming society's roots.
In other words...
It's the stereotype that
"devils are dangerous."
As long as people
accept this stereotype,
it doesn't matter
if you crush the CCC.
Someone else will be forced to
step in and take their place.
That is why I choose to
stay inside this box,
and use the CCC to fight
against those at the top.
[MAKIMURA]
You can't build anything...
on a foundation of murder.
[KIKUHARA]
This little chat has
gone on long enough.
It's time we end it.
Let's draw the curtain
on this act.
[MAKIMURA]
Ugh...
You're still there, huh?
That little...
Uh...
(Gunshot)
(Anzai groans)
That's one down.
Oof...
Anzai's been shot!
(Tsukasa stunned)
[NANAKO]
On the roof!
A sniper hit Anzai!
[ISHIMARU]
Anzai? Anzai?
Anzai! Hey!
(Anzai gasping)
[ANZAI]
Am I... am I dying...?
[ISHIMARU]
Anzai! Anzai, can you hear me?
[RIOT POLICE]
Freeze!
[SAWAZAKI]
Come in, Anzai! Answer me!
[YANAGI]
This isn't good.
If we don't do something,
he'll die!
(Tsukasa gasps)
[ISHIMARU]
If a devil engages in violence,
causes injury or
drinks blood...
C'mon hurry up and
call an ambulance!
I'm working on it!
But I don't know
if they'll make it!
(Tsukasa breathing hard)
[ISHIMARU]
Regardless of their reasons,
they'll be forbidden to
make contact with humans
for the foreseeable future.
[TSUKASA]
Hm...
[YANAGI]
Huh? Tsukasa!
'Kay Lee, get out.
I need you to take me
to him... to Anzai!
[TSUKASA & ANZAI]
DEVILS' LINE,
Line 12,
"DEVILS' LINE."