I really like you.
(Gunshot)
Huh?
(Anzai pained gasp)
(Gunshot)
(Gasp)
Uh!
Ah!
(Heavy breathing)
(Growly scream)
(Strangled gasp)
(Sobbing)
[ANZAI]
I really like you.
[TSUKASA]
No... Anzai, wait!
[SAWAZAKI]
Hey! What's wrong? Anzai!
We need to get going.
[YANAGI] Hm.
Jill, you're
staying here.
[JILL] What!? Why?
(Grunt)
It's your kind that are
the sick murderers here!
(Gunshot)
My mother...
she is dead because of you!
(Anzai growls)
If you devils never existed,
she'd still be alive!
(Gunshot)
[ANZAI]
Damnit!
(Gunshot)
(Anzai coughing blood)
[HANS]
You're weaker than
I thought you'd be.
[HANS]
Are you just a human?
Whoa! I think she
blew out your lung.
[HANS]
If you don't do something
quick, you're gonna die.
[HANS]
You've lost a lot of blood,
and we gotta fix that lung.
I guess I can give you this.
Organ restoration...
what's that like... 200ccs?
[HANS]
Nothing works better than
human blood, after all.
[ANZAI]
No...!
(Grunting)
I don't want... that shit!
(Strained breathing)
[ANZAI]
What is this? Where am I?
It looks...familiar.
(Startled)
[ZERO SEVEN]
Who are you?! You a friend
of that piece of shit?
[HANS]
Not really. I'm just here
as a passing life‐saver.
Shared a bit of
human blood is all.
Human blood?
So you're a devil too!
(Gunshot)
Oh, don't get any shady ideas.
I bought this.
It was for sale
by owner, you see.
You expect me to take
a devil at his word?
[ZERO SEVEN]
That man... that devil...!
He tricked my mother into
thinking he loved her!
Then he drank her blood
as she lay dying...
as he raped her!
(Devil screaming)
Huh?
[HANS]
You know, I think you might
be looking at this all
in the wrong way.
What I'm getting is that
that guy was a total degenerate.
And that he just so happened
to also be a devil as well.
[ZERO SEVEN]
Hrm!
[HANS]
It takes more than one factor
in someone's life
to drive them to crime.
You have to look at what sort
of environment they grew up in,
what heir interests are,
and who's always around them.
All of these come together
in a complex pattern to
create that foundation.
In other words...
treating someone like
a potential criminal
just because they happen to be
a devil is way too simplistic.
(Devil screaming)
[YOUNG ANZAI]
(Scared)
(Retching)
[TSUKASA]
Are you scared?
They're devils. Just like you.
[YOUNG ANZAI]
B‐but I'm not...
I'm only half...
[YOUNG ANZAI]
I'm nothing like these devil‐
[ZERO SEVEN]
Shut up! Not another word!
If he weren't a devil.
He would never have done
those terrible things!
[DEVIL]
Blood!
[DEVILS]
Blood! Blood! Blood!
(Devils screaming)
[YOUNG ANZAI]
I'm not...
I'm not like them!
(Growling)
[YOUNG ANZAI]
Blood!
[HANS]
But you have to realize...
people do terrible things too.
(Growl)
(Gasp)
Huh...?
[SAWAZAKI]
So, then Anzai just
ran off by himself?
[TSUKASA]
Uh... yes, sir.
[SAWAZAKI]
He must be
chasing the sniper.
[TSUKASA THINKING]
Oh, Anzai...
All because I was bleeding.
He was crying.
What do I do? It's my fault.
I have to do something.
[YANAGI]
What the hell just happened?
He wouldn't!
[YANAGI]
Sawazaki, come on!
We need to find Anzai fast!
[TSUKASA]
Uh... Wait!
I am going with you!
(Roaring)
(Hiss)
(Grunting)
[YANAGI]
So you're telling me that
Anzai didn't lick your wound?
[TSUKASA]
That's right.
Anzai... he resisted.
[YANAGI]
I see. Well then there's
still hope for him.
[TSUKASA]
Maybe if Anzai sees me,
he'll come back to his senses.
(Beeping)
[SAWAZAKI]
Hey, what's that sound?
[YANAGI]
You know that ring he wears?
I can monitor him,
track his temperature,
in case of an emergency.
This sound is the alarm
that goes off when he gets
above 102 degrees.
[TSUKASA]
He's normally only 80 degrees.
That's a big jump!
[YANAGI]
There's only one thing
that could have this much
effect on a devil.
He must have ingested an
extremely large quantity
of blood.
The problem is... if his temp
keeps going up like this...
it'll effect his brain and
other vital organs, leading
to permanent damage.
Worst case scenario,
he might die.
[SAWAZAKI]
He might die? Seriously?
[TSUKASA]
Anzai...
[YANAGI]
We must make sure to find him,
so we can stop him
before that happens.
I've never seen something
this drastic before.
[HANS]
Hey, I want you
to calm down now.
(Roar)
Oh well...
his wounds are healed,
but now the blood's
totally gone to his head.
Go to Hell... I'll kill you!
[HANS]
Whoa!
(Growl)
(Gasp)
[YANAGI]
This is only a theory,
but it's possible
the sniper
is identifying vampires
by their temperatures.
With thermo‐imaging,
there's a heat signature.
[SAWAZAKI]
And you're sure...
you're absolutely certain
Anzai's consumed blood?
[YANAGI]
Yeah I didn't believe it
at first, either.
In suppressing his desire
for Tsukasa's blood,
he might have just instead
amplified his bloodlust.
[TSUKASA]
So it is my fault.
[SAWAZAKI]
If he did drink blood, then
we'll need the tranquilizers.
[TSUKASA]
Tranquilizers? Not sedatives?
[SAWAZAKI]
Those are medicinal,
tranquilizers are
more like a weapon.
They're for
law enforcement only...
to use on crazed devils.
[TSUKASA]
He's a suspect?
[YANAGI]
We've no choice.
We have to help the blood donor.
Lots of devils tend to
go after young women, so...
(Pained gasp)
[TSUKASA]
What... was that...
That pain I just felt?
(Roar)
(Gunshots)
Ugh!
(Anzai hissing)
(Growling)
(Roar)
(Van accelerating)
Uh...
(Van braking)
[FIFTEEN]
Are you alright, Zero Seven?
[ZERO SEVEN]
Fifteen!
Huh?
(Anzai gasping)
[ZERO SEVEN]
Fucking vampire.
(Anzai charging)
[HANS]
Go now!
[YANAGI]
Okay, we're almost there!
It's coming up!
It's just at the next corner!
(Tires squealing)
[TSUKASA]
Ah!
(All groaning)
(Crash)
(Anzai growling)
(Anzai hissing)
[TSUKASA]
Ah! No, don't do it!
Don't drink her blood.
[SAWAZAKI]
Huh?
[ZERO SEVEN]
Ugh!
(Van braking)
[Anzai roars]
[TSUKASA]
Anzai, no.
(Gunshots)
[SAWAZAKI]
Drop it, now!
All units...
officer needs assistance!
[SAWAZAKI]
We have the sniper and what
appears to be a secondary.
Suspect is armed.
[YANAGI]
Look, over there!
[FIFTEEN]
Ugh!
[SAWAZAKI]
Jill!?
[JILL]
What happened to you?
[SAWAZAKI]
Hey! I told you to wait‐
[JILL]
Oh, don't gimmie that!
You want me to sit around
while a fellow cop
gets himself killed?
Sorry for eavesdropping,
but I heard it all.
You know only a devil
can fight off another devil.
If you don't try and use me
now... then why have
devils on the team?
(Gasps)
[JILL]
Snap out of it, Yuuki!
(Growls)
(Gasp)
[SAWAZAKI]
Well so much for backup,
she can't get
anywhere near him.
[YANAGI]
So is she the one
that shot Anzai?
It doesn't look like
he drank her blood...
[SAWAZAKI]
What? Then whose blood
did he drink?
[HANS]
My supply.
He took a larger caliber
shot to the chest.
He was most assuredly
going to die otherwise.
But now I don't have
any blood left for me.
[TSUKASA]
He's got a single red eye.
[SAWAZAKI]
And who might you be?
And what's with your eye?
[HANS]
My name's Hans Lee.
I'm half‐devil, half‐human.
[TSUKASA]
You're half? The same as Anzai.
[HANS]
Huh? Is Anzai the guy with the
black hair?
Would you happen to know...
is he from Hokkaido?
[TSUKASA]
How did you know that?
[HANS]
Wow. To think I'd run into
another half‐breed in
the outside world.
[JILL]
Ugh!
[SAWAZAKI]
Jill! You okay?
[TSUKASA]
Another devil can't even
stop him?
[HANS]
No, not when he's amped up
on human blood and she's not.
The difference is
night and day.
[SAWAZAKI]
Hey wait!
(Grunt)
[HANS THINKING]
I was just trying to heal him.
I didn't think it would turn
into this much of a mess.
Even I couldn't have
seen this coming.
Well, what's done is done.
I guess that's what happens
when you drink blood
without having a tolerance.
(Grunt)
[TSUKASA]
Oh, no. If we don't do
something, Anzai will...
(Thud)
Huh?
Uh...
(Hiss)
(Gasp)
[TSUKASA]
No... don't...
Stop...
Huh?
Oh...
Stop, Anzai!
(Growling)
(Roar)
(Gasp)
[TSUKASA]
Oh. That's what
that feeling was.
I felt... inadequate.
(Punch)
[HANS]
What are you doing?
You'd've died.
(Sawazaki & Yanagi running)
[SAWAZAKI]
Get back!
(Van starting)
[SAWAZAKI]
Goddammit!
(Footsteps running)
[POLICE OFFICER]
That looks like the guy!
[OTHER OFFICER]
We're on the scene!
We've found one of the suspects
described in the witness report!
[SAWAZAKI]
Wait, it's not him.
[HANS]
I don't think I really
wanna hang out with
the police right now.
(Surprised gasps)
(Labored breathing)
(Sigh)
Huh?
[ZERO TWO OVER RADIO]
Zero Seven's hit attempt
failed.
We're moving to Plan B.
[TSUKASA THINKING]
It's been two weeks.
Since that night Anzai
hasn't come to see me again.
(Sigh)
Of course he's not
trying to contact me.
I never gave him my phone
number or email address.
(Wind blows in)
(Shiver)
Is he... gone forever?
Why won't he come back?
This is the last place
that I saw him.
This is the only place I can
imagine where I might find him.
(Starts to rain)
Huh?
[TSUKASA]
It's you!
From the other day.
[HANS]
Oh, hi, fancy meeting you here.
So hey...
have you seen a cross?
I'm pretty sure I
must have dropped it
somewhere around here.
So? What brings you out today?
[TSUKASA]
I haven't seen Anzai
since that night.
And I have no way
to reach him.
[HANS] Well... that does
make some sense.
[TSUKASA] What?
I mean, you did jump right in
front of a rampaging devil.
Just try putting
yourself in his shoes!
It's not all that uncommon
for a devil to lose it
and kill their lover.
Happens all the time
as a matter of fact.
Then they either kill themselves
or fall into darkness.
[TSUKASA]
I... hadn't thought about that.
I've only been
thinking of myself.
I don't know anything
about Anzai.
Or about devils.
I don't know anything really.
If I keep talking to him,
maybe I can learn some things.
So, um...
can I see your left eye?
Uh... Why only the one?
That's an oddly
interesting reaction.
This eye doesn't scare you?
The guy I like is a devil.
Wait... wait
"the guy you like"?
You mean Anzai?
Uh...
I'm right, huh!
Are you two dating?
Oh, no!
We're not exactly...
Uh...
[ANZAI]
I really like you.
Perhaps I should
tell him I like him too.
Then maybe we can go out.
Wait! He's just
waiting around for you
to get back to him?
So when'll that be?
Oh right... you have
no way to contact him.
Hm. You know
you're probably right.
It's been a couple of weeks...
but I bet he's
bothered by what happened.
That was the most devil‐like
I'd ever seen him.
And he... almost attacked me.
(Knock at the door)
[SAWAZAKI]
Come on, Anzai.
How long are you gonna
hole up in there?
(Knocking)
Your suspension ends tomorrow.
We're meeting at the bar
downstairs at 6 o'clock.
Try not to be late.
[YANAGI]
If you're really worried about
it, I got something for ya.
Just think of it
as a gift.
A gift?
[YANAGI]
He's afraid he's going to
lose it and hurt somebody
close to him.
So that's a tool to help
ease his anxiety.
Hm...
[SAWAZAKI]
Anzai...
Who are you?
Are you a devil?
(Anzai sighs)
[SAWAZAKI]
No, you're a cop.
[HANS]
Come to think of it...
doesn't it bother you?
[TSUKASA]
Doesn't what bother me?
He almost killed you
back there.
Uh... that would
frighten most people.
Yeah I know,
but it was Anzai. Oh!
Huh?
You like him that much?
Then what if he trained to get
a tolerance for blood?
Tolerance?
See this?
I drink just a little bit of
blood every single day.
So you...
drink blood?
Is it really okay for you
to do something like that?
Yeah, I just drink a little
at a time to get my body
accustomed to it.
That way it's easier to resist
the urge to feed on others.
Therefore, I can see
or even taste blood and
still maintain my sanity.
It heals wounds, as well.
Oh!
So the other day, when Anzai
survived that gunshot wound,
it was because...?
I see now.
But then whose blood was it?
I have some volunteers
that don't mind sharing
a little with me.
That way it's not too hard
for any one person, you know?
I never would have
thought of that.
Do you want me to help you?
Y'know, find Anzai, that is.
Huh?
There aren't a whole lot
of half‐breeds out there,
so I'd like to meet him.
And then maybe...
I could introduce him to
the art of blood tolerance.
Oh...
Um‐hm...
[HANS THINKING]
She's smiling and crying?
I've never seen a
tearful smile before.
[TSUKASA]
Anzai, there's a way to build
up a tolerance for blood.
Do you think that would make
things a little easier for you?
Then maybe...
we could be together again.
I have to tell him.
I will tell him!
This time, I'll be the one
to tell him how I feel.
[WEATHER WOMEN]
Good evening, everyone.
I'm here at the fountain plaza.
We were able to enjoy
a little bit of sun today.
But tomorrow, we can
expect more snow.
Now, let's take a look at
the national forecast.
[TSUKASA]
I'll find you.
I will see you again.
Wait for me, Anzai.
(Crowd chattering)
Uh...
We won't see any real rise
in temperature, so get ready
for a cold day.
(Heavy breathing)
[WEATHER WOMEN]
Everyone, be sure to bundle up.
And do your best
to stay warm tonight.
Huh?
(Grunting)
(Crowd screaming)
[MAN] It's a slasher!
[WOMAN] This is on live TV!
[GUY]
Oh my God! What's he's doing?
(Crowd screaming)
(Feeding)
(Gasping)
[TSUKASA & ANZAI]
DEVILS' LINE:
Line 5,
"Plan B."