♪ Mr. Raccoon, Mr. Raccoon.
Can't you play with me somehow? ♪
♪ No, I can't... I'm eating dinner now. ♪
♪ What's for dinner? I want some! ♪
♪ I am eating pickled plums. ♪
♪ Can I have a little crumb? ♪
♪ Don't be such a greedy bum. ♪
♪ Get your own. ♪
Yes, it's true we raccoons like to live near humans.
But not to steal their food.
Let me clear that up right now.
The reason we live by humans
is because humans live on farms.
And where there are farms there are
fogs and grass hoppers and mice and moles.
All sorts of things for raccoons to eat.
And then there's all those fruits that fall off the trees,
which humans won't touch.
It's just so much better for us to live near
a farm than, say, in some mountain highlands.
Then last spring this farmhouse was
abandoned, no one seemed to be coming back.
So, we decided to move in.
The house was just a dream.
It was a lovely level two bedroom with
a loft, garden, a huge yard for the kids.
Oh, we spent a glorious year living there.
But then...
Uh, we raccoons generally get along well with each other.
But um, all of a sudden things were different.
I go out looking for food.
And no matter where I went there'd be a raccoon there.
And more kept showing up, and then fights started
breaking out over food and burrows, until one day...
Autumn, year 31, of the Pom Poko era,
so many raccoons have been displaced from their
homes in Tama Hills, that alliances begin to form.
Finally, tensions rose so high that
the opposing alliances engaged in battle.
The leader of the red army was Gonta
young hotheaded, a raccoon of action.
The blue army was led by Seizaemon older less
quick to strike, but still, a formidable opponent.
Although not a widely known fact, raccoons do walk
on two legs when humans aren't around as you see here.
Each side eagerly pummeled the other.
But their battle was soon interrupted.
♪ Blue, blue kill the red. Red, red knock blue dead. ♪
♪ It doesn't matter which side wins
you're all still all going to lose. ♪
♪ Kill'em all who cares who side is who's. ♪
♪ Red may lose today but blue will lose tomorrow. ♪
♪ There are too many that know where to burrow. ♪
♪ When you win the battle where do you plan to stay. ♪
♪ While you all were fighting the forests went away. ♪
♪ Red will lose tomorrow and blue will lose today. ♪
♪ Slaughter everybody kill as many as you can. ♪
♪ Wipe each other out that's part of our plan. ♪
♪ Massacre annihilate shoot down the reds. ♪
♪ Do us this favor and we'll give you our thanks. ♪
♪ It's about time our numbers shrank. ♪
♪ Those of us remaining must keep our family small. ♪
♪ Have another cub and you will lose it all. ♪
♪ The forest is shrinking at such a rapid rate. ♪
♪ We must act soon let's hope it's not too late. ♪
Moved by Oroku's words, the raccoons ceased
fighting to have a look at the situation for themselves.
They were stunned.
The destruction stretch for miles.
The situation was far worse than they realized.
Don't you see this is madness.
This is not the time for us to be fighting each other.
In the 1960s, Japan was entering
golden age of economic growth,
and the demand for housing in and around Tokyo exploded.
Developers snapped up giant tracks of farm land
and forest, creating a maze of poorly planned suburbs.
Then in 1967 the government decided to build a
completely new suburb with maximum residential potential.
They called the development New Tama.
The suburb would house over 300,000
people in less than 12 square miles of land.
To do so, they needed to clear forests, level
mountains, demolish farms and fill in valleys.
It was the largest urban development project in history,
all to be built in the raccoons, Tama Hills.
Uh, clearly, we raccoons
underestimated these humans somehow.
In the past we had always thought
that humans were animals just like us.
But, you know, now we realized
that these guys were powerful.
Maybe as powerful as "the Gods."
In response to the situation, raccoons throughout the
region secretly gather at the abandoned Manpooku Temple,
which was hidden deep in the forests of Tama Hills.
A motion was made that Osho, the temple's 105 year
old resident raccoon be the chairman of the meeting.
The motion was approved unanimously.
So, due to the severity of the current situation,
we must forgo our natural
tendency to sleep during the day,
and be prepared to take action
whenever necessary, be it day or night.
Despite the fact that raccoons have
trouble taking anything seriously,
they manage to agree to stop the development.
The motion passes and today's meeting is adjourned.
The raccoons quickly disbanded leaving it to
the elders to formulate the course of action.
The elders adopted a five year
program with two objectives.
One: Research and monitored humans.
And two: Revive the ancient raccoon art of transformation.
Next they decided to bring in the masters of
transformation from Sado and Shikoku Islands.
Osho ask the elders, "Who will volunteer to go."
Although the plan was superb, the journey
was long and raccoons are notoriously lazy.
All the elders pretended to be asleep.
Well, let's wait for the young ones to
go up... then they can make the journey.
Hamburgers!
The hamburgers which were provided to facilitate
discussion were enthusiastically received.
The discussion however immediately concluded.
Pom!
The raccoons began step one of the
five year program the very next day.
Dad, the signs say no dumping.
The best way to research and monitor
humans they concluded was to watch TV.
The situated the television in the main hall of Manpooku
Temple which became the group's official headquarters.
Good evening.
The arrival of the television had an unexpected results.
Dozens of raccoons crowded into the temple, watched TV
all day, and lost all desire to accomplish anything else.
To learn to transform you must achieve
the highest degree of mental concentration.
So you can rearrange the very
order of your cells in an instant.
Lesser forms of transformation such as changing
color can be achieved by chameleon for example.
But the true art of transforming can own be
practice by foxes, raccoons and a few cats.
Gonta!
The fact that you were able to
change your appearance like that...
... means you've already mastered the
rudimentary techniques of transformation.
This is something all of you will be able to do.
If you pay attention and practice!
At least in theory.
To begin the lesson, I will do a demonstration.
Aren't you supposed to put a leaf on your head?
Leafs are only for amateurs.
Haven't done that in a while.
1, 2, 3, pom pom.
With Oroku guiding the way,
the raccoons made steady progress toward
their goal of reviving the art of transformation.
The students were eager and
enthusiastic, and some were quite talented.
Well done, Shoukichi!
I've been fascinated with humans
ever since I was a little cub.
I knew that according to raccoon
laws, I wasn't supposed to go near them.
But that just made me even more curious.
And my dad always encouraged me.
He said that, "Careful observation of humans
and their ways was the key to transforming,"
and getting near the humans was essential.
Over here!
My turn, catch!
Hey guys.
Keep it going.
Goal!
I guess that's why I'm a bit ahead of the curve today.
Unfortunately, not all the students were talented.
Some of them in fact were quite pathetic.
To become adept at transforming requires
technique and extreme physical and mental discipline.
Unlike foxes who are known for being
clever, raccoons are known for being lazy.
And those raccoons who weren't gifted
transformers were easily distracted.
Hey there!
Ponkichi!
♪ Disturbing to every sacred
high ground we can think of. ♪
♪ Some are this and some are that.. ♪
Back then, all I thought about was transforming.
I never dreamed that my friend Ponkichi
might just wanna be a normal raccoon.
♪ Some are this and some are that. ♪
One day at dusk, as the moon rose above the mountain.
A man went walking through a familiar mountain pass.
He noticed a pine tree which somehow
appeared different from what he had remember.
This distracted the man as very odd.
So, he said aloud, "There's never been a
branch on that side of the tree before."
And lo and behold the branch switched sides.
And then the man thought that look wrong too.
"That's not right there were
branches on both sides, I'm sure of it."
And sure enough another branch appeared.
Then all of a sudden there was a large crash.
What do you think had fallen out of the tree?
A raccoon!
That's right.
And why do you think he fell? Gonta.
He was a loser. I wouldn't have fallen.
Good answer, thank you, Gonta.
Sasuke, why do you think the raccoon fell from the tree?
He had to use both of his arms to make two branches.
Very good. And what lesson should
we learn from this story. Shoukichi?
That were overly accommodating
towards human. We're too eager to please.
That's right. We raccoons are to good-natured.
We shouldn't, … try so hard to please.
This is where we all go wrong. Do you understand?
Yes, master...
So, what do you do if you hear,
♪ Mr. Raccoon, Mr. Raccoon,
won't you sing with me somehow? ♪
♪ No we can't. We have to study now.  ♪
You see! All of you just fell for that.
Don't be so gullible.
The raccoons tried to stay focused on
researching humans and learning to transform.
But once winter had ended, the flowers and
trees were blossoming and love was in the air.
Recalling Oroku warning not to have any more cubs.
The raccoons decided to refrain from romance.
until their battle for Tama Hills was won.
It was left up to the females
to fend off the male's advances.
The females were remarkably successful.
Meanwhile, the New Tama development
project was picking up steam.
Forests were cleared the earth was leveled
and the construction zone grew bigger every day.
The raccoons watched with anger and
sadness as their forests were stripped bare.
♪ Hey there Post Man, what did you drop? ♪
Since the females were now free from the duty of raising
cubs, they too began to try their hand at transforming.
When the male's tried to transform into women or children,
the results were neither convincing nor pleasant.
But with the females participating, the males
followed their example and quickly improved.
Naturally the females soon wanted to
try their hand at transformed into men:
they experienced similar problems.
Oh, ah, I would like all the male's
to stay after class today please.
Osho decided it was time to let the
male raccoons in on a little secret.
Now then, notice this fine red
blanket we're all sitting on.
Want to know what it is?
My raccoon pouch.
It's 150 square feet and it retracts quite nicely. Watch.
Finally, it was time for the transforming
students to test their skills in the real world.
The exercise was conducted
like a driver's training lesson.
The students ventured into the streets of
Tokyo, while accompanied by advanced instructors...
who could help out in case of emergency.
Sasuke, Sasuke...
Get over here!
Sasuke...
Come on!
Transforming requires extraordinary amounts
of energy, especially when assuming human form.
The dark circles or masks commonly seen around
raccoons' eyes are the results are sheer fatigue.
Even the most experienced raccoons carry pick-me-ups so
they can replenish their strength at a moment's notice.
Even so, if their pick-me-up isn't fast acting enough,
out pops the fur, then the tail, and within
seconds the raccoon is back to his original form.
The recent rise in popularity
of fast acting energy drinks...
is almost entirely due to the
needs of transforming raccoons.
To graduate from basic training the
students had to pass one final test.
Each was required to go out into the world and
earn at least 10 dollars through honest labor.
Replacement.
Some raccoons work in teams and took
turns impersonating the same human.
Are you all right?
One raccoon posed as a monk and collected donations.
One female work in a bar but
spent all her money on energy drinks.
One raccoon hit the jackpot at the Pachinko Parlor.
One lazy raccoon broke into a donation
box but all he found were few pennies.
Rather than show up empty handed he transformed
a pile of leaves into a pile of dollar bills.
When I told you to go out into the world and
make some money I did not mean it literally.
Soon after finishing the test, Gonta
received an urgent report from home.
He raced through the forests to
witness the devastation for himself.
The construction had reached his childhood home.
Gonta went mad with grief.
He hurried back to headquarters and forced Osho
to call a meeting of the elders where he announced:
"Change of plans we began attacking the humans NOW!"
I am completely opposed to that.
Why is that?
It's way too soon.
We're still in the first year of our five-year plan.
We've all completed basic training.
Let's put our skills to work.
Oroku, what you think?
Are your transforming students ready for battle?
It's true they've mastered the basic techniques but...
But what?
They need practice.
Even the smallest mistake and
our secret will be discovered.
One question, Gonta.
I think that your anger over what happened to
your childhood home might be clouding your judgment.
No, my judgment is not clouded in the least.
This action will benefit all of you.
I guarantee it.
Of course, his judgment is clouded.
Don't forget, it wasn't long ago that Gonta
was trying to take over some of our territories.
Shut up! We raccoons from my part of
the woods will attack with or without you.
If Gonta's going to risk his
life then I'm going to help him.
Are you sure, Shoukichi?
Shoukichi, thank you.
So there!
You can stop us now. We're off to fight some humans.
Not so fast!
You can stop us!
Pay attention! I have one final
piece of advice to give to you.
If the humans catch you transforming, there is
a trick that you can use to protect our secret.
So, uh, what is it?
Pretend that you're a dead fox.
Summer, year 32 of the Pom Poko era,
with Gonta in charge 10 young raccoons
put their new transforming skills to work,
and executed a surprise attack against the humans.
The battle has finally begun.
Here they come!
Ready!
All right! This way! This way! This way!
Now!
We did it! Yay!
Disaster struck today, at the New Tama development site,
at approximately 2:30 in the afternoon, a
series of bizarre accidents killed three workers.
and destroyed a section of a residential
complex which was under construction.
Police suspect that the accidents were caused by
reduced visibility and soil erosion from heavy rains.
but the seriousness of the accidents and
the fact that they occurred simultaneously...
is causing local residents to express some concern.
many citizens believe there are fundamental
problems with the New Tama project.
and they requested that the development plan be reviewed.
Hold on everyone.
This isn't a time for celebration.
Three humans died because of us.
Shouldn't we be paying our respects to those
poor people who are victims of this operation.
Well, I have to agree with Osho.
Raccoons, we should have a moment of
silence for the unfortunate victims.
And then, right after that, we can celebrate.
All pray.
I'd like to say a prayer for
the victims of this operation.
We wish that we could save our
forests without harming any humans.
That was never our intention, but
our forest is near and dear to us...
We save our forest! We save our forest!
We saved our forests...
Hey, it's Gonta!
You are my hero!
Hey, you did it, Shoukichi.
Nice work Gonta! You youngsters have brought back
hope to this old heart of mine. Well done, son. Well done.
Well done? We're not done. That was just practice.
Raccoons, this war has just begun.
We will not stop attacking until we have battered...
pulverize, and squeezed to death...
every last human in Tama Hills.
Shoukichi, you should say something too.
And then we'll plant fruit trees.
And in a few years all have to do is eat fruit.
Let's slaughter some humans.
Kick out humans!
OK, OK will beat up some more humans, but
first we need to have a little victory celebration.
Yeah, but there's one thing I'm worried about.
What now?
Do we really wanna get rid of all of the humans.
Of course we do.
Can we just a few of them live
around here, like the old days.
No way! The world is crawling with humans, like roaches.
We need to destroy as many as we can.
I see your point, but you know
what? I can't stand humans either,
although some of them are not so
bad, but mostly I hate their guts.
It's just that...
What, Ponkichi?
It's just that, if we get rid
of all the humans then that means:
we'll never eat tempura again.
Or beef jerky.
Or popcorn.
Hamburgers, Doughnuts, potato chips...
pepperoni pizza...
chicken wings!
Oh, I can taste it.
Hum, so then, do you think it would be all
right if we kept a few humans around, Gonta?
We have no choice.
A good decision by Gonta yet again!
♪ Shine, shine, shine on Gonta. ♪
♪ Pom pom-pom pom pom pom-pom-pom. ♪
♪ You show the world what we can do. ♪
♪ Why don't we tell you too. ♪
♪ All the kids are cheering for you. ♪
♪ That's the truth: we adore you. ♪
♪ Hail to Gonta ♪
Nevertheless, a government spokesman stressed that
the people of Tokyo are in such desperate need of...
living accommodations that the New Tama
development project will not be delayed,
despite today's tragic accidents.
It was needles to say an unfortunate accident.
Gonta, the mastermind behind the
dangerous attacks against the humans...
now suffered multiple fractured and internal
injuries that would take nearly a year to heal.
The situation plunged the raccoons into depression.
But the raccoons soon realized their
attack had not been a complete waste.
Some of the human who sold their land to the
New Tama developers were highly superstitious.
I think it was a bad idea to move those
shrines just to make way for more housing.
Can you elaborate?
All those accidents. Maybe the
spirits were exacting their revenge.
Weren't there many sacred objects
moved to make way for New Tama.
Yes, there were dozens of them. That's what worries me.
I asked the developers to hold the
proper ceremonies before moving them but...
And what are your thoughts about the situation, professor?
Your basic spirit or deity is generally
associated with a certain location.
If someone moves that spirit's shrine or statue,
this spirit will become extremely agitated
and wreak havoc on those responsible.
I'm sure if this is just the beginning of your problems.
Maybe we can save Tama Hills after all.
Shoukichi immediately led the raccoons back into action.
A man with land for sale in the section of Tama
Hills tour his property with two New Tama developers.
To the landowner's surprise, he saw far more
sacred statues on his land than he remembered.
He told the developers, "I better give this more thought".
And he postponed signing the contract to sell his land.
Meanwhile, in another section of Tama Hills,
a priest was holding a ceremony
at the Shrine of the White Fox,
which was slated to be moved.
Look!
A raccoon appeared on the roof
disguised as the white fox himself.
The fox's eerie cry so overwhelmed
the ceremony participants...
that the relocation proceedings
were brought to an immediate halt.
The witnesses to the event bowed down to the fox
and vowed that its shrine would be left where it was.
The raccoons were on a roll.
The raccoons played tricks on trespassers all
over the forests, each trying to outdo the other.
Go away.
Put that away.
Take it away!
Pick up that tempura. You don't want to be a litter bug.
Huh, tempura.
Leave it here.
Uh, is everything okay here, miss?
Miss, what happened?
I have no face.
Help! Somebody help!
I-I-I just saw a...
A murder?
N-N-No.
It was a…!
Not a murderer?
Well, that's too bad.
T-T-There was a woman.
Was she a vampire?
No no, she look like... aah...
Was it something like this?
Did she look something like this?
The raccoons took great pleasure
in frightening the humans,
and because raccoons have a weakness for throwing parties,
every time they scare a human, they had to celebrate.
Gonta however, saw no reason to celebrate.
Although his wife did all she
could to nurse him back to health,
she could not soothe Gonta's
frustration for being out of the fight.
Furthermore, Gonta thought his
fellow raccoons were acting like wimps.
So, did either of you watch the news yesterday.
They ran a piece entitled New Tama ghost town,
featuring an interview with the policeman we scared.
But the news crew started laughing
so hard that the police man ran off.
It was a...
What good did it do?!?
You idiots! You think that will stop the developers?
Don't just frighten them!
We need to hurt them!
Inflict some serious pain!
Not again!
Just as Gonta predicted, the development did not stop.
Rivers were paved with concrete.
Forest trails became cement roads.
Massive amounts of building materials were trucked in,
and the construction of thousands
of New Tama Apartments got underway.
The raccoons pranks however had not been forgotten.
Tabloids and talk shows continued
to give nationwide coverage...
to the strange occurrences at the construction sites.
The raccoons became more and
more confident of ultimate victory.
Autumn, year 32 of the Pom Poko era.
by waving of a enthusiastic game of rock paper scissors,
the raccoons chose two representatives to seek out
and the world's most advanced Transformation Masters.
The young and dashing Tamasaburou was
chosen to travel to the Island of Shikoku,
while the husky and robust Bunta was
chosen to travel to the Island of Sado.
So, on the night of the next full moon
the two raccoons said their farewells and
set off on their long and dangerous journeys.
What's that smell?
While they waited for Bunta and Tamasaburou to return,
the raccoons continued haunting the construction sites.
The raccoons seem to enjoy using their transforming skills
whether it helped prevent the New Tama development or not.
Out with demons!
Daddy!
I'm starting to get nervous.
What if our little pranks aren't doing any good at all.
What if the humans level the entire
forest, then where are we going to go?
Maybe Gonta's right. The only
way to stop them is to get violent.
I don't want to have to hurt anymore
humans. It just doesn't seem right to me.
But what they won't stop. Then what. To be or not to be.
Kiyo?
What's going on? Are you okay?
Is something wrong with your neck?
I was posing.
I was hoping you'd tell me that I looked pretty.
Oh, sorry.
Ow, now something is wrong with my neck.
Well, you looked pretty.
No. Too late.
But I mean it.
OK, but I could use some practice.
Everyone loves that song, don't they?
It's stupid, but I kinda like it too.
Hey, do you like the hunter song?
It's, pretty good.
My dad used to…
♪ There once was a hunter who shot a big raccoon. ♪
♪ He fried him up and ate him... ♪
Did you know a hunter shot my grandfather?
Sorry, I didn't know.
It's okay. My grandfather wasn't fried up and eaten.
The hunter sold his pelt for a whole lot of money.
Well, you got beautiful fur too.
Really!
It's so nice of you to say that.
So, what about the hunter's song?
Oh, my dad used to sing it to me, when I was just a cub.
Sounds like your father was kinda strange.
He'd sing:
♪ "Fried him up and ate him" ♪ really loudly.
And then he'd give me a lecture.
About what?
He'd say, "Did you hear that, son?"
"Even in children's nursery rhymes."
"Humans sing about how they love to shoot us."
"And then fry us up."
"Humans are sick cruel heartless beast
and don't you forget it, Shoukichi."
Hey, wanna play ball with me?
Oh, sure. Right now?
Here, I'll make one.
Hey, let me try that.
♪ Mr. Eike, where you from?
Higo, sir. Higo, that is where? ♪
♪ Kumamoto, sir. Kumamoto, that is where? Senba, sir. ♪
♪ A raccoon came from Senba and he wandered into town. ♪
♪ Along came a... ♪
When are you going to do that plan you were talking about?
The Operation Twin Star?
I don't think I'm going to do it anymore.
Why not? That was such a wonderful idea.
Why don't we do it? Just you and me.
Are you serious?
Yeah. Don't you think I can do it?
No it's not that. It's just...
that I...
Come on Shoukichi, I'm dying to do something.
Then lets do it. I think that you and
I can be really frightening together.
How sweet.
Hello?
Well, look what we have here.
What can we do for you girls?
Where is our home? We just got back from
our trip to the stars and our home's gone.
A trip to the stars?
We travel from the red-eye of the Scorpion...
to the swollen Cygnus’s great wings.
around the coils of Hydra the Water Snake...
to the forehead of the Little Bear Cub.
And we sprinkle each day with dew
and frost as we journey among stars.
Hey, what the heck is wrong with you...
We're cold and we wanna go home.
Mister, do you know what happened to our home?
Not-not me!...
I-I-I don't know anything about your home.
Don't look at me! Come on, get out of here!
We should call the police. Let them deal with it.
What are you doing?
Now you get off of there!
Come on come down!
T-T-They must be spirits.
What do you mean spirits?
Please, please spirits don't be angry!
W-we didn't mean to destroy your home!
Ah, come on. Hold on a minute. You
wanna raise? We can work something out.
Come on guys, wait!
Look I don't care how much you
pay me. I'm getting out of here!
I've never seen anything that creepy in my life.
Hands down.
Don’t do this to me. Please.
People warned me that Tokyo was a scary
place, but this is way too scary for me.
And if you know what is best for
you, you’ll get out of here too.
Hey, come on, you guys...
Someone or something doesn’t want this project to happen.
Surprisingly the racoons decided to celebrate.
The evening celebration was especially grand in honor of
the spectacular performances by both Kiyo and Shoukichi.
Way to go!
That night for the first time in weeks the
construction workers barracks were dark and silent.
But the next morning...
There seemed to be and endless supply of humans.
No matter how many the racoons got rid of,
more showed up to take their place.
Now some of your employees have suggested that
these incidents are the work of foxes or raccoons.
What I'd give for that to be true.
We could just skip the criminal
investigation and put out a few animal traps.
The raccoons feared the humans
were catching on to their secret.
You must admit the similarities between
these events and the old folk tales are uncanny.
How would you explain these similarities?
That's easy. Who's ever making up these stories
isn't even clever enough to come up with something new.
We did not make anything up! We saw it with our own eyes!
Fine, you win.
Yeah, little racoons and foxes from old folks
tales are responsible for all these incidents.
As soon as you catch one in the act,
you give us a holler. We'll exterminate it for ya'.
That is... if it doesn’t just transform away.
Shoukichi began to worry, whether using their
transforming skills was the right thing to do.
He was not the only one.
As you all know, there was a
time a few hundred years ago...
when transforming was openly performed by racoons.
It was a highly respected art form,
and was a popular subject for
the artist and writer of the time.
But unfortunately we racoons went to far.
We were to conspicuous with our skills.
And we aroused the resentment of humans.
Since then, we’ve been hunted for our pelts and our
fur has been used to make paint brushes and tooth brushes.
This is how the humans exacted their vengeance.
And remember the last few decades
have been very peaceful for us,
because we've shown restraint with our transforming.
When humans see racoons these
days they generally just ignore us.
This was not always the case.
The ability to transform is a double-edged sword.
So, be sure to use your sword with discretion.
We can not afford to evoke the
hatred of the humans yet again.
Following Oroku's lecture,
the young racoons' spirits were dashed.
Furthermore, autumn was now upon them.
A time of year when racoons need to find plenty of food,
so they can store ample fat and grow
long fluffy coats for the coming winter.
The young racoons focused their attention and there
transforming skills on finding as much food as possible.
Now more than ever they needed the advice of experts.
They were desperate for the
masters from the islands to arrive.
Then finally one day, an unfamiliar
raccoon arrived in Tama Hills.
Hey it's okay, I'm a raccoon too.
Thank you.
You seem to be quite exhausted.
How far did you say you have traveled?
From Fujino Woods.
Oh, is that on Shikoku Island or Sado?
Uh... neither. It's just on
the other side of the mountains.
Huh, what do you mean?
Aren’t you a Transformation Master?
Transformation Master? Oh no. I’m
sorry, you were expecting someone else?
That's okay well just have to wait a little bit longer.
Right, not your fault that all.
So, what brought you to Tama Hills then?
I was trying to find out:
who in the world keeps dumping dirt into
our drinking water and on top of our homes?
Truckloads of dirt which had been
excavated at the New Tama construction site,
were being illegally dump all over the Fujino woods.
The dirt polluted the streams and cause
frequent landslides, which devastated the forest.
The animals of Fujino Woods knew something had to be done.
To find out where all the dirt was
coming from, they decided to send a raccoon.
The raccoon disguised himself as a
human, snuck aboard one of the dump trucks,
which was responsible for the illegal dumping.
Unfortunately, he was not skilled
at the art of transformation.
The swaying of the truck and the stress of the journey so
exhausted him that he was unable to maintain human form.
It's not just Fujino that's in
trouble. It's other woods too.
And now there are garbage dumps
and golf courses all over the place.
First, the developers dig up
Tama Hills and cause us to suffer...
then they dump the dirt on Fujino
Woods and cause you to suffer as well.
The insanity just never ends.
Yeah, I was shocked when the dump truck brought me here.
I just assumed all the dirt was coming from some
enormous construction site in the middle of Tokyo.
But we were in the countryside here.
I'd never dream they'd dig one
forest so they could dump it on another.
Why would the humans do such a thing?
So, if we find a way to stop the New Tama construction,
we'll be saving all the raccoons in the
Fujino Woods as well as the Tama Hills.
You think it's possible to stop the construction?
All of you here are so accomplished
at the art of transformation.
I bet with your impressive skills,
you could easily stop the development.
It'll be a piece of cake.
It's not that simple.
We've tried everything we could think of.
If only Bunta and Tamasaburou would
return with the Transformation Masters,
I wonder why we haven't heard from them?
Soon winter was upon them,
but there was still no word from Tamasaburou,
Bunta or the Masters of Transformation.
Food was scarce and the raccoons needed
to use all their energy for foraging.
Therefore, they were unable to continue transforming.
And all the work they did, haunting
the construction sites was soon forgotten.
The media quickly moved on to the
usual celebrity and political scandals.
♪ Snow, snow, snow's falling down. ♪
♪ Snow's falling down but we'll still come. ♪
♪ We'll breathe. Candies and ice
cream must be covering the ground. ♪
♪ Now just pass the fudge and caramel.
Pom, pom, pom, pom, pom. Pom, pom. ♪
New year day, year 33 of the Pom Poko era,
all of Tama Hills was covered with a blanket of snow.
And most of the construction workers
had already returned to their hometowns,
and were enjoined the holidays with their families.
Push!
Wait for us!
We'll help.
Hey, that's our rig.
What's going on?
What?
Oh no!
In what world... raccoons?
♪ We smashed your tractor. Now you're cold and cold ♪
♪ But you made our home a construction zone. ♪
♪ If you don't want to be so accident prone. ♪
♪ Keep off our forests and will leave you alone. ♪
Hey, don't point the finger at us.
The raccoons did it. We all saw it with our own eyes.
So get off our backs.
Nevertheless, police still suspect
these workers were responsible.
And that they were inspired by the numerous pranks
which occurred at this construction site last fall.
Police are searching the area for footprints.
But the snow around the crime scene has already melted.
Why in the world could do that, Shoukichi?
I don't think there was anything wrong with what we did.
You should have done more than that.
No. Shoukichi was just trying to encourage the
raccoons who can't transform by letting them help out.
Should we be worried, Osho?
I think we'll be okay this time.
It was just as Osho predicted.
No one believed that the raccoons
were responsible for the incident.
Rather, most believe that the
construction workers were guilty.
Due to lack of evidence however, the men were released.
To this day, the case remains unsolved.
Soon, it was springtime.
And love was in the air once again.
After refraining from romance for an entire year the
raccoons were unable to control themselves any longer.
The air was filled with the sounds of
lovers' quarrels, and sweet nothings,
and the raccoons courted each other
until even the skies turned rosy.
Hey, wait up!
Wait for me!
Come on Gonta, you gotta catch me.
Don't tease me! Hanako!
Wait!
As soon as it's springtime everybody goes crazy.
All of a sudden they wanna get married and have families.
Nobody seems to remember Oroku's warning
that we're not supposed to have any cubs.
The second the sun hits their fur they fall in love.
But not us, you don't see us chasing
after each other like we're lunatics.
We can handle not getting married,
and not having cubs, don't you think?
Of course we can.
I'm so pleased. It's just what I'd hoped you'd say.
You're, wonderful!
Yeah, we can hold off. I don't need
to kiss or cuddle or rub noses or…
Oh, Shoukichi!
That was a mistake…
Kiyo and Shoukichi were soon married and
had 4 charming raccoon cubs within the year.
During the previous Autumn,
Tamasaburou had managed yo reach the Island
of Shikoku despite a long and difficult journey.
As soon as he arrived he presented his request for help
to Kinchou the VI, one of the Masters of transformation.
But then he collapsed and was gravely ill for many weeks.
Luckily, Kinchou had a daughter, Koharu,
who stayed at Tamasaburou bedside and
miraculously nursed him back to health.
With the coming of spring the bond
between the two young raccoons deepened.
And Koharu soon bore Tamasaburou three cubs.
Inside the shrine, the elders of Shikoku Island
held a meeting to discuss the situation in Tama Hills.
They all agreed that putting a
stop to the New Tama project...
would send a much needed message of hope to
raccoons in similar situations all over the country.
But the elders were divided as
to who should go to Tama Hills,
who should stay behind to govern Shikoku Island,
and if any of the masters died while on
this dangerous mission who should replace them.
Even after months and months of discussions,
they were unable to reach a consensus.
Father the elders never stop talking.
They should get outside.
It's such a beautiful day.
I can't believe that they've been
debating for over six months now.
I'm beginning to wonder if
they'll ever come to a decision.
I hope they never decide what to do.
Tamasaburou…
I beg you, don't go back to Tama
Hills with the Transformation Masters.
The thought of you being so far
away from me and the children...
I can't stand it!
It breaks my heart!
Ah, darling. I too wish we could stay together forever.
But you must understand…
No we don't understand.
Why can't you stay here with me.
The Masters can make it to Tama without you...
I'll talk to father and the elders.
Why don't you stay behind and be father's successor?
While Tamasaburou struggled to decide
whether or not leave Shikoku Island,
Bunta roamed the fields and mountains of Sado Island,
searching for the islands Master of Transformation.
Oddly, not a single raccoon on the island
knew the whereabouts of the renowned master.
Back in Tama Hills the raccoons
were facing some serious problems.
Their woods were continuing to
shrink due to the New Tama development.
The recent baby boom doubled the
number of mouths they had to feed.
And poor summer weather brought
about a serious food shortage.
The chestnut and persimmon trees on witch they always
relied provided nowhere near enough food to go around.
Having no where else to turn, the raccoons with
transforming skills went in search of human food.
Despite all their efforts, they were still unable to
collect enough food to sustain the raccoon community.
Finally, even raccoons who couldn't
transform began scavenging around human homes,
desperate to find anything to feed their cubs.
Inevitably, many raccoons lost their
lives on the roads and in animal traps.
I can't take this anymore!
We got to stand up to the humans now!
Even if it cost us our lives!
Right, Shoukichi?
Wait a minute… have you healed yet, Gonta?
Of course I have! Watch this!
You're better than ever.
Hey, we should have a party and celebrate.
There's no time for a party. It's time to attack!
Hold on, Gonta. I think that we should wait for...
the Transformation Masters to
arrive before we plan another attack.
What is wrong with you, Shoukichi?
You're too young to be such a big coward.
You're wrong, we can't underestimate the humans.
If we attacked them head on they will destroy us.
We have waited long enough!
Calm down, give Shoukichi a chance to speak.
I propose we adopt three policies
while we wait for the masters.
One: Have the raccoons that can
transform go to the city and gathered food.
Then we'll all share the food equally.
Two: Train every one in traffic safety.
Yeah!
Three: Organize rescue squads to
free any raccoons caught in traps.
That's it.
Shoukichi, you sound like a human.
Are you sure you're ready a raccoon?
Yes! And don't you ever doubt it!
Well then, assuming will work out all the
details later I think we should take a vote.
All those who agree with Shoukichi's proposal…
Stick 'em up!
Agreed!
What kind of nonsense is this, Gonta?
Shut up! It's for real.
Anybody who dares to oppose me from
now on will be killed by my private guard!
Got it?
Yeah!
You need to think about what you're saying, Gonta.
You'll address him as sir Gonta!
Raccoons! We all know the humans are dangerous!
But if we attack without concern
for ourselves, we will win.
As the old saying goes,
"When a mouse is cornered he will bite a cat!"
He's a mouse?
He's not a mouse.
He means that if we're desperate
enough we can beat anyone.
That's right. When a mouse is cornered
he can find the strength to defeat a cat!
That's what I said.
But we're not mice though.
Why would we want to beat up a cat, you know?
I'm starved. Sure would like to
have a mouse to eat right about now.
A good mouse tempura can't be beat.
Not true. Plain deep fried is better.
I don't know, I think the tempura
batter is what really makes it.
The thought of the crispy tail makes my mouth watered.
What is the matter with all of you?!?
I say that:
♪ That mouse tempura is the best. Oh yes it is. ♪
See, Gonta. We can't fight.
all we can think about is food.
I think it's best if we wait for
the Transformation Masters to get here.
Sorry about that.
If only we could have held off on having more cubs.
But nobody wanted to listen.
I guess it was too much to expect from every one.
You're wrong!
Instead of reducing our ranks we
should be reducing the number of humans!
The forests where we used to live
are now occupied by swarms of humans!
They're the ones who are the intruders!
We should kick them out!
Kick out the humans!
Kick the humans out!
Kill them all!!!
Little did they know, at that very moment…
Hey, taxi!
Hey, look!
Oh my goodness!
I'll go tell everyone you're here.
Tamasaburou!
The Masters from Shikoku Island are here!
You did it, Tamasaburou!
Raccoons, on our way here we witness the
devastation that is occurring in your forest.
We feel your pain.
Call all the raccoons in the area, we will hold a
meeting tonight to address this problem immediately.
Autumn, year 33rd of the Pom Poko era,
the masters had finally arrived.
The raccoons gathered to greet them. Their hope restored.
I am pleased to see such a fine moon out tonight.
Fellow raccoons, I am Hage of Shikoku Island.
In a few days I will be 999 years old.
Raccoons, why is Tama Hills ravaged by
development while our island is nearly untouched,
That's because we raccoons of Shikoku never
stop haunting our forests and our mountains.
Therefore, the humans on our island are
well aware that disaster will befall them,
whenever they dare to enter our territory.
In fact, Master's Kinchou, Hage, and
myself, are so good at frightened humans.
The various forms the three of us take are
worshiped in shrines and temples all over the island.
My name is Gyobu and I have led the
raccoons of our island to peace and prosperity.
I can lead you there, as well.
Allow me to formally introduce myself as well.
I'm the Kinchou the VI.
In order to frightened every
last human being out of Tama Hills.
Voilà!
We've decided to execute Operation Specter, our
plan which relies on our mastery of transformation.
This plan requires extreme amounts of mental energy,
so much energy, in fact, that any
one of the three of us may not survive.
But my fellow raccoons, we the Masters
of Shikoku are willing to take this risk.
If we all combine all our efforts at successfully
carry out this plan, the humans will be so frightened,
they will never set foot in Tama Hills again.
Yeah!
And then…
once the human beings are fully primed with fear
we'll be able to stop their infernal development...
of destruction of the forests once and for all.
Mark my words we will prevail.
We have brought you a boat, a
boat that will swiftly ferry...
the raccoons of Tama Hills back to an era of greatness.
Fellow raccoons, we promise you
we are now in this boat together!
What a spectacular moon.
There is nothing better than moonlight.
Let us all bow our heads and
pray to this gorgeous full moon...
that Operation Spector will be
safe, sound and extremely successful.
The Masters immediately began a special training
regimen to prepare the raccoons for Operation Spector.
Congratulations on your 999th birthday Master Hage!
Thank you, everyone. Thank you.
Thank you.
Master, will you reenact the tail
of the young samurai who shot the fan.
Ah, I'll need some help.
Yes, today's the day.
Winter, year 33 of the Pom Poko era,
after months of preparation the day
for Operation Specter had finally arrived.
The winds were calm, the skies partially
cloudy, temperature 55°, humidity 65%,
perfect transforming weather.
♪ Pom ♪
♪ pom ♪
Raccoons have always been able to transform
themselves into simple ghosts and goblins forms.
For Operation Specter to be successful,
the raccoons had to become much more advanced.
The Masters taught them to
utilize not only their own energy.
But also the energy of the world around
them in fire, earth, water, and air.
The training was so physically taxing
and intense its nearly beyond description.
All the raccoons participated,
whether they could transform or not.
And together they generated and
focus phenomenal quantities of power.
That night, the fighting spirit of
the raccoons was greater than ever.
In fact their enthusiasm was so boundless...
they began transforming into a parade of frightening
specters long before they reached the human city.
♪ Pom ♪
♪ pom ♪
Hey, look at that?
What is that?
Make the trees bloom with flowers!
Hey, what's going on?
What's going on?
Let the trees bloom with flowers!
Look!
Hey mom, we're missing the monster parade!
Honey, wait.
I used to see stuff like that too when I was a kid.
You know, monsters in the closet. That kind of thing.
You know when you're young they seem so, so real.
I swear I saw these ghosts dancin' on my ceiling.
Just have another drink you'll see them again.
Isn't that weird? Now where do you think you see that?
Do you think ghost really exist?
Huh? Don't be stupid.
It's your brain playing tricks.
It must be… your brain plays
tricks on you when you're young.
Things like the bogeyman and monsters in the closet.
They're all in your head because of…
all the scary stories people tell you as a kid.
It plants the seeds in your brain.
So, as a kid you think it's real.
Kids are suckers because there's
no way those ghost stories are real.
Still… they frighten you have to death.
Yup.
The brain is scary that way. You think
things and then you see them whether real or not.
You ima... imagination.
There really are monsters out there.
See, we talk about ghost and you start to see em.
Hi, dear.
Honey!
FIRE BURNING BRIGHTLY!
WATER FLOWING SWIFTLY!
The trees!
Master Gyobu!
He's gone.
That was unreal!
I've never seen anything like that my whole life!
Aw, is it over already?
That was really great wasn't it mom.
Yeah.
Alright bedtime, let's get inside.
Kay.
Hey, don't forget to brush your teeth okay?
Kay, mom.
That was amazing. I feel like I just woke up from a dream.
I know. What in the world you think that was anyway.
I don't know.
Maybe they were UFOs.
Some things you just can't explain.
Long ago when various raccoon families
were feuding on the Island of Shikoku,
Yoko Labelle then allied himself with the enemy.
His betrayal led to the downfall of his clan.
Yoko so profoundly regretted his actions that he took
a solemn vow to devote his life to further injustice.
We must ensure that his sacrifice
to this cause was not in vain.
We must continue his noble quest for justice.
And we must vow that we will keep
fighting until our day of victory.
♪ Praise to Gyobu. ♪
♪ Before he got here our lives were a mess. ♪
♪ But Operation Specter was a big success. ♪
The raccoons were so convinced of their success that even
the ones on monitor duty pay no attention to the news.
Big success. Big success. Big success.
The videotape is completely blank.
I have no idea what happened.
It came through this crack and then
it flew around the kitchen ceiling.
It was terrifying.
I swear, there's no way someone could have stage that.
Uh yeah, something strange is
definitely going on in New Tama.
I'd like to move out but I just can afford to.
Tune in at midnight tonight for a special program,
which will cover this evening's
bizarre events in greater detail.
The more the humans investigate Operation Specter...
the more they'll be forced to
admit that what they experienced...
was not their imagination, a dream, or
a hallucination, but irrefutable fact.
Then they'll turn to science and
technology and their fancy machines.
When that fails to solve this mystery,
the humans will finally be humbled.
And now since they've witnessed something
they can't explain no matter how hard they try,
they will be forced to realize that humans are
not the only worthy form of life in the universe.
Raccoons, the changes may take
time but why wait to celebrate.
It's time to party.
Come on, it's time to sing and
drink and dance until alights out, yes.
♪ We're dancing, we're dancing.
Master Hage Hage Hage Hage. ♪
The next day however, events took an unexpected turn.
It appears that the massive parades staged yesterday...
in a recently constructed portion of the New Tama
residential complex was a publicity stunt for Wonderland,
a theme park now under construction in the area.
Police say the responsible party will be
fined for staging a parade without a permit.
You're kidding!
However, residents of the New
Tama complex remain convinced...
that what they saw yesterday could
not have been a publicity stunt.
That's more like it!
The president of Wonderland admitted that last
night's parade was an unauthorized promotional event.
It was not!
Let me uh... apologize for any inconvenience.
you might have had from our little parade.
Who is that guy?
Our intention here at Wonderland Theme
Park was just to let the community know...
how wonderful our wonderful Wonderland Theme Park will be.
So, we thought the best way... was to...
give the public a taste of Wonderland for free.
As the park's president, I take
full responsibility for the decision...
to stage this unauthorized but
truly spectacular event for free.
Liar!
We've received an overwhelmingly
positive response to our parade.
Yeah the public's enthusiasm
quite frankly was astonishing.
Because of this, I must admit I do not regret
my decision to hold this parade in the least.
I'll have you know, that even
if I have to go to jail for this,
I believe that your positive reaction was worth it.
Is this for real?
He's stealing credit for all of our hard work!
I believe that your positive...
You liar!
The news sent the raccoons into a state of panic.
Meanwhile, at Wonderland headquarters,
the president was desperately searching
for those responsible for the parade.
No way, are you nuts? We can't back down now!
Just find out who put on that parade?
And then, hire them all!
Yeah! Throw as much money as you can at them.
Pay them whatever they want!
What if raccoons are the ones that did it?
What you mean raccoons!
I don't care if it was raccoons or penguins or gopher's.
You go find them and get them working exclusively for me!
Uh, wait a minute… why did I say raccoons?
Oh I'm sure you're just joking.
Where'd you come from?
Who are you? You're not supposed to be in here!
Don't worry, your assistant let me in.
I'm Ryutarou. I called you earlier remember?
I am the only one who could possibly lead you to
the ones responsible for that spectacular parade.
But I require my fair share of the business.
Forget it! How about a million dollars.
While Ryutarou negotiated highly
lucrative terms for his partnership,
the raccoons were dumbfounded.
This bizarre human had completely stolen their thunder.
And at first they railed against the unfairness of it all.
But soon the sheer hopelessness of their
situation began to sap their will to fight.
Meanwhile, with no footage of Operation Spector,
media coverage quickly petered out and the
public soon lost interest in the whole affair.
You're a fox, isn't that right?
You have a good eye.
Indeed, I am a transforming fox.
I am Ryutarou, at your service.
I am honored to meet such a world
renown raccoon as yourself Master Kinchou.
I've heard much about you.
I am nothing more than a sixth in a long line.
So, what business brings you
all the way out to our forest?
I wanted to congratulate you on
the fabulous parade you staged.
You knew we were behind it. Did you?
Of course. And I give you my condolences
for Wonderland stealing all the credit.
Thank you.
Of course, as a fox you would
understand that it was raccoons.
I wasn't surprised by what happened
after the parade, Master Kinchou.
How's that?
Ryutarou was, needless to say, as sly as a fox.
He and his silver tongue lured Kinchou
into one of the swankiest clubs in Tokyo.
Welcome.
Now don't you worry all the girls here are foxes too.
What's the problem? Don't you like them this way?
Were you rather they were foxes?
Or perhaps you prefer they were raccoons...
I'll get right to the point then.
There's no future for the raccoons of Tama Hills.
They'll die off soon. Just like the foxes.
So, that's what happened to all the foxes.
Yes, I'm afraid so.
Except for those of us with transforming skills.
We have learned to survive by
living among humans like this.
As humans?
It's the only way to survive
if you plan on living near Tokyo.
And that is why I wanted to meet with you today.
To invite you raccoons to live the same way as we do here.
Now hold on a minute!
I know we may sound a little strange
but allow me to complete the picture.
You won't be living like ordinary
humans. You'll be filthy rich.
You'll be extremely well fed.
And you will be working in the luxurious
environment of Wonderland Theme Park...
with your fellow transforming raccoons.
You're insane! Do you think we'd work for
those liars who stole credit for our work!
Let's not get upset.
It's a fact that it's time for you to live as humans.
But here's the problem.
♪ The human world requires wealth and greed, ♪
♪ so how will you make the money you need? ♪
♪ You use the skill you have and you will succeed. ♪
And where do you think you can
earn the most money for your skills?
I'm afraid that would be your
great enemy, Wonderland Theme Park.
They tell me that you'll get benefits too.
Let me just show you the amount of your monthly salary.
And of course I will be the only one who
knows you as raccoons. It'll be our little secret.
So, how about a little snack?
It's not good to make big decisions on an empty stomach.
I've heard such fabulous things
about the food on Shikoku Island.
It must be hard on you, eating the
measly scraps you can find at Tama Hills.
That's not important to me.
I'm concerned about this.
The raccoons who can transform can live as humans,
but what happens to the raccoons who can't transform?
Those who can't transform will
have to fend for themselves.
It's sad but only the fittest can survive
in order for the species to continue.
We foxes were also forced to
abandon those who couldn't transform.
So, they all died.
Yes. We had no other choice.
Ah! It's not fair!
Look on the bright side, you raccoons
unlike us foxes can eat just about anything.
Those who can transform might do all right.
Meanwhile, the elders gathered at the temple to consider
what might be done to improve their depressing situation.
We'll ferry you back to an era of greatness.
We were idiots to think those old geezers
could help us out in the first place.
Mmm, reminds me of the saying,...
"Don't sell the pelt till you caught the raccoon."
Now, no one could have anticipated
the outcome of Operation Spector.
You shouldn't blame the masters for what happened.
Why don't humans respect us?
They never say "Sly as a raccoon."
They all say "Sly as a fox."
Isn't that weird?
You're worried about stupid
human sayings at a time like this?!?
No, Gonta, I'm just saying that
we need to study the humans a bit.
Shut up! It's Time To Challenge All
The Humans To A Fight To The Death!
Control yourself, Gonta!
It seems to me that we raccoons have finally
come to a point where we've absolutely no choice.
We must reveal to the humans that we
were the ones who stage Operation Spector.
Have you lost your mind, Osho?
We can't let the human know. That's
an ironclad rule. You know that.
She's a right, Osho, if the humans find
out about our transformation abilities,
they'll never stop hunting us down.
Yes but, it's just not fair.
Somebody else got the recognition
for our spectacular masterpiece!
I just can't take it, I wanna scream! We Raccoons Did It!
Osho, what could we do to convince
the humans that we were responsible?
We would need to get the message out to the whole world.
We can write to the television stations or the newspapers.
Yeah but, the humans were just think
that it was somebody playing another prank.
Then one of us could go on TV and prove it to them.
Ah, give me a break. It's like Operation Spector.
They'll think it's staged and we'll be exploited again.
See, were just wasting time.
Gonta was right.
The debate dragged on until morning
and still they didn't have a solution.
See, just wasting time.
But if we run out into the world and start attacking
the humans, they're going to turn on us and wipe us out.
We won't let them know it was us.
How many times do I have to tell you.
Something that's small won't be effective.
Oroku's right the only answer is to do something big.
I think that we need to regroup and
launch another even bigger Operation Spector.
What makes you so sure things won't
turn out just like last time, Shoukichi.
Because, all of us have experienced now.
We can do it even better.
Huh, you are just stalling because you're afraid to fight.
If I didn't know better, I'd think you are a little girl.
Don't make fun of girls, Gonta.
I'll show you how girls fight.
All I meant was that if he were
a girl he'd be the sissy kind.
Yeah well, this sissy is gonna start
getting ready for Operation Specter Part II.
By yourself? No one gonna listen to you.
What! You think they'll follow you?
Shut up you!
Hey, break it up!
Listen everyone…
I have a proposition. Please take a seat.
All we have to do is use our transformation
skills the same way we did for Operation Specter.
Operation Specter clearly overwhelmed
the humans and won their admiration.
So much so indeed that a human being is
tried to claim responsibility for our great work!
So, how could we possibly benefit from this?
How can you make an egg a stand on end?
Sound impossible?
This is how Columbus did it.
So that's it!
He must have a very clever solution.
The solution is, from this day
forward we'll be living as human beings.
That's stupid.
Now hold on. You should all take a moment to consider it.
Yeah but, what about the ones who can't transform?
This is stupid.
From the Tama Hills Raccoons.
The raccoons were incensed by Kinchou's proposal. Without
Osho, things quickly fell apart and the meeting adjourned.
For months now Operation Spector had
taken precedence over preparing for winter.
The raccoons scrambled to find food for their families.
But Gonta spent his time rounding up raccoons
who wanted to participate in guerrilla warfare.
Master Hage rounded up the raccoons who couldn't
transform and started a Buddhist dancing cult.
At 999, the raccoon had finally gone senile.
♪ I'll have to make a boat and sail to heaven instead. ♪
♪ If you would like to join me just jump in my boat. ♪
♪ Come sail us to Nirvana
with my Buddhist chanting tout. ♪
Well, that's a depressing sight.
Hage has been mentally sound for all these years,
and he spends a few months in Tokyo
and he's completely lost his mind.
Tokyo is a strange place, Tamasaburou.
I don't understand the people here at all.
If we were to have executed Operation Specter on
Shikoku Island it would have worked beautifully.
Offerings at our temple would have tripled.
Master Kinchou, please take me back with you to
Shikoku Island and train me to following your footsteps.
There's nothing that would value more.
I see. Tamasaburou?
Yes?
Do you honestly wish to become my successor?
Yes, Master Kinchou.
I've been hoping you would say that.
However, you must assure me...
that you're not making a selfish decision,
and abandoning your fellow raccoons
just to get back to my daughter.
Are you?
Of course not master!
Only…
Only what? Tell me.
Even you Master Kinchou have lost
the support of the other raccoons.
So what good can we achieve by staying here?
There is something. Come with me.
Wow, what an amazing place!
Do you like it? The people that you're about to
employ assured me that this visit would be memorable.
Look, I'm everywhere!
Unbelievable! This is worth every dime.
And so the raccoons of Tama Hills not only got their
revenge on the credit stealing Wonderland president,
they also obtained a substantial
sum to finance future operations.
The president ran to the authorities to report the
theft of 1 million dollars by a pack of raccoons...
But this time no one would listen to him.
Meanwhile, Gonta and his crew of rebels were taking
various steps to prevent further clearing of the forest.
Are you okay?
Attention all environmentalists...
you must not interfere with our attempts to
exterminate this snakes in the Tama Hills area.
If you do not leave the area immediately,
you'll be subject to prosecution for
trespassing... and for possession of dangerous weapons.
This is your last warning.
Leave the area now or you will
be a arrested and removed by force.
But Gonta and his army of rebels refuse to budge.
They're threatening tactics kept the police,
snake exterminators, and construction workers at bay.
Even as night fell both parties remained at an impasse.
Don't just sit there. Gonta's out there risking his life.
We all need to get out there and help him.
Can't you hear that? The riot police
are already here. It's too late, Shoukichi.
I'm gonna see what I can do!
I'm coming with you!
Are we ready?
Yes!
Now, let's hear the kamikaze motto.
"Even if we should fall in the heat of
battle. Our deaths will not be in vain.
Our sacrifice is certain to rally our
brothers to fight on until the day of victory."
That is the kamikaze spirit.
♪ If you don't want to be so accident prone. ♪
♪ Keep off our forests and will leave you alone. ♪
♪ Amen. ♪
Special forces!
Gonta! Wait!
Don't do this!
Now!
Gonta.
Although Gonta and the rebels fought
bravely, their battle did end with their deaths.
Mr. Raccoon?
Mr. Raccoon, Mr. Raccoon.
Meanwhile, in another part of Tama Hills,
a television reporter and his crew arrived.
Mr. Raccoon?
Please come out there's no need to be afraid.
Feel free to take whatever form
with which you feel most comfortable.
I and the entire staff of Action 8 News are on your side.
We're your friends.
Apparently they're hesitant to show themselves.
♪ Mr. Raccoon Mr. Raccoon won't you talk to me somehow? ♪
♪ No we can't. We're too hungry now. ♪
Unbelievable! They answered!
So, the raccoon's letter we received was indeed real!
Please come out raccoons! We've read your letter
and we want the world to know all about your troubles.
There they are! There they are! Raccoons! Raccoons! Wait!
Just tell us, are you raccoons
responsible for the Wonderland parade?
Of course we are!
Can you give us some proof. Why don't you
transform yourselves into something for our viewers.
Otherwise no one will believe you.
Not every raccoon can transform into something else.
That's why if our woods disappear
will not know where to go.
Raccoons, listen, please.
If you don't give us some form of prove,
this news report will look like it's a hoax.
Aren't you the ones who requested
this interview in your letter?
This is for your own good.
Osho?
We have no choice. I think it's time
that we tell the humans everything.
He came out! He came out!
A ceramic raccoon figurine is walking towards me…
Mr. Raccoon, a-a-a word for our viewers?
We'd like to say... That we were ah…
Yes?
Go on.
Oroku!
WE WERE THE ONES WHO PUT ON THAT PARADE!
The forest of Tama Hills are our home.
So, you can't keep destroying them all.
This plea is from every living creature in the forest.
♪ The ones you loved yesterday are gone today. ♪
♪ The ones you love today may be gone tomorrow. ♪
♪ We do not know what the future will... ♪
Master Hage the last surviving witness of
the age of the samurai was 999 years old.
Over the years he had earned many
honors and seen many fascinating sites.
But now he had seen enough and he
decided to bid the world farewell.
With a song of triumph the raccoons
stretched Master Hage's pouch to the limit,
and turned it into a magnificent ship,
trimmed with gold, and loaded
to the hilt with exotic treasure.
Dreaming of their heavenly destination a
large number of raccoons who couldn't transform...
boarded Master Hage's great ship.
They danced and sang in joyous celebration
of leaving this world of suffering behind.
And so, on that kind of moonlit
night that Master Hage adored,
the ship set sail down the Tama Hills river,
pulled along by a balmy breeze.
Gently the raccoons drifted off towards Nirvana.
They partied like never before.
And the Pom Poko sound of the raccoons
beating on their bellies like drums...
could be heard throughout the Tama
Hills until the wee hours of the night.
Although they knew the raccoons aboard a ship were happy,
the raccoons who were left
behind could do nothing but weep.
As if in a dream, the ship sailed
past forests and fields shrouded in mist.
The raccoons aboard the ship strained to see through
the fog and catch a glimpse of their glorious destination.
Despite the fact that the closer they got
to paradise, the closer they were to death.
And so the ship crossed over to the next world,
and the raccoons sailed away on a
trip from which they would never return.
Bye!
Well, I guess we're no match for the humans.
Bunta? Bunta, is that you?
Bunta!
Tamasaburou!
It's Bunta!
It's good to see you.
You made it!
Welcome home.
Sasuke! Shoukichi!
How was your journey, Bunta? Were you able to reach
Sado Island and locate their Transformation Master?
Yes sir, however, my news is quite grim.
Many years ago when food was
scarce he was… killed by a hunter.
How sad…
I was looking forward to meeting him.
I'm very proud of you, Bunta.
So, what has been happening to our forest?
It's only been three years. I feel like Rip Van Winkle!
We did everything we could to try and stop it.
But every inch of the woods has changed!
How could the land be so transformed?
We're so sorry. This must come as quite a shock.
So the humans did all this themselves.
That's right. They transformed all of Tama Hills.
But how! Only raccoon should be able to do that!
We're the only ones!
Who do you think you are, you stupid humans!
Raccoons are the ones who transform
things! How could you do this!
How could you do this!
The only way this makes any sense
is if all you humans are raccoons!
You're all stupid, evil, selfish, raccoons!
No!
How about one last try?
Let's use whenever strength we have left
to put Tama Hills back the way that it was.
That's an idea. We'll show those humans
the right way to transform this land.
Mmm, that sounds like fun.
I can remember every last little
detail of the way things used to be.
Oh yes! Time for one last gorilla attack!
But, it's already too late. It won't do any good.
Oh, it'll be fun. Let's have some fun!
Good idea. It's our playful spirit that
keeps us raccoons and that's what really matters.
Right?
Yeah, so then will you give us a hand, Kinchou?
Yes, of course. Although it may
end up looking like my home instead.
Ponkichi?
Here I am!
Want me to round up all the raccoons?
Yeah, you mind lending us some energy?
No problem.
Hey look!
What is it?
Wait for me!
Oh, that looks just like my mother.
Yoshi? It's Yoshi!
Yoshi!
That's us! That's us when we were cubs!
Hey! Raccoons!
Aw, there's so cute!
Aren't those raccoons?
I wonder what they're doing here?
They don't usually come so close to the city.
Hey, wait raccoons! Don't go!
Aw, they're gone.
I wish we could have fed them something.
I wonder if they can change
their form like in fairy tales?
After that, our last terra,
Manpooku Temple was knocked down.
And the New Tama development continued without delay.
Soon residents settle in and the town
became an ideal place for humans to live.
In fact the hill where the temple stood is
now the most popular section of the development.
Also, I'm happy to report that revealing
ourselves to the humans did have a positive effect.
Now humans are concerned about preserving nature.
And they're setting aside little bits of the
forests that they develop for parks and nature preserves.
Even the newspapers published articles proposing
various ways to help humans and raccoons to coexist.
Unfortunately, these changes came too
late for our group of raccoons to benefit.
Some of us tried moving to the other side of Tama Hills...
where some forests and farmlands still remained but
there were raccoons already living there of course.
And with all the construction and traffic in the area
it was a daily struggle to survive.
So, we finally gave in and followed Kinchou's advice.
Those of us who could transform followed in
the foxes' footsteps and started living as humans.
Some raccoons sold real estate and unable to resist the
money they could make promoted leveling even more forests.
I got a prime piece of forests
just waiting to be developed.
I now have a desk job while my
wife Kiyo works at a snack bar.
but most could barely handle the
stress of living in the human world,
and they wanted nothing more than to return to the hills.
I'm constantly impressed by the humans.
It takes a lot of stamina to live the way they do.
Eventually many of the raccoons quit their desk
jobs and started begging and living in the streets.
As for Ponkichi and the others who couldn't transform,
they adopted a lifestyle perfectly suited for raccoons.
They lived for the moment.
Knowing their lifestyle was dangerous, they
made sure to fully experience life each day,
and never letting the destruction of their
homes or accidents on the road get them down.
They had cubs, relaxed, ate,
drank, and died... all too quickly.
Ponkichi!
It's Shoukichi!
You look great!
No, you look better.
Shoukichi!
Uh... Hello.
Many of you have probably heard.
Someone on the news saying how animals
are disappearing because of development.
I don't think that's quite accurate.
It's true that some raccoons can
transform and disappear although,
What about things like rabbits and badgers.
They can't transform, so where do they go?