[PHOENIX] Maya signed up for
advanced spiritual training
at Hazakura Temple up in
the snow-capped mountains,
and Pearl and I tagged along.
There I met someone who
was strangely familiar.
Her name was Iris and she
was the spitting image
of Dahlia Hawthorne,
my old flame.
Later that night,
after Maya crossed
the infamous Dusky Bridge
to begin her training,
all hell broke loose.
Acclaimed children's book
author and illustrator,
Elise Deauxnim, was murdered on
the grounds of the main temple.
Adding to the chaos,
a lightning strike
incinerated Dusky Bridge,
leaving Maya completely stranded
on the other side of the ravine.
I tried to save her.
[BUTZ]
Nicky!
[PHOENIX screams]
[PHOENIX] When law
enforcement finally arrived,
they arrested Iris
for Elise's murder.
I believe in her innocence,
so I entrusted my old
friend Miles with the case
and my defense attorney's badge.
[MILES]
Although I can't say I'm
enjoying these
frigid temperatures,
it is interesting to visit
the site of Dusky Bridge.
[GUMSHOE]
Whoa, Prosecutor Edgeworth!
[MILES]
Hello, Gumshoe.
It's been too long, sir!
I heard you'd be here, so I
busted out the ol' kneepads
to work this case!
[MILES] Honestly,
I'd expect no less from you.
[GUMSHOE] So rest assured
you'll have "Big" Dick Gumshoe
at your service
whenever you need me!
That so? Appreciate it.
Full disclosure,
there's something that
I need to tell you first.
[GUMSHOE]
Objection!
You gotta be kidding me, pal!
You're really gonna
defend Sister Iris?!
Yes. It was a shock
to me as well.
[GUMSHOE]
But how can you be a prosecutor
that's not a prosecutor?!
"Prosecutor Edgeworth
standing for the Defense"
makes my brain hurt!
It's like a crime
against nature!
Regardless, I'll need
a briefing from you.
Uh--
But a cop giving the defense
that kind of inside scoop
could get into some murky
territory, ethically speaking.
[MILES]
Don't let that get in your way.
All you have to do is leak it to
me without telling anyone else.
[GUMSHOE]
Hmm...
I'll be leakier than
a discount diaper!
Just... be discrete.
So, as I understand it,
Maya Fey is stuck in a temple
on the other side of this gorge.
[GUMSHOE] Yeah, and with all
this wind whippin' around,
an aerial extraction's
off the table.
She's there till tomorrow
at the very least.
In this bitter cold.
I hope she's okay.
I'm curious.
Do you know what caused
the bridge to burn?
[GUMSHOE]
It was a lightning bolt.
After it quit snowing, there was
some kinda electrical storm.
Completely fried the bridge.
[MILES] Looks like there's
another building that way.
[GUMSHOE]
All right, pal.
We should head over
to the main temple
and see what the
eyewitness has to say.
[MILES gasps]
An eyewitness? Really?
Yep! The Bikini lady saw it all.
[MILES]
O...kay...
[MILES] Well, I don't
see a bikini anywhere.
I know I'm probably
not what you expected,
but I gotta bundle it up
for the cold weather.
Come back this summer.
I shoulda made it clear we'd
be talkin' to Sister Bikini,
the head nun, but I totally
thought the same thing.
Details like that are
important, Detective.
And perhaps you should
take this as a clue
to why you have
never gotten a raise.
You're right about that, sir.
Sister.
Can you tell me what
happened last night?
I took the trainee over
to the Inner Temple,
where she'd be doing
her spiritual exercises.
By "trainee" you mean Maya Fey?
[BIKINI]
Yep.
The training lasts
all night long
and the head nun has to be there
to observe throughout
the process.
[MILES]
So you're there all night.
But didn't the incident occur
over here in the courtyard?
[sighs]
I did have to leave
my post for a bit,
but Iris took over for me.
So Iris was there?
[BIKINI] My lower back's
been giving me trouble.
Iris came to see
how I was holding up
and told me she'd sub in for me
so I could get some
decent rest in my own room.
And then at 10 PM I rang
the bell for lights out.
After that, I was in my room
until I heard all the commotion.
I headed back to
the Inner Temple
to check on things after a bit
and that's when I saw
it in the courtyard!
What did you see?
It was like it was something
straight out of a nightmare!
[BIKINI whimpers]
No... I can't...
I can't even say it!
What?
[BIKINI wails]
[BIKINI]
Iris... She...
Are you saying Iris
was in the courtyard?
I saw her with my own eyes!
How could that gentle girl
do something so horrific?!
I screamed bloody murder
and then passed out.
I only came to when that spiky-
haired man ran across my belly.
[MILES] That corroborates
Wright's story.
And she doesn't
appear to be lying.
[BIKINI cries, blows nose]
[GUMSHOE]
Ew, that's disgusting!
Is there anything else
you'd like to mention?
Yes, come to think of
it, there is something.
I have no idea where
Pearl ran off to!
Who might that be?
A sweetheart of a little girl
who came here with the trainee.
I haven't seen her all day,
but I heard she went up to
Elise's room last night.
You mean the victim?
[sobs] It's all because...
This happened because
of my creaky old back!
[BIKINI wailing]
I got a search together
for little Pearl Fey.
Good work.
So the crime scene--
We took the body, of course,
but everything else is
practically untouched.
[MILES]
That's the murder weapon?
[GUMSHOE] Seven-pointed sword,
the "Shi-something."
[MILES]
Any info on the victim?
Yessir.
All we know is that she
was a picture book author
who went by Elise Deauxnim.
Don't know her real
name or much else
besides she won
an award last year.
That kind of privacy
is rare these days.
[GUMSHOE]
Time of death is estimated
between 10 and 11 PM last night.
The cause is being
ruled as blood loss
resulting from a
stab to the back.
That poor woman.
And you should probably
know the victim's body
was practically covered
head to toe with bruises!
[MILES]
Really?
Yeah.
They seem to be consistent
with falling out of a
second-story window.
[MILES] Like the one in
the room above us, correct?
Which just so happens
to be the exact room
the victim was
staying in last night!
[MILES]
Interesting.
Leads me to believe she may
have been pushed from there
and then stabbed with the sword.
What's that?
The victim's fingerprints
were all over it,
so we're guessing it's
some kind of cane she used.
Oh, speaking of fingerprints.
Yes, what?
[GUMSHOE] That crazy sword,
the murder weapon,
had the accused's
fingerprints on it, too.
That sort of evidence
will be difficult to refute.
Whoops, it totally
slipped my mind
that you're the
defense, Prosecutor.
[MILES] Things definitely
seem desperate right now.
Is this how Wright felt
every time he stood in court
for one of his clients?
You weren't kidding
when you said
you're gonna be the
defense attorney, were ya?
No.
But you're a pretty
famous prosecutor,
so won't that be a problem
when they see you walking
into the courtroom tomorrow?
[MILES]
I realize that,
which is precisely the
reason why I arranged
to have a different judge
presiding over this case.
[GUMSHOE]
Okay, well, we've been waiting
for Godot to get back to us,
'cause he's supposed
to be the prosecutor.
Not a problem.
I've made arrangements
for a prosecutor as well.
[GUMSHOE stammers]
[MILES]
Problem?
Nope, that's just the sound
of my mind being blown away
by how amazing you are!
[sighs]
Let's go.
[GUMSHOE]
Crazy, I didn't even know
there was a shack over here.
[BUTZ]
I knew you'd come.
Edgy boy.
Hello, Larry.
You took your time.
What've you been doing?
[MILES] I should be
asking you that question.
Huh?
I'm saying I don't understand
why you're even here
in the first place.
Come on, bro!
I'm an artist, so I'm working on
some snowy landscape pieces.
An artist? Surely you jest.
This guy was apparently the dead
picture book lady's apprentice.
That so? This dullard?
Hey man, why you
gotta call me that?
I'm Laurice Deauxnim,
the artiste,
and I'm here to do a
study of Dusky Bridge!
[BUTZ]
What's up with Iris?
Have the po-po finally
let her outta jail yet?
She will be standing
trial tomorrow.
It's not lookin' good, pal.
[BUTZ] That's the craziest
thing I've ever heard!
There's no way in hell
she could be the killer!
And what makes you so
certain of her innocence?
I mean, you guys have
seen her, haven't you?
She's way too cute
to be a murderer.
[MILES]
Why did I even ask?
[BUTZ]
But man, in my opinion,
a beautiful girl like
her shouldn't be taking
those kinds of risks.
[MILES]
What's that mean?
[BUTZ] Nothing! Just one
of those Butz brain farts!
As I understand it,
you're actually the one who
called the cops last night
after the body was
found, aren't ya?
Is that true?
Huh? Oh, yeah, right.
Man, that was insanity!
First, the lightning was all
like "crashentino," "zaparroo,"
there goes the bridge and
Nick whizzing right off it!
[MILES] I don't speak your
made-up language, Larry.
Anyway, Nick had run
up screaming at me
to call the cops, so I did,
and boy howdy was I a mess.
With the lightning, the fire,
and your buddy whizzing
off the bridge,
I mean, how could
anybody not be?
Oh, naw, it's because of the
totally bonkers thing I'd seen
before all that happened!
Uh--
You care to elaborate on that?
Well--I told you
everything I know
so you should be on your way.
Larry, you're hiding
something from me, aren't you?
I'm offended that one
of my oldest friends
can't tell when I'm telling
the honest-to-god truth.
I can tell, that's how
I know you're lying now.
You better start
talking, pronto,
or we're gonna throw
your butt in the slammer!
[screams]
Quit hassling me, bro!
[GUMSHOE]
Hey!
Don't make me have to chase you!
[MILES]
Your choice.
But I will drag you
into the courtroom
if that's what it takes
to hear the whole story,
old friend.
[JUDGE 204A] And now, this
court is hereby in session
for the trial of Sister Iris.
The defense is ready to present
our argument, Your Honor.
[MILES] It is a prosecutor's
duty to doubt the defendant,
but today I must take
an opposite approach.
Wright told me
a defense attorney
must believe in their
client's innocence
through to the last
moments of the trial.
Am I truly up to the task?
I am fully prepared
to defend my client!
[JUDGE 204A]
Mm.
If the prosecution is ready,
then we shall begin without
further ad--[groans]
Does my whip feel ready to you?
[JUDGE 204A]
Oh, and you are?
[FRANZISKA]
My name?
Franziska von Karma.
Uh, really? Like the
legendary prosecutor?
That von Karma?
[FRANZISKA]
"Legendary" describes the past,
but I am bringing
us into the future!
[JUDGE 204A gasps]
[MILES]
She left home for America
and became a prosecutor at 13.
And like her father, she'll
do whatever it takes to win.
I'm glad you're here, Franziska.
[JUDGE 204A clears throat]
Guess that's been cleared up.
But I do have a question
for the defense.
[MILES]
Yes, Your Honor?
I can't help feeling
I've met a prosecutor
to whom you bear such
an uncanny resemblance.
He could practically
be your twin brother.
Must've imagined it.
Prosecutor von Karma, do you
know who I'm talking about?
[FRANZISKA]
You imagined it.
Why would I invent
such a person?
[FRANZISKA] I had expected
that I would be squaring off
against Phoenix Wright
in the courtroom today.
But perhaps this is the battle
I've been preparing for
my entire life.
This is my chance to crush Miles
Edgeworth once and for all!
Prosecution, with
that out of the way,
please begin your
opening statement.
[FRANZISKA] The victim
is children's book author
and illustrator, Elise Deauxnim.
Her bloody corpse was discovered
in the courtyard of
Hazakura Temple.
As seen here, she was
stabbed through the torso
with a ceremonial sword
held by a golden statue.
What an awful tragedy.
An act of brutality clearly
carried out by Sister Iris.
The proof? Well, it was all seen
by an eyewitness with
an honest reputation.
Let's hear them out.
Very well. Please bring the
witness to the stand at once.
[MILES]
And so it begins--
my first and my last trial
as a defense attorney.
[FRANZISKA] Witness,
state your name and occupation.
Your Honor, I'm the
head nun in charge
over at the Hazakura Temple,
and my name is Bikini, but
don't get the wrong idea okay?
It does cause one to conjure
up certain ima--[groans]
[FRANZISKA] This courtroom
is a sacred place.
Those who enter it
with impure thoughts
should be forced to leave
without exception!
You think I should
leave my own courtroom?
Now there's no need to go
gettin' your bikini in a twist
until you see me in my
preferred summer attire.
[laughs]
So about the murder.
You claim to have seen
the crime take place,
is that correct, Sister?
I'm afraid I did.
I'm shocked my sweet
little Iris could do this.
[JUDGE 204A]
This may be difficult for you,
but please describe
the events of that night
as accurately as possible.
[BIKINI]
Mm-hmm.
On that night,
I was helping a trainee
begin her exercises
in the Inner Temple.
Then around 10 PM,
Iris came for me.
She stayed to help the trainee
and I went back to
the main grounds.
[MILES]
Hold it!
That can't be true,
because the defendant never
went to the Inner Temple
on the night in question.
Isn't that correct, defendant?
I was in my room in
Hazakura Temple all night
up until I heard the commotion
outside when the body was found.
I swear I saw her
with my own eyes!
She was dressed exactly the
same as at dinner earlier!
[MILES]
And how was she dressed?
[BIKINI]
Same robes she always wears
and with her head scarf
on just like before!
Unfortunately,
that is also untrue.
[BIKINI gasps]
[MILES]
Iris. This head scarf, or hood--
Had you done anything with it?
I gave it to Mister Wright
on my way to ring the bell
for lights out before 10 PM.
You gave it away?
[MILES] Indeed. Which means she
wasn't wearing her head scarf
when the witness claims
to have seen her--
a fact that begs the question
"who did she see that night"?
Ha! Are you suggesting the
defendant had a doppelganger
come to the Inner Temple?
We don't really
know who was there.
However, this witness
needs to be precise
with the details
of her testimony.
[BIKINI]
It's so bizarre!
I know exactly what
I saw that night.
[MILES] I don't think
she's purposefully lying.
This contradiction is sure
to come up later in the trial.
[JUDGE 204A] You may continue
with your testimony, witness,
but keep in mind you'll need
to be precise in your account.
Yes.
After resting for a short while,
I headed back to the
Inner Temple around 11 PM.
Then, I heard a strange noise
coming from the courtyard.
When I looked that way,
I saw Iris holding a sword.
It was plunged to the hilt
into poor Ms. Deauxnim's back!
I imagine that was a
very traumatizing thing
for you to witness.
That's all I remember.
I let loose a scream
and passed out.
Are you absolutely certain
that you saw the defendant?
[BIKINI]
Yes. Without a doubt.
She wasn't wearing her
head scarf at the time,
but I know it was Iris!
When I awoke,
Ms. Deauxnim was lying dead
underneath Mystic Ami's
golden statue.
Game over, Edgeworth.
You've nowhere to turn.
[grunts]
The witness stands by
her damning testimony,
which is corroborated by the
defendant's fingerprints found
on the seven-pointed sword that
was used as the murder weapon.
Sister Iris' prints were on it?
This proves she
murdered Ms. Deauxnim.
Therefore, this court
must find her guilty.
[JUDGE 204A] Do you care to make
a counter-argument, defense?
[MILES] So this is what it's
like to be on the other side.
Not bad.
Very well.
I shall have to find my own
way to turn things around.
Objection!
[FRANZISKA gasps, screams]
[MILES]
Plunged in to the hilt?
Then the entire blade should
be covered with blood.
But if we check the
crime scene photo...
[JUDGE 204A]
It's only on the very tip of it!
[FRANZISKA gasps]
[MILES]
Considering its unique design,
is it even possible to stab a
person all the way to the hilt
with this particular sword?
Th-That's what she saw!
When I looked over,
the sword was totally run
through the poor woman
and the hilt was the
only part sticking out!
If you'd be clear, defense,
what is the point you're
trying to make here?
My point is simple.
This sword was almost
certainly not the weapon
used in this murder.
Don't be foolish.
[MILES] And if it was indeed not
the weapon used in this crime,
her fingerprints on it would
have no bearing whatsoever.
It doesn't prove she
committed the murder!
[FRANZISKA gasps, groans]
[MILES] Seems to me the
prosecution's chilling claims
have melted like snow in spring.
[CROWD murmuring]
Expertly done.
You found a major contradiction
by merely looking at
one piece of evidence.
Who would've imagined
that bloody blade
wasn't the murder weapon?
[FRANZISKA]
Objection!
If that is the case,
then why don't you take a stab
at answering this question,
Miles Edgeworth.
What do you believe was
the actual murder weapon?
I cannot answer that.
How typical.
Even so, no matter the weapon,
the conclusion is the same.
[JUDGE 204A] What exactly
do you mean by that?
The witness explicitly stated
what she saw that night.
She was there to observe
the moment when Sister Iris
brutally stabbed the victim
in the temple courtyard.
[groans]
[FRANZISKA]
Isn't that right?
Oh, gimme a break. I never
said anything of the sort.
U-Uh--
[BIKINI] The sword was already
sticking out of her back
when I came across
them that night.
Seemed to me that Iris
was just holding it.
Do you mean to tell this court
that you did not, in fact,
witness the defendant
stabbing the victim?
Yeah, just seeing that
would've killed me, too!
--[CROWD gasps]
--No way.
[MILES]
However,
since it's quite obvious there
was a different murder weapon,
we must ask what became of that.
[FRANZISKA]
What do you mean?
Following the incident,
the local police conducted a
thorough investigative search
of the surrounding area.
Yes, they did their
jobs quite well.
But nothing suspicious was found
on or near the temple grounds.
I see. That's very
peculiar indeed.
Although there is an extremely
secure hiding place nearby.
Is that so?
If it were disposed of there,
it may never be discovered.
Where might that be?
[FRANZISKA]
Eagle River.
[MILES]
Really?
There was a snowmobile next to
Hazakura Temple's main gate.
Somebody could have driven
this over to the bridge
and thrown the weapon into the
gorge where the rapid current
would whisk it away
to who knows where.
Uh--the snowmobile?
Have you any proof of
this, or just conjecture?
Do I? Of course I have proof.
[MILES]
Nonsense!
[FRANZISKA] There were
snowmobile tracks leading from
Hazakura Temple to Dusky Bridge
that were made that very night.
[gasps]
It makes sense if you
consider another weapon.
The killer drove there to
get rid of the evidence.
Tell us, witness.
Who could have used the
snowmobile that night?
Well, just Iris.
She's the only one.
What? Why just her?
[BIKINI] Because she had the
only key to the snowmobile.
Iris! Did you really do this?
[MILES]
Iris...
I'm so sorry, Sister...
but I can't answer that.
Not right now.
--[CROWD murmuring]
--[JUDGE 204A] Order!
--I demand order in this court!
Seems you've failed, Edgeworth.
So admit defeat.
[MILES grunts]
[MILES]
Iris, why won't you answer?
Your Honor, the defendant's
stubborn refusal
is practically a confession!
I demand a verdict this instant!
If the defendant will
not speak on her behalf,
I see no need to continue
this trial any further.
[BUTZ grunts]
[BUTZ]
Objection!
[JUDGE 204A]
Wait, who in the hell are you?
Gotta say, this performance
is kinda hard to watch.
[MILES]
Larry!
Sorry, Vincent van Bro, but you
can call me Laurice Deauxnim.
Did he say Deauxnim?
[BUTZ] Everything that
happened that night--
I saw it all.
And if I can save my
beautiful little flower,
I'll paint you a masterpiece
with my testimony!
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
Larry's sudden appearance
in the courtroom
may be what turns this
whole case around.
His artistic rendering provides
a crucial piece of info
that shocks everyone.
And as rookie defense
attorney Miles Edgeworth
defies von Karma's relentless
line of questioning,
he discovers a
glaring contradiction.
Also, I make my
triumphant return!
I'm back in the saddle, Miles,
and I'll ride the facts
straight into justice!
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Next episode: "Bridge to
the Turnabout - 3rd Trial"!
Take that!