[PHOENIX]
My name is Phoenix Wright,
and I'm a defense attorney.
I've made a pledge to
stand up for those who have
no one else in their corner.
No matter how
tough the case may be,
or how high the odds
are stacked against us.
I'll do whatever it takes
to fight for the truth!
But of course,
there was a time before I made
that pledge and earned
my attorney's badge.
Five years ago,
something changed
the direction of my life
and convinced me
to be a voice for justice!
[DOUG] Listen, man.
You should stop seeing her.
[PHOENIX]
What? How is our relationship
any of your business?
[thunder rumbles]
Please. This is
for your own sake.
She's bad news,
and that's putting it lightly.
[PHOENIX growls]
You're lying!
[DOUG] There's something
you need to know about her.
Before you get hurt.
[thunder rumbles]
[PHOENIX]
Shut your mouth!
She's not like that!
There's no way!
[blow lands]
[PHOENIX]
No. It's not my fault.
It... couldn't be.
I didn't kill this guy!
[thunder cracks
[MIA]
Ugh. It's almost time.
I can't believe
how nervous I am.
[MARVIN clears throat]
[MIA yelps]
You startled me, Mr. Grossberg!
Good morning!
Now, now, Mia.
There's no need to be so jumpy.
You might get questioned
for suspicious behavior.
I'm perfectly calm, thank you.
Is this not the face
of tranquility?!
--Uh... Ms. Fey! [coughs]
--Please forgive my outburst.
I understand the emotion,
but no more manhandling!
[sighs] Your first time
trying a case, eh?
I, Marvin Grossberg,
vow to be your rock.
Actually, to be clear,
this'll be my second
time to try a case.
Nevertheless,
you gave me quite a surprise.
What made you come to me
all fiery eyed last night
and insist on handling this?
When I heard about it yesterday,
it caught my interest.
[MIA] The defendant's name
is Phoenix Wright.
He's accused of murder,
and the official cause of
death was electrocution.
[MARVIN]
And here he is.
This is Phoenix Wright.
The man whose freedom you
will be fighting for today.
[PHOENIX] Thanks so much
for taking my case!
I know you can clear my name!
I'll help you anyway I can!
[coughs]
Yes, of course. Thank you.
Mister Wry!
[PHOENIX]
Great!
Oh, but my name.
It's Wright, like
the flying brothers.
I misspoke, Mr. Wright!
It won't happen again!
I swear on my life
I won't fail you!
[coughs]
Forgive me.
[PHOENIX] All I want is
to prove my innocence,
because I would
never kill anybody!
[MIA] I need to keep
things in perspective,
he's got every right
to be nervous.
Come on, Mia. Stay strong!
My first trial, a year ago,
was such a
traumatizing experience.
I thought I'd never set
foot inside a courtroom again.
But I can't keep running away.
I have to go back
and face my fears.
And this time...
...I believe in myself.
I'm gonna win this!
[CROWD murmuring]
Order, please!
This court is hereby in session
to hear the murder trial
of Mister Phoenix Wright.
The defense team is
ready to begin, Your Honor.
Yes, Your Honor. The
prosecution is ready as well.
Ms. Fey. Am I to understand
that you'll be
leading the defense?
Um... Yes. Is there a problem?
No, but I was under the
impression Mister Grossberg
would be fulfilling
duties of council.
Oh. Well... Mister Grossberg
had an urgent matter
that came up all of a sudden.
So I'm here in his
stead, Your Honor.
Is that the case?
Because that man
standing next to you looks
a lot like him, Ms. Fey.
That's true.
It turns out the urgent
matter was that
I desperately needed to
observe this trial, Your Honor.
[MIA]
Mm-hmm.
[JUDGE]
Hmmmm.
[CROWD murmuring]
[JUDGE]
Well then.
Mister Payne, proceed with
your opening statement.
[PAYNE]
Hmm. It boggles the mind.
To think they would send
someone so green to go
against a "rookie
killer" like me.
[MIA growls]
[PAYNE] Anyway, I'd like to
proceed with a brief summary
of the events in question.
This tragic incident
occurred one rainy afternoon,
on the local campus
of Ivy University.
The victim of this
horrific crime was Doug Swallow,
a senior so close to finishing
his pharmacology degree.
[JUDGE]
Pharmacology.
[PAYNE] Some fellow students
discovered the crime scene
and notified the authorities.
They found Mr. Swallow's
body, and the defendant
who'd made a complete
mess of his get-away attempt.
Phoenix Wright sits before us.
Wright is a third-year
Ivy University student
who is pursuing a degree
in the arts, of all things.
Apparently, this man
and the late Mister Swallow
had some bad blood
between the two of them.
Please elaborate.
[PHOENIX] You make it sound like
there was some big feud, but...
[coughs]
[JUDGE] Contain your coughing
or we'll be forced to eject you.
[CROWD murmurin]
But there was a disagreement
between the two men.
Wasn't there, young lady?
[MIA gasps]
Nothing to say?
[chuckles] If you call yourself
a defense attorney,
surely, you must know all
about what went down.
[MIA] So. He wants to
test me, does he? Fine.
I'm not scared of Payne.
I assume this so-called
"bad blood" you mention
has to do with Dahlia Hawthorne?
[JUDGE]
And who might that be?
[PAYNE] Currently, the
defendant's girlfriend.
But until half a year ago,
Miss Hawthorne could usually be
found hanging on the arm of
the victim, Mister Swallow
I'm sure that romantic
entanglement was the motive
behind this senseless murder.
[JUDGE] Hmm. So it was your
run-of-the mill love triangle.
[PHOENIX]
I object!
You'd better keep my
sweet Dollie out of this!
--[JUDGE] Hmm?
--[PHOENIX] You hear me?
[PAYNE] Please take
another look at the victim
in the crime scene photo.
[gasping]
[JUDGE] Hm. Is he
holding a medicine bottle?
[PAYNE]
Indeed. It's Coldkiller Z,
an elixir that claims
it "kills colds dead."
[PHOENIX]
Hey, wait a second, that's mine!
I'd been trying to
kill this cold with it,
but I ended up losing the
bottle somewhere that day.
I could swear I had it
on me till lunchtime, at least.
[JUDGE]
Defendant! Control yourself!
[PHOENIX]
I'm sorry, sir.
[MIA]
He behaves like a child.
[PAYNE] Your Honor.
The defendant's fingerprints
were found all over the bottle,
so he's telling the truth.
Mere moments
before his untimely death,
the victim used the last
bit of his strength
he could muster to wrest it
from the hands of his attacker.
All to ensure
that the killer would be
identified as Phoenix Wright!
[PHOENIX yells]
His argument
carries incredible force!
Another thing I'd
like to mention is the watch
pictured here on the
victim's wrist is broken.
[JUDGE]
Is that so?
[PAYNE]
The impact from the death-blow
is what likely
caused it to break.
So we can take that to
mean the time of the murder
was exactly 3:05 PM.
Let us proceed to the
defendant's cross-examination.
State your name and occupation.
[PHOENIX] Gladly! My
name is Phoenix Wright!
My occupation is,
uh, accused murderer?
What did you do
before you were arrested?!
[PHOENIX]
Oh. I'm a college student!
[JUDGE] Mister Wright,
please tell the court
about the events of said day.
[PHOENIX] That morning,
Doug had asked me to meet him
behind the Pharmacology
Department at 2:45 PM.
We talked for a bit and then
parted ways around 3.
So, had you and the victim
had any previous interactions?
[PHOENIX]
Never. That was the first time
we'd spoken to each other.
He said he wanted to
talk to me about Dollie.
Dahlia Hawthorne. Right, Wright?
[PHOENIX]
Yes, Dollie, my soulmate!
This sweater I'm wearing
is a token of our love.
And she gave me
this beautiful pendant!
Before I met him,
she and I had lunch together!
She made omelets and
it was just like eating
a little bite of Heaven!
You testified that you
and the victim had a talk.
Was that really
all that happened?
[PHOENIX]
Uh, what do you mean by that?
Did the situation
get heated and escalate
into something physical?
Like shoving?
[PHOENIX] No way, I'm just
not that kind of person,
I would never lay
a finger on the guy!
[PAYNE]
Objection!
Please, Your Honor.
Go and take another look
at the crime scene photo.
You can see the victim
was wearing a leather jacket.
Upon further inspection,
we found the defendant's
palm print on the left breast.
It's there, clear as day.
[MIA gasps]
Obviously, Mister Wright,
your testimony
to the court is full of lies!
[yells, coughs]
Well, Wright,
what do you have to say?
[PHOENIX]
That's exactly what happened!
I'm so sorry!
I really did shove him!
[CROWD gasping, murmurin]
[JUDGE] Order in the court!
Order, please!
I'm shocked. This is
the first I've heard of it.
We're done, Mia. Might
as well stick a big fork in us.
Not yet. I can't
just let it end like this.
I can think of only one
way the defendant could have
left such an
unmistakable hand print.
He assaulted the
victim with an intent to kill!
[gasps]
[JUDGE]
Hmm. That does make sense.
[MIA]
Objection!
[gasping]
[PHOENIX]
Ms. Fey?
Even if my client
did shove the victim,
the blow did not
actually cause his death.
This is not a murder!
Care to explain that, defense?
Look at the autopsy report.
It states the cause of
death was electrocution.
He died by electrocution?
Remember what
the weather was like?
I mean it was raining cats
and dogs the entire day.
[thunder cracks
Considering that fact,
it stands to reason the
most likely cause of death
would be a lightning strike.
[JUDGE]
It was an act of God?
This wasn't a murder after all.
But rather an unfortunate
freak accident!
Oh, brilliant
deduction, Ms. Fey.
[PAYNE chuckles] I wouldn't
begin the celebration yet
if I were you, young rookie.
A seasoned prosecutor
covers every base,
so of course I investigated
the meteorological report.
[MIA gasps]
There were, in fact,
no lightning strikes
in that area on the
day of the murder.
What? There weren't?
Simply look at
the crime scene photo.
And Mister Swallow's true cause
of death is clearly visible.
[MIA]
That thing. Above him.
Is that a severed
electric cable?
Precisely. Your
client heartlessly pushed
the victim toward that cable
hoping it would end his life.
Which, as we all know,
was exactly the thing
that killed Mister Swallow.
[yelps]
[MIA]
Was that all just a trap?
The prosecution has
presented a credible motive
and explained the method
of murder in this case.
Hold on. No one's proven
Wright meant to kill him!
Did he even know about
the severed cable?
[coughs]
It's so sad. The defense
has resorted to conjecture.
Very well.
I suppose I'll spare you
from any further desperation
and finish you off for good.
What do you mean by that?
[PAYNE]
The prosecution has a witness
whose testimony is unassailable.
[JUDGE] And who might
that be, Mister Payne?
This witness has
had a horrifying image
burned into their mind forever.
They actually saw
the murder as it happened.
[gasping]
[JUDGE]
Did they now?
[PAYNE chuckles] She has already
come up in this very trial.
Her name is
Miss Dahlia Hawthorne!
[MIA growls]
[PHOENIX] Oh, I knew
that my sweet little Dollie
would come and save me!
My love!
[coughs]
[JUDGE]
Order in this court!
I call Miss Dahlia Hawthorne
to come to the witness stand!
[PHOENIX]
Dollie!
[DAHLIA giggles]
I'm afraid this witness
reeks of bad news for us.
[MIA]
Hmph. I doubt that.
In fact, this is just the
news I've been waiting for.
Your time's up...
Dahlia Hawthorne!
[PAYNE]
If you would be so kind--
Who are you, and what do you do?
Who, me? Well, I, uh...
Aww, poor thing.
There's no reason for you
to be nervous, sweetie.
Yeah! If anyone
even makes one rude remark
toward you, I will make
them eat their words!
I'll use my gavel to
teach them about respect!
[MIA] How comforting
that they're glaring at me
when they say that.
You're both sweet.
Oh, but of course.
It's my pleasure, dear.
I believe you'd asked for
her name and occupation?
[DAHLIA] Hmm. You're still
the same as ever, Mia Fey.
[MIA]
Hmph.
Oh, my. Does this mean the two
of you are already acquainted?
We've met, just once.
To answer your question,
my name is Dahlia Hawthorne.
A literature student
at Ivy University.
It's truly an honor
to be here in the presence
of such great legal minds.
I'm honored, too.
Yet still we try to stay humble.
She wasted zero time
getting the old boys
wrapped around her
little finger.
[DAHLIA] That day, I
had gone over to meet
sweetie Feenie
after class let out.
[JUDGE]
Who's that? Oh, the defendant?
[DAHLIA] Yes, sir. I came
across Feenie and Dougie.
They were having
some sort of conversation
behind the building.
I was too far to hear
what they were saying,
but all of a sudden Dougie got
angry and gave Feenie a big pow.
Say what? The victim
pow'd the defendant?
[DAHLIA] Yeah! I didn't see
Feenie do anything
to deserve it!
He had no choice but
to shove him back after that.
[DAHLIA] Poor Dougie
slammed into the utility pole
and snapped the electric cable.
I could see Dougie
get up and desperately try
to skedaddle his way outta
there, but Feeny followed him.
He ran over and shoved him
again from the back,
knocking him to the ground.
And at the exact same
moment that Dougie collapsed,
I heard an extremely loud,
cracking noise.
I thought my little
heart was going to pitter-patter
right out of my chest!
I'm pitter-pattering
just hearing about it.
A loud cracking noise, you say?
There's no doubt that what
you heard must've been
the victim being electrocuted.
[DAHLIA] All of this happened
mere moments after
that cable was knocked
loose and fell.
[MIA gasps]
Well then.
The witness's testimony
makes it crystal clear
how the murder happened.
And the prosecution
has also gathered
corroborating testimony.
Oh? Who'd you get that from?
[PAYNE] The science majors
who were conducting experiments
in one of the labs nearby.
Allow me to read
their prepared statement.
"Around 3 PM, all of the
electrical equipment in the lab
simultaneously lost power."
[JUDGE]
So, was there a blackout?
[PAYNE] Yes. There are
logs of a blackout taking
place at 2:55 PM.
The equipment
in that particular lab
requires high
voltage to operate.
Which was being supplied
by the cable that had been
severed at that time.
The defendant met with the
victim at 2:45 that afternoon.
And a mere ten minutes later he
had caused the untimely death
of poor Mister Swallow.
This is the shocking
truth of what happened
that fateful day!
[CROWD murmurin]
[JUDGE] Hmm. There's
little room for doubt.
Thanks for your brave
and helpful testimony.
Thank you.
I couldn't hide the truth
from you, Your Honor.
[MIA]
Objection!
--[yells]
--[screams]
I hate to break it to you,
but that's not going to fly.
Huh?
[MIA] The only thing brave
about her testimony...
...is that she's
risking perjury!
[PAYNE]
Really? In what way?
[DAHLIA growls]
The electric cable
was severed at 2:55.
This must be when my client
admittedly shoved the victim.
But looking at
the crime scene photo.
We can see the victim's watch
stopped functioning at 3:05.
How can you explain
the ten minute gap?
[gasping]
[gasps]
In the sworn testimony
you gave the court,
you stated that the incident
took place mere moments
after the cable was
severed right?
I'll ask again!
Do you have any
reasonable explanation
for this discrepancy?
[DAHLIA whimpers]
[yelps]
[CROWD murmurin]
Tell me, Miss Hawthorne.
Why must you continuously
spout these lies?
What?
[MIA] It's almost like
you're actively trying
to frame your boyfriend.
[DAHLIA growls]
--[JUDGE] Hmm?
--[PAYNE gasps]
[PHOENIX] But... why would
she wanna frame me?
[CROWD murmuring]
[MIA] You seem to be a magnet
for tragic incidents like this.
The last one was
only eight months ago.
[JUDGE]
Hmm? What happened then?
[DAHLIA gasps, growls]
To jog your memory,
this particular event took place
in this courthouse.
Observe.
[PAYNE]
What is it?
[JUDGE] Hm. I remember now.
What a shock that was.
[MIA] Miss Hawthorne.
You were on the scene as well,
when that terrible
incident took place.
[DAHLIA gasps]
[MIA] When researching
the investigation reports
submitted at the time,
I couldn't help but notice
who was the prime suspect.
It was you!
That's totally ludicrous!
[PHOENIX]
Dollie was the prime suspect?
I don't believe it.
The crime that rocked this
courthouse eight months ago
has a link to this case.
--Say wha...?
--And what would that be,
--defense?
--There was a trial going on.
The defense lawyer
summoned a witness
to come in for questioning.
And they are the link
to this current case.
The witness
was Dahlia Hawthorne.
[DAHLIA growls]
[MIA] She met the lawyer
in the cafeteria downstairs.
[MIA] And that's where
it all happened.
Somebody laced
the coffee that lawyer
was drinking with poison.
And Miss Hawthorne was named
suspect number
one in that crime.
[PHOENIX]
Not my sweet Dollie.
No. It's not true.
I have a request.
No, a demand, that Miss
Hawthorne give sworn testimony
regarding that incident
before this court!
[PAYNE]
Objection!
What? That's completely absurd!
I won't stand for this!
I, uh...
I fail to see how
an isolated incident
has anything to
do with this case!
[DAHLIA]
Mister Prosecutor?
I believe I was speaking,
when you interrupted me.
Oh. I'm sorry. Go ahead, dear.
I appreciate it.
And what Ms. Fey
was saying is true.
Eight months ago, I was
under a suspicious eyeball.
[JUDGE] You mean...
The police were eyeballing you?
[DAHLIA] That's why I wanna set
the record straight for good.
And prove beyond any doubt
I had absolutely no part in it!
But... There's no need
for you to go through
all that trauma again!
[gavel bangs]
The end goal
of this trial today,
is to figure out who's at
fault for a loss of life.
You believe her
testimony on that case
will help us reach that goal?
I do.
Then the prosecution's
objection is overruled.
I appreciate it, Your Honor.
[PHOENIX]
Dollie...
[PAYNE whines]
[MIA] All right, now that I've
tied the two crimes together,
I need to stay on the offensive.
I've got this!
Excellent move, Ms. Fey.
I finally understand why you
were so hell-bent on taking on
this particular case.
I had my reasons.
Oh. This kind of spunk
lights a fire inside me!
Go on and take no prisoners!
Give 'em hell!
Right!
Things are about to get real!
I'll make you proud.
Just watch me!
Now, Miss Hawthorne,
you know what's expected of you.
Tell us about the events
of eight months ago.
That day, I was
meeting with the lawyer
in the cafeteria downstairs
to discuss something.
I left my seat briefly,
just for a moment,
and that's when it happened.
When I came back to the table.
I found him lying prone
on the floor.
You say you left your
seat for "just a moment."
How long was it, exactly?
If I were to
guess at a specific time?
Ten to 20 minutes.
[MIA] Why did you leave
and where did you go?
[gasps]
Well, I, uh...
Huh. There are some things a
lady doesn't need to divulge.
Anyway, the police
investigated her back then,
so this line of
questioning is redundant.
I concur.
[DAHLIA]
According to the constabulary,
they discovered some traces of
a lethal poison in the coffee.
Supposedly,
a special kind of poison.
What does that mean?
[DAHLIA]
Well. They said it was purified
through a very unique
chemical process.
I'd like to point
out this young lady
studies literature,
not advanced chemistry.
Right. Anyway,
once the authorities arrived.
I was thoroughly
frisked for evidence.
What? No way!
Those swine! How dare they?
[coughs]
Obviously, they
didn't find any poison on me.
Nothing. So that
proves my innocence!
She's right!
My Dollie is the most
innocent girl I've ever met!
About this poison.
Do you happen to know how
large a dose he was given?
I don't.
Sorry, they didn't tell me.
Oh. Ms. Fey.
According to the officer I spoke
with, it was a liquid poison.
Small enough to be contained
inside an eyedropper bottle.
That's not very much at all.
[JUDGE]
After the incident,
the entire courthouse was turned
upside down in the search.
But unfortunately,
there was no small vessel
like that to be found
anywhere in the building.
[PAYNE]
So, no trace of it?
[CROWD gasping]
[MIA]
By the way. If you would...
Can you tell us what
you were here to discuss
with the lawyer that day?
It was in regard to an
incident that I was swept up in
when I was just a little girl.
For some reason he
wanted to talk to me about it.
Will you share with the
court what that incident was?
Objection!
Whatever it is, I'm sure it has
absolutely nothing to do
with this trial, Your Honor!
Objection sustained.
The defense's question
will hereby be stricken
from the record.
[MIA] You seem to get
"swept up," as you say,
in a fair number of
incidents, right?
When you were younger,
eight months ago,
and now, this one.
Looking at the
specifics of that case,
the tragedy with the lawyer
occurred on the 27th of August
this past year.
You certainly have
had an abundance of misfortune.
Yes, that's true.
Sometimes, I feel like I must've
been born under a bad sign.
[PHOENIX wails]
Oh. My. What's wrong with you?
August 27th?
That was our day of destiny!
Meaning what exactly?
That was the day
Dollie and I first embarked
upon our love journey together,
inside this courthouse!
[JUDGE gasping]
[DAHLIA growls]
You remember
that magical moment!
Right, babe?
When we first met down in
the basement reading room?
Feenie. Not now.
That's between us.
You met Miss
Hawthorne down there?
You bet!
I was studying in the reading
room when my angel descended.
My soul mate was sent to me
straight from Heaven!
The moment we
laid eyes on each other,
the air itself became electric!
We're living proof
of love at first sight!
And she is so generous!
She gave me this
pendant right then!
A symbol of our undying love!
She took one
look at me and said,
"I want you to have this."
And she shyly took it off
her neck and put it on mine!
Oh, wow. So she gave
this to you that very day?
--Just on a whim?
--She did!
It fills me with so much joy,
I show it to everyone I meet.
Joy is contagious,
and I'm trying to spread
--as much as I can.
--[DAHLIA] Feenie, I said...
But she gets
embarrassed so darn easily.
So every time that
we've met up lately,
she tries to make me
give it back to her.
Give it back?
But it was a gift, right?
Huh. Seems odd to me.
Ha! Well, she's definitely
a one-in-a-million girl!
Even on the day I met Doug,
she was like, "Give it back!"
and I was like, "But I'm
so proud of our love!"
Feenie, stop!
[gasps]
[DAHLIA growls]
Enough! I will have order!
Ah! [coughs]
Let go! [coughs]
[gasps]
[MIA]
Eight months ago,
Dahlia Hawthorne left
her seat at the table,
and my colleague
collapsed onto the floor.
That same day, she met
Mister Wright in this building,
and gave him a strange pendant.
It's perfectly clear to me now.
[JUDGE]
Hmm? Well, that makes one of us.
Your Honor,
I know what happened
eight months ago.
And the one who
poisoned that cup of coffee...
...was this woman,
Dahlia Hawthorne.
No, that's impossible.
Remember? The police patted
me down and searched me.
Of course, they didn't
find any trace of poison.
What's more...
The poison container was nowhere
to be found in the courthouse.
You have no evidence
to support this claim!
Because all you had
to do was hide the container.
Somewhere they
wouldn't think to look for it.
[DAHLIA growls]
[PAYNE]
But they searched everywhere!
Right? Every corner.
High and low.
Tell us. Just where
did she hide it?
[MIA]
This is a pivotal moment.
I've reached the
point of no return.
That day, after you had
poisoned the lawyer's coffee,
you left your seat, so you could
go and dispose of the evidence.
Immediately afterward,
by some miracle of fate,
in the basement
of this courthouse,
you met your new boyfriend.
[gasps]
Uh, what? Hang on.
[MIA]
But in truth...
What she'd really found
on that eventful day,
was the perfect hiding place.
Somebody completely unrelated.
A person the cops
would never think to search.
A rube.
That man is right there.
Phoenix Wright.
[PHOENIX]
Uhh...
What? No... Don't tell me!
Hidden in the pendant?
There is a very
high likelihood it contains
the same deadly poison.
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
If you look at it closely,
you can see there is still some
liquid remaining in the bottle.
It must be analyzed at once!
[screams]
[CROWD murmuring]
[JUDGE]
Order! Order, please!
Calm yourselves!
Now, what's going on here?
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
On behalf of
sweet Dollie, I object!
Wait! Seriously?
[JUDGE] I warned you,
defendant! Get back!
Ah! No! It's not right!
My girlfriend would never
do anything like that!
But how can you be so sure?
First off... Because...
I mean, there's no way
she could've whipped up
some kind of specialized poison.
Yeah! Right!
It took knowledge of advanced
chemical processes to purify it!
Dollie's an artist.
She would have no idea
how to go about that!
Sorry. All she had to do
was know where to find it.
[gasps]
[MIA] Just think. What was
the victim's field of study?
It was pharmacology, remember?
If she could access his lab,
she could then procure all
manner of poisonous chemicals.
[PHOENIX gasps]
Mister Wright,
I ask that you please
hand over that pendant.
If we can analyze it,
you could leave this courtroom
as a free man.
[PHOENIX groans]
What do you say?
[PHOENIX]
What do you think?
I say...
There's no freaking way!
[wails, sobs]
[PAYNE]
Where could he be going?!
[JUDGE] Bailiffs! Don't
let him leave the building!
The boy's gone nuts.
Is he pleading insanity?
What is he thinking?
What kind of fool
tries to flee a courtroom?
Have you no sense, boy?
[PHOENIX]
I'm sorry, sir...
[banging]
[PAYNE]
If apologies worked in court,
all of us would be out of a job!
Anyway.
Mister Wright, will you please
hand over the pendant?
[PHOENIX grunts]
[MIA]
You do have it, correct?
[PHOENIX sighs]
I'm sorry!
Uh... [gasps] Sorry for what?
[PHOENIX sighs]
For... eating it.
[BOTH sigh]
--Huh?
--[MIA] What did he say?!
[PHOENIX]
Yeah. It was too big.
So I had to break it into
little pieces and chew it.
[groans]
You... did... what...?
[wails]
[screams]
[PHOENIX sobs]
Mr. Wright! Are you okay?!
That botttle--
There was poison in it!
[DAHLIA cackles] I bet
you're really disappointed
that he didn't die, huh?
Aren't you, hag?
[MIA gasps]
Because...
the fact he's alive
proves there wasn't
any poison in there.
[MIA] But that tiny little bit
that was left probably
wasn't enough to do anything.
And besides...
It has been eight months!
Maybe it lost its potency!
Think so?
[MIA gulps]
[DAHLIA chuckles] Talking down
to me without proof I've done
anything wrong must
be an old lady thing.
Yeah. Wouldn't
you agree, grandpa?
Huh? Uh... I guess.
In any case...
Right now, the victim is dead.
The pendant is inside
the defendant's belly.
You don't have any decisive
evidence against Miss Hawthorne.
Or do you, defense?
[MIA growls]
You're here
to defend your client.
Trusting him is
the noble thing to do.
It's actually rather
heartwarming to see
how much faith
you've put in the boy.
[PHOENIX gasps]
[PAYNE] But! The prosecution
is no different!
I would trust my very
life on Miss Hawthorne's word!
I take her testimony
as absolute truth!
Which is why I state
without fear of reproach
that your deduction
was pure fantasy.
Well. I'm done.
What a total waste of my time.
Can someone remind me who
started this whole witch hunt,
and tried to drag a completely
unrelated case into this one?
I was under the
impression we were here today
to solve Dougie's murder.
Am I wrong? Old hag.
[PHOENIX]
Whoa. Dollie...?
[MIA]
I've almost got her.
I can't let her just
stroll out of here,
but I have to find the
evidence to nail her.
It seems you've
reached a dead end.
[MIA growls]
Please, Mister Wright!
The truth. You need
to start telling the truth!
Not the lies she fed you!
I know you're better than this.
You can be a voice for justice!
[PHOENIX]
I... don't know.
The time has come for you
to start doing what's right,
Mister Wright! We can't find
the truth without your help!
[PHOENIX]
Me? Really? You need my help?
Very well.
Now that the cloud of suspicion
surrounding Miss Hawthorne
has been cleared up, the line
of questioning regarding
old cases will come to an en--
Hold it, judge!
[gasping
[PHOENIX]
I'm so sorry, Ms. Fey.
You believed in me and
were willing to stake
your reputation on my word.
I've let you down...
Mister Wright...
[PHOENIX]
But I can't keep this up.
I need to tell you
what really happened.
It's not what you said?
Feenie. Careful.
[PHOENIX]
Mm-mm. Sorry, Dollie.
I'm done lying.
I can't keep covering for you.
Ugh! Feenie!
Your time is up!
It's his turn to testify!
[DAHLIA growls]
I'll tell you
everything I know
about what happened that day.
The day Doug Swallow
was murdered.
[DOUG] Listen, man.
You should stop seeing her.
[PHOENIX] What?
How is our relationship
any of your business?
Please, this is
for your own sake.
She's bad news, and
that's putting it lightly.
[PHOENIX growls]
You're lying!
[DOUG] There's something you
need to know about her.
Before you get hurt.
She stole poison
from our lab and I'm scared
of what she'll do with it.
No. Seriously?
[DOUG] Mm-hmm.
Look, she's done it before.
Eight months ago,
a drug sample came up missing.
We noticed it immediately
after she dropped by the lab.
I know it was her.
Without a doubt!
[PHOENIX gasps]
Shut your mouth!
She's not like that!
There's no way!
[DOUG grunts]
[PAYNE]
Bah. What rubbish!
[MIA] Did Mister Swallow
really tell you all of that?
[DAHLIA] You're full of it!
That's a lie and you know it!
[PHOENIX]
After I pushed him,
I got out of there as fast
as I possibly could.
But I got worried, so I came
back a little bit later.
And I saw Dollie
kneeling over him.
[CROWD gasping]
[DAHLIA growls]
[DAHLIA gasps]
[gasps]
[PHOENIX gasps]
But she told me
that I had to swear on my life
that I wouldn't tell anybody.
I'm so sorry!
[MIA] I knew it. She stole
that poison eight months ago.
And now she's done it again.
I can win this.
With his testimony,
I can finally make the link
between the two cases.
[MIA] The night before Doug
Swallow's young life
was tragically cut short,
Dahlia Hawthorne stole
poison from his lab.
Her motive was simple.
She committed the
theft because murder
was next on her agenda.
To poison someone?
What? That's ridiculous!
Doug Swallow's cause of
death was electrocution!
He wasn't the person
she intended to poison.
Huh? Then who?
We know. That there
was a certain item
that you desperately wanted to
get back into your possession.
Even if it meant
killing someone.
Wait, you mean...
Ah... Dollie...
I'm sorry.
But I'm afraid the one
Dahlia Hawthorne
was trying to poison...
...is here.
Her boyfriend, Phoenix Wright!
[PHOENIX gasps]
[wails]
[PHOENIX]
My sweet Dollie...
She really... was
trying to kill me?
Objection!
Enough with all this poppycock!
Miss Hawthorne is clearly
in love with this man!
Yes. Madly in love!
I'd never hurt my Feenie.
How could you say that?
It's sick.
Eight months ago, after
you poisoned that coffee,
you had yet another
nefarious goal on your mind.
Getting rid of the evidence.
The pendant with the poison
bottle had to be disposed of.
Miss Hawthorne
put her wiles to good use.
She found someone
who'd gladly take it from her.
However...
There was one big problem
she didn't account for.
Her love-struck mark refused
to give back her "gift."
[PHOENIX gasps]
Mister Wright, excuse me,
but have you wondered
why she fell so hard
for you that day,
and why you've stayed
together all this time?
[PHOENIX]
Well, because she...
[MIA]
She was after something.
She wanted the pendant back.
[PHOENIX gasps]
She got close to you for
that crucial piece of evidence.
Her "gift" for a man
she didn't know.
To you, it was a treasure.
A symbol of true love,
and something you shared
with anyone who'd look.
So... you mean...
The only reason
she dated him was...
To get it back, even if it
meant she had to murder him.
[PHOENIX] No. It's because
we were in love, right?
Ugh. Moron. Would you
get out of the way already?
Dumb boy, how could
any woman ever count on you
to take care of things for her?
I don't know how many times
I told you to keep
your big mouth shut about me.
You're worthless!
[PHOENIX gasps]
Uh... Witness?
Ah, I can tell
you plan on making me out
to be a murderer
no matter what I say.
You've done it to yourself.
It's all on you.
Oh, is it now?
You have nothing concrete on me.
You're screwed, because
this blubbering little man-child
took your best piece of
evidence and gobbled it up.
You have no proof, and you
still have the nerve to treat me
like I'm some sort of
homicidal maniac?
I've wasted enough
of my time here,
so I'll be taking my leave.
[JUDGE]
Uhh, we're not done yet.
[DAHLIA] Your Honor. I trust
you'll discipline this nasty,
overzealous old hag
appropriately, won't you?
[MIA]
Hold it!
For what? Did you find
your decisive evidence?
I refuse to let a person
like you walk free.
[MARVIN]
Careful, Mia.
If you keep badgering
the witness like this,
you could be forced to pay
the ultimate price for it.
And what do you mean by that?
He means the penalty
could entail you being
permanently stripped
of your badge.
What? Really?
It's the truth.
You'd be even more washed up.
[MIA] If I don't back off,
I could be putting
my career in jeopardy.
But I swore to fight for
justice and uphold the law.
What good is this badge if
I abandon the fight so easily?
Very well. I order
the defense to present
any evidence it has
against Miss Hawthorne.
Yes, Your Honor.
You stupid old cow.
[MIA] The key to this whole
thing is that poison
she stole from the lab.
And for me, it's do or die!
C'mon, Mia!
[DAHLIA] I've read a
lot of books in my time
studying literature, but you
going down in flames is
going to be one of
my favorite stories.
Maybe I'll write about it.
I believe in you, Miss Fey.
There is irrefutable evidence
of Dahlia Hawthorne's crime.
And I have it. Remember this?
It's what kills colds dead.
This bottle of Coldkiller Z
the victim was holding.
Don't make me laugh.
That's your "killer" proof, huh?
Perhaps our rookie
defense lawyer
isn't feeling well either.
[MIA]
I'm fine.
But no matter how I felt,
I wouldn't be taking this.
Especially not
this particular bottle.
'Cause this stuff, will
kill more than just a cold.
[CROWD gasping]
[PAYNE]
Wait. You think it's poisoned?
[DAHLIA growls]
Do you recall the
defendant's testimony?
[PHOENIX] I'd been trying
to kill this cold with it,
but I ended up losing the
bottle somewhere that day.
I could swear I had it
on me till lunchtime, at least.
Lunchtime.
That's when Miss Hawthorne
made off with his bottle
of Coldkiller Z.
She knew he would take it.
So she laced it with poison.
Bunk. Utter claptrap.
If that's true,
how do you explain
why the victim
was holding the bottle?
[MIA] Think back to the crime
that happened eight months ago.
Where did she hide the
evidence after that went down?
[JUDGE] And where
would that be, defense?
[MIA] In that instance, the
poison was inside her pendant.
Which she made sure to quickly
pass along to someone else.
The boy she ran
into in the reading room--
Phoenix Wright.
She used a
similar tactic in this case
with Mister Swallow.
My client says he left
the scene immediately
after he shoved the victim.
She had seen
and heard everything.
The argument,
Mister Swallow's accusation.
She watched as he was shoved.
She also saw the
severed electrical cable.
She realized the victim
would not remain silent
about her crimes.
So she decided to use
the cable to guarantee
he wouldn't tell anybody else.
[JUDGE] If that's the case,
then what do you make
of the testimony she
gave the court earlier?
[MIA] Nothing but
a well-rehearsed lie.
[PAYNE]
How could she have done it?
[MIA] Well, she is
a rather frail little thing,
so it would take her some
time to move Swallow's body
to where she needed it.
Which explains the time
discrepancy in the testimony.
The ten minutes between
the cable falling and his death.
[PHOENIX gasps]
At this point.
Another problem arose
for Miss Hawthorne.
The defendant, who she'd seen
leaving the scene, came back.
Also, because
of the power outage,
the students in the lab
came out to investigate.
Which caused her to panic.
After all,
she was carrying something she
did not want to be caught with.
The bottle of
poisoned cold medicine.
The police had
frisked her before,
what if they did it again?
It was the same situation
she'd been in the last time.
And so she did what worked
so well for her eight months
earlier in the courthouse.
She passed it off.
And placed it
in the victim's hand!
[DAHLIA]
Ugh. This is so stupid.
If you think anybody would
believe this, you're crazy.
Wouldn't you agree?
Uh. Yeah.
The defense has
gotten desperate.
Don't worry, it's just drivel
and nothing more.
[MIA]
Objection!
As a matter of fact,
I feel quite confident.
However, speaking
of desperation.
Miss Hawthorne.
Are you willing to take
this cold medicine?
[gasps]
Mister Wright ate
that little pendant of yours.
Care to do the same with this?
If it's not poisoned,
then what would be the harm?
[DAHLIA growls]
You've testified to the
court about your innocence.
So, why don't you take
this chance to prove it?
Right here and now!
[DAHLIA snarling]
[DAHLIA, demonic voice]
Mia... Mia...
Fey...
Mia Fey!
[MIA grunts]
[demonic] Do you believe you
can take me down forever?
[cackles]
Okay, fine. You stupid hag.
Enjoy it while you can.
[normal voice] I suppose I can
allow you to claim victory
this time around.
[gasps]
Just know... This won't
be the last you see of me.
You and I will meet again.
Of that, I'm certain.
I must be going now.
Off to spend some time
with the boys in blue.
I wish you the best of luck.
You'll need it
[PHOENIX gasps]
[MIA]
Finally, it's over.
[banging
[gasps]
No, this is a total
miscarriage of justice!
You failed to present
a drop of proof against her!
If you believe that...
I should ask you.
Would you like to try
a sample of this medicine?
Huh?
[MIA] If she's as
innocent as you claim,
surely, there's nothing
harmful in this bottle.
It may even clear your sinuses.
Oh. Well, uh...
I don't really care
to right now.
But going off
of what you said earlier,
I thought you would bet your
very life Miss Hawthorne's word
was the absolute truth.
Huh?
Well, "Rookie Killer"?
Why don't you show this
rookie how it's really done?
Do you still abide by
your previous assertion
of trust in her?
If you're really willing
to put your life on the line.
Just how much
is that life worth?
Please, no!
This can't be happening!
Not my beautiful pompadour!
It's flying right off my head!
[groans]
Defense.
I have a sneaking suspicion you
may harbor some sort of grudge
against Miss Hawthorne.
[gasps] Your Honor. My feelings
had nothing to do with this.
Very well, then.
If there is no further testimony
to be heard today,
the court is ready to
hand down the verdict
for Mister Phoenix Wright.
Not guilty!
[CROWD cheers]
[PHOENIX]
Dollie...
I declare this
court to be adjourned!
[MARVIN] Great work!
Quite masterfully done!
I appreciate that.
Thanks, Mister Grossberg.
This case really made
me think about something.
Just how crucial it is to
have a client relationship
that is built on mutual trust.
Heh. Congratulations,
Mister Wright.
You know... I've
been doing some thinking, too.
About what?
Was that really her?
Have I been that
naïve this entire time?
Huh?
The girl I loved...
She would never have said and
done all those terrible things.
[MIA sighs]
It's tough, but learn from
this and move on.
I know. You're right.
Let me ask you this.
About your job--
Lawyers help people out whenever
they're in trouble, right?
Well, that's my
personal philosophy.
Nice.
I've been taking law classes
and it's got me thinking.
If I become a lawyer
there's a friend I could help.
After meeting you,
I've made up my mind.
Oh, really?
I have! I'll study hard.
I'm gonna be a lawyer for sure!
And maybe someday--
You and I will meet again
in the courtroom!
[MIA]
Hmm. Yeah.
[heart monitor beeping]
[MIA] I finally settled the
score for you, like I promised.
I'll be back.
[PHOENIX] It's been five years
since that case was closed.
[PHOENIX]
I did become a lawyer.
And I even helped my old friend.
But... Mia's no longer with us.
She's in a better place.
Even though she's gone,
she's here in other ways.
And I can always
hear her in my mind.
[MIA]
Phoenix.
Remember to always believe in
your client, no matter what.
The power of that trust
will guide you through
the toughest cases.
Like a light in the darkness.
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
A broken shell weaves
a tale of memories
from Mia to Maya to now.
Little Pearl's journey
through her past
is about to begin.
Wait! I can't let her go alone!
I gotta go with her!
Look for a new shell,
solve the mystery,
and carve a path to the future!
For the first time,
Pearl and I are gonna have
an adventure together.
Let's hit the road!
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Next Episode: "Hear the
Waves of Turnabout!"
Take that!