[PHOENIX] Illustrator Elise
Deauxnim was murdered
at Hazakura Temple,
an idyllic retreat where spirit
mediums come to train.
But the first day of
her suspected killer's trial
ended with more
questions than answers.
Further investigation
revealed secrets
about the murder.
Firstly, the crime took place
at the remote Inner Temple,
not on the grounds
of the main Temple.
Also, the victim was,
in fact, Misty Fey.
Maya and Mia's mother who had
not been seen in 17 years.
And, Iris was the twin
sister of Dahlia Hawthorne,
who just last month had been
executed for her crimes.
The most bone chilling
truth uncovered, though,
was that little Pearl played
an unwitting accomplice
in her aunt's murder.
The one pulling the strings
behind this fiendish plot
was her mother, Morgan Fey.
Her objective was to
wipe out the main bloodline
of the Kurain School.
And throughout all of this,
Maya has been trapped
in the sacred cavern.
Oh. I hope she's okay!
So, it's still locked?
And poor Mystic Maya is still
trapped in the Sacred Cavern?
[PHOENIX] Mm-hmm. But Iris
is working hard to open
all those trick locks, so...
[MILES] If you're talking
about Sister Iris,
she's here at the courthouse.
Wait, what's she doing here?
Discussing her testimony
with the prosecution team.
Really? She's taking the stand?
Um, sir? Mystic Maya...
Is she okay?
Don't you worry.
We have somebody else working on
the locks while Iris is here.
Who's that?
Franziska is there.
She chose not to sleep
and has been at it all night
with guidance
from sister Bikini.
[PHOENIX gasps]
So, the trial today.
Someone else is handling it.
Godot, I believe?
[PHOENIX sighs]
I was afraid of that.
[MILES] Hmph. I'm going now. I
suppose the rest is up to you...
...partner.
Right. I came here to win!
[PEARL sighs]
[PHOENIX] I'm walking headfirst
into the final showdown!
This is for you, Maya!
Good morning.
Court is now back in session
for the trial of Sister Iris.
Hang on. Why are you here?
My little brother had a fever
so bad he fainted from it,
so I'll be hearing the case.
[PHOENIX]
They're brothers. Ahh.
Prosecutor Godot,
your opening statement, please.
[GODOT] One's heart can change
as the clouds move overhead.
In this mixed-up world,
there's only one constant.
There's a darkness underneath.
Complex and bitter. But still...
...tasty.
[PHOENIX] Can you just
say it in plain English?
To put it more simply,
I'm announcing that
the prosecution's plans
have changed.
In earlier proceedings.
the accused refused to admit
she had a role in the crime.
But as the clouds have shifted,
she's had a change of heart.
[gasps]
And her confession today
will illuminate what was
once shrouded in darkness.
[PHOENIX]
Confession?
Why couldn't she have told me
about this last night?
[PEARL gasps]
[GODOT] Besides my curiosity,
the present situation requires
that I ask your name
and occupation.
Yes, my name is Iris.
And I am but a simple nun
serving at the Hazakura Temple.
Iris. What do you
need to confess?
I hope you'll forgive me.
But I can no longer
continue to lie to everyone.
The truth is, I did have
a hand in this terrible tragedy.
[JUDGE gasps] Young lady,
please explain yourself.
Are you confessing to the
murder of Ms. Elise Deauxnim?
Not that, but I did play
a major part in the cover-up.
[PHOENIX gasps]
What cover up?
I gathered her lifeless body,
and transported it to
the main temple's courtyard.
Then... I desecrated it.
[PHOENIX gasps]
[JUDGE]
And this was all your doing?
[IRIS]
Yes. I did it to cover for her.
Hold on a second!
What's that mean?
Who are you covering for?
[IRIS]
Someone who I had to protect.
Even if it meant putting my
own freedom in jeopardy.
It was the Master
of the Kurain School
of channeling's daughter,
Mystic Maya Fey.
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
No! That's insane!
She's no killer. You're lying!
[JUDGE]
Overruled.
We must let the witness
give her testimony, defense.
[PHOENIX growls]
That night, I did go over
to the Inner Temple
to relieve Sister Bikini
for a while and assist
Mystic Maya with
her training as well.
[PHOENIX] But in your previous
testimony, you told the court
that you never went to
the Inner Temple that night!
I did, but that's
because I was lying
in order to protect Mystic Maya.
After she had finished
preparations for her training,
she passed through the garden.
Then, Elise showed up out of
nowhere and just started
attacking her with her staff!
[MAYA gasps]
[IRIS]
As Maya stumbled away in terror,
Elise threw the staff
down in the snow,
and pulled a dagger
from her robe.
[MAYA gasps]
[IRIS] Maya desperately tried to
take control of the situation
and stole the weapon
from her hands.
[MAYA whimpers]
She was only
trying to defend herself!
--[CROWD gasping]
--[PHOENIX] Hmm...
[IRIS] Elise was going
to kill her in cold blood!
That's why I did it.
All I wanted to do was
protect poor Mystic Maya!
And if you moved
the body across the gorge
to the Hazakura Temple,
nobody would suspect
that Maya was involved.
I'd say you brewed
up a pretty solid plan.
[PHOENIX]
Iris... I can't imagine
what your true motivation
must be with this,
but your testimony has
one glaring contradiction.
[gasps]
Elise would not have
thrown her staff aside
to attack. This thing
has its own secret.
[IRIS gasps]
[gasping]
My god! Is that blood?
[PEARL gasps]
Defense. Can you tell us
whose blood that is?
[PHOENIX] There's a sample
being analyzed as we speak.
But Sister Iris testified that
Elise threw this sword away
in favor of a dagger,
which makes no sense!
It's compounded by the
simple fact that Elise Deauxnim
would never try to
murder Maya Fey!
[GODOT]
How can you be sure?
I say "Elise Deauxnim,"
but that was just
a clever pseudonym.
Her real name was Misty Fey.
[CROWD gasping]
Misty Fey?
[gasps]
It can't be!
Master of the Kurain school.
A woman who'd been
neither seen nor heard from
in well over 15 years.
And what's more...
Besides being Kurain's master,
she was also Maya Fey's mother!
[JUDGE]
Are you serious?
No way... There's no way...
What?! Mystic Misty?!
[PHOENIX] Why would she
try to kill her daughter,
who she hadn't seen
in so many years?
There's just no reason!
You can't give me a single one!
--[screams]
--[CROWD gasping]
[JUDGE]
Order! Order in this court!
[GODOT] Well... Who can
really say with family?
But when we went back
and investigated the garden
of the Inner Temple, we
discovered something that
backs up the sister's testimony.
The tip is completely
covered in blood.
Forensics is processing
a sample from this as well.
I see. Are you saying this
was the murder weapon?
[GODOT] That is what
the prosecution believes.
[PHOENIX growls]
[JUDGE]
This crime scene photo.
There's something
rather odd about it.
Why was the snow cleared
out around the lantern?
[PHOENIX sighs]
[JUDGE] And there seems
to be something scrawled
on the lantern itself.
[GODOT]
Huh?
[JUDGE] My goodness!
It looks like a bloody message!
Like someone wrote
"Maya" backwards.
See? I wasn't lying!
After Elise was stabbed, she
reached out behind her and wrote
the killer's name
in her own blood!
There's the proof!
[PHOENIX]
Crap! I forgot all about that!
[GODOT]
Hold it! Hang on just a minute.
What are you all seeing?
There are backwards letters
written on the stone?
It's right in front
of our faces.
The center of the frame.
[GODOT grunts]
Nonsense.
Do you really expect me to
believe that there's something
written on that thing?
[PHOENIX gasps]
[PHOENIX] Is he joking,
or can he not see it?
[JUDGE]
Regardless, this is a very
important clue, Prosecutor.
What do you say?
[GODOT growls]
[JUDGE]
Prosecutor Godot?
Yeah. O-Okay, witness.
Shall we move on?
[PHOENIX] He looks like he's
sweating bullets over there.
When it was done,
I fulfilled my duty.
I believed the most important
thing was to protect
the future master
of the Kurain School.
And so we decided I would
use the snowmobile to move
the body to the main temple.
[GODOT] Yeah. There were
clear snowmobile tracks
leading from Dusky Bridge
to Hazakura Temple.
Did you just say
that the tracks were clear?
Oh, yes.
By the time I carried
her body to the bridge.
The snow had already
stopped falling.
[PHOENIX]
So there was no more snow?
Are you absolutely certain?
[IRIS] Uh... Yes.
There's no doubt in my mind.
Objection!
[IRIS screams]
[PHOENIX] That statement
is patently false!
[gasps]
That night,
the snow didn't stop
falling until 10:50 PM.
But at 10:45,
an exceptionally noteworthy
event took place.
What are you talking about?
Oh, yeah.
[IRIS gasps]
You have to ask?
Gotta say, I'm surprised
you didn't know.
That's when the lightning
strike hit the bridge!
Uh, lightning strike?
So there's no way you
moved the body like you claim!
--I--
--[PHOENIX] No.
Because by that time,
Dusky Bridge was already
consumed by flames!
[gasps]
In other words,
this means your testimony is a
complete and utter fabrication!
[IRIS whimpers]
[shrieks]
[CROWD murmuring]
[PHOENIX] She's trying to
frame Maya for the murder.
What I wanna know... is why?
[CROWD murmuring]
Young lady. Lying under
oath is a serious crime!
You can be charged
with contempt of court!
The snow stopped
five minutes after
the lightning strike?
Pfft. Don't make me laugh.
The weather in the mountains is
as fickle as a maiden's heart.
It can unexpectedly
change from one moment
to the next.
He's right, you know!
Just like a maiden's heart!
Oh, you have
gotta be kidding me!
The point is, on the
night of the murder,
the victim's body was indeed
moved to Hazakura Temple.
That fact is not in contention.
But can you provide
a better explanation
for how it got there?
[IRIS] Yeah! Or are you
trying to tell us her corpse
jumped across the burning
bridge on its own?
[PHOENIX] I don't know
what happened exactly.
But the body did make it
across the ravine somehow.
Think of something.
[JUDGE] The bridge was
definitely burned to a crisp.
And it would appear that one
of the suspension wires is gone.
[PHOENIX gasps]
[PHOENIX] Is that it?
Could that be what happened?
No answer, huh?
If you have no explanation,
then it's abundantly clear that
you don't have a leg to stand on
when you call
Sister Iris a liar!
Objection!
[GODOT grunts]
[screams]
A corpse jumping
over a burning bridge
seems impossible.
But believe it or not...
...it could happen.
[GODOT] Tch. Do you really
believe that's possible?
Well... Okay.
What I can't swallow is
how you'd back that up.
It's not all that difficult.
Don't forget...
...we do have
eyewitness testimony.
What do you mean?
[PHOENIX] I'm gonna have to
bulldoze my way through this.
It was Laurice Deauxnim!
Right? A potentially
brilliant artist!
Brilliant?
He's... an artist?
Uh, don't see it.
[CROWD murmuring]
[PHOENIX] Ahem.
On the night of the murder,
he was staying in
a cabin very close by.
And from there,
he witnessed the
moment in question.
I don't follow you. When?
Look here. He actually drew
exactly what he saw that night.
It's all on the page
in front of us!
Defense. Are you proposing that
this rendering is accurate?
And these scribbles
prove the victim
literally flew through the air?
Yes!
[GODOT] Hmph. You've
brewed up a full pot.
You expect us to drink it down?
The truth is here!
You can see it clearly.
If you just change
your perspective!
[GODOT]
Hmph. Spoon feed me, would ya?
Just tell me what I'm
supposed to be seeing here.
The piece of art
that Laurice Deauxnim
created that night... couldn't
be more of a contradiction!
[gasping]
We're quite aware of that!
Your Honor, I think
you misunderstand me.
Take a look at this photo.
The suspension
wires are below the bridge.
But here, in this sketch,
they appear to be
above the entire thing!
[JUDGE] Hmm... Perhaps the
artist just saw it wrong?
I think he probably
just drew it wrong.
I think that you're
just wrong in the head.
He drew it like he saw it.
So there has to be a reason for
this difference in perspective.
[gasps]
[PHOENIX] According to
the court transcript,
he was in the cabin
nearby, as he puts it,
"cranking out a true work
of art, in my dreams."
His dreams? Huh.
At that moment,
lightning shot from the sky
and set the bridge aflame.
The whole thing happened
right before his eyes.
However...
...he was lying on his back!
--[gasps]
--So what?
The fiery scene
that he saw that night
was actually upside down!
[GODOT] Heh. So that's what you
meant when you said we needed
to "change our perspective."
This looks quite different.
The victim's body isn't
flying above the bridge.
It's clearly swinging
underneath it!
You see? Just like a pendulum!
[GODOT]
Objection!
Dusky Bridge is about
20 meters long, you know?
So where would somebody
just conveniently find
a rope to swing across it?
One couldn't be closer.
[GODOT]
What?!
[PHOENIX]
Don't you see it?
[JUDGE]
The broken suspension wire?
[gasps]
When lightning
struck the bridge that night,
one of the suspension
wires began to come loose
from its anchor point.
The culprit noticed this,
tied the body to it...
...and then swung it across.
[GODOT growls]
[PHOENIX] They were completely
hell-bent on getting
the body over to
the main temple.
But still...
Since they couldn't
cross a burning bridge.
This "pendulum" method
was the only way
they could make that happen.
[growls]
[gulping]
[coughs]
[JUDGE]
Order! Order in the court!
[IRIS]
Mister Wright!
Do you have any proof that
the culprit did such a thing?
Or are you just guessing?
[PHOENIX]
Of course there's proof.
It's right here. The police
said the corpse was covered
with bruises consistent
with a high fall.
After swinging over the gorge,
the body crashed to the ground.
The resulting impact...
...knocked this crystal
orb from the staff.
[JUDGE] I believe the defense
has shown a plausible theory.
Explaining how the
victim's body was moved.
[GODOT]
Objection!
[PHOENIX]
Uh...
This cold cup of coffee
should help lower
your temperature a little bit.
Uh... What are you doing?
[GODOT] A half-brewed deduction,
and still quite bitter, Trite.
You see, you forgot something.
[PHOENIX gasps]
Yeah? What?
If the perpetrator swung
the body over like you say,
then one might assume somebody
on the other side caught it.
[PHOENIX gasps]
Meaning they had an accomplice.
Tell the court, Mister Blight.
Who was there
to receive the body?
"Who was there?"
Obviously... It could
only be you, Iris.
Uh... It's me?
[PHOENIX] The only way
to transport the body from
Dusky Bridge was by snowmobile.
Objection! Were you
listening to her testimony?
This cutie pie was
helping Maya Fey.
Cleaning up the crime scene
at the inner temple.
Which means...
...she must've been the one who
sent the body swinging across.
You're the one who
hasn't been listening.
Sister Iris was later
seen at Hazakura Temple.
And she admitted
to taking the body
to the courtyard
to fake the crime scene.
[CROWD gasping]
[JUDGE]
Hmm... This is quite puzzling.
It's almost as if the defendant
was in two different places
at the same time.
No objections!
[gasping]
Uh... None? Really?
Right. On the
night of the murder,
there were, in fact,
two Irises on the scene.
I gotta hear
your reasoning. Go on.
To be more precise,
there was a pair of twins.
--Your Honor!
--[JUDGE] Hmm?
[PHOENIX] Think back to
a big case from years ago.
Does she look familiar?
[JUDGE]
Hmm.
Hmm?
[gasps]
Wait! Could it really be her?
Yes. Her twin sister
is the murderer--
Dahlia Hawthorne.
[CROWD gasping]
Objection!
Some strange brew.
Considering Dahlia Hawthorne
was recently executed.
[PHOENIX] Yeah. I heard that it
was carried out last month.
Uh, she was?
Yes, she's gone!
My sister's no longer
of this world!
Not completely true.
[gasping]
Seriously.
You of all people
should understand that.
It's in your family.
You're part of the
bloodline that makes up
the Kurain School of Channeling.
--[gasps]
--[CROWD murmuring]
What? Channeling?
[PHOENIX] By the way, why
didn't you mention it earlier?
That the body was
moved by pendulum?
[IRIS gulps]
Well, because...
I, uh... I honestly had
no idea about that.
It's true. I really didn't know.
[PHOENIX]
It's obvious that you did know.
Because you were the one
who received the body.
[IRIS whimpers]
[PHOENIX] Something has
felt off to me today.
A few things, really.
Your sudden confession,
and your attempts to frame
Maya out of nowhere.
[sighs] I believe you're
not actually Sister Iris.
[gasps]
It's strange.
Because I thought the day
would never come when
we'd see each other again...
...Dahlia Hawthorne.
[growls]
But... I thought she was dead.
Didn't you just say
she was executed?
Yes. This woman is not
Dahlia Hawthorne in the flesh.
[gasps]
She's currently
serving as a vessel.
Dahlia's spirit is inside her.
She's been channeled!
But... Can that really be true?
[CROWD gasping]
Everything is spelled
out here in these instructions.
Dahlia Hawthorne was
to be channeled on
the night of the murder!
It can't be...
This was written by
your mother, Morgan Fey,
--who's in jail right now!
--[PEARL gasps]
[JUDGE]
I still don't understand!
This hood is proof
that a second Iris made
an appearance on the night
of Misty Fey's murder.
Before 10, I met her
at the main temple,
where she insisted
I take this hood.
However, right after that,
Sister Bikini spoke to her
at the Inner Temple
where she was wearing the same
hood she had just given away.
That's quite a contradiction.
--[IRIS growls]
--Objection!
The witness has been in police
custody the entire time.
So tell me, when could
she have switched places
with Dahlia Hawthorne?
It was quick,
but she did have a chance.
[GODOT gasps]
Right? It was yesterday.
When she went missing
for a few minutes.
Right around the time
of the earthquake.
Earthquake?
[PHOENIX] She made a beeline
for the Inner temple,
which is where we found
her moments later.
But by then, the switch
had already taken place.
And Dahlia was
in control of her.
[JUDGE] But... If we were
to give credence to
this channeling theory,
my question is this--
Could we even have a--
[IRIS (DAHLIA)]
Stop yammering.
[JUDGE]
Hmm?
[IRIS (DAHLIA)]
It's been a long time.
Right, grandpa?
That horrible attitude.
I remember it well.
Okay, then.
Seems we have to go through
this one more time.
My curiosity and
courtroom procedures
both require that I ask
your name and profession.
My name is Dahlia Hawthorne
and I'm permanently retired.
[CROWD gasping]
Long time no see, Feenie.
[PHOENIX growls]
[PHOENIX]
Dahlia Hawthorne!
It's time to finish this
chapter of my life for good.
To turn the page
on her and my past.
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
It's clear that Dahlia has
crossed over the void
and taken over Iris's body.
Now, she's going to take
this opportunity to finally
reveal the horrifying plot that
she and Morgan Fey concocted.
In order to save Maya,
I reach a shocking conclusion.
The trial enters
into its final stages.
Very soon, the truth
will shine through.
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Next episode, "Bridge to the
Turnabout--6th Trial"!
Take that!