[PHOENIX]
In the peaceful mountain setting
of the Hazakura Temple,
a brutal murder has taken place.
Filling in for me
as the defense,
Miles called the presumed
crime scene into question,
sending the case back to
the investigative stage.
[PHOENIX grunts]
She should've never
taken you under her wing.
You're a coward!
If you had any guts,
she'd be with us right now.
And it's not just her!
You're gonna let the same thing
happen to her little sister!
[GODOT grunts]
[PHOENIX] I believe the murder
took place in the Inner Temple's
courtyard across Dusky Bridge.
I've found evidence
to back up that theory.
But it also raises
troubling questions.
[PHOENIX]
What the hell is going on?
We just got
the results back from
the forensics lab,
and they're saying the victim
wrote this in her own blood.
So it's a message
from Ms. Deauxnim.
But why was
it written backwards?
That's the thing that proves
she wrote it out herself, buddy!
[PHOENIX]
Uh...
So there she was,
being backed into a corner
by this cold-blooded killer.
She was walking like this, with
her back facing the lantern.
As you can see,
if the victim wrote down
her attacker's name
while standing in this position.
[PHOENIX]
It would look backwards!
[GUMSHOE chuckles]
This spells out "Maya."
You said she wrote
her attacker's name.
So you believe
Maya is the killer?
[gasps] Well... I hate
to break it to you, uh...
That's what HQ's thinkin'.
[PHOENIX sighs]
There's no way.
[gasps] I've seen this before.
Elise was wearing it that night.
[PHOENIX gasps]
[PHOENIX]
Whoa. It's the same crest!
The one that's on
the scroll inside.
Maya told me what it stands for.
So why did Elise have it?
Oh, before it slips my mind.
I found something I thought
was a little weird over there.
[gasps]
[GUMSHOE chuckles]
Let's check it out, huh?
Somebody obviously
tried to burn up this note.
[PHOENIX gasps]
What is this?
It talks about channeling and
what to do after lights out.
Are these some
kind of instructions?
Hey, Detective.
You mind if I hang on
to this for a little while?
Heh. As long as you keep
it in this bag, we're good.
[PHOENIX]
Iris!
[IRIS]
Ah. It's Mister Wright.
[PHOENIX] Please, you gotta
get Maya outta there quickly!
Of course. I'm heading over
to the Inner Temple right now.
Back off! You can wait for
us inside the Main Hall.
Are you serious? I'm going, too!
I assure you, I'm quite serious.
I know what's going on.
It's because Maya's
a suspect now, right?
Good to know
that you do understand
the position you're in.
Iris! I'm counting on you!
You're the only one who
can open up that door!
Right.
[FRANZISKA]
Let's move!
[PHOENIX] Okay, guess I gotta
focus on what I can do to help.
[BIKINI]
Well, this is shocking.
I didn't think you'd
survived that fall.
May the gods
have mercy on your soul!
You do realize I am alive?
I caught a terrible cold,
but that's about it.
I am absolutely
delighted to hear that!
[sighs]
My word.
I'm afraid I've made a
horrible mess out of everything.
First Mystic Elise
dies on my watch,
now all this with Iris.
[PHOENIX]
Wait. Did I hear that right?
Excuse me.
But I couldn't help noticing
that you referred
to her as "Mystic Elise."
[BIKINI gasps]
Why's that? I thought
she was a book illustrator.
Oh, well, uhh...
It has something
to do with the amulet
she was wearing doesn't it?
[gasps]
[PHOENIX] I remember seeing
this same crest before,
on the scroll hanging over
in the training hall.
It's reserved for
the Master of Kurain, right?
What'd you say?! Hold on,
how do you know about that?!
Maya explained it to me.
Did you know that she's
the master's daughter?
[gasps]
That young trainee?!
Wait... If she's the
daughter of the master...
[PHOENIX] Hmm.
It means she's the next in line.
[BIKINI wails]
Oh, Mystic Misty!
[wails]
[PHOENIX whimpers]
So it's true.
And "Ms. Elise Deauxnim"
was really just Misty's
Fey's pseudonym.
Yes. She arrived a week ago.
Of course,
I wasn't expecting her.
[BIKINI]
Huh?
[BIKINI] And when she
showed me the talisman with
the master's crest on it.
I tell you, I nearly
died from the shock.
It had been 17 years
since anyone had seen her.
That's quite an absence.
Why'd she come back now?
She was worried
about the state of things.
[MISTY] The Kurain's main
bloodline is in trouble.
We're dangerously
close to dying out.
I'm going to
stop that from happening.
That's why I've come here.
The main bloodline?
The Kurain School has
but one successor at the moment.
Only the master and
her daughters are considered
part of the "main family."
And the others
are branch families.
That right?
[BIKINI] Mm-hmm. You can
imagine the Kurain's history
is littered with... "incidents."
Times when the branches tried
to take out the main family.
Assassinations and the like.
Sounds like a war.
That's the
same motivation behind
a case from last year.
When the master's older sister
tried to frame Maya
for a murder in the village.
That's exactly
what I'm talking about.
But she's been sent away.
She's in prison,
where she belongs.
Her main goal in all of that,
was to make little Pearl
the next master of Kurain.
That's true.
If you're already aware
of Mystic Morgan,
surely you know her
connection to Iris.
Who she really is.
What? No, who is she?
Sister Iris is
the estranged daughter
of Mystic Morgan.
I had no idea!
One of a pair
of identical twins,
and part of another
sad chapter in the family.
Wait. Iris has a twin?
Seems like Pearl would've
mentioned that she had
older twin sisters by now.
[BIKINI] Several years ago,
when Mystic Morgan's husband
at the time learned she would
not become the master,
he divorced her and
left Kurain Village,
taking the two girls with him.
[BIKINI] Later, he realized he
couldn't care for both of them,
so he brought one
to Hazakura Temple.
And that's how Iris got here.
How much do you know
about the twins?
Can you at least tell me
Iris's sister's name?
Was it... Dahlia?
Yes. I believe
that was her name.
[gasps]
That's what's been bothering me!
I can't believe it.
Iris is Dahlia's twin sister!
--[rumbling]
--[BIKINI gasps]
Ah! What in the world
is happening?
No! An earthquake!
[PHOENIX grunts]
[BIKINI] May the gods
keep watch over us
and protect us from harm...
I think it's over now.
Ah! Oh, no!
The tremors were strong!
You have to go and check
on the sacred cavern!
Yeah, you're right!
[GUMSHOE whimpers]
[PHOENIX]
Iris got away?
[FRANZISKA] Because this scruffy
oaf couldn't control her!
[yelps]
I'm sorry, ma'am!
I had just arrived
here with the perpetrator.
When the ground
began to tremble.
[GUMSHOE] I went over
to escort the defendant.
Man, I took my eye
offa her for a second!
I really stepped in
it this time...
Fool!
Well, the more capable officers
have set up checkpoints.
That'll only be a waste of time.
What do you mean?
Answer me, Wright!
I know where Iris went.
Right over there.
The Inner Temple?
Don't be foolish!
It's completely isolated!
There's nowhere to run!
From what I know,
Iris isn't the type to run away.
--[gasps]
--Wait. What's this?
[GUMSHOE gasps]
No, those damned trick locks.
There are more of them!
[PHOENIX gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[PHOENIX]
Iris.
I'm sorry for running earlier.
I wasn't trying to make
things more difficult.
Just worried
about Sacred Cavern.
Wonder who put
all those locks on the door.
[FRANZISKA]
I don't care who.
Only that they're
removed at once!
That will prove a
difficult task to accomplish.
What do you mean?
[IRIS] These are trick locks
that can only be opened
by the person who set them.
[gasps]
Yeah, you're right.
[IRIS] There are hundreds
of possible combinations.
The only way is to try each
one until it works. But...
[FRANZISKA]
That's going to take a while.
[IRIS] Yes. An entire
day, I would imagine.
You think so?
Well, if that's
the case, so be it.
You should get started
on them immediately.
Right. I'll work
as quickly as I can.
[PHOENIX grunts]
[PHOENIX]
I'm so worried about Maya.
She's gonna be trapped
in there another day.
Please, stay strong.
[MILES] Are you trying
to catch another cold?
[gasps]
Hey there, Miles.
[PHOENIX] I just wish
there was something I can do.
I hate feeling helpless.
[MILES]
Hmm.
So what brings
you out here, anyway?
I was curious
about this crystal.
Wanted to check if
it truly was the victim's.
You're always
working, aren't you?
It's so heavy.
I know.
I was thinking that I might look
around here again as well.
Perhaps I could find
the real murder weapon.
[gasps]
Oh, wow. Looks like blood.
Guess your instincts
were right about this one.
The murder weapon
really was here.
I'll take it to
forensics right away
and have them figure out
whose blood this is.
Thanks.
[PHOENIX]
Why was Misty Fey carrying
something like that around?
[MILES]
I did some research on Iris.
[PHOENIX grunts]
[MILES] From the moment
I met her in the jail.
I couldn't shake the feeling I
had seen her somewhere before.
But where?
Now I know.
My first trial as a prosecutor.
A nightmare for
everybody involved.
You mean Dahlia
Hawthorne. Right?
[MILES]
Yes. Dahlia.
A woman I'm certain
you can't erase
from your thoughts either.
[PHOENIX sighs]
Yeah, she's hard to forget.
Yet another thing the two of us
have in common, I suppose.
I didn't know this before,
but it seems that
she had a twin.
Which happens to be Sister Iris.
Yep, that's right.
I'm kinda impressed.
You've really done
your research.
This is slightly out
of character for me to say.
But I feel like Dahlia
Hawthorne's shadow
is looming over this case.
'Course it's impossible
she could be involved
at this point.
Because she's in prison?
Well, Dahlia was in prison,
but now she's no more.
[gasps]
[MILES]
It happened about a month ago.
Her sentence was carried out.
She was executed.
[PHOENIX gasps]
Really...?
This must be quite
a shock for you.
My apologies.
But you should know that she
had nothing to do with this.
Because the simple
fact is that the dead
can never come back.
[PHOENIX] Is that a fact?
I don't know what to believe.
[IRIS]
Mister Wright. Is that you?
[PHOENIX]
Yeah.
I have some bad news.
This is harder than I thought,
so I can't open it
until tomorrow.
Please don't stop on my account.
But I'd like ask you
something if you don't mind.
[IRIS]
What is it?
It's about the night
of the murder.
After ringing the bell for
lights out at 10 PM,
you went back to your room,
or at least that's what
you claim you did.
You think I'm lying about that?
I saw you there.
When you were on
your way to ring the bell.
And I heard it, too,
not long afterward.
[PHOENIX] But around the same
time, somebody else saw you
in the Inner Temple.
They say it happened
at 10 PM as well.
[IRIS]
Was it Sister Bikini?
It was. I wasn't in court today,
but I heard about it.
She said she saw you there.
And even talked to you.
If she's telling the truth,
the only explanation is
that there were two of you.
If that's a joke,
I don't get it.
How in the world could there
be another one of me?
Well, what about Dahlia?
I found out she was
your twin sister.
And that she was
executed a month ago.
[IRIS]
What of it?
I mean, if she's dead, there's
no way she could have been seen.
[PHOENIX] Mm-mm. Things work
a bit differently around here,
don't they?
You know exactly
what I'm talking about.
The other "you" who
showed up that night
was your twin sister's spirit.
So Dahlia was, in fact, here.
Yes. 'Cause a spirit
medium channeled her.
[IRIS]
Hmph. You never miss a thing.
It's kind of amazing.
I see. So you knew after all.
But I don't understand why
you didn't say anything sooner.
I've proven myself a traitor.
So I wasn't about to go and get
in my sister's way this time.
[PHOENIX]
What do you mean?
I'm surprised you have to ask.
I mean the fake kidnapping.
Everything that happened
all those years ago.
After that, our lives
would never be the same again.
My sister committed
crime after crime,
and that's why she's dead now.
But I know none of
this would have happened
if I hadn't betrayed her.
Betrayed her, how?
It wasn't a coincidence
that Dusky Bridge was where
the ransom was going
to be handed over.
There was a reason behind it.
Because in the original plan,
I was supposed to be the one
helping her pull it off.
Is that true?
[IRIS] I got too scared
by the whole thing.
And ended up
running away instead.
That's a good thing!
It means you didn't want
to be an accomplice!
Naturally, you wouldn't
want to steal two million
from your own father!
Yeah, but she told me
that he deserved it
for everything he'd done.
Especially for abandoning
our poor mother like that,
because she couldn't be master.
I heard about that.
And about all the
family infighting.
Yes. Thinking
back on it all now,
I realize I should've
helped my sister that day.
[PHOENIX gasps]
Not to be rude,
but I need to concentrate.
[PHOENIX]
Can I ask you one last thing?
[IRIS]
Yes?
Years ago,
right after Dahlia poisoned
that defense attorney's coffee,
she started dating a college
student for several months
so she could use him.
I'm curious. Did she ever
talk about that guy?
[IRIS] Not really, but she
did tell me one thing.
She said...
she hated his guts.
[PHOENIX]
Thank you.
Ah, looks good. Yeah.
Hot! Be careful with it, okay?
Thanks, I appreciate it.
[PHOENIX]
That looks good.
[gasps]
Mister Nick.
Hey, back off. You can't
just come and steal our taters.
I wouldn't worry.
[BUTZ growls]
Actually... I was hoping to chat
with Pearl for a minute.
You want to talk... to me?
There was a magazine.
A magazine you had that
mentioned the temple.
That's what got Maya
interested in coming here
in the first place, right?
But I wanted to know something.
Did somebody ask
you to show it to her?
[PEARL gasps] Yeah, but how'd
you figure that out?
This was found in the
incinerator by the Inner Temple.
Uh...
It looks like a plan.
A way to carry out
this whole thing.
But somehow it didn't
totally burn up in there.
[PEARL whimpers]
Tell the truth.
You were the spirit medium who
channeled Dahlia Hawthorne
that night, weren't you?
I'm not mad.
But I'm curious
if you actually know
who that person is.
No. I don't.
You be nice to her! You hear?!
'Cause if not,
I'll tater ya!
I don't want your stupid tater!
I swear! I didn't know
anything about a letter!
No?
There's no proof!
You need proof if you're
gonna accuse someone
of something don't you?
You really didn't know?
Yeah! Show her
the proof, law man!
[PHOENIX] All the pieces
just fell into place.
And now I know exactly how
this whole thing went down.
How 'bout this?
Somebody read that letter,
and they channeled Dahlia's
spirit just like it said.
And whoever did it
was a child. I'm sure.
Huh?
I mean, it's pretty obvious
no adult would've made
a silly little
mistake like that.
[PHOENIX] There was curry
splattered all over that scroll
that hangs in the inner temple.
Come on.
You did that, didn't you?
[PEARL whimpers]
How'd you know?
From your reading lesson.
Remember?
Uh...
[PHOENIX]
"Gravely" and "sunder."
She taught you how to read them.
But she never explained
what they really meant.
"Gravely sunder the Master,
roast her in the
fires of Hades."
Huh? That sounds crazy.
There's your proof.
That work for ya?
"Gravely" sounded like "gravy."
So I got pretty confused
about what to do.
That's why you smeared
curry on that scroll.
Because that's the closest thing
you had to gravy, right?
I'm really sorry...
Now this letter.
I have a good idea about
who it was that sent it to you.
It was your mom, wasn't it?
That's why you
followed the instructions.
I felt like I didn't
have any other choice.
That the only way to
honor her final wish,
was to do everything exactly
like the letter said.
It was her "final wish"?
She said that.
She also made it seem like
the plan would be good
for Mystic Maya, too.
Did you ever talk
about it in person?
It was during one
of the times that I went out
to visit her in jail.
She told me to look for
the letter at our house.
[PHOENIX] If she hid it there,
that means all this was planned
before she had
even been arrested.
[PEARL] It's weird. The seal on
the letter had been broken.
Like somebody already
had opened it before I did.
So you don't think you
were the first one to read it?
Yeah.
--[PHOENIX] Hmm...
--[BUTZ] Hmm? It wasn't me!
[PHOENIX sighs]
[PHOENIX] Who else could
have known about this?
And what did they do
with the information?
I know that I'm being
punished for being bad.
That's gotta be the reason
why I lost my powers.
Oh. Like you can't
channel anymore?
No, I can't.
After dinner that night, I never
went up to Ms. Elise's room
to read with her,
like she'd asked.
I was too worried
about Mystic Maya.
I see. You went to
the Inner Temple instead.
The letter said that
I should wait to channel
the spirit, until after they
rang the bell for lights out.
[PHOENIX] Then you called
Dahlia Hawthorne's spirit?
[PEARL] I tried, but I
couldn't make it work!
No spirit came?
No, never. That's not normal.
I was really surprised.
But I went ahead and followed
the letter as best I could.
[PHOENIX] But you got
confused and splattered
the curry on the scroll.
[PEARL]
That's right.
I kept trying over and over
again to summon the spirit.
But nothing I did ever worked.
Could there be
any other reason why
you couldn't channel her?
I mean besides the
mix-up with the curry?
Well, I can think of one thing.
There's a small possibility that
another medium had already
channeled her spirit.
Everybody only
has one, you know.
[PHOENIX]
I never thought of that.
Did somebody really get
to Dahlia's spirit first?
Mystic Maya's
gonna be okay, right?
I'm scared. But I know
Mother is watching over her.
Yeah. I'm sure she is.
[MORGAN] My dear little Pearl,
you've made your mother proud.
It's best you don't know
about all the ugliness,
but now, the main family
is out of the way.
And at last, you can
assume your rightful place
as master of the Fey clan.
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
This entire debacle
was the direct result
of a succession fight between
the Kurain school's families.
And of course, I'm involved
in a strange way,
because of my past
connection to Dahlia.
This trial will be my chance
to prove that Iris is innocent!
Her confession just
doesn't sit right with me.
There's clearly
something missing!
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Next episode: "Bridge
to the Turnabout - 5th Trial"!
Take that!