[PHOENIX]
My name is Phoenix Wright.
And I'm a defense attorney.
I've been building my
reputation over several cases,
and I'm really starting to
make a name for myself.
No matter how tough
the case may be,
or how high the odds are
stacked against us,
it's my job to
stand up for those
who have no one else
in their corner.
[PHOENIX] I'll do whatever it
takes to fight for the truth!
I suppose I should
take one last look
at this file before
we get started.
--[PHOENIX] Hmm...
--[cell jingle plays]
Hello?
[PHOENIX]
Guess they hung up.
--[blow lands]
--[PHOENIX grunts]
[laughter]
Try not to take this
personally, Mr. Attorney.
--[cell jingle plays]
--[PHOENIX grunts]
What the heck is going on?
[JUDGE]
There is no escape!
You can run but you
cannot hide from
the mighty hammer of justice!
[PHOENIX groans]
Ow...
[PHOENIX]
Huh...?
Good morning, Mr. Wright.
Thanks for your help!
Uh. Sure. And who are you?
Sir, my name is Maggey Byrde!
And today, I'll be putting my
life into your capable hands!
Oh. Your life, eh?
Don't you remember
the promise you made?
You swore that you could
prove my innocence!
Did I?
Yes, and even though all
my friends like to call me
the "Goddess of Misfortune,"
what I'm dealing
with now is a tragedy
on an unbelievably epic scale!
But when you said you'd
help me, I felt my soul rising
from the ashes like
a Phoenix, Mr. Wright!
And that's me?
Right! Phoenix Wright!
I see now. What a crazy name.
You do believe me?
I promise I didn't kill him!
Whoa! There was a murder?
No! That's horrible!
--[door opens
--[BOTH] Hmm?
If you're ready,
the trial's about to begin.
I put my faith in you!
[PHOENIX chuckles]
Courtroom Two.
[PHOENIX]
No pressure at all.
[JUDGE] This court is hereby
in session for the trial
of Ms. Maggey Byrde!
[PHOENIX]
Is that old geezer the judge?
[PAYNE chuckles]
I knew we'd meet again
someday, Wright.
Right.
[PHOENIX]
This is gonna be a pain.
[MAGGEY whimpers]
Prosecutor Payne,
are you ready to begin
your opening statement?
Quite! Your Honor, today,
I will prove the defendant
murdered her lover.
[PHOENIX gasps]
You murdered your lover?
[MAGGEY]
No, it wasn't like that!
Constable Prince was more
like a mentor to me.
What makes this crime
even more horrendous
is the victim was a
decorated officer of the law.
Wait, you mean he was a cop?
Please call your
first witness to the stand.
Uh, my name is
Dick Gumshoe, Your Highness.
I'm the head detective of
the homicide department
down at the precinct.
[PHOENIX] This guy looks
like he's about to cry.
Constable Byrde.
Well. She's served me
and my squad faithfully
and with respect!
So you worked
under Detective Gumshoe?
Sir! He's been a guiding force
since I was a trainee.
A detective like no other.
Detective. Can you tell us
about the murder?
Sir!
The crime took place
at "Exposé Park"
which is near the precinct.
The victim was a local cop
named Dustin Prince.
There were signs of blunt
force trauma on his body,
and his neck was snapped.
We believe he was
pushed over the railing
from the path
several feet above.
I'd like to add there
was a crucial piece of evidence
found under the body.
Here it is.
It seems during the struggle,
the victim grabbed these
glasses off the killer's face,
and held onto them as
he fell to the ground,
breaking them and his neck.
You think they're
the killer's glasses?
What about those?
Oh. Well, today
I'm wearing my spare pair.
[PHOENIX] What? Then does that
mean the glasses are yours?
No, the ones from
the scene aren't mine!
It just so happens that
I stepped on the ones
I usually wear on that same day.
Oh, yeah?
It kinda goes with my
reputation of having bad luck.
[JUDGE]
Defense, your cross-examination?
[PHOENIX] Me? You mean I have
to ask him questions, too?
[JUDGE] That is the nature
of a cross-examination.
Yes! Time for you
to flex your legal muscles!
You've got this!
Question, what exactly
am I supposed to do?
I'm lost.
This is really not the
time to be making jokes!
I know. I'm being
completely serious here.
For some reason, I can't
remember anything right now.
Huh? Wait!
Are you trying to tell me
that you have amnesia?
I have amnesia?
And once again,
life proves that my nickname
is devastatingly appropriate.
Please begin your
cross-examination, defense.
Look. Just go for it!
Yeah, okay. So. The glasses.
Do you have any
proof these do indeed
belong to the defendant?
The lenses are for
a person with near-sightedness
and are almost the same
prescription as hers.
And you can see,
the frames even kinda look like
the ones she's
wearing in her ID.
Wait a minute!
"Almost" and "kinda" are not
good enough in a murder case.
[GUMSHOE groans]
--[GUMSHOE squeals]
--Do you even have
a shred of definitive proof?
One moment!
If definitive proof
is what you need,
look no further
than this photograph!
[CROWD gasping]
[PHOENIX]
Uh. That says Maggie?
[JUDGE]
Indeed it does.
Which as we know,
is the name of the defendant.
[MAGGEY] It's all a setup!
A big fraud! Fake!
[JUDGE]
Order! Order!
[PHOENIX] If the victim wrote
her name as a dying message,
we are completely hosed.
[MAGGEY sighs]
[PHOENIX grunts]
[PHOENIX]
Wait.
--Hold it!
--[yells]
Oof. That always
hits me like a punch
to the breadbasket.
My poor belly...
[PHOENIX]
What was that all about?
It was just an instinct.
Like I had to yell out as
loud as I could and point
my finger at him.
Detective, I'd like you
to clearly state
the defendant's name for us.
Uh. Well, it's
Maggey Byrde, of course.
And would you mind
telling the court exactly
how she spells her name?
[PAYNE] Hold it! The question
is pointless, Your Honor.
It's right there in the photo!
It's true that this message
does spell "Maggie."
But. Her name is
spelled M-a-g-g-e-y.
[gasping]
[screaming]
The contradiction
of facts is undeniable!
[PAYNE] But have you considered
the possibility that the victim
didn't know about
her peculiar spelling?
Surely, you recall
what you said earlier.
Constable Byrd stands accused
of brutally murdering her lover!
There's no way he wouldn't
know something like that!
[yells]
Tragically, the day
Officer Prince was murdered
also happened to be
his birthday, and Maggey
had gotten him a present
to celebrate the occasion.
[PHOENIX]
I guess this is it?
That is an extremely
yellow glove.
Yeah, it is!
He was a huge baseball fan and
yellow was his favorite color!
Oh. And does that
yellow glove have
any kind of relevance to
this case whatsoever?
Uh. Well. Not sure.
[CROWD murmuring]
Yes! In fact, that
blindingly yellow glove
holds the key to
this entire case!
[gasping]
If you look closely.
You can see that it's made
for a left-handed player!
Ah...
[PHOENIX] Hmph. And now,
let's take another look
at the crime scene photo.
--[gasping]
--That's the wrong hand!
Good catch!
Dustin did always like to
call himself a southpaw!
There's no way a lefty
would use his other hand
to write his final message.
So the only explanation is...
...the victim was not
the one who wrote it!
[yells]
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[PHOENIX]
What happened?
It's like before. This sudden
rush just takes over.
A jolt of energy
surges through my body!
If the prosecution has
nothing further to add--
[PAYNE]
Hold it! Uh, Your Honor,
the prosecution is not ready
to rest its case at this moment!
--[gasping]
--You have more?
Oh, no!
Yes, I do.
It so happens there was an
eyewitness to the murder.
[CROWD murmuring]
[PAYNE] They were at the
scene the very moment
poor Officer Prince was
pushed to his death!
In fact, they were close
enough to clearly see
the face of the assailant!
But I'm telling you.
It was not me!
[JUDGE] Bring this witness
to the stand at once!
[PAYNE] Sir, meet the drifter
who was trying to take
a nice walk in the park
when he was subjected
to this horrible crime!
Hi!
[MAGGEY, PHOENIX grunt]
[PHOENIX]
He saw the murder?
[PAYNE] Will you please state
your name for the record?
[WELLINGTON] Yes, but first, I'd
like to make a clarification.
You just introduced my fabulous
personage to the court
as "a drifter taking a walk"!
Oh, well, I suppose I did.
I simply cannot abide
such a biased assessment
of my character.
[speaking speed increases]
True, calling me a university
student would be a bit of
a stretch at this precise
moment in time.
But as a man who will
settle for nothing less
than the absolute finest of
everything that this world
has to offer, I find
myself searching for
the learning institution
worthy of my intellect...
Yes! I hope you'll
pardon my confusion!
Only top tier fashion,
cars, women,
and glasses for moi,
And that's why.
I can't choose a university.
[PHOENIX]
Why did he mention glasses?
I believe Mr. Payne
only asked for your name.
Well, I'm sorry.
But he should already know that.
If I must state the obvious,
I am Richard Wellington,
and I am, in essence,
a university student.
[PHOENIX] What does he
mean by "in essence"?
If I may, I'd like to
begin my testimony.
I was strolling
through Exposé Park
that evening, when suddenly,
before my very eyes!
It was as if the
officer had fallen from the sky.
In a panic, I looked up and
locked my gaze with a woman
who looked positively aghast!
It's her. I'm sure of it!
--[MAGGEY growls]
--[CROWD whispering]
[PHOENIX] Was there anything
else that caught your attention?
[WELLINGTON]
Hmm. Let me think.
Oddly enough a bunch
of bananas fell with him!
Uh. Bananas? That's very odd.
True. But there they were...
...remarkably yellow
and quite appealing.
[PHOENIX]
"Remarkably yellow bananas"?
[PHOENIX] Can you describe
them in more detail?
Why? They're lying
right there in front of you.
[gasping]
Is that so?
You said they looked appealing,
so would you like to
try a bite of one?
[WELLINGTON]
Hmm...
[screams]
It can't be. That's bananas!
And how good is
your eyesight, by the way?
Hey, what does my vision
have to do with this?
Objection!
That baseball glove could
easily be mistaken for
a bunch of bananas!
I'll allow the
line of questioning.
Both eyes are
twenty-two hundred. Okay?
"Twenty-two hundred"?
That's definitely not very good.
Is there a reason
you're not wearing
your glasses today?
[WELLINGTON gulps] Of course.
Because I recently lost them.
Lost them? Maybe I can help.
Might these belong to you?
[gasps]
Wait. Where did you find them?
The police found them
crushed beneath
Officer Prince's body.
Oh, my god! That can't be true!
[PHOENIX]
Mr. Wellington.
Can you explain why they
would turn up there?
[CROWD gasping]
How would I know?!
And besides the victim clearly
told us in the sand message
that it was Maggie who
murdered him, not me.
Sure, he did
write down "Maggie,"
but her name is
spelled this way.
--[gasps]
--No!
[PHOENIX] The real killer made
a conspicuous mistake by
using the victim's right hand.
Since the victim
was left-handed,
this was just a ham-fisted
attempt to frame Ms. Byrde.
That may be the case,
but obviously the murderer
would still have to know
her first name to try to
frame her in such a way.
It couldn't have been me,
because I don't know her at all.
--[laughs]
--[MAGGEY growls]
[PHOENIX] Ms. Byrde. You don't
know him either, do you?
No, sir. But since you
brought up my name...
That day, when Dustin and I were
walking around the park,
we happened to find
a cell phone.
This is Maggey, are you
trying to get ahold of
the owner of this phone?
[WELLINGTON] Great!
This is my phone, actually!
I lost it!
You're in luck! I just
found it at Exposé Park!
[WELLINGTON]
I'll be there shortly!
So. Dustin and I
waited at the park
for what seemed like forever.
He needed to head back home.
Right after he left,
I heard him scream.
And then I saw him.
[PHOENIX]
Hmm.
Maggey's name. It all adds up!
[PHOENIX] Tell me. Did you also
lose your cell phone recently?
What? Why would that matter?
[PHOENIX] I can assume that you
tried calling your own number
to locate it.
And what does that prove?
[PHOENIX] For one,
that you found out her name.
She answered with
"this is Maggey," right?
[WELLINGTON growls]
[PHOENIX] Just hearing the name,
one would think it would look...
...exactly like this.
Since you heard it,
you weren't aware of
its unusual spelling.
[gasps]
You might as well admit it.
You killed officer
Dustin Prince.
Isn't that right?
[screams]
Objection!
The witness has
no motive for the murder!
[gasping]
Y-Yes, that's true!
Why would a scholar like me
want to kill a cop?
Indeed.
Well, defense, do you care to
explain what motive the witness
could have had to
commit such a crime?
Your Honor...
[chuckles]
They had never met.
So, what could the reason
to kill Prince possibly be?
[PHOENIX] There's something
right on the tip of my tongue.
Something about the case,
but I can't remember what it is!
Ahem. If the defense is unable
to provide a motive, then--
[MAYA]
Hold it!
[MAYA] I'm sorry
I kept you waiting, Nick!
[gasps]
[MAYA]
I was so afraid I was too late.
Just in the nick of time!
Way to go, Maya!
Hey there, Maya.
[MAYA]
Don't you worry.
I've come to save the day, with
this super-important evidence!
[PHOENIX]
Hm?
Feast your eyes on this!
What is it?
It's this crazy list
you had me put together
just for you!
O... kay.
It wasn't easy compiling
all that stuff, ya know?
[PHOENIX sighs] A bunch of
names and phone numbers.
Uh, thanks. But what
does it all mean?
Huh?
You mean you don't
remember asking me to gather
all that info?!
The names and numbers
are all of the contacts I found
in the phone
I picked up that day!
And the crazy thing is,
every last one of them belongs
to a ring of local con men!
[WELLINGTON gasps]
[PHOENIX] A ring of con men...
Cell phone... Names...
Defense. Please wrap
up your cross-examination.
[PHOENIX] I get it. This is
what I was trying to remember!
Do you know where
that cell phone is now?
I'm pretty sure you
have it, don't you?
[gasps]
Yeah, I gave it to you
right when I hired you
to defend me.
Huh.
See? I knew you had it.
Yep!
Thank you, miss.
You handed me the
last piece of the puzzle.
"Miss"?
[PHOENIX] Your Honor,
I have the motive right here!
--[CROWD gasping]
--[JUDGE] What is it?
[WELLINGTON gasps]
The cell phone the
defendant found that day.
When we investigated the
list of contacts stored on it,
we discovered that they were all
part of a ring of con artists.
[PAYNE]
Say what?!
Tell me. The names
and numbers on this device
all belong to your
associates, do they not?
Objection!
If the witness was told that
it would be returned to him
without incident,
then why on earth would he
have to kill to get it back?
Because of who
he saw waiting for him.
And what they were wearing.
[MAGGEY gasps]
[MAYA]
A policeman's uniform!
Yes. Constable Prince
was still wearing
his uniform when he met
with Ms. Byrde that day.
Which led you to make
the assumption that she had
brought a cop along to arrest
you, right, Mr. Wellington?
You were worried that
they had checked out
some of the contacts
in your phone.
And that they knew you were
one of those con men, too.
So you went into a panic
and pushed Officer Prince
over the railing to his death!
[WELLINGTON giggles, laughs]
Oh, my. Not bad for
a third-rate lawyer!
And what's so funny?
[WELLINGTON]
The joke's on you.
That's not my cell phone!
[gasps]
[WELLINGTON chuckles]
They really have
the exact same model?
It's true I had
misplaced my phone,
but I found it shortly after.
Yeah, but unfortunately,
all my contacts went "poof"--
vanished into the ether.
It must've glitched
when I dropped it.
[PHOENIX] He erased those
numbers to hide the evidence.
"A ring of local con artists"?
What a pathetic
defense that was.
Nick. What are we gonna do?
Lucky for you,
you found your phone.
Will you tell us where it was?
Will I?
[chuckles, laughs]
You've got to be kidding me.
The only thing you need
to know is that this is it!
Enough! Control yourself!
[grunts]
Ow.
[cell jingle plays]
[PHOENIX gasps]
Guess they hung up.
[blow lands]
[PHOENIX]
It's all coming back to me now.
The moment when it happened.
I heard that ringtone.
If you were hoping to find
any evidence on this thing,
it's gone with your
chance for victory!
[cackles]
I really thought we had
him with that list.
But I guess he turned
the tables on us.
[PHOENIX gasps]
[PHOENIX]
"Turned the tables"?
Then all I gotta do is
turn them back on him!
[MAYA]
Here you go.
Aww. Thank you, young lady.
The defense appears
to be out of questions,
so that concludes
the cross-examination.
Well, my work here is done,
so time to say toodle-oo!
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
Ah! What is he doing to me?
[gasping]
Sorry to burst your bubble,
but I have more
evidence against you.
Wanna hear what it is?
What nonsense!
[PHOENIX] Maya, will you
do me a favor, please?
Call my cell phone.
So. You want me
to call you right now?
Okie-doke.
[PHOENIX] This will prove
my point. You'll see.
[MAYA]
All right, I'm calling you.
[different cell jingle plays]
[PHOENIX]
What?
You did call my phone
number, didn't you?
[MAYA]
Mm-hmm. Hold on.
Wait. Why would
my phone be ringing?
It's quite simple, because
the phone you're holding
now actually belongs to me.
No way!
In case you're wondering,
that lump on the head you gave
me is starting to go down.
[WELLINGTON growls]
It's pretty easy to figure
out how it all happened.
You knocked me unconscious and
tried to take your cell back.
But. You picked up
mine by mistake.
[whimpers]
The truth is calling and you're
accepting the charges!
[screams]
[JUDGE]
Now that we've re-convened,
where is your witness?
Well. He was arrested
during the recess, Your Honor.
It's been a while since
I've seen you put on
such a show, Mr. Wright.
[gasps]
Oh, yeah.
I hereby conclude the
trial of Ms. Maggey Byrde
and I am prepared
to hand down my verdict.
Not guilty!
[CROWD cheers, applauds]
Thank you, Your Honor!
[JUDGE] That is all!
This court is adjourned!
[MAYA]
You had amnesia?
I guess you were acting
pretty weird earlier.
And you don't usually
call me "miss" like that.
Well, I'm feeling better now.
I truly appreciate
everything you've done
for me today. Now that it's
over, I think I'm gonna cry!
[GUMSHOE] Maggey!
Congratulations on the verdict!
Thanks for all the
support in there, Dick!
[GUMSHOE groans] That's fair,
but I never thought
you could have actually done it.
I'm gonna take this
opportunity and turn it
into a new lease on life!
And I'll bet
the next time we meet.
I'm gonna have more good luck
than I'll know what to do with!
Now that's the spirit!
We're gonna have
to start calling you,
the "goddess of good-fortune!"
Right? Don't you think so?
Yep. Totally! Wait a sec.
What's up?
We've met before,
haven't we, miss?
Oh, no way!
Nick, please don't tell me
you still have amnesia!
I'm just kidding with you, Maya!
[PHOENIX]
My name is Phoenix Wright,
and I'm a defense attorney.
No matter how high
the odds are stacked against us.
It's my job to stand up for
those who have no one else
in their corner.
I'll do whatever it takes
to fight for the truth!
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
The phantom thief,
Mask DeMasque,
has stolen the sacred urn
from Kurain Village.
Maya's childhood home.
And to make things worse,
the stolen urn
goes missing again!
As the plot continues
to thicken, a bizarre detective
and the shady
characters surrounding
the phantom thief
enter the fray.
What's more, the
prosecutor waiting for us
in the courtroom is
yet another mystery!
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Next episode: "The
Stolen Turnabout--First Trial"!
Take that!