[PHOENIX] Turns out I have
an imposter who earned
a guilty plea for
a client of mine.
I can't let injustice
happen on my watch,
so I petitioned for a retrial
to prove her innocence.
But the testimonies
given by the two star witnesses
left a bad taste in my mouth.
Something is definitely
rotten here.
Maggey swears
she saw the killer.
But where did they go?
To get to the bottom of this,
I'm returning to the scene of
the crime to look for clues.
[MAYA]
Bonjour, Monsieur!
[PHOENIX]
Maya?
That's moi! Très Bien!
[MAYA] That retrial really
made things more complicated,
don't you think?
It's true,
we definitely have a lot
on out plate in this case.
The elusive second waitress,
and the victim's
mysterious earpiece.
It's strange.
And then there's
that whole imposter thing
with Fake-nix Wrong
I'm not sure I can
stomach that part of it.
By the way...
Is he the only customer?
Yeah, this place is so boring.
You should order something
to liven things up!
It is lunchtime.
So I think you should
get today's special,
which is the Twin-T plate!
Twin-T, eh?
Well, how much is that?
That'll be 20,
thank you kindly!
--No way!
--Aw, come on, Nick!
Be a sport and get it, please!
No, honestly, this
case has killed my appetite.
Well, this will bring it back!
One special coming up!
Twin-T, see-voo-play!
Hey, wait a second, Maya!
[MAYA] Here. Bone-apple-teeth
to you, mon-sewer.
Wow, this actually
looks like it could be
worth 20 bucks.
[PHOENIX groans]
Y'okay?
I think my tongue hates me now.
[MAYA] Oh. That explains
why this place is so empty.
[GUMSHOE]
Yeah, that's the number, pal!
Come on, come on, come on!
Now give me an eight!
I can smell it coming up!
I know that voice.
[yells]
No! I said an eight!
[yells
Hello?
[GUMSHOE]
Huh?
[gasps]
A little radio? Ah, I get it.
What exactly do you get, bub?
Well, from what I overheard,
it sounded to me like
you were listening to
the lottery results just now.
[GUMSHOE growls]
[PHOENIX] Knowing how
Glen Elg hit the big jackpot
right before he kicked the
bucket gave you an idea. Right?
Are you some kind of psychic
mind reader or something?
No, it was just really obvious.
You got me, kid.
I was listening to "Millionaire
Radio" where they read
the results, and I guess I kinda
let myself get carried away.
Millionaire, huh?
I could see listening to that.
[GUMSHOE] It comes
on Wednesdays at 1:30
and runs for about ten minutes,
if you wanna check it out.
I'll buy a ticket today!
Good luck!
By the way...
Maggey didn't happen to
say anything, did she?
I don't recall her
saying anything, do you?
No, no. Not really.
Just tell me what
she said about me.
I can take it.
To be honest, we all
know you painted her
into a corner with the
testimony you gave the court.
So, after the trial...
I can hardly believe
that stupid ol' Dick!
Ugh! I hate him!
[yells]
What could I do?
Take it easy.
These things happen, pal.
You ain't helpin' me here, doll.
So, uh...
I assume the reason you came
here today was because
you wanted to question
Mr. Armstrong again.
Yeah. That's the chef!
Well, coincidentally,
that's why I'm here, too.
Oh, he's back in the kitchen.
Weird. I could swear
he was just here.
[MAYA] A vanity? I guess
he does his makeup here?
[PHOENIX]
What's all this?
[GUMSHOE]
Looks like aromatherapy bottles.
[PHOENIX] Okay. But one of these
things is not like the others.
Yeah, you're right.
Doesn't even have a label.
[GUMSHOE]
A mystery liquid?
It's odorless.
But I'll tell you what,
I smell a rat here!
I'm gonna take this
back to the boys in the lab.
Get Byrde outta that cage!
See ya, pal.
[ARMSTRONG]
Oui-oui. Next month?
[VIOLA]
If you don't have it by then,
I'll turn your
bistro into toast.
[giggles]
[screams]
That won't be necessary!
[VIOLA]
Don't let me down.
Because I'll be watching you
like a hawk, doughboy.
[giggles]
[PHOENIX]
That's her.
Au revoir!
[sighs]
Ooh-la-la!
[MAYA whimpers]
Sorry.
[ARMSTRONG]
Non. Zis is who I am.
I try to be un petite angel,
but my wings, zay are broken.
I 'ave to do everyzing
'e tells me to.
I'm at ze mercy of
the Big City Tiger!
Big City Tiger?
You must be very
careful when you need
to borrow a few francs
from someone, no?
Every time 'e
starts to yell and rage
with z'at spiky head
of 'is... si terrifiant!
Oh! 'E will flatten me
like a crepe
and use me as a rug!
[BOTH]
Like a crepe?
[MAYA]
The Big City Tiger sounds scary.
You sure you can
just leave the restaurant?
[MAYA] Yeah. I'm on
break until dinner time.
[KUDO] Hey! You think
you're too good for my seeds?
Ya lousy buncha ingrates!
[MAYA]
What a kooky guy!
[PHOENIX]
Hello!
Argh. And now you! Hmph!
I hope you can forgive
me about what happened in court.
Well. You weren't
wrong, were ya, Wright?
I was so busy admiring
the waitress's figure,
that I didn't see her face.
I'm just a dirty old man!
Buh-buh-birdie!
Pretty, pretty bird!
Okay, then.
Work your magic, Maya.
Hey, sir. What do you say you
and I have a teeny little chat?
With a "teeny little" girl?
No, thank you.
Run along and play on the slide.
Ow!
[PHOENIX]
Didn't take the bait.
[MIA]
Excuse me. Do you have a moment?
Huh?
Have all the time
you want missy!
[PHOENIX]
Mia?
Good. Thank you.
I hope you don't mind talking
to me for a few minutes.
Sure. I'm Victor Kudo,
nice to meet ya.
That trial must've
been so hard on you.
You bet yer tookis.
No matter what anyone says,
I know what I saw!
That waitress put
some kinda white powder
in the young lad's javaccino!
The poor sap
listened to his earphone
while he gulped it
down none the wiser.
Yeah. It was in his left ear!
[PHOENIX]
He doesn't seem to be lying.
[KUDO]
Don't stare at me like that!
I know, I'm just
an inconvenience!
At home, at that restaurant.
All I'm good for
is running errands!
Oh, errands, you say?
Sure's you're born.
On that very day the
unlucky lad met his end.
Did somebody ask
you to do something for them?
Yeah. That pasty chef!
Excusez-moi!
Call zee policemen,
s'il vous plait, pépé!
Whole thing had me
feeling like a deer
in the headlights.
But I ran outta there
just like he asked me to.
I needed to find
a pay phone, ya see.
[PHOENIX] Why didn't
you use your cell phone?
I don't trust those
new-fangled thingies.
What then?
Did you find one quickly?
'Fraid not. I ran around
looking for ten minutes or so.
That long?
And Maggey was passed out,
so the chef was alone.
[KUDO] Gotta say,
that definitely ruined
my javaccino time.
[MIA]
Your javaccino time?
[KUDO] My daily routine is to
enjoy a nice cup of javaccino
at 2 PM sharp every day.
That chef's got no sense.
If you're carryin'
around that kinda debt,
you should value your regulars!
[PHOENIX] Wait. You know
about Armstrong's debt?
Sure do. And I recently
heard he let it blow up
to 500,000 smackerooneys.
Five hundred grand?!
[KUDO] And then he
wants to cry about it
bein' "society's fault."
[PHOENIX] It's obviously
his cooking skills.
[KUDO] Well, he borrowed
from the Tiger,
so he shoulda seen this coming.
That name again.
[KUDO]
If you're in dire straits,
don't make the mistake of
goin' to the Tender Lender.
You don't say.
Is that this "Tiger's" business?
That it is.
But make no mistake--
he's just a loan shark.
[MIA]
Thank you very much.
--I appreciate your help.
--[yells]
Well, sir.
Can you tell us where to
find this "Tender Lender?"
[VIOLA]
You're here to discuss a loan.
Is that right?
Yes, we are.
The office manager
is away at the moment.
So I hope you don't
mind waiting a bit.
[giggles]
[PHOENIX] Yeah. That's
who we saw at Très Bien earlier.
[clattering]
[PHOENIX]
Hmm?
Maya! What are you doing?
This is our
only chance! Come on.
How are we gonna find any clues
if we don't start looking?
Is this a good idea?
So much junk.
Where do we start?
[PHOENIX]
Hold on.
That the CD Maggey
told us about?
[MAGGEY] No, it said
"MC"-something on it in marker.
[PHOENIX]
Hmm.
What's that?
This appears
to be a work invoice
from a car body shop.
Whoa, that is a lot of money!
That's crazy!
[MAYA] The car's registered
to the Cadaverini Group.
[PHOENIX]
Cadaverini?
Hey, I noticed this earlier.
Don't you think this
suit looks a lot like
the one you always wear?
[PHOENIX]
Yeah. Hm? What the heck?
[MAYA]
A badge like yours.
[PHOENIX] But it's cardboard!
And nobody noticed?
[TIGRE]
Hey! What's goin' on?!
How come you two is
snoopin' around my office?!
Huh?!
Guess you figured
it out, didja tough guy?
The Big City Tiger?
I didn' expect the
genuine article to show up.
So you're the imposter?
Say what?!
[MAYA whimpers]
Just calm down.
[TIGRE] Yeah? How'm I s'posed
ta be calm when there's ash
all over my Persian rug?
Was it you?!
No, I had nothing
to do with it, I swear!
Listen, boul.
I'm gonna pummel you
flatter than a pancake,
then use youse as my new rug!
[MAYA whines]
[VIOLA]
I'm sorry.
[TIGRE gasps]
Look. I accidentally
knocked over
the ashtray earlier.
[TIGRE growls]
[PHOENIX]
Oh, man. What am I gonna do?
Now he's gonna
pancake her instead.
It's okay,
I'm just glad you didn't
hurt yourself doin' it.
You know I could never
get angry at you, Violetta.
[PHOENIX]
What happened to the pancaking?
Huh? What was that?
[PHOENIX]
Nothing!
Well... Don Tigre
and I are lovers.
He's very tender with me.
Did you call him Don Tigre?
Yeah! We're
cuckoo for each other!
Got it?
[MAYA whimpers]
As a matter of fact, I owe
this incredible man my life.
You see, I came awfully
close to dying recently.
[giggles
You almost died?
Yes, but I was saved by
my knight in shining armor.
He gave up everything for me.
[giggles]
I'm so happy now. Don Tigre.
I'd do anythin'
for youse, dollface.
[BOTH groan]
What in the hell
are youse two deadbeats
still doin' here?!
Make like some eggs,
and scramble!
[BOTH yell]
[MAYA, PHOENIX]
Yes, sir!
[GUMSHOE]
The Tender Lender?
You might as well kiss your
keister goodbye, cupcake.
I didn't borrow money.
Even for a loan shark,
that operation is super fishy.
And they've had some
sort of trouble lately.
I hear they've been
extra heavy-handed
on calling in their debts.
So, uh... Do you
know who the gloomy lady
we met at the office
could've been?
Yeah. Viola Cadaverini.
Wait a second.
That was the name
I saw on the invoice!
[GUMSHOE] She's the
only living granddaughter
of Bruto Cadaverini.
[PHOENIX]
Should I know who that guy is?
[GUMSHOE] Head of the
Cadaverini crime family.
Controls all the black
market cash in the city.
He's got the Tiger by his tail,
and his you-know-whats.
He sounds scary.
I'm glad we ran into her
instead of her grandfather.
He's about
as tough as they come,
but he sure has one
heck of a soft spot
for that little girl of his.
Hey. Speaking of the Tiger,
the victim borrowed some
scratch from him, too.
How much we talkin'?
[GUMSHOE]
It was around a hundred grand.
[gasps]
Apparently, he was
a big-time gambler
and that's where
all the money went.
Stupid, but kinda gutsy.
Wait, didn't he
win 500,000 big ones
in the lottery that day?
Five hundred grand! I won!
Some guys really
do have all the luck.
[PHOENIX] But... What was he
planning to do if he didn't win?
He'd racked up
some serious debt.
[GUMSHOE] Well, according
to his coworkers,
he said he was gonna use his
skills to pay those bills.
[PHOENIX]
What do you mean?
It seems that the
victim had programmed
a nasty computer virus.
What was he gonna do with it?
If you can create one
with enough wallop to it,
that sucker can
fetch you millions
on the black market, easily.
Now we're talkin'!
Our boy was top of his
game, as far as programmers go.
[PHOENIX] I've never been
savvy with computers myself.
[GUMSHOE] I think
the virus he had written
was called MC-something.
Oh. Was it MC Pipe wrench?
It was MC Bomber, wasn't it?
Yeah, you're right.
It was MC Bomber!
[PHOENIX]
So that CD actually contained
the virus that Glen Elg wrote.
Dunno if this'll help ya,
but it looks like the victim
was planning to meet up
with somebody the day
he kicked his oxygen habit.
Can you tell me who it was?
[GUMSHOE] Sorry, but
I couldn't figure that out.
Aw, man.
I'm sure you tried hard.
Oh, yeah. Hey, kid.
There's something
else I had for ya.
Ooh! Wonder what it is!
Hang on. Well, actually.
It's for Maggey!
[PHOENIX, MAYA]
Huh?
[MAYA]
A lunch box?
Got up early this
morning to make it for her.
I've been worried
because I could tell
she's lost a lot of weight.
That's a lot of weenies.
Good work.
I could eat a buttload
of these little guys.
So please, be a pal
and give this to her.
Sure! Of course, pal!
[TIGRE]
No problem!
Yeah, be right there!
I'm just about to head that way!
Aw, boss, you're
killing me with that joke!
I'm dead! In stitches over here!
Yeah, five minutes, tops.
[snarls]
Damn it all!
This is that
gloomy bitch's fault!
[gasps]
Wow! Weenies!
They're my faves! Thank you.
Did you make this for me?
Nah, it was all Gumshoe.
So these are
Dick's weenies, huh?
He's been worried
half to death about you
and wanted to make sure you
were getting enough to eat.
[MAGGEY groans]
Y'okay?
Well, no. I can't
really eat this crap.
You were so excited to get 'em.
Why don't you take them, Maya?
Are you sure?
[MAGGEY]
Hmm.
[TIGRE]
I'm headin' out, baby!
See ya later.
Please be careful.
[VIOLA]
Don Tigre...
[MAYA snarfing, gulping]
I'm glad you're here Mr. Wright,
because there's
something that
I really wanted to
talk to you about.
Yes, what?
Well, it's concerning
the old man's testimony.
At the time
I took the coffee over to
the victim's table,
there was another customer
inside the restaurant with us.
Wait, do you mean
somebody other than the old man?
Yeah. I do.
There was a strange
woman there, too.
[gasps]
She had some
bandages on her head.
And she was all like...
[VIOLA's giggle]
It was a really creepy laugh.
Hey, isn't that...?
She was present. You're sure?
Definitely!
Was she around because
she was involved somehow?
I'm sorry, the
manager's out right now.
[sighs]
Viola. We're actually
here to ask you something.
[VIOLA] There was a woman
with bandages on her head?
Yes. And she laughed like this.
[VIOLA's giggle]
So...
Huh. I have no clue
who it could be.
[giggles]
Uh... Seriously?
[MAYA]
Hmm...?
May I ask about your bandages?
[MAYA] Oh, yeah! You
said you nearly died.
It was a car accident.
Four months ago, a motorbike
ran out in front of my car,
and we collided.
Then, I had to undergo
a complicated surgery.
The medical bills
were quite expensive.
Thankfully, Don Tigre
was able to save me.
How'd he do that?
He paid for all
my hospital expenses.
He said it was out of love.
That's so noble.
But do you really
believe that's the truth?
[VIOLA gasps]
[PHOENIX]
I apologize for snooping.
But this is the
repair bill for a car.
The vehicle's registered
to the Cadaverini Group.
[VIOLA grunts]
Four months ago, the person
who caused your accident...
...was Don Tigre himself.
[gasps]
[PHOENIX]
Just look at his scooter.
It's practically falling apart.
[PHOENIX] Deep down.
You know this is the truth.
No, sir. He was
being honest with me.
I love you, Violetta.
And that's all there is to it.
[chuckles]
Can't you see?
That's why he stepped
in and saved my life.
He spent all his money on me.
I heard something
about your grandfather.
He controls the
black loan market.
Of course,
Tigre can't anger him.
And I heard that you,
his granddaughter,
mean everything to him.
If you weren't Bruto
Cadaverini's granddaughter,
would Tigre have
paid for your expenses?
[VIOLA sobs]
Hey, take it easy, Nick.
I apologize, ma'am.
But a person's freedom
is on the line here.
Please tell us what you believe.
[VIOLA whimpers]
[TIGRE] This is that
gloomy bitch's fault!
[VIOLA] You're right.
It's because of who I am.
My operation was pretty cheap.
Wait. Hold on.
But didn't you say it
was super expensive?
A million dollars.
Eh?!
The majority
of that money was
for "compensation," though.
Punishment.
[PHOENIX] Tigre had
to pay for the accident.
The pieces are
falling into place.
[VIOLA]
I wanted it to be real.
I wanted to believe
that he loved me.
That it wasn't because
of my grandfather.
I tried to convince myself.
Even though it was a lie.
I just wanted it so badly.
Viola...
And so I did every
possible thing I could.
To help Don get back
on his feet again.
I... I'm sorry.
[sobs]
Where are you going?
Take these. They may help you.
What's in here?
Don Tigre. Watch your back.
Huh?
[PHOENIX gasps]
That was such
a depressing story.
[PHOENIX]
Look. Viola's medical records.
[MAYA]
Why did she give those to us?
[VIOLA]
Don Tigre. Watch your back.
Watch your back, huh?
Maybe. Check the back?
[PHOENIX]
Hmm.
[gasps]
--There it is.
--[engine putting]
[MAYA]
Huh?
[TIGRE]
Hey! You two punks again?
Whatchu got, huh? Lemme see it.
Uh, Nick, what are
we gonna do now?
What'd that dumb broad give you?
Just cuz her
grandpop's the boss,
she thinks she's hot stuff.
Hand that over!
Not a chance. You've no right!
Huh?! Youse wanna
play games wid me?!
[GUMSHOE]
Hold it!
[TIGRE grunts]
[MAYA shrieks]
[GUMSHOE growls]
Detective Gumshoe?
[MAYA gasps]
Huh? A detective?
You ain't gonna stop me, copper!
[yells]
Leave this guy to me!
[MAYA]
You sure you got this?
Just get outta here!
You gotta save Maggey!
If you don't,
she'll be convicted.
Count on us. Let's go.
Yeah!
[PHOENIX] There are two things
I consider inexcusable.
Poisoning and betrayal.
They're the cowardly acts,
and the most hurtful crimes.
I'm going to settle
this in court tomorrow!
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
I'm getting closer to
the truth, I can feel it.
The Tiger, who
pretended to be me.
The bottle found at Très Bien.
Mr. Armstrong's debt
to a loan shark.
The truth behind MC Bomber.
The other man Maggey saw.
It must have been...
Yes!
Everything will be revealed
in the upcoming trial.
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Next episode: "Recipe for
Turnabout -- Last Trial"!
Take that!