[PHOENIX] While the Kurain Urn
was being stolen,
a brutal murder took place in
the office of Kane Bullard,
CEO of KB Security.
Since Ron's alibi for the theft
put him in that very office,
he was arrested
once more for murder.
But the actual
assassin was someone
artfully arranging all this
from behind the backdrop.
This court is hereby
in session for the murder trial
of Mister Ron DeLite.
[RON whimpers]
Court is now
in session for the trial
of Luke Atmey.
Please take your seats.
[PHOENIX]
Two trials linked at the core.
I have to get him to the stand.
If the prosecution is ready.
You may now proceed.
I always limit myself
to no more than 17 cups
of coffee during
any given trial.
But that first one
is something special.
Gives me the right
amount of stimulation.
[JUDGE]
Uh. Okay.
[PHOENIX] I get the feeling
he's ready to grind me up.
[GODOT]
I did some digging.
Trying to find out exactly
why you were terminated
from KB security last year.
[RON whimpers]
It was because
of your wife, wasn't it?
Because of me?
[BOTH gasp]
[RON gasps]
No. You got it all wrong.
Is that so?
In order to satisfy her
thirst for spending,
you stole confidential company
data you thought you could sell.
The CEO found out and
poured you down the drain.
[RON grunts]
[GODOT] Of course, the truth
would leave a bitter taste
in the missus' mouth.
Quitting on "principle"
sounds much sweeter.
Personally,
I'd call it saccharine.
[RON whimpers]
Mister Bullard then
brewed up a plan to spill
the beans about you.
Blackmail. You decided
he needed to get burned.
Ronnie. That can't be true...
[RON whimpers]
Definitely a robust
motive if you ask me.
This is bad.
[GODOT] Moving on. What did you
do after receiving this letter?
We need to know.
[RON gasps]
Just what it said.
I followed the letter's
instructions and went up
to my old boss's office.
I opened the door...
[RON] ...and that's when
I saw a suspicious shadow!
They clocked me hard on the
forehead and knocked me out.
Next thing I knew,
Bullard was dead on the floor!
[gasps]
[BOTH whimper]
[gasps] If I hadn't decided
to wear it that night,
I might have died
right there beside him.
[GODOT]
Huh?
Wait, what protected you?
Oh, I was wearing my mask.
So, you wore a costume?
Yeah. I was wearing
my full "Phantom Thief"
regalia for the meeting.
Mask and all.
[JUDGE gasps]
[gasping]
Uh. Is that important?
Guess I didn't think
to mention it earlier.
It is kind of a major detail.
I would've really
liked to have known that.
Since I was being
blackmailed over my identity
as Mask DeMasque,
seemed like showing up
in the costume would be
the thing to do, yeah?
[groans]
I gotta start to
move things along.
[PAYNE chuckles] Do you have
anything to add, Mr. Atmey?
[LUKE chuckles] Perfect
performance Prosecutor Payne.
Your professionalism
is without parallel.
It appears that we're
absolutely accelerating
toward appropriate adjudication.
As far as stories go,
I'm finding the kid's
testimony a bit unpalatable.
He walked in and
was knocked out cold?
Bit hard for me to swallow.
Look at the evidence!
There are logs documenting
every time the emergency buzzer
in that office rang up security.
And according to the records,
the alarm was hit
just after 1 AM.
If Ron were the killer,
he would've run
as soon as it sounded.
You sure of that?
He would know a
security guard was on the way.
But Ron's previous testimony
stated that he hid
Mister Bullard's body in
the safe after he came to.
Would a killer stay
at the scene when he assumed
a guard was on the way?
[GODOT]
Objection!
But the fact of the matter
is the security guard
never arrived to the scene.
Ah. Yeah, well.
That's just a coincidence.
[BUTZ giggles]
Perhaps the watchman on
duty at the time simply didn't
notice the buzzer going off?
[PHOENIX]
Not a chance.
The alarm is ear-splittingly
loud and impossible to miss.
That is... Unless, you
were completely unconscious
when it sounded, of course.
[JUDGE] You mean the
guard was unconscious?
Surely, you do recall
the defendant's testimony?
Someone hit him over the
head and he only discovered
the victim's body
when he woke up.
So what are you trying to say?
Obviously, when
the alarm went off,
Ron DeLite was
passed out on the floor.
He was? Right then?
By the time the buzzer rang,
Kane Bullard had already
been brutally murdered,
and the defendant was
attacked and rendered
completely unconscious.
With the real killer
choosing that window to escape.
What conclusion
would be reached?
[RON] Anybody walking into
that situation would think
I was the murderer!
And so! The emergency buzzer was
set off by the actual killer!
It was all an attempt
to make Ron DeLite look guilty--
to frame him!
[GODOT grunts]
And just who might
this "actual killer" be?
Are you prepared to
make an accusation?
I believe that it's Luke Atmey.
Oh, yeah?
You do realize the phantom
thief is currently on trial.
Just one courtroom
over, in fact.
[PHOENIX]
He's not the phantom thief.
Two crimes were being
committed simultaneously.
One theft and one murder.
Which of those would
be the lesser offense?
[JUDGE] No question, it would
clearly be the robbery.
If the robbery charge
resulted in a conviction,
that could be used as
an alibi for the murder.
The trial next door
is a cover-up!
A cunning scheme deviously
devised by Luke Atmey!
--[JUDGE] Hmm?
--You can't be serious.
The defense requests
that Luke Atmey take the stand!
Right now! Before the
guilty verdict is declared!
[JUDGE] Now then, this court
is once again in session.
[LUKE growls]
Well, he's here, so now what?
Things are about to get real.
At 1 AM, the night
of September 12th,
Kane Bullard was killed in
his office at KB security.
What were you
doing at that time?
You insist upon the same
imbecilic inquiry, is that it?
I had made a particular pledge.
Yes. To purloin a
priceless piece,
and was in the process
of perpetration.
Simply scrutinize the
stamp on the surveillance
to substantiate said statement
signaling the specific second.
[gasps]
At that time,
you were actually in
the CEO's office at KB Security.
There is no way this
picture could've been taken
when you claim.
[LUKE]
Nonsense!
[JUDGE]
Care to elaborate, Mr. Wright?
What I'm saying is,
this photograph was taken
at 1 AM, several days before
the dual crimes were committed.
You're alleging this
photo was staged, somehow?
[PHOENIX] Yes. And on
the night in question,
you made sure to kill Kane
Bullard at the exact same time.
And this photo...
...is nothing but a false alibi!
Argh! Stop that!
The stamp shows
time but not date,
you used that to your advantage.
[GODOT]
Objection!
Quite an unsavory accusation.
But there's not a drop of proof.
[PHOENIX] Hm. On the contrary,
there is considerably more
than just a drop.
But what may be more damning
is what's missing entirely.
[LUKE]
Huh?
[PHOENIX]
The golden statue of Ami Fey.
In fact, the exhibit's
coordinator made
a statement about it.
[ANDREWS] With the
urn back in one piece,
I realized how ugly
the paint stains looked.
So I hid them
behind Mystic Ami's statue.
On the night in question,
the statue was in direct
view of the security camera.
But then somebody
pushed it away.
I'm sure it was you,
Detective Luke Atmey.
[LUKE growls]
Care to share a motive for that?
[PHOENIX]
Continuity.
If you recall when the statue
was delivered to the warehouse,
it makes perfect sense.
It arrived there
the day before the crimes.
Wait. Hold the phone.
You see now?
That's why I'm confident this
photo was taken days prior
to the incidents.
When that golden
statue wasn't in the frame.
It must've been pretty
jarring walking into the scene.
Suddenly there was a large
set-piece right in the shot,
where it hadn't been before.
Which means, at the very least,
you had to move it somewhere
out of the line of sight.
So everything would
match your pictorial alibi
for Bullard's murder.
Lordly Tailor provided
the security camera,
which prevented you from
tampering with the photo.
But you knew that
no date would be shown,
and exploited that fact!
I'm right! Aren't I?
Answer me!
Agh, gwah!
[GODOT]
This is cup 11.
I'm still good till the
last nutty drop of the 17th.
So you allege Detective Atmey
brewed this whole thing up?
[PHOENIX]
I do.
[GODOT] Hmph.
That just won't fly, mi amigo.
Oh, yeah?
The question isn't where
he was several days before
the crime, but at the time
it was being committed.
You got a claim, but no proof.
And kid, that's
worse than decaf.
[PHOENIX growls]
[CROWD murmurin
Hey, Nick?
Can you prove where he was?
What do we do?
[BOTH gasp]
My proof? I don't know.
[GODOT]
There we are!
Then I say it's about time for
the phantom thief to head back
to his own trial and get served
a hot cuppa justice juice.
One venti verdict, please.
No! Not yet!
[LUKE chuckles, cackles]
Zvarri. I am both
the virtuous and valorous
investigator, and the
vainglorious villain,
which will be verified by my
verdict in the very next room.
I am a vessel of veracity.
And the truth of this twisted
transgression is that Ron DeLite
is the taker of life.
The fact that foppish
fool is a phantom thief
fanatic is merely
a fortuitous fluke.
I mean, this man here
is such a massive maven
of Mask DeMasque,
that he was moved to masquerade
as the mythical midnighter
when meeting his blackmailer.
As the highwayman himself,
his homage is humbling.
[cackles]
No. Ron's gonna
get fried for this.
We can't give up now!
If we find the evidence
we need, then--
We don't have that kind of time.
But why not?
Because of a little
thing we call double jeopardy.
Huh?
That means if a
defendant has been brought
to trial and declared
innocent in a case,
then it's impossible for
them to stand trial again for
the exact same offense.
In the extremely likely
event he is roasted in
the next room and found guilty
for the Phantom Thief crime...
...that would be
an airtight alibi.
It would prove beyond
a shadow of a doubt
his innocence in
Bullard's murder.
If Mister Atmey was
proven to be elsewhere
and found innocent of this
heinous crime, he could
never be tried for it again.
Finally clear on it now?
Poor Ron...
[PHOENIX growls]
[PHOENIX] What can I do? I can't
let this guy get away with it.
[MIA]
Phoenix.
[PHOENIX gasps]
[MIA]
This is your moment to laugh.
[CROWD murmurin]
[MIA]
Come on, Phoenix.
Look at this as an opportunity.
It can't be. She's here?
Turn your thinking around.
You've got this.
Don't you remember
what I used to tell you?
When things seem
most desperate, we laugh.
[PHOENIX]
Mia, I...
We can talk later.
There's work to be done.
But the cross-examination
is over now.
It's not finished quite yet.
That garrulous detective
ran his mouth too much.
In what way?
He got carried away
in what he was saying
and made a fatal mistake.
[PHOENIX gasps]
[MIA]
Think about what he just said.
[PHOENIX grunts]
Gentlemen and gentlewomen.
It's time for me
to face my fate.
Tout à l'heure.
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
Wait. Come again?
Luke Atmey.
You can't leave here.
You basically confessed.
By placing yourself at
the scene of the murder!
Absurd!
[PHOENIX] Recall what
you just told the court.
I mean, this man here
is such a massive maven
of Mask DeMasque,
that he was moved to masquerade
as the mythical midnighter
when meeting his blackmailer.
I was simply stating a fact.
[PHOENIX] How did you know
about that particular detail?
I cannot comprehend your query.
The DeMasque costume.
Ron was indeed
wearing it on that night.
But that specific fact was
not actually revealed until
earlier today in
this very courtroom.
Is that important?
Guess I didn't think
to mention it earlier.
At the time
he shared that info with us,
you were standing trial
in another courtroom,
so there's no way you
could have known about it.
[gasps]
[CROWD murmuring]
But he obviously
did know that somehow.
[PHOENIX] Mm-hmm. There's
only one explanation how
he could corroborate
Ron's testimony.
Earlier, Ron stated
that he had seen
a suspicious shadow just
before he was attacked.
If you shift the perspective
and turn things around,
that would also mean
the shadow saw Ron, as well.
[PHOENIX] That's how Atmey knew
about the Mask DeMasque costume.
[LUKE whimpers]
Because, he was on the scene.
Committing murder!
[LUKE yells]
[RON gasps]
[MIA]
Hmm.
Now look, Atmey.
You have to see how
you just fingered yourself.
So confess to it!
Bravo!
That pyre in your peepers
and your cuspidated coiffure...
...counselor!
You, sir... without
a dollop of doubt...
...do deserve...
A downpour of distinction!
[cackles]
Before you take your leave,
you need to tell us
everything you know.
Is that clear, detective?
Indeed, it was all
initiated on the evening
of Mask DeMasque's inaugural
infractions of illegality.
As he scampered from
the scene, he stumbled into
a side street, where nary
a soul stood sentry.
[LUKE] Nary a soul save
the sobriquet Ace Detective,
surreptitiously
surveying the spot.
So it came to pass that
Mask DeMasque would be unmasked.
At that moment I masterminded
a magnificent maneuver
for myself in the matter
of the moonlighting marauder.
The cat-bird seat I'd
acquired, meant I was capable
of controlling the criminal
and coercing him
into committing
continued capers.
Simultaneously shining
the spotlight on the struggle
surrounding DeMasque
and the Ace Detective.
Whatever I wanted
was well within warrant!
I made myself master of
Mask DeMasque and the masses.
They were practically
pirouetting in my palm.
And... at the conclusion
I could claim his capture.
Resulting in reports of
my righteous reputation
resounding 'round the realm!
Ah! I'd be atop
the apex of acclamation!
You were really
doing all this for fame?
Alas!
An unanticipated obstruction
unfortunately occurred.
I can only guess that
Kane Bullard got a whiff of
the schemes you'd
been percolating?
--[LUKE growls]
--[SECURITY GUARD] Hold it!
[LUKE] I summoned my servant
to steal something sacred
to the CEO of the selfsame
security syndicate.
This scarlet stone.
He figured out the
fact that the fancy fixture
was affixed to my finger.
Before I knew it,
I was being blackmailed by that
behemoth blackguard, Bullard.
Unbelievable!
You mean to tell us
Kane Bullard blackmailed you?
For his deliberate
display of disrespect,
I decided that he should die.
After careful calculation,
it came to me that
I could co-opt my current
client to carry out this caper.
Are you saying you used
the Kurain exhibit as cover?
Yes, precisely!
It could prove possible
to permanently purge
the person picking my pocket.
And furthermore frame the
fabled phantom for the felony.
Thus, in the bowels of
that boutique's basement...
...my magnificently
masterful machinations
were set into motion!
You sent the calling
card to Lordly Tailor.
The next step...
...was to take that staged
photo on the premises
to shore up an alibi.
And then you delivered
Bullard's blackmail letter
to Ron DeLite.
That's what drew him to
KB Security on the night
of the double crimes.
Which brings us to
the last part of the plan.
To take the fall for the stolen
urn which would mean
a far less severe penalty.
Because you thought
you'd be famous?
[LUKE giggles] I'd be lauded
as a living legend
of both law and larceny!
The surprise would
secure my celebrity.
Yes. Imagine the shockwaves,
shuttling throughout society!
An ingenius plan generated
by the most gargantuan
of geniuses to have
ever graced the globe!
That's enough!
[LUKE]
Heh?
[GODOT] You rode up on a high
octane rocket and flamed out
in a blaze of glory.
What's left is dark and empty.
Thirst can make a man
guzzle down everything there is.
At this point, brother,
it's all over but the crying.
[LUKE growls, sobs]
[JUDGE]
In all my years on the bench,
the case brought before
this court today is among
the most complicated that
I have ever encountered
[JUDGE] But justice has
prevailed in the end.
This young man narrowly avoided
being labeled a murderer
and stricken of his freedom.
So it's time this
court hands down
the verdict he deserves.
Not Guilty!
[CROWD cheerin]
[sighs]
[BOTH]
Hooray!
Well done, Phoenix.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you. I needed your help.
Promise me this.
That you'll continue
to watch over Maya.
[gasps]
Did we win?
Yes, we did. Thanks to you.
I appreciate all
your help, Mr. Wright.
You saved my life.
But... the reality is,
I actually don't have
all that much to
live for anymore.
--[PHOENIX] Hmm?
--I know that was stressful,
but don't be so
down in the dumps.
You beat a murder rap,
and didn't even get charged
for whatever you did
as Mask DeMasque.
Ixnay on Askmay.
I was able to
hold on to my freedom.
But I feel like it cost
me everything else.
[MAYA]
Huh?
All I ever truly wanted
was for my darling Dessie
to be happy. But this was
the only way that I knew
how to get enough money to
make sure she stayed that way.
By being the phantom thief?
Dessie is pure.
She's not the type of woman who
would be married to a criminal.
So I know this means
I'm gonna lose her.
Now, calm down.
I'm sure she'll forgive you.
You can't just put a
broken bowl back together again!
[GROUP]
Hmm?
[gasps] You got through it,
Ronnie! I'm so happy!
[RON]
Dessie! That was a close call.
But, listen...
[DESIRÉE]
Oh, sweetie.
Why didn't you ever talk to
me about what was going on?
I knew you were
into Mask DeMasque,
but I never thought
you were him.
I'm sorry, Dessie, I know
you can't stand criminals.
[gasps] Oh. The only
types of people I can't stand
are slimy and
full of themselves.
Like that awful detective.
Wait. Are you saying...?
But you always gave
fair warning and declared
your intentions before
sticking it to your targets.
It only proves that
you're the guy for me.
That kind of sportsmanship
turns me on.
You are talking about crimes.
You mean that?
[DESIRÉE]
Hmm. Hey, Nicky boy.
Uh, yes?
Asking you to defend
my Ronnie was one of
the best decisions of my life.
Thanks for your hard work.
Oh, yeah. Sure!
Aw, look at that. You're
blushing like a little kid.
You guys did such
a wonderful job in there!
Major congratulations!
[gasps]
Hang on. Let me explain.
Making time
with another man's wife.
And right in front of
poor Mystic Maya.
How dare you!
[PHOENIX grunts]
[PHOENIX] As I slipped into
unconsciousness,
I thought about the
case we just closed.
Ron said that a broken
bowl can never be put back
together again,
but I know that's not true.
I offer this urn as exhibit A.
Back in one piece
and better than before.
Well, Mister Trite.
It would appear that the party
has only just begun.
Let's drink in
everything it has to offer.
Ah. Bitter.
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
We were all kids
when it happened.
A tragic incident that sent
a dear friend far away.
But a signal from the radio
reminds us of how close
we really are.
Little Edgeworth may
feel lost living in
that cold von Karma household.
But as we can see, that
which is lost, can be found.
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Our next episode
is an anime original:
"Sound the Turnabout
Melody!" Take that!