[thunder cracks]
[PHOENIX] Among Kurain
Village's sacred treasures
is the "Shichishto," or
"Seven-Branched Sword."
This relic was forged to be
a symbol of life itself.
Though our choices
may seem infinite,
with possibilities branching
out in every direction.
Much like our destinies,
the sword eventually leads
to one end.
It severs the delicate
thread that binds us
to this world without mercy,
and impales us with truth
by slashing through
the fantasy that we can
escape this grim fate.
[MAYA] Wow, I am so glad Pearls
showed me this magazine,
or I would've snoozed
on an awesome chance
to give my spiritual
powers a boost!
Thanks a million, Pearls!
I'm just happy
that it makes you happy!
[PHOENIX chuckles]
[MAYA whimpers]
Oh, my goodness, Nick!
I'll freeze to death
before we get there.
It's so cold!
Ah-choo!
Exactly why
I dressed for the weather.
I'll just think of it as
my first phase of training!
Ah-choo!
That's the way!
We're almost there, Mystic Maya,
you can tough it out!
Yeah!
[PHOENIX] Winter is cold enough
in the heart of the city,
but here we are trudging through
the snow-capped mountains,
all to support Maya
in her training.
Oh! It's right up there.
There's Hazakura Temple!
[giggles]
[PHOENIX chuckles]
[gasps]
[PEARL] This place was built
so spirit channelers
from the Kurain school can
go get additional training.
I-It's amazing!
We made it here alive!
Ah-choo!
[BIKINI] Come in, come in,
right this way!
Have a seat around the fire!
We appreciate it, ma'am.
[BIKINI] Well, we appreciate you
coming all this way.
Now sit down, get cozy!
Oh, yeah!
Now that is exactly
what the doctor ordered!
Quit acting tough and
warm your bones, Nick!
I'm not trying to act tough.
[BIKINI]
Now. Let me introduce myself.
I'm head nun at
our quaint little temple.
My name is Bikini.
Bi...
--...ki...
--...ni?
I wasn't born with that name!
But I took it on when
I came to this temple.
Bi! Ki! Ni!
Not what you expected, is it?
Yep. It can be quite
a shock for some folks!
[laughs]
[GROUP chuckles]
So who might you be?
Me? I'm the one who signed up to
get some specialized training!
[BIKINI] Aren't you
a brave little firecracker?
Coming out here
in the deathly cold.
Oh, to be so young and reckless!
Don't blame me if you die.
[cackles]
What does she have to do?
Chant Kurain mantras
while sitting on ice.
Thirty thousand iterations!
All while dousing herself
with freezing cold water.
--[MAYA] Mm-hmm.
--[PHOENIX groans]
You could turn yourself
into a human popsicle,
if you're not careful.
[MAYA whines] But I don't
wanna be a human popsicle.
Well, get comfortable.
There's a little time
still before dinner.
In that case,
I think a nice hot bath
oughta thaw me out.
Did you say "hot"?
Oh, you youngsters
love to crack jokes.
--[PHOENIX gasps]
--We do training here!
And "hot bath"
is not part of that.
You can shower in
the cold waterfall, though.
[cackles]
I'm dead...
[groans
Maybe you can
boost your power, too!
Oh, Mister Nick,
you'll always go through hell,
or the coldest of water
to prove his devotion.
[ELISE] My, what an
adorable little acolyte.
Do you mind if join you?
The fire's warm.
No, not at all.
Hey. Judging by your outfit.
You must be here to
get a power up as well!
[ELISE] Heh. Sounds delightful,
but no. I'm actually--
[PEARL squeals]
Is something wrong?
Uh, sorry, ma'am. But...
I hope you don't mind me asking
if you're Elise Deauxnim?
Oh. It makes me
so happy you know who I am.
[PEARL squeals]
[MAYA]
Do you know who she is, Nick?
Well, she kinda looks like...
a fortune teller?
[ELISE chuckles]
Good guess.
But I'm a writer and illustrator
of children's books.
Oh, neat. Like picture books?
Looking at your drawings
is a purification ritual
for my heart!
That must be the most
beautiful compliment
I've ever received.
[gasps]
I've thought about writing
a children's book someday!
Oh? When the time comes,
you'll create a
beautiful piece of work.
[MAYA gasps]
Well then, teach me your ways!
Owie!
Oh, no! Are you
hurt badly, my dear?
Nah. I'll be okay.
[PHOENIX laughs] It's karma
for trying to ditch training.
--[MAYA growls]
--Ah!
Sorry 'bout that.
I'm flattered.
But I was just recently
asked by a young man
if he could become
my apprentice.
Oh, really?
He even calls himself
Laurice Deauxnim.
He's around here working
on his landscape sketches.
So, then.
Did you come here to do
research for your next book?
Yes. I suppose
you could say that.
Friends, you'll have
to excuse me for now.
I promised to help with
dinner preparations.
Wow, does that mean
you're going to be
cooking for us tonight?
Yes. So I hope you like curry.
Oh! I'd love to
lend you a hand, if I could.
That's so sweet.
Ooh, let me help!
The two of us will be fine.
I think you should
see the inner temple,
where your training
will be taking place.
Well, sound good, Maya?
[MAYA gasps]
Yeah!
[BOTCH chuckles]
Who knew little Pearl
would meet her idol here?
I've never read her books
but I'm already a super fan!
[PHOENIX] Look! That's
gotta be Dusky Bridge!
[bridge creaks]
[MAYA] "Dusky" Bridge?
More like Spooky Bridge.
What's wrong, Nick?
You're like a weird
shade of green.
Oh. That so?
Well, I don't do heights.
But I'm cool, though.
Yeah.
[PHOENIX]
As long as I don't fall over.
[MAYA]
Just cross it, ya big baby!
[PHOENIX]
No! Maya--
[pants] There goes my
daily brush with death...
[MAYA] Come on, Nick.
You're fine, so hurry!
[MAYA]
Anyone here?
[PHOENIX]
Looks pretty no frills to me.
And that's a rockslide
just waiting to happen.
[MAYA] But the Inner Temple's
Hermit Hall is strong! Yikes.
I'm not so sure
"strong" was accurate.
Is this really where
you're gonna be training?
Creepy, huh?
Probably full of ghosts.
[PHOENIX] Heh. A spirit-medium
that's afraid of ghosts
is kinda ironic.
[MAYA screams]
There's one!
[gasps]
[PHOENIX groans]
[PHOENIX gasps]
Whoa, awesome!
I think she's actually alive!
Hi. I'm gonna be doing some
advanced training
in here tonight.
Oh. I'm Iris, one of the nuns.
We're very glad to
have you at the temple.
My name's Maya Fey.
It's nice to meet you, Iris.
Yes, you as well.
Please excuse me,
I have chores to do.
[PHOENIX]
Ah... Iris! Hang on a sec!
You wouldn't happen to--
[MAYA] What? Nick, you
gotta check this out! Quick!
[PHOENIX]
What am I looking at, exactly?
That woman...
It's her. It's my mom.
[gasps]
Ah!
[MAYA] "Master of the Kurain
School of Channeling.
Misty Fey."
Is that really her?
Do you see that crest
at the top of the scroll?
[MAYA] That's the symbol
of a Kurain Master.
[PHOENIX]
What is it?
[MAYA]
That crest is how I knew.
If it wasn't there, I'd have
no idea it was my mother.
[sniffs]
I haven't seen her
in over 15 years,
so I don't even
remember her face.
[PHOENIX sighs]
Poor Maya...
I am so glad that's over.
You okay? You've turned
a different shade of green.
Yeah. I'll probably
be fine eventually.
[BUTZ]
Hey! Move it, you two!
I'm working on
a landscape here,
and you clowns are ruining it.
I'm not into portraiture--
[gasps]
What the--? It's you!
[BUTZ groans]
Hi! A pleasure to meet you.
Uh... I'm Laurice Deauxnim!
[PHOENIX] Are you insane?!
I know it's you, Larry!
--[blow lands]
--[BUTZ] Owie! Shut up!
My name is Laurice!
And I'm here to do an artistic
study of Dusky Bridge!
[MAYA] Deauxnim?
Oh, are you the apprentice?
[BUTZ]
Truth is...
I was starting to feel
like I didn't wanna be
ol' Larry Butz anymore.
And that's when
I discovered her books!
Elise Deauxnim turned me
into a new man!
Like your heart
had been purified? That it?
Yeah! Exactly!
I have been reborn!
--[motor whirring]
--[ALL gasp]
[PEARL squeals]
Whoa! That is so cool!
Hungry? It's time for everybody
to come and eat dinner!
Meet us in the
Main Hall, if you please.
Time to get some curry!
Just who is she?
She's a beautiful flower.
[MAYA chomping]
Here you go. Eat your fill.
[PHOENIX]
She looks exactly like her.
But there's no way.
That would be impossible!
All right!
I'm stuffed to the gills
with curry and ready
to start my training!
Be careful.
Promise you won't overdo it.
[giggles] Haven't you ever
heard the old saying,
"No pain, no gain?"
Maybe not too much pain, okay?
Best of luck, Mystic Maya.
Luck? Or skill?
[chuckles
Iris. If you would, please
ring the bell at 10 PM
for lights out.
Yes. Of course, Sister.
[PEARL whimpers]
Hey, Pearl. If you'd like...
...you can come
to my room for a bit.
Maybe we could read
some books together.
Yeah, that would be amazing!
But, um... The truth is...
I'm not really the
strongest reader just yet.
[ELISE chuckles] Well,
then I'd be more than happy
to help you improve.
Aw! You're so nice!
So, um... Do you think
you can tell me what this says?
That word is "gravely."
[gasps]
And what's this word?
"Fruition." Those
are fairly difficult words.
[PEARL gasps, giggles]
[PHOENIX]
What the heck is she reading?
[BUTZ]
All right, later, Nicky.
Don't wanna keep
my canvas waiting.
All this snow ignites
an artistic fire
deep inside my soul.
Just try and stop me!
Why would I even wanna stop you?
Looks like a bad winter storm.
[PHOENIX] That tree has
some kinda aura to it.
Is it a weeping cherry?
[IRIS gasps]
[gasps]
Uh, hey, Iris.
Sorry to bother you, good night.
[PHOENIX]
Hang on!
Mister Wright.
Do you need something?
[gasps]
[PHOENIX]
How does she know my name?
Sorry. I'm being rude.
But if you would... could you
take off your head scarf?
[IRIS gasps]
Please, miss.
[PHOENIX] It's way more
than a resemblance.
She's the same person.
But... Dahlia is
still in prison!
[IRIS] Mister Wright.
Is something wrong?
Uh... Excuse me, Iris.
But can we talk for a minute?
[IRIS]
Sure.
I appreciate it.
When did you come
to Hazakura Temple?
I've lived here ever
since I was a little girl.
Because, I really don't
have any family to speak of.
[PHOENIX] People come
here to train and boost
their spiritual powers, right?
[IRIS] Right. The temple
is loosely affiliated
with the Kurain School
of Channeling.
It does seem extremely
different from that place.
I believe that's a good thing.
[gasps]
Communicating with the
dead has never helped anybody.
I don't like it at all.
[IRIS gasps] Forgive me. I have
to ring the bell for lights out.
Sorry, I didn't
mean to get in your way.
Hey. Mister Wright?
Yes?
[IRIS]
If you don't mind...
...I'd like you to take this.
This scarf will protect
you from evil spirits.
On a night like this,
you may need some extra help.
Thanks, but what about you?
Now don't worry about me.
Thanks again.
Uh. Iris?
The two of us haven't ever
met before now have we?
[gasps]
I have to get going.
I have to ring
the bell at 10 PM.
[PHOENIX gasps]
[PHOENIX] She knows me.
There's not a doubt in my mind.
Definitely need to bring it up
with her again tomorrow.
[BIKINI]
Gyaaah!
[PHOENIX gasps]
What the hell?
[gasps]
[PHOENIX]
What is that?
[gasps]
Elise!
[PHOENIX gasps]
Elise! Oh, no.
[whimpers]
[BIKINI grunts]
[gasps]
Wait... Sister Bikini?
Why are you on the ground?
Obviously, because I passed out!
Just hurry up and
call the police! Now!
[PHOENIX]
Ah! You're right!
I don't have my phone!
I think I must've left it back
at the office or something.
[gasps] There's a public phone
next to Dusky Bridge!
Run over there!
[PHOENIX]
All right!
What the...?
[gasps]
No, Maya!
[BUTZ] What the hell do you
think you're doing, man? Stop!
[PHOENIX]
Hey! Let me go! Now!
No way! The freakin'
bridge is on fire!
[PHOENIX] Larry,
you gotta call the police!
Huh?!
[PHOENIX] I'm serious!
There's been a murder
over at the temple!
Wait, for real?
[PHOENIX] I'm worried that
the killer might have tried
to flee across the bridge!
[PHOENIX] Maya's over there
inside the Inner Temple!
[BUTZ]
What? I'm totally confused!
[PHOENIX] Just get it together
and call the police!
I gotta help Maya!
[gasps]
[BUTZ]
Nicky!
[PHOENIX screams]
[Signal Samurai theme plays]
--[MILES] Hello? Er, Larry?
--[BUTZ] Hey man,
It's Laurice Deauxnim! It's bad!
Nick's in trouble, I think he--
Tell me what happened.
[coughs]
[PHOENIX] Reading over
the transcript of Mia's
very first case is
making my head spin.
To think it all revolved
around events that
took place on that same bridge.
The defendant died
in the courtroom,
and Dahlia was involved
in the whole thing.
I had no idea about
some of this stuff.
Almost as crazy as
what happened last night.
Rushing across
that burning bridge,
then plunging into
the icy river.
I'll probably be in
the hospital for a while,
but it's a miracle
I even survived.
I can't believe
I'm stuck here in this bed.
I don't know exactly what
happened at the Temple,
but the police started their
investigation of Elise's murder.
And Iris is in custody as
their number one suspect.
I know she's not a murderer.
But above all else...
...I'm really worried about
what's going on with Maya.
That bridge was the
only way for her to get back.
So she's trapped
inside the Inner Temple.
Dammit. I've gotta
find a way to help her.
[MILES]
I'm shocked to see you're alive.
[PHOENIX]
Miles?
[MILES]
Larry called me last night.
He was crying and
saying that you'd drowned.
[PHOENIX grunts] Nope.
Fortunately, I am still alive.
I guess luck was on my side.
Hey, Miles.
Thank you for coming here.
Actually, it's just a
coincidence that I happened
to be back in the country.
Only for a bit.
[coughs]
This is pathetic,
being stuck here
at a time like this.
Wish I could clone myself.
[gasps]
Miles. I need a favor!
[MILES gasps]
[PHOENIX]
Take this.
And do what with it?
Please defend Iris!
She's not guilty!
What? Hang on!
I'm a prosecutor!
I know. A great one.
There's no problem.
I know you can do this.
[MILES]
There's no turning back now.
I'm Iris, a nun
at Hazakura temple.
I'm Miles Edgeworth.
I was sent here at the
request of Phoenix Wright.
[IRIS gasps] Really? So you've
actually talked to him?
How is he doing?
[MILES]
All things considered,
he's doing remarkably well.
I'm so relieved!
At first I heard that
he didn't survive the fall.
[MILES] Of course Larry had
to go and tell everyone that.
[MILES]
This may seem odd,
but I feel as though you
and I have met before.
I don't see how that's possible.
I hardly ever leave
Hazakura Temple,
so unless you've been there...
Understood. Tell me.
Are you there training to
boost your spiritual abilities?
[IRIS] Mm-mm. I'm afraid
I don't have those abilities.
For me, I'm strictly trying
to atone for my wrongdoings.
The sins of my past.
[IRIS]
I'm training to purify my soul.
About last night...
Can you share with me your
recollections of what happened?
[IRIS]
Of course.
After dinner I led the new
trainee and Sister Bikini
across the bridge and
over to the inner temple,
and then at 10 PM I rang
the bell for lights out.
After that, I was
in my room until I heard
all the commotion.
I'm going to ask you directly.
Did you murder
Elise Deauxnim last night
on the Hazakura temple grounds?
No. I swear it wasn't me.
Before coming here to see you.
I paid a visit to Wright
at the hospital.
He requested I do him a favor.
That I act as your defense
attorney in the trial
tomorrow morning.
What? He really asked for that?
[MILES]
He did. Be honest with me.
You knew him
before this, correct?
[IRIS gasps]
Why... would you think that?
[MILES] He acted strangely
when your name came up
in our conversation.
He couldn't hide it from me.
So let me ask you.
Do you consider him to be
a friend Mister Edgeworth?
Without a doubt.
One of my oldest.
You should know this.
Five years ago,
I betrayed his trust
and deceived him.
What do you mean by that?
[IRIS] Well. Long story,
but I was a weaker person then.
I know that my cowardice
truly hurt Phoenix.
I made a vow that
I would never show my face
in his presence again.
Whatever you did to him,
he's still hurting from it.
I firmly believe
the only cure for
that kind of pain is honesty.
[gasps]
[MILES]
It's not too late.
You can tell him the
truth and set him free.
[IRIS]
I will. I promise.
Very well, then.
I'll provide your defense.
[MILES]
Okay. Now that's taken care of,
it's time to begin
the investigation.
[MILES] I'll have to try
a different approach
in this trial. So I'll do
things your way, Wright.
[PHOENIX]
I may be stuck here in bed.
But the situation is going
to go on without me.
And still...
The Inner Temple is cut off
from everything.
[PHOENIX] Poor Maya.
I really hope you're okay.
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
Iris is in jail, awaiting her
trial for the murder
of Elise Deauxnim. But I have
faith my old friend Miles
can argue her defense
in my absence.
Maya is locked away
inside the inner temple.
How strange that a setting
which figured so largely
in Mia's first case has
come up once again.
As the various motives come to
light, a shocking trial begins!
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Next episode: "Bridge to the
Turnabout - 2nd Trial"!
Take that!