[PHOENIX] The murder at
the French bistro Très Bien
has served up a full
course of mystery.
The strange bottle
found in the kitchen,
chef Armstrong's massive debt,
the computer virus
that the victim wrote
worth millions on
the black market,
and the shadow of the
Cadaverini Crime Family
looming over it all.
But I was able to figure
out who my imposter was.
A dangerous loan shark.
There's only one
thing on my menu:
Justice for Maggey Byrde!
Her trial heats back up today!
Good morning, Mister Wright!
Well, you seem in high spirits!
Dunno 'bout high spirits.
More like high-strung!
Now simmer down!
It's the cops!
[grunts]
And that's my cue to exit!
[PHOENIX]
Uh...
Uh. Maggey, I--
[GUMSHOE groans]
By the way, pal, the lab
results on this came in.
[gasps] They said it was
full of poison, didn't they?
Sorry, but sadly for us,
it's a harmless bottle
of ear medicine.
You don't say.
The victim had a
ruptured eardrum.
This has to be what he was
prescribed to treat it.
[PHOENIX]
What was Glen Elg's ear medicine
doing in the kitchen?
We were able to find some
unknown fingerprints
on the bottle.
They're trying to turn up a
match down at the precinct,
so I'd better run back
to check on that.
See ya!
[GUMSHOE screams]
What's wrong?
[GUMSHOE]
Almost forgot.
How did that lunch I made
for her yesterday turn out?
Uh... Well, it was, uh...
It was delicious!
That's what she said?
Best news I've heard today!
She may not have used
those words exactly.
[MAGGEY] Well, no, I can't
really eat this crap.
Why don't you take them, Maya?
[MAYA]
Uhh...
[GUMSHOE]
Great!
'Cause I whipped up a
jumbo-sized helping today!
Oh, yeah!
She can celebrate her freedom!
[GUMSHOE yells]
[PHOENIX] Anyway, I know
the Tiger is the key
to this whole case.
I have to find a way
to get him to testify.
This court is hereby
back in session
for the trial of
Miss Maggey Byrde.
Let me remind you that
yesterday we were presented
with the testimony of
Mister Victor Kudo.
He claimed to have
witnessed the defendant
pouring a mysterious powder
in the victim's coffee
right before he died.
However, this
testimony was plagued
by some rather troubling
inconsistencies.
Mister Kudo had stated
that he'd seen the victim
pick up his coffee
using his left hand.
But upon examining the mark
on the rim of the cup,
it clearly shows that he
drank his jitter juice
with his right hand.
There was another
questionable point.
He said Elg was
listening to the radio
with an earphone
in his left ear.
But Mister Elg's left
eardrum was ruptured,
so it would've been painful to
be listening through that one.
Seems like we've got
ourselves a steaming cup
of contradictions to digest.
Cheers.
[JUDGE]
Very well.
Let us call upon today's first
witness to take the stand.
[ARMSTRONG]
Bonjour!
Jean Armstrong à votre service!
Génie culinaire!
Muchas gracias, Señor Chef.
You were in the kitchen day of
the incident, is that correct?
[ARMSTRONG]
Oh-la-la!
Well, monsieur. Aren't you
a yummy little bon-bon?!
Oh-la-la! C'est magnifique!
Not my cup of joe.
Ahem!
Please remember, you're
here to give testimony.
Now then, if you would,
tell the court what happened
that day at Très Bien
to the best of your ability.
Truthfully.
Oui, but of course.
On z'at afternoon, Monsieur
Elg was at my bistro.
'E came inside alone.
Pépé Kudo arrived
not long after 'im.
When 'e got word 'e
won le grand prix,
Monsieur Elg became
very aroused, indeed.
Five minutes after
'is 'appy ejaculation,
a 'orrible scene unfolded.
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
You're cooking up some
falsehoods, aren't you, chef?
Nani?
The victim was listening to a
certain radio program that day.
A show called
"Millionaire Radio."
It runs every Wednesday
from 1:30 to 1:40 PM.
And why do you bring 'zis up?
Well, as Mister Kudo told us.
[KUDO]
Gotta say,
that definitely ruined
my javaccino time.
[MIA]
Your javaccino time?
[KUDO] My daily routine is to
enjoy a nice cup of javaccino
at 2 PM sharp every day.
[PHOENIX]
He said it was 2 PM.
If the incident occurred five
minutes after the victim
found out he'd won the lottery,
then Mister Kudo could
not have witnessed it.
Because he wouldn't have
even been in the restaurant
at that time of day!
[ARMSTRONG]
Non!
[PHOENIX]
The earphone in his damaged ear.
The radio program that
should've been long over.
We can clear up
these contradictions
with a simple answer!
The murder Mister Kudo
witnessed on that day
was nothing more than
an elaborate fake!
You think it was staged? How so?
[CROWD whispering]
Are you implying that
the witness was correct
when he testified the
earphone was in the left ear?
The reenactment was
elaborate, not perfect.
Perhaps because the murderer
simply didn't know
about the victim's
ruptured eardrum.
[GODOT]
Objection!
If you're truly serious
about that theory,
let me ask you somethin'.
When the fake was putting on
the act for the old man,
tell me, where was
the real Glen Elg?
By then, he'd already
been poisoned.
[GODOT] But that would've
left behind a corpse.
Surely they wouldn't
have left his body
lying around the bistro.
It stands to reason the killer
must've hidden it nearby.
Maybe in Très Bien's kitchen.
Mon dieu!
[PHOENIX] Mister Armstrong,
do you recognize this?
I 'ave never seen zat before!
All ze bottles I use
are cute and delicate!
This particular one was found
inside Très Bien's kitchen.
Why would that 'orribly
plain zing be zere?
What a pertinent question.
Analysis shows this bottle
contains the ear medicine
prescribed to the victim.
Non, but 'ow could zat be?
It must've fallen
out of his pocket
while his body was
being stowed there.
So, let me ask you this!
You were back in
Très Bien's kitchen
when the incident
occurred, were you not?
Sacre bleu!
Immediately after the incident,
you told Victor Kudo
to call the police,
causing him to leave the scene.
The only witness was
gone for ten minutes,
which the killer
put to good use.
In that time, he took the
body back to the table
and put the bottle of poison in
the pocket of the defendant
who was still unconscious
on the floor, right?
[gasps]
Only one person could've
pulled that off.
You, Chef Armstrong!
[ARMSTRONG]
Oh! No!
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
Seems the defense has made
a rather stunning allegation
that the witness was
the actual perpetrator.
Did you murder Mister Elg?
No, never, I swear
on everyzing tasty!
I think scumbags who perjure
themselves in court
should have their
mouths rinsed out
with a piping hot pot of coffee.
No cream or sugar.
[ARMSTRONG gasps]
Je vous demande
pardon, monsieur!
Please, you must 'ear me out!
[JUDGE]
Mhm.
Tell your story. Remember,
perjury is a serious offense.
[ARMSTRONG]
Oui. I understand.
It is true zat I 'id zat man's
lifeless body inside ze kitchen.
But I 'ad no choice.
Un homme forced me to do it.
And then you waited
around for ol' bird brain
to show up like he usually did
so he could see
the re-enactment.
But I swear to you I 'ave
never killed anybody
in my entire life!
I am not 'zat kind of person!
Someone forced you into it?
Who was this mystery man?
My lips, zay must remain sealed,
or else I myself will be
thrown into ze broiler.
Chef Armstrong. Look.
We know there's a man
with leverage over you.
The holder of this loan.
[gasps]
You're 500 thousand in the
hole with this loan shark.
That's why you have no choice
but to do whatever he asks.
Right, sir?
Let ze accusations fly,
I cannot confirm or deny
zees zings you are saying.
You are in a very
dangerous situation, sir.
You claim someone
forced you into this,
so tell us who it was.
The firm Tender Lender
holds this loan.
Mon dieu!
Run by the Big City Tiger.
He made you do it!
I figured this would happen,
so I called this wild
tiger in to testify.
He's here right now.
[PHOENIX gasps]
[MAYA screams]
[PHOENIX]
What the--?
[TIGRE]
You want me?
[PHOENIX]
This is my big chance!
So, uh, your name is Mister
Big Tiger, is that correct?
That's what they
call me! Yeah!
[grunting]
[MAYA screams]
[MAYA]
Huh?
Who the hell's got the stones
to call the great Furio
Tigre to this dump?
Was it you, red eye?
You know that you don't
have to yell like that.
Yeah?
But we should expect
a tiger to growl.
Especially when he's been
trapped in a legal cage.
Let's start with
the basics, shall we?
Tell us everything you know
about the incident in question.
Ha! I don't know
nuttin', cyclops!
I'll ask you this.
Were you a spectator
at Maggey Byrde's
murder trial a month ago?
My time's too valuable to waste
it in some courtroom, boul.
Listen up, smart guy,
I'll bill ya 50K for
every dumbass question.
And my interest rate
is a real killer.
Hey, Nick. You got this!
Are you hiding?
So tell us, Mister Tigre,
on the day of the murder,
you had made plans to meet up
with Glen Elg at Très Bien
bistro, is that correct?
What?
I don't know nuttin'
about none of that
or what the hell a
tray bee'in even is!
You're lying to me.
Nuh-uh!
[PHOENIX]
Then can you explain this note?
What the--? Where'd you
get dat from, huh?
Take these. They may help you.
Don Tigre. Watch your back.
Viola's medical records.
[MAYA]
Why did she give those to us?
"Watch your back," huh?
Maybe... Check the back?
[PHOENIX]
Hm.
[MAYA gasps]
There it is.
[PHOENIX]
This note, in your handwriting,
is decisive proof that
you were planning
to meet the victim
at the crime scene
the very day he was murdered!
[yells]
This calls for another
steaming cup of liquid gold.
[growls]
That stupid broad.
Heh!
What does it matter if I
made plans to meet dat kid?
Note doesn't say "kill 'em."
Have you already forgotten
the old man's testimony?
He stated that the victim
was all alone at his table.
Have you forgotten about
the defendant's testimony?
She told the court, under oath,
there was another man
sitting there that day.
So that must mean only one
of them is telling the truth.
You know which one
that would be?
Well they're both
true, actually.
[MAYA]
Huh?
[PHOENIX]
The incident the defendant saw,
and the incident Mister
Kudo witnessed,
were two completely different
events altogether.
And your theory is
the second one
was just a little performance
so they could frame the lady?
Now that's a hot take.
Yes.
The "victim" Kudo
saw was an imposter
who was pretending to
be Glen Elg for the show.
But I know who that phony was.
And he's right over there.
Furio Tigre!
[TIGRE]
Damn you!
[screams]
[MAYA screams]
[BOTH yelp]
Calm yourself!
Or I'll have you thrown
out for contempt!
You'd better stop
with all the banging
before you get
thrown out with him!
[JUDGE gasps]
[PHOENIX] The defendant fell
to the floor unconscious
immediately after the incident.
As she lay there,
somebody got the idea
to try and frame her
for Glen Elg's murder!
That was when our
feline friend over here
pretended to be
the victim, right?
But somebody had to play
the role of the waitress
serving up his final
cup of the good stuff.
Viola Cadaverini.
Who happens to be a
Tender Lender employee.
[TIGRE growls]
[TIGRE] Youse makin'
a big mistake wit' her.
Both she and the Tiger set up
the fake murder together!
[GODOT]
Objection!
Shouldn't jump to
conclusions, you know?
It's not a good
look for anybody.
What the heck are
you talking about?
[GODOT] You're overlooking
a critical detail.
There's simply no reason
for the ol' tiger man
to poison the victim.
[BOTH]
Uh?
[grunts]
It wouldn't make any
sense for me to kill 'em.
He won 500 grand, but he only
owed me a hundred thou.
So that means he could pay
back what he borrowed
and I wouldn't have to do the
wet work and grease nobody.
[PHOENIX]
But the fact is,
a hundred thousand wasn't
nearly enough, was it?
The hell you mean?
About six months ago, you caused
a traffic accident, didn't you?
Say what?
[PHOENIX]
The victim was the granddaughter
of the head of the
Cadaverini crime family.
They wanted about
a million from you
to pay for her
extensive surgeries.
Which are listed on
her medical file!
If you didn't compensate
them for the expenses,
you'd be the one
getting "greased."
So you had to do
whatever it took
to get your hands on the money.
Even if he killed Elg and
took his lottery ticket,
that's half the money
he owed the Cadeverinis.
He'd still be deep in the
hole for the rest of it.
But it wasn't the
money he was after.
Oh, yeah?
[PHOENIX]
This is MC Bomber.
An especially potent computer
virus the victim had written.
Why do youse have dat?
Glen Elg had a reputation
as a skilled programmer.
That skill was the collateral
on his loan from you.
A virus such as this one
could net you millions
on the black market.
Wow. Millions, you say?
If you got your
hands on that disc,
you could pay off
the Cadaverinis.
That's what you thought, right?
And so, on that day, when he
won that 500 thousand lottery,
which meant he wouldn't
have to give you the CD,
you decided to go
with another plan.
[PHOENIX] To murder Glen Elg
and steal the virus anyway.
And then you made
a last-ditch effort
to frame the defendant
for the crime!
But that wasn't enough
to satisfy you.
A month ago,
you pretended to be me in
a trial in this courtroom.
Really? He impersonated you?
He posed as her lawyer
in the first hearing
and made sure to lead her
into a guilty verdict!
[growls]
I have to say, this is
making sense to me.
There's something
familiar about you.
I'm sorry about the
mix up, your honor,
but I would never dream
of doin' anything like that.
I'd say the defense
just got decaffeinated.
What'll you do?
You scared me!
[PHOENIX]
I'm so close,
but I don't have the
evidence to back it up.
[GUMSHOE]
It's the cops!
[MAYA, PHOENIX]
Gumshoe's here!
[GUMSHOE]
I came to drop some evidence!
And this is gonna clinch
this whole thing up!
All in the name of love!
Are you drunk?
I wonder what he means.
[growls]
Turns out, that bottle we'd
found had Furio Tigre's
grubby fingerprints all over it.
Huh?
[MAYA]
That's it, Nick! We did it!
What's the matter?
This just isn't the
smoking gun we needed.
His prints may be on it,
but that doesn't serve as
a way to prove my theory.
He admitted that he'd met with
the victim that same day,
so he could've
touched the bottle.
No, that's awful.
[PHOENIX] I can't prove
my case with evidence.
How can I get myself
out of this corner?
Come on, Phoenix!
You gotta use your brain!
So, what now?
All right. Looks like
you're screwed, boul.
Defense, would you care
to explain to the court
what exactly that bottle
has to do with the murder?
[PHOENIX]
I've got it!
I would like to
introduce this item
as the defense's final
piece of evidence.
Why the hell should
we give a crap
about that tiny little bottle?
Because it contains
the potassium cyanide
that cut Glen Elg's
life short that day.
What?
Pump your brakes, kid.
In other words, your
fingerprints were found
all over the murder
weapon itself.
And there's only one way
that could've happened.
I think you're
confused, Bubba.
[TIGRE laughs]
You're a real clown.
You should quit your day job,
especially when you think
a lame bluff like that
is gonna take down Don Tigre!
I don't see what's funny.
The bottle with
the cyanide in it
wasn't some cheap,
plastic piece of garbage
it was a nice brown one,
made outta glass.
[PHOENIX]
He stepped right in it.
So that's the game
you're playin'. Huh.
What's the deal?
Why did everybody
get all quiet-like?
You described the cyanide
bottle in detail, Tigre.
Just like this, right?
Yeah, that's it!
But youse ain't gonna
find none of my prints
anywhere on that thing!
Don't let this clown
pull a fast one on ya!
Tell 'em they got nothin'
on me, coffee boy!
I'm guessing you still don't
realize what you just said.
Rewind your brain a sec
and think about it.
What I said? Which part of it?
[PHOENIX] Today was the first
time you'd been summoned
to the court regarding
Miss Byrde's case.
If you had nothing to
do with the murder,
you'd have no way to know
any of the finer details.
Like what kind of bottle the
poison was in, for example.
Yeah? Well, I--
[PHOENIX]
You just described it to a tee.
Then went on to identify it in
front of everyone gathered here.
Yeah, so what?
I just seen it before.
They showed it at the
chick's trial last month.
It is true that the
bottle in question
was presented as evidence
in Miss Byrde's first
hearing a month ago.
However, you stated earlier that
you didn't attend that trial,
nor knew anything
about the case itself.
[TIGRE]
I did see it then!
I was right over there.
Where youse was standin',
playing the defense lawyer.
And that brown bottle
was brought out
in front of everyone.
He was the guy!
So what you're actually
admitting to, Tiger,
is that you impersonated
Mister Trite
in the previous murder trial?
Uh, that's right!
I didn't kill the guy,
I just saw the poison bottle
during dat dog and pony show!
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
[yells]
Then explain to the court
why you would even do that!
Why would you go to
all that trouble
to pretend to be someone's
lawyer in a trial
that had nothing to do with you?
Look, I, uh.
[PHOENIX] There's only
one plausible reason.
You were trying to cover up
a murder you committed!
I have to appreciate the
irony that a fraud like you
was brought down by a bluff.
There's a kind of
"poetic justice" quality
to the whole thing.
You tried to trick
the legal system
by pretending to be
something you're not,
only to reveal how much
of a criminal you are!
[screams]
Today the defendant was given
a second chance at justice
and the truth has prevailed.
This court has found
Maggey Byrde...
Not guilty!
[CROWD cheering, applause]
[chuckles]
[MAYA chuckles]
[TIGRE]
Huh?
Violetta. Why'd you sell
me down da river?
It's simple. I did it
because I'm a Cadaverini.
We always get our payback.
You know I could never
get angry at you, Violetta.
I'm so happy now, Don Tigre.
I'd do anythin' for
youse, dollface.
[growls]
Damn it all! This is that
gloomy bitch's fault!
I'm headin' out,
baby! See ya later.
[VIOLA]
Don Tigre.
Thank you so much,
Mister Wright!
I can hardly believe that you
saved my bacon a second time!
Speaking of food,
we brought some snacks
to help celebrate
your victory today!
[MAGGEY gasps]
You know, weenies
aren't really my thing.
If you wanna thank someone
for getting you out of jail,
you should thank Gumshoe.
He worked his tail off.
Put in a lot of hours because
he was so worried about you.
Right up until the last moment
when he brought in the
final piece of evidence
to seal the case.
Are you sure you're not hungry?
[MAYA gasps]
How 'bout we go in
halfises, Maya?
Okay!
Honestly, I was just
being bratty before.
Weenies are my favorite food!
[GUMSHOE gasps]
[PHOENIX chuckles]
[GUMSHOE]
This is great!
I am so darn happy!
You really redeemed
yourself, Dicky!
[PHOENIX] I think we've all
had our fill of fakes.
The truth is much
more satisfying.
Maggey's reputation and her
plate have both been cleaned.
And she's ready to enjoy the
next course life has to offer.
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
The Silver Star luxuriously
shoots through the night
along the coastline.
Maya and I were invited to take
a ride in the ultimate comfort.
And it turns out Detective
Gumshoe and the judge
have also come along.
Unfortunately, the trip
goes off the rails
when the train is hijacked.
The perpetrator demands
an impromptu trial
aboard the non-stop express!
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Next episode: "Northward,
Turnabout Express -- 1st Trial"!
Take that!