[MAYA] And now, I shall
hereby hand down my verdict!
I find the defendant,
super guilty!
No! If only I had
an Ace Attorney to help!
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
[MAYA]
Who is that?
[PHOENIX] A man who
believes in his clients.
And will strike down
any evildoers!
Lawyer Samurai,
Phoenix Wright enters the fray!
Sally Forth!
Going to court, you say?
Call Wright and
company right away!
[PHOENIX groans]
[MAYA]
Hmm. Nope.
One more time!
With some feeling!
[groans]
Do we have to?
You bet!
We're not stopping until
we get the perfect take.
--[stomach growling]
--[BOTH gasp]
[MAYA]
Well, maybe after a snack.
[PHOENIX]
I'm not cut out for showbiz.
Huh? You're really
gonna stop filming?
[coughs] I think we should
try exploring other avenues
to get the word out.
I get ya.
You just don't feel like the
Lawyer Samurai character works.
--Well...
--How's this for an idea?
A new character, called
the Lawyer General.
You're completely
missing the issue here.
[ Signal Samurai theme plays]
[gasps]
It's your song!
The Signal Samurai theme!
Reminds me of when I was a kid.
That was your favorite right?
You still have the figures.
Radio, huh?
[MAYA]
Hmm? What's on your mind?
Oh. I just kind of
have a thing for radio.
[MAYA] Really? I bet
there's a story behind that!
[PHOENIX]
Hmm.
[PHOENIX] Well, it all started
when I was in middle school.
[PHOENIX hums]
[BUTZ]
Yo!
Hey, man.
Hey, Nick.
So, did you watch
Rainbow Samurai yesterday?
[BUTZ]
Huh?
Take down evil
with colorful justice!
No way. I told ya,
I grew out of that kid's stuff
after Signal Samurai.
What a buzzkill.
Yeah, yeah whatever.
Radio's my jam.
Grown-ups only.
You don't say.
[DEE] Sending you some good
vibes while you grab some
quick bites, it's your portable
lunch date, Delicious Dee.
She's sweet and yummy.
[DEE] Watch out for this
track 'cause it's spicy!
Hold the wasabi and taste
the fire through the airways.
Aw, yeah!
So, this is you
being an adult, huh?
[BUTZ]
Hm? You dropped something, bro.
[PHOENIX gasps ]
I can't believe you still carry
that dinky little thing around.
Yeah, well...
I'd bet my life ol'
Edgy-boy's thrown his
in the trash by now.
Sounds like something he'd do.
After all, he transferred
without telling us
how to keep in contact.
I don't think it's fair
to blame him for that!
When you think about
what happened to him.
Yeah, you're
not wrong, but still.
[PHOENIX]
Three years ago.
There was a horrible murder
that actually happened
inside the courthouse!
The victim was Miles' father.
A prominent defense attorney.
With nobody left to call family,
Miles had to move out of town.
We haven't heard so much
as a word from him since.
We still don't know
who killed his dad.
But whoever it was
left him to die alone.
[PHOENIX] Wherever Miles is,
I hope he's okay.
[BUTZ]
Yeah me, too.
And I hope his li'l
pup is doing well.
[MISSILE yipping]
[MISSILE pants]
[MILES]
Uh...
[MISSILE barks]
Cool. Right? He looks like Papa.
Why'd you go and dress him up?
Well, because...
...I thought it would
make you smile.
[gasps]
[gasps] I think this cravat
suits him better, though.
[MISSILE whines]
[FRANZISKA]
Hey! Don't go! Come back!
[sighs]
[pants, barks]
[FRANZISKA yelps]
[NARRATOR]
Yo, yo, yo!
Seven blades of justice,
each a different shade!
[RAINBOW SAMURAI]
We are the Rainbow Samurai!
[FRANZISKA]
That's so lame.
[MISSILE pants]
[KARMA]
Hm?
I'm glad you're home, Papa.
[MILES]
Welcome back, sir.
[KARMA]
Hm.
How was court today?
I'm sure you won,
like you always do, right?
But of course.
That's because you're the best!
Some day, I'm going to be
a prosecutor, like you.
Obviously.
Will you follow in your
father's footsteps?
[MILES gasps]
Oh. I'm not quite sure.
I know.
Why don't you take Miles to one
of your trials sometime, Papa?
Oh. He doesn't have to.
Consider it done.
[FRANZISKA]
Yay! In that case,
I'd like to go with you--
there's something I really
want to do afterwards!
[MILES]
I miss you...
[KARMA] Let's get to work
on this orphanage deal.
I'll be sending
Miles there soon.
[groans]
That damned old wound.
You're still trying to get in
my way, aren't you, Edgeworth?
Even beyond the grave.
Let him go!
Don't hurt my father!
[gunshot]
[KARMA bellows]
[gasps]
[MISSILE whines]
[DEE]
So what's on today's lunch menu?
I'm being bad and
having jelly donuts.
Yum, yum, yum, yum.
Yum-my!
[PHOENIX]
Cutting class, I see.
[DEE] All right, my Dee-vo-tees,
this one is a special request!
[PHOENIX]
Yes! That's it!
This is how we can
get in touch with Miles!
Huh?
[PHOENIX chuckles]
[LAWYER growls]
This wasn't in discovery.
I object!
[KARMA] It's your fault
for not being thorough
in your investigation.
Von Karma is
meticulousness personified.
But you are a subpar attorney.
Don't forget: Someone's
life is in your hands.
Guilty!
[CROWD cheering]
[gasps]
[EDGEWORTH] Von Karma's
an extraordinary attorney.
But, aren't prosecutors
your enemies?
That's not how I look at it.
We fight each other, sure,
but to find the truth.
At the end of the day, it's
both our jobs to make sure
evil is punished.
Or at least, that's
how it should be.
Incredible work.
Would you like to comment?
[REPORTER B] Your perfect
record remains intact!
I don't care about my record.
I fight for justice.
That's my duty.
[FRANZISKA] Papa never
lets any criminals get away.
He always wins!
He's basically a superhero.
I can't wait to grow up
and be just like him.
Maybe I'll even get
to be his partner.
[FRANZISKA]
Papa!
Your case was
absolutely perfect.
[KARMA]
Naturally.
Brilliant cross-examining.
If only your father
had been my opponent.
Then I might actually
have enjoyed myself.
[gasps]
Why don't the
two of you wait in the car.
'Kay!
[FRANZISKA gasps]
[MISSILE barks]
Can you spare some
change for these dogs?
A little goes a long way!
Hey, come on! Let's shop.
[MILES]
Sure.
[FRANZISKA] I think this
place is huge overseas.
But there's only one in Japan.
Whaddaya think?
The red one or the blue one?
Uh. I dunno.
Well. In that case...
...I'll go with the red one.
It's almost the same
color as your vest!
Oh! Papa! Look at these!
[MISSILE barks]
[FRANZISKA gasps]
Wait! Come back!
Stay here. I'll go get him.
Sure. Please hurry!
Missile! C'mere!
[gasps]
Please, forgive me.
[GOLDY]
Hmph! What a rude boy.
[DEE]
Now for some serious news.
A little poor doggo's
gotten lost in
the Lordly Tailor Shopping Mall.
Lordly Tailor? Wait, here?
[DEE] Her name is Napalm,
and she's a white Pomeranian
wearing a cute
little pink ribbon.
The heart-shaped spot on her
belly makes her extra special!
The owner's really
worried about her.
Wait, is this right?
There's a 5,000 dollar reward?
I guess my dog's not the
only troublemaker here today.
[DEE] Anyway,
here's a special request.
[Signal Samurai theme plays
Signal Samurai?
[theme continues to play]
You guys...
I want to become a defense
lawyer, just like my dad.
[gasps]
You'd be amazing!
I can't wait to watch
you battle in court!
[gasps]
I can't wait to grow up
and be just like him.
Maybe I'll even get
to be his partner.
If only your father
had been my opponent.
Then I might actually
have enjoyed myself.
[MILES]
Father. What should I do?
[DEE]
What a catchy throwback.
That's a request coming
to you from Signal Blue.
[MILES gasps]
[DEE]
Oh, wow, cool!
It even comes with
a heartfelt message.
Signal Red.
Hope you're doin' well.
We miss you.
[DEE, PHOENIX]
And your puppy, too.
[PHOENIX] I really wish
we were all together
playing Signal Samurai again.
I know you had to
move away suddenly,
but know it doesn't
matter where you live.
I've always got your back
and am rooting for you.
We'll meet again one day.
I know it.
That was you, Wright?
[DEE] I hope Red and
Blue meet again, too!
Darlin' Dee's
cheering for you two!
You never change, do you?
I'm glad.
[MISSILE barks]
[MILES gasps]
[NAPALM whines]
I see. So that's
why you ran away.
[MILES] A white Pomeranian
wearing a ribbon.
You must be Napalm, right?
[GOLDY]
Ah. There's my widdle baby.
[MILES gasps]
I looked all over for you.
You naughty little pup.
[FRANZISKA sighs]
What's wrong?
We came all the way here
so you could eat pancakes.
I know.
But... I want to wait for Miles.
Thank you so much
for finding my precious girl.
I'm Goldy. And that fluffy
nugget is my bad dog.
Ah. You're the owner?
Thank goodness.
Oh, yes. I was
so worried about her.
[NAPALM growls]
Oh, she's playing.
She's mad that her mama lost
track of her while shopping.
[MILES]
Yeah. Seems like it.
I never did have kids.
So. You know, I may have
spoiled her because of that.
--[NAPALM growls]
--It's okay. Come to Mommy.
Get over here!
Poor dear. She's rattled.
I guess I'll have to give
her some extra treats.
[laughs]
We're leaving, Napalm.
[NAPALM barks]
It doesn't sound
like she's happy
to be going with you.
Is that right?
So, you think you know
better than her mother, then.
I don't mean
to sound rude, ma'am.
But are you certain that
you're the owner of this dog?
Why would I lie about that?
[MILES]
I'm sorry.
But something about this
situation is making me uneasy.
I see. You're trying
to steal my dog?
I knew you looked
like a delinquent.
[MILES]
What was that?
[FRANZISKA gasps]
Miles--
Here's a bit of advice.
You've got an ugly mutt already.
If you know what's good for you,
you'll take him and leave now.
[MISSILE barks]
Do you have proof
that she's yours?
[laughs]
Proof. Sure.
I know everything
about my darling.
[gasps]
She loves being brushed.
Especially on her tummy.
Isn't that right, sweetheart?
She's got this adorable
heart-shaped spot on her belly
that she likes tickled at
the end of the day.
Ooh! Look, Look!
[NAPALM whines]
It's our favorite game!
We play it every night
'cause she's my dog.
Now. If we're done here,
I'd like to be on my way.
[MILES]
Okay. Fine.
[laughs] Come on, pumpkin.
We should get you home.
[MISSILE whimpers]
[NAPALM whines]
[GOLDY] Stupid kid. Now that
reward money is all mine.
[GOLDY singing Signal Samurai]
♪ O-O-Oh. Olde Tokyo. ♪
Hold it!
[gasps]
One more thing.
That theme song...
Are you a fan?
I'm sorry, what do you mean?
[MILES] Do you know
the TV show it's from?
Um, maybe. It just happened
to pop into my head.
[MILES]
Actually, there's something
I've heard said before.
That there are no such
things as coincidences
or random occurrences.
[GOLDY]
Huh? What are you talking about?
Our actions are never
completely random.
Everything we do,
we do for a reason.
It's almost the same
color as your vest!
For example, the song
you were singing.
You may think it came to
your mind out of nowhere.
But I don't believe in chance.
What I'm thinking is,
you heard it recently.
[gasps]
[DEE] Anyway, here's
a special request.
[Signal Samurai theme plays]
Just like me.
You heard the song playing
a few minutes ago.
--On the radio.
--[gasps]
What's more...
...at about the same time,
the DJ had some news.
That whoever found this
poor lost dog would be
rewarded handsomely.
She even mentioned that
heart-shaped spot on her belly.
Wait. I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I heard nothing.
Then how'd the
song get in your head?
Oh, I remember now.
Yeah, it was on TV earlier.
It's the theme song
to a children's TV show.
And before, you said
you didn't have any kids.
Well. It's a popular
enough tune.
I'm sure it was on in a store.
[MILES]
Objection!
[GOLDY gasps]
I hate to break it you,
but that would be impossible.
What? How come?
[MILES]
Because... Signal Samurai ...
...has been off the air
for three full years.
[GOLDY wails]
[NAPALM whines]
Just admit it,
you were listening to the
same station I was.
Who the hell do you
think you are, brat?
Don't you know not
to question your elders?
If you really are
the owner of that dog,
aren't you forgetting something?
Huh? What do you mean?
Five thousand dollars.
[gasps]
I found Napalm for you.
Which means...
you owe me a reward.
[GOLDY growls]
[MILES]
If you want to take her home.
You'll have to pay me first.
[GOLDY growls]
[bellows]
[GOLDY] You don't get to tell
a woman like me what to do.
Hand over that
mutt and scram, kid!
That's enough!
[GOLDY]
Huh?!
Your scheming
ends here. Be gone.
Hey. Who are you?
You can't just--
[KARMA]
Oh. Can't I?
Would you like to
present your case again?
--In court, this time?
--[whip lashing]
[FRANZISKA]
Hmph.
[GOLDY whines]
No. I won't go back to prison!
[sobs]
[FRANZISKA] Miles. We've been
looking all over for you.
I apologize for
causing you trouble.
Let's go. I imagine the
pancakes must be ready by now.
Yummy! Come on!
[FRANZISKA sighs]
I had so much fun today.
[VOLUNTEER] Please spare
some change for these pups!
You can change a life!
[MILES] Sir. If I receive
the reward money,
can I donate it to
this animal shelter?
Really?
[VOLUNTEER]
Got some change to spare?
--Save a dog!
--Please, sir.
You're the one
who found the dog.
Do as you wish.
Thank you so much!
[KARMA]
Regarding the orphanage.
Let's table that.
[KARMA] I've been wondering
what made me adopt
that boy three years ago.
When he was so hurt
over the loss of his father.
And I think today,
I finally began to understand
how we ended up
in this situation.
It wasn't because of my guilt.
I simply wanted to see where
the path of pain would lead us,
and how he would
eventually develop.
Karma has a strange
way of showing itself.
You can wear this
from now on if you would like.
[MILES gasps]
[laughs]
Thanks!
Well, you helped
me out once again...
...my friend.
[gasps]
[BUTZ] Huh? What are you
standing around for?
Let's go.
[PHOENIX]
Right! Coming.
[MAYA] So? Did Edgeworth
really hear the song?
How's it all end?
Who knows?
I'm sure it found
its way to him.
Just like our killer
ad will reach him
and everyone else in the world.
Uh, yeah, about that...
Now that it's done,
how do we get it out there?
What are you talking about?
We'll just throw it up on
the Internet and watch it
rack up the likes. Easy!
What are you waiting for?
Upload it now.
[PHOENIX] I don't know. I'm not
exactly great with computers.
They're so... confusing.
[MAYA hums]
--Here goes.
--[gasps] Hold on!
[MAYA]
And... done!
[MAYA, PHOENIX] ♪ Call Wright
and company right away! ♪
What the heck?
Hey. You didn't tell us how
crazy Japanese law ads can be.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
Maggey, The Goddess
of Misfortune, returns!
And, just her luck, she's been
accused of murder yet again!
This time, the crime happened
in a fancy French restaurant,
and nobody believes
what she has to say.
[PHOENIX] But even if
everyone thinks she's guilty,
I'm on her side!
Trust me, Maggey!
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Next episode: "Recipe for
Turnabout--1st Trial"!
Take that!