[PHOENIX] We've learned that
the murder at Hazakura Temple
was actually an attempt to
wipe out the bloodline
of the Kurain School of
channeling's main family.
A hit job orchestrated by
none other than Morgan Fey.
Also, the true identity of
the victim was revealed.
It was Misty Fey, Maya's
long-lost mother.
The final day
of the trial delivered
the biggest twist so far.
Sensing something
odd about Iris's behavior,
I realized who she really was.
The person on the
witness stand was not Iris,
but the spirit of her twin
sister, Dahlia Hawthorne,
who had recently been
executed for her crimes.
[DAHLIA]
My name is Dahlia Hawthorne,
and I'm permanently retired.
[PHOENIX] Now I need to know
where the real Iris is,
and if Maya is still alive.
[CROWD murmuring]
[GODOT]
Dahlia Hawthorne, huh?
So. It seems you're done
trying to hide your identity.
Yeah, well. I'm dead.
So what does it matter?
I was executed, so it's
not like I can be punished
any harder, right?
[JUDGE]
How is this possible?
These instructions
detail Morgan Fey's plan
for that night.
Tell me--Did you have
prior knowledge of this?
I did. Although I was
on death row at the time.
I was still allowed to
visit with my mother
every now and then.
She told me of her plot
during one of those visits.
[JUDGE] And what was
she planning, exactly?
[DAHLIA]
She wanted to murder Maya Fey.
[PHOENIX]
So the real target was Maya?
[DAHLIA] The idea was
that I would kill her.
Then Iris would be
the one to hang for it.
Things didn't go
exactly as we wanted,
but it all worked out.
[PHOENIX]
You're wrong!
Maya's trapped inside the
sacred cavern, but she's alive!
Still such an idiotic optimist.
Oh, Feenie.
[PHOENIX growls]
Let me share
a little something with you.
When I met you that day,
it was hate at first sight.
But after I got to know you,
and saw the naive faith
you have in others,
I grew to despise you.
[PHOENIX]
Why would you kill Maya?
[DAHLIA]
Hmph.
Making her youngest
daughter the Master, well,
it's practically all
my mother thinks about.
But to do that,
she needed to eliminate
the heir of the main
family. It's simple.
To make Pearl the Master?
What's all this "Master"
business, anyway?
It's about who would
head the small, but influential,
Kurain School of Channeling.
Both Morgan Fey and
Dahlia Hawthorne are members
of the so-called
"branch" family,
whereas Maya Fey is the
successor of the main family.
[DAHLIA] If the main
bloodline were to die out,
then the next master would
come from the branch family.
That's actually the
only reason she even raised
that little brat Pearl,
who luckily has strong
spiritual powers!
That's enough!
Whether that's true or not,
Pearl would never
go along with it!
Do you believe that
we cared if she agreed with us?
She just had to do
what her mommy said.
Be a good, obedient
little girl, and channel me.
And after you took
over her body,
you would be handling
all the rest.
Is that right?
Nail on the head.
I mean, the whole plan was
an absolute train wreck,
if you ask me.
[PHOENIX]
If that's how you felt,
why did you agree
to help her carry it out?
[DAHLIA]
Why do you think?
Because I thought it
would serve my interests.
I had my own agenda
to consider, you know.
[PHOENIX]
And what might that be?
Mine? Pure revenge.
Powerful force, huh?
[DAHLIA] Every day, the thought
burned inside my brain.
That I was sent to die
because of that damned woman.
[gasps]
Mia.
I wanted her to face
the same humiliation
that she put me through.
I wanted to make her feel
the kind of pain that I felt
every single day of my life.
That's pretty nutty.
I was absolutely livid
when I found out
she died before me.
But still... A person's soul
will live on into eternity.
So to harm her soul,
I would take the life of
the one she loved most
with my own hands!
And then... I would
finally have my revenge!
[PHOENIX]
Are you serious?
You'd kill an innocent
person for that?!
[DAHLIA]
I'm dead, remember?
So don't waste your breath
trying to make me
feel guilty about it.
There's nothing you
can do that's worse than
what I've already been through.
[PHOENIX growls]
On that night,
around 9:30, I crossed
the void back into this world.
I quickly pinned up
my hair and put on a hood.
Then I grabbed the
staff sitting next to me
and left Hazakura Temple.
That clown of a head nun
at the Inner Temple
never imagined
that I wasn't Iris.
She went back to the main
temple, which meant I would be
alone with Maya, who was
still getting ready to train.
[DAHLIA] I was able
to corner her in front of
the stone lantern,
took out the dagger
I found in the storeroom,
and went after her with
a huge smile on my face.
[slashing, blood splashing]
Say what? Do you mean
you stabbed Maya?
It's weird, things got foggy.
I don't remember
what happened next.
But I think maybe... I
somehow got stabbed instead.
By who? Who would stab you?
It was Maya, you dolt!
Who else could have done it?
She killed me!
No way! You're lying.
She would never!
[DAHLIA]
I started to black out.
So I scrawled her name
on the lantern in blood,
hoping that would draw suspicion
to her, at the very least.
Tch. Still so vindictive.
[DAHLIA] I don't know
how long I was unconscious.
But when I woke up.
I realized I was inside
the Sacred Cavern.
[JUDGE] Is that so?
How did you end up there?
[DAHLIA]
No clue, grandpa.
But I did know that I wanted
the satisfaction of seeing
Maya's dead body on the ground.
However...
...I couldn't get out.
[PHOENIX] Right, because
of the trick lock!
[DAHLIA] I took me hours
to get that damn thing open!
And almost the exact
moment I stepped out.
The earthquake hit.
[DAHLIA]
But I was in luck.
Because there she was.
[IRIS pants]
[DAHLIA] Iris showed up,
and to make it even sweeter,
she was all by herself.
I got her to tell me
everything that was going on.
[DAHLIA] And then, I locked
her up in the sacred cavern.
Shortly after...
...I put the pieces together.
What do you mean by that?
[DAHLIA] I'd misunderstood
one important thing.
I was under the impression
that Pearl Fey had been the one
who summoned me
the night before.
Well, that was part
of the plan your mother
had brewed up, wasn't it?
But that's not how it went.
The person who had actually
called my spirit over
from the other side was...
It was Elise Deauxnim, right?
Misty Fey herself.
Yeah! So then
I realized something.
After I lost consciousness,
it was her body left lying
in front of the lantern.
Even though
I wasn't able to kill Maya.
I did successfully force her
into committing one of
the most disgusting
and vile sins a person
could ever dream of!
[DAHLIA] Yes! I made her
kill her very own mother!
[DAHLIA] And unable to bear the
guilt for such a horrific act.
Maya Fey took
her own pitiful life.
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
Maya! She would never do that!
[DAHLIA] Well, if you
don't believe me,
why don't you tell me exactly
where she is right now.
[PHOENIX] Why don't you
tell us where she is?
The cave, right?
The bottom of Eagle River.
[gasps]
[DAHLIA] After killing
her poor mother to thwart
that unexpected attack,
she threw herself
into the river
in a fit of despair.
And most bodies that wind up
there, never come back out.
No! She's just been trapped in
the sacred cavern all this time!
Sorry. Somebody's
giving me a buzz.
Prosecutor Godot, not right now.
[GODOT]
All right, great, thanks.
Excuse me.
But I wanted to be alerted when
they got the locks removed
from the sacred cavern.
They're off?!
Has anybody found Maya?
Apparently, there was
a woman found inside the cave.
And that was Sister Iris.
She was alone.
They say anything about Maya?
[GODOT]
According to that call,
Iris was the only
one they found.
Oh, no...
I wasn't lying, you fool.
You should try dragging
the river instead.
Her body might turn up.
[PHOENIX growls, yells]
[cackles]
The plan actually worked!
Vengeance is mine!
So, like I said,
check the river.
Face it! There's
nowhere else around there
that little idiot Maya Fey
could be hiding!
She's dead!
[GODOT]
Hmph.
So Trite...
There's a saying you
might've heard before.
It goes, "Once you
eliminate the impossible,
whatever remains,
no matter how improbable,
must be the truth."
"Whatever remains is the truth."
Nobody has seen
or heard from Maya
since that night.
She's not in the main temple,
the cave, or the inner temple.
And I don't believe she'd
throw herself into the river.
So what's left?
Of course! It's improbable...
...but not impossible.
[PHOENIX] Dahlia. I have
an idea where we can find her.
One last place where
she could possibly be hiding.
You're terrible at bluffing.
But go on, tell us where she is.
Okay. But let me
ask you something first.
Who's channeling you right now?
[DAHLIA]
What a stupid question.
It's that pathetic, sniveling
little rug-rat, Pearl Fey.
But it can't be her.
'Cause she's here with us,
watching from
the courtroom gallery.
[DAHLIA]
Huh? Then who?
[PHOENIX]
There's one possibility.
And you're not gonna like it.
The person channeling
you is Maya Fey!
What?! That can't be!
[PHOENIX] After she
realized what was going on,
Maya then made the conscious
decision to channel you.
It was the only way
to defend herself.
N-No way...
Yes. The very last place
Maya could hide
is right here in plain sight.
She's hidden inside you!
[screams]
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[JUDGE]
Order! I will have order!
No. I don't believe
a single word you're saying.
That soft-headed little girl
could never come up with
such a smart plan!
She doesn't have
the brains for it!
So then why don't you
tell me who gave her
such a brilliant idea, huh?
It was...
[courtroom doors creak]
--[gasps]
--[MIA] It was me.
[GODOT gasps]
[gasps]
Of course. Who'd you think?
Mia!
[MIA]
Hmph.
How dare you show your face.
It's been awhile.
Seems like you missed me.
[GODOT]
So. It was you all along, huh?
It was.
Heh. You really
are something else.
But why? Why are you here?
That night,
you backed Maya into a corner
outside the inner temple.
But right before
you could kill her,
you blacked out, didn't you?
Yeah! That's because
I was stabbed!
Maya stabbed me!
[MIA] But she lost consciousness
at the exact same time.
[PHOENIX] Which means, it had
to have been somebody else
there who stabbed you.
[MIA] A short time later,
when Maya woke up,
she was in the training hall.
She immediately wrote a note
about what was going on
and proceeded to channel me.
She asked for my advice,
what I thought she should do.
I didn't think she was
smart enough for that.
I didn't have all
the details at the time,
but one thing was
perfectly clear to me.
Which was?
The simple fact that
you could not be allowed
to wander around freely.
I wrote down two things
that she absolutely had to do.
The first step was to
channel Dahlia Hawthorne.
And the second was to hide.
Lock herself in the
cavern until help arrived.
I see.
So it was Maya who put
that lock on the door.
I never would've
considered that.
She had to do it quickly,
or Dahlia definitely would've
been channeled by Pearl instead.
And if that had happened...
...this demonic spirit here
would have used the body
of that little girl to take her
murderous revenge out on Maya.
There's no way...
How could I have been...
Could have been such a failure?
Because that's all your plan
amounted to in the end.
Another loss.
Typical. Right?
[DAHLIA]
What do you mean?
[PHOENIX]
Your track record stinks.
I mean, have you ever been
successful in pulling off
one of your little schemes?
[DAHLIA growls]
[PHOENIX] The fake
kidnapping ten years ago...
...the time you
tried to kill me...
...when you wound up killing
somebody else and all you got
from it was a death sentence.
Just one stupid
move after another.
It's so bad,
it's not even funny.
[DAHLIA]
Shut up!
And now this.
You stepped in it once again,
because you couldn't fool Mia.
Maya was right
there in front of you,
and she still got away,
because of your incompetence.
[DAHLIA snarls]
Damn you, Mia Fey!
I despise you.
Why did you have to get
in my way again?!
[MIA] Oh, please,
it's not all my fault.
The fact is,
you will never beat me.
What'd you say...?
Never in your life, and,
apparently, not even in death.
Seems like you're going
to be a complete embarrassment
for the rest of time!
Remember this?
You said the dead
couldn't be punished.
But you also said that
a person's soul lives on
for all of eternity.
[MIA] And that's the punishment
from which you'll never escape.
You're always going to be
that weak, insecure,
pathetic creature known
as Dahlia Hawthorne.
A petty, perpetual loser!
To be honest,
that sounds like one hell
of a punishment to me.
And on the very day
you were executed,
your narrow little bridge to
freedom burned under your feet!
No...
You're wrong!
It can't be...
[demonic] How the
hell could I lose to you?!
I'm the superior one!
Think whatever you want,
but it won't make a difference.
Dahlia!
I order you to get out
of Maya Fey's body right now!
[roars]
[demonic]
Not yet! No! I'm not ready!
[shrieks]
Hey, Nick,
is that really you...?
And Mia...?
[sighs]
Yeah, it's me. Glad you're back.
[JUDGE]
Now, then. Is it safe to assume
I'm speaking with the
real Sister Iris this time?
Yes.
[JUDGE] I'm sure you've
heard this before,
but you two look awfully alike.
Well, anyway!
I shall hereby deliver
the verdict in this case!
[GODOT]
Objection!
Slow down with the gavel, chief.
Did ya have too much caffeine?
[JUDGE]
Uh, what are you talking about?
He means the trial isn't over.
[gasps]
You can't just
exorcise an evil spirit,
give yourself
a pat on the back,
then expect to go
on your merry way.
The bitter truth is Misty Fey,
Master of the Kurain School,
was actually murdered.
She's dead,
and we still don't know
who's to blame, do we now?
[JUDGE] But I'm afraid
the court isn't prepared for
any further
deliberations at this time.
The prosecution
will issue our final summons.
And this one is going to
clear up the whole mystery.
They'll answer the question
of who murdered Misty Fey!
[MIA] You sure about this,
Mister Prosecutor?
[GODOT] Hmph. But of course,
Madame Attorney.
I'm positive.
[PHOENIX gasps]
Mia...?
Okay. Who might
this final witness be?
[GODOT]
Heh. I thought it was obvious.
The only person we know
was there that night.
Who saw her mother die.
Wait, do you mean, Maya?
You can't put her on the stand
after what she's been though!
We need to find the truth!
[gasps]
[JUDGE]
Hmm. Very well, then.
The court will now adjourn
for a short recess.
Once the witness
is ready to testify,
we will proceed with the trial!
[GODOT]
Listen, Trite.
I'm just gonna get
this out there, okay?
What?
Put mildly, I don't
have a high opinion of you.
Your methods are sloppy,
you squeak by without even
the faintest understanding
of the case,
and then some beautiful woman
always comes dashing in
at the last minute to save you.
You haven't earned the right
to call yourself an attorney!
This time around,
you're gonna have to
do this all by yourself.
[PHOENIX sighs]
[IRIS] Please forgive me
for worrying you.
I'm glad you're okay.
Look, we're short on time.
Tell me what
happened that night.
Well, after I rang
the bell for lights out,
I got a phone call.
It would have been around 10:30.
I was asked to come to
the Inner Temple at once, so...
A call?
That's right. I got on
the snowmobile right away.
But then... I couldn't
reach the inner temple.
Because of what
happened to the bridge.
The lightning.
Yes. I had been told
to receive Elise's body
on top of the gorge
and take it to the temple.
So that's exactly what I did.
[PHOENIX] And when you
were staging the body
in the courtyard, that's when
Sister Bikini saw you?
[IRIS grunts]
Iris! I need the truth!
You gotta tell me who it was
that called you and told you
to move the body!
They have to be the one
who murdered Misty Fey!
[IRIS whimpers]
Please forgive me!
But I just can't do it. I can't
tell you who was behind this!
[sighs]
[BAILIFF 213A] Defendant,
the judge is calling for you.
Listen. Mister Wright,
--I, uh...
--[grunts]
[BAILIFF 213A]
Hurry up, defendant.
Phoenix.
[PHOENIX]
Mia! Uh... How's Maya?
Is she feeling okay?
[MIA]
Physically, she'll be fine.
However... Emotionally speaking,
she's been very badly hurt.
I understand.
Did anyone tell her
Elise was your mother?
I did. I talked to her just now.
And told her everything
I knew about what happened.
Poor Maya...
She's always been
extremely strong.
I've no doubt she can
handle it. All of it.
All of it?
What do you mean by that?
You're going to need
to figure that answer out
by yourself. This will
truly be the final battle.
Who's behind it?
I need to go back and re-examine
the sequence of events.
We know she was
really killed in the garden
of the Inner Temple.
I find it hard to believe the
killer was there by accident.
Which means they must've
known of the plan
from the very beginning.
What's more,
the victim was moved across
the burning bridge by
means of a pendulum.
In other words,
the killer wasn't able
to cross the bridge.
So that would mean,
it would have been someone
who wasn't on the main
temple side the next day.
[MIA]
Hmm.
The trial's about to resume.
We need the defense to
return to the courtroom.
Right.
I've done as much
as I can, Phoenix.
My time is up.
Thank you, Mia.
The rest of the battle
in your hands now,
but I have faith in you.
I've got it.
I appreciate all you've done.
[PHOENIX] It's time to finally
bring this case to an end.
What did Maya see that night?
And who was it that actually
killed Misty Fey?
[PHOENIX]
Whatever my conclusion,
I'll have to prove it.
And I'll have only
myself to rely on.
[JUDGE] Before we
resume the proceedings,
I have an important
announcement to make.
[PHOENIX]
What's that?
Two weapons were
presented as evidence.
The bloodstains on both
have now been analyzed.
And the results
indicate the murder weapon
was the sword hidden
inside the staff.
[PHOENIX] But, what about
the bloodstain on the dagger?
I'm not sure.
But at the very least
it was not the victim's.
[PHOENIX grunts]
Now. Bring in the final witness!
Maya...
[gasps]
Help me, Nick...
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
This case has reached
the final stage.
We have to learn what
really happened that night.
Who killed Maya's mother?
As the moment o,
truth draws closer.
Maya takes the witness stand,
and the harsh, painful
reality comes to light.
The end of this long trial
will be filled with tears
cried over sins of the past.
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Next time,
the final episode:
"Bridge to the
Turnabout -- Last Trial!"
Take that!