[PHOENIX] The Kurain Village's
sacred urn was stolen
by the infamous phantom
thief "Mask DeMasque."
Shortly thereafter,
a man named Ron DeLite
surrendered, claiming to be
the man behind the mask.
But something about his
claim didn't sit right with me,
and I took up his case.
At the trial,
I was able to prove that Ron
didn't steal the urn,
and even unmasked
the true DeMasque
in the process.
The culprit was his
rival, Ace Detective Luke Atmey.
We won the case,
but then Ron was accused
of something far worse.
[PHOENIX sighs]
I'm glad we got
the urn back, but...
[PHOENIX] To do it, we had
to place Ron at the scene
of a murder as it happened.
I just don't buy it.
How could that wimp
commit murder?
Well. What else
could he have been doing?
Mr. Nick proved he
was there at 1 AM.
Establishing an alibi's
a really strong move.
As long as it's verifiable, it
can turn an entire case around.
I was just trying
to prove Ron was
somewhere else at the time.
[MAYA] Too bad that
"somewhere else" was where
a murder took place.
Looks like you did
too good of a job this time.
What can I say?
I didn't know they'd
find a body there.
I'm worried.
I hope Desirée's okay.
This can't be easy on her.
All right.
We should investigate the
murder at K-B Security.
I don't think Ron has it in
him to kill someone, either.
There must be
another explanation.
I'll continue to defend him.
For his wife's sake, too.
--[MAYA] Good call.
--[PEARL] And with the urn back,
we can focus our efforts
on helping you.
Oh. Yeah, that reminds me.
Did the urn always
have these pink splotches?
And what's with it saying
"AMI" again all of a sudden?
It still said "I AM"
on the poster.
[PHOENIX]
The truth is, one year ago,
Pearl broke the urn by accident.
She tried her best to
put it back together,
but she isn't exactly great
at crafts... or spelling.
Whoa! I just had a thought.
Do you think this could
be a fake or something?
[PHOENIX]
A-A fake?
If you really think so,
then I'll bring it back to
the village and have
Great Aunt take a look at it!
[MAYA]
Good idea! I'll go with you.
Oh, no. I couldn't
possibly allow that.
[MAYA]
Why not?
I want you two to spend
some time together.
Maybe then you'll
get all lovey-dovey
like our new friends are.
"Like our new friends?"
[PEARL] You know! I mean
Ron and Desirée, obviously!
Taking matters
into their own hands
to defend each other.
Oh! So romantic!
Now that's what I call love!
I hope I feel that one day!
Someone's excited.
You can say that again.
[PEARL] I'm off!
Be a good couple while I'm gone.
No fighting, okay?
She, uh...
Seems to have the wrong
impression about the two of us.
I know. Right?
I'm not surprised though.
Why's that?
I'm sure I've
told you this before.
But our channeling powers
are strictly maternal.
Only the women inherit them.
So inevitably,
we become the center of life
in the village.
Maybe because of that,
many marriages in our
family end up falling apart.
I guess the men
must feel like outsiders.
Because many of them end up
leaving the village forever.
Even when they have a daughter.
I take it Pearls's father wasn't
the exception, then.
It's just...
She's grown up surrounded
by relationships
that never seem
to work out well.
It's only natural she'd want
to encourage healthy ones.
Besides, ever since
the incident last year,
she hasn't had a mom around.
Oh. Yeah.
[PHOENIX]
That's right.
Pearls's mother, Morgan Fey,
has been rotting in jail
for the last year.
So I get it.
I mean, I'm the only family
she's got left at this point.
That makes a lot of sense.
[ANDREWS]
Um, excuse me.
[PHOENIX gasps]
Ms. Andrews? What's the matter?
I... have some bad news.
I'm truly sorry!
[BOTH gasps]
Really? You shattered
the Kurain urn?
Yes.
[MAYA]
But... When did that happen?
Recently. It was
about two weeks ago.
The urn was sent
to us after they finished
the photo shoot for the poster.
I was carrying it to the
warehouse when it happened.
[ANDREWS wails]
[gasps]
[screams]
[shattering]
[ANDREWS] I'll never forget
that terrible noise.
I rushed over and
tried to check inside.
[screams]
[whimpers, sighs]
[ANDREWS] And then
blacked out from the shock.
[MAYA]
Yeah, that checks out.
The paint matches perfectly.
Of course... I tried
my best to repair the urn.
Fortunately, the shards
were pretty big,
so I was able to piece them back
together with relative ease.
With the urn
back in one piece,
I realized how ugly the
paint stains looked.
So I hid them behind
Mystic Ami's statue.
Okay, I think I'm
starting to understand
everything here.
Just one problem.
That's not where the
statue was last time.
[ANDREWS]
Um... Yes.
You're right.
You did seem
surprised back then.
But what is
she doing over there?
Oh, no.
Woah.
Does that mean someone
moved it without you knowing?
[PHOENIX] If I'm right, the
statue was only delivered here
a day before the theft.
The detective guarding
the warehouse, Luke Atmey,
is the only one who
could've moved it.
[LUKE chuckles]
[PHOENIX]
The question is why he moved it.
Furthermore, does
this have anything to do
with our new case?
Again. Sorry.
I sincerely apologize.
[MAYA]
Don't worry about it!
The urn looks the way
it's supposed to now.
If anything, we should
be thanking you!
Oh. Really? That's great!
[MAYA laughs]
I'm the new boss around here!
Watcha gonna do about it?
Hey. New guy.
Bring me a cup a joe,
will yah? Pronto.
[PHOENIX groans]
Just so you know,
that's where the victim was
sitting seconds before he died.
[screams]
[GUMSHOE] Man, today's
been a real train wreck
for you guys, huh?
I guess.
You got that right!
That caffeine-obsessed cyclops
made us look like total idiots!
That's a rough one.
I feel for you two.
Wait, what?
That's not like you at all.
Usually you're like,
"Serves you right!
You got what you deserved!"
[laughs]
Or something along those lines.
Well, I can tell when
someone puts their heart
into their work, like
you did, so... You know?
That, and I can sympathize
when things don't work out
for hardworking people.
Things rarely go the way
I want in my line of work.
Wow, Dick, you're so thoughtful.
That's a shock.
Oh. Oh!
While you're feeling talky,
what happened to Mask DeMasque
after the trial?
Him? That detective
that played dress-up?
Serves him right!
The guy got what he deserved!
[laughs
Now there's the
Gumshoe we know and love.
At least we know
there's nothing wrong with him.
--By the way...
--[GUMSHOE] Huh?
Would you mind telling us
a little bit about the victim
who died here the other night?
[GUMSHOE]
Sure thing, pal.
Kane Bullard, the CEO of
KB Security and a big fella
in his own right.
His corpse was
found at 9 this morning.
However, his estimated time
of death is 1 AM on the 12th.
It really did happen at the
same time that Mask DeMasque
stole the urn, huh?
Why did it take
an entire day for someone
to discover the body?
[GUMSHOE] Well, his corpse
was stashed away inside
that big safe,
if you can believe it.
Nobody had heard from him,
and when they opened
the safe in the morning...
[PHOENIX]
Out fell the body.
[gasps]
[GUMSHOE] Also, it seems
like this guy was involved
in some shady
business practices.
Shady like how?
If a company hired his
firm, they'd spy on 'em,
learn their secrets, then
sell the information to rivals.
Wow. Sounds like
a grade-A crook.
[GUMSHOE] The firm was
even in charge of security
for someone robbed
by Mask DeMasque.
But they screwed it up
and lost the victim's trust.
That's interesting.
--[thud]
--[BOTH gasp]
[PHOENIX]
What are you doing?
I'm tryin' to
open this dumb safe!
What's it look like?
[PHOENIX] I... don't think you
understand how safes work.
[GUMSHOE] It's worth noting
somebody must've opened that
on the night of the crime.
After all, the victim's body
was hidden in there.
Also... According
to company records,
Ron DeLite had the
clearance needed to open it.
But there are plenty
of others with the same level
of access as him, aren't there?
[GUMSHOE]
Of course there are, but still--
[alarm blares]
[PHOENIX]
Maya?!
Sorry! I wanted to see
what the button was for.
[GUMSHOE]
It's an emergency buzzer!
Can't you read?
It says right there!
Oops. Shoulda looked.
[GUMSHOE] It sets off an alarm
in the basement guard room
that tells security
to high-tail it here.
I have to wonder.
The other night,
was that button pressed?
[GUMSHOE] I had the same
thought, so I asked around.
Security says there's no
record of the alarm sounding.
Plus, we dusted
the button for prints
and didn't find a thing.
[PHOENIX] I'm surprised
the buzzer wasn't used.
[BUTZ] You again?
You need somethin' big man?
Larry!
[MAYA giggles]
[chuckles]
I am so jealous!
And here I was workin' my butt
off while you're out there
livin' the dream!
--[PHOENIX gasps]
--[BUTZ] It's a weekday, man!
And you two are on
an afternoon date?
Oh, no. It's nothing
like that at all.
We're just here to investigate
CEO Bullard's death.
Oh. Yeah.
That's right, that
guy died. Didn't he?
C'mon.
[MAYA] All right, let's actually
get down to business.
Larry, were you here on
the night of the murder?
Huh? Yeah, of course I was.
[PHOENIX] That's a lie
if I ever heard one.
What? No! I was here!
Why wouldn't I be?
[PHOENIX]
Yeah, you were playing hooky.
Whaddya mean? I resent that!
Besides. Do you have
proof I left my post?
Because I don't think you do!
[PHOENIX] I thought
you found Ron's wallet.
At least, that's what
you testified at the trial.
[BUTZ] Oh, yeah.
It was just two days ago.
I saw it on the ground outside
my building at work.
It's clear.
If you found it outside
two nights ago, you
must've snuck out of work!
[yells]
[BUTZ] You're not sayin'
it's my fault, are ya?
It's not my fault
he's dead, right?
[PHOENIX] Did you bail
for the usual reason?
Usual reason?
If you're insinuating that
I left to meet a girl
then you're way off!
[PHOENIX]
I knew it.
[BUTZ wails] I'm a fool.
If I was here, he'd be alive!
[MAYA]
Oh, Larry.
[BUTZ whimpers]
Huh? Ah! How can I ever
make up for what I've done?
I must atone, Nick!
[PHOENIX] Well, for starters,
you better tell me this...
Did the buzzer really
not go off that night?
I had the same thought,
so I asked around.
Security says there's no record
of the alarm sounding.
Nope! Had to check before.
No logs of it
goin' off all night.
[MAYA] Would you mind
looking one more time?
Just in case?
[BUTZ] Fine. I can't
say no to you, Maya. Let's see.
Well, I figured.
We might as well try.
Yeah, but I doubt it'll help.
Not even Larry could make
that kind of mistake.
[BUTZ]
Aww, crap!
[BOTH gasp]
[BUTZ whimpers]
I made a mistake.
[MAYA, PHOENIX gasp]
I don't know how!
It says it went off during
the night around 1 AM or so.
Around 1 AM?
That lines up perfectly with
the time of the murder!
[BUTZ sobs]
Say it ain't so!
I can't believe I missed that!
[PHOENIX] Yeah, I can't
believe it either, buddy.
Let's go ask Ron for some
clarification on that night.
[MAYA]
Hmm.
I'm begging you Mister Wright.
Begging! Please!
Don't abandon me!
Ron, if you want my help,
you're going to have to
start telling me the truth.
Do I have your word?
Yeah.
All right. Now tell me where you
were the night of the murder.
And I mean where
you really were.
Okay...
At 1 AM on September the 12th.
You weren't at Lordly Tailor,
but at K-B Security, right?
[RON]
Since I used to work there,
I knew where the
CEO's office was.
I knocked, but there
was no answer.
[RON] So I used the key card
to unlock the door.
I didn't notice,
but when I went inside,
someone was there in the dark.
[RON] Then suddenly they bashed
me over the head with something!
[MAYA] Could you tell
if it was the C.E.O
when you looked at him?
[RON]
No. Whoever it was ran away
while I was stunned, so I didn't
see what they looked like.
[RON] But when I came to, I saw
Mr. Bullard dead on the ground!
[RON] I thought I had to do
something about the body.
[MAYA]
And what did you do after that?
[RON] What do you think?
I got out of there!
Sure, I hid the body
in the safe,
but that's 'cause I was
afraid of how it'd look.
See? That's all I did, I swear!
[PHOENIX sighs]
I was scared the
police would find out, so...
I turned myself in.
If I had been found
guilty as Mask DeMasque
in the previous trial, then that
could have been my alibi.
One more thing.
Can you recall when you
received this blackmail letter?
Let's see...
When was it, again?
It's kinda hard to
tell them all apart.
There've been so many.
What does that mean?
This isn't the first one?
No. But this is the first
one that ever called me out
to a specific location,
if that counts for anything.
Do you at least
remember when
you received the first one?
I could never forget that.
I got the first letter only a
few days after my debut
as Mask DeMasque.
Ron, you said
you'd tell the truth.
You aren't the phantom thief!
It was Ace Detective Luke Atmey.
No, it wasn't!
I know it looks like I'm lying
because it wasn't me who broke
into Lordly Tailor that night.
But still! It really was me
on all the other heists!
[gasps]
I'm not lying.
Someone apparently spotted me
on my inaugural adventure.
I know because it said
so in the first blackmail.
Something like
"I know you did it."
You got busted
on your first theft?
And from then on,
I started receiving plans
and instructions in the mail.
[PHOENIX]
Plans?
[RON] They'd tell me what
to steal and how to do it.
They detailed security
blind spots, escape routes,
and even training methods.
Are you telling me
your heists were all planned
by someone else?
Yes. After the first one,
I was simply carrying out
my mysterious orders.
If I didn't, they'd tell
the cops! Pretty cool, huh?
Why is he so happy
about being exploited?
[PHOENIX] So Ron was
Mask DeMasque after all.
But someone else
is behind the thefts.
Someone who planned
it all out in detail.
[RON] All I had to do was
put the treasures I stole
into the designated
safe-deposit box.
Then just sit back
and wait for the cash
to arrive in the mail.
[PHOENIX]
You even got a reward out of it?
[MAYA] Is that why you went
after the Kurain urn, then?
I didn't. I've never
even seen that urn.
All I do is steal
what I'm told to,
and that urn wasn't
in my instructions.
Ron, do you swear everything
you've just said is the truth?
Yes. And now that
it's out, I'm done for.
If there's one thing
Dessie won't stomach,
it's breaking the law.
When she finds out,
she's never gonna forgive me.
If you knew that,
why'd you become a thief?
I had to!
She spends money
like it grows on trees!
You see, I love her,
compulsive spending and all,
but there's no job that could
bring in enough money for her!
Except being a thief, I figured.
[BOTH chuckle]
I tried telling her
I was Mask DeMasque,
but she immediately
laughed at the idea!
She thought I was joking around!
To be fair, I don't think
I would have believed it either.
Can't blame her.
[RON] Anyway, I wanted
to tell you something.
I heard that detective
who's taking credit
for my thievery is having his
trial at the exact same time
as mine, in the
courtroom next door!
Well, that's surprising.
Hold on. But we know that wacky
wordsmith isn't actually
Mask DeMasque, don't we?
[RON]
Right, he's not. I am!
[PHOENIX] It doesn't
matter what we know
if he's claiming to be guilty.
I have one more question
that I have to ask you
before we're finished.
Of course, ask away.
Be completely honest
in your response.
Did you kill Kane Bullard?
No, I didn't! Please.
Please believe me!
[MAYA grunts]
I'm sorry.
As you can imagine, I was
just trying to help my Ronnie.
Kinda backfired
on you there, didn't it?
[PHOENIX]
Don't say that.
Nicky boy, please.
We really need your help.
Ronnie's not a killer, I know
him better than anyone!
I'm on your side.
[sighs]
Thank you so much!
I just don't know what
to do anymore.
I feel so useless.
And that detective!
He's infuriating!
I want to knock that pointy
nose off his stupid face!
Knowing that, I'm less
surprised that you barged
into his office, but you still
shouldn't have done that.
[DESIRÉE]
I had to do something!
Ronnie was in major trouble!
We talked to him earlier,
and despite everything,
he's still claiming to
be Mask DeMasque.
[DESIRÉE]
He's so silly.
I know everything there is to
know about that cinnamon roll.
He always looks before he leaps.
Most of the time,
he looks and doesn't leap.
He's so fainthearted!
He just doesn't have it
in him to be a thief.
Right. You know him the best.
[PHOENIX]
I guess opposites attract.
[MAYA]
Huh?
Oh. Just thinking
out loud about how these two
are so different, yet somehow
ended up married to each other.
Come on, now.
You don't have to
sound so perplexed.
It was love at first sight.
For me, at least.
Wow! That's a surprise!
[DESIRÉE] It wouldn't be
if you'd been there.
Ronnie saved my life.
Back then,
I was working in a bank.
And one day, two men
suddenly rushed in to rob us.
[DESIRÉE] I can't stand
people like that, so naturally,
I gave 'em a piece of my mind!
[PHOENIX] You talked down
to armed robbers?
[DESIRÉE]
Yeah, and they took me hostage.
I was so scared.
But then help arrived--
in the form of Ronnie.
Stop! You thugs leave her alone!
[DESIRÉE] Crying and
swinging his arms like crazy,
he attacked the two robbers.
I think...
that's when I realized.
He's the kind of guy
who has real courage.
The courage to risk his life
when it matters most.
My Ronnie.
Tomorrow, let's send
that Prosecutor Godot
from espresso to depresso!
--Get it?
--[PEARL] Mystic Maya, Mr. Nick!
Hey, you two!
[MAYA]
Pearls!
[PEARL]
It's the real deal, apparently!
[MAYA gasps]
That's such great news!
Thanks again. You rock!
[PHOENIX] The urn. This
whole mess started with it.
At 1 AM on the night
it was stolen,
Ron was at K-B Security.
[gasps]
At the same time,
there was another Mask DeMasque
in the Lordly Tailor
basement warehouse.
Why'd Luke Atmey show up
there dressed like that?
And why would he pick that time
in particular to steal the urn?
Not to mention, why
was the statue moved?
There had to have been a reason.
And that's not
all we don't know.
Who attacked Ron in the
CEO's office at K-B Security?
And that emergency buzzer.
Why would the killer
let it be pressed?
He should've realized
security would rush there.
Wait, did he do it
because he knew
security would come?
Why didn't I see it before?
[LUKE laughs]
[PEARL]
I know that look!
You just figured something
out, didn't you?
Tomorrow's trial will
be a race against the clock.
Aww. I was hoping we could
take this one nice and easy.
Unfortunately, we can't.
That won't cut it tomorrow.
This court is hereby
in session for the trial
of Ron DeLite.
[PHOENIX] In a nearby courtroom,
another trial is set to begin.
Court is now in
session for the trial
of Luke Atmey.
Please take your seats.
Two simultaneous
trials, linked at the core.
I have to find the truth
and drag him to the stand...
...before the verdict
is handed down!
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
The two tangled trials begin.
In order to prove Ron's
innocence, I'll need to unveil
the crimes of Detective Atmey,
who stands as the accused
in the other ongoing trial.
Which means it's
a battle against time!
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Next episode: "The Stolen
Turnabout--Last Trial"!
Take that!
[RON]
Please believe me!
[BUTZ]
Oh, come on, Nick! [wails]