[PEARL hums]
[giggles]
[PHOENIX] My name is
Phoenix Wright, attorney at law.
I made a pledge to
help those in need.
--That's my duty.
--[doorbell rings]
[PHOENIX]
Sometimes they're strangers,
and sometimes the ones
who need my help most
are my good friends.
Hey, what's up?
Sorry to bug you, but
I need to ask you for the favor
of a lifetime, Mister Nick!
[gasps]
[PEARL grunts]
[PHOENIX]
Let me see what you've got.
Yeah, okay.
[PEARL] I need to find
another one just like this.
But one that's not broken.
[PEARL]
Mm-hmm.
It's one of my most
prized possessions.
But it slipped out of
my hands and shattered.
[PHOENIX]
That's too bad.
But the worst part is,
I can't hear the waves anymore!
What do you mean?
Before, whenever I
held this shell up to my ear,
I could always hear the
sound of the waves inside.
I hate to say it,
but that is pretty big hole.
I know. I looked, but I couldn't
ever find the missing piece.
So I came here today
to ask you to help me find
a new shell like this one!
Yeah. I'm sorry, but I've never
seen this kind of shell.
Is something wrong?
No. Nothing.
It's weird.
But I feel like I do recognize
this thing from somewhere.
I heard it was
a special seashell.
And it can only be found
at one particular beach.
Oh?
Do you happen to know
which one that would be?
[PEARL]
Not really.
But I do have some
clues that might help us.
[PHOENIX] Huh. Did Maya
write this for you?
[PEARL]
Yeah, she did.
I think they're supposed
to be directions.
[PHOENIX] Well, then
we should probably ask her.
[PEARL gasps]
[PHOENIX]
Ah, but she's not here today.
She had something
important come up.
--But...
--[PEARL] No!
Please promise me that you won't
tell Mystic Maya about this!
[PHOENIX]
O... kay.
[PEARL]
Also, we have to find it today!
[PHOENIX groans]
[PHOENIX gasps]
Hang on. I've got an idea.
[PEARL]
What is it?
[cell phone beeping]
Bingo. Just as I suspected.
All right, kiddo.
You ready to go beachcombing?
So this big ol' shell
is pretty important to you.
Yes, very.
It's a special treasure that
Mystic Maya herself gave me.
Oh, did she now?
Yeah.
[PEARL] Mother,
what kind of bird is that?
[MORGAN]
It's a kite.
They like to swoop down
and steal fried foods.
So be careful when
they're around.
Oh... You sure do know
about a lot of things.
[MORGAN]
And one of those things
is that it's time for lunch.
[PEARL] Okay. I'll go
and get Mystic Maya.
[PEARL]
Mystic... Maya?
Oh... huh?
--[door rattles]
--[gasps]
[MAYA]
Hey, Pearls!
[PEARL]
Ah? Mystic Maya! I'm sorry.
I came into your room
without permission.
I don't care. Did you
find something interesting?
Kinda. What is this?
[MAYA]
A shell.
A what?
Oh, I guess
you've never seen one.
You find them on the
beach or in the ocean.
And what's... the ocean?
[MAYA]
Look. This is the ocean.
Mia took this picture for me.
S'Pretty. It doesn't look real.
All that blue water just keeps
going on and on and on forever.
[MAYA]
Yeah. I felt the exact same way
when I saw it
for the first time.
It made me realize that
the world is a huge place!
What do you mean?
[MAYA] I mean the world
outside Kurain Village.
Huh? But I thought...
...that there actually wasn't
anything outside of the village.
Nothing besides the mountains.
'Cause. That's
what mother told me.
[MAYA] Heh. Uh-uh.
The ocean is incredible.
People call it
the cradle of life,
because that's where
all life came from.
All from there?
[MAYA] Yeah, the mountains
rose from it, fish of course,
and life that eventually
became people.
A long time ago, even our
village was part of the ocean.
Oh, wow. That's cool.
I can hardly believe it!
[MAYA] Hey, Pearls, do you
wanna see it for yourself?
Yeah, yeah, I would love to!
But how?
[MAYA chuckles]
Just leave it all to Maya!
[PEARL] "The world
is only Kurain Village
and the mountains
that surround it.
Which is why you can
never travel any farther."
That's what I'd
been told my entire life.
Your mother may
have been a bit overprotective.
So asking to see the ocean
was totally pointless.
There's no way they'd let me go.
[MORGAN]
Absolutely not!
No?
I cannot allow
Pearl to take a single step
outside of the village.
[MAYA] Oh. Well. The Dedication
Ceremony's coming up.
How about I take her
with me this year?
[MORGAN] Only the head of the
main family is allowed to leave
the village, once per year.
That's an ironclad rule
of the Kurain,
and one I should not
have to remind you of.
I'm aware of what the rules are.
But Mom and Mia both said
we need to see the world.
That we must keep
learning new things and--
[MORGAN] Consider this
discussion to be over
and done with.
[MAYA]
Aunt Morgan?
If you truly wish
to become head someday,
you'll never again
speak such nonsense.
Hey.
So, uh... Forget about all that.
Okay? About seeing the ocean.
I changed my mind. I'm sorry!
Wait a sec!
Okay, now let's see
if my hunch was right after all.
Oh, yeah! You ready to go?
[PEARL]
Hmm? Yes!
[PHOENIX chuckes]
[PEARL] Are you sure that
we should be doing this?
[MAYA]
Yep. I'm positive!
After all, I promised to show
you the ocean, didn't I?
[PEARL]
Yeah.
[MAYA] But this needs
to be our little secret.
So you gotta swear you
won't tell your mom, okay?
[PEARL]
I swear I won't say anything.
[PEARL] That happened
five years ago today.
You don't say.
I didn't know this
was the anniversary.
Yep! That's the reason why I was
so insistent on us coming out
here today to look for it!
[MAYA, PEARL]
Look, it's the ocean!
[MAYA]
Finally! We have arrived!
[gasps]
Oh, wow. It's huge.
I'm so glad you
could be here to see this.
[PEARL]
Thank you, Mystic Maya.
[PEARL] I'll start looking
for another one around here,
so if you could look
over in that area,
we might have better luck.
[PHOENIX]
Got it!
[MORGAN] Unbelievable!
What were you thinking?!
As a candidate
for the head of the family,
you should know
better than this!
--[PEARL whimpers]
--[MAYA] Yes, ma'am...
And the fact that you
took her out of the village
without so much as telling
anybody makes this worse.
What if something
had happened to her?
I'm sorry, Aunt Morgan.
I shouldn't have.
[MORGAN]
Good grief.
Obviously, the rotten apple
doesn't fall far from the tree.
[MAYA]
Huh?
[MORGAN] Think about
what befell your mother!
I mean, when she broke the rules
and got involved with outsiders,
how did that turn out for her?
After she almost ruined
the Kurain school's reputation,
she vanished and left me
to take care of you.
But the only
reason she left was to
make things better for u--
[MORGAN]
Not to mention Mystic Mia.
She left the village saying that
she wanted to become a lawyer.
Can you imagine the selfishness?
No, you're wrong!
She left because she's
trying to find leads
on what happened to Mom!
You women of the main family
are an embarrassment
to the entire clan!
[MAYA whimpers]
[PEARL] Mother! Mystic Maya was
just trying to be nice to me.
Don't worry, little Pearl.
You didn't know what you
were doing was wrong,
so I'm not angry with you.
I hope you realize
she's much more
powerful than you.
The only reason you have
any standing over her
is because of your blood!
Never forget that!
[PEARL]
Mystic Maya...
Hey, it's you.
[PEARL] I'm sorry.
You got in trouble
because I was being selfish.
[MAYA] Mm-mm. I was the
one who invited you
to come with me, remember?
You have nothing
to apologize for.
Wait just a second, okay?
[PEARL]
It's the shell!
[MAYA]
This is very special,
because there's only one beach
around where you can find it.
[PEARL gasps]
[MAYA] Hey, you should put
it up to your ear and listen.
[PEARL]
Whoa! I can hear something.
[waves crashing]
[MAYA]
It's the waves.
This shell is filled with
the sound of the ocean.
[PEARL]
Wow, that's amazing.
[MAYA]
You know... You should have it!
[PEARL]
Really? Are you sure?
[MAYA]
Mm-hmm. To remember this day!
The sound of the ocean will
take you back to the beach
whenever you want.
[PEARL gasps]
That is so sweet.
Thank you, Mystic Maya.
[waves crashing]
[PHOENIX] Your special
seashell is pretty hard to find.
[PEARL] I can't believe that
I just dropped it like that.
How am I gonna face
Mystic Maya again?
Luckily, Maya is
the understanding
and forgiving type.
Is that a shrine?
Looks like a pretty old one.
Since we're here, why don't
we ask the gods for help?
[PEARL]
Okay.
[BOTH] Please help us
find that special seashell.
[trumpet plays]
[BOTH gasps]
[playing continues]
[MAYA]
Yes! There it is!
[BOTH gasp]
Whoa, Maya?
[MAYA]
Eh?
[PHOENIX]
Uh. What are you doing here?
Are you asking me?
I mean the real question is what
are the two of you doing here?
And how in the world
did you find this place?
We just, uh...
[sighs] Anyway, I was just about
to take a wee little breakey!
[stomach growls
[giggles] What do you think
about coming along with me
to grab a bite to eat?
Umm... Around here?
Oh, yeah! There's a super
yummy noodle stand nearby.
It's kind of a
once-a-year treat for me!
Come on, Pearls!
--[PEARL] Okay!
--[PHOENIX] Wait. Hang on.
[MAYA] ♪ Yum, yum, yum.
Noodles in my tum! ♪
[MAYA]
Huh? How can they do this?
Ugh! It's so unfair!
We're gonna have to stand here
and wait around for the food!
Well, that's too bad.
We'll wait however
long as it takes!
[PHOENIX] Of course, going
somewhere else isn't an option.
[PHOENIX]
So you never answered.
What are you doing
out here, anyway?
Who me? I'm surprised
Pearls didn't tell you.
It's the annual
Dedication Ceremony.
[PHOENIX]
I don't know what that is.
This is the day
when the head of the
Kurain visits that shrine
near the cliffs to
perform a ritual that
returns spirits
back to the ocean.
Once a year?
What about five years ago?
That time?
I actually let little Pearls
tag along with me then.
I don't know if she remembers.
Oh, Well, uh...
I'm kinda curious
as to how you were able
to find this beach.
[PHOENIX chuckles]
This helped a little.
Whoa! I wrote all that,
like, a couple of years ago.
[PHOENIX] McSopp's Fables
is that Noodle chain
you love, right?
They're one of
my all-time favorites!
Something about their broth
is completely out of this world!
I saw these names
and made the connection.
That this had to be a list of
all the noodle shops on the way
from the station to the beach.
So then I looked up
coastal towns that had
these places, and here we are.
Wow! I would have
never thought of doing that!
[MAYA] All life on Earth
comes from the ocean.
It rises as it
ascends to Heaven.
So when our ancestors wanted
to call on the spirits,
they built their village
up in the mountains.
That's what Mia
told me, at least.
[MAYA] She explained that
to me the first time
we came here together.
What an amazing day.
[MAYA squeals]
Ohh! That shocked me!
I'll bet! Sure feels
good though, right?
[MAYA]
Mm! Yeah! I love the ocean!
I'm so happy that
I got to come here with you.
[giggles]
[MIA chuckles]
She gave me
the shell so I'd remember
our time here together.
Pretty sweet of her, wasn't it?
[gasps]
So it was Mia
who gave it to you?
[MAYA] Mm-hmm. Yeah. When
you hold it up to your ear,
you can hear the
sound of the waves!
[PEARL whimpers]
[MAYA]
Ah, what a beautiful memory!
[PEARL] Um... I gotta go
take care of something!
You two have fun!
[MAYA]
Pearls!
I need to ask you something.
You gave that seashell
to Pearl, didn't you?
[MAYA]
Mm-hmm. A few years ago.
[MERCHANT 14A]
Here ya go! Two wave specials!
[PHOENIX yelps]
Seriously?
Ooh! Didn't I tell you
this was worth the wait?
I mean it's not every day that
you can eat a yummy bowl
of noodles out of a huge shell!
[PHOENIX]
So that's what it was!
Huh? What do you mean,
what is what was?
[MAYA] Okay, so you guys
came all the way out here
looking for a shell.
Pearls could've just told me.
[PHOENIX] Man. I can't believe
this is really the case.
No wonder we couldn't find one.
Well, now that
it's all figured out,
I can give this one to Pearls!
Wait up.
Could you let me
handle this, instead?
[MAYA] She gave me
the shell so I'd remember
our time here together.
[PEARL whimpers]
[PEARL sobs]
[PHOENIX]
Hey, Pearl.
Oh. Hey there, Mister Nick.
Well. You have any luck?
Not really.
It's fine. Look here.
[gasps]
Where did you--?
It's exactly like this one!
[MAYA]
Pretty amazing find, huh Pearls?
Yeah. Incredible!
Maya actually just
found it a few minutes ago.
[PEARL]
Mm-hmm.
Nick told me that
you were out looking
for another one.
I'm sorry that the
old shell broke.
But this new one will
let you hear the sound
of the ocean again.
Great news, don't you think?
[PEARL whimpers]
[PEARL sniffs]
Pearls? Why are you crying?
[PEARL]
I'm so sorry about all of this.
Thank you for finding
this new shell for me.
It's so nice of you and
I really appreciate it.
But the truth is...
...I wanna keep this one!
I had no idea that
it was holding so many
important things inside of it.
Things that really
mean a lot to me.
It's filled with Mystic Maya
and Mystic Mia's
memories together.
I wish I hadn't broken it.
And that you could still
hear the ocean sounds.
It's not perfect,
but I love it very much!
I want to keep it forever!
So sweet. Thanks, Pearls.
[PEARL]
Aww!
[MAYA]
Thank you so much.
[PEARL]
Mystic Maya, why are you crying?
[MAYA]
'Cause I'm happy.
Thanks for the bowl, mister!
[MERCHANT 14A]
No problem!
So, do you really
think Pearls is gonna like it?
[PHOENIX]
Oh, yeah.
She'll have her own story to
tell about this one.
I can kinda hear
the ocean in this shell.
It's still there.
Yeah?
I'll go and return
this one to the noodle guy.
'Cause it seems the waves
decided to come back.
[BOTH giggle]
[MAYA]
Man, that was so good!
Wasn't it?
I'll never forget
coming here with Mom,
way back when
I was about your age.
This is the most
incredibly yummy bowl
of noodles I've ever
eaten in my life!
Yeah. They're amazing.
And so is the bowl!
[MIA] Obviously, it looks
like a huge shell.
But what's really cool is
if you hold it up to your ear,
you can hear the sound
of the ocean inside of it.
Whoa, are you kidding me?
Maya, please be careful!
Well then?
[MAYA] Heh. Yeah, I can
totally hear the ocean!
[MIA] Hey, Maya. Did you think
more about what I said?
[MAYA]
About me becoming the head?
It's a lot to ask.
I'm sorry for giving you
such a big responsibility.
However, I need
to leave Kurain village.
To become a lawyer
and discover the truth.
I'll take over
the clan if you need me to.
Don't worry about me.
You'll be an awesome lawyer!
[MIA sobs]
Oh, Maya...
[MIA]
Thank you.
[PHOENIX]
Some good memories.
[gasps]
[PHOENIX] Oh, I remember
something, myself.
[MIA] Hey, Wright.
Would you do me a favor
and bring in those
case files for me?
[PHOENIX]
Sure thing! [grunts]
Aw, man.
Hmmm.
That's Maya, and one
of my favorite memories
my sister and I shared.
Wow. That is
one monster seashell.
[MIA giggles]
Isn't it?
[PHOENIX] Memories are
what help keep us all together.
[PHOENIX] Thinking back
to the bonds we share,
reminds us of the warmth
we can provide each other.
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
Let's look back at the first
case Mia fought in court.
A year before she met me,
a helplessly love-struck
college student.
Her client was an
escaped death row inmate.
Accused of murdering
a policewoman
during his break out.
But did he really do it?
At Mia's side stood
Diego Armando,
a defense lawyer
that guided her.
as it turns out, there
was a link to this case
that nobody saw coming.
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Next episode: "Turnabout
Beginnings - 1st Trial"!
Take that!