[PHOENIX]
My name is Phoenix Wright.
And I'm a defense attorney.
No matter the odds,
it's my job to stand up
for those who have no one
else in their corner.
I'll do whatever it
takes to fight for the truth!
[VOICE]
The time is 1 AM.
There goes the
deadline that we were given.
And the jewel's still
resting safe and sound
under lock and key.
Bet he got scared
'cause he knew
ol' "big" Dick Gumshoe
and his crew was here.
Aw, for cryin' out loud!
We've been bamboozled!
[MASK laughs]
[BOTH gasp]
[MASK]
Sorry to get your hopes up.
Those are the breaks.
Mask DeMasque,
the phantom thief!
We shall meet again, detective.
When the moon
is bright and full.
[MASK laughs]
[PHOENIX hums]
Are you seriously
cleaning the toilet again?
No work, so I gotta
make myself useful somehow.
Oh, wow, that's just pathetic.
Hope I don't end up like you.
[PHOENIX growls]
You might.
Especially if you slack off
on your training.
[MAYA]
Get off my case.
I'm way too busy working
to train right now.
[PHOENIX] Busy working
on "becoming one"
with the couch, right?
Hey! I know you've been
playing games all night
when, in reality,
you should be trying to
gather up some new clients.
[PEARL] Oh, you two having
one of your couple's spats?
[BOTH gasp]
My gosh. You're so cute!
--[MAYA] Pearls?
--[PHOENIX] Pearl!
Glad you're here, but what
brings you into the city?
Heh. I thought that
Mystic Maya would've
told you about it by now.
Ah?
"Kurain Village treasures"? Huh.
Yup! Straight from me
and Pearl's hometown!
The exhibition doesn't
actually get started until
next week, but the
promoter was nice enough
to give us some VIP passes
so we could go early.
VIPs!
So I decided to go all out
and dress extra fancy.
Whattaya think?
[PHOENIX] That's, like,
the only thing you ever wear.
Yep, good 'ol Maya Fey.
She's the younger sister
of my friend and mentor,
the late Mia Fey.
I met her a couple of
years ago, and even defended her
when she was falsely accused
of Mia's tragic murder.
They're from Kurain Village,
home of the mysterious
Spirit Channeling technique.
Maya's the daughter
of the Kurain School's master
and is training to become
a spirit medium herself.
Of course, the
precocious little girl
is Pearl Fey.
She's Maya's cousin,
and also a young spirit
medium in training.
The promo poster
looks better than I'd hoped!
They even got a great picture
of the sacred urn!
[gasps]
I still feel bad.
First, I broke the urn,
and then I put it back
together all wrong.
It's fine!
I'm sure Mystic Ami's just happy
to know that you did the best
that you possibly could!
[PHOENIX] A year ago,
while we were investigating
a murder case in Kurain Village,
little Pearl accidentally
shattered the sacred urn that
contains the spirit of Ami Fey,
the school's founder
and protector.
But by breaking the urn,
she unwittingly broke
the case as well.
[REPORTER 2A]
In other news,
police are searching for
clues after a theft from
the upcoming treasure exhibit
at Lordly Tailor hall.
[MAYA]
Eh?
The rare item stolen, an urn,
was taken last night.
[gasps]
[REPORTER 2A] Authorities
believe the heist was the work
of the notorious, so-called
"Phantom thief," Mask DeMasque.
Masque the Mask?
A criminal mastermind.
A thief that targets
rare treasures.
He's like a ghost, and
no one knows who he really is!
Hence the name.
I just can't
believe they stole it.
That urn is sacred to us.
Oh, no!
Ahh...
The bitterness
stimulates the tongue,
while the richness
warms the throat!
Exquisite. Life is
about stimulation.
And not going through all the
highs and lows it can offer.
Leaves one sour.
We're on the scene at the
Lordly Tailor exhibit hall...
Tch. This ought
to be a real party.
[MAYA growls] Stupid jerk!
I mean, who would steal our urn?
All right, then.
Since it's our treasure
that was stolen,
it's up to you to
find the thief!
--[gasps]
--Yeah, she's right!
The only person who
can get it back is you!
But I'm just a defense
attorney, not a private eye.
Hey! Don't start making excuses!
A real hero will gladly do
whatever it takes to help out
his beloved maiden in need!
[PHOENIX]
Man, I can't win against
Pearl's fairy tale
ideas about romance.
But how are we gonna get inside?
It won't be easy.
[gasps]
[MAYA]
Excuse me. Coming through.
Hold it, lady!
No outsiders allowed!
I am not an outsider, pal!
I even have my lawyer and
my cousin here with me!
[PHOENIX] Why would
having a cousin matter?
[ANDREWS]
Mr. Wright!
[gasps]
Ms. Andrews!
[ANDREWS] Thanks again
for your help last time.
I was just doing my job, ma'am.
Anyway, I didn't expect
to see you here.
[PHOENIX]
This is Ms. Adrian Andrews.
Former talent agent
and a crucial figure in
the Nickel Samurai case.
[ANDREWS] Things have changed a
lot for me since the last time
we saw each other.
I'm now head of events and
promotion for Lordly Tailor.
I am truly sorry
about all of this.
I've failed you.
[gasps]
Your precious urn was
stolen from right under my nose.
I take full responsibility.
But, I promise--
No! The person responsible
is the phantom thief!
[gasps]
We know this is the last
thing you wanted to happen.
Thanks for that. And I'll
try to make things right.
You can start by telling us
everything you know
about the crime.
Well, first off, the phantom
thief himself sent us
a calling card of
sorts ten days ago.
[PHOENIX]
What did it say?
[ANDREWS] That he was
planning on stealing
the most valuable piece in
the Kurain Village exhibit.
Guess the urn's more
valuable than it looks, huh?
That urn has Mystic
Ami's spirit inside of it,
which makes it
unbelievably valuable!
Hard to believe.
We had an appraisal
done that discovered
it had zero monetary value.
Zero...?
But I did my best to
polish it and make it look
like it was worth millions!
I think it's quite a beautiful
work of art, honestly!
Aw... Poor Mystic Ami...
Oh, but of course
money isn't everything!
You simply can't put
a price on historical value.
Not to mention on a soul!
I misspoke! Please forgive me!
[ANDREWS]
This is where it was stored.
So it was in here?
Doesn't really look like
a crime scene to me.
[GUMSHOE]
Fancy seeing you again.
[PHOENIX]
Detective Gumshoe!
It's nutty. What are the odds?
How are you there
every single time?
Aren't you a homicide detective?
Look! Over there!
It's Mystic Ami!
Oh. Very impressive.
But what is she
doing over there...?
Something wrong, Ms. Andrews?
[ANDREWS]
Ah? Oh, no.
But the little girl is right,
that's a statue of Ami Fey,
the founder of the
Kurain School's
spirit channeling technique.
It was delivered
yesterday afternoon.
Just think about it,
Mystic Maya,
someday, you'll take over
the clan and become
the master of Kurain.
Isn't it cool?
Uh. Oh, yeah!
My, my, might this be
a meeting of the minds?
[GROUP]
Hmm?
[LUKE chuckles]
Wait. Who's this?
Welcome to my little soiree.
A Feast of Chaos!
[LUKE chuckles] I see it as
clearly as the nose on my face.
You do? But what is it?
[LUKE]
Zvarri!
And once again, the truth so
elegantly reveals itself to me.
I see a lawyer
and a spirit medium.
Both but beginners in their
particular professions.
Say what? How could you
know all that just by looking?
[LUKE] How, you ask?
For a skeptical mind,
"how" is as pertinent
a question as "why."
I am a tried and true
traveler of both time and space.
As well as a man who
drifts through dreams.
I might call him a lot of
things, but not any of those.
He's just trying
to put on a show.
The poster for the exhibition
had a little blurb about you.
And the attorney's
badge I'm wearing
is kind of a giveaway.
I am Luke Atmey!
A man unto whom some
have bestowed the title.
Ace Detective.
Sounds familiar.
I've seen him on the news,
he was on the "Great People
in Town" segment.
[PHOENIX]
Is that really even a thing?
Seems there's
a plethora of things
you don't know, counselor!
It's quite strange.
Usually, the tales of my
investigative prowess
precede me wherever I go!
Very well.
Please, allow me the pleasure
of enlightening you on
the topic of myself!
If this has not permeated
the particular rock
you're living under,
there is a yin and yang
of good and evil in this city!
I am on the side of light,
while Mask DeMasque
dwells in darkness!
And when his shadow
enshrouds all under its pall,
I shall turn a spotlight on
that ghostly figure
and expose him to the world!
You get the feeling his
voice is his favorite sound?
[PHOENIX]
Mm-hmm.
[LUKE] I have been personally
pursuing the pseudonymed phantom
since the inception of his
immorality, and thwarted
his latest loathsome larceny
armed only with my intellect
and insatiable
inquisitive ingenuity!
One could argue that
we're two sides of the same coin
buying our way into history.
A rivalry for the ages!
And last night, at 1 AM,
we stood face to face
in the bowels of this building,
engaged in brilliant battle!
[PHOENIX]
So it was 1 AM. Wait.
You mean to tell us that you
were on the premises
when the robbery took place?
But of course. You see...
Wherever DeMasque dares
to tread, be assured, Atmey
has already set an elegant trap.
Ah. But the trap was
not elegant enough.
Actually, I allowed him
to escape filled with fantasy.
An illusion of victory.
But still, you were
on guard last night. Why?
The gentlewoman solicited
my services as sentry.
Twenty days ago, in fact,
which was ten full days,
before DeMasque declared
his dastardly designs
to dame Andrews.
She hired you before the
calling card was delivered?
I did. I couldn't
shake the feeling
something bad was
going to happen.
And her premonition
proved to be prescient.
The calling card
arrived soon after.
Indeed!
And since I am an Ace Detective,
I expertly arranged an elegant
trap to ensnare the thief.
If you knew something
was gonna happen,
why not go to the
police for help?
Feh. Like I need backup from
that bumbling bunch of boobs.
Why, you-- What did you say?
Well, previously...
...I personally pried
a priceless possession
from the prowling purloiner.
The masked marauder's
mischief making is matched
only by my meticulous mind.
Meanwhile, you metropolitan
meatheads missed
the mark on Mask
DeMasque's malfeasance.
[GUMSHOE growls]
So, counselor.
Am I correct in my
characterization that
you're committed to
capturing this caped criminal?
Oh, we'll get 'im!
I won't let this phantom
clown get away with taking
Mystic Ami's urn!
[LUKE]
Positively perfect.
Please proceed with
perusing the perimeter
whist I explore elsewhere.
We shall catch up counselor.
Happiest of hunting.
[PHOENIX gruntz]
That tool's a ton to take.
He'd better start
respecting my authority.
[phone rings]
Yeah?
[MAYA]
Hmm?
[GUMSHOE] What? Mask DeMasque
really just turned himself in?
[BOTH gasp]
[GUMSHOE]
Sit tight, folks.
The guards are gonna be bringing
him over in just a second.
I don't think that I've
ever seen you this happy.
It's a great day!
We got our criminal
and that weird detective
can go suck an egg!
I'm gonna go start typing
up the report, see ya!
Let's keep up
this winning streak!
Since he surrendered himself,
does it really count as a win?
Duh! Of course it's a win!
Why are you so worked up, Maya?
It should be completely
obvious why,
because we're the victims!
--Yeah, I guess so.
-[RON] Hey, there.
Since we're always
doing murder cases,
I usually think of the victims
as dead people and
that's super upsetting to me!
[RON]
Excuse me.
Wait, we gotta get the urn
back for Poor Mystic Ami!
In case you haven't noticed,
I'm talkin' over here!
Oh, sorry about that!
Someone's there?
Is that the guy?
Excuse me. But my
name is Ron DeLite.
And, uh... I'm also
known as Mask DeMasque.
Or The Phantom Thief.
Really? You're a
criminal mastermind?
Oh, yeah! That's right!
Or is it?
I guess I can't really say
which one's a character
and which one's me.
He doesn't strike me
as the mysterious type.
I mean... He talks like
he's trying to keep a secret.
I know those looks.
The last thing that I want
from you people is pity!
Okay, sure, we get it!
Hey! We need you give
us back that urn right now!
Yeah! I promise
I'll give it to you.
But can I? Not good
to make promises I can't keep.
Yo! Speak up when
you're talkin' to me!
I'm sorry about that!
But I hate it when people yell!
[GROUP]
Ah...
[pants]
Look, uh... I, uh, kind of...
I lost the Kurain urn, okay?
Huh?
You... What?
You have gotta be kidding me!
No, I wish this was
some kind of joke.
But these things
happen all the time.
You know, like leaving
your bag on a train.
You left Mystic Ami's
urn on a train?
And you were just
casually riding around
in that getup?
Now calm down! It's just
a hypothetical situation.
Anyway...
I'm so sorry!
This guy...
[DESIRÉE]
Ronnie!
[GROUP gasps]
[RON]
Oh, Dessie!
Don't worry.
I'm gonna do everything in my
power to get you outta there.
I know you will, Dessie.
So, uh...
Please forgive me,
my name is Desirée DeLite.
Desirée's my... My lovely wife.
[gasps]
The phantom thief has a wife?
My name is Phoenix Wright,
I'm a defense attorney.
You don't say?
Then, are you meeting with my
Ronnie because you're gonna
take on his defense?
Well, I haven't made up my mind.
Listen up, lady.
We're the real victims
here, you got that?
[gasps]
Wait a minute, are you Maya?
[MAYA]
Huh?
Do you two know each other?
She's on the poster. So.
You're the Kurain
master's daughter, right?
I didn't realize I was
starting to get so famous.
Gosh, you're making me blush!
[PHOENIX]
I thought you were a victim.
[DESIRÉE] Ronnie did what?
No, I refuse to believe it!
Why on earth would
he steal an urn?
That's a tough question.
But let me ask you something.
You know, don't you?
About your husband
and Mask DeMasque?
That's no secret.
He's pretty open about it.
I mean, he's practically
DeMasque's biggest fan.
He's a fan?
Oh, definitely.
And he can get carried away.
Wait, would you
clarify that, please?
What do you mean
by "carried away"?
He pretends he's
the phantom thief,
and sometimes,
it's like he believes it.
It's kooky, but so adorable.
[PHOENIX]
Ah...
Ronnie's timid. Always has been.
So. DeMasque is like his hero.
His hero? But the
phantom thief is a bad guy!
[DESIRÉE chuckles]
Anyway.
If Ronnie had stolen the urn,
wouldn't he still have it?
I'd think so.
Well. Yeah.
That would make sense.
He is odd.
But I would never let him
do anything illegal.
Good to know.
I wouldn't think otherwise.
I believe somebody
must've framed him
for the robbery.
Really?
I realize it's
a lot to ask of you.
But would you agree
to defend my husband?
--Well...
--There's a lot more
to this case than meets the eye,
I know it! Please!
I'm begging you!
Mrs. DeLite.
How's this sound?
I'll consider it and start
a full investigation.
Huh?
Seriously? Thank you.
I truly appreciate your help!
How could you...?
[PEARL gasps, growls]
I am very disappointed
in you, Mr. Nick!
What did I do now?
Don't play dumb!
You're gonna defend that thief!
He stole our family's
legacy from us!
But what if it turns out
that Ron DeLite isn't really
Mask DeMasque after all?
Oh, because his wife
said he was delusional?
She was probably lying to us!
Or she could
be telling us the truth.
[gasps]
[PEARL] I can't believe
you'd really defend that jerk
after what he did to Mystic Ami.
It breaks my heart...
I can never forgive you!
[gasps]
Hang on, Pearls!
[MAYA whimpers]
[PEARL]
Mystic Maya. I'm sorry.
[MAYA]
Eh?
You and Mr. Nick are
fighting because of me.
[MAYA] Mm-mm. You didn't do
anything wrong, sweetie.
But what if it turns out
that Ron DeLite isn't really
Mask DeMasque after all?
[MAYA sighs]
So, what do you think
we should do now?
Talk to her. We'll get
the whole story from Desirée.
Ah.
I want to know more about Ron.
Does that sound good to you?
[gasps]
Yeah.
[PHOENIX]
Uh, hello?
Hello? Is anybody here?
[sighs]
Don't know where he is,
but that guy is out to lunch.
I was hoping to get more
info on Mask DeMasque.
but I guess it'll have to wait.
[MASK laughs]
Sorry to get your hopes up.
Those are the breaks.
So then. To what do
I owe this pleasure?
Well, first off, sorry for
dropping in unannounced.
It's cool. Without Ronnie here,
my only company is all
these costumes and toys.
There are a lot.
It's wild.
To say he's got an
obsession is an understatement.
I don't know what to
do with him sometimes.
Anyway. What do you two need?
Well. I, uh...
[tea kettle whistles]
Hold on a second.
I'll go pour us some tea.
A-Ah...
[PHOENIX]
I wanna see what's in there.
No, that sounds like
something Maya would do.
I can almost picture
her egging me on.
Just open it up Nick!
A little peek won't kill ya.
[PHOENIX] No, that's not how
an attorney conducts himself!
Don't be such a scaredy-cat!
Now's your only chance!
[PHOENIX groans]
Yeah. Fine. Just a peek, then.
All right, little Pearls.
Time to get to sleuthin'!
Yeah, okay.
With all this crazy stuff here,
this has gotta be the
phantom thief's hideout.
[gasps, screams]
[gasps]
Oh, Mystic Maya, are you okay?
Ah?
--[doorbell rings]
--[DESIRÉE] Coming!
[MAYA gasps]
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate it.
[gasps]
Why's he here?
[PHOENIX] What is this?
Something smooth and hard.
[gasps]
Ahoy! Is anyone here?
Counselor, this
is quite concerning.
I'm flabbergasted to
find a friend of the law
flagrantly ignoring it.
Uh. I'm sorry about that.
Right. I suppose your
shortage of scruples will be
of service as you
stand on the side of that
sinister scofflaw,
some call DeMasque.
[PHOENIX]
Where did you hear that?
I'll be there at the trial.
Providing my perceptions
to the prosecution.
--[gasps]
--And Zvarri...
This testimony will
take its toll on you.
You miserable minion
of Mask DeMasque.
[sighs]
Minion, eh?
[LUKE chuckles] Although,
I alone am not your adversary.
Tomorrow's trial will
introduce a terrible threat
who will truly thwart
your thriving trajectory.
What do you mean?
[LUKE] A defense's most
fearsome foe is a properly
prepared prosecutor.
You may be used to
Edgeworth's excellence,
but your next enemy
is without equal.
He is correctly called the
most cunning counselor
in the country.
But you may know him as...
...Godot!
[GODOT] Hmph. We're to do battle
in this gladiator's arena.
[PHOENIX gasps]
The sole reason
I've returned from
the ghastly depths of Hell.
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
The case of Kurain's stolen
treasure continues as
the trial of Ron DeLite,
or Mask DeMasque, begins.
Standing before
me is the resurrected,
undefeated, legendary
prosecutor, Godot!
Something stinks
about this case.
And as usual, Butz is to blame!
But the most offensive
odor oozes out of Atmey,
the demented detective.
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Next episode: "The Stolen
Turnabout--2nd Trial"!
Take that!