[PHOENIX] Maya and I
traveled to Hazakura Temple
in the snowy mountains,
so she could further
her spiritual training.
But tragedy struck
when children's book author
Elise Deauxnim was murdered.
Lightning set Dusky
Bridge on fire,
stranding Maya on
the other side of the river.
Failing to cross over and save
her, I ended up stranded, too--
in a hospital bed.
The police arrested
Sister Iris for the murder.
The defendant is a secretive nun
who bears an uncanny resemblance
to Dahlia Hawthorne,
whose face I could never forget.
As a favor to me,
Miles agreed to argue
her case at trial.
Things looked bleak,
but when his fellow
Von Karma protégé, Franziska,
had him backed into a corner,
a voice cried foul!
[BUTZ]
Objection!
[MILES]
Larry!
Sorry, Vincent Van Bro,
but you can
call me Laurice Deauxnim.
Did he say Deauxnim?
[BUTZ] Everything that
happened that night.
I saw it all.
And if I can save
my beautiful little flower,
I'll paint you a masterpiece
with my testimony!
So you say
you name is Laurice Deauxnim.
That right?
Your Honor.
This man was apprentice
to the late Ms. Deauxnim.
That night, he was staying in a
small cabin near the scene.
I was having a ball
in Heavenly Hall!
That's not relevant.
What about the night
in question?
Hey, I'm just
tryin' to set the scene.
I'm gonna tell you my story,
'cause I ain't runnin'
from the truth!
[MILES] You say that,
yet you've proven you'll run
from my questions.
[JUDGE 204A] Well, sir,
please begin your testimony.
Iris did take the
snowmobile that night.
But it wasn't
to commit any crime.
No, she did it to
give us all a warning.
We needed to know
that dinner was ready!
[JUDGE 204A]
Dinner?
Yeah! She was
like "come and get it."
Oh, man, she looked super-cool!
A little later that night,
I was in the cabin cranking
out a true work of art.
Well, in my dreams.
Say what? Can you translate?
I'd wager he
means he dozed off
while painting or drawing.
Suddenly, crashentino!
Pow! It was hella loud.
Totally scared the
living crap outta me.
But then I saw that
creaky ol' bridge up in flames.
I rushed over to check it out,
and that's when I ran
into my buddy Nick.
Was the bridge still intact?
Well, I wouldn't have set
foot on it if you paid me to.
The thing was up in flames.
But Nick was feeling brave.
He tried to cross it and
tumbled right into the gorge.
Is that true?
[gasps]
He didn't sustain any injuries.
Caught a nasty cold, however.
He either has the
most incredible or rotten luck.
It's almost impossible to tell.
So Larry.
According to police records,
they received a call about
the incident at 11:30.
You were the one who made
that call, were you not?
[BUTZ] Yeah! That's exactly
what I shoulda done, right?
Lightning struck Dusky
bridge at approximately
10:45 that night.
Can you explain why
there was a 45 minute gap
before you called?
[gasps]
You said you
were staying in a cabin
a stone's throw away.
So why did you wait to call?
Uh, let's see...
Well... I, uh...
What the hell?!
Answer the question!
I wasn't just sitting there!
I'm an artiste, ya know?
It was divine inspiration!
I just had to make some art!
So, you were painting?
The bridge wasn't
the only thing burning,
my artistic spirit
was also on fire!
So you were just drawing
over by the burning bridge
until the moment Phoenix
Wright showed up?
Well, duh! I said that
it was divine inspiration!
The bridge was giving
up its life for my art!
What a selfish thing to say!
[BOTH gasp]
Okay. Then show
us your creation.
Why?
I'm not sure that the piece is
quite ready for exhibition yet.
When I saw you
yesterday, you said you
witnessed something "bonkers."
Does this artwork have
anything to do with that?
[gasps]
Wow.
I've actually been dreaming
about how this would happen.
But I never imagined
Laurice Deauxnim
would make his grand debut in--
--Ow! Man, that stings! Stop!
--Just show it to us, now!
[BUTZ growls] I hope your
brains can handle it.
Behold!
The world, as seen through
my unique artistic eye!
♪ Da-da-da-dah! ♪
It's unique.
But could you tell us what the
thing flying over the bridge is?
It's exactly what
it looks like, old pal.
You're going to have
to explain it.
Anybody with working eyeballs
can clearly see that's Iris!
[BUTZ] I still can't believe
she flew like that.
A beautiful girl like her needs
to take better care of herself,
or something's gonna happen
to ruin those looks.
[CROWD gasping]
Witness! Are
you really testifying to
this ridiculous claim that
the defendant was seen
flying over the bridge?
Yeah, and now
you understand why--
[yelps]
This all sounds like
something from a dream.
That's why I had to whip you.
To make sure everyone's awake.
If you're really worried
about that, then whip yourself!
So, Iris doesn't actually
need a snowmobile
to get from place to place.
'Cause it turns out that
gorgeous angel can fly!
Well, this is hardly believable.
[MILES]
Is this how he sees the world?
I should never have
let him speak.
[FRANZISKA]
Control your witness!
If you're able, please
bring this unhinged fool
back down to Earth.
Wait, you're asking me?
Yes, of course.
This, "artiste."
So he's your friend?
If true, you're
a fool's accessory.
[MILES gasps]
You heard the judge, Edgy.
An accessory!
[MILES]
What the hell is going on here?!
I mean, he's gotta be
high on something.
So just to clarify
things once again.
You saw Sister Iris
flying over the bridge?
Yeah.
I was watching the
fire for a second,
and then, all of a sudden...
Whoosh!
She was pulling like,
30 feet of air and a sweet arc.
I see.
And do you happen to know where
she may have been flying?
I got no clue,
I just kinda caught a glimpse
of her through the window.
And so, I started creating
my rendition like a madman!
But how can you be
so sure it was the defendant
that you saw? You couldn't have
had a clear view from the cabin.
[chuckles]
You do realize who
you're talking to?
I'm a Deauxnim.
Nothing escapes my artist's eye!
Including proof she
was the person I saw!
There's proof?
[BUTZ chuckles]
After Nick went
whizzing into the gorge,
I called the cops.
I came back to where
the bridge used to be
and saw something nutty.
"Nutty," how?
I'll show ya!
So, what is this?
A crystal sphere?
Or what?
Pretty sure it's
the thing from Iris's
weird hoodie that she wears.
I think that it probably
fell off when she landed.
[FRANZISKA] Well. Her headwear
did have a crystal sphere on it.
[JUDGE 204A gasps] There's a
red stain on this, right there.
I believe that
it might be blood.
There are bloodstains on it?
[CROWD gasping]
That's why I was worried
about her doing dangerous stuff.
Poor thing...
She must've hit the ground
too hard when she landed.
[MILES]
Objection!
[BUTZ whimpers, yelps]
After your testimony,
there is one fact that
I'm absolutely certain of.
[BUTZ]
Yeah? Well, what is it?
The person that
you depicted in this work...
...could not be the defendant!
Uh... No?
The night of the crime.
Sister Iris's head was
completely uncovered.
But as seen in this picture.
[JUDGE 204A] You can tell
she has the hood on right there.
What?
Oh, really? But how in
the world would you know that?
I mean, you weren't even at
the temple that night, man.
Because I talked to
the person to whom she had
earlier given her hood.
She gave it to Phoenix Wright.
What? So Nick had it?
I believe that
he may have been
the hooded figure you painted.
He was wearing one, after all.
[BUTZ growls]
Why does he always do this?
It was, like, totally obvious
I was into her!
Calm yourself!
So explain the crystal sphere!
It was discovered at
the foot of Dusky Bridge.
And there're clearly
bloodstains on it!
That one is too big.
[gasps]
Just look at the size of it.
The one you're holding.
It would be preposterous for
that to be attached to a hood.
[JUDGE 204A]
Oh. Yes. Excellent point.
That night, there was
one person at the temple
who lost a crystal sphere
and left bloodstains. Correct?
[BUTZ] Oh, is that so?
And who would that moron be?
I'm surprised you asked that.
I'm talking about the woman
who mentored you, moron.
Ah! What? You mean Elise?
[FRANZISKA]
Wait. So the victim dropped it?
As shown here,
there's a similar crystal
sphere affixed to her cane.
That may be,
but do you have any actual proof
that this one belonged to her?
Just look. The evidence
tells the whole story.
[FRANZISKA gasps]
[BUTZ]
Whoa! Her orb is gone!
To make sure
I understand, Defense,
are you implying it was
the victim who flew across
the bridge that night?
That would be
the logical conclusion.
Even though, the fact remains
that humans cannot fly.
[CROWD gasping murmuring]
[FRANZISKA]
Objection!
A fool, working with
another fool on a fool's errand
to foolishly reach a foolish
conclusion together.
What do you mean by that?
The night of the murder,
Elise Deauxnim was in her room.
Which is located
at Hazakura temple.
She had no reason to
go to Dusky Bridge at that hour.
[MILES growls]
[MILES]
Unfortunately, she's correct.
There's no proof that the
victim left her room that night.
But, there's also
no proof she didn't.
It seems that
you have nothing to say.
Rare that you're speechless.
[MILES] I have a hunch,
but can I prove it?
No, it doesn't matter if I can.
Because I must!
[MILES] After all,
that's the way Wright
would approach the situation.
I'm sure of it.
This new evidence
points us in the direction
of a new possibility.
[FRANZISKA]
A new possibility?
And what's that?
[MILES]
Of an entirely new crime scene.
She wasn't killed at the temple.
Maybe... the murder was
committed next to Dusky Bridge!
What? So the
scene's wrong, but ho--
[yelps]
How foolish! There's no way!
She must've gone
down to the bridge.
While she was there,
something happened.
And as a result, the sphere
was knocked loose.
Then it somehow came
into contact with blood.
And you think that
"something" was her murder?
The killer took her body
back to Hazakura Temple.
They wanted to make it appear as
though she was murdered there.
[FRANZISKA]
Objection!
Have you forgotten?
The head nun of Hazakura
gave us her testimony earlier.
She said she saw your
client killing the victim
in the courtyard!
[MILES]
Objection!
She later clarified that what
she saw, was the defendant
holding on to the
weapon sticking out
of the victim's back.
Not the moment
of the actual murder!
[gasps]
Maybe so.
But it takes ten minutes to walk
from the bridge to the temple.
It's too far.
The killer wouldn't
have carried
the body all that way.
There was a snowmobile,
was there not?
What?
[MILES] They must've used
it to transport the body.
Any "fool" can see that all
the pieces are in place!
[CROWD gasping, murmurin]
[JUDGE 204A]
Order, order! Please!
[yelps]
The defendant was
the only one who had
access to the snowmobile!
What's more, the witness saw her
with her hands on
the murder weapon!
Which leads us
to the same conclusion.
That Sister Iris
is the murderer!
Miss von Karma,
despite your assertions,
the defense has
completed our objective.
At least for the time being.
What? What are you
trying to say?
[MILES] We've proven it is
not possible to hand down
a definite verdict
at the moment.
The case requires
further investigation.
We need to discover
where the murder
really took place.
And why the killer
needed to move the body.
Also.
What's actually being depicted
in the witness's artwork.
Please. Don't be foolish.
Do you seriously believe the
victim was somehow flying?
[MILES] Her crystal sphere
was found at the foot
of Dusky Bridge.
And her body was completely
covered in bruises indicating
she fell from a sizeable height.
What stands out most to me
is this man would never
hurt or lie about a girl
with whom he is enamored.
Oh. Edgy-boy.
He drew what he saw then.
So something had
to have happened.
I hereby request
that both the defense
and the prosecution conduct
further investigation.
And so, with that,
court is now adjourned!
[FRANZISKA growls]
[MILES sighs]
I've done all I can here.
Wright. The rest is up to you.
[PHOENIX]
Thanks, Miles.
Way to stick to your guns.
I knew you could do it.
All I did was buy more time,
so we're not out
of the woods yet.
Anyway...
Are you sure you're
ready to leave the hospital?
Not to be rude, but, uh...
You're rather green.
The good news is
my fever has gone down a bit
since yesterday.
What's your temperature?
Well, I'm finally under 102,
so that's a major improvement--
[coughs]
[MILES sighs] So stubborn.
I've always admired that.
[rasping] It's something the
two of us have in common.
Indeed.
Which is why I can't stop
thinking about this case.
The Shichishito
wasn't what killed her.
So there's gotta be
another sword out there
that was used. We just
need to find it somehow.
That would be decisive.
I'll be stopping
by the old precinct,
to do some digging
on another factor.
And what's that?
I'm hoping to find some
more info on our client.
--What?
--Do you mean Iris?
I can't shake
this nagging feeling
that we've met before.
All I want is confirmation.
[gasps]
And it's perfectly
obvious that's something
I won't be getting from you.
[PHOENIX]
Hm. Yeah, sorry.
Well, the rest is in your hands.
So, are you about
ready to hit the road, pal?
We can take my patrol car.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
Well, it's a
necessary precaution.
Gotta keep you safe
so Edgeworth's defense
won't be in vain.
[MILES (recording)]
Objection! Objection! Objection!
Ah! Just got the news that
Dusky Bridge got patched up,
so we'll finally be
able to cross over.
[gasps]
Whoa! What the hell is that?
Not quite sure,
but it wasn't here two days ago.
Has anyone seen or heard
from Maya and Pearl?
We haven't been able
to locate those two just yet.
So they're still inside.
Can you hear me?
We'll save you!
[PEARL]
Mister Nick!
[PHOENIX]
Oh, Pearl!
I'm so glad to see you!
[PEARL sobs]
So you've been
over here the whole time?
I was so lonely,
and so scared that I was gonna
be stuck here forever.
'Cause when I woke up,
the bridge wasn't there anymore,
and I was by myself.
That sounds scary.
Hey, wait. You were alone?
Where's Maya?
[PEARL whimpers]
If you know where to find Maya,
you need to tell me.
I... I'm sorry, Mister Nick.
Uh, not your fault.
[GUMSHOE]
Something smells good.
[PHOENIX gasps]
Like a hot, spicy,
tickle in the ol' honker.
[sniffs]
Wait, that's weird. Curry?
[GUMSHOE]
Yeah, that's exactly what it is!
Looks yummy-- I mean, yucky.
My mouth's watering.
I mean, my skin's crawlin'!
[PHOENIX] We all ate curry
for dinner that night.
Is this the same
curry from then?
Why the heck is it here?
[PEARL]
Mister Nick. It is all my fault.
What? What is, Pearl?
[sobs]
Poor Mystic Maya!
Hey! Hang on! Pearl!
I'll handle it, okay?
You don't need
to be running around.
Come on, Phoenix.
This useless
schtick isn't cutting it.
[sighs]
Maya needs me.
[GODOT] I gotta say you're
looking pathetic, Trite.
[PHOENIX]
Huh...?
We're kinda lucky
to be here, ya know?
This place has been hit
by so many earthquakes
over the years that...
...I wouldn't be surprised
to see it turned into a pile
of rocks any day now.
Didn't expect to see you.
Looks like we've got
a trick lock on our hands.
Only one who can open that
is the one who set it.
Who could that have been?
Do you know?
Think about it.
Who came and took over
watch for the head nun?
It was Sister Iris, am I right?
She locked it?
I've made arrangements
for her to come here.
Hopefully she'll be
showing up before much longer.
[PHOENIX groans]
Heh. Feeling a little woozy, eh?
Maybe you should go
on back to your cradle.
I'll be fine. But tell me...
How come you decided to
not show up to the trial today?
Do you remember what
I told you in that first trial?
Right at the beginning.
That I would battle you
in the gladiator's arena.
"The sole reason I returned from
the ghastly depths of Hell."
Death is something
I've experienced firsthand.
Really? You died?
In order to maintain
my new lease on life,
I've gotta go through
a lot of annoying procedures.
Checkups, transfusions,
more of this fluid,
less of another one.
Modern medicine
is a pain in the ass,
but it's the only way
I can stay alive.
It's just who I am now.
Oh, I see.
You were in the hospital.
[GODOT] Hmph. I don't wear
this mask just 'cause
it looks cool, ya know?
Without this thing on,
I can't see all those puzzled
looks on your face.
But why?
What the hell happened to you?
[GODOT] Tch.
You should know all this, boy.
How I died.
And who it was that killed me!
[PHOENIX gasps]
[PHOENIX] I kinda feel like
I have answers somewhere
in the back of my mind.
Like maybe I've heard a story
about a prosecutor dying.
Wait. Hang on.
Look at the base
of that lantern.
There's no snow underneath it.
Did somebody clear it away?
That's what
was said in the trial.
The defense questioned
the crime scene.
He said that it was
somewhere else entirely.
Apparently, this is it.
Oh, really?
She was killed here instead.
I'm worried about Maya.
Stuck in there.
After that rickety old
bridge finally got patched up,
the cops looked all over
the Inner Temple.
But there was neither
hide nor hair of her.
Only place left.
Would be somewhere behind that
door with the crazy lock on it.
Gets really cold
inside the sacred cavern.
Below freezing.
I hope she can survive.
No way...
And if we can't
bust her out in time,
it means you sent a
woman off to die.
Won't be your first one.
The hell d'ya mean by that?
Your memory can't be so bad.
Just three years ago,
an innocent woman died
because of you, didn't she?
[gasps]
Do you mean... Mia?
Yeah.
Maya Fey's older sister.
And your mentor, right?
She'd still be alive now
if it weren't for you.
No.
[GODOT]
Three years ago,
Mia made a very dangerous
person her enemy,
and it cost her her life!
I know.
And I didn't rest until I made
sure he paid for what he did!
Yeah, he may have
been caught, but so what?
The truth is...
That's not gonna bring her back.
[PHOENIX growls]
And you...
You were with her right
until that psycho killed her.
It was your job to
make sure that she was safe,
and you failed!
[PHOENIX growls]
She should've never
taken you under her wing.
You're a coward!
If you had any guts,
she'd be with us right now.
And it's not just her!
You're gonna let the same thing
happen to her little sister!
No... I'm not...
You're just a weakling.
And that's why I will never
accept you as a peer.
[GODOT grunts]
[PHOENIX] Maya. I can't
let her die in there.
It's up to me.
[PHOENIX]
What the... It can't be.
I don't get it.
What the hell is going on?
[PHOENIX]
Objection!
This investigation is turning up
more questions than answers.
Why is Godot so against me?
And what's his
connection to Mia?
Meanwhile, the discovery
of new evidence puts Maya
under the microscope.
One after another, earth
shattering facts come to light.
But what's most shocking
is who's behind it all.
Profound darkness threatens
to swallow us whole.
Find the contradictions!
Believe in the truth!
Next episode: "Bridge to
the Turnabout - 4th Trial"!
Take that!