[NARRATOR]
Pars Era, the year 321. April.
Crown Prince Arslan issued
the Decree to Pursue
and Destroy Lusitania
and the Decree to
Abolish Slavery,
prompting numerous lords and
generals from across the kingdom
to rally to him.
Thus they found themselves
on the verge of a war
that would prove a turning
point in Parsian history.
[LUCIAN]
Greetings, Your Highness.
I am Lucian, Lord of Ray.
I've come in response
to your decree.
I shall be honored to fight
the Lusitanian invaders.
If my prince will have me.
[FARANGIS] The influx of
soldiers has been ceaseless
since His Highness
issued the decree.
The fortress will be
overflowing before long.
This is incredible, though.
To be part of it.
To be so close to something
that will change history.
Incredible indeed.
[DARYUN]
To be perfectly honest,
their number is far greater
than I had expected.
I find it heartening
so many would come
to His Highness' side.
You assumed abolishing slavery
would alienate the lords
and cause resentment among them.
[DARYUN]
Mm.
More than likely the lords
feel it won't be an issue.
Not an issue? How is that?
They'll defeat the
Lusitanians first.
Then, once His Highness
has the throne,
they think his youth will
allow them to prevail upon him
to abandon the Decree.
[DARYUN grunts]
There's another problem.
I'm sure you've noticed,
with the increase in
the Fortress's numbers,
tensions have also increased.
Indeed.
Do you suggest I've come here
intending to cause harm
to His Highness?
[JASWANT]
It is not my habit to trust men
who prowl about His Highness'
room in the dead of night.
I am the Prince's guard.
It is my duty to see that
nothing threatens him. Ever.
You aren't even
from this kingdom,
yet you would claim yourself
as a member of His
Highness's inner circle?
Go back to tending
your water buffaloes,
or whatever it is you do.
Watch what you say
to me, insolent dog.
Don't they call you
the Black Cat?
Your face is looking
more red to me.
[growls]
By all means.
Stop this foolishness,
both of you.
Or would you do the
Lusitanians' job for them?
Is something wrong?
I heard there was a fight.
Jaswant and Zaravant
nearly came to blows?
That has already
reached your ears, then.
[ARSLAN]
Yes.
So, it's true.
There is dissension here
within the fortress.
[NARSUS]
Yes.
I suspect that disgruntlement
and wounded pride
are at the root of it.
Some bristle to see those
of lower social standing
in positions of trust
to Your Highness.
I prefer to treat
everyone equally,
regardless of social standing.
What shall I do?
How can we see this
settled without bloodshed?
Well, Highness, to begin with,
you may consider demoting
me from my current post.
[gasps]
Surely you're joking!
What're you saying?
At the moment, I'm
His Highness's satruyp.
It is a post equal
to Grand Vizier.
By rights, it should be
given to someone older.
Someone experienced who enjoys
the confidence of the people.
Who would you recommend, then?
Lord Lucian should
fill the post well.
And what of you?
You aren't bothered by this?
So long as I may still command
the army, there is no problem.
This troubles me.
We already have an enemy.
We don't need such conflict
within our own camp.
That is the unavoidable
consequence
of swelling our ranks.
Unpleasant, but not unexpected.
You must be prepared for
such things as commander.
Your Highness.
Enough of this for now.
There is still something
else to speak of.
Let's bring Lord Lucian
into the discussion, as well.
[NARSUS]
One man in the enemy camp
poses a particular threat to us.
The Lusitanians' guest
general, Prince Hilmes.
Hilmes? You mean?
Yes, son of the
late King Osroes.
And, by extension,
Prince Arslan's cousin.
He is currently offering his
services to the Lusitanian army.
[LUCIAN] Still alive,
after all this time.
But why side with Lusitania?
[NARSUS] Most likely as
a means to get revenge
and take back the throne.
That is his main objective.
Prince Hilmes claims
he should rule Pars,
by virtue of his parentage.
And, in truth, there is
substance to his claim.
Had circumstances favored him,
he would be Crown Prince.
He's not worthy of the throne.
He's brought harm to the
people of his own kingdom.
Even if he is of royal blood,
I find such actions
to be unforgivable.
I agree with you, Daryun.
A king doesn't harm his own.
Surely the people
deserve better.
[LUCIAN]
Mmm.
I agree, as well.
Whatever his reasons,
such conduct is inexcusable.
I have no objection
to continuing to support
Prince Arslan as
the Crown Prince.
Your Highness?
[ARSLAN]
It's only...
I heard a rumor after
I was brought to Court.
It was my father who
assassinated the previous king,
they said.
[DARYUN]
Uh.
I thought it was a wild tale.
Just something dreamt
up by gossip mongers.
But was it?
If my father truly is
guilty of such a thing...
Prince Hilmes's anger
may be justified.
How can I blame him
for wanting revenge?
We cannot know
what truly happened.
But even if the rumor
is true, as you fear,
it does not change what
Your Highness must now do.
Have you the resolve
to defeat Prince Hilmes
and take the throne
for yourself?
We'll drive off the Lusitanians.
That fight must come first.
I will see to my cousin later.
For now, we go to war.
Is the burden too great? Or--?
He is still only
14 years old.
[NARSUS] The uncertainty
regarding his lineage
must trouble him, as well.
[DARYUN]
Hmm.
[GIEVE] So, His Highness
knows he is not of royal blood
and that there is another prince
with a legitimate claim.
Further, his own claim
to the throne
seems to be the result of crimes
committed by his father.
Our prince is sentimental.
He may seek to atone
for his father's crimes.
Perhaps, I don't know,
by yielding the throne
to Prince Hilmes?
Very possible.
You can't think--?
[NARSUS
I'm not alone.
The prince needs to find
his resolve, and swiftly.
He must decide what
the throne means to him.
Is what he hopes
to achieve so paltry
that he can simply give
it up to someone else?
[ARSLAN]
Who is the rightful king? Am I?
[TEMPLE KNIGHT A grunts]
You can live.
All you have to do is renounce
your god and abandon your faith.
Make your choice.
[TEMPLE KNIGHT COMMANDER]
O lord in heaven, be my witness!
[SAM]
It is done, sir.
There were 140-some Temple
Knights within the castle.
To a man, they have
all chosen death.
Zabul Fortress is ours, my lord.
And what of Bodin?
It seems he fled.
He abandoned his men.
[HILMES] Forsaken by their god
and forsaken by their commander.
Poor, pitiful wretches.
[ÉTOILE'S MAN A]
Lousy assignment.
Scouting Peshawar Fortress?
[ÉTOILE'S MAN B]
A lot of danger
and not even the hope
of good looting.
And you know what I heard?
Lord Étoile volunteered
for this mission himself.
He sure in a hurry to
make a name for himself.
[ÉTOILE'S MAN A]
Or a tombstone.
[ÉTOILE'S MEN laughing]
[ALL gasp]
[ÉTOILE'S MAN B] Lord Étoile!
Uhh, we were just saying--
[ÉTOILE]
At ease.
I'm not going to blame you
for complaining a bit.
[ÉTOILE'S MAN B]
Uh?
You men wait here.
Rest up while I see to
scouting the fortress.
Ah, yessir.
[ÉTOILE] In a hurry to make
a name for myself, eh?
[BARCACION]
I understand how you feel.
But I cannot allow you to take
such a dangerous mission.
Your grandfather
placed you in my care.
But that's why I left home
and came all the way here.
I must distinguish myself
in battle as a knight.
Don't you see?
It's worth the risk.
[ÉTOILE]
I must succeed.
I must become a fine knight.
For the sake of my family.
For the sake of
everybody back home.
[ÉTOILE] You have quite a lot
of provisions in your wagon.
[MERCHANT]
Oh.
Haven't you heard?
A whole host of soldiers
have gathered at Peshawar
from all across Pars.
Hey, with so many
soldiers in one place,
they're sure to want some
female companionship.
A pretty thing like you would
be more than welcome, I think.
[SOLDIER B]
I can't wait for battle!
I'll kill more of those
savages than anyone!
Ha! The men who say that
are always the first to die!
Say that again!
Here, let me give
you some more wine.
Look at me, girl.
You're a bit on
the scrawny side,
but there's nothin' wrong
with that face of yours.
[grunts]
Hey, hands off!
[SOLDIER B]
Huh?
[giggling]
Please, let me fill
your cup again, sir.
[SOLDIER B]
Uhh, sure.
[ÉTOILE]
I need to be careful.
[SOLDIER E] I don't know
about freeing the slaves.
That's a pretty drastic proposal
His Highness is making.
And especially before he's even
won the kingdom back, too.
Freeing Pars' slaves?
[ZARAVANT]
On May Tenth, we go to war!
For the restoration of Pars!
And for the Crown Prince!
Take back the Royal Capital!
To Ecbatana!
[SOLDIERS]
Yeah!
[ZARAVANT laughing]
[ZARAVANT]
We will triumph!
For Pars and the Prince!
These soldiers are unbelievable!
You would think
they'd already won.
Save the merrymaking
for after the battle!
Like a bunch of overgrown
children, aren't they?
[ÉTOILE gasping]
I, uh...
[giggling]
I don't envy you having to
wait on those drunken slobs.
It must be rough, huh?
Uh, and you are?
[ALFARID]
Oh.
Sorry, my name is Alfarid.
I'm a part of
Prince Arslan's army.
Since I'm a girl, and not
really a Parsian, either,
soldiers who don't know who I am
tend to look at
me a little funny.
I don't like it,
so I came out here.
[ÉTOILE] Is there discord
among their troops?
Maybe they aren't
solidly united, either.
Well, they can gawk
all they want.
I don't mind so long
as I have my Narsus.
Narsus, huh? Who's he?
[ALFARID] Only one of
the strongest, cleverest,
and most important people
in the entire army!
Oh, and he just happens
to be my lover, as well.
Your lover?!
[ALFARID]
Mh-hm.
In fact, he's probably
looking for me right now.
Have a nice night.
[ÉTOILE]
Uh.
[ÉTOILE] Using his rank to keep
a young girl as his mistress.
Pars is as degenerate
as I had thought!
[SOLDIER B]
Ah! There you are!
I've been looking
everywhere for you, girl.
Why're you out all alone?
Come here.
Let go!
You could do worse for
yourself than me, you know.
I'm a knight, off to
make a name for myself.
I could take care of you.
Truly? A knight?
A knight of Pars!
Shall we go?
[ÉTOILE]
Not a chance.
Huh?
Unhand me.
A knight is a proud
and honorable warrior
who will fight for the people!
Not a drunken braggart like you!
[growls]
[SOLDIER B]
You can't speak that way to me!
I'll show you, girl!
[ÉTOILE]
That was too far.
What now? Should I run?
No. I might be better
off just killing him.
[ARSLAN]
Pardon me.
Wait, are you...?
[ÉTOILE]
It's the spoiled rich boy again.
I can't believe
he's still alive.
He must be a great deal
smarter than he looks.
[ARSLAN]
Uh...
Well, I saw you
with that man earlier.
His attentions were unwanted?
[ÉTOILE]
Huh?
Yes. Very.
[ÉTOILE]
He doesn't realize it's me.
He's only unconscious.
Someone passing by
will find him, surely.
Thank you. I--
Best if you're not
found here, though.
I can sneak you out
of here. It'll be easy.
[ÉTOILE]
Uh... Oh!
[GIEVE]
Hm?
What have we here?
What do you find so
fascinating out there?
I was praying that the Goddess
Asashi may guide His Highness.
I can say one for
you if you like.
[GUARD A]
Hm?
The Fortress seems
rather a rough place
for a young lady of
your age to be employed.
What brought you here?
Some type of misfortune?
[ÉTOILE]
Oh.
A-A misfortune, yes!
My mother is ill,
my father has terrible
lower-back pain,
and all of my siblings are lame!
That sounds awful.
A whole family so afflicted.
Perhaps if you let me
find you a good doctor.
Don't trouble yourself.
No, please. I'd like to help.
I need no help from a heathen!
Did you say heathen?
[ÉTOILE]
Oh.
Heavens, no!
So, anyhow,
an awful lot of soldiers
seem to have gathered here.
[ARSLAN]
Yes.
We are all anxious to
take back the Royal Capital.
You ride to war as well?
Absolutely.
[ÉTOILE]
Truly?
Perhaps you shouldn't.
You do not look like you
would be much of a fighter.
Are you always this brutally
honest with strangers?
Could you help the war
effort in a different way?
There must be others
better suited to fighting.
Yes, there must be. Far better.
Why go at all, then?
What makes you
want to go to war?
I met someone.
A Lusitanian, actually.
A boy who'd been
brought here as a slave.
[gasps]
[ARSLAN] It was from him
that I first learned
about a country other than Pars.
It had never occurred to me
that ours was not
the only way of living.
He showed me that there
are many types of people
in the world and many ways
a kingdom can be run.
And after that, Narsus,
oh, he's one of
my close companions,
Narsus told me a great
many things about Pars.
And I came to see both the good
and the bad of our kingdom.
And there you are.
That is why I go to war.
To make Pars into a better
kingdom. If only a little.
You surprise me.
Surely deciding how Pars
is run isn't your job.
That's what the
king is there for.
But, helping your
country and her people,
well, you don't need
royal blood to do that.
[ÉTOILE] That's a noble
thing for anyone to do.
What is it?
[ARSLAN] Nothing.
I agree with you completely.
I've enjoyed our conversation.
It has been illuminating for me.
In fact, you remind me of that
Lusitanian boy I mentioned.
[ÉTOILE grunts]
Oh.
[ÉTOILE giggling]
Is that so?
[ARSLAN]
Eh. Uhh...
There're no soldiers here.
Hide in this wagon
for the night.
You can ride out with the
merchants when they depart.
It should be quite safe.
Thank you very much.
Well, then. Take care.
[ÉTOILE]
Uh.
Good luck if you do ride
into battle. I hope you live.
As do I.
[ÉTOILE] I thought he was
just a soft, spoiled boy.
I suppose even Pars
has her decent folk.
[ÉTOILE]
I never did ask his name.
I'll have to pray I don't
meet him on the battlefield.
[ARSLAN]
For Pars.
For Pars and for her people.
[ARSLAN] Daryun. Narsus.
Kishward. Lucian.
Is there something on
your mind Your Highness?
We're going to take
back our kingdom.
All of Pars will be ours again.
Of course. It will
be as you say.
[ARSLAN]
And once we have taken it back,
I will not yield the
throne to my cousin.
Based on bloodline alone,
he is likely better
suited to be king.
But I am the one who dreams of
making Pars a better country.
And I will see it done.
Whether or not
my blood is royal.
Your Highness.
Such conviction.
I am glad to hear it.
I will not waver.
I will need you all.
Can I count on your support?
You need not even ask.
I am at your side.
Indeed. That is true
of everyone at Peshawar.
We will fight to see that
your dream becomes reality.
Thank you all.
[NARRATOR]
Pars Era, the year 321. May.
Crown Prince Arslan
gathered his troops
and faced the prospect of
battle with renewed resolve.
The time for war
was almost upon him.
[NARRATOR]
In times of war,
friends may become enemies,
allies may turn on each other,
and sacrifices may
have to be made.
Next time: "A Song of Farewell."
And thus would the
boy become a king.