[ARSLAN] The foot soldiers will
be led by Rukham and Shagad,
the cavalry by Daryun, and
the flying column by Kishward.
To make this a decisive battle,
the cavalry must gain
entrance to the castle.
That cannot happen unless
we breach the castle walls.
And to do that, we must make
sure the enemy is occupied.
[NARSUS]
We'll have several options.
I have developed plans to
address a variety of situations.
The trickiest of those would be
if the enemy is able to make the
most of their superior numbers.
But my plans are
most thorough. Daryun?
Yes. I know what to do.
I'm counting on you.
Thank you, Highness.
The victory will be ours.
On that I give you my word.
I feel so frustratingly useless.
Once the battle begins,
there's nothing I can do.
At that point, it's in
everybody else's hands.
[NARSUS] Awaiting results
is a commander's duty.
You are the banner
around which we rally.
Standing tall at the rear.
Brave and valiant warriors
of Lusitania, hear me!
By decree of Emperor Innocentis,
I have been tasked with the
command of this coalition force.
Heed me well.
Today's battle takes place here,
at the Keep of Saint Emmanuelle.
Fight with all your strength.
Do that and victory
will be ours!
[HILMES] This earth is
the rightful inheritance
of those who follow
the Faith of Yaldabaoth.
The ignorant Parsians
do not understand that.
They have no right to this land.
Ours is the righteous cause!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS yelling]
[HILMES]
The Parsian devils would despoil
that which belongs to god's
faithful! Will we let them?
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS]
No, sir!
[HILMES] No! We will
destroy the heathens!
We are a hundred
thousand strong.
We outnumber the enemy.
I command you.
The man who thwarted Andragoras
and defeated Pars at Atropatene.
Follow me and I promise you,
we will triumph again today!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS yelling]
Battering rams.
Siege towers. Forward!
[SHAGAD]
Uh.
Is that? It is! Lord Sam!
How could he?
He turned traitor?
He was a man of
honor, a Marzban.
How could he have become
a pawn of the Lusitanians?
A report for you, sir.
The walls of the keep
still stand firm.
We have yet to find
any weakness.
Additionally, some of the men
seem to be apprehensive.
Because Lord Sam
sides with our foe?
[ELAM]
Yes.
He was a well-respected Marzban,
and it is said that no one knows
how to defend a fortress better
than he.
I cannot blame them
for their apprehension.
What shall we do?
We continue fighting.
We were already aware that Sam
is among my cousin's commanders.
This doesn't change
what we must do.
I chose this path and
I shall remain on it.
Sir, may I have a word?
Yes, Étoile, what is it?
My lord count,
considering the significance
of this great battle,
I would like to request a
position on the front lines.
I can't allow it. The risk
to you would be far too great.
War is full of risk!
We are fighting to spread the
teachings of the true faith.
As knights of Lusitania, it is
our duty to oppose the heathens.
I don't care what happens to me!
No danger is too great!
[BARCACION]
Mmm.
Spoken with the passion
and ignorance of youth.
I feel I should tell you
that whether or not you
grant me your permission,
I will go to join the battle.
I realize that this
is presumptuous,
and I do apologize.
But that is how strongly I feel
about fighting the heathens.
I hope you know that.
[ÉTOILE]
Why can he not understand?
I have the chance
to kill their prince,
and I must take it, though
it may mean dying myself.
This is so dull.
I wanted to fight in
the thick of the battle.
[FARANGIS chuckles]
I'm curious, Alfarid.
What is it?
You are of the Zot Clan,
is that correct?
Yes, I am.
Why, does that bother you?
No, of course it doesn't.
But as a nomadic people,
you don't recognize
the Parsian throne.
And yet, you have continued
to fight alongside us.
What of it?
Silver Mask killed
my father, you know.
And besides, I don't
mind helping the prince.
[FARANGIS] Because it's
what Lord Narsus wants?
[ALFARID]
Mh-hm.
That's just part of it, though.
I have a feeling about him.
I think Prince Arslan may
do something incredible.
[ALFARID] Narsus wouldn't
care about him so much
if he wasn't someone special.
You see it in him,
too, don't you?
I suppose so.
He would retake
the capital, restore it,
and reform the country.
Who could hope to accomplish
that at 14 years of age?
Maybe His Highness can.
When you're with him,
it's easy to believe it.
[FARANGIS]
He is fundamentally good.
If anyone can shape Pars into
a kingdom of worthy ideals,
it will be him.
[NARRATOR] The siege had been
in place for some hours.
The Parsians were beginning
to show signs of fatigue.
And then something
unexpected happened.
[PARSIAN SOLDIER E]
It's opening.
[PARSIAN SOLDIER F]
The gate is opening.
[PARSIAN SOLDIER G]
Don't ask, just charge it!
[ALL yelling]
Enough of your tedious siege.
Watch, Prince Hilmes!
I ride in your name.
When I return, it will
be with Arslan's head!
[JASWANT] Lord Daryun, the enemy
cavalry has sallied forth.
[DARYUN]
Yes.
For Prince Arslan and Pars!
Onward!
[PARSIAN CAVALRY yelling]
No cavalry can
best that of Pars!
[yelling]
[yells]
You are only useful to the men
you lead if you are still alive.
Be careful.
Heh. As if I need
advice from a foreigner.
The numbers are not on our side.
In a simple clash,
we're at a disadvantage.
I hope all proceeds as planned
with Kishward and his men.
I knew he would send someone.
Damn you, Sam.
Other Parsians?
[SAM] Use the aqueduct
to enter the Keep,
then open the gates from within.
That was the general
plan, was it not?
You send two simple
foot soldiers to take me?
If you want me dead,
you'll have to do better!
[SAM'S SOLDIER C]
Get him!
To Lord Kishward!
[yelling]
[KISHWARD]
Lower your sword!
You were once a proud
and loyal knight of Pars.
Why do you now obstruct Prince
Arslan's path to the throne?
I am now sworn to Prince Hilmes.
I fight for him as no one
did when he was a boy.
[KISHWARD] And do you know what
Prince Hilmes has done as a man?
He attacked his people
with an enemy army!
I know that!
[KISHWARD]
Then why?
I know right now he's consumed
with hatred and rage.
That will pass, however.
And when it does,
Pars will once again have a true
king seated upon her throne!
A throne he wanted so badly
he made his own people
suffer for it.
That man will never
be a true king!
[LUSITANIAN MESSENGER A]
In terms of raw numbers,
our cavalry clearly
has the upper hand.
Also, Lord Sam is seeing to
the defense of the aqueduct.
[HILMES] If there's no more
to report, you may go.
[LUSITANIAN MESSENGER A]
Yes, sir.
[HILMES] Damn Zandeh.
What a reckless fool.
Arslan, I have known years
of torment and humiliation.
It's your turn.
Whatever I must do,
I will make certain you
will suffer as I have.
Damn savages!
For god and his glory!
[LUSITANIAN CAVALRYMEN C]
After him!
Kill him, in the name of god!
Hell, you people don't even know
the name of your god, do you?
Looked like you could
use a little help.
Repent your sin!
Convert to the
Faith of Yaldabaoth!
You don't need to die!
I don't need your faith!
[BOTH yelling]
Kill the savage!
Damn fanatic!
Why can't you understand?
That boy. I know him.
[ÉTOILE]
What is he doing here?
Hold them off at all costs!
Our duty is to
protect the prince!
[ZANDEH]
Die!
Do not let him by!
Their main camp
is just ahead now!
There, I see it. Now charge!
[ZANDEH] Arslan! I'll have
your head for a trophy!
[LUSITANIAN CAVALRYMEN G]
There's nobody here.
What's going on?
[PARSIAN CAVALRYMAN K]
Fall back!
They ambushed us.
This camp was just a decoy.
[NARSUS]
Your Highness,
do you remember what I told
you shortly after we met?
About the first step
of any good strategy?
[ARSLAN]
Of course I do.
Control the gameplay.
Draw the enemy's focus where
you want it. Is that right?
[ZANDEH] We'll need to retreat
for a time and then regroup.
[DARYUN] I've not seen you
since our battle near Peshawar.
I've been waiting.
So, even a fall from a
cliff couldn't kill you.
You're a hardy bastard.
[DARYUN]
Surrender!
This time I will kill you!
[ZANDEH]
You're wasting your breath!
This is good.
I want you dead by my hand.
Today I will avenge my father!
Out of loyalty to
the rightful king,
my father suffered the
disgrace of bending the knee
to those Lusitanian dogs.
Then you killed him.
Before his treachery
could be explained.
But when Prince Hilmes
becomes King of Pars,
my father's name
will be cleared!
And everyone will know we
were the loyal ones all along!
[SAM]
The Twin-Blade General.
A knight feared
by our neighbors.
A commander famed for
holding our eastern border
against all threats.
I would not have
chosen you for an enemy.
And what of you?
The man trusted to safeguard
the Royal Capital.
This is not a fight I wish
to be having, either.
[SAM]
It cannot be helped.
The separate paths we've
chosen have led us here.
One of us will triumph.
Two kings cannot rule one
kingdom. It is that simple.
Aye, so it is.
[yells]
And the only thing that
men like you and I can do
is fight for that in
which we believe.
[SAM'S SOLDIER G]
Lord Sam!
Protect the commander.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER Q]
Here they are!
I won't be defeated!
My father dreamt of seeing
Prince Hilmes take the throne!
[DARYUN]
You know, Zandeh.
We're alike, you and I.
Your father, Kharlan, as well.
We are stubborn men
who can do nothing
but fight for the
master we believe in.
Do not speak my father's name!
He was a fellow commander.
We risked our lives together
on the same battlefields.
I know he was a knight
worthy of respect.
[growls]
To clear the name of my father.
To see Prince Hilmes
upon the throne.
For those reasons,
I will kill you!
[DARYUN]
I commend your dedication.
If not for the fact that
we serve different lords,
I suspect you and I
might've gotten along well.
[yelling]
[groans]
[DARYUN]
A sorcerer.
I'm afraid you and your people
must shed more blood
before we will be done with you.
[chuckles]
They're both gone.
It appears that they
successfully lured
the enemy to the fake camp.
Yeah. That should give
us the advantage.
[clattering]
[BOTH]
Huh?
The Lusitanian troops who
were lured into the ambush
have been demolished.
Good.
[NARSUS] We've been able to
whittle away the enemy's forces.
But the castle gate remains.
--[swords clanging]
--[PARSIAN GUARD A] Stop them!
What is that?
[PARSIAN GUARD B]
Don't let them through!
[NARSUS]
Elam, see to His Highness.
Lusitanian troops?
[ÉTOILE]
Where are you hiding? Arslan!
Your Highness!
[gasps]
Why're you here?
Why are you here?
You're not the one
I came to find.
Well, killing you would
be a waste of my time.
Where is the coward?
Where's Prince Arslan? Tell me!
Surrounded by soldiers.
[ÉTOILE]
You can't be.
You have found me.
I am Arslan.
[NARRATOR]
"Yashasuiin."
They charged, with
their spears lowered,
their swords raised,
and their horses' hooves
thundering across
the flagstones.
Next time:
"The Decisive Battle."
And thus would the
boy become a king.