[NARRATOR] Pars Era,
the year 320. December.
Arslan had finally arrived at
the border citadel of Peshawar.
Finding the Crown Prince
on the battlements unguarded,
Hilmes took the
opportunity to attack.
[ARSLAN grunting]
Your Highness!
If you kill him, Daryun,
the true bloodline of Pars's
royal family dies, too.
[NARRATOR] Veteran general
Bahman saved Arslan
from Hilmes's sword.
However, he pled for
the masked man's life,
and his dying words were
as sharp as any blade.
Amidst the chaos
came a startling report.
Sindhura, to the east,
had launched an invasion.
[RAJENDRA]
I will not be outshone
by First Prince Gadhevi.
His will not be
the name celebrated
throughout all of Sindhura.
That honor will be mine!
[KISHWARD] We are working
with rough estimates,
but we believe the Sindhuran
army numbers 50 thousand.
They have already crossed
the river at the border,
and are officially
on Parsian soil.
Excellent.
How much bad luck
is going to find us?
We have enough to
see to as it is.
[NARSUS]
Your Highness.
[ARSLAN]
Uh.
Oh, apologies.
If you aren't feeling
well, get some rest.
We can handle matters here.
I will keep you informed.
[ARSLAN]
Thank you.
I'm well enough, I assure you.
[BAHMAN]
If you kill him, Daryun,
the true bloodline of Pars's
royal family dies, too.
Everyone, on to business.
We will retake
the Royal Capital,
but before we can do that,
we must defend our border.
We will make a stand
against Sindhura.
[RAJENDRA]
Ah!
Feel how cold it is.
Frozen rain? It must be
what they call "snow."
[RAJENDRA'S ADJUTANT]
Pardon me, Prince Rajendra,
but are you certain
it was prudent
for us to launch this invasion?
[RAJENDRA]
Certainly I'm certain.
Matters within the borders of
Pars are in disarray just now.
This is a golden opportunity.
[RAJENDRA'S ADJUTANT]
Unfortunately,
matters within our own borders
are in disarray, as well.
For you to absent yourself from
the kingdom at such a grave time
given the health
of King Karikala.
You're worried about Gadhevi.
There is no need.
I am definitely not.
The First Prince? Hah!
He was born one measly month
earlier than I. One month!
What should a handful
of weeks matter
when I am clearly more capable
of ruling than he could ever be?
Your Highness!
Now.
Let us find that Parsian
prince and cut off his head.
That should prove
a worthy trophy.
[RAJENDRA laughing]
[DARYUN]
Your Highness.
All is ready.
Battle preparations
are now complete.
We shall be leaving.
[ARSLAN]
I see. But...
Something wrong?
Should I not come with you?
I know we decided
against it, but...
I feel like I would be
breaking faith with the men
if I stayed behind.
I'm their prince.
There must be
something I can do.
[NARSUS]
Your Highness.
You are now the
leader of an army.
There are tens of thousands
of men at your command.
There is no need for you
to take to the battlefield
for every engagement.
Are you sure?
[DARYUN] Please trust us to
command the men in your place.
I feel I can promise
a favorable outcome.
Yes, of course.
You have my trust.
Please do as you see fit.
[DARYUN]
That was it?
I assumed it was yesterday's
events that were on his mind.
[NARSUS]
Well, can we truly blame him
if he wishes to avoid
thinking about it?
He fears failing to ride
forth for every battle
would break faith with his men.
Hah.
That is not a sentiment
one often hears from a ruler.
Nobody could ever doubt
that he has a kind heart.
However, it takes more than
kindness to rule a kingdom.
Does it, though?
[DARYUN]
Hm?
[NARSUS] We follow him
because of the man he is.
Because he is just,
and hopeful, and kind.
There are worse things
that could happen to Pars
than to be ruled by a kind king.
I can't argue that.
Now, let's be off.
I made a promise to His
Highness, and I plan to keep it.
[SORCERER chuckles]
[SORCERER]
Unfortunate prince.
He seems to encounter one
obstacle after another.
One could almost pity him.
Are you certain leaving
now is the best course?
Daryun and Narsus
have left Arslan.
With his closest
advisors off at battle,
we have the perfect
chance to kill him.
I said we're returning
to Ecbatana.
[SORCERER chuckles]
Then return we shall.
About time for us to part ways.
We'll be going
ahead, as planned.
Good luck, though I
know you don't need it.
[DARYUN] Perhaps you could
answer a question for me.
[NARSUS]
And what is that?
[DARYUN] The invading army
numbers 50 thousand men.
We're riding to meet
them with ten thousand.
[NARSUS]
Yes.
We're attempting to defeat
an army five times our strength.
Is that not unorthodox?
Often, the unorthodox strategies
are the the best ones.
Think on it.
Remember what you
learned while in Serica.
I know you were taught
about the three factors
one must be mindful of in war.
What are they?
Terrain's advantage. Heaven's
time. People's harmony.
That is what this is about.
Those three factors.
With this invasion,
Sindhura ignores all three.
[RAJENDRA'S ADJUTANT]
Your Highness,
the hour is growing late.
Should we begin looking for
a place to make our camp?
No. We continue
over the mountains.
But, Highness,
our men and horses
are exhausted.
The cold is beginning
to take its toll.
All the more reason
to push on then.
The movement will
keep their blood warm.
We need only clear this pass
and we'll be at Peshawar's door!
Then we shall--
[SINDHURAN SOLDIERS yelling]
It's an attack!
[PESHAWAR SOLDIERS yelling]
The Parsians are attacking.
Fortunately, I expected
this. Forward!
[NARSUS]
Three factors.
Let us now consider
each of them.
Starting with time.
The Sindhurans are
from the south,
with its perpetual summer.
So how well will they fight
in snow-covered mountains
in mid-winter?
You think to invade my domain?
I'll send you back
where you came from.
If you live through the night!
Stand strong!
Let's teach these Parsian dogs
what true valor looks like!
Then we have terrain.
And so the trap closes.
They've got us
flanked. Fall back!
[NARSUS] We are intimately
familiar with the land of Pars,
but to the Sindhurans,
it is relatively unknown.
Now, begin the charge.
Yashasuiin!
Push them back!
You call yourselves
men of Sindhura?!
Trying to push back
by main force?
This general is
an arrogant one.
You thought you had us!
Your sneaky tactics won't make
my men turn tail and run!
[NARSUS]
Hmph. A confident man indeed,
to invade when both
time and terrain
are undoubtedly
against him.
However, there remains
our third factor.
The people.
We have them! Keep pushing!
Those shots came from behind.
There are more Parsians?
No. I think those
are Sindhurans.
It's true. Just look
at the banner.
[SINDHURAN SOLDIER P] Yes!
It's Prince Gadhevi's standard.
But what is the First
Prince doing here?
They could be here
as reinforcements--?
More arrow fire.
They aren't here to aid us.
[SINDHURAN SOLDIER Q]
Your Highness!
What's happening out there?
[SINDHURAN SOLDIER Q] It appears
to be Prince Gadhevi, sir.
He's come with an
army at his back,
and they're attacking our rear.
Impossible!
He shouldn't know I am here.
I did not make my
intentions known.
Perhaps not, but the First
Prince is treacherous.
I would not be surprised to
learn he had been spying on us.
Surely not.
Everyone, go around to the left!
Gadhevi's men are
closing in on us!
What're you doing? To the left!
Pushing out front will just
get us killed more quickly!
I'm pleased to see
the deception working.
Even given the new moon,
I doubt these soldiers would
normally be so easy to fool
as they've proved tonight.
Fortunately for us,
two Sindhuran princes are
fighting over succession
to the throne.
These soldiers carry the
uneasiness of that conflict
in their hearts.
Strike them in the right place,
and they will break
with little effort.
[DARYUN]
The third factor: The people.
[NARSUS] We have nearly
maneuvered them into place.
A few moments more.
Now! How can a smaller
force best a larger?
Ride with me and
have your answer!
[DARYUN]
Hiyah!
[SINDHURAN SOLDIERS yelling]
What is that? Do you hear it?
[RAJENDRA] The ground.
It's cracking! But how?
[RAJENDRA]
Run! Everyone!
Get away from here!
It's going to--
Yes, terribly sorry.
That's the trouble
with frozen lakes.
A nightmare.
This cannot truly be happening.
[NARSUS]
I have a message of some urgency
for Prince Rajendra.
Where is His Highness?
[RAJENDRA] The prince
fights beside his men.
What is your message?
This is him, the man we seek.
What?
I am afraid for you
the battle is over.
You'll be coming with us.
You will not survive
our next encounter!
[ALFARID]
You're a very pretty man.
But one move,
and I will kill you.
[RAJENDRA chuckles]
I can admit when
I've been beaten.
You have outwitted
me brilliantly.
[ARSLAN] You took him, Alfarid?
That was quite well done.
Me? I did nothing.
We succeeded thanks
to Lord Narsus's genius.
[ELAM]
Hmph.
[RAJENDRA] I'd heard the
Parsian prince was small,
but I thought the reports
were exaggerated.
Well, then,
what plans do you
have in store for me?
Will you make an example by
executing me in front of my men?
No, Prince Rajendra.
I'm Arslan, Crown
Prince of Pars.
And this is Peshawar Citadel.
I realize the means
was somewhat crude,
but I needed to invite you here,
as I wished to speak with you
in person about something.
[RAJENDRA]
Crude? I'll say.
In my country, an invitation
does not often involve
being tied up and hauled away.
Of course not.
You've my deepest apologies.
Perhaps now it will
be easier for us
to talk to one
another as equals.
Yes, as equals.
I am willing to hear
what you have to say.
You may find our hospitality
is somewhat limited,
being in the
borderlands as we are.
It will do.
That's quite good.
Borderlands or no,
this is delicious.
We don't have anything
like it in Sindhura.
Please. Be welcome, all.
Eat and drink your fill.
[ALL]
Hear, hear!
[NARSUS]
Well said, Your Highness!
[GIEVE]
I am famished!
[RAJENDRA]
Prince Arslan.
I had been told you
were still a child,
but your leadership
earlier was brilliant.
You outwitted me.
That is no small feat.
Alas, I cannot claim the
credit for our victory.
[ARSLAN] I was aided by
my friends, as I ever am.
Ah. You call them
friends, not subjects.
I find you a most
intriguing man.
Now, come. You must
drink as well.
I, uh, sure.
[FARANGIS]
If Your Highness doesn't mind,
I will keep our guest company.
Ah! Allow me!
Prince Rajendra, care
for some entertainment?
I believe a Minstrel's Song
would complement the wine
most perfectly.
No songs tonight.
I propose a drinking
contest, instead.
Wait, uh...
The two of you did me proud
on the battlefield today.
I'm only glad I could help.
Well, it was a simple mission.
I could've done it
alone just as easily.
You're the one we
could've done without,
but you always intrude
where you don't belong!
You're a fine one to
accuse me of being intrusive!
Now, run along!
Narsus and I are having
a private conversation.
[ALFARID, ELAM growling]
Can't you quit growling and make
an effort to like each other?
Oh, my head.
I can't.
A herd of water buffalo
is dancing in my head.
And singing, too, I think.
[RAJENDRA] Gods.
Someone I cannot out-drink?
Parsian women are not to be
taken lightly, it seems.
Oh, your cup looks empty.
Please, allow me to fill it.
It's full enough.
[ARSLAN]
Prince Rajendra.
Yes! Prince Arslan,
how may I be of service?
Shall we continue
our earlier discussion?
Certainly! I would
like nothing more.
Except.
I can't quite recall what
we were talkin' about.
I would like to enter
into an alliance.
[RAJENDRA]
Ah.
I'm listening.
My proposal is simple.
You're fighting to be recognized
as the Sindhuran heir.
I'd like to help you
achieve that goal.
And in exchange,
you would ask for my help
in your war with Lusitania.
Yes.
It is a fair deal,
all things considered.
[RAJENDRA chuckles]
How will you hold
up your end of it?
You're a prince
without a kingdom.
I fail to see what
you can do to help me.
What did you say--?
That's not important
at the moment.
Now, I hate to be
indelicate, but I do hope
that you haven't forgotten
your current situation.
That sounded very
much like a threat.
Harming me would be most unwise.
I warn you, my men would not
suffer such an insult lightly.
I would not do
something so barbaric.
Especially when there's no need.
Not when you consider
the information
we've already given Sindhura.
Which would be?
[NARSUS] Why, that Crown
Prince Arslan of Pars
and Prince Rajendra of Sindhura
have formed an alliance
based upon friendship and
respect for each other's' goals.
[RAJENDRA]
But I haven't said--
[NARSUS] And furthermore,
that the Prince,
eager to bring peace and order
to the Kingdom of Sindhura,
has begun a march upon the
Royal Capital of Uraiyur.
Bastards! I can't
return home now.
They'll kill me for a traitor!
Rajendra.
You were always going to
challenge First Prince Gadhevi.
We have done nothing to
truly change your plans.
All we did was slightly
accelerate their unfolding.
[RAJENDRA gasps]
It is not what I wish,
but I could use you to negotiate
with Prince Gadhevi, instead.
[laughing]
I am bested again. Pars has
a very clever prince.
Then we can expect
your cooperation?
Yes, you can.
Consider me your ally.
I shall aid you in the
defense of your kingdom.
[NARRATOR]
And so,
Arslan found his ever-shifting
fortunes changed once again.
Pars Era, the
year 320. December.
Leaving the defense of Peshawar
Citadel to Marzban Kishward,
Arslan joined his new ally,
accompanying Rajendra's
army as it began its march
toward Sindhura.
The path forward was uncertain.
Not knowing where it might lead,
the young prince had
to trust to fate.
[RAJENDRA] Well, Prince Arlsan,
what do you think of my men?
Are they not a sight to behold?
I'm sure they'll like you.
[laughing]
[DARYUN]
I don't like this.
Do you really think
we can trust that man?
[GADHEVI] I knew that my younger
brother was a fool, but this?
Allying himself with Pars?
Offering loyalty to some foreign
prince ahead of his own blood?
[MAHENDRA] It seems indisputable
proof that he has no intention
of acknowledging your
right to ascend the throne.
What do you wish to do?
What choice have we?
We'll destroy the
traitor Rajendra!
As the younger brother,
it is his duty to accept
my place as the heir.
Instead, he divides the kingdom!
[MAHENDRA]
It shall be as you wish it.
Indeed, I can bring
your brother to heel
more swiftly than you think.
Rajendra does not know it,
but I have already placed
one of my men in his ranks.
[NARRATOR]
Jaswant's piercing green eyes
shimmer with
intelligent ferocity.
Gieve's icy blue eyes shine with
mischief and reckless courage.
Next time: "The Black
Leopard of Sindhura."
And thus would the
boy become a king.