[SOLDIER A]
You want a clean death?
Tell us where the queen is!
[ATTENDANT A]
Mercy.
Sorry. What?
I can't quite make out
what you're saying.
Restore order! Clear
a path through here.
Make yourselves
presentable. His Majesty,
Innocentis the Seventh,
King of Lusitania has arrived!
[yawns]
[INNOCENTIS]
The stench!
[SOLDIER B] Kill everyone!
Grant no quarter!
[PRIEST A screams]
[SOLDIER A] The Queen has yet
to be found! Keep looking!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[SOLDIER C]
Any luck?
[SOLDIER D]
No sign of her yet.
[ARZHANG] Thus far, all
has gone according to plan.
Indeed. Pigs are
simple creatures.
Keep them fed and
they remain happy.
This victory will go
straight to their heads.
Damn Lusitanian savages.
[MONTFERRAT] I hear the
Man in the Silver Mask
captured Queen Tahamenay.
[BAUDOUIN] Oh? Well,
that's a point in his favor.
But what of his true motives?
Does he serve out of a genuine
interest in Lusitania's future?
Difficult to say. All I know
is that there's something
uncanny about his eyes.
I don't much care for that.
[door squeaks]
[BAUDOUIN]
Uh?
[MONTFERRAT]
Here she comes.
They didn't
exaggerate her beauty.
I hear her first betrothal
was to the Grand Vizier
of the Principality
of Badakhshan.
But his lord, Prince Keyumars,
reportedly stole her away.
[BAUDOUIN]
A lord taking the betrothed
of one of his advisors? But that
sort of thing just isn't done.
The Grand Vizier
took his own life.
Prince Keyumars fared
little better, however.
He leapt to his
death when Osroes,
the previous king
of Pars, invaded.
The story doesn't end there.
Osroes and his younger
brother Andragoras
fought over Tahamenay
and had a falling out.
Officially, Osroes
fell ill and died,
but it is whispered that
Andragoras actually had him
assassinated so he could take
both Tahamenay and the throne.
[BAUDOUIN] It sounds like
that woman brings misfortune
to every man who seeks to
possess her. What is she?
Some unearthly creature?
[MONTFERRAT] If so,
her sorcery will end today.
[yawns]
His Majesty will make no
allowances for a heathen,
however pretty.
The only question is what
sort of death she will face.
[INNOCENTIS]
Hm...
[MONTFERRAT]
Huh?
Oh, my!
[OFFICIALS gasping]
[OFFICER B] Prince Guiscard!
Has anybody seen the prince?
He is needed!
Prince Guiscard!
[GUISCARD] Such a racket.
What is the matter?
His Majesty. [groans] He's
demanding the impossible.
We don't know what
to do, Your Highness.
Take a breath, man.
What does he want?
Something ridiculous,
I have no doubt.
[OFFICER B] Will you not
prevail upon him to see sense?
[GUISCARD] I've many things
to see to at present.
All companies, check your
weapons and equipment.
There's no telling when
the Parsians will rally.
Well, what is it?
It's madness!
His Majesty insists that
Tahamenay become his queen!
[GUISCARD]
Huh?!
[OFFICER C]
Ah! The wealth of Pars
is even greater
than I had heard!
Yes, this is a most
impressive collection.
[GUISCARD]
Wait, Brother!
[INNOCENTIS] Oh? What
do you want now, Guiscard?
What's this... about
you marrying Tahamenay?
Yes, everyone seems
to be against it, though.
Find some way to persuade
them all, won't you?
[GUISCARD sighs]
Think it through.
Have you not heard about the
miserable fates met by other men
who were involved with her?
Would you be her next victim?
Of course I know
the stories.
But those other men were
all heathens. That's right.
They were unworthy of her.
And in His wisdom, perhaps
God was testing her, as well.
Wha...?
She will not know happiness
until she marries a practitioner
of the Faith of Yaldabaoth.
Such must be her true destiny!
[GUISCARD]
That's absurd.
[OFFICER D sighs]
[INNOCENTIS]
You men there!
It is God's divine insight that
has granted us this victory.
This treasure will be
offered up to Him.
It is not for the
likes of you to touch.
[OFFICER D]
Yes, Your Majesty!
This treasury and its
contents shall be placed
under Archpriest
Bodin's supervision.
What are you saying?!
It's our duty as faithful
followers of God
to show our devotion. [yawns]
I am so very tired. I must rest.
[GUISCARD]
Lord Brother!
[INNOCENTIS]
And bring me some sugar water.
[ATTENDANT A]
Yes, sire! Right away!
All of this will go to Bodin?
[OFFICER E grunts]
[GUISCARD]
Just the thought of my brother
siring a child
upon that heathen!
It turns my stomach!
[SILVER MASK] Don't concern
yourself. It won't happen.
Ah. You.
It is you who has led
Lusitania's army.
It is you who has
given the people
this sweet taste of victory.
You, and not your fool brother,
have the makings
of true greatness.
So worry not.
All of your subjects
know your true worth.
[GUISCARD exhales]
[SILVER MASK] However, the
time to act is not yet upon us.
For now, Your Highness,
you must endure.
[GUISCARD]
I understand.
I meant to tell you. Your
strategies were helpful indeed.
They certainly
aided our victory.
You honor me, Highness.
[GUISCARD]
However, that fog...
There are some
calling it uncanny.
Perhaps even the
work of a sorcerer.
Not sorcery, I assure you.
It was the grace of God.
[SOLDIER E]
Outta the way.
[MERCHANT A whimpering]
[SOLDIER F]
I'll take this.
Yes, sir. Of course!
[SOLDIERS laughing]
[ANIMAL KEEPER A]
Damn Lusitanian soldiers.
They have no respect
for anybody.
From what I hear,
they'll kill a man for so much
as lookin' at 'em sideways.
Hmph. Who can do
business like this?
Parsian soldiers? Impossible.
[ANIMAL KEEPER B] Oh. That
must be the traitor Kharlan
and his company.
The sneaky bastard who turned
his cloak at Atropatene.
[ÉTOILE]
Thank you.
Uh. Is that...?
Hey.
Sir!
How can we help you?
We don't have any
supplies to offer.
We run a show tent, you see.
[ÉTOILE]
No, that's not it.
You've been in the city for
a long time, haven't you?
Yeah.
[ÉTOILE] What do you
know of Lusitanian slaves?
Huh? Uh...
It was three years ago.
Some men were brought here
to become slaves. They were
soldiers from Lusitania.
[KHARLAN] How many times
did I warn you to be careful?
Useless bunch of fools!
We're sorry we failed you!
[KHARLAN grunts]
You're dismissed.
[MEN]
Yes, sir.
[SILVER MASK] Seems this
Narsus fellow led them around
by the noses. And yet
you go easy on them.
[KHARLAN] I blame myself
for their clumsiness.
You're a capable commander.
No oversights on
your part, I'm sure.
I shall continue to expect much
of you. Is that understood?
Yes, sir. I will go
to Prince Guiscard
and ask his permission
to muster my men.
He seems to think much of
himself for a dirty traitor.
He would've been defeated along
with the rest of his countrymen.
I have no idea what he's doing
in such a prominent post,
he hasn't even converted.
So much for bravery and loyalty.
Seems betraying your
friends is the way
to move up in this world.
[GENERALS laugh]
[ÉTOILE] Do you know
of any Lusitanian slaves?
They were in the city.
It would've been
about three years ago.
[MAN A]
Mm-mm.
[ÉTOILE ]
I'm looking for my friends.
Perhaps you know
something of them?
I failed.
I vowed to come back,
but I failed all of them.
[ÉTOILE] That boy I
took as my hostage.
He seemed like the son
of a prominent family.
I wonder if they
have many slaves.
[ÉTOILE gasps]
If I find him, he may know!
No. Such an idiot isn't likely
to have survived until now.
[ÉTOILE gasps]
Outta the way! Clear a path!
[TOWNSPERSON A]
Is there another battle?
[TOWNSPERSON B]
That's Lord Kharlan!
[TOWNSPERSON C]
He's no "lord" anymore!
[TOWNSPERSON A]
Shh!
[SOLDIER H]
You there! Girl!
Do you find soldiers
so fascinating?
Sorry, it's such a
grand procession.
I was wondering what it's for.
This?
They're heading out to look for
that prince who's on the run.
Oh, really? Have they found
out his location, then?
I don't know, but I bet they're
gonna do their best to find him.
They betrayed the prince and
his family after serving them
for years. Probably in their
interest for him to die.
You know much!
So, what about the rumors
of how King Andragoras
has gone missing?
They're true, as far
as we can tell.
Anyway, why don't you
just come with me?
We can talk in more
detail over here.
What are you doing,
sir? Let me go!
[SOLDIER H] Not to worry, girl.
Just talk, I promise.
Please! Don't hurt me, sir!
I converted to the
Faith of Yaldabaoth!
Oh, did you, now?
All the more reason for us to
get to know each other better.
Hey, stop!
[ÉTOILE grunts]
--Hey!
--[foot steps]
What are you doing?
Release that... woman.
Let me guess you're no
ordinary townsperson!
[ELAM] And I guess
you're no ordinary
Lusitanian dimwit, either.
I serve Count Barcacion.
He is a general in the
army, and I'm his squire!
I'm Étoile!
And what's your name?
[ELAM] I have no name that
I care to share with you,
Lusitanian dog!
Then you're a coward!
[ÉTOILE]
I've got you!
A man?
[ÉTOILE grunts]
[SLAVES murmur]
[ÉTOILE  groans]
[SLAVE A]
A Lusitanian soldier?
They're slaves.
Stay out of this!
[SLAVE B]
When?
[ÉTOILE gasps]
[SLAVE B] When are you
going to make us free men
like you promised?
[SLAVE A] We helped you! We
opened the gates from inside!
You promised to set us free
if we aided Lusitania!
[ÉTOILE]
Stay back!
I killed my master! I killed him
because I believed you people.
But nothing has
been done for me!
[SLAVE D] We'll starve to
death before much longer!
[ÉTOILE]
Stop!
--[SLAVE C] Hey!
--[SLAVES murmuring]
[ÉTOILE]
You--
[SLAVE D]
Are we free men or not?
[ELAM]
The Royal Capital
was completely under
Lusitanian control.
And my father?
[ELAM]
Whereabouts still unknown.
I asked all sorts of people,
but no one could say.
I see.
And Kharlan is on the move.
He's leading a column
of soldiers to capture
Your Highness.
I counted well over a
thousand cavalrymen.
What?! Doesn't that seem
a little excessive?
A thousand men
just to capture me?
He doesn't know our number,
so it's in his interest
to be cautious.
Lest you forget, you're
a walking, talking cause.
If we announced that you would
be at the head of an army.
we could rally together a force
that would stand
against Lusitania.
[ELAM]
And as you can imagine,
that would be pretty
inconvenient for them.
Yes, but how do you think
they intend to find me
when they haven't
managed it so far?
If I were in Kharlan's shoes,
and I wished to capture you
as quickly as possible, well,
I would find a village full of
your loyal subjects and burn it.
An entire village?
[NARSUS] That is one
tactic he could employ.
Burn the village, killing
all within, of course,
and announce his
deed to the world,
using it as a means to draw
Your Highness out of hiding.
He could then continue
in that vein,
burning village after village
until you finally
show your face.
[ARSLAN whimpers]
[NARSUS] Although, there
are other possibilities.
[ARSLAN]
Like what?
Surely he wouldn't
be so ruthless.
He is still a warrior!
A most honorable warrior,
selling out king and
country as he did.
[ARSLAN whimpers]
Very well. Though I doubt
you've a way to tell
which village he's
likely to attack.
I should be able to.
[ARSLAN]
How can you know?
Kharlan's cavalrymen
will lead the way for us.
All we should have to
do is follow them.
Is that what you wish,
Your Highness?
[ARSLAN] We leave immediately!
Saddle the horses!
[DARYUN]
Are you sure about this?
Kharlan is not
a simple man.
Forming up for all to see
and leaving the Royal
Capital in broad daylight?
[NARSUS] A trap to lure out
His Highness, you think?
That is a possibility.
If so, then why aren't
you stopping him?
[NARSUS] Am I to stop him from
proving himself a man of honor
and compassion, who
cares for his subjects?
Besides, Kharlan has
information we need.
Without it, we only
know half the story.
We're hoping to catch a
lion cub. Like it or not,
that may require us to
venture into the lion's den.
[DARYUN]
Ha. I see.
This was a little test you
designed for His Highness.
And what if he hadn't set
out to save the village?
Would you have deemed him
unfit to rule and left?
Why are you two chatting?
We must be off!
A village may be under
attack, even as we speak!
[GIEVE] Whoa, there!
Those are Lusitanian soldiers.
[GIEVE] It's always better to
avoid any unnecessary trouble.
[GIEVE]
Uh!
[GIEVE] Looks like they've been
raiding the local villages,
as I'd heard.
Ah, well. That's not
any concern of mine.
[GIEVE] What a woman! You
don't see many like that!
She's even more beautiful
than the queen,
and that's saying something.
Oh, no!
She's headed in the same
direction as those soldiers!
The brutes will
undoubtedly attack her.
Fortunately, I shall be
there to rescue her.
And naturally, she
will be most grateful
for my timely intervention.
She will want to find
some suitable way of
rewarding my heroism.
At least, I hope so.
Yes, surely she will!
It's decided, then!
I'm going after her!
[SOLDIER I]
Stop there.
Why's a woman traveling
this road alone?
[SOLDIER J] Answer his question,
wench, and be quick about it.
We're busy men.
[GIEVE] Oh, great Ashi,
Goddess of Fortune!
I must thank you for bestowing
upon me this most marvelous
of opportunities. I have ever
been your truest follower!
Come back here, you!
[SOLDIER I]
Uh...
[SOLDIER I groans]
[SOLDIER M]
She-- [grunts]
[SOLDIER O]
Quick, stop her-- Ah!
[GIEVE]
Hey, this isn't right.
How am I going to
put her in my debt
if she kills all the bastards?
Uh?!
Another...?
[GIEVE] So, they flee.
A wise choice.
Well, it seems that today
is your lucky day, madam.
If I, Gieve, had not just
happened to pass you by, you...
Hey, hold on.
What about my reward?
Madam, you're
forgetting something!
Wait, my lovely!
[GIEVE]
Uh...
Pardon, most exquisite beauty!
Are you addressing me, boy?
Not just a beauty,
but an exquisite one?
One doesn't find many women
who can be described as such.
[GIEVE] Your physical
beauty is enhanced
by your skill in
the arts of war.
I confess myself struck
dumb with admiration!
I am Gieve, my lady.
A humble traveling musician
with little to his name.
Yet I flatter myself that I
have a greater appreciation
for beauty than
any nobleman does.
I also happen to possess
some talent for verse
which I have employed to
compose a poem in your honor.
Her magnificent form, svelte
and straight as a cypress tree.
Her black hair. A piece
carved from the night sky.
Her bright eyes, which put
even emeralds to shame--
The night sky? Emeralds?
Your verse is sadly
lacking in originality.
Well, it is true that poetry
is not my greatest strength.
But I maintain that my
love for beauty and justice
is equal to that of
the great poets of old.
For that reason,
I was unable to stop myself from
rushing bravely to your rescue!
[FARANGIS]
My rescue? Bravely?
If it please you,
perhaps you would consider
favoring me with your name?
[FARANGIS]
My name is Farangis, minstrel.
I serve at the Temple of Mithra
in the Khuzestan region.
I am an emissary. I travel to
Ecbatana in that capacity.
Ah. Mithra! Yes.
My first loyalty is
to the Goddess Ashi.
But after her, it is to the
Divine Mithra that I turn next.
We share no ordinary
connection, lady Farangis!
We are fated to be--
I understand that the
capital has already fallen.
[GIEVE]
Uh.
I had not yet decided
where to journey next.
I was hesitant
to return home
and thought to
look for lodgings.
That was when I ran into
those Lusitanian dogs.
Their savagery is inhuman.
I don't know how much
more of it I can stomach.
[GIEVE] Yes. I've seen
that for myself.
They claim to serve their
god, but their hearts
seem to be empty of anything
like love or compassion.
Parsians are not blameless.
I hear some are reveling in the
chaos wrought by the invasion.
Even looting temples
of their riches.
Such acts disgust me. In fact I
find it particularly loathsome
to steal from
one's own people.
So, what's an emissary from
the temple doing way out here?
My sworn duty. I was sent as
both priestess and warrior
to find His Highness,
Prince Arslan.
[MALE VILLAGER A]
Please, have mercy!
[MALE VILLAGER B]
We know nothing!
I swear that's the truth!
[FEMALE VILLAGER A]
Why are soldiers of Pars
attacking their own people?
How can you do this?
[KHARLAN] Let them burn. You
heard me. The men only, for now.
If we knew anything,
we would tell you!
Please, you have to stop this!
You live only to
spread the word.
Any community that
gives shelter to Arslan
and his company will be
torched to the ground!
[MALE VILLAGERS scream]
[NARRATOR] In Kharlan's voice
there lies something too dark
and ruthless to be described
as simple derision.
Next time,
"The Treasonous Hero."
And thus would the
boy become a king.