[LUSITANIAN CAVALRY yelling]
Askriios!
Yashasuiin!
[PARS CAVALRY yelling]
[NARRATOR]
Pars Era, the year 317.
When their ally, Maryam, was
invaded by the Lusitanian Army,
Pars responded decisively.
Their king,
Andragoras the Third,
met the invaders with a
force 300 thousand strong
and crushed them.
They left a mountain of
Lusitanian corpses behind.
Now, come at me again!
[ARSLAN]
Very well!
[VAHRIZ]
Upper block! Center block!
Upper block! Lower block!
Upper block!
[ARSLAN] You beat me
quite handily, Vahriz.
You must show me that maneuver.
[VAHRIZ laughs]
Swinging a sword to and
fro is hardly a "maneuver."
Those were simply
fundamental sword strokes.
Although, without a sound
knowledge of the basics,
you cannot hope to master the
more complicated techniques.
Fundamental strokes
are important.
Hone them, Prince Arslan.
[ARSLAN]
You're a harsh teacher.
Why did you not
accompany my Lord Father
on his campaign against
the Lusitanians?
Because my duty is here
at this moment, my Prince.
Safeguarding this, the Royal
Capital of Ecbatana.
Lusitania is not
the only threat.
Kingdoms to the east
have set their eyes
upon our beloved city, as well.
We mustn't let our guard down.
It sounds as if you're
terribly busy, General.
Perhaps forgoing my daily sword
lessons would free you up a bit.
[VAHRIZ] How can you hope
to become a proper king
with such little ambition?
You must take your
training seriously.
[VAHRIZ] Even simply mastering
the fundamentals of the sword
will show in your
bearing and presentation.
You have yet to fight your
maiden battle, my Prince.
If you hope to survive it,
you must train with the
sword often in preparation.
Everything you say is true.
I know that, but even so.
[VAHRIZ]
If you know,
then try to carry yourself
as a swordsman would.
The soldiers expect it.
[TAHAMENAY]
Loyal soldiers.
Your allegiance to the Kingdom
of Pars does you credit.
You have our thanks.
[ARSLAN]
Oh, uh.
[PARS SOLDIER B]
Her Majesty the Queen!
Prince Arslan! Salute!
[ARSLAN]
Heh.
Lady Mother!
Yes, Arslan? What do you need?
Nothing, really.
I only wanted to apologize
for my tardiness.
[TAHAMENAY]
Not at all.
I understand that you are busy
with daily sword practice.
Yes! I hope to be a fine
king like my lord father,
but I know that
will take hard work.
And I'm not making
the swiftest progress.
Vahriz always says--
Good.
[gasps]
What does it even mean
to be a fine king?
I fear I don't know.
It's Azrael! And Sorush!
Ah! If they've returned,
it can mean only one thing.
To me!
[LADY-IN-WAITING B]
Your Highness!
Welcome home.
It's good to see you.
[KISHWARD]
Your Highness.
And Lord Vahriz. I trust
I find you both well?
[ARSLAN] You're back!
Greetings, Kishward.
[KISHWARD] So, they
greet Your Highness first
instead of their master,
do they? The cheeky bastards.
[VAHRIZ chuckles]
You must teach them
some respect.
On the contrary, my lord, it's
not that they don't respect me.
Rather, it is a sign of the deep
affection that they harbor
for His Highness here.
Birds and beasts are far
better judges of character
than we humans
can ever hope to be.
They've read what dwells
within His Highness's heart,
and know that it
is pure and good.
You've returned
from the campaign.
All went as expected?
[KISHWARD]
Yes, sir.
Our losses in the field
were negligible.
The Lusitanians are sorry they
ever thought of invading Maryam.
We defeated them soundly
and at little cost.
[KISHWARD] His Majesty
will be returning shortly.
[RESIDENTS cheering]
[RESIDENT A]
Look, it's Lord Marzban Kharlan!
--[RESIDENT E] He's so gallant!
--[RESIDENT B] Lord Kharlan!
[RESIDENT C] And there's Lord
Marzban Kubard and his wine jug.
[RESIDENT D]
An inseparable pair.
[RESIDENT F] Honestly,
is that man ever sober?
You see that scar? The one
over his left eye there?
That's from when Lord
Kubard fought a dragon.
You're makin' that up!
He's not my favorite, though.
Lord Twin-Blade
General Kishward is!
You just wait. I'm joinin'
the cavalry when I grow up.
I'll protect the king
like the Lords Marzban.
That's stupid! The king
killed a lion when he was 13.
He doesn't need the likes
of you to look after him.
Yeah. You're probably right.
[RESIDENT G]
Who're the prisoners?
[RESIDENT E]
They're Lusitanian soldiers.
They go to war in the name
of that god of theirs, right?
The Cult of Yaldabaoth,
I think it is.
[RESIDENT G]
I hear they kill babes in arms
if their parents
are non-believers.
[RESIDENT H]
Barbarians!
[RESIDENT I]
Look there! He's just a lad.
Lusitania's so desperate,
it sends children into war?
[RESIDENT I]
Oh, the poor little dear.
What kind of parents
would allow that?
Go on, Highness.
[ARSLAN] Lord Father,
I'm glad to see you safe.
I worried for you, off
fighting in distant lands--
Defeat was unthinkable.
[ANDRAGORAS]
Report, Vahriz.
Tell me how the
kingdom has fared.
[VAHRIZ]
Majesty.
What do you think
about Prince Arslan?
Eh. He doesn't seem very brave.
[BOY B] Then maybe we'll
protect him instead of the king.
[BOY A]
Maybe!
[RESIDENT J]
A little on the young side.
I'm lookin' for one that
can do a man's work.
Forgive me, my Prince, but such
quarters are hardly suitable
for one of your station.
[ARSLAN]
Hm. Why ever not?
It's a perfect opportunity
to speak with Lusitanians.
If you require a slave,
we can easily send a messenger.
That's not it. I wish
to learn from them myself.
Of their culture, their homes.
There's just so
much I don't know.
[UNDERLING A] Filthy bastard!
Get back and do as you're told.
Everything all right here?
[SLAVER A]
Prince Arslan.
This is a surprise.
Whatever brings you
to such wretched quarters?
[ARSLAN] Are these
the men from Lusitania?
[SLAVER A]
Yes, Highness.
[ARSLAN]
Good afternoon.
If you don't mind, I'd like
to ask you some questions.
It shouldn't take long.
[SLAVE growling]
[ARSLAN yelps]
[UNDERLING A]
Get your hands off the prince!
Are you hurt, Your Highness?
I'm fine.
[UNDERLING A]
You're slaves now, ya got that?
You wanna live, you do what
you're told, when you're told.
He's just a kid.
This'll be easy.
Uh. I don't really know
if we should do this.
What, you're backing down now?
I thought you were
gonna be a cavalryman.
They don't take cowards.
We'll give him a thrashing
he won't forget.
That oughta teach him!
[BOYS gasp]
Hey, you!
[ATTENDANT A]
They're such a barbaric people.
This was a bad idea,
Your Highness.
If something were
to happen to you--
[ARSLAN]
I'm not a total fool, you know.
I shall be more careful.
[thud]
[BOY A yells]
[BOY B]
H-Help me!
My Prince, please remain here.
[BOY SOLDIER yelling]
[gasps]
[ARSLAN]
Hey! Stop that!
[BOY SOLDIER]
Stay back!
One more step
and I'll kill him!
Now, don't be hasty.
Would you maybe consider
just letting him go?
Yeah, why not? I'll let him go.
[ARSLAN] Young sir!
I think you misunderstood me!
What happened here?
One of my slaves
is on the loose!
--[PARS SOLDIER C] What?
--He just ran off!
That much I could
handle, but you see--
[BOYS crying]
He took the prince!
His Highness protected us!
What?
Find him, now!
[PARS SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
Boy, lots of
commotion today, huh?
[PARS SOLDIER E]
The west side!
[PARS SOLDIER F]
Get the vermin!
[DARYUN]
What in the world is going on?
[MAN A]
Lord Daryun!
[DARYUN]
What is it?
It's Prince Arslan, my lord!
[PARS SOLDIER D]
There he goes! Get him!
[PARS SOLDIER G]
There he is!
[PARS SOLDIER I]
Halt!
[PARS SOLDIER G]
Let him go.
[PARS SOLDIER I]
We've got you cornered.
You stay back!
Come any closer and I'll
slit his scrawny neck!
[PARS SOLDIERS gasp]
If you wanna live,
you better run fast.
[ARSLAN]
Huh?
[ARSLAN yelps]
[ARSLAN screaming]
[PARS SOLDIER I]
Prince!
[BOY SOLDIER]
Come on!
[PARS SOLDIER G]
Down there!
[PARS SOLDIER H]
I see 'em!
[PARS SOLDIER G]
Let's move!
--[BOY SOLDIER A] Run faster!
--[PARS SOLDIER H] C'mon!
Hey, wait. Was
that Prince Arslan?
[PARS SOLDIER G]
Damn it!
[PARS SOLDIER H]
We're in trouble.
If the palace hears about
this, it'll be our necks.
You! Which way did they go? Huh?
All right! Let's go!
[PARS SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
Someone's practically
sending an army after us.
What are you? Some
big-shot nobleman's son?
Looks like taking
you hostage instead
was the best decision
I made today.
[ANIMAL KEEPERS]
Huh?
Are you injured?
No, I'm fine. Thanks to you.
What on earth is this
long-necked demon creature?
You haven't seen one before?
They're often part
of traveling shows.
And these strange things
are native to your land?
Not sure.
You don't know?
You do live here, right?
[ARSLAN]
Ah!
[BOY SOLDIER]
Come on!
Such wealth!
Everywhere you look, people
are buying and selling things.
[ARSLAN] We are at the heart
of the Continental Highway.
In Pars, we lead lives
of culture and prosperity.
No man goes hungry here.
[ARSLAN]
So, where're we going now?
[BOY SOLDIER]
Wherever I tell you!
You sure have a
lot of slaves here.
Well, of course we do.
That's further evidence
of our kingdom's prosperity.
Why would you want to run away?
[BOY SOLDIER]
Uh!
It isn't all that much work,
and you'd never want
for food or shelter.
Not a bad life,
once you accept it.
Certainly better
than what you're--
Yeah, rich boy?
And what would you know
about my life, huh?
Very little, but if children
like you are being sent to war.
Who are you calling "child"?
I'm 11 years old!
Only 11? That's my age,
as well. You truly are a child!
Well, not in my kingdom!
I'm a Lusitanian soldier!
A warrior!
Devoted to the
God of Yaldabaoth,
and pledged to rid
this world of heathens!
Why is it you so despise
those who don't believe?
[BOY SOLDIER]
Our god is just.
He treats all people as equals.
But the same cannot
be said for your kind.
Just look at your
system of slavery.
It's cruel and barbaric!
Our god won't tolerate
something so inhumane.
[ARSLAN]
Huh?
Hear me, heathen.
All men are equal!
Except for people like you
who do not follow
our god's teachings.
You can be treated differently
and killed as we see fit!
[ARSLAN]
Sure, that's logical.
What was that?
--Nothing at all.
--[rumbling]
[BOY SOLDIER]
Uh.
[ARSLAN]
Uh?
[PARS SOLDIER K]
There he is!
[ARSLAN]
Here we go again.
All people should just accept
the will of the
God of Yaldabaoth.
Then there'd be no fighting
to begin with! It's simple!
I bet you don't know
anything about other kingdoms.
I bet you don't
even give a damn!
Too rich for that
kind of learning!
[PARS SOLDIER K]
Comin' through.
[LADY-IN-WAITING C] What do
you suppose is happening?
There's quite a
commotion down below.
[ANDRAGORAS]
Tahamenay, my wife.
I have returned.
[ANDRAGORAS]
I trust you've been well
since I've been off on campaign?
[TAHAMENAY] Can you not spare
a moment to remove your armor?
[ANDRAGORAS]
I brought gifts.
I know how you
enjoy fine silks--
That is most kind.
Leave them there, please,
I will see to them.
[ANDRAGORAS]
I shall return.
[PARS SOLDIER L] To the
west rampart! Get the rat!
Your Highness!
[BOY SOLDIER]
Run faster!
Back off!
You wanna keep him
in one piece, don't you?
Looks like we're
done running, rich boy.
Just surrender yourself.
There's no need for you to die.
[ARSLAN]
What?
[BOTH yelp]
[DARYUN]
Your Highness!
[ARSLAN screams]
Something fall?
[ARSLAN]
Daryun!
[TRAVELER B]
That was a long fall.
There's another.
[TRAVELER C]
Are you all right, young man?
[TRAVELER A]
Come now, up we go. There.
Hey! He's stealing that horse!
[TRAVELER A]
Get back here, horse thief!
Stop him!
[ARSLAN]
Daryun!
[TRAVELER C]
Wait, lad!
Don't shoot him! Wait!
[DARYUN] I'm here, Prince
Arslan. Are you injured?
[ARSLAN]
Daryun.
I'm unharmed.
I don't understand
why you stopped me
from shooting the little rat.
Me neither.
Heh.
[DARYUN]
Uh.
Very well, Your Highness.
Should anyone ask, we'll
say the sun was in my eyes.
What an adventure. Thank
goodness he's all right.
Captured by an escaped slave
and dragged throughout the city?
[MAN E]
It's a wonder he survived.
[MAN D] What was he doing
down there in the first place?
You must be more careful
with that royal neck of yours.
Had things gone differently, you
might've had it broken today.
You make it sound
worse than it was.
[PARS SOLDIER M]
Your Royal Highness!
We have captured the miscreants
whose actions led to
the prisoner's escape.
[BOYS grunt]
Your Highness!
We're sorry for what we did!
[MOTHER A] Please forgive
the little ones, Highness!
We beg you!
[MOTHER B]
Punish us instead!
[FATHER A] They're only
boys, Your Highness!
They didn't mean
anything by it, I swear!
Fools! His Highness's
life was threatened
because of what those three did.
You think they'll
be shown mercy--?
Yes. Release them now, please.
Do what? Don't be ridi--
Oh! Your Highness.
No harm came to anyone.
See to it.
[PARS SOLDIER K]
Yes, sir!
[GROUP] Thank you
very much, Your Highness!
I swear! When I'm old enough,
I'll join the cavalry
and serve Your Highness
with my whole heart until I die!
[BOY C]
Uh-huh!
[BOY B]
Same for me!
[BOY SOLDIER]
Comrades. Stay alive.
I'll come back
for you, I swear it.
[DARYUN]
I'll get you a horse.
[ARSLAN]
Some of what that boy said
was quite different from
what I've been taught.
I wonder what else the
palace tutors have left out.
I shall have to hear what the
other captive Lusitanians say.
[UNDERLING B] Hurry up,
they're starting to stink!
[ARSLAN]
Oh, no!
[PARS SOLDIER N]
Uh. My Prince!
[ARSLAN]
Hey!
[SLAVER A]
Faster, you louts!
Y-Your Highness!
What is this?
Forgive me, Highness. This is
no sight for royal eyes.
You killed all the captives?
[SLAVER A]
They...
...were unmanageable and
needed to be put down.
Lusitanians are no different
than wild animals, Prince.
You either tame them,
or kill them. That simple.
[SLAVER A]
Hurry. Load them up.
[ARSLAN]
They didn't have to die.
If they'd simply accepted
their lot as slaves,
no harm would've come to them.
[ARSLAN]
Why did they fight?
Your Highness.
Someday, the Kingdom of Pars
will be yours to rule.
When that happens,
there's a friend of mine
you might appoint.
You have a great many questions,
and I think he may be the
one to answer some of them.
[ARSLAN]
Oh? Who is this man?
[DARYUN]
Uh.
Sorry, Highness.
Simply thinking aloud.
Please, forget I said anything.
He'd never be a proper advisor.
Well. Now you have
piqued my interest.
No matter, I suppose.
My Lord Father's reign is likely
to continue for decades still.
I cannot yet even begin to
imagine ascending to the throne.
As long as my father is king,
Pars will remain strong.
So it seems it will be a while
before I meet this
friend of yours.
[DARYUN]
Indeed.
[ARSLAN chukles]
[NARRATOR]
However, in three short years,
the Royal Capital of Ecbatana
would be shrouded
in fire and blood.
Despite their attempts
to stem the tide,
Maryam would fall to
the Lusitanian invaders,
and that onslaught would finally
reach the Parsian border.
Pars Era, the year 320.
Autumn.
Crown Prince Arslan is about
to embark on his maiden battle.
He is 14 years old.
[NARRATOR]
The wind changes course.
The fog rolls in.
To Arslan, it seems
an inauspicious omen.
Next time:
"Age Fourteen, Maiden Battle."
And thus would
the boy become a king.