I would add my
voice to Daryun's.
I'd feel more confident
with both of you by my side.
I hate to refuse
you a second time.
Well, then, accept my offer.
I hope you don't think your
loyalty would go unrewarded.
I would compensate
you handsomely.
Once I have driven
off the Lusitanians
and succeeded my father
on the throne of Pars,
I promise you this.
I will appoint you,
Lord Narsus, Court Painter!
[NARSUS]
Uh.
[NARSUS chuckling]
I find I like you, Highness.
What say you?
From his lips, Daryun.
His Highness has
magnanimity of spirit!
Your Highness, you would truly
appoint Narsus Court Painter?
Doing that would leave
an indelible stain
upon Parsian culture!
It seems a worthy trade.
At least, I know what
I would choose
between Narsus painting
a living portrait of me
versus a Lusitanian artist
painting my death portrait.
But do consider.
King Andragoras finds the
very mention of my name
to be offensive.
This offer of yours will surely
cause him great displeasure.
Are you willing to
accept that, Highness?
Without question.
[NARSUS]
Very well.
I pledge you my sword and
what wisdom I may have.
I am at your command,
Prince Arslan.
I accept your service gladly.
And now that that's settled,
we need to depart in haste.
We must return to the Royal
Capital as soon as possible.
Yes. We'll just pack our
bags and ready the horses.
Yes, sir.
Ah, one thing, Elam.
Sir?
I believe I'll have a friend
in the port town of Gilan
look after you while I'm away.
Uh. My lord, why?
The man I have in mind
owns a merchant ship.
So if the Lusitanian
incursion continues,
you can take to the sea.
Even crossing to foreign
lands, should need be.
You should at least
be safe there.
I don't wanna go to sea!
I owe you a greater debt than
I could ever hope to repay
even were I to spend a
lifetime in your service.
I beg you to let me accompany
you on this journey, my lord.
[NARSUS]
It will be dangerous,
and you're hardly
more than a child.
I cannot ask you to risk
your life in such a way.
[ELAM] I am more of an
adult than you, my lord.
[NARSUS gasps]
Sorry, but the fact is,
you're incapable of doing
anything for yourself!
There's the laundry,
and cleaning,
acquiring art supplies.
[DARYUN] You have to admit,
the boy has a point.
Quiet, you.
Help me convince him.
He'll listen to you.
[ARSLAN]
Narsus, I make another request.
Your Highness.
[ARSLAN]
Allow Elam to come.
If we were to leave him behind,
who else could prepare
such delicious meals?
We might starve out there.
It's settled, then.
Elam, I look forward
to having you along.
And I look forward to coming.
I'll see to the bags
and horses now.
[ARSLAN]
Excuse me.
I must get my things
in order, as well.
Let me help. Is there
some task I can perform?
As I've explained before,
Your Highness,
you need not trouble yourself.
[ARSLAN]
But I'm happy to.
Surely there's something
you could use...
As you can imagine, His
Highness had little chance
to make friends
his own age at Court.
[DARYUN]
He and Elam are of an age.
It would be nice if they
could form a friendship.
[ARSLAN]
All right, if you're sure.
[NARRATOR]
Pars Era, the year 320. Autumn.
When Prince Arslan made good
his escape from the battlefield,
he had only the warrior
Daryun at his back.
To his company,
he now adds the strategist
Narsus and his page, Elam.
The four set out upon a journey
that will be nothing
if not perilous.
[KHARLAN'S MAN B]
What? The horses!
Where are they?
[KHARLAN'S MAN A]
Damn that man!
Well, they won't
escape so easily.
We already have men in place
along the mountain path
ready to intercept them.
The poor fools. They've headed
down the mountain on foot.
[NARSUS]
How unfortunate for them.
There is very little likelihood
they will reach
bottom by day's end.
It would be tragic if they came
across a bear or pack of wolves.
[NARSUS]
Your Highness.
There is something
weighing on you.
I can't stop thinking
about Ecbatana.
Your frustration
is understandable,
but have patience.
Were we to descend
the mountain immediately,
a fight with Kharlan
would be unavoidable.
Better to remain in this cave
for a bit and wait them out.
We can use the time to think of
a way to turn their scrutiny
to our advantage.
How do we do that?
We can't leave until
they stop looking for us.
So we draw their focus
where we want it to go.
Controlling the game play, the
first step in any good strategy.
No matter your military prowess,
the goal of a sound plan
is to secure victory
without exhausting
your strength.
[ARSLAN]
Daryun used his strength.
He broke through a
whole army to get to me.
And there is no
denying his valor.
But warriors like Daryun
are one in a thousand.
If the commander of an
army hopes to succeed,
when planning for battle he
must use his weakest soldier
as his standard.
This holds doubly true
for the monarch of a kingdom,
who must devise his plans
so that even his least competent
commander is used to advantage.
[DARYUN]
Hmph.
What's funny?
Nothing at all. Do continue.
If he puts too great an emphasis
on strength over strategy,
should that strength
then fail, the war is lost.
You were there at Atropatene.
You know how disastrous
such a situation can be.
[NARSUS] King Andragoras
had never experienced
the sting of defeat.
Because his army was so strong,
he had no interest in politics.
Relying instead upon battle
to resolve all conflict.
If you would be his
successor in that,
I beg of you to stop
wasting both of our time
and tell me now.
Because I say to you, I would
not serve such a king,
not even as Court Painter.
I take your words to heart.
And as for you. Should we
come upon Kharlan,
do not kill him.
We need information. There's
more to this than we know.
I'm well aware.
[ARSLAN]
What kind of information?
I cannot yet guess
at the specifics,
which makes me fear
the truth is unthinkable.
[KHARLAN] There were
circumstances, Highness.
Poor, pitiable prince.
Truth of it is, you've
done nothing wrong.
No, you've done
nothing wrong,
and yet, you must
die here today.
[ARSLAN]
Something truly remarkable.
[AZRAEL squawking]
[ALL]
Huh?
That's Azrael.
Why are you here?
I sent you to accompany
Prince Arslan in his battle.
[SOLDIER C]
Lord Kishward!
I've been looking all over, sir!
[KISHWARD]
What's the matter?
[BAHMAN]
Kishward!
[KISHWARD]
What is it, Lord Bahman?
What's happened?
A mounted courier has just
arrived from Atropatene.
What news then from
the battlefield?
[BAHMAN] Our army was
slaughtered on the fields.
And after the battle, King
Andragoras went missing!
[BAHMAN] The Lusitanian
Army is closing in
on the walls of Ecbatana.
The Royal Capital is threatened!
[RESIDENTS whispering]
[RESIDENT A] We're surrounded
by Lusitanian soldiers?
[RESIDENT B]
What happened at Atropatene?
[RESIDENT C]
Surely our army wasn't defeated.
[RESIDENT D] With King
Andragoras commanding? Never.
[RESIDENT E] But they say the
enemy's surrounding the capital.
[RESIDENT F]
Probably a lie.
[RESIDENT J]
Then where is the king?
[RESIDENT G]
What's happening?
Are we going to die?
[MALE RESIDENT H] The walls
of Ecbatana are impregnable.
They'll never fall.
[PARSIAN SOLDIER A]
What's that?
[BOTH gasp]
Those bastards! Look!
[SAM]
Their captive.
It's Lord Shapur.
[PARSIAN SOLDIER D]
Impossible!
[PARSIAN SOLDIER E] They've
taken one of the Marzban!
Hear me, heathens!
All among you who know
not the grace of god!
Consider me a holy emissary.
I am Grand Inquisitor
Archpriest Bodin.
I bring the Word of the
One God, God of Yaldabaoth.
Listen to me well!
Using the body of this
heathen as our medium,
we shall convey
to you god's will.
[BODIN]
How?
We will begin by cutting off
one toe from his left foot.
Then we'll cut off
another, and another.
When we're done with the left,
we'll move on to the right.
After that, his hands.
[chuckling]
Minute by excruciating
minute, we will show you
what befalls those foolish
enough to defy god!
[BODIN laughing, LUSITANIAN
SOLDIERS cheering]
Filthy savage!
Only a coward would
do something so barbaric!
[PARSIAN SOLDIER H]
You animals worship an evil god!
[PARSIAN SOLDIER I]
Don't you touch Lord Shapur!
[chuckles]
[PARSIAN SOLDIER J]
Stop it!
This creature is an apostle of
evil who seeks to deny god!
Those like him are
more beast than man!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS yelling]
There can be no mercy
for any heathen!
[SHAPUR]
I've had enough of this.
[BODIN]
Huh?
I can't listen to any more
of the blatant hypocrisy
that spews from your mouth.
Kill me and have done.
I would sooner go to
the deepest pit of hell
than to any heaven
your god has to offer me.
And from there,
I will happily watch
as your kingdom is
destroyed from within,
brought low in the end
by your own cruelty.
Though you deserve far worse.
[BODIN]
Why you sinful cur!
You heathen scum!
You cursed beast!
You enemy of god!
[BODIN]
Do you have more to say?
[SHAPUR grunting]
You on the walls of Ecbatana!
Pierce me now with an arrow!
It's too late to save my life!
Don't give them the
satisfaction of torturing me!
I would die with honor!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER A]
Enough!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER B]
No arrow will reach you here.
We'll try, Lord Shapur!
You heard him! Start shooting!
[PARSIAN ARCHER B]
I'm aiming for the priest!
[PARSIAN SOLDIER M]
Savages!
The fools. We are well
out of arrow range here.
[BODIN] By all means!
Keep wasting those arrows!
[yelling]
[laughing]
[SHAPUR exhales]
It's not safe, Lord Archpriest.
Please stand back.
[BODIN] Was that shot
really fired from the wall?
Who fired that?
Bring him to me now!
It shouldn't be possible.
Not from that far.
Hey, look up there!
[TAHAMENAY]
I want that man brought to me.
[LADY-IN-WAITING C] The one who
fired the killing shot, my lady?
[TAHAMENAY]
We must grant him a boon.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS yelling]
Fire at will, men!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER D]
Forward!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER E]
Kill the filthy heathens!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER F]
Before this day is done,
we'll teach the blind fools
to fear the wrath of god!
A message for your god.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER H]
Slaughter the heathens
and make an offering
of their city!
Give these devils the
deaths they deserve!
Will you tell us
your name, archer?
[ARCHER]
If it pleases my Lady Queen.
I am called Gieve, and
I am a traveling musician.
[LADY-IN-WAITING A gasps]
[GIEVE]
I play the oud.
I am also a flautist, a singer,
a poet, and a dancer.
In addition to my
talents as a performer,
I must admit I wield
the bow, sword, and spear
better than your
average soldier.
You have demonstrated your skill
with a bow for all to see.
I thank you for
saving loyal Shapur
from further suffering
at Lusitanian hands.
I am not to be charged with
his murder, then, Your Majesty?
[LADY-IN-WAITING A] I beg your
forgiveness for interrupting,
my lady, but that man
is a base charlatan!
Explain this accusation.
You claimed to be royalty from
the Principality of Sistan,
traveling abroad as part
of your warrior training.
Don't deny it!
You told me that
story just last night!
I don't deny it.
And now you tell the
queen you're a musician!
Which means you lied
about being a prince!
T'was not a lie, but a dream.
A lovely dream I invited
you to share with me
for one exquisite night.
[PARSIAN SOLDIER R]
He's got a smooth tongue on him,
doesn't he?
[GIEVE] Dreams are such
precious, beautiful things.
It is a shame that
they must fade and die
with the harsh light of day.
Had you but accepted
it for what it was,
the dream could've
become a memory,
growing ever sweeter
as time passed
and lending depth and
richness to your life.
I will say I find myself
eternally confounded
by how easily moved women are
upon hearing the word "prince."
It seems to me a great weakness.
But when woman after woman
dreams of a prince in disguise--
And now you've demonstrated
your eloquence for us as well.
Your list of skills
is truly impressive.
Perhaps you would be so kind
as to display your talent
as a minstrel next?
Well.
[GIEVE]
Even as we speak,
the heroes of Ecbatana
stand strong on the city walls,
defending the Royal Capital.
For them, I offer this tale of
the Heroic Deeds of Kaykhusraw.
[GIEVE] Upon the desolate
plains of Mazangran,
Kaykhusraw's royal
standard proudly rippled.
Evil Zah-hak's army fled,
scattering in confused fright,
as a flock of sheep flees the
rolling boom of spring thunder.
They fled Kaykhusraw
and his sword, Rukhnabad,
which, forged from
a piece of the sun,
could cleave even steel.
They fled Kaykhusraw
and his horse Rakh-shna,
who, possessed
of invisible wings,
was truly a steed
worthy of the Jahangir.
Just as there is only
one sun in the heavens,
so is there only one
Shah upon the earth.
The hero with
no equal, Kaykhusraw.
With sun-forged sword and winged
steed, who will him succeed?
[CROWD applauding, murmuring]
Excellence deserves reward.
One hundred pieces for
your deed with the bow,
and another hundred
for your music.
I award you 200
gold pieces in total.
[GIEVE]
What, is that all?
For that performance, I was
expecting at least 500.
I have already deducted
a sum for the crime
of having misrepresented
yourself to my lady-in-waiting.
Majesty.
[NARSUS] Given Ecbatana's
distance from Atropatene,
the Lusitanian army has
most likely already launched
a full-scale attack on the city.
Now, the gates of the
Royal Capital are sturdy.
They will not be brought down
with flaming arrows
or battering rams.
However, there is no such
thing as an impregnable wall.
No matter how sturdy, a wall
can always be breached.
[ARSLAN]
I see.
You're saying the gate
could be opened from within.
Yes.
[ARSLAN]
Surely not.
How could such a
thing even be done?
Quite easily.
[gasps]
[NARSUS] If I were
leading the Lusitanians,
do you know what I would do?
I wouldn't force the gates.
I'd open them with words
rather than arrows or swords.
[ARSLAN]
What do you mean?
If I wish to open the gates
of the city from within,
I need only
assistance from within.
But there's nobody
inside Ecbatana
who would aid the
Lusitanian army.
[ARSLAN]
Uh.
Wait.
There may be some who would.
A great many.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER J]
Hear us, Parsian slaves!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS]
All men are equal!
You deserve to be free!
How long will you bow your heads
to those who chain
and misuse you?
The time has come to rise up
against your masters!
[PARSIAN SOLDIER S] What tactic
are those bastards trying now?
What's the yelling for?
Who knows?
I don't understand the way
savages think, do you?
[SAM]
Very clever.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS]
We speak the divine truth!
Under the God of Yaldabaoth,
the one and only god,
all men are equal.
Come to the aid
of Lusitania now.
You will be granted
the rights of a free man.
And riches beyond
your imagining.
Claim your freedom now!
Overthrow your
Parsian oppressors!
Fight the oppressors?
Claim our freedom?
Rise up against Pars?
They can be breached.
By the slaves within.
[NARRATOR] Though his methods
may be brutal and bloody,
the man in the silver
mask does not doubt
the righteousness of his cause.
Next time: "The Royal
Capital Burns ~Part Two~."
And thus would the
boy become a king.