The slaves may be
Lusitania's best weapon.
They could open the city gates.
All the Lusitanians
would have to do
is give them a reason
to fight against Pars.
They could promise them freedom,
or some kind of reward.
If they felt that freedom
was within their grasp,
I'm sure some among
the slaves would rebel.
The slaves in Ecbatana outnumber
the members of the ruling class
by a good margin.
If they do fight.
[NARSUS] Yes, I came to
the same conclusion.
If enough slaves were to rise
against their masters,
even impregnable Ecbatana
is unlikely to last for long.
Then what're we doing?!
We need to get back
there with all haste!
That's exactly what
we must not do.
There are only four
of us, Your Highness.
What can we possibly hope
to do to save Ecbatana?
It's too late to
avert this disaster.
If your father had
freed the slaves,
things would be different now.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS] Listen
to our words, Parsian slaves!
Seize your freedom!
All men are equal in god's eyes.
The time has come to rise
up against your masters!
Overthrow your
Parsian oppressors!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS yelling]
[PARSIAN SOLDIER A]
Lord Marzban Garshasph!
Down there.
[GARSHASPH gasps]
[GARSHASPH]
Damn those Lusitanian beasts.
There's Marzban Manuchurh
and Marzban Khayr.
[GARSHASPH]
No. Even Lord Eran Vahriz.
[TAHAMENAY]
All of them? His Majesty?
[SAM]
No, my lady.
From what we saw, his head
was not among those exposed.
[LADY-IN-WAITING D]
My Lady Queen.
Thank you, men. You did
well to tell me this.
That will be all for now.
[BOTH]
Majesty.
[SAM]
Am I alone,
or do you find it odd that she
didn't ask after Prince Arslan?
[GARSHASPH] It only shows
how troubled she must be
by the news.
We must act.
I still believe we should open
the gates and launch an attack.
What else is our
cavalry good for?
Patience, friend.
We should wait for
reinforcements
to arrive from Peshawar.
Then we can attack
on both fronts.
We'll suffer fewer losses
and put an end to the siege.
I don't like it.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS]
All men are equal!
You deserve to be free!
The time has come to rise
up against your masters!
All men are equal
in the eyes of god!
Fight for the dignity
all men deserve!
Throw off the shackles
of captivity!
[GARSHASPH]
Damn rabble!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS] You do
not have to remain slaves!
Fight for Lusitania...
[GARSHASPH] Clear out! Don't
listen to the enemy's drivel.
Garshasp! What do you
think you're doing?
We mustn't use force with them.
[grunts]
It is best to take
decisive action. Always.
[SAM]
Listen.
We must remain firm with them.
Who knows what trouble
these cattle might cause
given the chance.
[SAM]
Wait a while longer.
When the reinforcements arrive--
And when will that be, Sam?
They must first hear of our
defeat, then muster more troops.
Even assuming they march day and
night, how long till they come?
[MESSENGER]
My lords, come quickly!
The slaves are rebelling!
We must hurry! They've already
set fire to the Great Temple!
Uh. What?
[MESSENGER]
Worse than that,
they're trying to open
the western gates!
[GARSHASPH] They mean to
invite the Lusitanian Army in!
[SAM] The discontent
among the slave population
runs even deeper
than I had imagined.
[SLAVE A]
Open the gates!
[SLAVES]
Freedom! Freedom will be ours!
Guard the gates with your lives!
They must remain closed!
[GARSHASPH]
Ungrateful bastards! Step aside!
[SLAVES gasping]
Keep well away from this gate.
Any man who approaches will
be killed without a question.
[SAM]
Stop this!
Does killing unarmed
slaves make you proud?
[GARSHASPH]
I don't see any slaves here.
I see rebels.
Who have nothing but
sticks to fight with?
In their hearts they
are holding swords.
[grunts]
[SAM]
Look at them, Garshasph.
You killed ten rebels,
but you did nothing
to help the city.
Because now that
those ten have fallen,
a thousand more will rise
up to take their place.
[RESIDENT A]
Stay clear of the north gate!
Another group of
slaves is revolting!
What the hell are
they thinking?
Are the lazy brutes so
afraid of honest labor?
We should keep 'em in cages
with the rest of the livestock.
We could lock them up,
but no work would get done.
They're little better
than rabid dogs.
--[thud]
--[RESIDENT E yells]
[SAM]
Your Majesty.
Force will no longer be adequate
to keep the slave
revolt in check.
[TAHAMENAY]
But how is that possible?
The slaves should not
even have proper weapons.
They may not be as well
armed as the soldiers,
but they've grown
too numerous to fight.
If we want to put a stop
to this rebellion,
we must try a
different approach.
To that end, I would ask that
you issue a proclamation
granting the slaves
a modest sum,
and guaranteeing
better treatment.
How can I do such a thing?
It would shake the
foundations of our society!
The enemy is using those very
foundations against us, my lady!
We must act soon
or all will be lost!
I shall give it
careful thought.
[grunts]
I am most grateful.
[GIEVE]
Things seem to be going
from bad to worse in
a hurry around here.
I think, perhaps,
I ought to take my leave
before much longer.
[knocking]
[VOICE A]
Master Gieve.
Grand Vizier Lord Husrab
would like to see you.
[HUSRAB]
From what I've seen, young man,
I believe your wit is as sharp
as your skill with a bow.
Would you agree?
[GIEVE] That's something I've
been told time and again
since I was a child, Your
Excellency. I suspect it's true.
Ah, is that so?
Then I've a task for
that razor wit of yours.
Might you be willing
to assist me?
[GIEVE] I believe I detect the
clink of swords and armor
behind that curtain.
How very annoying.
[GIEVE sighs]
What say you?
I will accept on
a few conditions.
That the cause is just,
the reward large,
and the chance of success good.
As for the cause,
I trust the continued
survival of Pars
will be reason enough for you.
And the reward will be generous.
Now, listen closely. Here is
what I'm asking of you.
Using a secret passage,
you are to escort the Lady
Queen to a safe place
outside the palace.
[GIEVE]
You may want to watch your step.
It is rather slippery.
[GIEVE]
No king in residence,
and now the queen
is leaving, too.
Some Royal Capital.
The one million
people of Ecbatana,
abandoned by the people
meant to lead them.
Poor, forsaken Pars.
Surely this country
deserves a more worthy ruler.
[DARYUN] How long do you
intend for us to remain here?
I don't know. Perhaps we should
make for Ecbatana soon.
[NARSUS] Must I lecture you
on strategy as well, then?
No matter how spectacular
a fighter you may be,
one man on a horse cannot
win against an entire army.
If we could join up with the
men inside the city, maybe--
[NARSUS]
Let it go, Daryun.
Together, the slaves
and the Lusitanians
number several hundred thousand.
With only the soldiers
left within the walls,
we simply have too few.
Would you knowingly expose
His Highness to such danger?
[DARYUN]
Uh.
Consider this.
While we cannot win
against a whole army,
we can surely bring
down one commander.
Just explain what
you're getting at.
It's a question of
choosing opponents.
Forget the Lusitanian
Army for now.
We need Kharlan.
At the moment,
he is no doubt fully occupied
with the siege of Ecbatana.
But once that is over,
he is certain to come
after Prince Arslan,
and with relatively few men.
[DARYUN]
How can you know that?
He was an officer
in the Parsian Army;
he's unlikely to have
yet earned much trust
among the Lusitanians.
Fear not, our time
to fight will come.
But it will come when
Kharlan makes his move
apart from the rest of the army.
By capturing him,
we will not only diminish
the enemy's strength.
We will learn why
he turned traitor.
And that is information
we most certainly need.
Wouldn't you agree?
[DARYUN] So we just have
to sit here quietly
and wait for Kharlan
to make his move?
[NARSUS] Controlling your
emotions isn't your strong suit,
I know.
I'm back. Would you
like my report?
[NARSUS]
By all means, report away.
[ELAM] They don't seem
to be getting anywhere,
from what I can tell.
Their search for us
is haphazard at best.
I don't think we're in any great
danger of being found.
Then Kharlan has yet
to leave Ecbatana,
which means we stay
put a while longer.
[GIEVE]
You must be getting tired.
Perhaps we should rest awhile.
[GIEVE]
Don't want to work you too hard.
Just pretending to be the queen
must be an arduous enough task
without me adding to it.
[FAKE TAHAMENAY gasps]
[FAKE TAHAMENAY]
How did you know I'm not her?
[GIEVE]
By the scent of you.
Your skin gives off
a different aroma
than the Queen's noble flesh.
Even if you're using
the same perfume.
You're playing
the part of decoy.
Drawing any lingering attention
while the real queen escapes.
That is the idea, isn't it?
Such an attitude is
typical of the aristocracy.
They expect others
not only to serve them
but to sacrifice their lives
for the good of the nobility.
It works well for them.
[FAKE TAHAMENAY] I won't listen
to you disparage the queen so.
[GIEVE]
She's got you snowed.
[FAKE TAHAMENAY]
Whatever the Lady Queen
or the Lord Grand Vizier
may be planning,
my sole concern
is to fulfill my duty.
[GIEVE]
Are you just well trained,
or are you truly so servile?
[FAKE TAHAMENAY]
Consider your point made.
Now, will you continue
as my escort or not?
I accepted this job
when I thought
I was escorting the queen.
Not a lady-in-waiting poorly
disguised as the queen.
Whoa.
Ha. Now, wait.
From what I can see, you
are reasonably attractive,
so I wouldn't be opposed to
delivering you to your final--
--[FAKE TAHAMENAY grunts]
--[GIEVE groans]
[GIEVE]
Hey, hold on.
You shouldn't go
off on your own.
[gasps]
[SILVER MASK chuckles]
[SILVER MASK]
My, what have we here?
I never thought
I would happen upon
the esteemed Lady Queen of
Pars in a place such as this.
You've saved me the
trouble of looking for you.
It appears that you and
Andragoras are better matched
than I had imagined.
One abandoned his men
to flee the battlefield.
The other abandoned her city
to hide away underground.
What's become
of the stoic dignity
of those who sit on the throne?
[FAKE TAHAMENAY]
Who are you? What do you want?
SILVER MASK]
Who am I?
Why, I am the man who would
bring true justice to Pars.
[gasps]
[FAKE TAHAMENAY]
Lord Kharlan?
What're you
doing here? With him?
[SILVER MASK]
Lord Kharlan did you call him?
You are not the queen at all!
[FAKE TAHAMENAY whimpering]
[SILVER MASK] I dispose of
those for whom I have no use.
[gasps]
[SILVER MASK] The only person
you have to blame is yourself.
You chose the wrong master.
[FAKE TAHAMENAY choking]
--[crunch]
--[splash]
[SILVER MASK]
Let's go.
Before the night is out,
we will have thrown the palace
into confusion from within.
With any luck,
the real queen will still
be waiting inside its walls.
[GIEVE]
Just a moment.
I don't know who you
are beneath that mask,
but you just murdered
a beautiful woman.
There's no telling what sort of
reward she might've granted me,
had she lived.
Why not remove your mask?
Show me your face.
But maybe that is your face?
Does mercury run through
your veins instead of blood,
changing your very flesh?
Are you going to be all right?
[SILVER MASK]
I am fine.
I leave swatting this pesky fly
to you. We shall continue ahead.
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[GIEVE]
Farewell, then, Silver Mask.
It's been fun.
Till we meet again.
[SOLDIER A yells]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Well, that's one point for me.
[SOLDIER E]
Come on! Together!
[SOLDIER A]
I've got you!
[GIEVE]
Well, that's done.
What to do now?
Should I go back
and warn the queen
of the danger that's
heading her way?
Or should I get myself
safely out of this mess?
[GIEVE]
I know.
I'll take advantage
of the chaos
and see what sort of
treasure I can make off with.
While I'm at it, if there
are any beauties around,
I shall make off
with them, as well.
[GIEVE] Don't have
any use for this, friend.
I, however, can find many
noble purposes for it.
You have my sincere thanks.
[water splashing]
[GIEVE]
Sounds like quite a few men.
I think I had best be on my way.
[SAM]
The east gate needs men!
Reassign some from
the north gate!
--[PARSIAN SOLDIER D] Yes, sir!
--[PARSIAN SOLDIER E] Lord Sam!
[PARSIAN SOLDIER E] No matter
how many we bring down,
more come to replace them!
[SAM] They are attacking
even more fiercely
--than usual tonight.
--[rumbling]
[SAM]
Uh.
The palace is ablaze.
How can this have happened?
You have the command here!
[PARSIAN SOLDIER F]
Sir!
Where did the
bastards come from?
[SLAVE E]
What's goin' on?
[SLAVE F]
I wish I could tell.
Get back!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER B] You all
know what to do now, don't you?
Rise against your masters! Go!
[SLAVES yelling]
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER C]
Savor your freedom!
A gift from the
God of Yaldabaoth!
Damn!
They must've come through the
aqueducts! But how did they--?
[SAM]
Kharlan!
So it is true!
You deserted Pars
for Lusitania.
--[SAM] Why did you do it?
--[swords clanging]
[KHARLAN]
I have good reason!
You wouldn't understand.
[SAM] You're right. I could
never understand betrayal!
[KHARLAN]
Just surrender, Sam.
If you convert to the
Faith of Yaldabaoth,
I will guarantee your
life and your rank.
An offer of protection
from a cur like you?
I'd rather die!
Sam! Come back!
[SAM grunts]
[SAM]
Who.. are... you?
--[SOLDIERS yellsl]
--[SAM groans]
[PARSIAN SOLDIER I]
Lord Garshasp! Look!
The gate, sir. It's opening!
[GARSHASPH]
What? Impossible!
[SLAVE C]
Turn it faster!
[GARSHASPH]
It's the slaves.
Guard the west gate
with your lives!
[PARSIAN SOLDIER J]
No use! It's opening!
[GARSHASPH]
To the gate, men!
Keep as many from
entering as you can!
[NARRATOR] Pars Era,
the year 320. November.
The Royal Capital fell to
the invading Lusitanians.
With the fate of King
Andragoras still unknown,
the kingdom was plunged
into chaos and confusion.
[NARRATOR]
One soul moved in secret
behind a curtain of
fear and hysteria.
One soul gazed upon the cruel
fires that lit the night sky.
And one soul raced through
the now-hostile land,
determined to do her duty.
[NARRATOR] The board was laid
out. The pieces were assembled.
It was time to begin the game.
[yells]
[NARRATOR]
Surely death by execution
could be the only way to
deal with a heathen queen.
But one among the faithful
may have a very
different idea in mind.
Next time: "The Beauties
and the Beasts."
And thus would the
boy become a king.