[ÉTOILE]
Why are you here?
You're not the one
I came to find.
Well, killing you would
be a waste of my time.
Where is the coward?
Where's Prince Arslan? Tell me!
You have found me.
I am Arslan.
Damn.
You made a fool of me!
Well, for that
I'll make you pay!
[ARSLAN]
Elam!
Your Highness, please
step back from him.
[NARSUS]
Elam.
I am impressed you were
able to find us here,
but it's over.
What's happening?
Your assassination
attempt has failed.
You need not die.
You can surrender yourself.
[growls]
You filthy heathens!
Commander, we can't
hold them off!
Please, withdraw, sir!
I stay!
But think of the count!
Who will watch his back if
you are not there to, sir?
[ALFARID]
You bastards!
You're not getting away!
[NARSUS]
Alfarid!
We have the castle
completely surrounded.
To have gotten past our men,
they must've used
a hidden passage.
Understood!
[ARSLAN]
Elam!
Hold on. Someone
come tend to him!
[NARSUS]
It looks grave.
[ELAM] I'm sorry, my Lord.
Of all times to be injured.
No need to speak.
Although, I know I did not train
you to be so rash or reckless.
I made the right
decision, though.
Indeed.
You must rest.
Your Highness, try not to
look so frightened and sad.
You're in the midst of trying
to win a war and claim a throne.
You must remain
strong at all times.
You're right. Thank you, Elam.
[ÉTOILE]
Curse him. Curse him!
That sneaky coward's been
playing me for a fool all along.
How many opportunities
did I have to kill him?
I let him get away!
[ALFARID] A secret passage
tucked in among the cliffs.
How handy.
Now, time to turn
the enemy on his head.
Like a true Zot fighter.
[DARYUN]
Your Highness!
I've returned.
Is it true the camp
came under attack?
[ARSLAN]
It did.
But as you see, I'm unharmed.
However, Elam took a nasty
sword cut that was meant for me.
Gods. Poor Elam.
[NARSUS] A hasty incursion
made in pursuit of glory.
Common enough among
boy commanders.
Boy commander?
[ARSLAN]
You might remember him.
It was the Lusitanian
who took me hostage.
The one we let escape.
[DARYUN]
Him.
[ARSLAN]
His gaze was so intense.
Challenging. Even more
so now than before.
[DARYUN]
Your Highness.
That's it. I've decided.
I'm going to ride out.
[DARYUN]
You mean to ride into battle?
[ARSLAN] If we are evenly
matched in this fight,
perhaps I can tip the
scales in our favor.
It's what a king would do
to help inspire his men.
I know I'm not
my father's equal,
but those who have given
themselves to my cause
deserve to see me fight.
[PARSIAN MESSENGER A]
Lord Narsus!
A report from Mistress Alfarid!
Let's have it.
She says she'll open the gate
with the coming of the dawn.
Good, thank you.
Victory today hinges upon us.
We must not falter.
Not long ago, I fought
my first battle,
and I fled that day in defeat.
I despaired of ever
seeing Pars whole again.
But thanks to my loyal advisors
and stalwart friends,
here I stand today.
And now I have hope.
I believe that, together,
we can retake Ecbatana.
The country will be ours,
and I will become your king!
[PARSIAN SOLDIERS yelling]
[ARSLAN] The castle's
defenses are strong,
but even as I speak,
a company of our troops
is entering through
a hidden passage.
With the dawn, they
will breach the gate!
[ARSLAN] Hear me, gods of Pars,
and spirits of our fallen!
Lend us your aid!
Fight beside us in
the coming battle!
Yashasuiin!
[PARSIAN SOLDIERS yelling]
Here they come.
Let's go!
Charge!
Move quickly!
I want that gate open
before sunrise's, got it?
Where did they all come from?
There aren't many. Stay calm!
Call men from below, and--
Support our men! Keep firing!
[SAM]
A surprise attack on the gate?
Get men up there quickly!
The gate must hold!
Yes, sir!
[SAM]
If they can get the gate open,
the Keep is as good as theirs.
[PARSIAN SOLDIER A]
Lord Zaravant, look!
[PARSIAN MESSENGER B]
The gate has begun to open!
Wait, something's wrong,
the gate shouldn't be opening.
Get some more men down here!
We'll form a wall just insi--
For Pars and the Crown Prince!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Just a little longer!
We almost have it!
Push them back!
If we let them in any further--
Deploy companies to
the left and right.
Storm the fortress gate and
subdue enemy opposition!
Everyone else, continue forward.
Push through and
bring down the castle!
[ALFARID]
Narsus!
[BARCACION]
The enemy has come.
Shields up! Don't let
them in any further!
[NARSUS]
Daryun! Kishward! Into the fray!
[DARYUN, KISHWARD]
Right!
[BOTH yelling]
To the rear!
We're blocked in?
Protect His Highness!
[yelling]
That looks like...
[ARSLAN]
Kubard!
Greetings, Prince Arslan.
You've grown into
a gallant fighter.
I'm doubly glad I
rushed to join you.
Now, off with you.
You claim the throne of
Pars as rightfully yours?
I, for one, am eager
to see you prove it.
[DARYUN]
We are through!
Your Highness,
we must push forward.
Jaswant, you're up.
Yes, sir!
When this is over you owe me
a jug of wine. Fight well.
Almost there.
Sam's leading them!
Now, charge!
Shall we press forward?
Yes!
Narsus!
[NARSUS]
Keep going!
Stop for long and the enemy
soldiers will surround you!
Very well, friend. Fight well!
My fate depends
on the rest of you.
[WOMEN screaming]
God of Yaldabaoth have mercy.
[HILMES] In the end, these men
are on loan from Guiscard.
I care not how greatly
their numbers are reduced.
Indeed, this will likely be
a heavy loss for Lusitania.
Come, spawn of Andragoras.
It will be so sweet
to see you humiliated
before your troops
and loyal servants.
Stay here. I'll push on.
I can't. I've come too far.
Beyond these men,
my lord cousin awaits.
What're you doing?!
I am under the protection
of Divine Mithra.
I have no fear of being struck.
Not by the arrows of heretics.
[FARANGIS]
Your Highness,
that divine protection
falls upon you as well.
The barbaric Lusitanians must
be made to change their ways.
You are the one who can do that.
You are the only one.
[FARANGIS]
Please go,
but know that wherever
Your Highness may be,
whatever enemy you fight,
you will have my bow.
Now's our chance, Highness.
[ARSLAN]
Right.
[BARCACION]
Are you Prince Arslan?
But you are still little
more than a child.
[BOTH yelling]
I expected to see the Knight
in Black at your side.
[ARSLAN] We've not met since
that night at Peshawar.
How fare you, cousin?
I find it repugnant to hear
myself named your cousin,
but I'm glad you came.
Tell me, cousin.
Have you suffered terribly
on your journey here?
Has it been difficult
for you? Well, has it?
Rantings of a madman.
Pay him no heed.
Actually, I wish to hear
what he has to say.
Your Highness?
Do you think whatever
hardships you've faced
can hold a candle to my own?
Don't make me laugh!
I will see you slain
here in battle today.
Your very memory
will be disgraced!
But that's not enough!
You still won't know the
depths of the humiliation
I have suffered.
Nothing can appease
the rage I feel for you!
Is that why you bear him
this senseless grudge?
Because he hasn't "suffered"
as much as you have?
[HILMES]
Senseless grudge?
You don't understand the pain
of wounds that never heal!
[ARSLAN]
Yes, I do.
But you are not the only
one who has been injured.
All of Pars has... gravely.
Lord cousin,
you claim you're of the
royal blood of this kingdom.
What say you?
Will you lend me your
aid in protecting her?
And if I did that, would
you yield me the throne?
I have a responsibility
to my people.
Their goals are mine.
I must fight for them.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER Q]
Lord Sam, we can't hold.
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
Retreat!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER Q]
My love for Pars
is strong and true.
I care deeply for her people.
I will be her king!
You will never rule!
[DARYUN]
Your Highness.
I will carry your words
engraved upon my heart forever.
Daryun.
I've never been more
proud to serve you.
[HILMES]
How can you worship him so?
His blood is impure.
Yet you serve him
like a loyal dog.
You disgrace the
knights of Pars.
If I am a dog, let me
show you my fangs!
Daryun!
[SOLDIER yelling]
You are Count Barcacion?
I am.
Many men in my service
have died today.
War is a hard business indeed.
I agree.
It would be best for us
to end this quickly.
[BARCACION]
Mm.
I think perhaps you would
be a kind and just king.
The Faith of Yaldabaoth
denies all others.
So it has been for centuries.
Is it possible there could
be some other way?
I don't know.
[HILMES]
It is a shame, Mardan fu Mardan!
If only you'd given your
strength to serve me.
You could be on
the side of right!
Impossible!
I can serve none
but Prince Arslan!
Your gaze infuriates me.
Such unwavering conviction!
How can I prove it to you?
That mine is the side of right.
I will not kill you yet.
Not until you know
in your heart of hearts
that you have been
well and truly beaten.
Otherwise, it will
be meaningless.
I must destroy you utterly.
Nothing short of that
will appease my rage!
Damn you--!
Can't... breathe.
[ÉTOILE]
Where is Count Barcacion?
[BARCACION]
The Keep will fall.
It seems unstoppable now.
Surrender. Let the rest
of your men live.
[KISHWARD]
Do not kill needlessly!
We are the citizens
of a civilized country!
And there will be no pillaging,
do you understand?
No! Stop this!
Count, please,
the fighting is over!
Make them stop!
You are a kindhearted prince.
This is not something
that can be stopped.
Faith is an unstoppable thing.
[ARSLAN]
No!
[BARCACION] This is the
only power left to me.
To choose to join
my people and my god.
[ARSLAN] Why? I've given
you the chance to live!
Why must you choose death?!
[thud]
[ÉTOILE]
You!
[ARSLAN]
Get back!
He's dead. Count
Barcacion is dead.
You killed him.
[NARRATOR] Tears spilled
unchecked from Estelle's eyes.
After tragedy,
after countless deaths,
there came a birth.
Next time, "The Highway
of Blood and Sweat."
And thus would the
boy become a king.