[swords clanging]
[yells]
Disarmed again.
I continue to make
little progress.
You judge yourself
too harshly, Highness.
Your sword-work has most
definitely improved.
You mustn't be discouraged.
So you always tell me,
but frankly I find it
difficult to believe.
I suppose battle is the
only real test, though.
Huh. You have the
right of it there.
But, given the state of things,
I can't say I expect any attack
on our fair kingdom
in the near future.
If it's battle
you're looking for,
you may yet have a
long wait ahead of you.
[VAHRIZ chuckles]
[CIVIL SERVANT]
Pardon me, Lord Er Vahriz.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[VAHRIZ]
What is it?
[CIVIL SERVANT] A message
from King Andragoras, sir.
[VAHRIZ]
What does His Majesty write?
It can't be!
What message does
my father send?
It would seem I spoke too soon.
It's war.
[NARRATOR]
Pars Era, the year 320. Autumn.
The Lusitanian Army invaded and
conquered the Kingdom of Maryam.
It then set its sights
on Maryam's ally,
the Kingdom of Pars.
In response, Andragoras the
Third gathered his army
and led them himself to
the Fields of Atropatene,
where he intended to intercept
the invading Lusitanians.
Crown Prince Arslan is about
to embark on his maiden battle.
He is 14 years old.
[KHARLAN]
Are you terribly nervous
about the coming battle,
Your Highness?
Nervous?
This is your maiden
battle, after all.
No one would blame you.
Right.
Take heart. We're
sure to triumph.
The king has taken
to the field himself,
and everyone knows
his martial prowess.
Supreme General Vahriz
is here, as well.
And consider the
other captains,
Shapur, Kubard, Mankchurh,
Khayr, Khurp, Khshaeta,
and Daryun.
We eight Marzbs each
command ten thousand horse,
add to that the king's
personal guard,
and our army totals
85 thousand cavalrymen
and 138 thousand infantry.
We also have the
advantage of terrain,
knowing the Fields of
Atropatene as we do.
By day's end, the
Lusitanians will find
they have marched all this way
only to dig their own graves.
Yes, quite.
But do you not find it strange
that they took Maryam
and so easily
when three years ago
they failed so utterly?
As for that.
[AZRAEL cawing]
[ARSLAN]
Uh.
Azrael!
[chuckles]
Welcome back. Did you
have a good flight?
[ARSLAN] Kharlan.
Azrael's feathers are damp.
What did you say?
The skies are
mostly clear ahead.
Does it not seem odd?
[KHARLAN] Perhaps I should
scout the area once more.
[ARSLAN]
Yes, please do.
Who cares about a little rain?
The Crown Prince sure seems
to worry a lot though.
First battle and all.
Bet he's just nervous.
Too bad he didn't inherit
King Andragoras's courage.
Go, Azrael. Back to Kishward
with you. Fly true.
[AZRAEL squawking]
Don't fear for me.
I'll be all right.
[ARSLAN]
Head East!
Kishward is out on the border,
at the Peshawar Citadel!
I'll be all right.
[BOY C] It turned out as you
feared it would, Your Highness.
[BOY A] We can't see anything
through fog this dense.
[ARSLAN]
Not a thing.
Your Highness, I'm ready
to lay down my life for you.
[ARSLAN]
Uh.
As am I, sir.
That makes three of us!
Three years back, you
saved our fool necks.
We've waited to
repay you ever since.
I shall rely on you.
[BOYS]
Always!
Even should it cost our lives!
Please, do not say such things.
Focus on staying alive.
It would sadden me to lose you.
We return to Ecbatana together.
[BOYS]
Yes, sir!
[hooves clattering]
[VAHRIZ]
Your Highness!
You shouldn't stray so far
from the encampment.
[ARSLAN]
Oh, sorry.
[VAHRIZ] It would be most
dire were you to lose sight
of the road in this fog.
[ARSLAN]
Are you concerned that this fog
will be to our disadvantage?
I am not concerned
in the slightest.
Led by King Andragoras
the Third,
the army of Pars has never
been defeated in the field.
As I'm sure Your
Highness is aware.
Perhaps some physical exertion
will keep your mind off
such unnecessary concerns.
Whaddya say? Care for
a practice bout?
I don't know that
my ego could take it.
[MESSENGER]
Lord Er! Please hurry!
You're needed, my lord.
What's the trouble?
Lord Daryun has incurred
His Majesty's wrath.
It's looking bleak.
He what? Oh, foolish nephew.
Such conflict before a battle
will affect the morale
of the entire army.
I'll be right there.
[ARSLAN]
Uh. I will come as well.
[thud]
[ANDRAGORAS] I thought
better of you, Daryun.
When did the ghost of a coward
come to possess your body?
I never thought to hear the word
"retreat" come from your lips.
It makes me sick to my stomach.
[DARYUN]
Your Majesty.
I can assure you,
what I have said does not
have its root in cowardice.
[ANDRAGORAS] A warrior
seeking to avoid battle?
If that's not the very
essence of cowardice,
I don't know what is.
[DARYUN] Your Majesty,
please consider this.
The Parsian cavalry is known
to be virtually undefeatable.
That reputation has
been justly earned.
So I wonder.
Why would the enemy choose to
await our forces upon a plain?
Such terrain is clearly
to our advantage.
I think it very likely they
have laid a trap for us.
There is also the fog.
We can hardly even see
our own troops' movements.
I believe we should
withdraw for the time being
and reposition our forces
outside the walls of Ecbatana.
[ANDRAGORAS]
I wonder when it was
that you became more
skilled with words
than with the bow or the sword.
The terrain here is unfamiliar
to those filthy savages.
How could they surprise
us on our own soil?
That, I do not yet know.
However,
there is always the chance
they have the help of a guide.
Then the terrain would
not be so unfamiliar.
You suggest one of my
subjects has turned traitor
and is aiding the enemy?
Impossible!
All due respect, sire,
it is possible!
The desire for revenge
could motivate an escaped
slave to aid Lusitania.
[gasps]
You would speak
to me of slavery?
I see now the words spilling
from your lips are not yours,
but those of an exile.
What ideas has that
worthless Narsus
filled your fool head with?
[DARYUN] While I do not deny
that Narsus is my friend,
I have not seen him once
these last few years.
[ANDRAGORAS]
You claim him as your friend?
Fine words, coward!
I hereby dismiss you
from your post as Marzb.
Consider it a mercy I do not
strip you of your Mard
and Shirghir titles, as well.
Remove yourself!
You are no longer welcome
in the royal presence!
Huh?
Lord Father, I--
[ANDRAGORAS]
I did not summon you, Arslan.
What're you doing here?
Your sole focus right now
should be distinguishing
yourself in battle!
Hm?
Lord Unc-- Uh!
[gasps]
You are an insolent child!
You would speak thus
to His Majesty?
You know what we owe him!
Please, Lord Uncle.
It's not as if I--
--[thud]
--[DARYUN grunts]
[growls]
[DARYUN]
I forgot my place, Majesty.
I spoke out of turn. Forgive me.
[VAHRIZ]
Your Majesty.
I know that my nephew
has behaved inexcusably.
I hope you can pardon an
old man his sentimentality.
But I beg mercy of you.
Forgive Daryun his most
egregious transgressions.
All right, Vahriz.
That's enough.
Daryun, I grant you a
chance to redeem yourself.
You will take part in
this battle as a knight
assigned to
the main army.
Distinguish yourself and I will
consider reinstating you.
[DARYUN] I have no words
to express my thanks
for your kindness.
Arslan! Why're you still here?
I shall withdraw immediately.
My apologies.
[DARYUN] I am sorry for
having inconvenienced you,
Your Highness.
Think nothing of it.
You spoke the truth as
you saw it, did you not?
Yes, I did.
Lord Kharlan is of the
same mind as I am on this.
[ARSLAN]
Uh.
He supported my plan to bring
our concerns to His Majesty.
That's good to hear.
He must've taken my
worries earlier seriously.
[BOY A]
Your Highness!
[ARSLAN] I'm sorry.
I should return to the ranks.
You know, Daryun,
when this battle is over,
you and I should
have a long talk.
Yes. I would like that.
[DARYUN] I would think
His Majesty might show
a bit more consideration
for the Crown Prince.
Or fatherly concern.
He treats Prince
Arslan like dirt.
Enough now, nephew.
Or do you want your head
separated from your shoulders?
Honestly, boy.
When something gets
under your skin,
there's just
no stopping you.
You lose all sense of caution.
[VAHRIZ]
By the by.
How would you describe Prince
Arslan's physical appearance?
Sir? That seems an odd question.
Looking at the king
and the queen,
who do you suppose
the prince more favors?
[DARYUN]
Uh.
If I had to say, then,
it would be Her
Majesty, I suppose.
[VAHRIZ]
Mmm.
My thoughts, too.
Interesting that he does
not resemble the king.
[VAHRIZ]
Daryun.
[DARYUN]
Sir.
[VAHRIZ]
Here and now,
will you swear your
loyalty to Prince Arslan?
Is that necessary?
You know I remain ever
steadfast in my devotion
to the Royal House of Pars.
I mean to His Highness
personally, Daryun.
[DARYUN]
Uh.
I understand. If that's your
wish, I'll be honored to.
[VAHRIZ]
Do you swear it upon your sword?
Yes, sir. On my sword, I swear.
If you'd like, I can present
you a written oath, as well.
[VAHRIZ]
No, nephew.
You have given your word.
That is more than enough for me.
If he can count on no one else,
I wish for His Highness
to have an ally in you.
Only a handful are granted
the title of Mard fu Mard.
You are truly a warrior
among warriors, nephew.
My thanks, Uncle.
[horns sounding]
[VAHRIZ]
Hm?
That's the signal to march!
We fight to avenge Maryam!
And to teach these
savages about justice!
[KUBARD] We may not have seen
battle in quite some time, boys,
but that is no excuse
for laggin' behind!
Well. I guess it's time, huh?
If I do well today,
will I finally be accepted
as Crown Prince?
Sir?
[ARSLAN]
Nothing.
[ANDRAGORAS] Kharlan,
how many do the enemy number?
An estimated 25 to 30
thousand cavalry, sir,
and roughly 80 to 90
thousand infantry, as well.
They've been campaigning
for some time.
Their numbers
must've diminished.
It's possible that
reinforcements from home
have swelled their
numbers instead.
[ANDRAGORAS]
Hm.
With this fog,
we cannot hope to see
the enemy's position.
[KHARLAN] That sword cuts
both ways, Your Majesty.
It's true that we cannot
see the Lusitanians,
but nor can they see us.
Provided we begin the
fight on equal footing,
I believe our victory to
be a foregone conclusion.
[MESSENGER]
Enemy ahead!
The enemy vanguard has
been spotted, Your Majesty!
They're about eight amaj away!
It's time to act.
I trust that our people
have conducted a survey
of the land ahead of us?
A thorough one, sir.
Before us lies
a vast, flat plain.
There are no dips
or rises to speak of.
Despite the
thickness of the fog,
we can trust the horses
to carry us straight forward.
[ANDRAGORAS]
I call upon thee, kings of old!
Sage King Jamsh+d!
Hero King Kaykhusraw!
Spirits of those
who came before!
We beseech you to watch
over the Army of Pars!
[PARS ARMY] We beseech you to
watch over the Army of Pars!
Yashasuiin!
Your Highness!
Oh!
Yashasuiin!
[PARS ARMY yelling]
Here they come.
The great Parsian
Army is charging.
Almost here.
[PARS SOLDIER D]
Halt the charge!
Your Highness,
rein in your horse--
[PERSONAL GUARD B]
Your Highness!
[gasps]
What is happening here?
[PARS SOLDIER G]
Turn back!
[PERSONAL GUARD B]
Stop, men!
[PARS SOLDIER E]
What is this?!
[PARS SOLDIER H]
Bastards!
They coated it all in oil!
They wouldn't.
[PARS SOLDIERS screaming]
[PARS SOLDIER L]
We can't pass!
--[PARS SOLDIER M] Go around!
--[PARS SOLDIER N] To the left!
[PARS SOLDIER M] Keep going!
There's a gap ahead!
Archers?
[PARS SOLDIER P]
Damn it! It's a trap!
[ARSLAN whimpering]
[PERSONAL GUARD B]
What happened?
[whimpering]
[PERSONAL GUARD C]
Your Highness, please stay back!
[BOY A]
Your Highness!
You made it through unscathed?
Please keep going,
Your Highness.
We'll hold the enemy here!
Go safely, sir!
No, come back here!
[BOYS yelling]
[PARS SOLDIER C]
Hurry, Your Highness!
I can't just flee!
[yelps]
[ARMIES yelling]
[grunts]
Not bad for a child!
Now you're going to pay!
You heathen bastard!
[whoosh]
[thudding]
[groaning]
[ARSLAN whimpering]
Lord Father!
Daryun!
Vahriz!
Azrael!
Somebody.
[ARSLAN]
Anybody!
[DARYUN]
Whoa!
Your Highness!
C'mon, I just wanna
see it a second.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER E]
Hey! Watch it!
That's my trophy!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER D]
Trophy? You just found it.
And besides, I think it
looks much better on me.
See, that's where you're wrong.
Pretty sure that big,
bald head of yours
is round and shiny enough
--as it is.
--[whoosh, thud]
Huh?
I'll ask only once.
Where'd you find the helmet?
[KHARLAN]
Your Highness!
Crown Prince Arslan!
[gasps]
[KHARLAN]
Speak so I can find you!
Where are you? I heard
your voice before!
[ARSLAN]
Kharlan! I'm over here!
My men have all been killed!
Please, help!
[stammering]
Ah. Excellent. I've found you
at last. Hello, my Prince.
[ANDRAGORAS]
Kharlan!
Where's Kharlan?!
[PARS SOLDIER W]
Sir!
Lord Kharlan disappeared
some time ago!
I want him found!
Do it at once!
[BOTH]
Yes, sir!
You men go as well.
I don't want to see your faces
again until you've found him!
Yes, sir!
[DARYUN yelling]
[ARSLAN]
Why, Kharlan? Please tell me!
There were
circumstances, Highness.
Poor, pitiable prince.
Truth of it is, you've
done nothing wrong.
No, you've done nothing wrong,
and yet, you must
die here today.
[ARSLAN]
Why?
Why have you betrayed us?
[ARSLAN yelps]
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS laughing]
--[thudding]
--[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER I groans]
--[thud]
--[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER J yelling]
[KHARLAN]
Hm?
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER K]
Attack!
Where are they?
What's their number?
Your Highness!
Daryun!
I will always keep you safe.
Always.
[NARRATOR] Before his cries
ceased to echo through the air.
Daryun's black armor
was mottled red
with the blood of
Lusitanian soldiers.
Next time:
"The Knight in Black."
And thus would the
boy become a king.