[NARRATOR] Having completed
their infiltration of Ecbatana
and gauged the
likely survival
of King Andragoras
and Queen Tahamenay,
Narsus and Daryun returned
to Prince Arslan's side
to guide and protect
their future king.
[ARSLAN] The six of us can
only accomplish so much.
How can we find more allies?
You must start
by making changes.
You must alter certain policies.
Ones that have been
long supported in Pars,
but have become
increasingly untenable.
Your royal blood can
only take you so far.
Securing the throne requires the
skilled use of statecraft, too.
I understand that,
but perhaps there is a
more direct stratagem.
Your Highness, please.
Your place is giving orders,
but you need not be concerned
with every plan we make.
You may leave the minutiae
for us to see to.
[NARSUS]
As a monarch,
you simply make clear what
you wish to accomplish.
[gasps]
[NARSUS] Tell us
your aims, Highness,
and it will be our pleasure
to see them achieved.
Then I'm counting on you.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS yell]
[GIEVE]
How many in pursuit?
[NARSUS]
Five hundred cavalrymen?
[GIEVE]
A few too many, then.
Four hundred I could manage,
but five could be stretching
it, even for me.
[FARANGIS]
Pay him no mind.
He's an unabashed braggart and
an idiot of the worst sort.
Lord Daryun will return soon.
Apologies, Your Highness,
please bear with us.
I shall.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER B groans]
[GIEVE]
An excellent shot!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS grunting]
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER F grunts]
[FARANGIS] I've received
good word from the Djinn.
According to them, we've
made the wind our ally.
[DARYUN]
Your Highness!
[ARSLAN]
Daryun!
[DARYUN]
This way!
[ARSLAN]
Right!
[DARYUN]
Over there!
[horn blows]
What was that?
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER I]
Sounds like a horn.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS groaning]
There are too many. Retreat!
Retrea-- Ah!
[KASHAN SOLDIERS cheering]
[ARSLAN]
They have a lot of slaves.
[HODIR]
Prince Arslan,
how good of you to remember
a humble man such as myself.
I feel such gratitude that
I am nearly speechless.
Not at all.
On the contrary, it is I
who should be thanking you.
I am grateful for
the reinforcements.
[HODIR] Please, Your Highness,
think nothing of it.
Upon learning of Pars's
tragic defeat at Atropatene,
I was deeply concerned
for your safety
and that of your lord father.
How could I do anything less?
I only regret I could
not act sooner!
I had not the resources to
launch a retaliatory attack
against the entire
Lusitanian army.
I was forced to remain here,
waiting and worrying.
And then today,
Lord Daryun presented himself
at my humble castle,
and granted me the
opportunity to prove
my enduring loyalty
to Your Highness.
Words cannot express
the joy in my heart.
Now that you have arrived
at Kashan Fortress,
rest assured that
time of worry is over.
Please don't hesitate
to make yourself at home.
If there's anything in
particular you desire to eat,
you have but to ask.
[HODIR]
We pride ourselves on dishes
made with ingredients
imported from all over.
[ARSLAN] You seem to have a
large slave population here.
[HODIR]
Indeed.
We have more slaves per master
here than even Ecbatana.
[chuckles] A number rivaled...
I'm curious to know. What do
you make of our jolly host?
Clearly a man of many words,
his slick tongue must
require frequent oiling.
He proves the saying,
"the more you speak,
the more of yourself
you reveal."
Like someone else I know.
...made me happy man
today, Your Highness.
Incidentally, did you know
I have a young daughter?
She is thirteen years old.
I may be her father,
but I believe I speak truly when
I say that she is a lovely girl,
and most sensible, as well.
If you were to allow her
to serve at your side,
Your Highness, well,
nothing could bring greater
joy to her or to me.
Wha... Huh?
Ah.
May I ask, what will you do to
strike back at the Lusitanians?
How do you intend
to proceed from here?
As I see it, we must first
save the people of Ecbatana,
who are suffering the most.
I shall declare myself,
and make my intentions known.
Then gather as many
reinforcements as I am able.
To that end, I will soon
be making some changes.
Altering policies that
have become untenable.
Firstly, I intend to
free all the slaves.
What an interesting plan.
I'm glad to see Your Highness
has prepared for the future.
Though I expected no less!
And? Is my plan one
you can support?
You've my full
support, of course!
Truly impressive,
Your Highness.
Such revolutionary
ideas you have! [laughs]
[VASSAL A] Here we are. This
will be Your Highness's room.
And yours is there, Mistress.
The rest of you
shall be over here.
[DARYUN] I'm sorry.
That's unacceptable.
I won't leave
His Highness's side.
Surely it'll do for the night.
I'm afraid the room
has only been made up
for a single person.
Then I will happily
sleep on the floor.
But, sir...
Daryun, let it be.
Uh... Very well, then.
Your Highness, should
you need anything,
please find me at once.
Certainly.
Uh!
[knocking]
Your Highness. You and I
have something to discuss.
Uh...
[DARYUN] I know that man is
plotting something, but what?
[NARSUS] Clearly, he would like
to see the daughter he mentioned
married to the new king of Pars,
thereby gaining influence
as the king's father-in-law.
Well, knowing the motives
for his hospitality,
should we not be taking
action of some sort?
[NARSUS] He has purposefully
separated us from His Highness.
Uh! You might have
mentioned that sooner!
I had even considered sleeping
in front of His Highness's door!
It was my intention to go
along with Lord Hodir's scheme.
[HODIR]
Well, then, Your Highness.
I will leave you for now.
I'm sure you will give careful
thought to what I've said.
Yes. I certainly will.
[DARYUN] The fortress has
a large number of troops.
I'd greatly prefer not to
make an enemy of its master.
[NARSUS] But if he wants
to make enemies of us,
what choice have we?
[DARYUN grunts]
[GIEVE sighs]
[ARSLAN yelps]
[NARSUS, DARYUN, ELAM gasp]
It's only me.
[GIEVE]
Your Highness?
Hi...
[DARYUN] Traversing
across the balconies?!
[laughs]
Of all the reckless,
foolish things to do!
There were guards at
the door, so I improvised.
And if your foot had slipped?
You would have fallen
to your death,
and I wouldn't have
been there to help you!
What are you,
his nursemaid?
[NARSUS]
Let's have it, then.
What did Hodir
have to say to you?
[ARSLAN]
There were two "suggestions"
that he wished to offer me.
The first was that I marry his
daughter and make her my queen.
As for the other,
he counseled me against
making extreme reforms
that would go against
Parsian tradition.
Such as freeing the slaves.
[ELAM grunts]
What grand suggestions!
And how did Your
Highness respond?
I said that I could
not answer immediately,
but that I would give him my
response sometime tomorrow.
Was that all right?
That should be fine.
[ARSLAN sighs]
Honestly, though.
What can he possibly
be thinking?
I've never even met his
daughter. How could I marry her?
[ELAM, NARSUS, GIEVE, DARYUN]
Mm?
I doubt we have much time.
Hodir is likely to act
before the night is out.
Your Highness, make ready to
leave at a moment's notice.
As for the rest, you
can leave it to us.
I understand.
[NARSUS] Gieve, will you escort
His Highness back to his room
and deliver a message
to Farangis?
[GIEVE]
Mm. I shall be happy to.
And, Elam. I've a task
for you, as well.
Sure!
The Djinn appear
agitated tonight.
[GIEVE chuckles]
--[GIEVE groaning]
--For some reason,
the Djinn believe I should
stick my foot out the window.
Please but give me a
chance. I can explain!
[FARANGIS]
What do you want?
[GIEVE] I've a message
from the Lord Tactician.
[FARANGIS] And you couldn't
deliver this message
using the door?
[GIEVE] I could, but it makes
for a far more poetic story
to enter from the window.
Interesting. It would
seem that your message
has something to do with
the Djinn's agitation.
Here and now,
will you swear your
loyalty to Prince Arslan?
[KHARLAN] The rightful heir
will ascend the throne.
[DARYUN] What are you saying?
The rightful heir is--
[DARYUN gasps]
[NARSUS] What is it?
What troubles you?
[DARYUN] There is something...
I would like your opinion on.
Do you suppose... is there
any chance Prince Arslan
is the son of the late
King Osroes the Fifth?
[NARSUS] That thought had
crossed my mind, as well.
However, considering when
His Highness was born
it would not have
been possible.
[ELAM] It's finished.
I did as you instructed, sir.
[NARSUS]
Good work, thank you.
I found this. It was in the
space above the ceiling.
[NARSUS] Just the sort of low
trick I would expect from Hodir.
I presume he intended
to put us to sleep
so he could have time to win
His Highness to his side.
Surely there can be no further
need for us to hold back.
There appears to be some sort
of commotion brewing outside.
In that case,
it's time for us to
make our move, as well.
[HODIR] Your Highness?
Do pardon the intrusion.
[ARSLAN]
One moment.
I'm loathe to
disturb your-- Uh!
What is it?
[ARSLAN gasps]
Soldiers?
Your Highness.
The companions you have
gathered to your side
during your travels are likely
to do you more harm than good.
It would be best if they
were done away with.
I had hoped I might
have your permission
to dispose of them now.
I can see no reason for
them to be "done away with."
They have served me
loyally in all respects.
They have misguided
you to a degree
that borders on treachery.
If they remain,
they will certainly bring
disaster to the kingdom.
What a ridiculous notion!
[HODIR] Can you not see that
I am acting for your sake?
Consider the
"strategist," Narsus.
Your lord father had him
banished from the Court.
Do you know why he
would do such a thing?
Because Narsus spoke
of abolishing slavery,
of redistributing the wealth of
the temples among the people,
of treating commoners
the same as nobles!
In short, it was because
he had extreme ideas.
I am sure his ideas
were well thought out.
Well thought out?
I don't care how much
thinking he may have done!
If men such as him are going
to be governing this kingdom,
I say we would be better off
surrendering to Lusitania
here and now!
To be entirely clear,
you are telling me to forsake
my current companions.
[HODIR]
Indeed I am, Highness.
[ARSLAN] Let me ask this.
Assuming I do forsake those
who have served me
loyally and choose you,
can you be sure there won't come
a day when I forsake you, too?
[HODIR gasps]
[ARSLAN] You've made unkind
assertions about Narsus.
But unlike you, Lord Hodir,
he offered me shelter
without seeking to ambush
me during the night!
[HODIR grunts]
[ARSLAN] Daryun! Narsus!
Gieve! Farangis! Elam!
We leave immediately!
[KASHAN SOLDIERS murmur]
We've been awaiting
your order, Prince Arslan.
[HODIR]
What is this? Impossible!
My thanks for your aid.
[NARSUS]
Hmph.
[DARYUN]
You're right, Your Highness.
I can see no need for us
to remain in such a place.
[GIEVE] Agreed, they're woefully
short of beautiful women.
[HODIR growling]
[HODIR] Your Highness!
Please, wait but a moment!
I have invited your suspicion,
and I have only
myself to blame.
I will not seek to stop you now.
But if you will at
least do me the honor
of allowing my men to
provide you an escort.
[KASHAN SOLDIERS yelp]
You would allow your men
to approach His Highness
carrying concealed daggers?
Not a very wise idea.
I see, so this
is where it ends!
[KASHAN SOLDIERS yell]
Go no further!
Let us leave in peace,
or I promise it will
go badly for you.
[KASHAN SOLDIER C]
It's... Lord Daryun!
[HODIR]
Archers, fire!
[KASHAN SOLDIER D]
Wha..?
[KASHAN SOLDIERS gasping]
[KASHAN SOLDIER F]
What's going on here?!
Well done, Elam.
I should have known you would
have some trick up your sleeve.
[NARSUS]
Yes. You really should have.
While we may be few in number,
we do have working bowstrings.
[HODIR growls]
[NARSUS]
Wise man that you are,
I imagine you'll be more than
happy to open the gates
and see us on our way without
further interference.
[HODIR] If I let you leave here,
I'll be known as a traitor!
And I won't have
that! Now, men!
[KASHAN SOLDIERS chuckle]
Capture the prince
and kill the rest!
[KASHAN SOLDIERS yelling]
[DARYUN yells]
[KASHAN SOLDIERS groaning]
[KASHAN SOLDIERS yell]
[NARSUS grunts]
[KASHAN SOLDIERS groan]
[KASHAN SOLDIER Q]
You-- Ah!
[KASHAN SOLDIER T]
Hey!
[KASHAN SOLDIER U]
What's that?
[KASHAN SOLDIER V]
It's too dark!
[KASHAN SOLDIERS groan]
[KASHAN SOLDIER AA]
Damn you! [groans]
[DARYUN grunts]
Hodir!
You belong to the
Angel of Judgment.
Now is the time to
confess your sins.
Confess your crimes
against the prince.
--Confess your betrayal!
--[HODIR] No! [yells]
[HODIR groaning]
[KASHAN SOLDIERS murmuring]
The lord of Kashan
Fortress is dead.
Will you fight for him, or
will you lay down your swords?
[ELAM] Your Highness, shouldn't
we be getting on our way?
[SLAVES mumble, yawn]
I bring good news!
From this day forward,
you are all free!
Maybe I'm not being clear.
You're not slaves anymore.
Who said we're not slaves?
Was it Lord Hodir?
Well, no. Lord Hodir
is dead. That's why.
[MALE SLAVES murmur]
What?!
[MALE SLAVE B] Were you
the one who killed him?
[ARSLAN] It was one
of my companions.
[MALE SLAVE C]
You bastard!
[MALE SLAVE D]
Murderer! Let's get him!
Wait, I don't under-- Ah!
[DARYUN]
Back away! Your Highness!
[MALE SLAVES shouting]
Stop!
[NARSUS]
You're quiet tonight, Highness.
Thinking about the
slaves from the fortress?
[ARSLAN]
Yes. Why were they so angry?
I don't understand.
[NARSUS]
Loyalty to Hodir.
As bad of a man as
he seemed to us,
he must have been
a good master.
You knew.
You expected something like
this to happen, didn't you?
Yes.
[ARSLAN]
Then why didn't you tell me?
[NARSUS] Even if I had
given you warning,
I sincerely doubt you
would have believed me.
There are some
things in this world
that have to be experienced
to be understood.
And now? Are you speaking
from experience?
I am.
Five years ago,
when my father died
and I took the title,
I freed all the slaves
on our holdings.
After doing so,
I left for the capital.
I returned after some time,
only to find that the
slaves had returned.
They came back?!
[NARSUS]
In a society like ours,
being a slave with
a generous master
can be easier than
being free but poor.
[ARSLAN]
But, you did what was right!
Surely they must have realized
that and thanked you for it.
And what is "right"?
Is it like the sun?
Or is it, perhaps,
more like the stars?
Only one sun casts
its light upon us,
but infinite stars
guide our way at night.
[NARSUS] Regardless,
I hope you won't be deterred
by my experience,
or by yours earlier.
You're attempting to do right
according to your
own convictions.
And I would hate to see you
swayed from such a path.
[ARSLAN] How much longer will
five capable, honorable people
such as these be content
to follow me?
I have to become a ruler
worthy of their loyalty,
or soon enough,
they will despair of me.
Your Highness, we must
decide which direction
we will be traveling
come morning.
[ARSLAN]
East. We ride for Peshawar.
[BAHMAN]
Lord Vahriz. I am lost.
The parting gift you left
is a weighty one indeed.
Why would you give such a thing
into clumsy hands like mine?
[BAHMAN] The Royal House
can trace its line
back to the Hero
King Kaykhusraw,
but if things go awry, I could
see its end during my lifetime.
If only I had died
two kings back
during King Gotarzes's reign.
That would've been
a peaceful end.
[NARRATOR] If Arslan's
company must split apart,
Gieve would greatly
prefer Fairangis
as his traveling companion.
But he is doomed
to disappointment.
Next time,
"The Road to Peshawar."
And thus would the
boy become a king.