[LUSITANIAN OFFICER B]
Pardon, Your Highness.
But it appears the priests
have been hunting heathens
despite being ordered not to.
Not again. Stop the
zealots however you can.
With force if you must.
[LUSITANIAN OFFICER B]
Lord Bodin will object.
We're a small kingdom to
have become conquerors.
Was it the "might of God" that
led us to take Maryam and Pars?
No, sir.
I-I know we owe our
victory wholly to you.
Then trust me when
I give orders.
[BODIN] The decision should
be an easy one to make.
The lives of ten thousand
of these heathens
would make a suitable offering!
Oh. I don't know.
[BODIN]
There can be no question!
What possible reason can
you have to hesitate?
You must heed me!
[GUISCARD] I think it
better not to stir up
the people's hostility
for mere sport.
[BODIN grunts]
If we're not careful,
Pars's neighbors may join
her in outright rebellion.
We likely could not withstand
such an alliance.
[BODIN growls]
[BODIN]
If the heathens wish
to rise up in rebellion,
then I say let them.
My army of three hundred
thousand believers
will happily crush them,
down to the last man.
War is a problem dealt with
by those on this earth.
Strategies are made by men,
not granted by heaven.
Thus, this is not a matter
that requires your attention.
You dare!
You wouldn't want to act outside
the bounds of your duties.
Such prideful presumption
on your part might anger God.
Never! This is a holy war!
It cannot be won by
secular forces alone.
To that end,
I have determined the best
course of action is to
add to our fighting strength
with the loyal forces of God.
More soldiers! Who are they?
They're supposedly
holy warriors.
They serve their god
rather than man.
[NARRATOR] Pars Era.
The year 320, December.
The Temple Knights,
a fighting force
answering directly to the
Archpriest, entered Ecbatana.
Their presence could
not mean anything good
for the Royal Capital.
[SAM]
Who... are... you?
[SAM] I'm alive. What I
don't understand is why.
[gasps]
Why've I been spared?
You ought to climb out of
that bed and kneel at my feet.
Captive or not, I am
still a knight of Pars.
There is only one man I will
kneel to, and that is my king!
Heh. If that is the case,
then I am happy to lay claim
to your obedience, knight.
[SAM]
Huh?
Impossible!
[HILMES] Not impossible at all.
I am Osroes's heir.
I am the rightful king of Pars.
[SAM gasping]
You were supposed to have died
in the fire 16 years ago!
[groans, panting]
[HILMES] Think upon
your earlier statement.
No doubt you'll realize who
your true lord and master is.
[NARRATOR]
As various factions
fought for control
of the capital,
Arslan and his company
sought to avoid ambush,
as they made their
way east to Peshawar,
and the largest remaining
Parsian force.
And what is "right"?
Is it like the sun?
Or is it, perhaps,
more like the stars?
Only one sun casts
its light upon us,
but infinite stars
guide our way at night.
Regardless.
You're attempting to do right
according to your
own convictions.
And I would hate to see you
swayed from such a path.
[ARSLAN] How do I know which
path to choose?
Or what it is to
be a good ruler?
A poorly planned revolution
is doomed to fail.
[ELAM]
Your Highness.
If we continue at this speed,
the horses will tire quickly.
[ARSLAN gasps]
We need them to carry
us quite a ways.
Right. Elam?
[ELAM]
Uh?
[ARSLAN]
What is your path?
What do you think the future
has in store for you?
[ELAM]
Uh...
Perhaps you wish to
become an advisor,
helping steer the
kingdom's policies?
Or a fearless commander,
leading warriors into battle?
[ELAM]
I don't know my future.
That's something Lord Narsus
will decide for me.
Until he does, I'll just have
to do my best serving him,
and learn as much
as he'll teach me.
A worthy goal.
If I want to rule well,
I should study, too.
I have a lot to learn.
You're going to be a good
king, I'm sure of it.
[ARSLAN]
Huh?
With Lords Narsus and
Daryun guiding you,
you're definitely
off to a good start.
You're right.
With all of you helping me,
I can't go wrong.
And I have you to thank
as much as the others.
I'm grateful, Elam.
Uh. My actions are only those
of any other proper attendant.
They are certainly nothing
worthy of your notice.
I disagree.
Rather an odd prince, isn't he?
How so?
You're the prince's vassal,
and Elam is your servant.
He doesn't serve
His Highness directly.
Why would he ever
pay him any mind?
[NARSUS] Hmph. The prince
doesn't behave
like most royalty.
I'll grant you.
[GIEVE] Hm... I've never
known any of the royalty
to care one whit
for their vassals,
much less their servants.
It isn't in their nature,
as far as I can tell.
[HILMES whimpers]
I did it!
I finally brought down a
lion during today's hunt.
That means I'm a
Sheer-gear now, too!
Ah! I expected
no less, Hilmes.
I'm lucky to have been
blessed with such an heir.
[OSROES]
Someday you shall become
the greatest hero
in all of Pars.
I'll try, anyway.
[OSROES chuckles]
[HILMES] That night, my father
was killed by his brother,
Andragoras. And as for me...
[LADY-IN-WAITING A gasps]
Fire! In the prince's room!
[MALE COURT OFFICIAL A]
Prince Hilmes! Prince Hilmes!
[ATTENDANTS scream]
[MALE A]
Hurry!
[FEMALE A]
Save the prince!
[MALE A]
To His Highness!
[HILMES whimpers]
[screams]
[HILMES]
I have captured Andragoras.
That just leaves Arslan to
see to. Once I have killed him,
the throne will return
to its rightful owner.
[LADY-IN-WAITING B]
If you'll pardon me. I--
[gasps]
This disgusts you?
Not at all.
[HILMES]
Then what is it?
Do you find my face
so terrifying?
I'm not frightened
at all, master.
Please. I beg your pardon.
I shall take my leave now if
you wish. Please forgive me!
[whimpers]
[HILMES]
Why are you here?
Sir, you have a visitor.
A man has come.
Who is it?
[ZANDEH] My name is Zandeh,
Your Highness.
I am Lord Kharlan's son.
I have come to serve you
in my late father's place.
I hope you will accept my
fealty just as you did his.
Sorry for your father's
death. He served me well,
and I'm certain you shall,
too. You have my faith.
I shall strive to do justice
to that faith, Highness.
[HILMES]
I know you will.
[ZANDEH]
Sir! I pledge you this.
I will find Arslan and Daryun,
and I will kill them as
they killed my father.
And once I've done so, I will
bring you their rotting heads.
You believe you would
prevail against Daryun?
Yes.
[HILMES]
Hmph.
Then you have
my leave, Zandeh.
I shall grant you
the opportunity
to take your revenge.
[ZANDEH]
Thank you!
[HILMES] My men are
nipping at Arslan's heels.
We shall have him
before much longer.
[FARANGIS] Hear me, Djinn.
Be still! Hadeed! Hadeed!
[gasps] Is something wrong?
[FARANGIS]
It's the Djinn.
I'm afraid they're in a
rather foul mood tonight.
It seems there are
bloodthirsty folk nearby.
[gasps]
Our pursuers?
They've caught up to us.
Not surprising, really.
We took many detours
to avoid ambush.
[gasps]
[GIEVE]
This certainly isn't the most
pleasant
journey I've taken.
[ARSLAN]
Huh?
[GIEVE] The one consolation
is that I travel with you,
beautiful mistress of my heart!
[FARANGIS]
Ironic. For me,
the one stroke of misfortune
is that I travel with you.
Come, Mistress Farangis!
Are you not a true servant
of the divine Mithra?
A priestess should never
be false to her own heart.
Now is not the time for
your games, musician.
[CAVALRYMAN A] Find them!
They should be in this area!
[DARYUN] Your Highness, please
take the others and go ahead.
[ARSLAN gasps]
[DARYUN]
I'll handle matters here.
[ARSLAN]
No!
Daryun!
[NARSUS]
Highness!
[ARSLAN]
Uh!
You need to trust Daryun in
this. Let's go on, as he says.
[sighs]
Very well.
Into the forest, as
fast as we're able!
Protect the prince at all costs!
Yes, sir!
Off we go.
[ARSLAN grunts]
[ARSLAN]
Where are Narsus and Farangis?
[GIEVE] We must have
lost them along the way.
We ought to go on
without them.
We'll meet again at Peshawar.
It's what they would want.
Yes, you're right.
[ELAM]
Let's go.
[ARSLAN]
Please, you three. Stay safe.
[CAVALRYMAN B yelps]
[DARYUN] I'll rejoin
you soon, Your Highness.
Stay safe just a while longer.
[DARYUN]
Uh?!
[CAVALRYMAN BETA]
I've got you now!
[CAVALRYMAN BETA groans]
[DARYUN]
What are you doing here?!
That's a lot of men to
fight off, even for you.
I thought I would help.
[CAVALRYMEN yelling]
[CAVALRYMEN whimper]
Target the woman first!
She'll be the weaker one--
[CAVALRYMEN groaning]
Weaker, is it?
We can't win this fight.
[CAVALRYMEN scream]
[CAVALRYMAN K yelps]
[CAVALRYMAN L groans]
[DARYUN, FARANGIS gasp]
[ZANDEH]
What a disgrace!
Spineless maggots, all of you!
Move!
[CAVALRYMEN groan]
Daryun! I know it was you
who killed my father Kharlan.
I'm here to make you pay!
Kharlan's son?
[ZANDEH]
Ha!
You should stay out
of my way, woman!
[ZANDEH yells]
What?
[ZANDEH groans]
[DARYUN]
Whoa.
His strength is incredible.
[DARYUN grunts]
[ZANDEH yells]
Die!
Many thanks for earlier.
[DARYUN yells]
[ZANDEH]
Uh!
[FARANGIS]
Shall we go?
[DARYUN]
Let's!
[CAVALRYMAN M]
Stop them!
[ZANDEH]
Dammit!
[FARANGIS] You hesitated.
You had the chance to kill him,
and you didn't take it. I
doubt he'd have done the same.
[DARYUN]
As do I.
But I make it a point
never to kill an opponent
who is already unhorsed.
[FARANGIS]
You're softer than you look.
[DARYUN]
Regrettably so.
[GIEVE] Honestly!
I came on this mad journey
for Mistress Farangis, not
to defend some royal brat.
[SOLDIER B groans]
Watch what you say. You need
to show him more respect.
Alas, lying has never
been a talent of mine.
[ARSLAN grunting]
[SOLDIER C groans]
[ELAM] Your Highness, most
of the enemy is on foot!
We can shake them!
[ARSLAN]
Good idea.
I'll protect from the rear.
[ENEMY CAPTAIN A]
Archers! Fire!
[ELAM screams, groaning]
[ARSLAN]
Uh! Elam!
Please, you have to keep
going, Your Highness!
Go!
[ARSLAN gasps]
Uh. Wha...?
A prince rescuing a servant?
What in the world is he doing?
[ELAM grunts]
Die!
[ELAM]
Uh?
Huh?
Highness. Why'd you come back?
It was the right thing to do.
[ELAM]
Uh. But I...
--[ELAM, ARSLAN gasp]
--[SOLDIERS grumble]
So it's come to this.
[GIEVE]
Hup!
Those... are gold pieces!
That isn't all, boys!
[GIEVE]
Time to get going.
[CAPTAIN A] What are you
idiots doing?! Charge!
[GIEVE grunts]
Too far down.
[ARSLAN gasps]
It's a dead end.
We have no choice
but to fight here.
[ELAM]
So it seems.
[sighs]
[CAPTAIN A] Well, they
didn't just vanish. Find them!
[splash]
[CAPTAIN A]
Uh? Huh?
[CAPTAIN A] Do they mean
to follow the river?
Head downstream and
look for them. Quickly!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
How could they hope to
survive from such a height?
The idiot really thought
we made the jump?
[ARSLAN, ELAM sigh]
Apologies for earlier, Highness.
My weakness shames me.
It is my job to protect
you from harm.
Yet you saved me.
That's just wrong.
Stop, Elam. I acted
to save a friend.
What's wrong in that?
You call me friend?
But I am the child
of two freed slaves!
Our ranks are much too
far apart for friendship.
Must we always
observe rank, though?
If we do, I'll never
have any friends at all.
Or is it maybe that
you dislike me, Elam?
Of course I don't dislike you.
That settles it. We're friends.
Consider it a royal decree.
[ELAM]
Uh!
Well, whatever
the case may be,
you saved my life,
Your Highness,
and I shall do my best
to repay the debt I owe.
[ARSLAN]
Gieve.
[GIEVE]
Yes?
I am very sorry
about earlier.
[GIEVE]
Hmm?
I know gold means
a great deal to you,
and you threw yours
away to save me.
[GIEVE]
Uh... Uh.
[ARSLAN]
I promise, I'll repay y--
Oh, no! It's enough to hear
royalty just apologize!
Er, I, uh. Out of curiosity,
what was your childhood like?
Did you spend your younger
years outside the palace?
Uh. How could you tell?
Let's just call
it a... hunch.
Yes, until my nursemaid
and her husband passed away,
I lived with them,
outside the palace.
My childhood was
simple and normal,
uncomplicated by
any royal lineage.
I played with other children.
I was friends with them, even
went to school with them.
[GIEVE]
Hm. I see.
That likely explains
why you're so different
from the other royalty
I've encountered.
[ARSLAN]
Different?
Yes.
I hadn't realized.
I can see why Narsus has taken
such a keen interest in you.
I think the kingdom you build
when you sit the throne
will be one I shall be proud
to be a part of. Eh?
[ELAM]
Uh!
[ARSLAN]
Thank you, Gieve.
Now, let's go. On! To Peshawar!
[NARRATOR] Daryun and
Farangis find themselves
encircled by an
overwhelming enemy force.
To make matters worse,
they must also face a man
still bent on revenge.
Next time,
"A Knight's Loyalty."
And thus would the
boy become a king.