[DARYUN] How are the
preparations coming along?
[NARSUS]
Exceedingly smoothly.
With Lord Lucian taking
on the role of satruyp,
I'm able to concentrate
fully on my duties
as military strategist.
He seems to be doing well.
I'm glad we appointed him, too.
And luckily for us, he's
harder working than you are.
[DARYUN]
Uh! Me? What about you?
Foisting half your tasks off
on that poor old fellow.
[ZARAVANT] Would you
like to say that again?
You should watch your tongue,
you damned Sindhuran cur!
[JASWANT] I'll say it
as many times as needed.
You will obey the orders
Lord Narsus has given you.
[ZARAVANT] I've read through his
orders. There must be a mistake.
He can't mean for us
to act as reserves
to Lord Daryun's company.
Why is that a problem?
How can we
distinguish ourselves
if we're relegated to the rear?
Now, where is Lord Narsus?
I should be speaking
with him, not you!
[TUS]
Come now. Let's cool our heads.
I backed down the other day out
of respect for Lord Kishward,
but I won't let this foreigner
continue to disrespect me.
It's only getting worse.
We must do something soon.
[music playing]
Surely there's no need for
violence. The day is fair.
Why not take a moment to bask in
the sunshine and enjoy a song?
The matters we have to discuss
don't concern you, musician.
Be on your way.
You will have to pardon me.
I had forgotten that you
hail from Oxus, you see,
and thus aren't likely
to appreciate more
sophisticated music.
Why, you little--!
[NARSUS]
Lord Zaravant.
I decided on our formation
after considering the unique
qualities of each company.
It is by no means an indictment
of your soldiers' abilities.
That said,
I do not wish to offer even
unintentional offense.
Perhaps you could allow me time
to consider the matter further.
Yes, certainly.
That is, if you would be kind
enough to do so, Lord Narsus.
[NARSUS] Will that suit
you as well, Jaswant?
I can think of no objections.
Let us leave him to it then.
By the gods.
First the Sindhuran dog and
now that traveling musician.
His Highness should
be more careful
of the sort of person he
surrounds himself with.
[TUS]
That's not for us to say.
This is a problem.
Such infighting
is bad for morale.
Especially on the
eve of a march.
The more people
gathered in one place,
the more issues will arise.
And I cannot entirely
blame Lord Zaravant
for his reluctance to accept us.
Consider it from
his point of view.
The prince's closest advisers
are a mismatched group
of questionable people.
Yes, including me.
Even so, we can hardly
leave matters as they stand.
True.
We shall have to play one
more gambit before we depart.
[door opens]
[KUBARD]
Cross these mountains
and I'll be at
Peshawar Fortress.
We can't let you
continue any further.
Thought he'd send someone.
Can't well have Prince
Arslan finding out
what your little crew
is up to, right?
Prince Hilmes did send you?
[SOLDIER A]
Hmph.
We're here to dispose
of a traitor.
Such duties are beneath
his Highness' notice.
Ah, then I suppose
it was Zandeh.
[BOTH yelling]
[KUBARD]
Sorry for this, Sam.
[thud]
[SOLDIER A groans]
[KUBARD]
You can choose your loyalties.
But you can't choose mine.
[ISFAN]
What?
You?
You were the one who shot
and killed my elder brother?
[GIEVE]
Yes, and what of it?
[ISFAN growls]
[GIEVE] I've heard
the stories about you.
Abandoned as a babe on
a snow-covered mountain.
Doomed until Shapur rescued you.
And for that they call
you Far al'Khu Din.
That means, "one who was
raised by wolves," yes?
We're discussing my
brother right now, not me.
Do you know how badly
your brother was suffering?
My arrow was what freed him.
You've no cause
to be angry with me.
[growls]
Master Gieve, just let it lie--!
[GIEVE] By rights, in fact, you
really ought to be thanking me.
I'll kill you!
He's no better than a murderer!
You can't lose to
a musician, sir!
[SOLDIER I]
Get him!
[ZARAVANT]
Hey, Isfan!
Give that outsider a
punch from me as well!
[GIEVE] See, that's another
thing you've got wrong.
From where I stand, you
people are the outsiders.
I've been by His Highness' side
ever since he left Ecbatana.
I protected him throughout
his journey here.
Unlike you and your men,
who came like sheep
to join his flock.
That's all I'm gonna
listen to from you!
[ISFAN]
Maybe you'll show some respect
once I cut out
that lying tongue!
Don't you understand?
The Lusitanians were
the ones torturing Shapur.
You should blame them for
his death, instead of me.
Oh, they will pay.
But you're here now!
Sheathe your swords,
both of you!
You are in the presence
of Crown Prince Arslan.
[ARSLAN]
What is the meaning of this?
Gieve? Lord Isfan?
[GIEVE]
Your Highness,
it was nothing but a small
difference of opinion.
[thud]
I saw everything, Gieve.
This was avoidable.
You were clearly provoking
Lord Isfan to no purpose.
[GIEVE]
Indeed.
And what do you plan
to do about it?
I have been troubled by
your irresponsible conduct
from the beginning.
You've presumed upon
His Highness' kind nature
long enough!
Listen to you.
It's always "His Highness
this, His Highness that."
Have you no identity
of your own, Daryun?
I hate to say this
to you, but really,
it's sad.
That's enough, both of you!
[GIEVE]
Highness.
I'm done.
You've been given
enough chances, Gieve.
I hereby banish you.
[SOLDIERS murmuring]
Ha, ha. As good a time as any.
My thanks for your hospitality
until now, Your Highness,
but court life doesn't
suit me anyway.
[KISHWARD] Now, Master Gieve,
Let's not be rash.
Surely if you apologize--
Your Highness, I wish you well.
I shall pray for your
good fortune in battle.
[KISHWARD]
Wait, Master Gieve!
[ARSLAN]
Narsus.
Did that truly need to
be done? You're certain?
I apologize.
It was a most unpleasant role
we asked you to play.
Never mind me.
My thoughts right
now are with Gieve.
He's the one who's been wronged.
[NARSUS]
A necessary charade.
Punishing him will
gratify the lords,
and should allay their
dissatisfaction for a time.
Gieve understood what
we asked of him, Highness.
Don't be troubled.
Perhaps if I spoke to him...
[NARSUS]
He has already departed.
On a mission.
I tasked him with finding
a certain someone.
[ARSLAN]
Finding who?
Someone we may
eventually have need of.
If you'll forgive me, I will
say no more for the moment.
I understand.
Though I do wish I'd had
the chance to bid him farewell.
[GIEVE] I think the kingdom you
build when you sit the throne
will be one I shall be
proud to be a part of.
[ARSLAN]
And so it shall be, Gieve.
Now we march! We will
strike down the enemy!
We will reclaim the
Royal Capital! To war!
[ARSLAN'S ARMY yelling]
[GUISCARD]
I see. Arslan has taken action.
I was expecting as much.
Who leads the effort to
muster our own troops?
[LUSITANIAN OFFICER B] Generals
Baudouin and Montferrat, sir.
Our troops were scattered
throughout Pars,
but all are now making
their way back to Ecbatana
to form a unified
army once again.
All except...
All except for Silver
Mask. Is that right?
[LUSITANIAN OFFICER B]
I'm sorry, Highness.
The messenger we sent to
Zabul Fortress hasn't returned.
Fine. Don't worry overmuch.
He'll return here eventually.
If for no other reason
than to take Arslan's head.
Hmph. Let him make his plans.
As long as he remains useful,
I will be happy to use him.
And when I no longer need him,
we'll see who has
the last laugh.
[NARSUS]
This is our initial destination.
Here. The Keep of
Saint Emmanuel.
[ARSLAN]
Saint Emmanuel?
[NARSUS]
Yes.
It is the name of an
historical Lusitanian figure.
The fortress had
long been abandoned.
In fact, it was all
but forgotten
until they came to occupy it.
I don't care for the
look of this terrain.
[NARSUS]
Nor I.
But given its location right
on the Continental Highway,
we can not be able to move
forward without taking it.
As for the man
guarding the keep,
his name is Lord Barcacion.
He was the Chief Royal
Librarian in Lusitania.
The chief librarian?
He is not a military man?
[NARSUS] A weakness we can
likely use to our advantage.
Good.
First we take back the
Keep of Saint Emmanuel.
It will be a foothold
on our way to Ecbatana.
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, Sir!
[ELAM]
Excuse me, Lord Narsus?
If we are making our way
to the keep from here,
we will be passing near this
castle as well, won't we?
[FARANGIS]
Chasoom Fortress it's called?
Curious. I don't believe
I've heard of it.
It is another structure
the Lusitanians have recently
made into a fortified base.
They likely mean to keep
an eye on our activity
by controlling a key
point along the highway.
Yes.
Their strategist,
Prince Guiscard,
is no slouch as a
tactician, it would seem.
[ZARAVANT]
Lord Narsus.
I beg you grant me
and my men permission
to lay siege to
Chasoom Fortress.
We'd be glad of the opportunity
to prove ourselves
an asset to His
Highness's cause.
[NARSUS] Your offer, while truly
noble, will not be necessary.
[TUS]
Lord Narsus?
Our primary objective at present
is the Keep of Saint
Emmanuel and that alone.
Strategically speaking, there's
no need to take the fortress.
[ARSLAN]
Isfan. Zaravant. Tus.
I appreciate your
bravery and dedication,
but if this battle
need not be fought,
I'd sooner save our
men and resources.
Surely you understand.
It shall be as you
wish, Your Highness.
Slower, Zaravant.
Rein in a little.
If you're worried, you rein in.
[TUS]
Hey! Both of you slow down!
You'll outpace the
rest of the army.
[ZARAVANT, ISFAN]
Shut it!
So prideful.
You're in command here
until I get back.
Choose 500 men and follow me!
Yes, sir!
[ZARAVANT] What is that up
there? Some sort of trap?
[ISFAN] Ha. They think to stop
us with a couple platforms
and a makeshift barricade?
Be careful. We haven't fully
assessed their defenses.
We should turn back and
report this to His Highness.
Ha. Go ahead.
We charge!
[TUS]
No, wait!
[CAVALRYMEN yelling]
Give the signal.
Yes, sir!
[growls]
We're cut off!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER C]
We're trapped like rats!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER D]
Slaughter the heathen scum!
[ALL gasp]
[ARSLAN]
Where are they now?
[NARSUS] It seems they
are completely cut off
from the rest of the army.
The survivors report that they
engaged a Lusitanian force
that was waiting
along the highway.
The enemy sprung a trap that
cut off our troops' retreat
and forced them
into the mountains.
[DARYUN] Is there any way
we can locate them?
[NARSUS] They are almost
certainly being pursued
by the enemy, and the sun
will be setting soon.
It won't be an easy to
find companies on the move
in the dark.
There's another option.
We can give them up for
lost and move forward.
However, that's not
my decision to make.
[ARSLAN]
There is no decision.
First call an immediate halt,
then prepare a rescue party.
[KISHWARD]
Huh.
As it happens,
I've already sent Elam and
Alfarid to scout the area.
As soon as they return, I'll
see that our men are retrieved.
[ARSLAN]
Do so.
I was too eager for glory.
If I die today, I can
only blame myself.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS yelling]
[NARSUS]
You had no luck finding them?
We saw no sign of them.
The cliffs in this
area form a maze.
We nearly got lost ourselves.
And there won't be
a moon tonight, either.
I don't think there's
anything else we can do.
[NARSUS] "Terrain's advantage"
goes to the enemy this time.
A situation I prefer to avoid.
Is there nothing we can try?
[gasps]
I think I hear something.
Silence! Everyone stop talking!
[music playing]
[FARANGIS]
Ah, the Djinn. Ever capricious.
It appears one has seen fit to
help us find our lost soldiers.
Oh, good.
Uh...
What's this?
[TUS]
It appears we're surrounded.
[ZARAVANT] Urgh. I came so
far to fight for my prince,
and this is how I end?
What a useless way to die.
I am truly a fool.
[TUS]
Consider it another way.
We'll be here keeping
the Lusitanians busy.
Which will allow the main
army to progress unscathed.
When you put it that way,
I believe our deaths
will have purpose.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
More Parsians.
Impossible!
They're ours. Let's go!
Right! With me!
I can't...
believe we were saved.
[ARSLAN]
Zaravant! Isfan! Tus!
[ISFAN]
Your Highness!
I am glad to see
you three are safe.
[ISFAN]
With all due respect,
we're grateful,
but why come for us?
You could easily have chosen to
give us up as sacrificial pawns
and ridden on ahead unharmed.
[NARSUS]
True.
It would have made for
a more relaxing evening.
[DARYUN] But we have a
momentous task in front of us.
We cannot afford to lose you
before we've even begun.
[ARSLAN]
Listen to me.
I'm sure many lives will
need to be sacrificed
in the fight to
regain our country.
[ARSLAN]
That said.
When it's over, I want as many
of my men standing as possible.
Instead of valorous deaths,
let us seek honorable lives.
Your Highness.
[TUS grunts]
[ISFAN]
If you still judge us worthy,
we ask permission to swear
our loyalty to you anew.
[FARANGIS] Were you going to
leave without saying anything?
It wasn't pretense when I said
that court life doesn't suit me.
[GIEVE]
Narsus has given me a task.
I don't plan to return
for quite some time.
Understood. I am not
here to stop you.
I would only deliver a
message from His Highness.
Will you hear it?
[FARANGIS] He said he is sorry
to have made trouble for you
to the very end.
[music playing]
What is life?
It is a risk.
An adventure. A journey.
And cannot the same
be said of death?
Time flies swiftly.
A bird with midnight
feathers and sharp talons,
bringing old age to a man in the
space of a single dark wingbeat.
[GEIVE] And with those
words, I leave you.
Think back on them when
the nights are lonely.
I will treasure them.
Although if that was a ruba'i,
it was a poor one indeed.
[GIEVE]
Hmph. Farewell, then.
[ZANDEH] We've received a report
from one of the sorcerers
that Arslan's army
is on the move.
They've passed by
Chasoom Fortress entirely.
It appears they are
continuing westward.
Oh, are they?
We should move, too.
Make the preparations.
Sir.
[HILMES]
Come, Arslan. I am ready.
The stage is set for
our final conflict.
I will be waiting
for you... eagerly.
[NARRATOR]
On the eve of battle,
Arslan found himself
contemplating
many weighty matters.
Such is the burden of
those who assume command.
Next time: "The Night
Before the Attack."
And thus, would the
boy become a king.