[NARRATOR]
Pars Era, the year 320. Winter.
Led by Narsus, the Parsian
army defeated Rajendra,
the Second Prince of Sindhura,
who had crossed the border into
Pars with an army at his back.
Rajendra was marched into
Peshawar as a captive,
but Arslan welcomed
him as a guest
and the two men entered
into an alliance.
Thus it was that the two armies
departed for Sindhura,
launching a campaign to
challenge Rajendra's brother,
the kingdom's First
Prince, Gadhevi.
[ALFARID]
Nice try! Don't think so!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[RAJENDRA]
Ah.
[PARS SOLDIERS cheering]
[RAJENDRA]
Prince Arslan.
Well done.
Once again, I am impressed by
the strength of your soldiers.
[ARSLAN]
That's kind of you.
[RAJENDRA]
I found Lord Daryun's valor
to be particularly magnificent.
Yes. I have better
companions than I deserve.
On the contrary,
that such people follow you
must be seen as proof
of your able leadership
and noble character.
I only regret I was
not able to see
Lord Kishward's prowess
in battle, as well.
I have heard much about the
Twin-Blade General's skill...
Listen to him.
I just cannot bring
myself to trust that man.
You're not alone in that.
I wonder what sort of
deception he has planned.
I do hope it's inventive.
[RAJENDRA laughing]
[MAHENDRA]
I have a task for you.
You will feign
support of Rajendra
in order to join his army.
[JASWANT]
Yes, sir.
It will be a
dangerous assignment,
but you must halt their
advance at all costs.
Do you understand?
Yes, Your Excellency.
My entire life, you have
been as a father to me.
Ask, and that life is yours.
[NARRATOR]
Pars Era, the year 321.
Arslan and his companions
welcomed the new year
in the wastelands
of western Sindhura.
They conducted the
new year's ceremony
in the Parsian tradition,
with Arslan standing
as the king's proxy.
[PARS SOLDIERS]
Arslan! Arslan!
The star shining in the heavens!
The favorite of the gods!
With your wisdom
and your strength,
may you bring peace and
prosperity to our kingdom
and all its people
in the coming year!
[GIEVE]
Alas.
Even the wine in my cup
holds no power anymore.
This may as well be water,
for only a glimpse of your
beauty can intoxicate me.
No, from the sound of it,
the wine seems to be doing
its job most adequately.
Here, you must be hungry.
[ELAM growling]
Please. I can eat
without your help.
I want to! Ahhh!
Can you not see that
you're irritating him?
Oh, please. Off with you.
You're not needed here.
You can both go.
The finest tactician
in the kingdom,
and he's helpless
against two children.
Glad to see you
as always, Azrael.
This is unexpected.
[RAJENDRA]
Whoa!
Prince Arslan! I come to pay
my respects upon the new year!
[ARSLAN]
Kind of you to take the trouble.
[RAJENDRA]
Mm.
And I am glad to
see your soldiers
enjoying their celebrations
though they are
so far from home.
And since I'm here, my friend
and brother-at-heart,
there is something I
would discuss with you.
If you have a moment to spare.
What is it you wish to discuss?
Rajendra's soldiers
and ours would continue
on different paths so that
we can strike Gadhevi's forces
from two directions?
[ARSLAN]
Yes, or at least,
that is the strategy that
Rajendra has proposed.
What say you?
[DARYUN] I mislike that man.
He is not to be trusted.
I advise that you decline.
I am afraid I must
agree with you.
No doubt the prince
proposed this plan
because he intends to
use our army as a decoy.
Would you not agree with my
assessment, Mistress Farangis?
Though it pains me, I do.
Rajendra is considering
his interests alone.
He will be best served if
we can draw attention away
from his army.
[ARSLAN] I'd feared you
would say as much.
I would hear your
thoughts, too, Narsus.
Your Highness, first, I
offer my congratulations.
[ARSLAN]
What?
[NARSUS] Well, it must
be a relief to learn
that none among your closest
advisors is a gullible fool.
It is just as you all have said.
Prince Rajendra intends
to advance his own cause
by using us as a decoy.
That said, I actually believe
you should agree to his plan.
[ARSLAN]
Why do you say that?
We can say with some certainty
that the prince
means to deceive us.
As such, it is better for us to
operate at a distance from him,
where we will have more freedom.
[ARSLAN]
That makes sense.
[NARSUS] But you should lay down
conditions when you agree.
Provisions, the oxen
to transport them, maps,
and a guide who can be trusted.
Make those your requirements.
[JASWANT] Pardon me. I was
sent by Prince Rajendra.
I am Jaswant, Your Highness.
the prince has selected me
for the honor of serving
as your guide.
[ARSLAN]
Please, be welcome.
Jaswant, is it?
[JASWANT]
Yes, sir.
If you wish it, I shall go
to the front of the army,
that I might direct its course.
Uh.
[yelps]
[JASWANT]
A venomous snake, sir.
Common in this area.
They remain active
during winter,
so it is best to be on
your guard at all times.
Yes, thank you. I'll remember.
[JASWANT] If you'll excuse me.
I'll be about my duties.
Provisions transport
team, form up now.
A fine way to welcome
a man. Who might you be?
[GIEVE] Sorry, target
practice. My hand slipped.
I'm Gieve, resident minstrel.
And what is your purpose here?
[JASWANT] I was sent to serve
as a guide to your army.
[GIEVE]
Hmm. Were you, indeed?
You're good with a sword
for a simple guide.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
[DARYUN]
That is no ordinary soldier.
Damn Rajendra.
Is he planning to
harm His Highness?
Yes, it is a possibility.
[NARSUS] Your Highness,
that is the Fortress of Gujarat.
There are a number of ways
that we might take it.
However, we cannot spare
much time in doing so.
Then, what do you advise?
I think our first step
should be sending an envoy.
Let us explore the possibility
of passing through
without a fight.
He's handsome for a foreigner.
[LADY-IN-WAITING A giggles]
[BOTH gasp]
[GIEVE chuckling]
Lord Fortress Commander Gauvin!
Make your obeisance.
So, the Parsians
have sent envoys.
Sir, my name is Gieve.
I am Jaswant, Lord Commander.
[GAUVIN]
Why have you come here?
[GIEVE]
We have come seeking a truce.
We ask that you grant the
Parsian army permission to pass.
[GAUVIN]
Do you know what you ask?
I could never justify
a truce to Prince Gadhevi.
He would have my head.
Naturally, we know
there are risks.
But once Prince Rajendra
has taken the throne,
he will be able to properly
demonstrate his gratitude
for such a service.
Whether you desire land or rank,
he assures me you will
be well rewarded.
[GIEVE]
What say you?
I must consider this further.
Very well.
Give us your answer tomorrow.
We look forward to
a favorable reply.
We've prepared a small
banquet to welcome you.
Come, let us show these
men our hospitality.
If you will please
follow us, Master Envoy.
Are you thirsty? We have
the most excellent wine.
And will you ladies
stay by my side
to do me the honor
of filling my cup?
Yes, it would be our pleasure.
We have food as well as drink.
[ALL chatting]
[GAUVIN]
What answer shall we give them?
[TAARA] If Pars is
siding with Rajendra,
as it appears they are,
that gives him the advantage
in the fight for the throne.
In which case...
That is true, but if we
support him and he doesn't win,
we'll be traitors.
If we don't agree, we'll have
to fight the Parsian army.
--[knocking]
--Hm?
Excuse me, sirs.
We didn't think to see
you again so soon.
Is something the matter?
[JASWANT] I wish to
discuss something with you.
But first, please look at this.
Sir, that appears to be the
signature of Lord Mahendra,
advisor to First Prince Gadhevi.
[GAUVIN]
Do you care to explain this?
As you've seen, I answer
to Lord Mahendra.
It is at his command
that I came here,
as he has charged me with
halting Rajendra's advance.
You should be aware. The man
Gieve plays you false.
He has made nothing
but empty promises.
Lying rat!
But I may have solution.
[JASWANT] The Parsians
sent envoys as a diversion.
Their strategy
is to distract you
with the request for a truce.
They will use the time
you spend deliberating,
to bring the army past
the Fortress unnoticed.
Shameless sneaks!
Only cowards would
plan such a ruse!
Where is that deceitful dog?
We'll see how the Parsians
feel when I cut off his head
and hang it at the gates!
[JASWANT]
If you will but wait.
The Parsian army is strong,
it would be better not
to confront them directly.
[GAUVIN]
Then, what are you suggesting?
We will outsmart them instead.
The Parsian column
is led by the cavalry,
who make up the main force.
At the rear is
the provisions team.
That is where we should strike.
The loss of supplies
will halt their advance,
and our casualties
will be minimal.
I will ride with them
and await the proper time.
At my signal, you will attack.
[GIEVE] I always find you
skulking about on your own.
What a lonely little
life you must lead.
[JASWANT]
You followed me?
The Black Cat of Sindhura.
That's what they call you, yes?
Well, kitty, I'm here to
clip those claws of yours
before they can do any damage.
[JASWANT] So you've known
who I am all along.
[GIEVE] Our Master Tactician
always seems to know more
than any man has a right to.
[GAUVIN]
Why has he not signaled yet?
Before long they will have
passed by the fortress entirely.
Can't wait any longer.
Launch the attack!
[GUJARAT SOLDIERS yelling]
[GAUVIN]
Target the supply wagons!
We're under attack!
Damn! Those aren't
supply wagons at all!
We've been trick--!
Cowardly dogs!
[yells]
[GUJARAT SOLDIER F]
Lord Gauvin!
We were tricked. I'm sorry, men.
Circle around!
The Parsian boy-prince!
For this, you die!
On your right!
[GUJARAT SOLDIER J]
Lord Gauvin is dead!
[GUJARAT SOLDIER I]
Quick! Retreat!
It should not be long now.
[GIEVE]
This battle is over.
The Fortress Commander is dead.
Will you surrender?
You were holding back earlier.
Do I seem the type who
enjoys giving up his secrets?
[ARSLAN]
Well done.
Tell me something.
Did you mean to betray
me from the beginning?
"Betray?" That word
doesn't apply.
I am a Sindhuran!
I followed the Grand Vizier's
orders as they were given to me.
It is not you to
whom I am loyal.
I assume you are sworn
to Prince Gadhevi?
[JASWANT]
No.
I obey Lord Mahendra,
the Grand Vizier of Sindhura,
who has been as a father to me.
Pardon, Highness,
but I would be happy
to permanently silence
this wretch's babbling.
Have patience, Gieve.
I wish to speak with
him a bit longer.
Jaswant, how is the Grand
Vizier like a father to you?
He raised me.
I was an orphan and never
knew who my father was.
But a man took me in
and cared for me.
That man was Lord Mahendra.
I would give my life for him.
Never knowing your own father.
That must've been difficult.
Now. End my life swiftly.
I am ready for it.
Certainly. I'm happy to oblige.
Hold your sword.
Untie him. I wish
this man released.
[gasps]
[GIEVE]
I suspected you might say that.
If Your Highness bids me,
I must of course obey.
We shall set the Black Cat free.
I hope we don't regret it.
For what it's worth, I think
you're being too soft,
but it is done.
And whatever harm may
result from this fit of mercy,
I suspect we can overcome.
Yes, I understand.
Thank you.
[ALFARID] I shall prepare
Narsus's meal tonight.
No, I will do it.
I know his preferences
better than you do.
I've spent years seeing to his
nutritional and culinary needs.
Ha, ha. Do you think
he'd rather have
a pretty girl cook for
him or a scrawny boy?
What do you say, Narsus?
[ELAM]
Whose food would you like?
[NARSUS] Uh. I can't decide, so
I'll sample both of your dishes.
Will that be satisfactory?
Yes!
I will prepare
your meal immediately.
I know you'll love it!
Ha! I'm sure Lord Narsus
will swiftly realize
that he needs no other
cooking than mine.
[ALFARID]
We'll see about that!
[groans]
[DARYUN chuckling]
You saw all that?
Yes. I found it
most entertaining.
[NARSUS grunts]
Ah, do not glare so.
Oh, foolish Elam.
He can still behave like
such a child at times.
[DARYUN]
He is a good boy, though.
And someday, when
Prince Arslan is king,
Elam will be at his
side to advise him.
And if you ask me,
Pars will be fortunate
to have them at the helm.
Agreed.
I only hope it will come to
pass before a decade is up.
Though, in all likelihood,
the prince is not
Adragoras' son,
and does not belong
to Pars' royal line.
That is true.
He must be aware
of it, as well.
[NARSUS] Nevertheless, I fully
believe he should become king,
for the sake of
Pars and her people.
Yes. As do I.
[GADHEVI] How could Gujarat have
fallen in a mere three days?
These Parsians must
be powerful indeed.
Forgive me, Prince Gadhevi,
but I believe the time has come
for us to ride against them.
Our troop strength is
still superior to theirs,
even with the combined force
of the two opposing armies.
And we mustn't forget that
we have the war elephants.
You are right. I had forgotten.
Even the vaunted
commander Andragoras
would not triumph against
the war elephants.
What hope could a boy
such as Arslan have?
[chuckling]
[roaring]
[ARSLAN]
It was reckless,
allowing Jaswant
to go free as I did.
But like him, I do not
know whose son I am.
[DARYUN]
Your Highness.
Perhaps you ought to
retire for the night.
The winter air has
a chill up here.
[ARSLAN]
Daryun.
Who am I? Do you know?
All I know... is that
I'm not of roya--
Please stop there,
Your Highness.
If you'd like, I will
tell you who you are.
Yes, please tell me.
You are my leader
and my liege lord.
You are the man for whom
I would gladly give my life.
Can that not be enough
for now, Your Highness?
[ARSLAN] Perhaps it can,
Daryun. Thank you.
[NARRATOR]
Magnificent and invincible,
the war elephants descend
upon the Parsian army.
What soldiers could stand
against such fearsome beasts?
Next time: "Elegy for
the Setting Sun."
And thus would the
boy become a king.