It's you.
No, it... it can't be.
Count Barcacion is dead,
and you killed him!
I know how it appeared, but
the count took his own life.
You lie!
[ÉTOILE yelling]
[ÉTOILE]
First, you duped me.
Then, as if that wasn't enough,
you killed somebody
precious to me!
And for doing that...
I'll kill you!
[yelling]
Your Highness!
I didn't know
their women fought.
Capture. Don't kill.
[PARSIAN SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[ÉTOILE]
Let me go! Get off of me!
Filthy heathens!
[NARRATOR] The battle for
the Keep of Saint Emmanuel
came to an end.
Its lord, Count Barcacion,
took his own life.
As did many of
the devout followers
of the God of Yaldabaoth.
The few remaining sick and
wounded were not slain,
but cared for by the Parsians.
By order of Crown Prince Arslan,
do not kill any unarmed person.
Spare all who surrender.
Daryun!
[ARSLAN]
I am here.
Thank the gods!
Are you hurt?
Your Highness.
It shames me to report...
Hilmes yet lives.
I was unable to finish him.
I don't care.
You're alive.
That's what matters.
And you're unharmed?
Yes.
It's over.
We have taken Saint Emmanuel.
[DARYUN] You led us
to victory, Your Highness.
That must be gratifying.
[ARSLAN]
It is. Thank you, Daryun.
[PARSIAN SOLDIER C]
Stay vigilant!
We'll need to search
every last room.
[PARSIAN SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
Victory is ours, at
least for the moment.
[PARSIAN MESSENGER A]
There are enemy survivors.
Not many, but we
have taken some.
See that cots are
set up in the prison.
We can tend to
their wounded there.
[PARSIAN MESSENGER A]
Yes, sir.
Wait.
[PARSIAN MESSENGER A]
Sir?
What of the company
that stormed the gate?
I'm sorry, sir.
None have been found.
[NARSUS]
I see. Thank you.
[ALFARID screaming]
Alfarid!
Narsus? What are you doing here?
Where are we? This is
an odd afterlife.
Wait, hold on! Am I still alive?
[NARSUS chuckling]
What's so funny?
Nothing. I'm just relieved.
[ALFARID] So, you were
a little worried about me.
Nonsense!
What woman of the Zot Clan
would ever allow herself
to be killed so easily?
[ALFARID]
True.
Especially when she has
a husband to look after.
I feel like I would remember
acknowledging that union.
[ALFARID]
What is this place?
[NARSUS]
A food storage room.
You must've lost consciousness
and fallen into the chute
they use to send food down.
That makes sense.
Doesn't explain what
you're doin' here though.
My first concern
after a victory
is always the seizure
of enemy provisions.
Why're you so
worried about food?
You've never gone
hungry, have you?
Without weapons,
a soldier can still fight
with an empty hand.
But left with an empty
stomach, all could be lost.
[ALFARID]
Hmm.
And I thought a strategist's
only duty was to plan battles.
[DARYUN]
I'm grateful for the assistance.
[JASWANT]
It is no trouble.
It was quite a battle.
I'm relieved that
you are all right.
I'm sure His Highness
must be, as well.
His Highness does not rely
upon me as he once did.
He has grown into
a strong commander.
I don't dispute that,
but to have injured a fighter
like yourself so gravely.
He must be formidable indeed.
This Lord Silver Mask.
He is a strange
and terrifying man.
His is a dark soul.
[KISHWARD] He must be
frightening indeed
to make the Knight
in Black speak so.
He most certainly sounds it.
[DARYUN]
Were it not for his caprice,
I would already be dead.
He had that chance?
Then why did he not act upon it?
From what he said, he thinks
he's toying with us.
If he defeats us, he wants
his victory to be absolute.
Insolent bastard.
Be careful!
The wound is bound.
I will be fine.
My place is at His
Highness' side right now.
Ah!
There's nothing
like a jug of khukar
after a hard day of killing.
Is it true? That you
were one of the Marzban?
That's what they called me.
Most interesting.
To be honest, I cannot
say I would've guessed it
from looking at you.
[KUBARD chuckles]
[KUBARD]
Well? Another?
[FARANGIS]
Yes, thank you.
[ARSLAN]
I will be fine.
[PARSIAN GUARD A]
Yessir.
You again!
My apologies for
isolating you like this.
Your behavior made it necessary.
It was true about
the count, then.
He took his own life.
Just as his attendants told you.
He was a fine man, you
know. True and faithful.
Yes.
Even in a short time,
I could see that.
In truth, he was
too kindhearted.
Not a man meant for fighting.
So, when we met in Peshawar,
that was you as you truly are.
It was not!
I am a knight in Count
Barcacion's service!
I am Étoile!
You must be quite hungry.
I brought you some stew.
No!
I will not accept charity
from a heathen prince!
This food was already here.
It belonged to your army.
I'm not hungry!
[stomach growling]
Think of it another way, then.
You believe that this food
belongs to your enemy.
So, if you eat it, you will
reduce your enemy's provisions.
And doing that can
only weaken him.
Isn't that the entire
goal of battle?
You're manipulating me.
Telling me what I wish to hear.
Yes, but just because it
is what you wish to hear
does not mean
that it isn't true.
At the very least, it's not
as if this will help you.
Care for some bread?
I'd like to know more about you.
What's your real name? Why
did you wish to be a knight?
[ÉTOILE] If you must know,
my real name is Estelle,
but I've abandoned it.
[ARSLAN]
Why?
It's a girl's name, obviously!
Anyhow, I was adopted
into a knight's household,
and that particular
house had no male heir.
That's it. That's why I
decided to become a knight.
But first, you
needed to be a man.
[ÉTOILE]
Exactly!
How many female knights
have you met recently?
I know what you're thinking!
Pretend that night never
happened! Forget it!
[ARSLAN]
Uh. Must I? That's a shame.
What did you say?
Oh, nothing.
I believe I would like to reduce
your provisions some more.
Ah, that can be arranged.
I have plenty here.
You're not how I heard
Prince Arslan described.
They said you had two twisted
horns and a long, black tail.
No one said anything about
a scrawny, pampered boy.
I'm only 14. Maybe
the horns will grow in.
[BOTH chuckle]
You are an odd one, aren't you?
I have been told that before.
I don't really see
it myself, though.
You don't act
like a king at all.
Maybe that's why
Pars lost her capital.
Like a king.
Say,
do you think war between our
countries could be avoidable?
What?
No. Absolutely not.
As long as you continue to
revere idols and false gods
and refuse to follow
the true faith,
we will continue to fight you.
"True faith"?
One that calls for the massacre
of heathens, correct?
Of course.
[ARSLAN] That is what
I cannot understand.
It's simple!
We worship different gods,
but that shouldn't mean we have
to keep on killing one another.
It means we have to kill you!
Is that?
Yes, it's the book you gave me.
I have read it many times.
I think it is full of fine
teachings and moral messages,
however, such teachings
are easily manipulated.
And I wonder if that's just
what your leaders are doing.
[ÉTOILE]
Uh.
What are you--?
To satisfy their own greed,
they invoke the name of your god
and induce your people
to slaughter others.
Does it truly seem right?
Such mindless killing?
[ÉTOILE]
Be quiet!
How could you say that?
You don't understand anything.
Just leave me alone.
I'm finished talking to you.
[ARSLAN] I am sorry.
I got carried away.
I did not mean to upset you.
[ARSLAN]
Étoile,
I assume you are familiar enough
with the prayers of your faith
to recite them.
[ÉTOILE]
Of course I can.
Well then, tomorrow,
perhaps you'd offer
a prayer for the dead.
The Lusitanian dead will
need a Lusitanian prayer.
[ÉTOILE]
Hey! Come back here!
Was that on purpose?
Stupid heathen.
[PARSIAN SOLDIER D]
What?
[PARSIAN SOLDIER E]
Is that a Lusitanian soldier?
So, you didn't die.
O, my brothers in arms.
My fallen comrades.
Sacred believers,
followers of the true faith.
By god's hand, may you
be blessed and sheltered.
O departed souls,
may you rest in peace.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER A] The Keep
of Saint Emmanuel has fallen.
Count Barcacion and most
of those who served there
fell during the battle.
The Parsian army led by
Arslan is yet at the Keep,
but they will likely leave
for Ecbatana any day now.
How were we so
soundly defeated?
Departed souls, may
you rest in peace.
And what of Lord Silver Mask.
He claimed to have
everything well in hand.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER A]
As to that.
[HILMES]
I am here!
How bold of you to return here
after suffering such a defeat.
Sadly,
the Keep of Saint Emmanuel
must not have been blessed
with the divine protection of
the God of Yaldabaoth.
Do not dare speak of god
in such an offhand manner!
This is a disaster! How will
you pay for your failure?
My failure?
[chuckling]
What do you find so amusing?
[laughing]
Men, seize this lunatic!
Have you lost your mind?
[HILMES] I wished to speak
with you more privately.
My real name is Hilmes.
And my father was called Osroes.
As was the former
King of Pars. Can it be?
Andragoras, the bloody-handed
usurper, killed my father.
He and his pathetic son,
Arslan, must be made to pay.
I will see to it
that they suffer.
And, that they know the throne
is lost to them forever.
[GUISCARD]
So that's it.
From the beginning, your
intention was to use my country.
Why have you decided to
reveal your identity now?
[HILMES] Tell me, what is
it you are truly after?
It isn't the throne of Pars.
I suspect our interests may
still be closely aligned.
I understand, and I
believe you are correct.
You can have it, then.
I shall relinquish the
throne of Pars to you.
In exchange, will you see that
I become king of Lusitania?
As you ask, so shall
it be, Your Majesty.
[PARSIAN SOLDIER F]
We've finished with this load.
Must we do this?
It seems such a waste.
Unfortunately,
we do not have the troop
strength to leave men here.
An empty castle makes a good den
for bandits we'd only
have to root out later.
Right.
[ALFARID] So, what's gonna
happen to the Lusitanians?
Surely we won't
simply abandon them.
[NARSUS] Mmm. You've hit upon
a troublesome situation.
While I hate to further
stretch our provisions...
It seems His Highness has
already made up his mind.
[ÉTOILE]
Are you all right?
I'm fine. Thank you.
[ÉTOILE] No thanks needed.
Rest if you can.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER D]
That hurts!
[ÉTOILE] Sorry! Try to
stay still. I'll be gentler.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER D groaning]
[ÉTOILE] I said stay still!
Your wound will re-open!
I'll try to be quick.
See, that's not so bad, eh?
It will be all right.
I will get us all home.
We'll see Lusitania
again too before long.
There!
[ELAM]
You're not much of a nursemaid.
Don't you have any
experience with first aid?
I have plenty!
[ELAM] Here, give it
to me. I'll teach you.
You asked His Highness that
you be allowed to come along
and tend to the wounded.
If that's what you wish
to do, fine, but do it well.
And don't let pride
get in the way.
There you are.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER D]
Ahh.
[ÉTOILE] Are you all right?
You must be weary.
It is nice to lay
back for a bit.
[ÉTOILE]
I'll go fetch some water.
A kind enough girl.
For a Lusitanian, anyway.
You're sure she's a girl?
She has the gallantry
of a knight.
That she does.
[FARANGIS]
You, Lusitanian girl.
Are you keeping
yourself occupied?
[ÉTOILE]
Stop referring to me as a girl.
It feels strange.
You serve him because you
want to? Of your own free will?
Yes.
I don't understand.
He's young and inept.
Why do you all follow
him so loyally?
The throne is only as good or as
bad as the one who sits on it.
If it helps, this is
how I think of it.
Depending upon who
occupies the throne,
it can be a seat of fairness
and justice or one of cruelty.
As long as it is a man
who governs, and not a god,
he can never do so perfectly.
But if he makes no attempt
to reach for perfection,
he will slide instead
into complacency.
Perhaps even into evil
if left unchecked.
Crown Prince Arslan
is always striving
to become a better ruler.
A better man.
Those of us who serve him
see it in everything he does.
It is what makes him
unique among men,
and the reason we are
happy to serve him.
And why are you here?
Ha!
I came to keep an eye on enemy
movements, nothing more.
You just watch yourselves!
[ALFARID]
Ugh, she's horrid!
I mean what was that even about?
She didn't have to come along.
If she hates us so much,
why is she here?
[ÉTOILE]
It'll be ready soon.
[ARSLAN]
Uh.
What is it? Why are you here?
[ARSLAN] I thought I would
return your sacred text to you.
Come here!
You're the Crown Prince.
This is imprudent!
Is it truly? I do this
sort of thing a lot.
What is wrong with this army?
Well, thank you for
lending me your book.
There's no need for
you to return it.
You'll want it when I convert
you to the Faith of Yaldabaoth.
Ha. I don't know
how likely that is.
Was that all you
came here to do?
Why?
Do you need my help
with something?
You are next in line for
the throne, aren't you?
You should learn to act like it!
[ÉTOILE grunts]
[ARSLAN]
Uh...
[BABY crying]
Ah! You have a
healthy little boy.
Lord Étoile, will you?
What is it? What's wrong?
Are you in pain?
Will you hold him for me?
Oh. I suppose so.
[crying]
[ALFARID] Are you trying
to make the poor thing cry?
Here, this is how
you hold a baby.
There, there, little one.
You're all right now.
Oh, I see.
Now you try.
Okay.
[ALFARID]
You're a strong boy.
You'll make a good
little bandit someday.
[ÉTOILE]
Don't say that!
He's to become a
knight of Lusitania!
[FARANGIS] May this child's
path be lit brightly
by the love and
compassion of others,
no matter what gods
they might believe in.
[laughing]
This feels as if it's been
a terribly long journey.
Yes. We started a war
that day, you and I.
Come, Daryun.
It's far too soon to begin
indulging in reminiscence.
You might lower your guard.
That's just ludicrous.
I don't even lower my guard
when I sleep at night.
Truly, Highness.
This knight of yours
can claim no other skill
than wielding a blade.
And what of you?
Besides devising your
"clever military stratagems,"
have you a single
talent to your name?
But of course I do!
Have you forgotten
that I am an artist?
Would that I could forget it!
[laughing]
[GIEVE] If ye have ears
to hear, I say, pay heed,
to the tale of the
fair Kingdom of Pars.
[GIEVE]
Ye of good conscience,
recall the reign of
the king known to history
as Arslan the Liberator.
For His Highness, I shall
find it. If it can be found.
The supposed proof of
his right to the throne.
Onward! To Ecbatana!
[NARRATOR]
Pars Era, the year 321. May.
Crown Prince Arslan, age 15.
And thus would the
boy become king.