[RAJENDRA]
Lord Daryun.
I wish to entrust you
with not only my own fate,
but with that of the whole
kingdom of Sindhura.
Are you willing to accept
this task on my behalf?
I don't relish the thought.
Surely your nerve
doesn't fail you.
Or are you suggesting
you are not confident
that you would
triumph in the duel?
Interpret my words
however you wish.
I serve Prince Arslan
and no other.
I will accept no
request to fight,
save that it come
directly from him.
I love my kingdom
and cannot allow it to be ruled
by a man such as Gadhevi.
I realize the gravity
of my request,
but, Prince Arslan,
will you not lend me
your aid in this?
I-- That is...
You ask a great deal.
But if this can avert a war and
resolve the succession, then--
[sighs]
[ARSLAN]
Daryun.
Might I ask you to do this.
A duel to determine the throne.
It strikes me as a last resort.
King Karikala must be desperate.
I beg your help.
[DARYUN]
Your Highness.
What answer can
I give you but this?
I fight at your command.
Dueling before the gods.
It is a grave responsibility.
To be honest, I'm
not very worried.
I feel fairly confident
I can defeat any warrior
they send against me.
[NARSUS]
Oh, I do not doubt your skill.
Nor though, do I doubt our
opponent's willingness to cheat.
Remain vigilant.
[DARYUN] We have a
great task ahead of us.
I find this detour irritating.
[NARSUS] I know you'd rather
continue our true mission,
but there is another
way to think of it.
When this matter is resolved,
word will spread of Prince
Arslan's wisdom and honor.
Such renown can only be
to our future advantage.
Support will likely increase
for our uprising against
the Lusitanians.
Well, in that case,
I truly cannot afford to
lose this duel, can I?
The day Lord Bahman
saved His Highness,
I thought upon my uncle's words,
and upon the oath
I readily gave him.
No matter what his parentage is,
Prince Arslan will always
command my loyalty.
[GADHEVI]
What?
Rajendra has that knight in
black acting as his champion?
This bout will determine
the fate of all Sindhura
and he's chosen a Parsian?
Has he no shame at all?
Whichever kingdom
he may be from,
no one denies this particular
knight's strength and ability.
Is there any man among our
own forces who can best him?
[GADHEVI]
There may, in fact, be someone.
[MAHENDRA]
Sir?
We've no choice but
to unchain Bahadur.
You cannot mean that, Highness.
He's too dangerous to--
Then name me
another of our men
who can defeat
the Parsian knight!
Forced to entrust my
fate to a wild animal.
It is a wretched thing.
However, I will do what I must.
[BAHADUR growling]
This isn't an especially
welcoming crowd, is it?
What do you expect?
Their king is dying and
their princes are at war.
[SPECTATORS chattering]
It's like some kinda
grand tournament.
We're not here to
enjoy ourselves.
I know that, thank you.
Ah! Good!
I have been waiting for you.
Welcome, Prince Arslan.
Naming an heir is
a momentous event.
I wanted to be here
to see you chosen.
I am deeply grateful
you have come.
This is my father,
King Karikala.
[SPECTATORS cheering]
Your Highness, this will be
a test of your statecraft.
Whatever happens,
you must remain calm.
[ARSLAN]
I am aware.
What is it?
This duel.
Today determines which
of those ambitious men
the gods of Sindhura favor.
It will be interesting.
[SPECTATORS gasping]
[SPECTATOR A] That's him.
The knight from Pars.
[BAHADUR growling]
--[thud]
--[GUARDS yelping]
[roaring]
[GUARDS whimpering]
[laughing]
A Parsian warrior.
I hope there's
some fight in you.
If you die too fast,
it won't be fun.
Is that even a man?
[ARSLAN] Prince Rajendra,
what is going on?
Who is this Bahadur?
Nothing to be
concerned about.
He will be no match for
Lord Daryun, I'm sure.
[GADHEVI]
Hm.
It will be all right,
Your Highness.
Whoever he faces,
Lord Daryun won't lose.
We all know that
a greater warrior
has never walked this earth.
[SPECTATORS yelling]
[MAHENDRA] We have gathered to
witness a duel before the gods.
At stake is the
throne of Sindhura.
The outcome of this
duel shall be considered
sacred and inviolable.
Neither party may
contest the results
once the fighting is over.
Now let the duel begin!
[yelling]
[gasps]
[growling]
[laughing]
That should've finished him!
[GIEVE] That thing cannot
possibly be human.
Animals who wear human flesh
can be found in many places.
But that is truly
a savage beast.
Lord Daryun would never lose
to a man, but this creature...
[ARSLAN]
Daryun.
[ARSLAN gasps]
[yelling]
[SPECTATORS gasp]
Daryun!
Yes. Now, Bahadur!
Kill that miserable man!
Finish him off and
make the Parsians regret
ever setting foot in
the Kingdom of Sindhura!
[RAJENDRA grunts]
[laughing]
Come on, Daryun.
He did it!
[ARSLAN]
Daryun!
[roaring]
[chuckling]
It will take far more than
that to kill my champion!
You've toyed with
him enough, Bahadur.
Kill him and make an end of it!
[RAJENDRA]
I have heard of this.
As you thought,
he's no ordinary man.
In addition to his size,
he is also insensible to pain.
[FARANGIS]
Such a man truly exists?
[RAJENDRA]
Yes.
[ARSLAN]
You coward!
You knew about this and chose
Daryun to be your champion
instead of risking yourself!
[RAJENDRA]
Prince Arslan, please!
[ARSLAN] If Daryun is killed
because he took up your fight,
I swear upon the gods of Pars,
I will take your head and
the head of that monster
and hang them from
your castle gates!
[KARIKALA] Calm yourself,
my young guest. I can explain.
Rajendra chose first.
Only then did Gadhevi
select Bahadur.
We know your knight
is a hero without equal.
Certain he had no better
option, Gadhevi freed Bahadur.
That he would do such a thing
shows how feared your
man is by his enemies.
Perhaps you should
do him the honor
of putting your faith in him.
It seems likely to me
that he has earned it.
[GADHEVI]
Rajendra,
I hope you are preparing
yourself to concede defeat.
Disgraceful.
No crown prince should
ever lose his composure
over such a trifling thing.
These Parsians are
truly a weak people.
Are you so blind, Gadhevi?
If you cared for your subjects
as the prince of Pars does,
if you cared even
half so much so he,
there would be no need for this
duel we are now witnessing.
I would've named you
my heir long ago
had you any compassion
in your heart.
There are more important
qualities than compassion.
[KARIKALA sighs]
I am not surprised
to hear you say so.
I grow impatient!
Settle this now, Bahadur!
[roaring]
I've never seen such strength.
Bring the monster down!
One way or another,
it will soon end.
[roaring]
Do it!
[yelling]
What're you waiting for,
you tupid brute?
I should've left you
in that prison cell!
One last blow.
[yelling]
[SPECTATORS gasping]
He carries a short sword?
He bided his time,
as though the broken long
sword was his only weapon,
and sure enough, his
enemy let his guard down.
Daryun's not a bad
tactician himself.
Astounding!
[KARIKALA]
Thus it ends.
Daryun has won the duel;
which means, Rajendra
is heir to the throne.
[SPECTATORS cheering]
Prince Rajendra!
[SPECTATOR C]
Hail, our future king!
[SPECTATOR D]
Prince Rajendra!
I can't believe it!
Why not? It's Lord Daryun!
Thank the gods.
Your Highness!
I'm relieved is all.
[GADHEVI]
I don't accept!
No! It must be wrong!
This verdict is unjust!
Any fool can see that!
Think about what you're saying.
You would challenge a judgment
made by the gods themselves?
[GADHEVI]
Cursed brother! Cursed gods!
Don't you see? Obviously
the gods are wrong!
He's only now
realizing something
I've known a long while.
The gods are constantly
making mistakes.
Yet it's always we humans who
live with the consequences.
Stop this madness, son.
They are wrong.
Correct their mistake
and yield me the throne.
Do not make me harm you.
[RAJENDRA]
You've truly gone mad!
[GADHEVI] If you'd only been
content to stay in your place,
none of this would
have happened.
Royal Guardsmen! Kill Rajendra!
He and his allies
are frauds and liars!
Men! The king is threatened!
Take the traitor Gadhevi!
[RAJENDRA'S SOLDIERS yelling]
Rajendra must die!
[GADHEVI'S SOLDIERS yelling]
[NARSUS] The interested parties
can resolve any further dispute.
Let's go. We don't wish
to be caught up in this.
[ALL gasp]
[ELAM]
Lord Narsus!
We were invited here! Louts!
Go! See His Highness to safety!
Quick, Highness, this way.
[GIEVE] Can we never leave
anywhere peacefully?
[GADHEVI SOLDIER D]
Don't let them get away!
[GADHEVI SOLDIER C] The Parsians
must be here as spies!
Capture them!
An outrageous accusation!
We came to help them
settle a dispute.
Not much for
gratitude, are they?
[GIEVE] Obviously, the
First Prince never thought
he and his monster
friend would be defeated.
He's quite the sore loser.
Come on!
[DARYUN]
Your Highness!
[GADHEVI SOLDIER G yelling]
[JASWANT]
This way!
That's the second time
you've saved me.
This is a quarrel
between Sindhurans.
If a royal guest
were to come to harm
upon the day of the
duel before the gods,
it would bring shame
to our kingdom.
[ARSLAN] You would help me,
Rajendra's ally?
That's the best you can do?
Kill my fool brother
and take the king!
I beg you, Prince Gadhevi.
We've been defeated.
It's time to accept that.
Are you a traitor?
Why else would you
defy me in this?
There was a duel
before the gods.
To deny its outcome
is unthinkable.
Please don't ask me to do so.
I ask again.
Find it within yourself
to accept this verdict.
It's true then. You have turned!
You're his creature!
Tell me, what deal did you
make with that dog Rajendra?
Your Highness, there
has been no deal!
This was decided by
the gods themselves!
You betrayed me!
You're liars, all of you!
Please stop.
See reason and bow your
head to your brother.
Silence, traitor!
He struck down Lord Mahendra.
Lord Grand Vizier.
You are nothing but a coward.
What are you doing, guards?
Kill the traitors!
I am your king now!
Why are you just
standing there? Attack!
Put away your weapons!
Hear me, Sindhurans!
I came to fight a sacred battle
that would determine
the fate of your kingdom!
If you object to the outcome,
step forward and
I will duel you next!
A Sher Senani is among us.
Hail the Sher Senani!
[SINDHURAN SOLDIERS]
Hear me, all of you!
Hear and be still!
[RAJENDRA] Gadhevi has
defied both a royal mandate
and the will of the gods.
Any who follow him will be
found guilty of high treason
and punished accordingly!
No, he's the traitor!
Why aren't you listening to me?
Kill them all!
That is enough.
Please, before you
shame yourself further.
Seize him!
[GADHEVI]
No! Let me go! Obey me!
[JASWANT]
Lord Mahendra!
Lord Mahendra... no.
Jaswant, is that you, boy?
Yes, it's me. I'm here.
Do not grieve so.
Death comes to all.
There is no need to
lament my passing.
I knew the darkness in GADHEVI's
heart, yet still I followed him.
I was a fool and thus
I received a fool's end.
I cannot believe such a thing.
My only regret is that I never
said how proud I am of you.
Jaswant, my son, heed me well.
Don't choose the
wrong path as I...
[JASWANT wailing]
[NARRATOR] Narsus had fully
perceived the peculiarity
of Rajendra's character.
The Sindhuran was
such a performer,
he even fooled himself.
[NARRATOR] Next time:
"Once Again Across the River."
And thus would the
boy become a king.