[ARSLAN]
Have we received word?
Yes. Sir, Gadhevi has
left from Uraiyur.
He's leading their
war elephants.
[GEIVE]
Hmph.
How shall we respond?
They will not be
easily defeated.
Even King Andragoras never
dared to face the elephants
in a direct conflict.
[ELAM]
There is more.
What is it?
Our reports indicate
that Rajendra has circled
his army behind Gadhevi's.
Well, of all the possible
situations I had considered,
we face the one that requires
the greatest creativity.
[NARRATOR]
Pars Era, early in the year 321.
Gadhevi's army took the field,
supported by war elephants,
whose invincibility
was well known.
Set to oppose them
were the allied forces
of Rajendra and Arslan.
But even together,
their numbers were less
than half that of Gadhevi's.
Today we defeat Rajendra, who
seeks a throne that is not his.
This usurper must be destroyed!
Gadhevi has lost every
battle he's fought.
He is inept as
leader and general.
He simply does not
deserve the throne!
[NARSUS] This is our ten
thousand Parsian troops.
Here are Gadhevi's 150 thousand.
And, finally,
Rajendra's 50 thousand.
We have them caught between us.
Ordinarily, that would
be a tactical advantage.
Yes.
But when the enemy
outnumbers us so severely,
it is of no significance.
Gadhevi could easily send
20 thousand of his men
against our forces,
keeping us neatly pinned down.
His remaining 130 thousand men
would be free to
strike at Rajendra.
In which case, we will
certainly be defeated.
This battle is beginning
to seem unwinnable.
[thud]
[GADHEVI] You dare to return,
you worthless cur?
It was thanks to you that the
Fortress of Gujarat was lost!
My abject apologies.
[GADHEVI growls]
[MAHENDRA]
Prince Gadhevi!
[MAHENDRA] Your anger
is justified, of course!
I humbly beg for
the chance to atone.
You would abase yourself so?
And for a mere spy?
[GADHEVI]
I shall honor this request.
Out of respect for Mahendra,
you will keep your head for now.
However.
Fail me again in even
the smallest way,
and I will show no mercy.
I will not disappoint you again.
We shall be triumphant.
Our fighting strength remains
vastly superior to theirs.
I cannot imagine a situation
in which we could face defeat.
I'm well aware of that.
Are you going to be
all right, Jaswant?
[JASWANT]
I am so deeply sorry.
My failure is inexcusable.
To have brought trouble
upon you, Lord Mahendra.
[MAHENDRA] I am fine.
It was not your fault.
We are simply faced with an
uncommonly resourceful enemy.
And, regrettably,
First Prince Gadhevi lacks
compassion for his people.
As it stands,
he will only continue to lose
the hearts of his subjects.
Is that what it takes?
The Parsian prince
cares for his subjects,
and they for him, as well.
[DARYUN] The scouts tell us
that Gadhevi has indeed
divided his army.
One group is headed
in our direction,
while the other has been sent
against Rajendra's army.
Once again, things are
progressing as you predicted.
The enemy is following
standard tactical practice.
However,
Gadhevi is mistaken if he thinks
Pars is a standard opponent.
To be honest,
I find the conflict between
Gadhevi and Rajendra
feels distressingly familiar.
I am assuming it
puts you in mind
of the struggle between
Prince Arslan and Prince Hilmes?
How could it not?
In time, His Highness will have
to confront Prince Hilmes.
What path will he take?
What will that
confrontation look like?
Will he be up to the challenge?
When that time comes,
His Highness's fitness to
rule will be scrutinized.
[NARRATOR] Pars Era,
the year 321. February.
Rajendra's army and Gadhevi's
army faced each other
across the battlefield, prepared
for a fierce and brutal fight.
Hear me, Rajendra!
You are the son of a slave.
It is past time that
you learned your place.
If you climb down from your
horse and prostrate yourself,
I will spare your
miserable life.
Ha! I don't dispute that your
birth is higher than mine.
And yet our father did not
formally declare
you crown prince.
How could he when he always
had me to compare you to?
You're too weak to be king.
Crush the usurper!
Launch the attack!
[JASWANT]
Don't let the river deter you!
[JASWANT] With the river
splitting the army like this,
we cannot make the most
of Prince Gadhevi's numbers.
Did their strategist
plan this, as well?
[GADHEVI'S CAVALRYMAN A]
Prince Gadhevi,
the front line is
being pushed back.
Send in the war elephants, now!
[RAJENDRA SOLDIER C]
Ready!
[RAJENDRA] He brought them
in sooner than I expected.
Let's bring the archers forward.
Shower those elephants
with arrows.
[RAJENDRA'S CAPTAIN A]
Take aim!
Fire!
[RAJENDRA'S CAPTAIN A]
Take aim!
Fire!
[RAJENDRA'S CAPTAIN A]
What're you doing? Fire!
[RAJENDRA'S ARMY screaming]
[RAJENDRA]
Impossible!
Elephants are warm
weather creatures.
They shouldn't be fighting
so well in the cold.
They must drugged.
There are compounds
that will send the beasts
into a mad frenzy
and make them fight.
Damn.
If we at least
had Pars's cavalry.
Have they not yet arrived?
[footsteps]
[RAJENDRA'S SCOUT A]
A report, Highness!
Sir, the Parsians are detained
at the Fortress of Gujarat.
They've been surrounded.
They what?
[RAJENDRA] This means
we can no longer expect
the Parsians to reinforce us.
[RAJENDRA'S SCOUT A]
It seems so.
[RAJENDRA gasps]
The true battle is over.
At this point it's
nothing but a massacre.
[RAJENDRA'S ADJUTANT]
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
[RAJENDRA SOLDIER E]
Sir! The cavalry is decimated!
[RAJENDRA SOLDIER F]
Our reserves have been used up,
as well.
There's nothing more we can do.
These men put
their trust in me.
I cannot allow any
more of them to die.
The battle's over.
[horn blares]
[RAJENDRA SOLDIER G]
The Parsians have arrived!
Prince Arslan, you've come.
[PARS ARMY yelling]
Is that a man, or a demon?
This all started because
I was going to save her.
[GADHEVI SOLDIER K]
Think you can turn your back?
An excellent idea, Gieve.
[RAJENDRA]
How have you come here?
I had word that you and your men
were trapped in the fortress.
I thought we'd lost
our reinforcements.
We were not as
trapped as we seemed.
What?
[NARSUS]
I would wager
the soldiers who breached
the fortress walls
are feeling more than
a little disappointed.
They'll most likely know
by now they were tricked
into guarding a harmless
pile of stones.
There's no one within
the fortress, sir!
What do you mean?
Where are they?
Excuse me, sir.
A few Parsian soldiers were seen
fleeing from the back gate.
They what? Sly dogs.
Their main force must have
escaped before we even arrived.
Arg! Damn them! Damn! Damn!
[laughs] I should've
expected this of you!
You're a masterful
schemer indeed.
You honor me with such
praise, Your Highness.
Still, the most critical
part of the plan remains.
We must find a way to neutralize
Gadhevi's war elephants.
Yes.
I promise, it can be done.
As you'll see, the true
worth of our cavalry
lies in their mobility
and tactical flexibility.
Charge the Parsian army!
They won't stand
against the elephants!
[MALE ELEPHANT TRAINER A]
Remember, our target is Pars!
[MALE ELEPHANT TRAINER B]
Crush them!
[DARYUN]
Now, men!
[PARS ARMY yelling]
Close ranks!
[GADHEVI laughing]
Just look. Unbeatable
Pars is retreating.
Even their vaunted cavalry flees
before my fearsome beasts.
[JASWANT] We must stop
the charge, Your Highness!
Please! Something is not right.
I beg you to stop the elephants!
And why would I do such a thing?
This is a golden opportunity
to annihilate the enemy.
We will run down their
army to the last man!
I shall ride, as well!
You're making a mistake.
What's that up ahead?
Is it a trap?
Stop the charge!
It isn't obeying my commands!
By the gods.
[NARSUS]
Given their size,
elephants are not naturally
nimble creatures.
And when they've been whipped
into a drug-induced frenzy,
there's no stopping them.
Fire at will!
[NARSUS] Arrows will not
pierce an elephant's hide.
Instead, we are shooting
spears tipped with poison
so striking a killing
blow is not necessary.
Stop the stupid beast!
We should have time
at this distance.
[ELEPHANT RIDER D]
Halt, you!
Stop, do you hear me?
[ELEPHANT RIDER D]
Prince Gadhevi, Your Highness!
It's Pars's black knight!
[GADHEVI'S CAVALRYMAN A]
Protect the prince!
[GADHEVI CAVALRY yelling]
So, we carry the same weapon.
Let him come. I will show him
my skill with the spear!
[DARYUN]
Hiyah!
Go! We ride for
the black knight!
[ELEPHANT RIDER D]
Yes, sir!
[GADHEVI yelling]
[GADHEVI yelps]
Prepare yourself.
[JASWANT]
Prince Gadhevi!
[GADHEVI]
What're you doing?
[JASWANT]
Please hold on.
You won't get away.
[ARSLAN]
Hold fire!
Please, stop. Put your bow down.
As you wish, Your Highness.
But this will now
be the second time
you have spared that man's life.
Though you are merciful,
I hope that mercy is repaid
with gratitude, not with blood.
[NARRATOR]
And so ended the battle
upon the Fields of Chandigarh.
Desperate, Gadhevi's forces
allowed the elephants
to be annihilated, and fled.
The battle was an
undisputed victory
for the allied forces
of Rajendra and Arslan.
[GADHEVI] Why did you
flee the battlefield?
And I am not interested
in any feeble excuses
about saving my life!
Your Highness. I've no excuse.
[GADHEVI]
By leaving the field of battle,
I assured the defeat of my army.
A First Prince
should never flee!
Surely flight is
better than death.
[GADHEVI] Focus on assuring our
victory, not arguing with me!
I will not tolerate
another defeat!
I understand
completely, Highness.
Well. Isn't that a load off.
My heart is troubled.
I may have made a mistake
in whom I chose to advise.
[JASWANT]
I must apologize again.
Once more, my actions have
resulted in your disgrace.
Whether he sees fit to
thank you for it or not,
your intervention
is the only reason
Prince Gadhevi is still alive.
We have one hope.
The walls of the Royal
Capital are all that stand
between Rajendra and
the throne of Sindhura.
You must see that they hold.
I will do all I can.
I cannot promise to succeed,
but you have my word I will
serve you well and faithfully.
[GADHEVI SOLDIER L]
Pardon, sir!
An urgent message.
The king is awake!
[BOTH]
What?
[GADHEVI]
Lord Father!
Come closer.
Is that you, Gadhevi?
I am glad to see you have
recovered some of your strength.
And everything is well here?
Yes.
Go call Rajendra
into my chamber.
I should like to
see his face as well.
It saddens me to
tell you, Father,
but Rajendra seeks to kill me.
He would take my place
in the succession.
He what?
[GADHEVI]
He has gathered soldiers to him,
men who should be loyal to me,
and even now he seeks
to invade the capital.
I beg you, Father,
put an end to this violence.
Punish my brother
as he deserves,
and formally declare me the
heir to Sindhura's throne.
Foolish boys.
The kingdom is not
a toy to squabble over
like spoiled children.
I had thought you
would grow out of this.
[GADHEVI] But if you would
only name me heir.
It is too weighty a
decision for a sick old man.
And so I will not make it.
Instead this will be settled
by those with greater wisdom.
Let it be known:
The next heir of Sindhura
will be determined by
a duel before the gods.
A duel before the gods, you say?
[RAJENDRA]
Hm.
And what is that, exactly?
[FARANGIS] My understanding
is that in Sindhura
such a duel is something of an
alternative to holding a trial.
The two who have a
quarrel fight one another.
The victor is recognized
as the righteous one,
having been chosen by the gods.
Is that right?
[RAJENDRA]
Yes. That is a good description.
Essentially, Gadhevi and I are
to meet in single combat,
and whoever wins will
be named the next king.
It seems to me the king
of Sindhura didn't care
to take responsibility
for the succession
upon his own shoulders.
So instead he simply foisted off
the decision onto the gods.
It is strange.
A man wins a fight,
so his cause is righteous?
I find that troubling.
As you say.
It's a rather flawed method
of settling a dispute.
However, for our purposes,
it is not without merit.
How so?
It ends the need for our armies
to keep slaughtering
one another.
A duel will settle everything
with but a single casualty.
[RAJENDRA] There is another
factor to consider.
The combatants can name
champions to fight for them,
and though it wounds my pride,
I have a great favor to ask.
Brave Lord Daryun.
I ask you to serve as
my proxy in this duel.
Prince Arslan, Lord Daryun.
I beg of you. Grant me this.
[NARRATOR]
Arslan has no more loyal subject
or fierce protector than Daryun.
Will it prove a mistake
for the prince to risk
his Black Knight fighting
for another man's cause?
Next time: "The Duel
Before the Gods."
And thus would the
boy become a king.