[NARRATOR]
After leaving Kashan Fortress,
Arslan's company
found themselves
relentlessly harried
by the Lusitanians.
Forced apart, they continued
separately toward Peshawar.
--[DARYUN grunts]
--[SOLDIER A groans]
[SOLDIERS groan]
[DARYUN] How many men
have they sent after us?
It appears the enemy
is rather determined
to prevent us from
reaching Peshawar.
[DARYUN]
Hm.
We should hurry.
I dislike being away from
the prince for long.
[NARSUS]
Several dozen horses.
The Zot Clan, I expect.
They may not appreciate my
presence in their territory,
but this is the shortest
route to Peshawar.
That's the one we're
looking for, Chief.
The one in the strange
silver mask.
[ZOT CLANSMEN cheer]
[NARSUS]
A silver mask?
It's the Zot Clan!
Ah!
[ZOT CLANSMEN laughing]
This is Zot territory,
stranger.
We'll be taking your
gold and weapons.
[HALTASH]
Heh.
I won't ask again.
You're a savage.
More of a monkey than a
man from what I can see.
Why in the world
would I listen to you?
[HALTASH growls]
You bastard!
[HALTASH groans]
How could you?
You should consider it an honor
that your petty chieftain
died by my hand.
[ZOT CLANSMEN murmuring]
[whimpers]
[yells]
[growls]
[ZOT CLANSMAN A]
For the chief! Fight!
[SOLDIER F gags]
[ZOT CLANSMAN I groans]
[ZOT CLANSMAN N groaning]
[ALFARID growls]
[HILMES] A big sword for a
little girl. What's your name?
I'm Alfarid, daughter
of the Zot Clan Chief.
You... you killed my father!
[HILMES]
Alfarid, is it?
That's a name better
suited for a lady of noble
or even royal lineage, not
a painted savage like you.
I ought to punish you
for such presumption.
[ALFARID]
Go ahead and try!
[ALFARID yelps]
[ALFARID growls]
I'll kill you!
[ALFARID yells]
[ALFARID screams]
[HILMES]
You move well enough.
Unfortunately for you, the same
cannot be said for your men.
[ALFARID whimpers]
[HILMES]
What else would you expect?
This is what happens
when bandits
pit themselves against a king.
Die, filth.
[SOLDIERS scream]
What now?!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Ah, the inept painter!
We meet again.
Have you come all
this way in search
of somebody who likes your work?
I wish you would
stop following me.
You may not realize this,
but I don't much care
for your company.
Where have you
hidden Arslan away?
I will be happy to whisper that
to your corpse in just a moment.
Think you can do it?
Possibly. There is only one
way to know for certain.
This is not your fight!
It was my father and my
friends that he killed.
That makes him mine!
But you're unarmed.
You'll never defeat
him without a sword.
Then lend me yours.
It looks good enough.
[NARSUS] Do you have any
collateral for such a loan?
[ALFARID] I'm trying
to avenge my dead father
and you're asking
me for collateral?
Can you blame a man
for being prudent?
I don't know anything
about you, after all.
You're quite a charmer, huh?
I bet all the ladies want you.
Ha. You may not see it,
but I'm doing you a favor.
You won't win a fight
against that man.
You'd only be throwing
your life away.
You don't know that!
Please, just stay back.
It's past time to
put an end to this.
[NARSUS]
He is very good.
Any moment now...
[HILMES] Well, painter.
No, I'm sorry. Narsus.
Oh? Kind of you
to remember me.
[HILMES] You are a man
of great ingenuity.
It would be a shame to kill you.
Bend the knee now, and
I shall let you serve me.
[NARSUS]
Heh.
[HILMES]
You find something amusing?
I've never met a fighter
who could match your
skill with a sword,
but you lack a quality that all
truly great rulers must have.
[HILMES]
What is that?
Humility.
Prince Arslan is far better
suited to the throne than you.
He would never order
a man to serve him.
[HILMES]
You dare!
[HILMES yells]
--[rumbling]
--[SOLDIERS murmur]
[SOLDIER I]
He's escaping!
[SOLDIER J screams]
[SOLDIERS scream]
[SOLDIER L groans]
Lord Silver Mask!
Are you all right?
[ARZHANG] So, he got
away from you again.
[ARZHANG chuckles]
[ALFARID] I'll kill him
the next time I see him.
I swear on my life I will!
[NARSUS]
I'm glad you kept your head.
If you had attacked
him back there,
you would likely now be buried
in rocks along with his men.
[ALFARID cries]
[ALFARID]
I had to live.
I couldn't avenge my
father and clan if I died.
I'm glad you see that.
[ALFARID]
They're gone. All gone.
[ALFARID sobs]
I bet you've never seen one
of the Zot crying. Thank you.
I don't know what you're
thanking me for.
[ALFARID] Yes, you do.
You saved my life back there.
So... so, thank you.
[ALFARID] You know,
you're nicer than I thought.
That's worth something, yes?
[ALFARID] I just realized
I owe you my life,
and I don't even know
your name. What is it?
My name is Narsus.
[ALFARID]
Given what happened,
I can't say it's nice to
meet you, but I'm Alfarid.
[NARSUS]
Well met.
[ALFARID] It's a lucky
thing that rockslide
earlier happened when it did.
If not for that, I don't know
how we would've gotten away.
[NARSUS]
That wasn't luck.
It happened because
I made it happen.
[ALFARID] What? But how
could you cause a rockslide?
With magic or something?
[NARSUS] Making a few
rocks fall down a hill?
That doesn't require magic.
Just a leather thong,
a piece of wood,
and a little knowledge
about levers.
[ALFARID]
Levers?
[NARSUS]
Yes. It's simple, really.
The force created by
the thong applies torque
to the piece of wood,
then that force--
[ALFARID] I have no idea
what you're saying.
You're a pretty smart
man, aren't you?
Not bad with a sword, either.
What else would you expect?
This is what happens
when bandits
pit themselves against a king.
[ALFARID]
I've been wondering...
Tell me. How old are you?
[NARSUS]
Twenty-six, why?
[ALFARID] Really? Looking at
you, I wouldn't've guessed it.
I thought you were at
least a little younger.
[NARSUS] Terribly sorry
if I've disappointed you.
[ALFARID]
No, it's all right.
There are exactly ten
years between us.
Maybe that's lucky or something.
Plus, someone older is
probably more dependable.
[NARSUS]
Uh!
[ALFARID]
All right! It's settled.
I've decided that
I'm coming with you.
There are other members of
the Zot Clan who still live.
Don't you need to go back?
[ALFARID]
No, I don't.
[NARRATOR] One month
after the fall of Ecbatana.
There were three powerful
Lusitanians vying for control.
Archpriest Bodin, who
commanded the Temple Knights.
The king's brother, Guiscard,
who had the full support of
the military and the ministers.
And the king himself,
Innocentis the Seventh,
who had lost the
trust of his subjects
due to his affection
for the heathen queen.
As tensions between these
factions continued to rise,
something occurred
that tipped the scales.
Hildigo, Commander
of the Temple Knights,
was assassinated.
[BODIN]
I've misjudged you!
You are an apostate,
and no true king!
God will punish you
for what you have done!
What? Archpriest!
I don't know what
you're speaking of!
I opposed your marriage
to the heathen temptress,
and you retaliated
by killing Hildigo!
No, never! I--
[BODIN]
I won't hear your lies!
Your depravity is a curse
upon this kingdom!
God will surely smite you!
But, Guiscard, please!
Bodin is obviously under
some sort of misapprehension.
You can help clear
this up, can't you?
You may not be aware
of this, Archpriest,
but the ever-virtuous Commander
of the Temple Knights
was not alone
when he was killed.
[BODIN]
What's this?
In fact, when he was found,
he was sharing his bed
with a heathen woman.
What? Such slander is bold
even for you, Guiscard.
That's nothing short
of blasphemy!
[GUISCARD]
What of Hildigo?
Is bedding with a heathen
not blasphemy, as well?
To imagine the Commander
of the Temple Knights
would commit such a sin!
Do you think the men below
him will follow his example?
No doubt his death
was divine retribution.
And for such a thing to have
happened right under your nose.
Who will listen to your
zealotry now, I wonder?
[BODIN growls]
You were responsible for this!
One other thing.
Given the circumstances,
we saw fit
to lower the banner of the
Faith of Yaldabaoath for now.
[BODIN]
You had no right to--
[GUISCARD] So sorry for not
informing you until now.
[BODIN]
How dare you!
They've lost their commander,
they have lost their
virtuous reputation,
and they have even
lost the sacred banner
that is the symbol of
the church's authority.
[BODIN growls]
[GUISCARD] What are
the Temple Knights now
but a motley crew
of common soldiers?
[BODIN] You will go to Hell
for this, I swear it!
[SUBORDINATE B]
Prince Guiscard.
Bodin has departed Ecbatana,
and he's taken the
Temple Knights with him.
[GUISCARD] Well, that rids
us of one inconvenience.
[SUBORDINATE B] Reports have
them heading for Maryam, sir.
[ELAM] We should arrive at
Peshawar soon, Your Highness.
You must be tired. But we
won't be riding too much longer.
[ARSLAN]
Please. I'm bearing up.
This is the farthest
I've traveled in my life.
It's been quite an experience.
There must be so many more lands
that I've never
seen or heard of.
[ELAM]
That may be true.
The legendary cities to
the southwest, for example.
Do you know of them?
No, I can't say I do.
[ELAM]
Far to the southwest of Pars,
there is a vast, empty desert.
But beyond that wasteland lie
the City of Bronze and
the City of Pillars,
two places only spoken
of in legends.
[ARSLAN]
They sound fascinating!
[ELAM]
When I'm old enough,
I hope to journey to such places
and make a study of them,
learning all the lost
histories and legends.
[ARSLAN] So, that's
your life dream, then?
[ELAM]
Yes.
[ARSLAN]
Well, someday
when you've learned all
these histories and legends,
I hope you'll
share them with me.
Uh?
You'll have such
stories to tell.
I'm excited even now,
just thinking about it.
If that is Your
Highness's wish.
It most certainly is!
Ah! Then I'll be glad to.
[GIEVE]
So much chatter.
You've grown awfully friendly
with the prince, Elam.
I... I meant no disrespect.
[GIEVE] Your Highness,
we can see it now.
That's Peshawar,
there in the distance.
[ARSLAN gasps]
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER A]
If you beg for mercy, I might--
[grunts]
I've never cared for
men who talk too much.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER B groans]
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS groan]
[ZANDEH]
The rest of you stay back.
I intend to kill
this one myself.
So, he did come after me.
And I don't think
he's likely to stop.
Today I'll take the head
from your shoulders,
and see my father avenged.
Your father is to blame
for his own death.
It was his decision
to betray his kingdom
and become a pawn
in Lusitania's game.
He was no traitor!
Andragoras stole the throne
and had no right to
be called Pars's king!
[ZANDEH grunts]
We serve the man worthy of the
crown, not the man who stole it!
It is we who serve the
rightful king of Pars.
Who is this "rightful king"?
[DARYUN gasps]
[ARZHANG] More observant
than I gave you credit for.
[DARYUN]
What?
[FARANGIS]
Earth-travel magic?
[ZANDEH]
Hm? And who are you?
We serve the same
master, Lord Zandeh.
I'm here to provide help,
should you require it.
[ZANDEH]
Do as you like.
This makes things harder.
--What are these tricks?
--He's using sorcery.
I was unaware the enemy had the
likes of him in their arsenal.
[DARYUN gasps]
[ZANDEH yells]
[FARANGIS, DARYUN gasp]
[FARANGIS grunts]
[ZANDEH] You serve the son of
a usurper! You are traitors!
We are the true and
loyal subjects of Pars.
[DARYUN] The son of
a usurper, you say?
[ZANDEH grunts]
[DARYUN] It doesn't matter
who this master you serve is.
Nor does it matter to me
what Prince Arslan's
origins might be. I intend
to protect him and--
[ARZHANG yells]
[DARYUN gasps]
[DARYUN groaning]
[ZANDEH]
I have you!
[DARYUN grunts]
[ZANDEH grunting]
[ARZHANG chuckles]
[DARYUN grunting]
[ARSLAN]
Daryun!
How else can I help?!
At your feet! Watch the ground!
[ARSLAN groaning]
[ELAM]
Your Highness!
[ARSLAN]
Thank you, Elam!
[ARSLAN, ELAM groan]
Unwise to look away!
[DARYUN yells]
[ZANDEH screams]
[DARYUN]
Uh!
That is my prince!
And you will not harm him!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS groan]
[GIEVE]
Hmph.
[ZANDEH]
Daryun!
[yells]
[DARYUN grunts]
[ZANDEH groaning]
--[ZANDEH panting]
--[FARANGIS] Disgraceful.
[DARYUN] Forgive me!
I can't apologize enough.
I am ashamed to have
placed you in such danger!
[ARSLAN] It's quite
all right. I am unhurt.
Due to Elam's speed,
so thank you.
Oh, it was nothing.
How many times have
you saved me, Daryun?
Is it so terrible if I return
the favor once in a while?
[ARSLAN]
Where has Gieve gone?
[ELAM]
Uh?!
[GIEVE]
Dearest mistress of my heart!
I've been sleepless
with worry for you
every night since
we parted ways.
And I have no doubt
that you were suffering
in a similar fashion.
[FARANGIS] On the contrary,
my nights were untroubled.
You are the sort of man
who will always survive,
even if it means cheating
the gods themselves.
[GIEVE]
You know me well!
You must also know
if it meant seeing you,
I would happily cheat
the gods five times over.
[sighs]
I'm glad we were able
to meet up again.
It wasn't the same without
you. I need you by my side.
It's kind of you
to say so. My thanks.
[ARSLAN]
Heh.
[DARYUN]
The throne doesn't matter.
[DARYUN] It is for the sake
of this young man himself
that I will continue
to wield my sword.
[NARRATOR] Silver Mask's heart
brims with loathing for Arslan.
If hatred alone could kill,
the prince would be in
grave danger, indeed.
Next time, "Two Princes."
And thus would the
boy become a king.