[NARRATOR] Pars Era.
The year 321. February.
Daryun emerged victorious
from the duel before
the gods in Sindhura.
The people of that kingdom
lauded his valor,
hailing him as Sher Senani,
the Fierce Tiger General.
Driven out of his
mind with jealousy,
Gadhevi turned his sword against
his own father, King Karikala,
and was imprisoned.
The Sindhuran throne
passed to Rajendra.
I know you have much to do.
I'll try to be brief.
Please, Father.
I am never too busy.
Summon me at any time,
and I'll come to your side
as swiftly as I can.
I would ask something
of you. A final request.
Yes, anything.
Your brother's
actions were wrong,
but for my sake, can you find
it in your heart to forgive him?
I do not have much
time remaining now.
I would die in peace,
but I cannot bear the idea
of leaving this life
knowing that one of my sons
will kill the other.
Then rest easy.
Gadhevi is my brother.
I could not bring myself
to take his life.
I shall have him placed
in the care of a temple.
Thank the gods,
and you, as well.
Thank you for your
mercy, Rajendra.
[RAJENDRA] It is not
my place to seek revenge.
Rather, I must work
to reunify Sindhura
in the wake of this conflict.
[RAJENDRA]
Now, try not to speak any more.
You must be careful
not to exert yourself.
You have grown from a
brave boy into a fine man.
I know now that I was not wrong
to yield the throne to you.
My mistake was in not
turning it over sooner.
[DARYUN]
I hope he's found peace.
Although his decisions were
not always the most wise,
it seems he was still a
good king to his people.
Yes.
That's plain from
the number of subjects
who have come to mourn him.
Indeed.
And I believe he was as good
a father as he was a king.
That is quite a display.
But if he hopes
to be convincing,
he may be overdoing it.
I suspect those tears are real.
I don't think it's an act.
Oh?
Then you think his love
for his father is greater
than his thirst for power. Huh.
Well, I wouldn't
go quite that far.
All you need to
know about Rajendra
is that the man is
a born performer.
Such a performer, in fact,
that he can even fool himself.
[DUNGEON GUARD]
Get up.
[JASWANT]
Prince Arslan. It was you, then?
You're the one who had me freed.
[ARSLAN]
Yes.
To be more specific, I had
you placed in my custody.
If that is the case,
I suppose I owe you my thanks.
[ARSLAN]
Now that you're free,
what does the future
hold for you?
[JASWANT] That is something
I cannot answer yet.
All I know for certain is there
is no longer a place for me
in this kingdom.
As different as we may be,
you and I have
something in common.
And what is that?
We both have uncertain origins.
My parentage is a mystery, also.
I am called the Crown
Prince of Pars,
but my true station
may not be so lofty.
And yet, they
remain loyal to me.
Daryun, Narsus, all of them.
In turn, I strive to be worthy
of the faith they place in me.
If you wish, there is room
for you in my company.
You would take me in?
I'd be honored to.
You say you have no
place in Sindhura?
Well, you have one with me.
Prince Arslan, there you are.
I have been looking for you.
Good day, King Rajendra.
How may I be of help?
We are going to be holding
a banquet this evening.
I apologize for the
lateness of the invitation,
but I wonder if I might
I ask you to attend
as a guest of state?
That is quite sudden.
A banquet for whom?
[DARYUN]
I don't understand this.
Gadhevi may be royalty,
but he committed treason.
And they're holding a
banquet in his honor?
[NARSUS]
Seems odd, I know.
It is tradition in Sindhura
to offer a royal prisoner
good food and wine
before he is executed.
Well, that's kind of them.
The process is likely less
painful for the condemned
if he's in a drunken stupor.
[FARANGIS]
Knowing that,
Gadhevi must suspect he's eating
the last meal of his life.
Does something
trouble you, Brother?
You don't seem to have much
of an appetite this evening.
[GADHEVI]
It has been difficult for me,
but I am ready to admit it.
The gods have spoken.
The throne is rightfully yours.
Oh?
[GADHEVI]
I will swear my loyalty to you
and place myself
in your service.
If I do, then surely you'll
allow me to live, won't you?
Please stop.
It hurts me to see you beg
for your life so pitifully.
Are we not brothers?
Do we not share the same blood?
So... then you'll...?
[SUBJECT A]
It's the Crown Prince of Pars!
[SUBJECT B] I didn't know
he was attending tonight!
[SUBJECT C]
Ah! Prince Arslan!
[GADHEVI]
The young Parsian prince.
Ever since he came to Sindhura,
things have gone badly for me.
If only he had never
set foot in our land.
If only he stayed in his own
kingdom, where he belongs.
Restrain yourself, Gadhevi!
[GADHEVI]
You!
[yells]
[GADHEVI yelling]
This is all your fault!
I'll make you pay!
[GADHEVI screaming]
I don't know why I
expected better of you.
Perhaps father will
know what to do with you
in the world beyond this one.
Unhand me! Insolent fools!
[RAJENDRA]
Do it.
[GADHEVI]
No! No, stop!
How are you faring?
We were always
ill-suited as brothers.
Perhaps if we'd been unrelated.
Well, no sense in wondering now.
The rivalry between us
has truly come to an end.
I'm sorry. I feel at fault.
No. You mustn't, please.
After all you've done
for me, I am grateful.
But that's enough of
such unpleasantness.
You'll soon be returning
to Pars, will you not?
I will.
We plan on leaving
tomorrow, in fact.
Going home to drive
out the Lusitanians
once and for all, eh?
[ARSLAN]
Yes.
[RAJENDRA]
Hmm.
You know, if I were making
the strategy for Lusitania,
I would try to rile up
Pars's neighbors.
Which kingdoms did
you have in mind?
You have Turk to the east
and Turan to the northeast.
I would send envoys to both.
Incite them to violate
Pars's borders.
Which would leave
Lusitania perfectly poised
to attack us from behind.
Then you think I've
read the situation?
Yes. Narsus has spoken of
that possibility, as well.
Has he? In that case,
maybe you would like my help
devising your strategies, too.
But, fortunately,
Narsus also listed off
seven possible ways
we could foil such a plot.
Sorry. Seven, you say?
Yes. Impressive, eh?
[RAJENDRA]
Quite.
I would be interested
to hear more about them.
He refused to provide any
further details, even to me.
Seems they're confidential.
[RAJENDRA]
Oh.
[ARSLAN]
Hm.
[RAJENDRA]
Well, enough about that for now.
I'd like to discuss
the promise I made you.
That in exchange for your
help against my brother,
I would offer you my help
against the Lusitanian invaders.
Right.
It is time I fulfilled
that promise.
I know how great
a debt I owe you,
and as long as it
is within my power,
I will assist you in any way.
Land, I'm afraid,
I cannot offer you.
But perhaps provisions or funds.
Or lovely ladies for company?
Let me think.
Very well. If you would lend me
five hundred or so soldiers.
Is that all?
A mere five hundred soldiers?
You would think
we were strangers
for you to ask so
little. Come now.
I will lend you three
thousand cavalry.
Oh, no. I couldn't possibly.
It's done! Three thousand!
Any fewer, and people will
think I don't repay my debts.
Well, I certainly wouldn't
want to embarrass you.
Three thousand cavalry it is.
Good!.
As your brother-of-the-heart,
it's the very least I can do.
[RAJENDRA chuckles]
Your Majesty, what
are you thinking?
We cannot spare so many
men at a time like this!
We have not yet even
fully restored peace
within our own borders!
To loan out troops
now is foolhardy!
[RAJENDRA]
You don't see it, do you?
Those three thousand
men are the kindling.
They'll start a fire that
reduces the Parsians to ash.
I don't understand.
Daryun and his men
may be mighty fighters,
but surely even they will fall
if undermined from within.
To turn on them like that.
They held up their end of
the bargain, didn't they,
Your Majesty?
And that is why I am
going to help them.
Prince Arslan.
I actually grew to like
the sentimental little fool.
By playing this trick on him,
I will help him to
mature as a ruler.
I imagine it will be a rather
educational experience for him.
So whatever happened
to that bastard, anyway?
Which one?
You know. Jaswant.
He didn't end up
coming with us, did he?
No, I don't believe so.
That suits me just fine.
After all that has happened,
I don't know how
we could trust him.
So, Daryun,
how do our borrowed
soldiers fare?
Do they seem to
be adjusting well?
[DARYUN] You mean General
Kunthavai's company?
They are well officered.
And they respond readily
to orders from our men.
I expect they would already
be useful in a fight.
[NARSUS] I see.
That's good to be aware of.
Your Highness, the sun
will be setting soon.
Shall we find somewhere
to make camp?
[RAJENDRA'S ADJUTANT]
It has begun.
Sly old Kunthavai.
I knew he was the right
person for this task.
Let's go! They're
ripe for the picking!
[RAJENDRA'S ARMY yelling]
Prince Arslan is
not to be killed.
I want him taken captive
and brought to me!
What?
[RAJENDRA] There's nobody here.
What's going on?
[RAJENDRA]
Kunthavai!
You cowardly, faithless liar.
This is what comes of
plotting against Pars!
[ELAM]
Hmph.
We're found out! It's a trap!
Retreat! Retreat!
Archers!
Rajendra!
[yelling]
Damn!
Our Master Tactician is
always one step ahead.
If you don't want
to be outwitted,
you'd best keep to
your own kingdom.
[gasps]
Stupid minstrel.
You won't be going any
further this evening.
Rein in your horse
and drop your weapon.
It looks as though
I must admit defeat.
I'm afraid I don't
have it in my heart
to harm such a beautiful woman.
I'd hoped we were wrong.
Don't look at me
like a hurt pup.
It's not my fault.
This is the nature of war.
Although,
how did you see through my plot?
I thought I'd concealed
it rather well.
It's as I suspected, then.
Hello, Jaswant.
I'd gathered the broad strokes
of what you were up to,
but he was able
to paint the picture
a bit more clearly for us.
Your Highness. Sorry.
Your Majesty now.
I make this request as
a loyal Sindhuran subject.
Please do not bring further
disgrace upon yourself.
Ah, ha.
You do not show much
respect for your new king.
Still, a wise ruler knows
when to admit defeat.
[PARS SOLDIERS shouting]
[PARS SOLDIER A]
Shameless wretch!
[PARS SOLDIER B]
This is how you pay a debt?
[PARS SOLDIER C]
Ungrateful, faithless savage!
[RAJENDRA]
Well, this is familiar.
This is the second
time I've faced you
bound as your prisoner.
Yes, it is, isn't it?
[RAJENDRA]
So, I ask again.
What will you do with me?
Will you kill me this time?
[ARSLAN]
No.
I will keep you and
take you back to Pars,
and I think you'll remain
there for a while.
Let me see. Two years should do.
[chuckles]
Two years, eh?
I'm sure I shall
enjoy it immensely.
[NARSUS]
You can't think that's all.
[RAJENDRA]
Uh.
Oh, gods. Narsus.
Out with it, then.
What scheme have you
concocted this time?
I believe I'll catch up
on some correspondence.
I'm sure your neighbors would be
keen to know your whereabouts.
[RAJENDRA]
What?
I'll need to inform
Turk, of course,
and Turan shouldn't be left out.
You can't do that!
Those kingdoms have
coveted our land
for as long as I can remember.
If they learned of my absence...
They would be
shocked, I'm sure.
For a ruler so freshly
acknowledged
to abandon his
kingdom so suddenly.
I beg you, don't!
If you go through
with this scheme,
there won't be a Sindhura for me
to return to in two years' time!
[ARSLAN]
Very well.
I have an alternative
option you may prefer.
Sign a nonaggression treaty.
Engage in no conflict
with Pars for three years.
[RAJENDRA]
Three years.
Fine! I'll sign the thing!
That's what you want,
are you happy?
[ALFARID] Hey, Narsus.
Can I ask you something?
[NARSUS]
Of course.
[ALFARID]
You had him cornered.
Why not go for more
than three years?
Ten, fifty, even a hundred?
Rajendra is not a patient man.
For someone like him, even ten
years would be as an eternity.
He would never be able
to hold back for so long.
[GIEVE]
I see your logic.
With a term of three years,
he's more likely to wait
rather than violate the treaty.
However,
three years will leave
him plenty of time
to restore harmony to Sindhura.
And then, he's likely
to invade Pars again.
[NARSUS]
Quite.
Which is all the more reason
we must help His Highness
to drive off the Lusitanians
and retake the capital
as soon as we can.
[DARYUN]
Your Highness.
Daryun.
I still can't bring
myself to hate him.
Surely after all that Rajendra's
done, I should despise him.
Does that way of thinking
make me overly indulgent?
If King Andragoras found
himself in your position,
I cannot believe he would
forgive Rajendra's actions.
I imagine you're right.
But you are you.
You are not your father.
And there's nothing
to say you must emulate
his way of thinking.
Nor will I.
The treaty should buy
us the time we need.
It oughtta keep Rajendra
quiet for a while, at least.
I hope so.
[ARSLAN]
Jaswant.
I am a Sindhuran subject.
If Pars and Sindhura should
find themselves at war again,
I will side with my kingdom
and fight against Pars.
Will you?
[JASWANT] However,
you have now saved my life
on three separate
occasions, Your Highness.
It's a debt of honor,
and I mean to repay it.
Until I do, I am your man.
If you will have me,
then I will swear to serve you
to the best of my ability.
Yes. I'll be honored.
[NARRATOR] And so, with the
addition of a new companion,
Arslan's first foreign military
campaign came to an end.
[NARRATOR] Pars Era.
The year 321. Mid-February.
The theatre of war shifts
back to Pars once again.
[NARRATOR]
The time has come for Hilmes
to carefully consider his
ultimate aspirations
and decide which course of
action will serve them best.
Next time: "The End of Winter."
And thus would the
boy become a king.