[NARRATOR]
Pars Era, the year 321.
Arslan made his way
toward Peshawar,
the northern fortress that had
become Pars' main stronghold.
Joining him was a new
companion, Jaswant,
a Sindhuran soldier
lately sworn to Arslan.
[HILMES] You are asking me
to take Zabul Fortress?
[GUISCARD]
Yes.
Our scheme worked well
enough to rid the city
of Bodin and his Temple Knights,
but now they've taken
refuge at Zabul.
They're using their position
to disrupt communications
with the homeland.
In addition,
the damn zealot's begun issuing
rather pointed demands.
What sort of demands?
First, the execution of
Andragoras and Tahamenay.
And then, from my lord brother,
he demands repentance
to god for his infatuation
with a heathen woman
as well as a solemn vow
to never again violate
a religious precept.
I know what his game is.
He's using the name of god in
an effort to increase the power
of the church.
He's gathered 30 thousand
fanatics to him.
Bodin has complete
control of them.
If he ordered it, every last one
would walk through fire.
[SAM] You should accept
this mission, Your Highness.
[HILMES]
Why do you say that?
Guiscard's true intentions
are as plain as day.
Pitting me against
Bodin and his knights,
he's hoping we'll
destroy one another.
[SAM]
That may be true,
but in the course of
completing this mission,
you will have to raise an army
and outfit and equip them.
And best of all,
you will be able to use
the Lusitanian coffers
in order to do so.
[HILMES] Yes, I see it.
You make a good point.
Furthermore, the men we will be
facing are religious fanatics.
Among the most violent and
detested of the Lusitanians.
The people of Pars would
rejoice to see them brought down
and would be grateful
to whomever accomplished
such a thing.
As the future ruler of Pars,
it would not hurt if
that person were you.
It's never too soon to win
your subjects' loyalty.
I understand the
arguments you're making.
However, what if
we are defeated?
Due respect, but I'm surprised
to hear a descendant of
the Hero King Kakhusra
speak so easily
of being defeated.
We must rebuild Pars.
To do that we must defeat Bodin.
And this is the perfect
opportunity to do so.
You are correct, of course.
I can see the wisdom
of your counsel.
You are kind to say so.
[HILMES] This is further proof
I was right to welcome you
into my service.
[GARSHASPH]
We must act.
I still believe we should open
the gates and launch an attack.
What else is our
cavalry good for?
Patience, friend.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS] Listen
to our words, Parsian slaves!
Seize your freedom! All men
are equal in god's eyes.
The time has come to rise
up against your masters!
[SAM]
Stop this!
Does killing unarmed
slaves make you proud?
[GARSHASPH] I don't see any
slaves here. I see rebels!
[SAM] Who have nothing
but sticks to fight with?
[GARSHASPH] In their hearts,
they are holding swords.
[PARSIAN SOLDIER G] Where did
these bastards come from?
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Damn!
They must've come through the
aqueducts! But how did they--?
[gasps]
[SAM]
Kharlan!
So, it is true.
You deserted Pars for Lusitania.
Why did you do it?
[KHARLAN] I have good reason!
You wouldn't understand.
[SAM] You're right. I could
never understand betrayal!
[SAM]
Who... are... you?
[SAM] The throne of Pars
should have fallen to you.
[HILMES] It's for you to decide
whether or not to follow me.
But consider this.
I threw my spear that night
intending to kill you.
And yet here you are
now, alive still.
Perhaps fate spared your life
because you were meant
to entrust to me.
I'll leave you to think.
[SAM]
I need proof of my own
before I can decide
what to believe.
No one is allowed to
pass beyond this point!
[ANDRAGORAS]
Is that you, Sam?
Forgive me, Your
Majesty. It is I.
[ANDRAGORAS]
Why have you come here?
[I thought you might help
me confirm the veracity
of a story I was told.
[ANDRAGORAS]
And what story would be?
It is about the events
of 17 years ago.
Your Majesty, I hate to ask
it, but, if I may be so bold,
were you the person responsible
for the assassination
of King Osroes?
Did you kill your brother
so you could take the
throne for yourself?
And what about
young Prince Hilmes?
Did you attempt to
burn him to death?
[ANDRAGORAS] What's the point
of asking such questions now?
Beyond my abilities
as a fighter,
I can claim few talents.
However, I was lucky enough to
find favor with the royal family
and was thus granted the
honorable position of Marzban.
I owe much to
the royal family,
and my love for the Kingdom
of Pars is deep and unwavering.
I came here because I had hoped
that you would be able
to deny these accusations,
and wake me from this nightmare.
Hah.
I thought as much.
You come down here,
claiming to seek the truth,
but you're not ready to stare
into the abyss of Hell.
Majesty.
I was merely abiding by
what had been prophesied.
Drenched in blood.
Steeped in a thousand lies.
Such is the history
of Pars's royal family.
[ANDRAGORAS]
What purpose can it serve
for a man such as you
to know the truth?
[ANDRAGORAS laughing]
Your time's up.
[GUISCARD] I'm glad you've
agreed to take this on.
[HILMES] Of course,
I will expect weapons
and supplies to be
made readily available.
Additionally, I imagine
you can ill afford
to spare sufficient men from
among your regular troops.
Therefore, I think it best if
I assemble an army of Parsians.
Very well. I shall
leave it to you, then.
Excellent.
Forgive me, Your Highness,
but is it wise to use
the heathens like this?
Won't an army of such
men be just as likely
to turn its spears on us?
Yes, of course. There
is no doubt in my mind
"General Silver Mask"
is plotting something
to undermine us.
For now, at least, his
willingness to fight those fools
at Zabul Fortress
makes him useful.
And he's sure to
suffer losses, too.
[SAM] The fortress may
appear to be impregnable,
but in truth, it has
several weaknesses.
I have visited there
several times,
and believe I am fairly
familiar with its interior.
Indeed?
Anyhow, I can see no reason
to overexert ourselves
on the Lusitanians' behalf.
We should take all
the time we need
to make preparations
for our attack.
[HILMES] Yes. I cannot
afford to lose this battle.
It is an important step on my
path to driving the Lusitanians
from our kingdom and ascending
the throne as I am destined to.
[SAM]
Yes, sir.
And once I am king,
I will kill Andragoras
and his whelp Arslan,
and adorn the city gates
with their heads.
[NARRATOR]
March First.
A force was sent
against Zabul Fortress,
led by Hilmes, and comprised
entirely of Parsians.
[LUSITANIAN OFFICER B]
We didn't expect this.
That army must number
more than 30 thousand.
For now, perhaps,
but we'll see how many
return from battle.
So, you have been
having some trouble
with bandits in the area,
and you believe they are
men who formerly belonged
to the Temple Knights?
[FARMER A]
Yes, sir.
They were wreaking
havoc in these parts.
But this traveler you mentioned,
you say he was able to fight
off the bandits singlehandedly?
Yes.
He was a soldier, I guess,
and to hear him tell it,
he was ranked
awfully highly, too.
Used to lead tens of thousands
of men to battle, he said.
So, in your estimation,
he was a fairly strong man?
[FARMER A] Well, he easily
took down 15 men by himself,
so I would say
he was very strong.
How would you describe him?
Well, let me think.
A one-eyed giant who
seems to love his women
as much as he loves his wine?
Many thanks.
You have been most helpful.
[FARMERS]
Sir.
[SAM]
Your Highness.
I have an idea of who the
man they spoke of may be.
I would like to seek him out
to confirm my suspicions.
If he's indeed the
man I have in mind,
he'll make quite
a formidable ally.
[KUBARD]
I'll be leaving shortly.
There's no need to
thank me any further.
You haven't changed, Kubard.
[KUBARD]
Huh?
Long time, Sam.
[SAM] It's been half a year.
You seem well, though.
Cheers!
You know, it honestly
never occurred to me
you might still live.
Are there any other surviving
commanders in Ecbatana?
It shames me to say so,
but I am the only one.
I suppose you'll just
have to be ashamed enough
for both of us, then.
I don't seem to find this
existence as distasteful
as you do.
As long as I can drink a jug of
wine and bed a beautiful woman,
I'm more than
content with my lot.
And I don't mind the
occasional opportunity
to hack a Lusitanian
savage to pieces, either.
[SAM]
You said you're about to leave?
Hah. Yeah.
While I enjoyed the
villagers' gratitude,
I draw the line when
womenfolk start arguing
over who will become my bride.
Sounds like a good
problem to have.
Sure, to you.
But I've no desire to be
tied to only one place
or to only one woman,
for that matter.
A fact I took great pains to
make clear from the beginning.
I'll be brief.
I am going with
the man I now serve
to eliminate the Lusitanian
Temple Knights,
who have established a base for
themselves in Zabul Fortress.
I had hoped you might
consider accompanying us.
We would be lucky to have
a man of your strength.
I'm listening.
Who is this man you now serve?
[NARRATOR]
Zabul Fortress,
where Bodin's Temple
Knights were entrenched,
was perched atop
a craggy mountain.
Its cliffs rose straight from
the plains, offering no cover
and no opportunity
for a surprise attack.
However, Hilmes had no intention
of fighting a protracted battle.
Rather, he devised a plan
to lure the enemy
from behind the fortress walls.
Those vile heathens!
They dare to burn the sacred
banner right under my nose?
I want them torn limb from limb!
Give those animals
what they deserve!
Send them to the
fiery pits of Hell!
[TEMPLE KNIGHTS]
Yes, sir!
[HILMES] Excellent.
Bodin doesn't disappoint.
He's as hot-tempered as ever.
Your Highness predicted
his reaction well.
[SAM]
Kubard.
Well? What're our orders?
My men will attack
from the left flank,
Zandeh will lead our
forces in the center,
and the right flank will be
under His Highness's command.
[KUBARD]
Where do I come in?
If you don't mind,
play spectator for
just awhile longer.
As long as there's khukar
I don't mind at all.
I find I have a mighty
appetite for battle today.
Run down the savages!
Do not falter!
[TEMPLE KNIGHT H] In the name
of the God of Yaldabaoth!
Attack on our flank!
[TEMPLE KNIGHT N] Your day
of judgment has come, heathen!
In the name of god,
I condemn you!
You think I give a
damn about your god?
[TEMPLE KNIGHT N]
This, too, is His will!
No, fool. You die today
because of my will.
[TEMPLE KNIGHT O]
Evade them!
Now, Kubard!
[TEMPLE KNIGHT Q] Glory to
the Faith of Yaldabaoth!
You're a bunch of savages
in sore need of killin'!
Your Highness.
Be more careful.
I would have you there
to witness my triumph
when I am crowned king and
ascend the throne of Pars.
Till then, you are to
keep yourself alive.
Yes?
Sir!
[NARRATOR]
The Lusitanian force
was bested by Hilmes
and his Parsian troops.
With more than two thousand
Temple Knights dead
on the battlefield,
the remainder took refuge
in Zabul Fortress.
They closed the gates,
believing themselves secure
within their impregnable
mountain stronghold.
My thanks. You did
well for us out there.
[KUBARD] Yes. The fortress
hasn't fallen yet, though.
They're likely hunkering
down for a siege.
Fortunately, we have
a plan to avoid that.
Yo.
Watch your casual tone!
This is Prince Hilmes,
the rightful king of Pars.
Show him the proper respect!
[KUBARD]
Hm.
My humblest apologies,
Your Highness.
Sam told me you were
a truly fierce fighter.
I'm glad to see
he didn't exaggerate.
Bringing down Bodin
and his fanatics
will not be an easy task.
I'll be glad of that
giant sword of yours.
A moment, Highness.
Might you permit me
to ask a question?
What drives you
to seek the throne
with such single-minded purpose?
Kubard.
I would be grateful
for an answer.
That's enough of your insolence!
It is simple.
I would reclaim the throne
that was stolen from me,
so that I can restore peace to
the kingdom and to its people.
Was it Lusitania that stole
the throne from you, though?
Or was it--?
I said that's enough!
No! But he's right.
That is enough.
[KUBARD sighs]
I mean you no ill will,
but it's time I go.
The defeat at Atropatene
freed me to do as I please
whenever I please, and I find
I like that way of life.
Are you sure?
You may do as you wish.
Reward this man
for his service today.
[SAM]
Yes, sir.
You know what it means
if Prince Hilmes truly is of the
royal bloodline as you insist?
[SAM]
Huh?
[KUBARD] It means taking our
kingdom back from Lusitania
is only the beginning.
After that, there will
still be a bloody feud
for the throne of Pars
to be settled.
[SAM]
I suppose.
[KUBARD] Only a stupid man would
get caught up in such a dispute.
Sorry, Sam.
You best forget me.
So, Prince Hilmes
is fortunate enough
to have you playing advisor.
And what about Prince Arslan?
Who's acting as his
adivsors these days?
He has Daryun and Narsus.
Oh!
That court-hating recluse
came out of hiding
to ally himself with
Prince Arslan, eh?
Interesting.
[chuckles]
[KUBARD]
So, then. What're your plans?
Will you stay on as a
supporter of Prince Hilmes?
As I've sworn him my loyalty,
I can see no other
honorable course to take.
And I must admit
I don't like the idea
of him being without any
staunch Parsian ally.
Though, of course,
I know I haven't much to offer.
You have a tough road ahead.
I'll pray that you find
luck in battle, at least.
Mind you, though,
I'm an unbeliever,
so it's entirely possible
a prayer from me
will actually have the
opposite effect with the gods.
Farewell.
[NARRATOR]
March of that year,
from his seat at Peshawar,
Arslan used his authority
as Crown Prince
to issue two momentous
proclamations.
[NARSUS] The Decree to Pursue
and Destroy Lusitania.
It is an appeal to
all Parsian fighters
to come together at Peshawar
Fortress and form an army.
The army will be
commanded by you
and will be used to drive
the Lusitanian invaders
from our borders.
Good.
[NARSUS]
And then there is this.
The Decree to Abolish Slavery.
It states that once Your
Highness has become king,
you will free all slaves
living within Pars,
and that you will prohibit
the buying and selling
of human beings.
Yes.
[NARRATOR] It was for
this historic proclamation
that the young prince
would later be hailed
as Arslan the Liberator.
[NARRATOR]
Arslan.
Fourteen years,
six months of age.
He walked a dangerous
path, one yet rife
with unknown obstacles
and unforeseen hardships.
However,
it was only by treading
this long and perilous road
that he could assume
his place in history.
[NARRATOR] Arslan must
defeat the Lusitanian horde
that has overrun
the Kingdom of Pars.
To do so, he will need
not only strength and wit,
but also a firm resolve.
Next time: "The True
Face of a Knight."
And thus would the
boy become a king.