Let's try the Full Turn
Extension next.
[WATARU]
One, two, down, up!
[SAKU gasping]
Do it again!
Right. I'm sorry, Coach.
[BREAKERS]
One... two... three, Breakers!
[BREAKERS chattering]
Uh? What do you need?
Oh, nothing!
It's nothing at all, Miss!
Step back. That's "Coach"
to the two of you.
[BOTH]
Uh! We're sorry, Kin!
[HARUKI]
Hm...
Kirari. Come on!
You've already read my message
so why the heck
won't you just reply?
Kirari?
Stop invading my privacy and
mind your own business, man!
Hey, you're the one
thinkin' out loud.
Gen. Do you know
where she is?
[GEN]
Not a clue!
[ICHIRO] Hey, come back!
You know something!
All right. What's going on?
Why do you think everyone's
acting so weird today? Kazu?
Hello?
Uh! Oh. Yeah. Sounds good.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Kazu, you okay?
Uh! Yep. I'm great!
Are you sure?
I'm just a little worried
about regionals.
Working on new stunts
for 'em sounded fun,
but it's gonna take a whole
lot of practice, you know?
Hard work's never bothered
you before, Kazu.
Yeah, you're right. My bad.
It's easy enough to turn over
a few heads of broccoli.
But turning over
an entire team
and making them the best in
the show is no small task!
True dat. Right on, bro!
[TAKERU]
Don't call me that.
Takumi. Stop calling
everyone "bro."
[TAKUMI]
Yeah, whatever you say, bro.
Sho, is there a trick to
the Full Turn Extension,
or does it just take time, bro?
He's not your bro, bro!
A trick? Not really, you
just have to get it right.
When you lift up the flyer, use
their heel as an axis point.
When they start to rise,
that's when you twist.
[TAKUMI]
Huh?
[TAKERU]
What? Sorry, I blacked out.
Hey, that's good advice.
I suck. Big time.
I completely screwed
up the Full Turn.
How do I get better at it? Kazu?
Uh. Yeah.
I'm in a hurry. Gotta go.
[HARUKI] I know something's
wrong with him. But what?
[HARUKI]
Uh?
[gasps]
Hey, Sis.
Uh? What's up?
Are you okay?
Why wouldn't I be?
Nevermind. Just thought I'd ask.
Shouldn't I be asking you that?
I saw you and Kazu. Cheering.
[gasps]
[HARUKO] Why would you do
that at the school festival
in front of all those people?
Do you like getting that
kind of attention?
The Men's Cheer Club?
Come on. What do
you think you are?
Welp. Good talk.
[HARUKI sighs]
[SAKU] What? For real?
Kazu's taking today off?
[TAKAGI] Yes. He sent me a
message letting me know.
It's news to me.
Haru. Did you know
anything about this?
I didn't.
[SAKU exhales]
But the regionals are
right around the corner.
Where could he be?
No clue. But without him,
there's not a lot we can do.
At least not with
the new material.
Worry about yourselves,
not the Captain!
[DOH, GIN grunt]
Yes, sir!
And look me in the eyes
when you talk to me!
[BOTH]
Yes, sir!
Well, there's nothing we can
do about it now, right?
Let's buckle down and get
outta here early, guys!
Hey, Gen. You're in a good mood.
Did something happen?
Nope, not really.
[ICHIRO growling]
Haru. I fear our friend
has been afflicted.
With what?
It's perfectly obvious.
Not to me.
With love!
Oh! Wow!
[WATARU]
It's plain as day.
How would you know, you
haven't been in love?
[WATARU]
Ouch.
[BREAKERS chattering]
[HARUKI]
Mm? Hey.
I'm afraid that she
might be in love.
Oh?
Wait. Who's this?
Kirari, duh!
I still don't know who that is!
My sister!
I didn't know you
had a sister, too.
She's way too young
to fall in love!
Well, then go and
ruin it for her.
That's what older siblings
do best, right?
I'm trying, dude!
But it's kinda hard when she
already has a freakin' date!
How do you know about
that? She tell you?
No, she didn't tell me.
I got all ninja and listened
in on her phone call.
She won't even tell me the name
of the guy she's talking to.
She's super pissed 'cause she
caught me eavesdropping.
Apparently, I'm not as good at
the ninja-thing as I thought.
Which is exactly why I
need you to help me, Haru!
What?
[ICHIRO]
She should be here any second.
[HARUKI] Are you sure you don't
have "ninja" confused with
"creepy stalker"?
Oh, it'll be ninja, my friend.
Cause once her date shows up I'm
gonna go Bruce Lee oh his face!
Right, but considering
what happened,
isn't this just gonna
piss her off even more?
You don't have a little sister,
okay? You wouldn't understand.
You're right, I wouldn't,
which is why you should ask
someone besides me for help.
Like Gen?
I can't. He's been acting
like a total weirdo lately.
And Kazu has too.
What's that all about?
Well...
Maybe they're both--
What? In love?!
Come on, dude, there's
no way that's it.
If he was into a girl? He'd
totally tell me about it.
She's pretty cute, huh?
Her? Well...
Yeah. I guess. Like
in her... own way.
[ICHIRO]
And Gen?
[HARUKI]
I don't know, in my opinion,
he seemed like he was in
a pretty good mood today.
[ICHIRO, HARUKI]
Mm!
[ICHIRO, HARUKI yelp]
[GEN humming]
What the heck is he doing here?
[KIRARI]
Hey, there! Sorry I'm late!
[ICHIRO gasps]
It's her!
Whoa.
Ah, it's all good.
I just got here myself.
[KIRARI]
I'm glad to hear it!
So, is he her date then? Yikes.
He's been macking on my
little sister behind my back!
Slow down!
That's a really lovely
outfit you have on.
It matches your eyes.
[ICHIRO growls]
Shall we? I'll take you
anywhere you wanna go.
For the day's duration, consider
me your knightly escort.
[ICHIRO growls]
Who's knightly now,
you jerk off?!
[HARUKI]
Ichiro!
Huh?!
Bro...
[KIRARI]
Huh?
[ICHIRO growls]
[KIRARI]
Hey, Ichiro.
[ICHIRO growls]
[GEN]
Are you okay?
[ICHIRO screams]
Kirari picked this out
just for me!
She was worried
cause she didn't know
what to get you
for your birthday,
so I agreed I'd help her
look for something.
So yeah, it wasn't weird.
I'm glad we got
that cleared up.
[WATARU] Hijinks.
What a comedy of errors.
Speaking of...
There's something we feel
that we must show you.
[HARUKI]
Huh?
Coach Takagi sent us this video
and it's peculiar to
say the very least.
[SHO]
Everybody focus!
Your cradle's loose, bases!
[GEN]
What am I watching right now?
[HARUKI] I mean... It looks
like a Sho fan video.
That's exactly what it is!
And when someone
makes one of these,
there's only one
possible reason!
She's fallen in love
with Sho. Right?
Like, what else could it be?!
Oh snap!
Sweet! That's like every
man's secret fantasy!
The thing is, we can't bring
ourselves to tell Kin.
Yet we feel completely horrible
for withholding the truth!
This is hell!
Haruki, please. You gotta
help us out here, buddy!
What? The video I sent to Gin?
Oh, right! That wasn't meant for
him. Total mistake on my part.
I did put it together.
But I intended to send it
to... one of Sho's fans.
Which fan?
Thing is... I'm keeping it
a secret from him for now.
But I'll explain everything
when the time is right.
Uh. Cool.
Oh, man. Glad that's done!
Thanks for sorting it out.
Yeah, for sure.
Just remember not to jump
to conclusions next time.
[HARUKI]
I bet Kazu's fine, too.
[SHO]
Well?! Let's get started, guys!
Hey. Hold on.
It looks like Kazu's out again.
It's not like him
to miss practice
without letting us know.
[WATARU]
No. It isn't.
He's definitely okay. Right?
I hope.
[TON] I can't believe Kazu
just no-showed on us.
[HARUKI] He's not checking
his messages, either.
[SHO]
Something's definitely going on.
[TAKUYA]
I just hope he's all right.
Same here. He never
did this in judo.
I can't imagine what would make
him no-show without telling us.
He's been shot with
Cupid's arrow.
Right through his poor,
tender heart.
If music be the food of love--
Then play on?
I, too, am drunk on love.
[GIN, DOH]
For real?!
So what, he ditched
practice for a date?
Maybe he tried to
kiss her goodnight
and she slapped his face?
Or maybe she punched him right
where it hurts the most. Huh?!
Or perhaps she broke
his fragile heart?
I just don't see Kazu
missing practice
over something like that.
Yeah. Let's not get ahead
of ourselves, guys.
[SAKU]
Mm...
[bell rings]
[BREAKERS chattering]
Hey, Sho? I think I should
drop by his place.
Please do. Thank you.
[SAKU]
Haru.
[HARUKI]
Uh?
Look. I lied.
I actually do know
where Kazu is.
I was worried about him.
So I decided to follow
him after school.
The thing is... It's
his grandmother.
I don't think she's doing well.
Yeah, Granny's fine!.
She sure hasn't
lost her appetite,
girl eats a dozen apples a day.
She talks and talk and talks
and when I try to leave
she won't let me!
[HARUKI exhales]
I'm on it. I'll try going
by the hospital first.
[SAKU]
Mm.
[gasps]
Uh!
[KAZUMA]
Hey, bud.
Thanks a lot.
[KAZUMA]
I'm sorry about practice.
[HARUKI]
I get it.
Really though. I feel bad.
Coach told me that a team's
Captain is like its sun.
This is, I'm not feelin' very
bright at the moment. Sorry.
It's funny. The crazy stuff
the guys were saying.
Like how you got dumped.
By the secret girlfriend
you've been hiding.
[KAZUMA laughs]
That's ridiculous.
Kazu, is your Grandma sick?
Truth is, I've been lying to
you this whole time, Haru.
About her having
a good appetite.
About her talking so much
she wouldn't let me leave.
I wish that were
all true, I really do.
But it's not...
Granny doesn't even know
who I am anymore.
[gasps]
One by one, she's slowly
losing her memories.
She can barely remember her
own name, much less mine.
But one day,
she saw some cheerleaders on TV.
[GRANDMOTHER]
Kasu...
[KAZUMA]
Uh?
Kasumi.
"Kasumi." Yeah. She just said
my Mom's name out of the blue.
It was the cheerleaders.
Somehow, they jarred her
memory and opened it up.
And that's when I got an idea.
If I did my parents'
cheer routine,
then maybe somehow she'd
remember me, too.
I wanna do that routine
at the school festival.
Just like my parents
did back in college!
Look. I thought about telling
you so many different times.
But, I...
I was scared to say it out loud
cause I thought I'd
lose my courage.
And if I lost that I was afraid
I'd lose her forever, too.
Dumb. I know.
Not dumb.
[KAZUMA] But it's all over now,
so what difference does it make?
I'm done cheerleading.
I've lost the will for it.
I'm sorry.
I know I told you I wanted to
start something new with you,
but it was for selfish reasons.
And now I've dragged
everyone else into it.
I feel like a jerk.
[KAZUMA]
Haru. I'm all alone now.
My family... The people
who looked after me...
They're all gone.
Hey. Look at me, Kazu.
You're wrong. You're
not alone at all.
Trust me. You might feel
that way, but it isn't true.
Even if your grandma
was the reason
you started the cheer club,
because of your leadership,
this group has done
incredible things!
And we're here for you,
now and always.
And nothing in this world's
ever gonna change that.
Coach is right! You're our sun.
So you can't cry!
[HARUKI]
You can't.
Don't tell me that. You're
the one who's crying. Dammit.
Welcome home!
[HARUKI]
I'm sorry I'm running late, Mom.
So how was your day?
[HARUKI]
Fine.
[MOM] Glad to hear it!
Are you hungry?
[HARUKI]
Mm-hm.
[MOM] That reminds me. We
haven't seen Kazuma lately.
[HARUKI gasps]
Where's he been?
He used to eat dinner with us
at least two times a week.
[HARUKI] I don't think I've ever
seen Kazu cry like that before.
[HARUKI]
Poor guy.
I guess he's just been suffering
in silence this whole time.
[HARUKI grunts]
[ICHIRO]
So that's what it was.
[HARUKI grunts]
That's so sad.
Feeling like you have to fake a
smile when you're really down.
Yeah. I didn't even know
he was hurting.
I'm pretty sure he
didn't want us to.
[ICHIRO] What's with him?!
We're a team, aren't we?!
If he can tell anyone
what was going on,
it's his freakin' teammates!
I mean isn't the whole point
that we're in this together?!
Even if he was hiding this,
I think his time here might've
helped make it better.
That's been true for me.
So this whole club was
really about his grandma.
He planned to use us
to jar her memory.
And that's why he wanted us
to do his parents' routine.
Makes sense.
He wanted us to help
him break through
the barrier in her memory.
How sweet.
Guys. I wanna support Kazu.
I want us to support
him as a team!
Yeah!
It shall be so.
I am all in. For me, nothing
matters more than family.
Truth is, I was a trouble maker
when I was a little kid.
I gave my folks a
lotta headaches.
I wish I could do it over again.
But something good did
come from that time.
I realized how much
I love my family!
[BOTH]
Same here.
[WATARU] "Doubt the stars are
fire. Doubt the sun doth move.
Doubt truth to be a liar.
But never doubt your bros."
Most of that was
William Shakespeare.
Okay... How are we
supposed to support him?
There's only one thing
we can do. Cheer him on!
Granny. Do you want tea?
[NURSE 1A] Kazuma. How about
a little air in here?
[KAZUMA]
Uh?
[NURSE 1A]
It'll be nice.
Oh my. Look at all those boys.
[gasps]
A little peek never
hurt anyone.
Go on. I bet she'll get a
big kick out of this.
[KAZUMA laughs]
[PATIENT 9A]
What are they doing?
Hi! We're the Breakers!
The Meishiin Men's Cheerleading
Club! Enjoy the show!
We ready to cheer, Breakers?!
[BREAKERS]
Ready when you are!
[ALL] Go, fight, win!
Let's go... Breakers!
Now!
♪♪♪
[BREAKERS]
Breakers... go!
Meishiin! Hey! Come on!
We are Breakers!
This is showtime!
We feel great!
B-R-E-A-K-E-R-S!
Go... Breakers!
[BREAKERS]
Go Breakers!
[PATIENTS cheer]
[KAZUMA]
Heh.
Granny. You'd be proud.
Mom and Dad would be too.
I have so many teammates.
So many friends. Heh. I'm lucky.
Because they all support me.
[KAZUMA] Seriously, guys.
Thank you all so much.
This means the world to me.
No problem. That's what
teammates are for, right?
[SAKU laughs]
Pretty sure you're the one
who taught us that.
Uh! I guess so.
We'll see you at practice
tomorrow, then?
Without our Captain, I'm
afraid we are a hot mess.
That's so true.
Yeah. I'm there. Heh!
You're the real reason
I do this, you know?
I wouldn't miss it
for the world, guys!
Hey, look, it's
the Winter Triangle.
[HARUKI]
Kinda cold.
[KAZUMA]
Yeah.
But can we look at the stars
just a little longer?
[HARUKI]
Sure.
[KAZUMA] I know I'm gonna
get past this, Haru.
Because all my friends
are there to cheer me on.
I won't give up again.
Hey, Kazu. Do you remember
those notebooks?
The journals that Coach gave us.
Mine said I had to beat you.
[KAZUMA]
For real?
Yeah. But the thing is,
you're just too cool.
You've overcome so
much in your life.
I'm never gonna beat
you at anything, man.
Haru...
Dude. Trust me,
you will beat me.
[HARUKI]
Oh yeah?
Well, at the very least,
you're gonna get
a girlfriend first!
What?! No way!
[KAZUMA]
Come on, spill it,
how have things been
going with Chihiro?
I'm dying to know!
[HARUKI] I can't! I mean,
there's nothing to tell!
[KAZUMA]
You sure about that? [laughs]
[SPARKS]
One, two, three... Sparks!
[SPARKS chattering]
What's goin' on? You... okay?
Look...
[KAORU]
The Breakers?!
They actually made
it to Regionals?!
How 'bout that.
Hey, wait a second!
Doesn't that mean we're gonna
be up against Sho Tokugawa?!
[HARUKI]
Concentrate. Focus.
Concentrate. Focus...
[TON]
Guys, what's wrong with Haru?
[SAKU]
He's kind of freaking me out.
[HISASHI] It sort of looks like
he's possessed by the devil.
[HARUKI]
...focus, focus...
Next episode, "What I
Wanted to Tell You."
Go... Fight... Win!