♪ ♪
Oh, wow. This is the coolest
thing I've ever seen.
My glasses!
It's so steamy.
I can barely see!
Don't they seem a little
amateurish to you?
If by amateurish you mean
totally bad ass, then oh yeah.
Kazu? Is that who I think it is?
Sure is.
[CHEERLEADERS]
Let's go, Peaches!
[CROWD cheers]
I wanna do that routine
at the school festival.
Just like my parents
did back in college.
[KAZUMA] It was their first
performance as a group,
so I think it should
be ours, too.
I still can't believe
your old man
was your mom's
Cheerleading Coach.
It's great that you have
this video as a momento
of their time together.
If your folks made it
all the way to the
World Championships, they
must have been quite a pair.
I used to hear stories
about it all the time.
They remind me of our team.
They started with seven members.
But they worked hard to made
the most of what they had.
Makes sense.
So, that's why you were so
obsessed with the number seven.
Brilliant!
This plan saves us from
having to choreograph
a routine ourselves!
Wataru. Not the point.
[stomach growling]
[KAZUMA laughs]
Listen. It won't
be easy to learn,
but if my parents could
do it, then so can we!
I'm in. Let's do
it together, guys!
Yeah!
We're agreed.
[TON] It is gonna be
a challenge though.
The festival's still
two months away.
If we practice as
hard as we can,
I know we'll be ready to go.
Plus, it doesn't hurt
to have the Master of
Tumbling on our team.
The toughest part of this
routine is the first stunt.
It's gonna take some doing.
It requires a mid-air back flip.
That's no small feat
for any flyer.
We only need one stunt
group to attempt the move.
But if we don't get it exactly
right, we're dead in the water.
Kazu. Can you do it?
'Course I can, but I'm not the
only candidate for this stunt.
Isn't that right, buddy?
[gasps] I can't.
Don't forget, we're
the Breakers, dude.
Let's break through
this together!
[HARUKI]
Huh...
All right then.
Well, we have time, so let's
get closer to the event
and see how you progress
before we make our choice.
[knocking]
[WATARU]
Hm?
[WATARU'S MOTHER]
I'm coming in, Wataru.
[WATARU]
Uh!
I am so sorry for disturbing you
during your video research.
But I wish to say thank you for
all you've done for Wataru.
Dinner is ready.
Would you boys care to
join us for a nice meal?
[ICHIRO] Dude. Your mom's
all right for an old girl.
[GEN]
No. She looks just like Wataru.
[ICHIRO]
Uh.
[stomach growls]
[HARUKI]
Can we shut up and go eat?
[WATARU]
Special delivery!
Hey guys.
[ALL chuckle]
[GEN]
Ichiro, hold it up!
[ICHIRO]
What do you think I'm doing?
[KAZUMA] You're the one
who needs to rotate...
[HARUKI]
Come in.
[WATARU sighs]
That was great!
Glad you had fun.
How boutcha give me a little
heads up next time?
[WATARU] This is exactly what
Dreams practices with.
We can't have second-rate
equipment.
[ICHIRO] Hey, Wataru, how much
did this stuff set you back?
Unclear. I choose not to look
at price tags while shopping.
How loaded are you?
It's a good step.
Having the right equipment
makes a difference.
Guys! Let's practice
our butts off.
Maybe we'll get lucky and
score ourselves some dates.
[HARUKI gasping]
One, two and down and up!
[HARUKI yelps]
--[GEN] We gotcha!
--[WATARU] Nice try!
[gasps] Guys. I'm so sorry.
It's not that I don't trust
the bases. I swear.
My mind knows I'm safe,
but my body--
Look. It's fine.
You've got the basic idea
of the Elevator down.
I think you and Kazu
should start working
on your jumps and flips next.
[KAZUMA]
Cool!
[HARUKI]
Uh...
[SHO]
All right.
Listen to me carefully:
push down without bending
your knees too much,
then jump while fully
extending your legs
and raising your hands
above your head.
Once you feel steady,
hug your knees to your chest
as tight as you can
and then flip backwards.
[SHO] Kazu looks like he's got
it down. You're next Haru.
You ready?
[SHO]
Haru!
[crash]
It's all right if you wanna
stick to small jumps for now.
No need to rush.
I'm fine.
[KAZUMA]
Haru.
[HARUKI gasps]
Just give it time, man.
[HARUKI exhales]
Now say it with me, everyone!
Let's go Meishiin!
[STUDENTS muttering]
Thank you, Haru.
It's really nice to
see such enthusiasm.
But I'm afraid your presentation
got a little bit off topic.
[ICHIRO, KAZUMA laughing]
By the way, gentlemen.
Starting next semester, my son
will be studying here;
he's an extremely
sensitive young man
so I'd appreciate it if
you'd be nice to him.
[CAFE MANAGER 1A] Shaved ice
with a sunflowery summer theme!
[ALL]
All right! Let's dig in!
Are you kidding me man?
Do you ever lose your cool?
[KAZUMA]
Where're Ton and Wataru?
They have one class
left, I think.
[GEN] Lame. Well, I finished
my last final yesterday!
[ICHIRO]
You finished it,
but do you think you
actually passed this time?
[GEN]
Dude...
[ICHIRO] You suck at
Chinese and you know it!
[GEN]
Mind your own business!
[laughs] Get ready, cause
starting tomorrow morning,
we meet in the park every day.
Then after lunch we make a
company move to the rooftop.
We're gonna eat,
sleep, and breathe
cheerleading this summer.
Hey, Ichiro. What's
with the wrist band?
Never seen it before.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Ain't it awesome?
No, it's not,
why are you wearing it?
It was a present from
my super-hot girlfriend.
Not! I'm still single!
Show me your wrist!
[ICHIRO grunts]
[ALL gasping]
[gasps]
Oh, right. That.
It's no biggie.
I sprained it at work.
Why didn't you tell us sooner?
[HARUKI] Any idea how
long it'll take to heal?
The Doctor said four weeks,
but screw that!
I can be ready to go
in half that time!
I'm sorry, Ichiro, but if the
Doctor told you four weeks,
then that's what it's gotta be.
Relax! All I have to do
is tape it up every day
and then it'll be good as new!
No way.
We're about to start tossing
and catching practice soon.
You can't risk aggravating
it or even worse,
getting another injury.
[sighs] Whatever you say, Sho.
[WATARU]
One, two, down, up, down, up!
Gen. You gotta tighten
up that grip!
Use the force from the
load-in to propel him up!
Ton, you're still not
using your knees properly.
[BOTH]
Right.
[SHO]
And Wataru,
during the cradle you have to
watch the flyer more carefully.
Catch him with your entire
body, not just your arms.
Understood!
[SHO]
Kazu, your prep jump is too big.
And you can't control
your posture mid-air.
Pay more attention
to your body's axis.
[KAZUMA]
Right!
[SHO]
Well? Again!
[CROWD chattering]
Hey, man.
I'm shocked! You managed
to get outta bed!
[HARUKI]
By the way,
thanks for inviting me
to practice with you.
Back when we did Judo,
the two of us would practice in
the morning a lot, remember?
Yeah, I guess that's true.
[KAZUMA] It's always way more
fun to work with a friend
than it is to do it
all by yourself.
Plus, we're both flyers
so it makes sense.
Kazu, listen--
Stop worrying, man.
[gasps]
I've been around you
for a really long time.
Whenever you struggled
with a Judo technique,
you worked at it till it
became your specialty.
And I was right there watchin'
so don't try to argue.
[HARUKI] Hey, Kazu!
Eventually, I am gonna fly!
[KAZUMA] Cool! But if
you wanna be the one
to do that backflip,
you'll have to earn it!
[SHO] It's fine if you'd rather
start with a straight up jump.
[HARUKI grunts]
[WATARU]
One, two, down, up!
[HARUKI whimpers]
Careful!
[GEN]
You're okay.
[gasps] Guys. Thanks.
Sorry.
I guess I need to go practice it
a little more on the trampoline.
[panting] One more time!
♪ ♪
[ALL]
Go! Let's go, Breakers!
We are... B-O-Y!
One... Two... Three,
are you ready?
Stop!
[HARUKI panting]
This sucks. We're trying,
but no matter what we do,
we can't get in sync.
I'm so sorry.
I'm doing my best but
I just can't keep up.
Until today, I had no idea my
sense of rhythm was this awful.
It's all right!
Just concentrate on
keeping with the count,
pay attention to your teammates,
and stay focused.
I know we'll get there.
I wouldn't be so sure!
[TON] At this rate, our debut
gonna be a total disaster.
'Kay. Let's call it
a day, everybody.
[ICHIRO]
No way!
If we don't keep practicing,
we'll never be ready!
Look, man.
I'm not saying you're wrong,
but we need a break.
[ICHIRO] What we need is to dig
in our heels and keep working!
You're right. And we
should start tomorrow.
[ICHIRO] Here's a quote:
"When the going gets tough,
the tough get going!"
You can't can solve every
problem by pushing forward.
That includes your
sprained wrist, Ichiro.
[growls] You think I'm gonna let
a little injury slow me down?!
[ICHIRO grunting]
You okay?!
I'm fine!
[GEN] Just stop it!
Have you lost your mind?
You're gonna make it worse!
Shut up! Get your hands off me!
No way man! You lied to us!
You didn't sprain that at work!
[ICHIRO gasps]
[GEN] You got hurt practicing
by yourself, right?
[ALL gasp]
[ICHIRO chuckles] This sucks.
Why'd I have to get injured?
Why am I the one draggin' the
team down? I'm so stupid!
Listen to yourself!
You're not draggin'
anybody down.
You're working harder
than everyone else.
The fact that you got injured
proves it. You're amazing.
Don't you get it?
No matter how hard I try, I'll
never be as good as you, Ichiro.
If anyone here is
stupid, it's me.
Well, if you're stupid, then
I'm the dumbest person here.
My body's massive but I
don't have real strength.
And more than any of you, I
take forever to learn new stuff.
You're wrong, Ton.
I have White Boy Rhythm.
My movements are rigid and
stiff. I should spare us all
some pain and quit before
I ruin our chances.
Guys. That's enough.
[KAZUMA]
I'm sorry, everybody.
[gasps]
This is all my fault.
I'm the one who suggested
we perform this stupid
routine in the first place.
You idiots!
That was harsh...
Give me a break, Kazu!
You're the person who brought
our team together!
You led us the whole way!
Ichiro and Gen.
Don't give me that crap when
you're both way better athletes
than me! It's very rude!
And remind me Ton: who's the
fried pork curry champ here?!
Wataru! Your quotes
make me cringe,
but damn you're committed and I
dunno you're helpful sometimes.
Sho! Aside from your total
lack of fashion sense,
you're a pretty cool guy!
Don't you all realize how
incredible you are?
[HARUKI]
It's obvious that the only one
"slowing down" the team is me.
But I'm not giving up and
neither should you!
Y'hear me? We'll break
through this barrier!
So, are you with me
or aren't you?!
Come on! Let's go, Breakers!
Go, fight, win!
Let's go, Breakers!
...Go, fight, win!
Let's go Breakers!
Go, fight, win!
Let's go, Breakers!
--Go, fight, win!
--Guys...
Let's go, Breakers!
Go, fight, win!
[ALL]
Let's go, Breakers!
Go, fight, win!
Let's go... Breakers!
[WATARU, TON chuckle, sigh]
I don't really get what just
happened, but I feel great!
Yeah, me too.
[HARUKI]
Kazu.
[KAZUMA]
Hm?
Y'know what? I think I
might be ready to fly.
[SHO]
Don't push yourself too hard.
[WATARU]
One, two, down, up, down, up!
[ICHIRO]
Gotcha!
[KAZUMA]
Not bad.
You good?
That was fun.
I could feel you supporting
me. It was great.
I trust you guys.
Let me try again!
Heck yeah!
All right!
[WATARU]
One, two, down, up, down, up!
[laughs] Way to go!
You did it!
Thanks.
--Now you're a flyer!
--That was so cool!
Wow! You've opened a new door!
[KAZUMA]
More like he kicked it down!
Way to go, seriously,
I knew you it in ya.
[ICHIRO] That's what I
call a back flip! Right?
Uh? Yeah. You looked
like a real pro, Haru!
[gasps] You guys. I...
I broke through.
Woo-hoo! [laughs]
[ICHIRO] The Breakers take the
stage at one pm on the dot,
so get ready to have
your minds blown!!
[GEN] This ain't no joke,
ladies and gents,
we're the Men's
Cheerleading Club!
[ICHIRO]
Be there, you'll love it!
You go on at one,
right? We'll be there!
We wouldn't miss
it for the world!
We're the Men's Cheerleading
Club! We're on stage at one p.m!
Blurry. Fuzzy...
[TON] Hey. What's wrong?
Are you sick?
Only optically, Ton.
[HARUKI] Check us out!
We're the Men's Cheer Club!
We hit the stage at one p.m.
sharp, so don't miss out!
It's gonna be a lotta fun!
But don't take my word for it!
Come on out and
see for yourself!
[CHIHIRO]
Hey there!
Chihiro? You look great!
Yeah, uh... Your name
is Haruki, right?
Yeah. Sure is!
I really like your
hair like that.
Thanks. It's new--
Hey there. Haru's
told me 'bout you.
[HARUKI growls]
Kazu! What the hell?
Stop being a weirdo.
[KAZUMA]
What? I'm totally helping.
[laughs]
Well, I hear our performances
start at the same time.
It's too bad. I wanted to
watch the Breakers debut.
Haru really wanted to watch
you, too, isn't that right?
Heh. He can catch the next one.
Just wanted to say that
I'll be rooting for you!
[HARUKI]
U-Uh...
Ohh!
Not cool, dude.
She's pretty hot!
Good luck, man.
Your babies be so cute!
I gotta go.
It's alost showtime.
Hey! Wait for me--
Aww, man.
[KAZUMA]
My bad!
Are you okay?
Uh. Thank you.
[KAZUMA]
Sorry about that!
So he's a Breaker?
--[NATSUKI laughing] Sucker!
--[DAICHI] You're a unicorn now!
Welcome, friend!
We're taking last orders for the
day so you should--Oh, hello.
[GEN]
Ah, man! This is bad, guys.
I'm gettin' super nervous here!
Dude! Stop!
You keep saying that
you'll make me nervous!
[GEN] Yeah, well,
misery loves company.
[ICHIRO]
You jerk!
I was lost to a dark
void of blind despair...
Next time, fix your
contacts before the show.
Relax. It's perfectly normal
to feel nervous before a
big performance, guys.
I'm a total wreck, too.
Same here.
But we've come too far to let
fear get the best of us,
am I right?!
You sure are.
[GEN]
Hell yeah!
I'm gonna go out there and
cheer so hard the girls
are gonna go lose their
ever loving minds!
That goes for me, too!
I'll also make the females
go wild with joy!
Hey, Ton. You're really quiet,
is everything okay?
Yeah. I guess.
I just got a last minute
message from my girlfriend
saying she can't
make it out today.
[ICHIRO, GEN, WATARU scream]
[STAFF 5A]
Uh, Breakers. You're on standby!
[KAZUMA] Okay! Let's
huddle up real quick!
[GEN, ICHIRO, WATARU sigh]
Don't look so down.
Who would have guessed
you'd be our dark horse?
Great. What's the
point of living?
I guess this is the end
of the Wataru Boys.
Don't worry, guys!
If you can really strut
your stuff onstage?
You're sure to pick up a girl!
Trust me on this one!
Wait. Two girlfriends?
[laughs] God forbid.
[inhales] Let's break it all to
smithereens. Are you ready?
[HARUKI]
Go... Fight... Win!
Let's go... Breakers!
[KAZUMA]
Hello, everyone!
[KAZUMA] We're the Meishiin
Men's Cheerleading Team.
The Breakers!
[SAKU gasping]
[NATSUKI, DAICHI growl]
[KAZUMA] This is our squad's
debut performance!
Well folks.
We'll do everything in our
power to make you smile.
We hope you enjoy the-- Uh!
[CROWD chattering]
[KAZUMA]
Uh. We hope you enjoy the show!
[ALL laugh]
Start!
♪♪♪
[HARUKI] In my whole life, I've
never flown so high before.
[ALL]
Breakers! Go!
Meishiin! Hey! C'mon!
We are Breakers!
This is showtime!
We will break!
B-R-E-A-K-E-R-S.
Go... Breakers!
[HARUKI]
The sweat beading on our brows.
The blood pumping
through our veins.
The sound of our breath.
The feeling of moving in sync.
[BREAKERS]
Go! Let's go, Breakers!
One... two... three!
Are you ready?
Come on, fans! Follow us!
Say black and yellow!
You say black... and yellow!
Okay! Three... two...
Three... two... one... Go!
[BREAKERS]
Yeah!
[HARUKI] We still have
lots of work to do.
But right now?
We're giving it our all!
Together!
[ALL]
Go, Breakers!
[CROWD cheering]
[ALL panting]
[ALL laughing]
The Breakers totally
put on the best show.
[GIRL 5B] They sure did. Men's
Cheerleading is the coolest!
A Men's Cheerleading
Team? For real?
The Breakers...
[WATARU] "Dream as
if you'll live forever.
Live as if you'll die today."
[KAZUMA]
Those are the perfect words
to motivate our team right now.
We need to keep our
eyes on the prize
and practice like it's our
last day on earth!
[HARUKI] We're gonna have to
push ourselves extra hard, guys!
Next Episode, "Restart!"
Let's go... Breakers!