[STUDENTS chattering]
[WATARU groans]
No. I can't take it! Uh!
[STUDENT 2A]
Let's go.
[STUDENT 2B]
Yeah.
[WATARU groaning]
Please stop groaning like that.
[laughs] Look at you, Wataru,
you're stiffer than a board.
But my mind is very flexible.
What, as opposed to tight?
I am only tight with my
wallet and my morals.
--[HARUKI] You are the weirdest.
--[laughing]
[phone chimes]
Yeah!
[HARUKI]
Hm? What's goin' on?
[HARUKI, WATARU gasp]
It's our fourth member.
[WATARU grunts]
[WATARU laughs]
Oh, yeah!
Ni shi xuesheng ma ?
As you can see,
you add ma to the end of
most interrogative sentences.
And in Japanese,
you add ka to desu
at the end of a sentence
to make desu ka .
Now, does anyone have
any questions?
This will be covered on the
final, ladies and gentleman.
So it's imperative you always
have a firm grasp
of this information.
[ICHIRO]
What the crap?!
[gasps]
[STUDENTS murmuring]
Can I help you, young man?
[ICHIRO whimpers]
Ew, A bug...!
A freaking bug landed on me!
[HARUKI]
Uh...
All set.
[exhales] Ha, ha!
Hey! Thanks, man!
[WATARU] Never been to a
place like this before.
You're kidding, right?
That's weird, pretty much
everyone at Meishiin's
eaten here at least once.
My family runs a
high-end restaurant.
They told me to avoid cheap,
tawdry places like this.
So leave then.
[GEN]
Old Man!
Where's my pork curry, dude?
Almost done!
Sorry to keep you
waiting, my friend!
[GEN laughs]
Are you really gonna eat that?
You're crazy.
Cheer me on, would ya, ladies?
And... begin!
All right. Down the hatch!
How grotesque.
If he eats it all in 20,
he doesn't have to pay.
There's no way that guy's
our new recruit, is there?
[WATARU]
I hope not.
I know this name, though.
I'm positive I've
seen it somewhere.
Uh? It's been awhile!
Yeah, it's good to see you.
Guess what, kiddo?
Ya still hold the record.
[KAZUMA, HARUKI gasp]
[KAZUMA]
It's Koji Tono!
[HARUKI]
He has the fastest time
in the fried pork
curry challenge!
[KAZUMA]
I don't know why,
but I thought our old judo
captain held that title!
Oh, boy. I really wish
they'd picked a different photo,
that one's from high school.
Are you guys with
the Men's Cheer Club?
Uh. Yeah. I'm Kazuma Hashimoto.
And this here is Haruki Bando.
We're both freshman
sociology majors.
Wataru Mizoguchi.
Freshman business student.
Cool. I'm a freshman, too,
and I study literature.
So, uh. Quick question?
'Course. Fire away, my friend!
Wait... I should order first.
When you get a chance,
could I get a fried pork curry
with noodles and rice, please?
Sure thing!
Yum! It's from the secret menu.
It's my favorite dish.
[ALL]
Ohh...
[GEN]
Man, what a rip off!
Welp, how 'bout some dessert!
Uh?! They ditched me!
What the hell, man?!
Why'd they run off?!
That's about half
of what you owe me.
[GEN]
Are you kidding me?!
[CAFE MANAGER 1A]
Come back with money!
[KAZUMA] Guess you texted me
after you saw the flier?
[TON]
Yeah.
[WATARU]
So, Ton--
[HARUKI]
Ton?
Clearly, Ton is short for Tono.
That's his new nickname now.
You can't just give
him a nickname.
[WATARU]
Too late!
Besides, you two are
always calling each other
"Haru"and "Kazu."
In fact, from now on, I'd like
you to call me "Mizo."
[HARUKI]
Not happening.
[KAZUMA]
No way.
[WATARU] So, tell me, Ton.
How much do you weigh?
[TON]
Uh...
I'm truly inspired by
your social finesse.
Well. Uh. I don't know,
220 pounds?
What's your background;
did you play any sports?
Oh. No. I'm so sorry.
There's no need to
apologize at all.
Best thing about this sport is
there's a position for
every type of person.
One question: Why cheerleading?
[TON]
Because I want to change.
That's great.
[WATARU] I'm thinking of a
famous quote that applies here.
"Today is the first day
of the rest of your life."
Okay... I feel like "there's
no time like the present"
would be more appropriate?
What's more appropriate
than Lester Burnham
in the film American Beauty ?
That is a good movie.
[TON]
Mm-hm.
So, uh. Earlier you said
that there's a role in
cheerleading for every type of
person, does that include me?
Well yeah, of course it does!
The girl holding her hands up
in the air is called the flyer.
All positions matter equally,
but for the audience,
the flyer is the
star of the show.
They do lots of acrobatics, so
they need to be small and light.
As well as spry.
That's me and you, Haru.
Wait, me?
[KAZUMA] The people supporting
the flyer are called the bases.
They carry the flyer on their
shoulders, and steady them
with their palms.
Bases need to be big and sturdy.
Like Ton.
[KAZUMA] The person in the
back is called the spotter.
It's their job to
assist the bases.
Sort of like a tripod leg.
The most important thing that
spotter's have to do is
is decide when to
lift up the flyer.
They have to be intelligent.
[WATARU]
That's me to a T. I'm in.
I made copies in case
you wanna watch later.
But wait. Even with me,
we don't have enough
members, right?
If we want to compete
in a tournament,
we'll need 17 people.
But for now, our goal is to
get seven official members.
Once we have 'em...
...we can make our debut at
the school festival in October!
[HARUKO]
Haru!
[HARUKI]
Uh.
Hey, Sis.
Welcome back.
Thanks a lot.
Is it really true?
Are you quitting Judo?
Just answer me.
[HARUKI]
Mm-hm.
Because of your shoulder?
Not really.
[HARUKO]
So... why then?
I'm asking as your
sister. Please.
Don't walk away.
Whatever you do, don't quit!
[inaudible]
I'm sorry.
[HARUKO] If you aren't
happy with your progress,
you should practice harder!
[HARUKI]
Sis?
There's something I want...
It's not important.
[HARUKI]
Let's see...
Kay, so there's the flyer,
the bases, and the spotter.
I forget, which one am I?
I think I'm that one.
[HARUKI grunts]
No way. I can't do that.
[ALL gasping]
Who wants to give it a try next?
[WATARU]
Me. I'll go first!
Guys? Stand back!
[WATARU grunting]
You're up, Ton.
Uh. Okay!
[TON grunting]
[WATARU]
What are you doing?
Well, look! It's a headstand!
You gotta learn to do that
on your hands though.
Well? Haru?
[WATARU]
He's walking!
Yeah, it's way easier to
stay balanced that way.
Haru, can you stop?
Handstands build up
strength in your core.
They can also improve
your sense of balance.
So do them every chance
you get, understand?
You should be stretching
every day, too.
If you're not flexible,
you run the risk of injury.
It also affects your tumbling.
Wait... tumbling?
You know what tumbling is.
Backflips, somersaults,
acrobatics.
You're gonna be
one of our flyers,
so start practicing
on a trampoline,
we don't want you
breaking any bones.
Uh! Look, this whole
flyer thing...
It's just-- It's not for me.
If you work hard,
you can do anything.
I'm gonna nail this handstand
soon. Just watch!
Me, too.
Now that we covered tumbling,
it's time to talk
about attitude.
When cheering, you need charm,
heart, enthusiasm,
and a smile!
[TON, WATARU]
Yeah!
[KAZUMA]
All right, everyone, line up.
Call and response time!
On me!
Go! Fight! Win!
[WATARU, TON]
[KAZUMA] Smile more, boys!
Come on now, I can't hear you!
[HARUKI grunts]
Go! Fight! Win!
[ALL]
[KAZUMA]
Let me see that big smile, Haru!
[BOTH sigh]
Hey. You feelin' all right?
What?
You know, with this?
Oh. For sure.
I'm having a good
time, it's just...
I'm kinda worried about
the handstand. It's hard.
And I've never been much
of an athlete to be honest.
[HARUKI]
You'll be fine.
[TON]
Huh?
It's kinda weird. I hate being
the center of attention
more than anything.
But since Kazu asked me to do
it, I feel like I have to try.
You sought this out
yourself, though.
You took the initiative
because you wanted to
make a change, right?
I think that's awesome.
Do your best.
And let's have fun.
Thanks a lot, Haru.
[WATARU]
Whoa!
They're tambourelling!
Think you mean tumbling.
[GEN chuckles]
[HARUKI]
Hey! Don't we know him?
The one who lost the fried
pork curry challenge.
[KAZUMA]
Is he in the Tennis Club?
I can do 'em, too!
[HARUKI]
Uh. That's the ladybug guy.
[gasps]
Oh, wow!
That's nice, but it has
nothing to do with tennis.
[ICHIRO]
No, it doesn't.
And neither do you, dude.
[TEAMMATES laugh]
Kazu?
[UPPERCLASSMAN 2A]
Hey!
You losers wanna go
and grab some grub?
--[TEAMMATE 2B] For sure!
--[TEAMMATE 2A] Totally!
[KAZUMA]
Sure thing!
[ALL gasp]
[UPPERCLASSMAN 2A]
Well?
[GROUP]
Salud !
[GIRLS giggle]
Wow!
Awesome!
So are you fellas lookin' to
join our little gang or what?
[HARUKI]
Uh--
Right! Yes!
Haru, just roll with it, dude.
Until we can make our
move, we gotta blend in.
Well. You guys seem
pretty lame to me.
Just cuz you join the
best club around,
doesn't mean you're guaranteed
to get chicks any you know.
Hey. Next time we should
hit up that Italian place
near campus, whadaya say?
[WATARU]
Italian, huh?
That's good stuff!
[HARUKI]
Wataru, are you drunk?
[WATARU] Who cares?
I'm old enough to drink.
Did you get held
back or something?
I'm a failure.
But I will not fail you
sweet comrades! [laughs]
I don't think this
is gonna end well.
[ICHIRO, GEN laugh]
You guys are stupid funny!
You should take that comedy
routine on the road!
Please, you guys are
the funny ones!
Flattery will get
you nowhere here.
Speak for yourself!
[WATARU laughs]
By the way, the name's Soichiro.
But it's Ichiro for short.
And this is Gen.
We're both business majors
but what we are really
into is comedy!
Knock, knock, Ichiro.
[WATARU laughs]
He didn't get to
the punch line yet!
Those were some great
backflips you did earlier.
You guys ever play any sports?
I played baseball in highschool.
I prefer soccer.
[WATARU laughs]
I think maybe you should
put the bottle down.
I think you're just jealous.
So, you played
baseball and soccer.
What made you decide you
to join the Tennis Club?
Well. All boys' clubs are fun,
but they're not as fun as girls.
Since we're both in college now,
we decided to join a club
with a little bit more style.
How can you talk about
style with hair like that?
[KAZUMA]
Yeah, but--
[BOTH]
Hm?
[KAZUMA] It's not what
you expected, is it?
[BOTH]
Uh...
[KAZUMA]
You two should join our club.
Huh?
Hold on... Join your what now?
Men's Cheerleading Club?
I thought you came 'cause you
wanted to hang with this club.
Yeah... Well... That was a lie.
We came here to recruit you.
So are you in, or not?
[ICHIRO, GEN]
Uh...
[UPPERCLASSMAN 2A]
Yo, nerds.
How's everything
down in Nerdville?
Huh? The Men's
Cheerleading Club?
You mean these dorks?
Wearing itty-bitty
little girly skirts,
and dancin' around with
their pom-poms in the air?
What are you,
a bunch of perverts?
Shut up!
We're not perverts...
We're cheer boys!
Cheer boys pour their hearts
and souls into their craft!
And they never look back.
Read the flier, jerk!
[ICHIRO] "Become a hero by
supporting someone else."
[GEN] "Gain the strength
to inspire someone."
Welp. Looks like our
work is done here.
[UPPERCLASSMAN 2A]
What the hell?
Did you really just
infiltrate my club
so you could poach my peeps?
[UPPERCLASSMAN 2A yelps]
[thump, glass shattering]
[PATRONS gasping]
[HARUKI gasps]
Nice takedown. Thanks, man.
[gasps]
[TON]
So, you did Judo before this?
[HARUKI]
Yeah, kind of.
[TON] Well, you're
pretty strong, Bando.
[HARUKI]
Call me Haru.
[KAZUMA]
Oh, and you can call me Kazu.
Haru. Kazu.
Harukalamazoozoo!
Man I didn't know that you
could get any weirder.
[laughs]
Those two are definitely
gonna contact us later.
Yeah? What makes you
so sure about that?
You see his towel?
Covered in messages
from old teammates.
That's a clear signal he's
the kind of competitor
who does what he does for
the love of the group.
[HARUKI]
Look who's talking.
[TON] I can't!
I'm not quite there yet.
That was a good effort!
You've got what it takes, Ton!
A fine hustle!
[laughs]
[HARUKI] You've been
practicing a lot, huh?
Just a little bit.
[KAZUMA] Come on, whaddaya
mean "just a little bit"?
By the way, have those
two contacted you?
Not yet.
So it didn't work.
Ah. What a bummer.
I wouldn't give up
hope just yet.
Oh, that's right!
There's something I've been
meaning to show you!
[HARUKI]
Uh...
Are you showing us that...
...you're not an artist?
Don't finish my thoughts!
Well. Since we need
a few more members
if we want this club
to go official,
I thought we should
put on a show.
Let's see... 'Kay. Next
we do a High V? I think?
[KAZUMA]
Okay. Big smiles, guys!
Arms up! Eyes forward!
[HARUKI]
Ugh.
My movements are so
stiff and awkward.
Uh... And my smile sucks, too.
[phone chimes]
[gasps]
[HARUKI]
Let's go.
Let's go, team.
Let's go, team!
Meishiin!
Go... Fight... Win!
[CHIHIRO]
Uh?
Uh! Sorry!
[HARUKI]
What?! No, I was just--
I should go!
[HARUKI groaning]
[HARUKI] I didn't think
anyone was gonna be here
this early in the morning!
This sucks.
Dude. We're really
doing it here?
We'll stick out
like a sore thumb.
Yeah, sticking out's
the entire point of this.
Let's do it, guys!
Whoa. Wait a minute, Kazu!
[KAZUMA]
No way!
Greetings, fellow
students of Meishiin!
The Men's Cheerleading Club
will now put on a demonstration
for your viewing pleasure!
You there!
Want to throw caution to the
wind and try something new?
How about you?
Take a walk on the wild side
and do something awesome!
Toss your cares away and
cheer your heart out with us!
Haru!
Uh?
You can do this.
Take it away!
[ALL]
Let's go, Meishiin!
Go, fight, win! Go, fight, win!
[ALL]
Let's go. Meishiin!
[clapping]
[STUDENT 2A] What're they?
Street performers?
[STUDENT 2AA]
Which club are they with?
[CHEERLEADERS]
Go... Fight... Win!
It's them!
What are they doin'?
[WATARU grunting]
[HARUKI, KAZUMA]
Let's go, Meishiin!
[STUDENT 2B]
Who are those guys?
[STUDENT 2C]
The Cheerleading Club.
[STUDENT 2B] That's a weird
thing for boys to do.
[CHEERLEADERS]
Go, fight, win! Go, fight, win!
[HARUKI gasps]
[HARUKI, KAZUMA]
Let's go, Meishiin!
Let's go...
[ALL]
...Meishiin!
[CHEERLEADERS]
Let's go, Meishiin!
Go... Fight... Win!
Go... Fight...
[gasps]
[STUDENTS gasping]
[ALL] Cheer Boys!
Let's make some noise!
The Men's Cheerleading
Club is on the lookout
for talented new members!
[panting]
I knew you guys were
gonna show up.
No, you didn't. That's a lie.
We wanna do somthin' new and
this fits the bill. Right?
This club'll get big fast
now that you've got us.
Now there's six of us total.
Yep!
We only need one more person
for the school festival.
We're getting close.
Check it out, it's that
group of guys from earlier.
Yeah, the Cheer Club.
Wasn't that it?
[GIRLS]
Whoa!
[GIRL 2C]
Too cool!
[GEN chuckles]
[ICHIRO exhales]
[HARUKI]
Quick question.
Did you two join the
Cheerleading Club
just so you could pick up girls?
[birds chirping]
[KAZUMA]
Risujiro?
[HARUKI]
Isn't he an advertising mascot?
[SHO] Yeah. He's the greatest
mascot of all time.
[TON] Squirrels are pretty
nimble, you know?
Truth is, sometimes I wish
I was more like a squirrel.
[WATARU]
I will be a squirrel!
I'm gonna be king
of the squirrels!
[KAZUMA] Next Time,
"The Seventh Squirrelurai."
Go... Fight... Win!