♪♪♪
[BREAKERS]
Go Breakers!
That's good.
Take a break everyone.
[ALL panting]
[TAKAGI]
You've worked really hard
these past few weeks, gentlemen.
And you've come a long way.
But there's one last
hurdle to cross.
[KAZUMA]
Oh, yeah?
What are you talking about?
[TAKAGI]
Here.
What do our journals
have to do with this?
[TAKAGI]
Everything you need to know
is written inside these books.
I've read every single word
each of you has written down
time and time again.
So, believe me boys.
More than your training.
More than your practice.
More than your routine.
This will be your
most important task.
[BOTH gasp]
[TAKAGI]
Pass 'em around.
[HARUKI, KAZUMA]
Uh?
Hold on. Why would we do that?
You guys are gonna read
each other's journals.
[HARUKI, KAZUMA gasping]
[ALL gasping]
[BREAKERS]
Huh?!
Why's everyone so down?
You're not gonna win lookin'
like that, kiddos.
[KAZUMA]
Yeah. You're probably right.
[HARUKI groans]
[CAFE MANAGER 1A]
Are you gonna talk to each other
or just sit there
looking embarrassed?
Your handwriting's adorable.
I had no idea you wrote
in bubble letters.
Be a gentleman and never
mention it again.
Hey Sho, so about your journal.
Uh. Why're there so many
Risujiro stickers?
'Cause Risu's totally awesome.
Hey, Takeru. You write with
such awesome passion!
Ahh! Just kill me now!
[ICHIRO] Ya know what?
This didn't happen!
Let's make a pact to never
speak of this again!
[WATARU]
I concur!
[BREAKERS chattering]
This is the worst...
You guys! Listen!
You know?
I never thought our Cheerleading
Club would make it this far,
but we did.
It began with me and Haru,
and it's gotten bigger
than we ever imagined.
We set out with no experience,
no equipment, heck,
we didn't even have
a coach. Just a dream.
On our first day of practice,
you two couldn't do a handstand.
[WATARU, TON grunt]
[KAZUMA] Then came Ichiro and
Gen, and we got a little better.
And when Sho got involved,
we finally started to look
like real cheerleaders.
But we didn't stop
there. No sir.
We performed at
the school festival,
and our numbers
swelled from 7 to 16.
And now? We're a day away
from the Championship.
Think about that. It's so cool.
Guys. I'm glad we
made it this far.
Regardless of
what happens...
[KAZUMA laughs]
Who am I kidding?
I want us to win it all
tomorrow, all right?
Ha!
So, leave everything
out there on the stage.
And let's put on a show
like they've never seen!
Heck yeah! I'm in!
I agree with the Captain.
[TON]
Mm!
You ready, Gen?
I'm ready when you are, dude!
[KAZUMA]
Let's get 'em!
[BREAKERS chattering]
[GIN] You know. It might
be your hair color,
but you don't look
like yourself.
My appearance may have changed,
but I'm still the same guy.
Right. I guess that's
true, but still.
I only dyed it for one reason.
Because I wanted to show off.
I was trying to be unique.
I was trying to be different.
Coach wasn't buyin' it, though.
She saw right through me.
Listen, about what you wrote...
[KIN] Mock my handwriting,
and I'll dye your hair pink!
I'm not making fun of you.
I found it very moving, Kin!
[DOH]
So did I!
[KIN]
Uh?
[KIN] I used to think a man
could only become stronger
by being the bad boy.
But now I see how far from
the truth that really is.
Back then? I was just another
miserable, good-for-nothing jerk
who didn't care about anyone
or anything but himself.
But, Cheerleading
opened my mind.
I learned that a man can
truly become stronger
through hard work.
Through blood, sweat, and tears,
and seeing a task
through to the end.
Can I ask you about
your journal?
Why did you write
so much about me?
Heh, well, uh. It's because
Coach wrote to spoil others
is to spoil yourself, so I put
all my spoiling in one place.
We're family, aren't we? We're
bros. If I'm spoilin' someone,
it might as well be you man.
[TAKUMI] Ya know my journal
said the exact same thing
as Gin and Doh's?
Weird, huh?
[GIN] Kin'll be graduating
and leaving the team soon.
And even though it'll be
weird not having him around,
I think we can honor
him by trying our best.
[DOH] I'm thankful I got
to be on the team with him,
and I'm lucky to
call him my friend.
[TAKUMI]
I'll miss Takuya when he's gone.
We did everything together.
Break-dancing, cheering,
competing in tournaments.
Heck, I'll even miss him
worrying about me.
You're the best, bro. I love ya!
Hey, Arale, how goes it?
[ARALE barks]
[HISASHI]
Sorry buddy,
but I gotta leave you
alone tomorrow, too.
[laughs]
You should'a seen
Sho's journal.
He drew a bunch of squirrels
all over the stupid thing.
[HISASHI]
Uh...
As for mine? Let's look.
It says, "Accept that people
are different from you."
Whaddaya think about that, pup?
Guess what?
I actually get it now.
[HISASHI] My reasons for
wanting to do cheerleading
were different than
everyone else's,
and at first, that annoyed me.
But now I realize it's
ultimately a good thing.
Sure, people butt
heads now and then.
But sometimes conflict is the
best way to solve a problem.
And ya'know what? That's part
of what makes team sports fun.
Perfect-o!
[sighs]
[TAKERU] I hope everything
goes well at Nationals.
If I don't pee my pants out
there, then, all things
considered, I'll count
that as a massive victory.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
"This club is the
worst of all time!
I can't goof off with my friends
and there's no time for fun!
And apart from Ichiro, my
teammates are boring and lame!
Why do I have to put up
with this crap anyway?
All I want from this Club
is to look awesome!
Why the heck are these idiots
falling down all the time?
I can't catch them like that.
It sort of freaks me out!"
Who am I kidding?
When they fall, it totally
freaks me out!
[SAKU]
Yeah, me too.
[TAKERU yelping]
Huh? Why're you here?
I just thought I could use
a brush up rehearsal. You?
[TAKERU]
Don't scare me like that!
[SAKU]
So, it freaks you out, too, huh?
Huh?
I thought I was the only one.
[TAKERU]
"As scared as I am,
it's gotta be a thousand
times worse for the flyers.
Which is why I have to make sure
I catch those guys every time!
They're depending on me!
I can't let them down!"
Ha, ha. I guess I'm a
bit of a drama queen.
Not at all. If I hadn't
read your journal,
I never would've
guessed how you felt.
It was really moving.
Eh, it's no big deal.
If anybody's a big deal, it's
you! Flyin' through the air!
I'm really happy for you, Saku.
You discovered your talent.
[SAKU gasps]
[SAKU]
"I've always felt self-loathing.
I hated how small I was.
How fragile and girlish
I felt like I looked.
But...
Those are the same qualities
that make me an awesome flyer.
Like Kazu, and like Haru, too!"
So, are ya gonna
do it, too, dude?
'Cause I think you
look all pumped up!
Yeah!
[TAKERU]
Double...
[BOTH]
...Buh-roccoli!
[BOTH laughing]
Twin Broccoli! A pair
of broccoli! [laughing]
[KAZUMA laughs]
[KAZUMA]
Mom... Dad...
Thanks to you two,
I'm not alone.
I have friends.
They're my teammates.
[HARUKI laughs]
[knocking]
[HARUKO]
Haru, can I come in?
Yeah, sure.
[HARUKO]
Here.
Thank you.
Good luck. I'll cheer for ya.
[HARUKI]
Uh?
Oh. I just thought of this is it
weird to cheer on cheerleaders?
No way. It's not
weird at all, Sis.
That's cheerleading.
Everyone coming together.
Performers and audience. To say,
"let's all do our best today!"
[HARUKO]
Mm.
[BREAKERS chattering]
Gentlemen.
Today we courageously
leap without looking!
That seems a little dangerous!
We will not stop fighting until
justice is achieved for all!
We're not Superheroes,
you know?
[ZI XUAN] Get out there
and break some legs, guys!
[TAKERU]
I'd rather not break anything!
Oh god, it's too much.
Somebody please make him stop
before I crash this
bus into a wall.
Zi Xuan sure has come a
long way. I'm proud of him.
Depends on what you
mean by "long way."
[HARUKI, KAZUMA laugh]
Still can't believe we're here.
Yeah.
[DREAMS CAPTAIN 4A]
Coach Takagi!
[TAKAGI] Hi! Did you all
just get here, too?
Yes, we're about to
have a team meeting.
[TAKAGI]
Well, I'm looking forward
to watching your
performance today!
Good luck!
[DREAMS CAPTAIN 4A]
Thank you very much!
We'll see you out there!
[DREAMS]
Later, Coach!
You're cool, right?
Yeah, I'm good.
[gasps]
[HARUKI]
Uh?
Hey!
[CHIHIRO]
Uh...?
Good luck out there!
You too! See ya later!
Haru. All my being weeps
for your broken heart!
Stop it dude, you're
gonna cramp our style.
Get it together!
[CHEERLEADERS chattering]
[KAORU]
Well, speak of the devil.
Hello, Jin.
I was talking, jerk!
Yeah. Sorry. Was it Kyle, or...?
It's Kaoru! Kaoru.
I guarantee you're gonna
remember it after today!
Doubtful.
[chuckles]
Uh?
Captain Jin. We look forward
to destroying you!
[TAKERU] Take it easy
with the trash talk, dude!
Yeah, hasn't anyone ever told
you not to poke a sleeping bear?
Too late, nerds, because
this sleeping bear's
already awake and he's about
to eat your loser lunch!
I think your mother should've
named you Kao-Rude!
I'd cut that out, Pee-Quan!
You need to hear this.
Our routine's not a circus!
Uh?!
[gasps]
Sho wrote that you called us
a circus in his journal.
But if you really believe that,
then you don't know
the Breakers at all!
[SHO]
Hey. That's enough, okay?
[ZI XUAN]
No, it's not right, Sho!
You know what Coach
wrote in my journal?
[BOTH]
You brought it with you?!
Check it out.
"Be everyone's teammate!"
I spent a long time
thinking about that.
About what a true
teammate really is.
And then one day it hit
me like a ton of bricks.
And I saw it clearly.
Teammates are the people who
stand up for you no matter what!
Now that was a cool speech.
Yeah, it was.
Let's get out there
today and show 'em
what the Breakers are made of!
We're about to make you
smile till it hurts Jin.
[TON]
Mm.
[SHO gasping]
You know. You're very lucky
to have teammates like them.
[inaudible]
Yeah, you're right.
I think I can finally
show you our routine
with my head held high.
Oh yeah? We'll see about that.
Cool headband, said no one.
[KAORU]
It keeps my bangs in place!
[ALL laughing]
[phone chimes]
It's Sakura. She says
she just arrived.
[SHO gasps]
There she is.
Hey, uh. Who's the little kid?
[TAKAGI]
That's my son, Haru.
[BOTH gasping]
He's not a bad looking
guy either, is he?
Coach, wait. Does this mean...
You're a mother. How lovely.
[GIN, DOH]
Uh...
[HARUKI, KAZUMA laugh]
[laughs]
Kirari!
--Woo! Go!
--You can do it, Saku!
You got this!
[SAKU whimpering]
[inaudible]
They're here.
[ANNOUNCER 10A]
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
it's time for the
National Cheerleading
Championship Finals!
How many more groups before us?
I think we're up next, so...
I'm nervous.
Like really nervous.
Yeah, me too.
[TAKUMI grunts]
What's more nerve-wracking, Ton,
going on a hot date or
competing in the Nationals?
I mean like in terms
of performance anxiety,
this is way worse.
[ICHIRO, GEN growling]
Almost time, Breakers!
Right this way, please!
Right!
♪♪♪
[SPARKS]
Go, Sparks!
[CROWD cheering]
[KAZUMA]
Hey, guys.
[ALL gasp]
We got this!
Kazu.
Just remember to smile,
and we'll make 'em
all smile with us!
[ANNOUNCER 10A]
Now onto the next team!
Hailing from
Meiyshiin University,
let's hear it for the Breakers!
[CROWD cheers]
All right! This is it.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER 10A]
An All-Men's Cheerleading Club,
the Meishiin Breakers formed
just about a year ago.
[BREAKERS]
Go, fight, win!
Let's go... Breakers!
[HARUKI]
Ready!
♪♪♪
[WATARU] I was always
afraid of my true self.
That's why I hid behind
famous quotations.
But now I realize it's
by embracing who we are,
that we can better
understand others.
So I don't hide anymore.
I use my own words now.
And they're awesome.
[ICHIRO]
I was arrogant.
That's what screwed me up during
practice for the festival.
I thought I could be better
than everyone around me.
And that's exactly what
was holding me back.
But now, I'm moving forward.
With open eyes and an open mind.
[GEN] Coach saw what
I needed right away.
[GEN]
Whether it was sports or girls,
I was always comparing
myself to him
instead of worrying
about the team.
But... everyone gets frustrated.
And everyone has things
they're trying to work on!
[GEN]
Before you can help the team,
you have to conquer yourself!
[BREAKERS]
Ha!
Welcome!
B-R-E-A-K-E-R-S!
[BREAKERS]
Go... Breakers!
C'mon, fans! Follow us!
Say black and yellow!
You say black and yellow!
Okay, let's go... Meishiin!
Go for love and... peace!
[inaudible]
[BREAKERS]
Ready!
[TON] I used to criticize
myself constantly.
I'd say, "I can't do this,
it's hopeless."
And I couldn't... Not alone.
But when I had teammates
depending on me.
Supporting me... I learned.
My body is a major
asset for this team.
And when I'm supporting others?
Well, that's when
I'm at my best.
[KAZUMA]
Here's the truth.
Without Haru, I couldn't have
accomplished any of this.
I don't even know if it's
possible to beat him.
But I'm always gonna give
this my all, no matter what.
Because... that's
exactly what Haru does.
[HARUKI]
I can't beat Kazu.
Every time I thought that, it's
like he saw right through me.
He knew what was in my heart.
[HARUKI] But, just like
the rest of this team,
I had to break through it.
After all, it's in the name.
[HARUKI] That's why, from now
on, I wanna beat myself!
[BREAKERS]
Go, Breakers!
[CROWD cheering]
[BREAKERS laughing]
[KAZUMA]
Wanna do something different?
Then join the Men's Cheer Club!
[HARUKI]
Does this look fun to you?
Join the Breakers today, and
let's make some people smile!
Go... Fight... Win!
[BREAKERS]
We are... Breakers!