[SHO]
Hold it for one minute.
Ready? Begin!
[ALL grunting]
Keep your bodies
completely straight.
You're almost there!
--[beeping]
--[ALL sigh]
[ICHIRO]
That was brutal!
[GEN]
No kidding...
You only feel that way because
you have no core strength.
[KAZUMA, HARUKI grunting]
[SHO] This isn't just a matter
of bulking up, okay?
Our focus is on training
the muscles necessary
for cheerleading.
Sho's super smart. We're lucky
he decided to join us.
[KAZUMA]
Mm. Thanks a lot.
If you're okay with it,
I think we should start
practicing stunts.
Wait. For real?
Don't you remember?
Sho doesn't want to.
[SHO] But listen, you should
know I won't do any stunts.
I didn't say I
wouldn't teach you.
One thing I know for
sure is I don't want
a bunch of amateurs getting
hurt on my watch.
Yeah, me neither.
A stunt is a
difficult group feat
performed chiefly
to gain attention!
Bases, flyers, and spotters
have to work together!
[ALL]
Whoa...
[SHO]
Heh.
[BOTH] Yeah, that's right.
We used the internet!
Time for the cheer boys
to take flight.
[TON]
Mm!
Yeah. Let's do this thing!
[ICHIRO, GEN, TON]
Woo!
We have a number of stunts
to choose from, as you know.
These drawings are garbage.
[WATARU] He makes Kazu
look like Rembrandt.
They kinda look like
prehistoric cave paintings.
Well, they're certainly...
expressive.
[SHO grunts]
I think we're missing
the point here.
Cool, let's have a look.
So, I think it'd make sense to
start things off nice and simple
by learning the Elevator stunt.
Let's see. Where is it?
[SHO]
It's this one.
First, the bases lift
the flyer into the air
to chest height.
Then they do an Extension.
They straighten their arms and
push the flyer straight up.
Then, of course,
there's the Basket Toss.
That's where you start
with the Elevator
and then throw
the flyer into the air.
[laughs]
Perfect.
Whaddaya say we head on
out and get to work, guys?
[door opens, bell chimes]
Sorry for making you
look after the place.
Thanks a lot, kids!
We'll need a practice facility
with a non-leaky roof.
Anyone have suggestions?
We could try out the local gym.
It's free, if we
win their lottery.
Yeah, I'm definitely
down for not paying.
[KAZUMA]
Should we collect dues?
I know it sucks,
but we'll have to pay for stuff
like uniforms eventually.
[ICHIRO] I have two words
for you: Unisex Uniforms!
[GEN] How about we just put
you in a miniskirt instead?
[TON] I'm a little worried
about the cost.
Aren't those things
kind of expensive?
[gasps]
Uh, oh. Kinda want to hurl.
I can't be a flyer.
[HARUKI groans]
[GIRL 4A] Whoa, it looks
like that guy's flying.
[gasps]
Dude, look that that ball soar!
I'd never fall for that.
[coughing]
[GIRL 4C]
Their prices are so high.
[HARUKI yelps]
[BOY 4B] Those are my noodles,
don't mix 'em up!
[HARUKI gasps]
[GIRL 4D]
He fell! He crashed! He burned!
[HARUKI whimpering]
[sighs]
[ICHIRO]
Ain't it the best bein' on top?
[gasps]
Do you wanna switch with
me, Haru? I'll do it.
[SHO]
No. You're better off elsewhere.
Kazu and Haru have the
best builds for flying.
I'm not sure it's a good idea.
You know, leaping... in the air.
Would you rather do
something else?
Well, I wouldn't
say that exactly.
You're painfully shy and you
always choke under pressure!
No, I wouldn't really
say that either.
[TON]
Hey! What's up, Wataru?
I come with joyful
tidings, my friends.
Hot damn. She is hot!
[WATARU]
She's a member of Dreams--
the Meishiin Women's
Cheerleading Team.
Since they have so
much experience,
I arranged for us to
practice together.
[ALL gasp]
[WATARU]
Hang onto your pom-poms.
[ICHIRO]
An all-female team.
[GEN]
All of them in miniskirts.
[WATARU]
Indeed.
[CHEERLEADERS]
Go... Fight... Win!
It's not speed-dating,
guys, it's practice.
I wanted to see some
live stunts up-close.
As our main spotter,
it's time I learned.
[GEN]
You've got a point.
[ICHIRO] Wouldn't hurt
to observe the bases.
Wataru. Any idea when
this practice'll take place?
[WATARU]
Two weeks from today.
Great. That gives us
plenty of time to work on
the Elevator and the Extension!
We can show 'em!
What?!
The Dreams have an excellent
cheerleading coach.
This is a great chance for
us to get some feedback.
Do you think we can pull
it off in two weeks, Sho?
Hello?
Uh! We can... by the
skin of our teeth.
[ICHIRO]
All right!
Let's show those sexy ladies
what we're made of!
And I'm nervous.
No need to be.
They'll be most impressed
by your diligence!
[GEN]
Haru and Kazu are so lucky.
The chicks always
dig flyers the most!
[HARUKI yelping]
[ICHIRO grunts]
Spotter. Hold him tight!
Doing my best!
Bend your knees and then
extend your legs!
Use the momentum
from the extension
to lift him with your body!
[BOTH grunting]
[SHO]
Flyer! Stand up quickly!
Nice!
It worked, guys.
It's just like Sho said,
standing up in one smooth
motion makes it easier!
Oh, wow. He's good!
Yeah.
All right. Your turn.
Huh?! Sure.
[TON] Try your best to
keep your knees aligned.
[ICHIRO] Use the momentum
from extending your legs.
And lift your body! Come on!
Oh, crap!
[SHO]
Straighten your knees, Haru!
Uh. Okay.
[SHO]
Stay upright! Don't wobble!
[HARUKI whimpering]
[TON groaning]
Let's take a break, guys.
[exhales]
I'm so sorry. I tried,
but I couldn't support you.
No. It's not you.
I'm the one to blame,
Ton. Thing is--
[KAZUMA]
Just give it another go.
Uh?
Don't stress out.
"If it at first you don't
succeed," right?
No matter what, I'll be
here. Right behind you.
Thank you...?
[HARUKI]
It's just no use.
[HARUKI grunts]
[gasps] Kazu!
'Cause guess what?
You and me, we're about
to start something new.
All right! Go, fight win!
Congrats. You just nailed
a perfect Extension.
Kazu sure is talented, isn't he?
Stand up!
You're almost there, Haru!
[gasping] Oh, no! Ahh!
Haru!
Hey. You all right?
What's wrong?
[HARUKI]
I can't do it.
[ALL]
Huh?
[HARUKI] I wish I would've
told you this sooner.
But the truth is...
I'm afraid of heights.
[KAZUMA] I thought you got
over that in grade school.
We chill on your roof!
[HARUKI] Yeah, but I still can't
look down from up there.
Everyone's been working so hard.
I just couldn't bring
myself to tell you.
I'm so sorry, guys.
I'm the one who should
apologize, Haru.
I wondered why you
sucked so bad.
Don't be such a jackass.
[ICHIRO groans]
So what about Dreams?
Are we going to cancel?
Do you think it's possible
they'll let us postpone?
Wait. Maybe Sho can
take his place!
Good call.
You wouldn't mind stepping in
just once, would you, Sho?
Yeah, about that.
I'm not going. Sorry.
[GEN, KAZUMA]
Huh?
Why not?
This is the first
I'm hearing of it.
[SHO]
I can't. I have a new job.
You didn't mention
that before, either.
Can't you take a day off?
Where ya workin' at?
Uh. At the restaurant.
Near the train station.
For real? That's weird.
I just got a job there too.
I start tomorrow.
[SHO]
Uh...
Anyway, I'm busy. I can't go.
[WATARU]
Not even for miniskirts?
That was inappropriate.
Hello, how can I help you?
Wipe that creepy look
off your face, kid.
You'll scare off the
customers like that.
Actually, it looks like
the damage is done.
Hey.
What's the matter
with you, Haru,
you look like a plague victim.
[KAZUMA]
I really am sorry.
I should've noticed
something was wrong.
Hey I'm sorry, too.
I had no idea that your mother
was a cheerleader.
And the thought of you wanting
to be one didn't cross my mind.
I'm supposed to know everything
about you, aren't I?
[KAZUMA]
Uh...
Let me worry about
the flying stuff.
You just focus on tumbling.
Whaddaya say?
[phone chimes]
[gasps]
It's the fellas.
[CHEERLEADERS]
Go... Fight... Win!
[DREAMS CAPTAIN 4A]
Five, six, seven, eight!
[CHEERLEADERS]
Go! Go Dreams!
We are number one!
[DREAMS CAPTAIN 4A]
I can't hear you!
[CHEERLEADERS]
Right!
[DREAMS CAPTAIN 4A]
Five, six, seven, eight!
[ICHIRO]
So hot...
[CHEERLEADERS]
Go! Go Dreams!
We are number one!
Hey, it's her.
She's amazing.
[TON]
Mm-hm.
[SATSUKI] You there.
What are you doing in my gym?
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL gasping]
We are with the Men's
Cheerleading Club of Meishiin.
Here for joint training.
Joint training, huh?
Welcome, boys.
I'm a Dreams OG.
But if you call me old,
you'll regret it.
It's nice to meet you,
Coach Satsuki.
There was no such thing
as a men's team.
At least not when I was a
student. You guys have a name?
We're still working on that,
we just formed a little
over a month ago.
Let's see.
You said that since you're
quite experienced,
both of our organizations
could benefit
from a joint training session,
or did I somehow mishear you?
[ALL]
Uh?!
[WATARU] In the words of George
Armstrong Custer, "My bad."
[ALL sigh]
[sighs] I guess we
don't have a choice.
A deal's a deal, we'll watch you
practice and do what we can.
[BOYS gasp]
Thanks a lot! I know
we're basically rookies,
but please don't feel like you
have to take it easy on us!
[KAZUMA]
Go... Fight... Win!
Listen up, bases, your elbows
are too low! Lift em'!
[HARUKI, TON]
Uh...
[BOTH]
Yes, mam!
Spotter, get your
head in the game!
[WATARU]
Uh. Right!
[SATSUKI] Flyer! Your posture is
terrible! Straighten those arms!
Right!
All right. Come on down.
So, tell me, what's
your position, Chubs?
Mm. I'm not a hundred
percent sure. A base?
Bieber?
[gasps]
I'm a flyer. Or trying to be.
[SATSUKI] What do you
mean "trying to be"?
Let's go! Get up there
and show me!
This is bad!
Did ya come here to practice
cheerleading or not?
Haru's not quite ready for this.
I'm fine.
But... you said...
The Elevator. Let's go.
[HARUKI whimpers]
Eyes straight ahead.
Try to keep both
your knees locked.
Yes, ma'am!
[SATSUKI] And put on a damn
smile if you still know how.
Oh God, stop.
[FLYER 4A]
Let's... Go... Dreams!
My girls make you look like
nursing home residents,
any guesses why?
You take care to
master the basics.
[SATSUKI] Yes. Basics are
important. But what else?
[KAZUMA]
Technique?
[SATSUKI] All right. Technique's
a big part of it, too.
You boys are obviously trying
to get through these stunts
with sheer force.
But if you had decent technique,
your stunts would look better,
and you could
practice for longer.
Still, the most important
element is trust.
If you and your teammates
have faith in one another
there isn't a move you
can't accomplish.
You shouldn't be afraid
of falling when you fly.
Not if you know that your
squad'll be there to catch you.
Your problem is you
don't have any trust.
[gasps]
That's why you can't stand
up during the Elevator.
Until you overcome it,
you'll never get better.
How can I not trust them? Jeez.
[CHIHIRO] Looks like you're
drinks good to go.
Are you following me?
No, I didn't know you
were a member of Dreams.
I'm Chihiro Sakai.
Okay.
[HARUKI]
See ya.
[CHIHIRO]
Coach is tough.
But if you were hopeless,
she wouldn't waste her time.
[HARUKI]
What?
So don't give up kay?
Uh.
Uh-oh.
[CHEER COACH 4A] Exceptional
work today, ladies! Well done!
Where in the world did Haru go?
I dunno.
[WATARU, KAZUMA]
Uh.
Huh? You two? Why're you here?
[ALL gasp]
[HARUKI]
Kazu! Guess who I jus--?
Uh! These are the idiots
I told you about.
The wannabes from our last show!
What are you talkin' about?
[SATSUKI] Hey there.
What can I do for you?
Hello ma'am.
Next month's joint
demonstration, remember?
We scheduled a meeting.
[SATSUKI]
Of course.
Guess I should make
some introductions.
This is Captain Domoto of the
Yomay University Cheer Squad.
Called Sparks.
You can call me Jin
I'm Kaoru Hanasaki.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Hey, Coach. What exactly is
your connection to these guys?
[SATSUKI] They're the Men's
Cheerleading Club of Meishiin.
Are you serious?
I don't think I've ever heard
of an all-Men's team before.
Thanks!
Always nice to meet more
cheerleading fans.
But, if you're just in
this for the limelight,
you might as well give up now.
Cause cheering's no joke.
Uh!
It's easy enough to start;
sticking around is
the hard part.
Cheerleading isn't a sport for
amateurs who delude themselves.
[ALL gasping]
Jin's absolutely
right about that.
To get better at this,
you're gonna need to work
with an experienced coach.
So tell me, have you
guys found one yet?
Well our friend Sho has
been training us.
We wanted him to come today
but he said he had to work.
[SATSUKI] Sho? Wait,
do you mean Sho Tokugawa?
Yeah, that's the guy,
how do you know him?
I guess he didn't give up
on cheering after all.
He'd be better off
if he had though.
I wonder what happened
between them.
Everybody has secrets, right?
He'll tell us when
he's good and ready.
[phone chimes]
[KAZUMA]
It's him.
I've got an idea: you guys have
time for a meeting tonight?
As long we don't have it at
Café Sunflower, I'm good!
My place. That cool?
[ALL]
Huh?
[KAZUMA gasps]
The fall here would be lethal.
No, it isn't that bad.
Are you kidding me,
it's like four floors?
[groans] Sorry.
[sighs]
[ICHIRO] That really wasn't
cool of me, my bad, Haru.
[GEN] You know... this isn't
a bad place to practice.
[WATARU]
Yes, I concur.
[KAZUMA] How 'bout we call
this meeting to order?
If there's one thing
we regret today...
...it's that we
didn't get a chance
to talk to any beautiful babes.
Although, we did hit
it off with the OG.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
What's OG stand for, anyway?
It means old girl, but you
know, she's still got it.
[BOTH laughing]
[HARUKI]
Sho. Take a seat.
It's higher up here
than I thought it'd be.
We're tryin' not to mention that
in front of you know who.
[SHO] Gotcha. So, tell me, how
did it go with the Dreamers?
[ICHIRO]
Honestly? Not that good.
Those cheerleaders were
a million times better
than we'll ever be.
It sort of kills me to admit
this, but they were great.
[ICHIRO] The only thing we ruled
at was failing. It was rough.
Complete and total suck patrol.
That bad, huh?
Their coach said it's that
I don't trust my teammates.
Uh!
This was my fault.
[SHO]
You're wrong.
[HARUKI]
Uh?
[SHO] Look. In cheering, it's
never one person's fault.
When the people who jump are
in sync with the people
who catch them, when everyone
trusts each other...
...that's when
perfection is possible.
"If you give up when
things go wrong,
then a failure stays a failure.
But if you persist
until you succeed, that
failure becomes a success."
The founder of
Panasonic said that.
They make great
consumer electronics.
Good thing we're not
giving up, then. Right?
[TON grunts]
--[ICHIRO] Heck yeah!
--[GEN] I'm all in!
And Sho?
We'll be counting on your
expertise moving forward.
Sounds good.
[TON] And, we still need
to think of a team name.
[WATARU]
The Wataru Seven?
[ICHIRO]
Yeah, not gonna happen.
[WATARU]
The Wataru Boys.
[GEN]
That one either, buddy.
[WATARU]
Well...
[ICHIRO]
I vote for Team Risujiro!
[SHO]
I like that one.
You know. I wanna
break some things.
The assumptions of those
who won't recognize
men's cheerleading.
The taunts of those who
say we can't succeed.
I wanna break through
Wataru's quotes
and see what he has to say.
[gasps]
[KAZUMA] Tono, I want to help
you break those insecurities.
Uh!
[KAZUMA]
Haru, your sense of guilt.
And Sho. Whatever it is
that's weighing you down.
I wanna break somethin'.
Like real bad.
Do you mean your dry
spell with the ladies?
Look who's talking!
[TON laughs]
[WATARU]
Heh.
Me too, Kazu.
[KAZUMA, SHO]
Uh?
[HARUKI] I wanna break
apart my old self.
And start over from scratch.
[KAZUMA gasps]
So let's do it.
[HARUKI]
Uh?
Let's break the beliefs
of all the naysayers.
Of anyone who doubts us!
Hold up. We could use
this, not break, but--
[BOTH gasp]
The Breakers!
Ha!
[KAZUMA]
Heh.
From now on, guys,
we're the Breakers!
That's perfect!
It's pretty cheesy,
but it works.
We'll save Wataru Boys
for next time.
[KAZUMA]
This feels right, guys.
Together, we seven'll
break it all!
Ha!
[KAZUMA]
All right.
[ALL]
Go, fight, win!
Let's go... Breakers!
[ALL laughing, chattering]
[SHO]
Risujiro's Breakers!
Don't look so down.
[GEN] Who would have guessed
you'd be our dark horse?
[WATARU] Guess this is
the end of the Wataru Boys.
[KAZUMA] If you can really
strut your stuff onstage,
you're sure to pick up a girl.
[TON]
Two girlfriends?
[HARUKI]
Maybe, yeah.
[KAZUMA] Let's break it
all to smithereens.
[HARUKI, KAZUMA] Next Time:
"Let's Go, Breakers!"
Go... Fight... Win!