[sighs]
[ICHIRO]
This is awesome!
I had no idea there was a
bathhouse this close to campus!
[KAZUMA]
It's not too bad.
Yeah. I could get used to this.
[GEN] There's nothin' better
than a little r and r
after a hard day's training,
that's for sure.
Yes, this is quite lovely.
Too bad it's men
only, am I ri--?
Hey. Where's Haru?
[ICHIRO] Uh. I don't know or
care, I'm not his mother.
I care. Come on, man.
We should go find him.
Fine...
Oh, darling!
Haruki dear!
[GEN]
Shut up...
[ICHIRO]
Excuse me sir,
you haven't seen our
baby boy have you?
He's terribly shy!
Stop it. Jerk!
[ICHIRO] And there's a
big mole right on his--
[GEN]
Making a scene!
[WATARU]
Pool fight!
[BOYS chattering, laughing]
We know how to joke around.
But can we cheer?
[sighs]
[ICHIRO] Yo, dude! Pass the
spice blend, would ya?
[KAZUMA]
Huh?
Sup, Haru? Why the
cold-shoulder, man?
[GEN] It's because you were
makin' fun of him... Right?
Huh? No, uh. It's nothing.
So what?
You shy or somethin'?
That's right!
I can't believe it, I almost
forgot to tell you!
I started a group thread so we
can stay in constant contact
about practice and events
and stuff like that.
How cool!
Yup! And remember, everyone,
you should be stretching and
practicing those handstands
at least once a day.
Now we'll always be together!
[laughs]
Listen, every time
you laugh like that,
I picture you killing cats.
Sorry, but I've never been on
a group text chain before.
That doesn't mean you
should spam us all!
[KAZUMA chuckles]
We're up to six members.
Add one more, and we
can make our debut.
Yeah. But who?
[ICHIRO, GEN]
Uh...
Not to worry boys.
Ichiro and I know just the
guy for this kinda job!
[WATARU]
He certainly is good looking.
That man right there
is Sho Tokugawa.
We won't find a better
recruit in the whole school.
Well, he does look the part.
But let's see if he's as
good as you say he is.
He's got a strong, athletic
build, doesn't he?
Oh! Kazu, you naughty boy.
My eyes are up here!
He's just yankin' his chain!
[sighs]
[gasps]
[inaudible]
So. You're taking gym
today, too, are you?
Uh. Well... Yep.
Your uh-- Is it okay?
Oh! Yeah. I fell on
the mat earlier,
face first, and got a
bloody nose, that's all.
[CHIHIRO]
Hey.
Thanks for caring. That's
really sweet of you. Bye!
[ICHIRO]
You guys! Showtime!
[KAZUMA]
That was a solid round-off.
His back handspring's good, too.
And his backflip is savage!
He's quite agile.
He's the one, you guys.
Let's go and get him!
Jackpot!
[GEN]
Tokugawa!
[ICHIRO]
You rocked it out there, buddy!
[ALL]
Uh...
[STUDENTS chattering]
[SHO] So, what's up?
What do you want from me?
Hey, is that Risu on your shirt?
[KAZUMA]
Risu?
Isn't he from one of
those nut advertisements?
Yeah. He's the greatest
mascot of all time. And?
[KAZUMA] Nothing!
Let's get down to business.
Me and the fellas
want you to join
the Men's Cheerleading Club.
Look, here's the deal.
We snuck into your class
because we've been thinking
of recruiting you.
And damn, you're the best
acrobat I've seen in person.
If you were to join us,
it would be quite the honor.
You'd make a great fit.
You're a Men's Cheer
Club, are you?
That's interesting. We already
have a female squad here.
But I guess you do
things differently.
[KAZUMA] Oh yeah.
This club is one of a kind!
[sighs] My answer is no.
Sho, please. We're meant
to be. I can feel it.
So...
Oh yeah, that sounded weird.
Why won't you join us?
Talk to me!
I saw your performance.
If a person can
even call it that.
Handstands and shoulder sits?
Did you really think you
were ready for a show?
I didn't see a single thing that
even resembled tumbling.
Those two jokers
did what they could.
But, the rest of you were
completely pathetic.
Listen, cheering isn't
something you just decide to do.
It takes years of dedication.
Not to mention you're
an all Men's Team.
Which sounds like it's meant
to be a practical joke.
But I'm not laughing.
You can't cheer, you can't
tumble, you can't do stunts.
You don't even have the training
to know how to practice.
Honestly, I don't want to join
a team of naive amateurs.
You can count me out.
[gasps]
We may be amateurs, but we're
not naive. We're dead serious!
[ALL gasp]
And we'll prove it!
In gym class,
one week from today!
So, how are you planning to
prove we're worth his time?
Oh. I have no idea.
[ALL groan]
You just said that off
the top of your head?!
Well, so much for that.
At least he gave us some things
to start thinking about.
Speaking of, what did
he mean by stunts?
[TON] They're the kind of moves
you see in group gymnastics.
You can't really do
cheerleading without them.
Guess Sho's not the only
one who knows his stuff.
Just a little bit. I looked up
a couple things last night.
[KAZUMA]
Listen.
[ALL]
Huh?
Wataru had the right idea.
We need to let Sho know
we mean business.
He knows this stuff
better than anyone.
We may not have his
level of experience,
but we do have heart!
If we work our butts off,
he'll respect the effort.
So that's how we can
change his mind.
So, what're you proposing?
The round-off back handspring.
If we learn that,
he'll change his tune.
You're joking, right?
Come on, Kazu. How are we
supposed to learn that move?
Work. If we try hard enough
we can do anything.
And when once we
have gotten it right,
he'll see that we're
not playing around!
He'll know for a fact that
we're serious about this.
Then he'll be begging us
to join the Cheer Club!
[TON]
Huh.
[KAZUMA] Watch me.
I'll give it a try first!
[grunts]
--Whoa!
--Nice moves, Kazu!
I've been training every
morning, and after class, too!
Between class and practice,
when do you sleep?
When you said--between
practice, class and practice.
When I commit to
something, I go all in.
Cool! First, the round-off!
If you don't land with both
your feet on the ground,
it's just a weird cartwheel.
Start like you wanna
do a cartwheel,
but rotate your body when
your hands touch the ground,
push all the way off, and
land with both feet flat.
Nailed it!
Awesome job, you two,
I knew you'd get there.
All right, Wataru.
It's your turn!
Right!
[KAZUMA]
Nice, Ton!
[TON groans]
[KAZUMA]
You're up, Haru!
[KAZUMA] Look guys, you already
know how to do a handstand.
The next step's a piece of cake.
Just get comfortable and then
flip over with all your might!
Make sure to keep
your knees straight!
Keep your eyes on the
gap between your hands!
And try to kick the
sky with your toes!
Oh, man. I can't,
it's just too hard.
We barely have a week, Ton.
There's no way we
can learn this.
[exhales]
[ROOSTER crows]
[RISUJIRO] ♪ Every single
morning, I go nuts-nuts-nuts! ♪
♪ In the mountains
and the ocean's, ♪
♪ I go nuts-nuts-nuts! ♪
♪ Everywhere I go,
I go nuts-nuts-nuts! ♪
♪ So be a nut with me
and go nuts-nuts-nuts, ♪
♪ let's go nuts-nuts-nuts! ♪
So sour! But so good!
[WATARU laughs]
That Risu is the nuttiest
squirrel of all time!
Nutty, nutty, nutty...
[TON] It says right here
that Risujiro is actually
the second of four siblings.
The others are Risutaro,
Risusaburo, and last, but
not least, Risushiro.
Huh...?
Here they are.
[HARUKI]
Wow. So you have a full set.
[WATARU]
I'd never noticed before.
You know, squirrels
are pretty nimble.
Truth is, sometimes I wish
I was more like a squirrel.
Doing a round-off with a
back handspring is just...
...way too hard.
I can't do it, either.
Track and field was
always my thing.
I've always been
good at running.
But I've never been
able to do a flip.
Well, boys.
It isn't time for food, it's
time to get down to business!
I will be a squirrel!
I'm gonna be the king
of the squirrels!
[HARUKI]
You are so odd.
[WATARU]
Here goes!
[TON grunts]
[WATARU, TON grunting]
Nice. Now our whole team
can nail the round-off!
Wow. You guys must've
been workin' hard!
[ALL laugh]
Big deal. If you want
to impress somebody,
then you gotta learn
the back handspring!
The round-off took you
three whole days.
The back handspring's way harder
and you have to learn
it just as fast.
[TON, WATARU sigh]
I'm pretty sure Haru will
be able to figure it out.
But what about Ton and Wataru?
They'll be fine.
We're gonna learn it together!
Yeah, right. What a joke!
[GEN]
Ichiro!
Well, we still have some
time so let's get to work.
I know you guys
have what it takes!
[KAZUMA] Back Handspring
Tip number one:
Until you perfect your bridge
technique, you'll suck at it.
[crash]
[HARUKI groans]
[KAZUMA]
Tip Number Two:
Push your center of gravity
behind your feet.
Kinda like when you
sit in a chair.
Tip Number Three:
If you can make a bridge
while jumping backward
through the air,
congrats! Have a gold star.
Great job!
You nailed it, Haru!
Heh.
Lame. I don't know
what took you so long.
That move is a piece of cake!
[ICHIRO grunting]
[laughs] I could do
it in my sleep!
[BOTH]
Uh...
[ICHIRO]
Watch this!
Sorry, guys.
No matter how hard something is,
he always makes it seem
like it's nothing.
[KAZUMA] I guess you two have
known each other for a while.
[GEN] Yep. We've been buds since
we played baseball together
back in elementary school.
[CROWD cheers]
[GEN] Almost as soon as he
joined, he was a first stringer.
And just a couple years
after our seniors left,
he was the best pitcher
on our team.
It became pretty obvious that
no matter how hard I worked,
I could never be as good as him.
So, I quit in high school.
Started playing soccer instead.
[GEN] Honestly. I was just tired
of competing with him.
[WATARU gasps]
He's so mean!
Why's he being so
cruel to us, Tono?
Sometimes he forgets that other
people can get frustrated, too.
[CROWD cheers]
[GEN]
He can seem like a jerk,
but he definitely means well.
Yeah. I see that.
And I think I know how you feel.
It gets confusing.
If you said he didn't make you
furious, you'd be lying.
But then, at the same time,
you also think he's cool.
Because he really is.
See Gen? He be a little
closed off at times,
but deep down, he's just a
sensitive boy with a big heart.
I am not sensitive, dude!
[KAZUMA] Right. Gen and I
will be your spotters, guys.
Let's keep working
on our technique
till we get this thing right!
[GEN]
Yeah!
You want some water?
As fun as this is, I have
to go to work. Peace.
Hey, wait!
Let him.
I'm really sorry, guys.
You've spent so
much time helping me
with my round off move.
But I just can't...
Same here. Plus, gym class
is tomorrow morning.
We failed.
You guys didn't fail at all.
Gen's right everyone!
Even if you mess up tomorrow,
you'll have tried your best.
What more can ya hope for?
Just have a good time! That's
what this is all about, right?
Why don't we call it a day
and rest up for tomorrow.
I'm really proud of all
the work we've done!
[GEN]
Yeah, I agree.
You guys tried hard;
you should be proud.
Thanks, but--
We wanna practice a little
bit longer. Right?
[WATARU, TON]
Mm.
Later, man.
Bye.
[HARUKI] Remember to look
right between your hands!
And keep your momentum!
[WATARU]
Jump! Make a bridge!
[TON grunts]
[groaning]
Ton!
[SHO]
That was dangerous.
[WATARU, HARUKI gasp]
[TON]
Uh...
You need to give this up
before one of you gets hurt.
Not gonna happen.
[gasps]
Just wait. Tomorrow,
you're in for a real treat.
We'll show you what we've
been practicing. You'll see!
[gasps]
Do whatever you want.
Thanks for caring, that's
really sweet of you!
Right. Let me give it a try.
Here goes!
Your form looks great. Do it!
[TON]
Go for it, man!
[WATARU yells]
[WATARU grunting]
Go... Fight... Win!
[BOTH]
Heh. Go... Fight... Win!
Right. Once more.
[HARUKI]
That was great.
Almost there!
[TON]
Fight for it!
[HARUKI]
You've got this!
[WATARU]
Again!
[HARUKI]
This is the one!
[TON]
You can do it, man!
[WATARU grunting]
No way... I did it.
Wow! Dude!
Sweet!
That looked fantastic, Wataru!
Congratulations, bud!
How truly grand it is
to have friends to celebrate
your accomplishments.
You drama queen.
[WATARU] For as long
as I can remember,
I've been running alone.
In track, I did long
distance meets.
With my schoolwork,
I left all my classmates
behind in the dust.
But I wasn't a winner. I could
never muster the composure
to perform under pressure.
[WATARU] I got sick during
my entrance exams.
When I failed them
for the second time,
I felt like a loser.
I was always alone after that.
"We mere mortals, though finite,
can embody an infinite
spirit of joy and pain.
It's through our pain
that we know joy best."
I'm paraphrasing a little bit,
but that is Ludwig
Van Beethoven.
He had a way with
music and words.
I get it. Joy through the pain!
I can do this.
At least I hope so.
Yeah!
We'll be Squirrel Kings
together. Right?
[ICHIRO]
What're you guys doin'?
[WATARU]
Hm?
I thought you would've
given up hours ago.
So, it's only Ton left, eh?
Let's get to work then!
[TON]
'Kay, guys! I'm ready!
[ICHIRO]
All right!
[WATARU]
Ton! Go!
[HARUKI]
You got this!
Whoa!
[ICHIRO]
Yeah!
[gasps]
[WATARU sobbing]
[ALL laughing]
[TON] Why are you crying,
Wataru, it's a good thing!
[ICHIRO]
Get a grip, would you, man?
I already watered yesterday.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[WATARU growls]
He's not here.
Great.
That dill hole ran away.
To-ku-ga-wa!
[TON] Maybe he just had
to go to the bathroom?
[HARUKI]
Ton...
[KAZUMA grunts]
[SHO'S FRIEND 3A]
Hey, Sho!
[gasps]
What's the deal? Why weren't
you in gym class today?
Uh, I'm sick?
'Kay. Well, there was a
group of guys doing flips
and stuff--they wanted
to show you something.
It was actually kinda cool.
They were jumping around
and nailing tricks
all over the place!
I think they were still
there when we left.
[gasps]
[HARUKI]
Go for it!
[ICHIRO]
This is your moment!
[KAZUMA]
Show us how it's done!
[GEN]
Right!
Look, kid, it's
almost lunchtime.
I'm gonna need to
close up pretty soon.
Right, sorry.
Just a little longer?
We'll try it again!
[HARUKI]
Are you sure about that?
Yes.
Same here.
[gasps]
Well! Let's try it again!
[sighs] Enough. Please.
You keep doing
handsprings like that,
you're gonna
break your wrists.
It's not safe.
I'll show you the
right way to do it.
It'd be irresponsible not to.
You're clearly joining the team,
so why are you
scared to admit it?!
If you're too cool for us then
what's with that jumpsuit?
[ALL laugh]
Guys. Don't freak out but
these things are super rare!
And don't look at me like that!
The risus are awesome
and you know it!
They're so cool.
[CAFE MANAGER 1A] I'll give'em
to ya to celebrate, kid!
[gasps]
Don't worry, I have another set.
Plus, you make me nervous.
Ahh! This is the greatest!
[ALL laughing]
[KAZUMA] I say we dedicate this
meal to our newest member, Sho!
What do you say, Cheer Boys?
[ALL]
Let's eat!
[clattering]
[SHO]
Uh!
[KAZUMA]
Hm?
[SHO]
I know I said I'd join the team,
but I do have one condition.
[ICHIRO]
Yeah? What's that?
Don't say it. No one else gets
to touch your squirrel dolls.
[SHO]
No, it's not that.
But listen, you should know
I won't do any stunts.
[OWL]
Good night.
[RISUJIRO]
You think?
♪ Even in my dreams,
I go nuts-nuts-nuts! ♪
♪ In the mountains,
in the ocean's, ♪
♪ I go nuts-nuts-nuts! ♪
♪ When I'm counting
all the sheep, ♪
♪ I go nuts-nuts-nuts! ♪
♪ So be a nut with me
and go nuts-nuts-nuts, ♪
♪ let's go nuts-nuts-nuts! ♪
So good! BBQ!
Don't you want to be in
our commercial, too?
Bases, your elbows are
too low! Lift them higher!
[ICHIRO, GEN]
Yes, ma'am!
Spotter, pay attention!
[WATARU]
Right!
Flyer! Your posture is terrible!
Straighten up your arms!
Get your butt in gear,
right now!
[HARUKI]
Right!
Next episode,
"What We Want to Break."
Go... Fight... Win!