[CROWD cheering]
Go... Fight!
[inaudible]
I can't win. Not like this.
[SHO]
Haru. Do the next motion.
Oh... Yeah!
Haru...?
What're you do-- [coughing]
What's goin' on with you, man?
Nationals are only
a week away,
so get your head in the game.
[HARUKI]
Sorry...
It's all good, just
try and stay focused!
Guys! Let's go! Get in position!
[BREAKERS]
Right!
[SHO chuckles]
What're you smilin' about?
Is that a message from
a special someone?
Oh. It's from Sakura.
[WATARU]
Sakura?
Is she your girlfriend?!
Another Saku? That's cool!
Lemme see that thing!
"First of all, the flyers
aren't turning in unison,
and it looks borderline awful.
Not to mention the dance
moves are super flat.
Tell them to smile more--
they look depressed."
Sakura and I cheered
together in high school.
We send her daily videos
of our practices,
and she gives us
constructive feedback.
[TAKERU whistles]
So he's a masochist...
[HISASHI]
So it would seem.
I'm really happy for Sho.
Yeah.
It's awesome. Proud of that guy.
[TAKUMI]
I said I'm fine, Bro, back off.
[KAZUMA]
Uh?
I'm taking you to
the doctor. The end!
Stop arguing, it's pointless.
Takumi, maybe you
should listen to him.
The way you've been coughing,
you probably should
go to the doctor.
Look, I'm good, my brother
just worries too much.
Oh do I? Plus, someone has to.
You sure don't take
care of yourself.
I appreciate your concern, man,
but I don't need a doctor.
[exhales]
He's your brother.
But you have to let
him be his own man.
Yeah, well, that's
easier said than done.
We've always been together.
In elementary school...
In high school and college, too.
But it won't always be that way.
So, I don't know,
it just makes me sad.
[HARUKI]
When I walked away from judo,
I wonder if she
felt the same way?
Was she sad? Does she miss me?
[HARUKI gasps]
[KAZUMA]
Uh?
[WATARU]
Is that who I think it is?
Still training.
Your sister's intense.
Why don't you go
after her, Haru?
But he can't, we have work.
It's no big deal, just tell your
boss he'll be a little late.
Well? Go!
[HARUKI]
Hey! Sis!
[HARUKI panting]
[HARUKO]
What do you want?
[pants] Uh. Nothing.
Well, no... One thing.
[sighs] Go on.
The thing is,
I heard that you...
[HARUKO]
Can't win?
[HARUKI gasps]
[HARUKO] That's what you
wanna talk about, right?
Uh.
Look, the National Championship
is almost here.
You've got enough
stress on your plate.
So worry about that
and not me, okay?
Wait a sec!
You've been wiping
that cup for an hour.
Hm? Oops.
Haru?
I just want you to know,
you can talk to me.
I'll always listen to you.
And I'll try to give
good advice like Kazu.
I've got your back.
Uh. Thanks a lot.
[door creaks]
Come on in.
Uh!
Well, hello!
Hey. I'll clean the toilet.
[HARUKI]
Thanks?
Haru. Congrats on the Breakers
making it to Nationals.
Yeah! Right back at ya!
[gasps] I got a
bloody nose again!
[HARUKI laughs]
[HARUKI]
Enjoy.
This looks incredible!
Wow. It actually tastes
even better than it looks!
Do you like the cake here too?
Uh. Yeah.
Hey!
[HARUKI gasping]
Give me the recipe!
Uh. Well, my boss
is out right now.
But there is a recipe
book in the back!
Ah! Uh. Here's an idea,
you can text it to me!
Oh. Sure.
Sorry to make you go
through the trouble.
But it's almost Valentine's Day.
And I thought I might try
my hand at making a cake.
If it turns out well I
can bring you a slice!
[gasping]
[SHO]
Well, I finally understand
why you're having
trouble focusing.
But you gotta get through this.
We need you focused
for nationals.
Yeah, uh. That wasn't
really about her.
Hey, guys!
Good morning!
[HARUKI]
Oh. Hey!
[SHO]
You're early.
Me and my brother just
got in a little fight.
Yeah, and, uh...
I thought I might benefit
from some extra practice.
[HARUKI, SHO grunt]
[WATARU]
One, two, down, up!
[SAKU grunts]
You need to engage
your entire body!
[SAKU]
I'm sorry, everyone.
There's no need to apologize.
Just think positive thoughts
and the rest'll fall in place.
Thanks, Coach.
We're off tomorrow,
but don't play around.
Make sure you train on your own!
[KAZUMA]
That's it for now, boys.
[BREAKERS]
Thank you very much, Coach!
[BREAKERS chattering]
[KAZUMA] Haru! I've got work,
so I'm gonna head out.
All right.
[gasps, sighs]
[HARUKI]
Saku?
Do you wanna practice
at my place tomorrow?
Kin and Hisashi are coming by.
[HISASHI]
One, two, down, up!
[SAKU grunting]
Whoa! Way to go, Saku!
You nailed it!
Talk about a perfect turn.
[KIN]
You should be proud.
Heh! Thanks a lot.
I don't know what it is,
but I can't seem to do it when
the whole team is watching.
I'm sorry I've been
holding us back, guys.
Truth is, I've always
been a bit of a wimp.
My parents always says
my older sisters
are manlier than I'll ever be.
[HISASHI] You have sisters?
I didn't know that.
I would kill for a big sis.
[SAKU]
Uhh...
Be careful what you wish for.
Your brother's way
nicer than my sisters.
It just drives me crazy
how naggy he can be.
The guy's got problems
of his own.
I want him to worry about
finding a job, not me.
The thing is, if it doesn't work
out for him, I'll blame myself.
You know?
Totally. I guess every
family has drama, huh?
You have an older sister,
too, don't you, Haru?
[HARUKI]
Yup.
We did judo together for years.
But she was always stronger
and way more talented.
That's rough.
[TAKUMI]
I get it.
In my family, my brother's the
more accomplished one, too.
Same here.
I'm real glad I came over today.
The only reason I
showed up initially
was to avoid having to
deal with my brother.
But it helps to know other
people are in the same boat
as me, know what I mean?
It makes me feel less crazy.
[SAKU] Mm. I guess that makes
us the Little Brothers Trio.
[HARUKI]
Heh.
[HISASHI grunts]
[KIN]
Mm-mm.
Welp! I better take off.
Oh. 'Kay.
Pretty sure I owe my
brother an apology.
He only worries
because he cares.
Guess you're right.
Well. This was fun.
Hey, Haru?
Sup? You headin' out now?
Well, uh, if you don't mind,
I could use your help
with something.
[HARUKI]
Valentine's Chocolate?
They sell this stuff at most
corner stores, you know?
Well, yeah, but that isn't
nearly as rewarding.
[HARUKI]
Hm?
Kazu's the reason I decided
to try cheerleading.
And I'm grateful to him. This
is my way of saying, "thanks."
So tell me, what kind of
chocolate does he like the most?
[HARUKI] Hm... I think he likes
the kind with almonds in it.
Almonds? Awesome!
I'll glaze them with chocolate.
Then I'll dust 'em
with hot cocoa!
Kazu won't even know
what just hit him!
[HARUKO]
Mom! What are you doing?
It smells like a chocolate
factory in here!
Uh?
Hi. My name's Saku!
I'm a member of the Cheer Club,
along with your brother.
Hi. I'm Haruko.
Sorry to interrupt.
Uh!
[door creaks]
[HARUKI]
Sis, wait!
Let's talk.
I told you to leave me alone.
Listen. I, uh...
I finally figured out what
I've been trying to say.
[TAKUMI] Pretty sure I owe
my brother an apology.
[HARUKI]
I'm sorry!
Huh?
I'm sorry I walked
away from judo.
I've wanted to tell you that
from the beginning, Haruko.
And there's something else, too.
The truth is, I didn't quit
because of my injury.
I'd been thinking about it for
a long time, and then one day,
I realized I had
to stop thinking
and do something about
it. I had to act.
[HARUKI]
Hey, Sis!
I just heard about the match.
I'm sorry you lost!
[HARUKO]
I envy you, Haruki.
Sometimes I wish
I wasn't a girl!
Why do I have to be so weak?!
Thing is... I had it easy.
I was a guy so I was a
lot stronger at first.
But that was only true
for a little while.
'Cause you flat out worked me,
and you got better fast.
Before long,
the only thing I was beating
you at was my height.
And as far as judo
was concerned,
there was no competition at all.
[gasps]
[HARUKO]
So... what?
Are you trying to say I was
pushing you too
hard or something?
What? No, that's not it at all.
I loved watching you fight.
But I could see that judo was
never gonna be my thing.
It was your thing.
And seeing how good you were
made me realize I needed to
try something different.
It's ok. I understand.
You wanted to go down a path
that was truly yours.
That's it.
[HARUKO]
But...
...judo's the only
thing I have, Haru.
[door slams]
I eavesdropped.
Don't worry. She'll understand
how you feel one of these days.
It'll just take a little time.
Uh!
All right! Now that's
what I call a turn, Saku!
Hey, excellent work!
Oh man! Did you
see that, bro?
I sure did!
You think you can do it
like that at Nationals?
Yeah. I definitely can!
[ALL gasp]
[SAKU]
I took Coach's advice.
I'm thinking positive thoughts.
I'm visualizing myself
nailing the stunt.
And it's actually working!
I feel great!
Way to look on the bright side!
I feel the strong impulse
to drop a perfect line.
But out of my vast
mental bank of quotes,
nothing I can think of
is quite as perfect
as what Saku just hit us with.
Good work, Saku. I'm impressed
with your progress.
Well done. Very manly.
Congrats, Bro!
[DOH]
Ya done good!
[laughs]
Hey. Happy Valentine's Day!
Thanks.
You excited about
your Valentine?
Huh?
[sighs] If only somebody would
make me some chocolate cake!
Hey! Who'd you hear
that from, Sho?
Just be happy you're
getting some!
'Kay. But I'm pretty
sure you are, too.
Huh?
Happy Valentine's Day!
[KAZUMA]
Uh...
[TAKERU]
I hope he's planning to share.
Kazu. You probably don't
remember this at all,
but at the school festival I
fell and you helped me back up.
Yeah. I guess I did do that.
It's cause of your kindness
I'm standing here.
And this has changed
me for the better.
Here's my way of
saying, "thanks!"
Well, that's really
sweet of you.
I have plenty extra if
you guys are hungry.
Hold on. You have leftovers?
Ooh, I love chocolate.
Thanks a lot, Sho!
I didn't even get one
from my own mother.
I just got one from my big bro.
And I got one from
my little bro, too.
Why don't you guys be more
sensitive and stop bragging!
Guess what?
I got one from Kirari.
Hey, so did I!
Yeah? And why is that?
As a thank you for helping her
pick out your gift, ya' dummy!
[TON grunting]
Guys with girlfriends
can breathe easy today.
Why is Ton the only one of us
with a girlfriend? No fair.
[TON] Oh. I haven't actually
gotten a gift yet.
But she did promise
she'd make me
some chocolate cake this year.
Chocolate cake?
[TON] Mm-hm. She said there's
a restaurant around here
with a pretty great recipe.
Apparently, someone who
works there gave it to her.
Wow...
Must be what all the girls
are doing this year?
[gasps]
[KAZUMA]
Heh.
[gasps]
[HARUKI gasps, clears throat]
[CHIHIRO]
Hey, Tono!
Oh. Hey there, Chi!
Hey guys, gimme a sec.
Thank you, Haru!
[GEN]
I didn't know Ton's girlfriend
was a member of the Dreams.
[WATARU] It's no wonder he knew
so much about cheerleading.
[ICHIRO]
She's super cute, too!
Uh, you cool?
[KAZUMA]
Haru. I'm so sorry!
I don't get it, why are
you apologizing, Kazu?
What? I'm not.
Hey. You keep your head up!
[TAKAGI]
Sorry I'm late, everyone!
You hungry? I brought
some for everybody!
[CAFE MANAGER 1A]
My Valentine's Day special:
spicy curried noodles
with a pork cutlet heart!
[TAKUMI] Ah. But if I eat it,
I'll break its heart!
[ZI XUAN] I guess that makes
them 'Heartbreak Noodles!'
Chihiro says her and Ton
dropped off your slice of cake
at the restaurant and that
Sho will bring it by later.
So I guess the silver
lining's that you
still get to eat
a delicious treat?
Who cares?!
Damn you, Cupid!
Don't worry, we're all
behind you, man!
There's no reason to be sad!
[HARUKI]
Uh-huh...
[WATARU]
"Love is a bitter medicine.
A fickle temptress,
and a mighty seducer."
Wow, that's a really
powerful quote, Wataru.
Where'd you get that one from?
Oh. My brain.
You made that up?!
[WATARU] Yes, indeed. I've been
using my own words lately.
It's totally awesome.
Until recently, I was no better
than a parrot, yapping away.
Albeit, a genius parrot,
but a parrot, still.
But then I decided to
join the Cheer Club.
And now I see things
in a new light.
Things I couldn't even
begin to comprehend before.
Ain't that the truth.
Before this, when
I played baseball
all I cared about were
my own achievements.
But the Cheer Club
taught me selflessness
and the value of working as
a team to achieve a goal.
Same here. I've learned
a lot from Cheerleading.
And from all my teammates.
Me, too. Other people
are quite different.
I've learned that that's both
annoying and strangely exciting.
[TAKERU]
True dat!
I learned that something
can be difficult and fun!
Now I think I
prefer it that way.
I agree.
I learned a lesson, too.
If you wanna make
someone else smile,
first, you gotta figure out
a way to smile for yourself.
You've all overcome so
much. It's incredible.
I hope I can get there.
[ICHIRO] I got it! We need
to find another nice girl!
[GEN] If you do, then
introduce her to me first!
[BREAKERS chattering]
Look, Haru. On the plus
side, you were probably
a great wing man for Ton!
Compared to you he probably...
[HARUKI laughs]
I'm sorry, Haru.
Looks like I got you
worked up over nothing.
Yeah. No need to be sorry.
It's not like everyone
knows I played myself.
[KAZUMA]
Uh...
There is something else
I wanted to say.
A little bird told me
there's an inter-university
tournament tomorrow. For judo.
Well, yeah. But we have
practice tomorrow.
Won't cheering on a real
match be practice enough?
Come on, buddy,
just give it a shot.
[phone chimes]
[KAZUMA]
Hm?
[HARUKI]
Go, Sis! You got this!
You can beat him!
Take him out!
I believe in you!
Go... Fight... Win!
Let's begin!
Yeah! That's it, attack him!
Let's go.
Let's go!
[CROWD cheers]
[REFEREE 11A]
That's the match!
[panting]
[HARUKO laughs]
[HARUKI laughing]
[KAZUMA]
Well, did the cheering help?
[HARUKI]
Yeah. She won.
[KAZUMA]
So the champs back, eh?
[HARUKI] My voice reached her,
I could tell.
[KAZUMA] You're the star flyer
for the Breakers, Haru.
Of course it did!
[HARUKO]
Kazu! Haru!
[HARUKO, KAZUMA]
Hm?
I know it's a bit late,
but here you go!
[BOTH grunting]
Wow! Thank you!
[HARUKI]
Not cool, Sis.
Why'd you buy us
the cheap stuff?
[HARUKO]
You should be thankful.
I don't see anyone else lining
up to give you chocolate.
As a matter of fact,
I got some from my Coach!
I wouldn't brag about
that if I were you.
[HARUKO laughs]
You know,
it's been a while since
the three of us have sparred.
[KAZUMA, HARUKI]
Uh...
--[HARUKO grunts]
--[KAZUMA groans]
--[HARUKI groans]
[HARUKO]
Who's next?
[KAZUMA]
I am!
[HARUKO]
Come on!
[KAZUMA groans]
[HARUKO]
One more time!
[KAZUMA]
All right!
[KAZUMA groans]
[HARUKO]
Nice hustle!
[KAZUMA]
Thanks!
[KAZUMA sighs]
[HARUKO exhales]
Not bad at all, Haruko.
[HARUKI]
Not bad? She destroyed us.
I hope you guys are ready.
Nationals are coming.
And I'll be there...
...cheering you on.
[HARUKI, KAZUMA]
Heck, yeah.
[HARUKO laughs]
[BREAKERS]
B-R-E-A-K-E-R-S!
Go Breakers!
Let's go... Meishiin!
Go for love and peace!
[HARUKI, KAZUMA]
Next episode, "Cheer Boys!"
Let's go... Breakers!