♪
[GUARD 1] Hurry up!
Move it!
The Fallen are coming!
We'll be all right.
Celes's barrier will
protect us in the city.
There's no way
the Fallen can get past it.
[GREGORE
maniacally laughing]
You must be
Celestine Baudelaire?
How'd you like
to be the first to die?
♪
[GREGORE]
Wish I could thank
your stupid human.
It's because of him
that your barrier
was so easy to bypass.
What good is
all your power,
if you can't even
detect a camouflaged Fallen?
Figures.
Leave it to Galluk to
lead a Fallen to our territory.
It must have been
some kind of trick.
-He wouldn't!
-Rem, we need you.
Please take care
of Celes for us!
[grunts]
-You'll never escape!
-[BOTH grunt]
[explosion]
[door opens]
[REM]
Everyone evacuate!
There's a fallen
in the city!
♪
[panting]
[CROWD screaming]
[laughs maniacally]
[REM and CELES panting]
♪
[CELES]
You're hurting my arm!
[REM] Come on!
Just hang in there!
[CELES]
That's the wrong way!
[BOTH gasp]
-[footsteps approaching]
-[CELES gasps]
Are you two
having a good time?
I am.
[REM]
Asulau, come forth!
Aw, what a cute
wittle summon.
[growls]
-[ASULAU roars]
-[explosion]
[GREGORE grunts]
[grunts]
[ASULAU roars]
♪
[grunts]
Oh, come on!
[GREGORE]
I changed my mind.
You die first!
[EMILE]
I'll save you, Rem!
[grunts]
And just who
the hell are you?
As if you don't know.
My name is
Emile Bichel Berger!
Hero and ally of all women!
[REM]
Was there no one else?
Well, now.
It seems we have
a Fallen in the city.
You, sir, will pay dearly.
No one targets
women on my watch!
Huh?
[MEN panting]
[MAN 1] I won't let you
harm the protector of our city!
[MAN 2]
We'll fight to defend Celes
no matter the cost!
[TOWN DEFENDERS]
Get away from them!
-You can't escape!
-We're not afraid of you!
[GREGORE] Well, aren't you
simpletons brave?
I appreciate you
keeping me entertained!
I love a good
laugh before a kill!
[yells]
[EMILE grunts]
[grunts]
[EMILE grunting]
Keep trying, but I crap
bigger than you, Goldie!
I am a fighter
and a protector!
When a woman is in danger,
I am invincible!
I love killing humans
who won't shut up!
[EMILE yells]
He's okay?
[grunts]
All right.
What's your secret?
It's called magic, human.
And you happen to be
battling the greatest Sorcerer
that ever existed
in the Man-Eating woods!
[EMILE]
What?
[GREGORE]
Worthless human.
Seeing your kind
conjure their best attacks,
then plunge into
despair is my favorite.
[GREGORE] I can't get over
the face they make
when they realize
they will not survive.
Sword Smite!
[grunts]
Whoopsie, forgot to
mention something.
I'm also a ridiculously
strong warrior.
[EMILE gasps]
Time for Dark Bullet!
[rapid firing]
[EMILE yells]
Emile, no!
[groaning]
Can you stand up?
We get it, Emile.
Thanks for your support.
But you're not
going to win this one.
[EMILE]
Fear not, fragile maiden!
I am a man who is
fighting for your honor.
I will never
turn my back on an enemy!
Not while I still have breath!
[snickers]
And you know why?
Because I am
Emile Bichel Berger.
Defender of all women,
and smokin' hot!
Not for long, human.
[rapid firing]
[whooshing]
[slashing]
[gasps]
[EDELGARD grunting]
[TAKUMA]
Oh yeah, she's strong.
I'd say about
a level 80. Not bad.
[wind howling]
[DIABLO]
It's foolish to believe
you can defeat me
with so little strength.
Do you wish to continue?
Yeah. I do.
But I'll use this.
[zapping]
Woah!
Do you see that?
[TAKUMA] Woah!
She's using Sacrificial Charge.
That's a powerful skill
that consumes
the user's own hit points.
When she sees me survive this,
maybe her will to fight
will finally be broken.
[DIABLO]
Interesting choice!
I approve!
I'll take it head-on.
Go ahead and do
your best to damage me!
Don't worry. I will.
Come forth, Sacrificial...
Charge!
♪
[grunting]
[yells]
[grunts]
♪
[explosion]
[grunts]
Did she break him?
♪
[DIABLO]
That was all right.
[grunts] No way.
What happened?
I know I hit him. Perfectly.
So awesome!
[footsteps approaching]
Boris! Bad news!
[SHERA]
Huh?
[TAKUMA]
Okay, that one kinda hurt.
So this is
how damage feels.
First time
I've taken any here.
[DIABLO]
Are you still questioning
the difference
in our abilities?
You've used
your most powerful blow,
and yet,
here I stand before you,
completely undamaged.
[panting]
[TAKUMA]
All right. Any day now.
Spoiler,
you're not going to win.
There's no
point in continuing.
It's a waste of time.
Call off your damn army!
[BORIS]
Diablo!
I just received
word from the city!
Celestine is
being attacked
by one of
the Fallen right now!
[gasps]
They also said she's
with a Pantherian woman.
It has to be Rem!
[grunts]
♪
Must be Gregore.
For such an idiot.
I have to say,
he does good work.
[TAKUMA]
They snuck a secret soldier
in before we ever got here.
I bet they're
planning to kill Celes
in order to
break the barrier.
Then they'll push through here
and storm the city
with these guys.
[EDELGARD]
So, yeah.
If we kill you,
you know what comes next?
It means the Fallen win.
[DIABLO grunts]
[TAKUMA]
I can't be out here long
if Rem is in
the middle of this!
I don't have a choice
but to end this quickly.
[DIABLO]
I'm going to use Grand Magic!
If you don't wish to die,
I suggest you duck
behind those stone walls!
[gasps]
[whirring]
I have no pity for the Fallen,
but I will offer you mercy.
Withdraw now and I'll agree
to spare you your life!
This is not my concern.
I seek only to revive
the Demon Lord.
Oh, and to exterminate
all of humanity,
but mostly reviving
the Demon Lord.
Got it? Till then,
I'll fight. Until I win.
Ha! You think you work
for the Demon Lord?
Not that that's any of
your business, but yeah.
[DIABLO]
You don't know
what you're talking about.
I am the one
true Demon Lord.
No other Demon Lord
comes before Diablo!
[gasps]
The true Demon Lord?
Come forth,
White Nova!
[gasps]
[clinks]
[screams]
[rumbling]
[whimpering]
[BORIS grunting]
[water rushing]
[ALL gasping]
He could've
just said so.
It must be true.
He's Diablo,
the Demon Lord?
[TAKUMA]
Wait, what?
She's still alive
after taking that?
♪
[SHERA]
Come on, Diablo!
We have to hurry!
[TAKUMA] We don't have
time to walk there.
[DIABLO]
I'm gonna try Return Magic!
[SHERA gasps]
[TAKUMA]
Please!
Let this work the same way
it does in the game!
[DIABLO]
Return!
[BORIS]
They vanished?
[EMILE groans]
♪
[groaning]
Is little Goldie
about to cry?
Shut up.
I'm gonna make you cry.
For the sake of my comrades
and damsels in distress,
I'll continue to fight.
You're taking
this way too far.
There's no point
in you risking your life.
If you continue to live,
then I'll know
my purpose was served.
How is it possible
that you haven't been
killed already
with a mouth like that?
Time to shut you up!
[explosion]
[grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
♪
Where have you been?
[DIABLO]
I see I didn't make it
exactly on time.
But you're both alive.
So, that's something.
Oh, Rem!
I was so afraid we'd lost you!
[REM]
I can't breathe!
What's with your face?
You don't look so good!
Because that's what
happens when a fallen
tries to kill you.
Can you tell if Emile's okay?
[DIABLO] Hey, hoss.
Are you still with us?
Yeah.
I'm here, friend.
You were a hero today.
We all thank you. Rest up.
I'll take it from here.
[thuds]
[gasps]
[DIABLO]
This is a healing potion.
Use it on Emile.
Of course.
Thank you, but,
are you truly ready
to take on a Fallen?
And risk your life
to protect us?
[DIABLO
I just wanna make sure
these insolent monsters
receive the proper punishment
for attacking my base.
Don't get the wrong idea.
[footsteps]
[CELES]
I guess it's possible
for even a Demon Lord
to have a good soul.
Well, isn't that sweet?
Though foolish
for a mere Demon!
[TAKUMA]
So he's a Sorcerer
who's developed
his abilities as a Warrior.
In Cross Reverie,
he'd be a Brawler Sorcerer.
Kinda crazy to think a Fallen
would be one of those.
Don't embarrass yourself
by begging for your life.
I'll destroy you!
Then I'll destroy
your stupid barrier!
[DIABLO] You plan to
do this on your own?
Edelgard's not coming.
[GREGORE]
Huh?
I did quite a bit of
damage to her.
Most of the Fallen Army
has been wiped out, as well.
Ha! Not gonna fall for it.
[DIABLO
I'll prove it to you
once we fight.
But be aware that no one
will hear you beg for your life.
And, no matter how much
you plead for mercy,
your life will not be spared.
[growls]
Dark Bullet!
[GREGORE grunts]
What was that?
It's that ring
thing he has!
[REM]
It's called Magic Reflection!
What's that?
What the hell did you do?
[DIABLO]
Dark Bullet.
[rapid fire]
[grunting]
[yells]
Quit whining.
I haven't used
any real magic yet.
Oh. You haven't, huh?
Then what was that?
[DIABLO] You're telling me
that a Fallen Sorcerer
only knows how to use something
as pathetic as Dark Bullet?
[growls]
Dark Press!
[whirring]
How 'bout this!
[GREGORE groans]
Fine. I give.
Enlighten me.
What is it that you're doing?
[DIABLO]
Aw, I'm disappointed in you.
Must be that
lizard brain of yours.
[echoing]
Dark Press!
[whirring]
[groaning]
[yells]
I get it now!
I will do as you say
and leave the city.
I yield.
Do...
Do you
want me to beg?
Please, let me go!
[DIABLO]
I gave you fair warning.
Your life
will not be spared.
I don't care if you beg.
[GREGORE whimpering]
It's too late
to earn my pity.
The price for
your crimes is death!
Please! Please, no!
I promise to leave here
and change my ways.
Please don't kill me!
Naraku.
[GREGORE groaning]
[GREGORE yells]
Your soul is sealed
in a dimension of darkness...
for all of eternity.
[sighs]
[TAKUMA]
I've never felt exhaustion
like this in my life.
I did use up a ton of
magic points just now.
Yay! You did it!
[giggles]
I knew you would!
Thanks so much!
[laughs]
[DIABLO grunts]
[REM]
Yes.
Thank you for rescuing us.
I thought it was over.
I'm truly grateful to you.
[DIABLO
What... Uh, huh?
[REM]
I know I had doubts before.
But seeing that,
I think you might
be able to save me!
[DIABLO]
Yes, because I promised you
I would, right?
[TAKUMA]
Crap! Crap! Crap! Crap!
Now what?
This never
happened in the game!
Women don't
thank Demon Lords!
How am I supposed to
respond to that, dammit?
[DIABLO] You-- you have
an enslavement collar!
-Yeah.
And what that means is
you're now one of
my possessions,
so, I just don't want
anyone ruining my things!
Don't think
it's 'cause
I was fighting
for you personally.
[TAKUMA]
"Things?"
Was that too much?
[REM] I think I
understand completely.
♪
So that means,
for as long as
I'm wearing this collar,
you own me.
[TAKUMA]
Since when is that a good thing?
[SHERA] What am I,
chopped Orc liver?
'Cause I belong
to you, too, don't I?
[TAKUMA grunts]
She's saying something,
but my brain only processes
huge yam yams touchin' my arm!
Oh, they're so silky.
[giggling]
That's bouncy
bouncy fun time!
[whimpers]
Wait, what're you?
[DIABLO grunts]
Nope. Not the same.
[DIABLO groans]
[SHERA]
He's passed out!
He hit his head
on Rem's rib cage!
[EMILE]
Oh, no!
[CELES]
Not that!
[REM]
Whatever!
[rain pouring]
♪
[TAKUMA]
Three days later,
all the casualties
of the Fallen's
assault on the city
were buried.
Nearly all of those lost
in the battle were Adventurers,
looking forward
to their next quests.
This world is
nothing like the game.
Here,
when someone dies,
there are no salvation spells
or resurrection potions.
And I was bitterly
forced to accept that.
♪
What surprised me most
was that even after facing
a devastating tragedy,
many still retained
a light of hope in their hearts.
They drew closer together
and did their best
to return to
their normal lives.
That was never part
of the game, either.
As for me, well...
[SHERA moaning]
Something like this?
Hey Diablo,
are you awake?
[DIABLO]
You go away now.
Sleepy time.
[SHERA]
Aw. I'm bored though.
Let's go on a quest!
[TAKUMA] It's been
10 days since the attack.
I'm still exhausted from
all the MP I tore through.
Which makes me moody
and lazy, apparently.
The next quest
is later when I try to
unstick myself
from these sheets.
[SHERA]
That's so lame!
Why would you wanna
make yourself sticky?
Come on!
Get up!
[DIABLO grunts]
♪
[giggles]
[DIABLO]
Huh? What? Why?
[SHERA] Did it work?
Can you get up now?
[DIABLO grunts]
It's something
Sylvie taught me.
She said if I ever
want to get a guy up,
this is the best way to do it.
[TAKUMA]
I knew there was
something evil
about that Guildmaster!
And, it worked.
Looks like
I got you up, huh?
[DIABLO groans]
-[REM] Damn it, Elf!
-[DIABLO whimpers]
Is there a reason
for being dressed like that?
[giggles]
Well, I, uh,
I was just hot?
[BOTH screaming]
Because you insist on
clinging to him like a parasite!
Personal space!
That means
at least 30 feet away!
[SHERA]
What?
But then I'd be
completely out of the room!
[REM] Why is it
so hard for you to keep
your fat sacks
off his arm?
It just happens
when I hug him, okay?
It's like when
you hug him,
but your ribs stab him
through your chest.
[growls]
Leave my ribs
out of your lies.
[DIABLO grunts]
[TAKUMA]
I mean, it's true. Ha.
At least two of them
are poking into me now.
Even so,
this is pretty cool.
[whimpers]
[gulps]
Good morning, friends!
Glad to see
we're all getting along!
Hi, Sylvie!
Look! It worked!
Atta girl!
Hey there, Deebs!
I'm so glad to
see you feeling better!
[DIABLO clears throat]
Well, what do you want, Sylvie?
[SYLVIE] Right.
I've gathered some info
that'll be of interest,
especially to you!
[DIABLO]
'Kay?
The Lord of Faltra City
has been receiving
several demands
from the Elves.
Their entire Kingdom
is requesting that
Shera be
handed over to them.
[ALL gasp]
The deadline's
10 days from now.
They said if their
demands are not met,
they won't hesitate
to wage a war.
-That so?
-Um, is he for real?
He thinks this is
worth starting a war?
Well, no.
The request is
for us to
try to resolve it.
But he did specify
that it should be quietly.
You accepted
a quest to return Shera?
What kind of crap
are you trying to pull?
Woah, hold on.
Don't get all
Diablo dude bro on me.
I'm not here to
seize Shera, okay?
It just came out wrong.
I know not to
piss off the guy
who defeated
an army of Fallen.
[DIABLO]
Fine.
I'll let you
backpedal this time.
Good man.
Let me try and phrase
the goal of this
quest correctly.
[SHERA whimpers]
Stop a war
from breaking out
between us
and the Elven Kingdom.
How's that sound?
[CHESTER] I'm Lieutenant
General Chester Ray Galford.
Pleased to meet you.
[ALICIA] I know
we can make this work
if we all do it together!
[SHERA]
No! Let go of me!
[DIABLO]
Shera!