[CROWD chattering]
[REM] We're supposed
to prevent a war?
Yup.
Like I said,
unless you'd prefer
to just hand over Shera.
[SHERA whimpers]
Do we all need a recap?
No prob.
The lord of Faltra City
has received demands
from the Elven Kingdom
to return Shera to them.
The deadline is
10 days from now.
So, in 10 days,
if they do not have her,
war will happen.
[SHERA]
Oh, no.
[SYLVIE]
It's your call, Dibster.
What do you think?
♪
[SHERA]
They want to start a war?
Really?
I don't get it.
Why would they involve
the entire Kingdom of Lyferia
over me?
Oh, I know it's crazy.
Both the lord and I
are in a mess of trouble
because of this.
[TAKUMA]
Man, they're persistent.
Shera was very clear
that she didn't want
to go back with them.
If they care that much,
wouldn't they just
want her to be happy?
[SYLVIE]
So here's what we need.
If you want to keep Shera,
then just find another way to
prevent the war from happening.
[SYLVIE]
Be creative.
[TAKUMA] Like it's
some kind of art project?
I refuse!
How am I supposed to
prevent a war?
Negotiate with
the psycho elves?
If I had communication
skills like that,
I wouldn't be
struggling to
keep up this
Demon Lord persona.
Surely there are
other people
who can figure this out.
But of course,
they won't
because that's
how the game works.
I'll need to find a way
to protect Shera until then.
-[TAKUMA] But how?
-[SHERA whimpers]
Fun fact.
Prince Keera
from Greenwood
has just placed
a huge bounty on Shera.
He wants to inspire
more people to look for her.
-[DIABLO] What?
-How could he?
Why?
That's so dumb.
[SYLVIE]
The reward would be enough
for a commoner
to lounge around
for the rest of his life.
So I'm not saying that
every adventurer
will be looking for Shera
and you could be
attacked at any time,
but maybe you shouldn't
go outside for a while?
[SHERA]
That's a lot to process.
[whimpers]
You okay?
-[SHERA gasps]
-Don't burn me!
[DIABLO]
He's placed a bounty
on his own little sister.
Big mistake.
Any fool blinded by greed
who dares to challenge me,
will rue the moment
such an idea
ever popped into their mind!
That was a lot.
I've told you before,
you belong to me, right?
That was clear?
Hmm.
So it doesn't
really matter
what idiot
comes after you.
I will always protect
whatever is mine.
You can walk
through the city
just as you always have.
No one will
lay a finger on you.
Yeah, I don't think
the Kingdom of Greenwood
is on the same
page with that.
We need
more information
before we can
clear the quest.
I want to go
talk to the lord
as soon as possible.
There's not
going to be a war.
I refuse to allow it.
-[SHERA giggles]
-[DIABLO grunts]
Thank you, Diablo!
You're the best!
I'll do anything you ask
and go anywhere
you need me!
I owe you all
the snuggles for life!
Ahem.
We can't go anywhere
until you cover up your
meat sacks, stupid Elf.
[DIABLO groans]
[CROWD chatting]
[SYLVIE]
Also,
the lord is
the hero of our city.
[DIABLO]
And why is that?
[SYLVIE]
Thirty years ago,
when the Demon Lord
was still terrorizing citizens,
the Lord fought
on the front lines.
He defeated several
Fallen single-handedly.
Just like
Diablo the other day!
Do you happen to
know what level he is?
So competitive!
No, we never
actually assessed him.
He's not an Adventurer.
He might have
been measured
before my time, but.
I'm not about to
ask him anything
I don't
absolutely have to,
if you know
what I mean?
[DIABLO]
Uh. Maybe?
Is he difficult
to speak to?
[SYLVIE laughs]
Yep.
That's a good way
to sum it up.
Scares the corn outta me.
I'm gonna offer you
some free advice.
It's a good time to
whip out your social skills
and an extra
pair of drawers!
[ALL gasp]
[SYLVIE]
Hey, Mr.Galford!
good to see you!
Is this weather
on point, or what?
[SYLVIE giggles]
I'll bet Diablo
doesn't have
another pair of pants.
Shh! How much
you want to bet
he can hear you?
Hmm.
[SYLVIE]
Good news. [giggles]
Diablo here
has accepted the quest
we discussed earlier.
-[DIABLO groans]
-[GALFORD] Has he?
He's not going to get
much accomplished in here.
Usually,
the way it works is,
you complete the quest
and then talk to me.
You are so right.
It's just the difficulty level
for this one is pretty high.
So he wanted to
gather some more
information
before they began.
[GALFORD]
I believe I've given you
all the information you need.
Right.
It's all coming
back to me now.
But they also
wanted to meet you!
Ya know, see the man
behind the magic?
I don't have
time for this.
How do
Adventurers not know
the name of their lord?
[ALL giggle nervously]
Very well.
I'm Lieutenant General
Chester Ray Galford.
His Royal majesty
has entrusted
the fortified city
of Faltra to me.
I'm Rem Galleu,
plain old adventurer.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Shera Greenwood.
[BOTH gasp]
[TAKUMA] I'm gonna
pee my Demon pants!
Why is an introduction
freaking me out?
How do I do this
as a Demon Lord
without pissing
that guy off
by being a Demon Lord?
It's too much pressure!
Trying to reason with him
seems way more difficult
than preventing a war!
[ALL giggle]
[DIABLO]
Oh. Uh.
My name is Diablo.
I've come
to hear you out.
[ALL gasp]
[TAKUMA]
I did it!
I managed
a normal introduction
with my awkward
communication skills!
There's hope
for me, after all!
-[TAKUMA cries]
-[GALFORD] According to
my reports, you're the one
who likes to call yourself
a Demon Lord
from another world.
So, is it true?
[DIABLO]
I dunno.
Shall I reduce you
to ash to prove it?
[ALL]
Awkward!
Ha! Isn't he so funny?
He didn't mean it
the way it sounded!
He's just
one of those guys
that makes jokes
when he likes you!
Hmm.
I'd forgotten
how strange
some of you
Adventurers can be.
[SYLVIE]
Yeah.
Look behind you.
[ALL]
Huh?
[GALFORD]
Southeast of the city
lies Seplia Lake.
And to the east
of that is a forest
that currently
conceals the Elves.
We still don't know
the exact number.
But considering
the Kingdom's forces,
we estimate
100, at most.
A hundred?
It's actually
not very much
if that's
the whole army.
[GALFORD] Their
numbers are the least
of my concerns,
right now.
It's more that their
specialty is hiding in trees
in order to
ambush their enemies.
If I were to send
troops into that forest
without any notion of
where these Elves lie in wait,
I would lose
too many of my men.
Having my men
die needlessly,
is the one thing
I hate above all else.
So you prefer to
sacrifice me instead?
You could save yourself
a lot of pain and struggle
if you'd just
hand over the princess.
-[SHERA whimpers]
-[DIABLO] I refuse!
Princess Shera.
What do you
seek so ardently,
that you would abandon
your life of luxury,
and disguise yourself
as an Adventurer?
To be myself.
I want to live a life
where I'm defined by
who I am,
not because of
my bloodline.
My worth should be
determined by
what I achieve myself.
And I know,
I'll never be allowed to
have that in the Elven nation.
Interesting.
[SHERA] Does that mean
you understand?
It means I've listened to
what you
have to say.
Not that I really
empathize with any of it.
Whoa, tough crowd.
[DIABLO] We aren't here
to ask for empathy.
[gasps]
We choose our own trials.
And how much
effort we put forth.
We challenge our
limits as we please.
Success is only measured
by our own strength.
When following a path
of your own creation,
you can't be led astray
by the expectations of others.
That's what it means
to live a life freedom.
[gasps]
[GALFORD] So, then,
you won't be handing
Princess Shera
over to the Elves,
and you'll be taking
other measures
to prevent a war with
the Kingdom of Greenwood.
Do I understand you correctly?
[DIABLO]
Shera belongs to me now.
Not the Elves.
I won't
give up what's mine.
Then I'll leave you to it.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Someone was
dispatched from
the royal capital
to look into this matter.
I'll introduce you.
[door opens]
[ALL gasp]
[door closes]
My name is Alicia Cristela.
I am an Imperial Knight.
I've received
orders to address
this matter
and offer my assistance.
From His Royal Majesty.
[TAKUMA]
An Imperial Knight?
I'm honored.
It's nice to meet you.
[sighs]
♪
[TAKUMA]
Alicia Cristela.
An Imperial Knight?
In Cross Reverie,
only powerful people
with a strong lineage could
become Imperial Knights.
They're supposed to be
the elite of the elite.
I can't remember if this
character was in the game.
Female Imperial Knights
are extremely rare
so I'm just
gonna stare at you.
That's so weird!
I thought all the Knights
had to be men?
Not me.
I've managed to
successfully serve
as a Knight for years,
despite my gender.
How very wonderful for you.
Thanks.
But we still have
a long way to go.
[ALICIA]
What's the matter, Rem?
It seems there might be
something on your mind
that's troubling you.
[BOTH gasp]
[REM]
Um.
What makes you think that?
[ALICIA]
I'm sorry.
It was just a guess.
The reports listed you
as a talented Summoner
with impressive accomplishments,
but I noticed you're
not working under anyone.
I was hoping
you might have
an interesting story
about why not?
Well, I don't.
[ALICIA] Please feel free
to reach out to me
if there's anything you need,
or that you
would like to discuss.
Sounds like a plan.
Thanks.
[ALICIA]
This is for you.
As reparations
from His Majesty.
What'd he do?
His regards
to you for losing
so many adventurers
in the incident the other day.
[SYLVIE]
Right.
Thank you.
[ALICIA claps hands]
And Shera?
I want you to know
I'm here on your side!
[SHERA gasps]
I know this fight
won't be easy
and we're sure to find
trouble along the way.
But I'm gonna
make it my duty
to see that everyone
remains in good spirits!
Yay!
[thunder rumbles]
[TAKUMA]
"Good spirits"?
-She's crazy!
-[BOTH laugh]
But I gotta
give her points
for communicating flawlessly
with some
people she just met!
That makes her level
a whole universe higher
than me
and my stutter-verse.
[ALL giggling]
[DIABLO groans]
[ALICIA]
Mr. Diablo.
There are no
words to express
the amount of
gratitude and respect
due to you for defending
the Bridge of Ulug
and then the City of Faltra
from the Fallen's attack.
I know that you have
no need for assistance, but,
please, allow me to
accompany you, regardless.
[TAKUMA] Why did she
have to ask me that?
Oh, man!
I can't be
around someone
so perfect
for an entire quest!
Any time
she talks to me,
I'll verbally crap
all over myself!
♪
-[DIABLO] Do as you please.
-[gasps]
However!
Huh?
If you don't
wish to die,
do not converse
with me so frivolously!
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL whimper]
[ALICIA]
Understood.
I shall prepare myself.
[DIABLO]
Huh?
-I'll do everything in my power
-[DIABLO farts]
to quell your rage, Mr. Diablo.
So be it.
I will not
begrudge you my life!
[TAKUMA]
She whadda-my-whadda-her-who?.
Ah, she's
too good at this!
♪
[CROWD murmuring]
Excuse me, Diablo?
Do you mind explaining
where we're
currently heading?
Please tell me
we're not going
straight to the woods
with the angry
Elves, are we?
We're visiting
a weaponsmith.
Thank you.
You realize there won't be
anyone in the entire city
who'll be able to
craft a better staff
than the one
you have currently, right?
You realize I don't need
your pessimism, right?
I happen to know
what I'm doing, Rem.
[TAKUMA]
My staff was enough
for the last battle, true,
but the residents
of this world
are on too low of a level
compared to the game.
They're weak.
I can't accidently
kill opponents
in front of
an Imperial Knight.
I need to find a weapon
today that will at least
make it look like
I'm having a hard time.
♪
[WEAPON FORGER]
Welcome!
Good to see you!
Ooh, nice choice!
Thank you so much!
I love it!
It's so big
and intimidating, Diablo.
It's perfectly suited
to take out small fries!
Exactly what I wanted!
Well, good.
As long as
you're happy.
[laughs]
[ALICIA]
Another question,
What is the plan after this?
[DIABLO]
Plan, right.
I suppose we
should head to a shop
to buy ingredients for potions.
I hope we won't
need to fight,
but it's always best to be
prepared for any outcome.
You never know.
[SHERA giggling]
Come on, guys!
Be careful, Shera.
Don't run on these roads
or you might trip!
[TAKUMA]
Her mom-game is strong.
[footsteps approaching]
[air hissing]
[REM and DIABLO grunt]
[CROWD screams]
[DIABLO]
What?
Seriously?
[SHERA]
No!
Let go of me!
Bring her back!
[DIABLO grunts]
[grunts]
[screaming]
Bounty hunters!
[DIABLO grunts]
[BOTH grunt]
You won't get by us!
But we'd love to play
if you're up for it!
No, thank you.
[gasps]
[grunts]
Out of the way!
[BOTH groan]
[MALE PANTHERIAN 1]
Ow, my head.
♪
That didn't kill you, did it?
Hello?
[MALE DWARF]
Shut up!
[TAKUMA] Okay good,
I can hold back on them.
This weapon really
was the right choice.
♪
[grunts]
[gasps]
Don't even try
to come near Diablo!
[ALICIA grunts]
[body thuds]
[grunts]
[REM]
This is unfortunate.
I hope you know you
ruined my shopping trip.
You bounty vultures
are getting an early start.
Better make this
worth my time.
[whimpers]
[grunts]
[MALE PANTHERIAN 2 screams]
I've got this.
Find Shera!
Right.
[grunts]
[explosion]
♪
[screams]
Shera!
-[SHERA screams]
-[KIDNAPPERS] One, two,
one, two, one two, one, two...
♪
[KIDNAPPERS] One, two,
one, two, one, two, one...
I think someone's
approaching us, brother!
Yeah, I hear it, too.
Who could it be?
[whimpers]
Shera!
Hold on!
I'm right behind you!
Diablo!
[KIDNAPPERS]
Who?
He's really fast, brother!
Run faster,
you stinky disgrace!
We can't let
ourselves be captured
after making it this far!
♪
[EMILE]
Double Smash!
[KIDNAPPERS scream]
[BOTH grunt]
[laughs]
And that's what happens when
cruelty is done to women.
-Not in my city, Scum!
-[KIDNAPPERS screaming]
You're back.
It's been a while,
hasn't' it, sport?
I am still
Emile Bichel Berger.
Defender of all women.
And the devastatingly
handsome hero of our tale!
[SHERA]
Thank you, Emile.
You saved me.
Where'd you come from?
I never thought of you
as the type to
cruise back alleys.
[chuckles] I am not.
Looks like you've
uncovered my secret.
When a woman
is in trouble, she sweats,
and I have the ability
to follow that scent!
[ALL groan]
Do your best to keep
the creepiness to a minimum.
That was a joke!
Actually,
I've come on word from
the Adventurer's Guild.
They said Prince Keera
put out a bounty.
I wanted to make sure this
fair maiden was protected.
That makes more sense.
There's another reason.
I wanted to
repay you for donating
your strength
to my rescue.
[DIABLO]
Uh?
What about them?
Do you have a plan?
They're still kidnappers
even if they're bad at it.
Dick.
We have an extra hand
if you need help.
Oh, heavens, no!
Leave these skunks to me!
I made a vow that
those who elicit the cries
of a woman shall be
eliminated from this world!
So you'll kill them?
[ALL]
Huh?
[EMILE] Perish that
thought this instant!
I wouldn't do
women this disservice.
These men must
learn from their mistakes.
And learn to love maidens!
They'll be like me!
-[ALL gasping]
-[MAN] Please kill me!
They will come to know
a life of honesty and bravery
and never again
will they endanger a woman!
[TAKUMA]
Be like him?
[EMILE]
And with that, I am off.
Do not believe
this is the last
you've seen of
those blinded by bounty!
Please, stay alert!
Okay, Emile, thanks!
Sounds great. Bye.
I feel so ashamed.
I nearly allowed
Shera to be kidnapped!
[ALICIA] You have my
deepest gratitude, good sir.
Oh, what's this?
It appears I've charmed yet
another beautiful woman.
My charisma
is downright sinful.
[laughs]
I mean,
I appreciate
his intentions, but, uh...
I'm not really
charmed by him.
Maybe if he never
said another word.
There's only so much
of that anyone can take.
[grunts softly]
Stay close.
Hmm. How close?
I mean,
don't stray from me.
Got that?
Yeah.
Thank you!
We don't have time
to keep hunting you down.
[whimpers]
Then...
[DIABLO grunts]
Um.
Could I please
hold your hand?
[TAKUMA gasping]
[DIABLO]
Yes.
I also wanted to say,
thanks for saving me.
That was Emile, Shera.
Not me.
Oh, yeah.
But you're
the one who took out
their kidnapping
buddies, right?
I was so afraid until
I saw you coming after me.
But from that moment,
I knew I'd be safe.
That you'd make sure
they didn't take me.
You're still
being hunted,
so I wouldn't
say you're safe.
Your optimism
is inappropriate.
[giggles]
[DIABLO]
Too close!
You're the one who said
you didn't want
to lose track of me.
Irrelevant.
You know,
I'm surprised.
I thought you'd be
weak without magic.
But you're not.
Way to be.
Well.
You should
know better than
to underestimate me.
I'm not some
low-level sorcerer.
I'm the Demon Lord.
[chuckles]
Right.
Please accept
my apology, Mr.Diablo.
This was my fault.
Shera was endangered
due to my inattention.
How can I
make it up to you?
I'll do anything!
How is any
of this your fault?
I'm the one who
ran ahead of you guys.
I promise you didn't
do anything wrong!
Really?
I think you're
confused, Alicia.
[gasps]
I'm Diablo,
the Demon Lord.
What made
you think that
I would require your
aid in the first place?
I don't know, I...
I'm so sorry.
I beg of you,
tell me how
I may be of better service!
Please!
[TAKUMA] Oh, man.
She's way too uptight
I get that
she's a Knight,
but she's gonna
lose her mind
if she doesn't
relax more.
[DIABLO]
Why try so hard?
Are you the type
who feels like
anyone who isn't
useful is worthless?
No. That's not it.
I believe
everyone has worth!
All right.
Then forgive yourself
for being completely
useless to me.
And if you still
wish to accompany us,
you have to stop insisting
that you produce results.
[stammers]
[sighs]
♪
Right.
I, Alicia Cristela,
swear on my pride,
and my honor
as a knight,
I will give my greatest
effort to forgive myself!
[TAKUMA]
Why is she yelling?
So, can we go,
or is this still
"feelings hour"?
Yeah, we rule
and elves drool!
Go! Fight! Win!
[stomach rumbling]
You're an elf, too!
Also, did you just
mess yourself?
Uh, no, I did not.
Oh, my gosh, Diablo?
How dare you!
I'm not
the gluttonous one
with no portion control!
Then who was it?
-[stomach rumbling]
-[ALL grunt]
[groans]
[giggles]
Your tummy's rumbling.
Are you hungry?
Well.
I am a little peckish.
We should eat,
they say you can't
fight on an empty stomach.
Oh. Do the
really say that?
[SHERA giggles]
Yay!
[SHERA] What are we
going to eat, you guys?
[REM]
Meat on a stick!
[SHERA] Be more
creative than that!
Food is art!
What would you like, Alicia?
[ALICIA] I don't really
have a preference.
-[REM] Meat sticks!
-[SHERA] No!
Something
colorful, like fruit!
[DIABLO]
Stop fighting!
You're giving me a headache!
[ALICIA giggles]
[SHERA and REM]
You figured out a way
to remove our collars?
[WOMAN]
We're body positive here.
[DIABLO] Send the power
of my magic into Shera?
[SHERA]
Diablo, wait!
This feels incredible!