♪
[EDELGARD]
Look who decided to show up.
[DIABLO]
Were you waiting long?
[EDELGARD]
Long enough.
[TAKUMA]
I remember this place.
It's where I was
first summoned.
[EDELGARD]
I've already taken care of
most of the preparations.
That includes
drawing the magic circle.
[scoffs]
Hmm?
[footsteps approaching]
[DIABLO] Oh, I brought
my knight along with me.
I advise you not
to question my motives.
Her name's Alicia.
[TAKUMA scoffs]
Not a crap
is being given today.
Didn't expect that.
[REM]
This isn't one of those rituals
where you fill
Krebskulm's soul
with as much
magic power as possible,
is it?
[EDELGARD]
No.
You will be
filling her soul
with the strongest
and most magic power possible.
[EDELGARD]
We should be able to hasten
her resurrection
that way.
Maybe. I hope.
So, yeah.
Tell me again
why we're putting my life
in the hands of a Fallen.
Should we call it off?
No.
[REM] I want
the Kreb-scumbag out of me.
I'm just saying,
I hope you know
what you're doing, Diablo.
I mean...
You're my only hope
at the moment.
Don't eff it up.
♪
[DIABLO]
I promised I would save you
from this
monster one day, Rem.
I won't let you down.
♪
[wind blowing]
[EDELGARD]
No more time to waste.
Let's begin.
The Demon Lord
is in Rem's stomach,
so you must pour
your magical power
into the soul
at that spot.
[EDELGARD]
That energy will then
trigger the resurrection.
As if it's NBD.
Have I mentioned
we're trusting
a Fallen with this?
I'm lounging
in her magic circle
and we're
all okay with that?
Surprised no one's
serving refreshments.
[DIABLO]
Relax.
[REM]
I can't.
Just get it over with.
[TAKUMA grunts]
[TAKUMA gasps]
There it is!
I see you, Krebskie.
Pack your bags!
[wails]
-[DIABLO grunts]
-[REM] Diablo!
Can you turn it
down a notch?
It's burning!
[REM whimpers]
♪
-That it?
-Not even close.
[DIABLO grunts]
[EDELGARD]
If it were that easy,
Rem could
cough her out.
She's much
deeper within.
Meaning?
[EDELGARD]
It's not enough.
-You'll have to create a hole...
-[REM shudders]
...that will take you
to her stomach.
You mean cut through
her organs and stuff?
She'll die!
Hmm...
Use the one
she already has.
What? Where?
-[metal clangs]
-[EDELGARD] Duh.
-Uh?
Uh?
[EDELGARD]
Hands go in that way.
It's easy.
Like this.
[TAKUMA]
The shocker?
Nope!
No times no,
divided by
no to the power of,
"Oh, hell no!"
What is wrong with her?
And where did she
learn that gesture?
[TAKUMA] My mind is
squashed grapes right now.
I get it.
We're all trying to save Rem,
but come on!
Just the idea of me
touching her like...
[grunts]
Like that will
make her wanna bail!
Just do it.
[DIABLO]
What?
Make it fast.
Unless you wanna
come up with a better plan.
I don't really know
what's going on,
but I think you'll be okay, Rem.
[TAKUMA]
But, what about me?
Are your hands clean?
I guess it's
too late now.
[REM]
Hurry up.
[grunts]
♪
[fabric tears]
[DIABLO grunts]
[whimpering]
[DIABLO whimpering]
♪
[cries]
[REM]
That's too fast!
Your hands are cold!
Is it over?
Did you get it out?
-[cries]
-[DIABLO] Not yet!
[TAKUMA]
I'm still a long way
from reaching my goal.
Where the hell is she?
[REM whimpering]
[whimpers]
[REM cries]
[grunts]
[TAKUMA]
The yarn ball!
Whoa.
Huge yarn ball.
This Krebskulm
demon thing
is not messing around!
[DIABLO]
You ready?
I'm going to thrust
all my power inside you!
Don't say it like that!
I get it!
[DIABLO groans]
[cries]
[REM gasps]
[KREBSKULM laughing]
[EDELGARD screams]
Yes!
The Demon Lord
has been reborn!
We should rethink this.
[SHERA]
I'm starting to feel like
this wasn't
the best idea!
[DIABLO]
Are you all right?
Say something!
Something.
Please win.
It's the least you can do.
I know!
The least you can do
is bear witness to it!
Don't you dare die, Rem!
[KREBSKULM laughing]
That power.
It's huge!
So strong.
Amazing!
[pop]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[BOTH grunt]
Uh, so...
[SHERA]
Is it out?
[gasps]
[grunts softly]
[KREBSKULM yawns]
Is there coffee?
There better be
a damn good reason
for waking me up
at this hour!
The Demon Lord!
[TAKUMA]
No way!
That's her?
This is Krebskulm?
Who are you?
[EDELGARD]
I am Edelgard
and I'm thrilled
to see you.
I'm overjoyed
by the success
of your resurrection!
[KREBSKULM]
It's impressive, right?
Go ahead and celebrate.
I am a pretty big deal!
[DIABLO] Indeed.
But before we do,
can you confirm you're
the Demon Lord Krebskulm?
-Yes, I confirm.
-[DIABLO] Perfect.
[DIABLO] I don't know
what I was expecting,
but it doesn't
matter, does it?
My name is Diablo.
I'm a Demon Lord
from another world,
and I'm here
to destroy you!
I get it now.
You're
Mr. Tickle Fingers
who woke me up.
That was rude.
But what can you do?
Now I'm awake
and it's time
for payback!
[ALL grunt]
[DIABLO grunts]
[KREBSKULM]
Are you ready to die
the most
brutal death ever?
Yes! Guts are gonna fly!
Uh...
[KREBSKULM] Hold on!
We have to start over!
I forgot how
it goes exactly,
but it's brutal and messy!
[groans]
What was it?
[ALL]
Huh?
[TAKUMA]
Seriously?
Has she been
asleep so long
that she's
forgotten how to fight?
Forget it! I'll just
burn everything to ashes
like a Demon Lord
with no creativity!
This guy gets it.
No, you can't do that!
But why not?
[gasp]
Don't listen to her!
You're the Demon Lord,
remember?
Kill them!
Burn them!
I mean,
I wanted to,
but they're
saying I can't,
so I guess I can't?
[gasps]
[TAKUMA]
What's going on here?
Did she lose some of
her memories while sleeping?
The Demon Lord
destroys the mortal races!
[ALICIA]
Isn't that true?
[KREBSKULM]
Huh. I guess?
Yeah, that sounds right!
[REM]
Then I have a question!
What for?
What does killing
anyone do for you?
I mean,
does it make you
more powerful or something?
You're slinging
a whole lot of questions
at someone
who just woke up.
Ugh.
If it's not gonna save
your life or someone else's,
you need to quit
killing all together!
-[grunts]
-[SHERA] Yeah, what she said!
Killing is really
stupid, you guys!
[scoffs]
[KREBSKULM]
Is it?
I'm sure there's
a good reason
for killing you,
but I can't
think of it right now.
[scoffs]
So, I guess I won't.
[TAKUMA grunts]
Wait, what?
Are you serious?
The demon lord
won't kill the mortal races?
[KREBSKULM]
I'm too hungry to think about
what to do with
mortal races right now.
[ALICIA]
Edelgard!
Are you okay
with all this?
I suppose
I have to be.
She is the Demon Lord,
my master.
If it's her will
to let you all live,
then, so be it.
[grunts softly]
[KREBSKULM] What are you
supposed to do when
your Demon Lord
is starving?
[SHERA] Oh. I brought
some snacks you can have.
[SHERA]
Here.
[KREBSKULM]
What are those things?
[SHERA]
They're called cookies.
[sniffs]
[chews]
These are so good!
I've got some
more if you'd like!
[KREBSKULM]
I'd like!
-[gasps]
-[KREBSKULM chews]
My mouth is
having a great day!
-[chews]
-[giggles]
[KREBSKULM] How did I
not know about these treasures?
Thanks to them,
I've remembered my mission!
[ALL gasp]
The reason
I was reborn today,
is so that
I could devour
every cookie
that exists in this world!
[TAKUMA]
I doubt that's true.
[KREBSKULM]
You!
Are there more
of these "cookie" things?
[SHERA]
So, my name's Shera,
and we'd have to
go back to the city
to get some more.
[KREBSKULM]
Then get moving!
Lead the way
to the city!
[SHERA]
What? I don't even know
if they'll let you in!
-[SHERA] You're a Demon Lord!
-[gasps]
[bugs chirping]
Okay. I think I can walk now.
You can put me down.
You haven't regained
your strength yet,
and I'm not going
to slow everyone down
so you can keep up.
It's your call.
[sighs]
[DIABLO]
I'm still not sure
how I feel about this.
-You?
-[SHERA] If you had to guess...
[REM]
It's not awesome,
that's for sure.
I remember my mother
and grandmother suffering
because of that Demon.
We spent
our whole lives
trying to defeat Krebskulm
and living in fear of her.
[BOTH talking]
[REM]
But I guess,
if she's not going
to kill any mortal races,
then there's
no need to fight her.
That's assuming she's
telling the truth, anyway.
[gasps]
[ALICIA]
Diablo! Above you!
[DIABLO]
Huh? Huh?
♪
[DIABLO]
What is that?
♪
[SHERA gasps]
Demon Lord.
Congratulations
on your resurrection.
-Who the hell is this guy?
-Uh...
[OUROU]
I am Eulerex.
I have served
the Demon Lords
for generations.
[DIABLO]
Eulerex?
[TAKUMA] I remember him
from Cross Reverie, too.
He's been around.
I'd say for at least
three generations
of Demon Lords.
He's the oldest of us all.
And the strongest, by far.
[OUROU] It's true that
I have been waiting
for your resurrection
for a very long time.
Please allow me
to offer a sacrifice
to celebrate
this most auspicious day.
[KREBSKULM]
What's that mean?
[OUROU]
"Fortunate."
It would be
an honor to
slaughter the mortals
currently still
breathing here
in your presence.
I offer their lives
in celebration
of your resurrection.
Uh, you better not!
If you kill them,
where am I
gonna get cookies
to complete my mission?
Huh? Uh...
[OUROU]
Edelgard,
it appears
that the Demon Lord
is not interested
in killing mortals.
Do you happen to know
the meaning of this?
[EDELGARD]
I have no clue.
You know as much
as I do, buddy.
[OUROU]
The Demon Lord is the ruler
of all dark beings.
Dark beings
kill mortal races.
-This isn't right at all.
-[DIABLO grunts]
Therefore,
I believe
the only
solution we have
is for the incomplete
Demon Lord
to reincarnate again!
[EDELGARD grunts]
[OUROU]
What are you doing?
Straining. Listen.
She has expressed her will.
We have to honor it. 'Kay?
Even Fallen have
purpose in this world.
So I will complete this
incomplete resurrection
of our so-called Demon Lord!
[gasps]
[grunts]
Alicia, protect
Rem and Shera!
You crazy?
I won't get too close.
He's known as
the strongest Fallen
for a reason.
[DIABLO]
Don't worry, Rem.
I intend to
end this quickly.
[whimpers]
-[OUROU] You are a silly one.
-[EDELGARD whimpering]
Do you really think
such a weakling
can handle
all of this boss meat?
It's not...
It's not right
for a Fallen
to disobey
a Demon Lord.
A Demon Lord's
soul is limited.
As long as this mockery
of Krebskulm is alive,
the true Krebskulm
cannot be resurrected!
[EDELGARD whimpering]
[OUROU]
I'm fairly certain
it was your
foolish actions
that have created
this incomplete resurrection
of our Lord.
[screams]
[EDELGARD gasping]
Hmm?
[EDELGARD grunts]
[gasps]
How'd you dodge that one?
A tiny little Demon
dares to stand
before a Fallen.
[chuckles]
You've lived a long life,
but you're missing
some important information.
My name is Diablo!
[DIABLO]
And you're the fool
who dares
to stand before
a true Demon Lord!
What?
[TAKUMA]
Just kidding.
There's no way
he's ever heard of me.
I'm just a player.
Let's hope he
doesn't realize that!
[DIABLO]
Flare Burst!
[OUROU grunts]
[DIABLO]
Did it work?
[OUROU]
Curse you!
[DIABLO]
Super Mine!
[grunts]
[TAKUMA]
Holy crap, he's fast!
Quartz Lance!
[grunts]
Come!
[BOTH gasp]
[OUROU groans]
Did you just use
Magic Reflection?
[DIABLO]
Well. I'm impressed you
figured it out
on the first shot.
[OUROU]
That can't be.
Magic Reflection was
the unique power of Enkvaros,
the Demon Lord of the Mind.
How did you?
[TAKUMA]
Yup. It's because I was
the first person to defeat
Enkvaros in the game.
I received the ring
as a reward for that event.
It looks like
living through
two generations
of Demon Lords
has given him a crap
ton of knowledge, though.
I'd better
keep that in mind.
[DIABLO scoffs]
Haven't you realized yet?
No matter how
hard you struggle,
you have no chance
of beating me.
[OUROU groans]
[growls]
[grunts]
The incomplete
Demon Lord must die!
[gasps]
Look out!
[BOTH grunt]
Lightning Bullet!
Seriously?
You protected me?
[KREBSKULM]
Are you feeling sick?
-[ALICIA] Rem!
-No.
I-I'm okay.
[KREBSKULM]
Good for you!
I approve of this!
[SHERA]
Well, actually.
when someone
does something for you,
you're supposed
to say "thank you."
[REM]
It's fine.
[KREBSKULM]
I see!
Thank you for saving me!
[gasps]
[OUROU]
What immense magic power.
You are no ordinary mortal.
[DIABLO]
I told you, I'm a Demon Lord.
It was only moments ago.
Have you gone senile?
[groans]
It's inconceivable.
The strength you
possess is abnormal.
I don't understand.
Yet.
Huh?
[wind howling]
[ALICIA]
Are you sure it was wise
to let him go?
[DIABLO]
I've just lost interest.
I don't care about
those who run from me.
[TAKUMA] I probably
could have taken him,
but if he used
some sort of attack
that wasn't magic,
I wouldn't be able to
protect this many people.
I'd rather
avoid putting
everyone in danger.
[DIABLO]
That delayed us for
far too long.
Let's get home
right away.
The Bridge of Ulug
should be coming
into view soon.
[SHERA]
'Kay!
[scoffs]
[EDELGARD]
Demon Lord.
If you wish to head
into the human city,
I will not be permitted
to accompany you inside.
I'll wait near the forest.
You can call on me
at any time from there.
Okay.
Good work!
[KREBSKULM]
And, uh, thank you?
It was
my pleasure, truly.
[ALICIA]
I was thinking.
We're likely to run into
several problems in the city
if we were to use
Krebskulm's name openly.
Don't you agree?
[DIABLO]
Very true.
That's an invitation
for unwanted chaos.
[KREBSKULM]
So make something up!
I may be a Demon Lord,
but it really doesn't
make a difference
how you refer to me
when there are
cookies at stake!
Uh...
Let's see.
Oh! I know!
[SHERA]
How about our friend, Klem?
[door shuts]
[DIABLO groans]
Are you feeling okay?
I am fine, but what's
the matter with him?
When Diablo
uses his magic,
he's always
worn out and tired
for a few days after.
That's right, I've heard
that about the mortal races.
You just can't
keep up, can you?
[SHERA] You don't get
worn out like that?
Don't be a dingleberry!
I've got infinite
magic power
constantly forming!
[TAKUMA]
That's cheating.
[DIABLO]
What happened to Rem and Alicia?
There wasn't room
for all four of us in here,
so Rem's sleeping
in Alicia's room.
Good, good.
[sighs]
[clothes rustling]
Huh?
[yelps]
[DIABLO]
Shera! What's going on?
[SHERA giggles]
Well, since
Rem's not here.
I figured I'd try
to help you recharge
your energy
a little faster!
[giggles]
[DIABLO]
Wait! What? How? What?
You mortals have to
work way too hard.
That's how you give each other
magic powers?
Would you like
to try it, Klem?
It helps to
strengthen your powers
at the same time!
Seriously?
So the supplier
gains energy, too?
[KREBSKULM]
I wanna do it!
[DIABLO groans]
-[KREBSKULM] Like this?
-[SHERA] Yup!
Keep pressing
against him just like that
and you'll see
he gets very active!
-[DIABLO groans]
-He does!
And you're right,
it's fun for me, too!
[TAKUMA]
What is happening right now?
It can't be good!
It feels like volts
of electricity!
Klem's pouring a crap
ton of magic into me!
[sighs]
What's the matter?
Don't you
like this, too?
[moaning]
Is it working, Diablo?
Are you feeling active?
[TAKUMA groans]
Damn it! Damn it!
I just want to
stare at them!
My life would be
so much different
if I could just
keep it together
in situations like this!
[whimpers]
[sighs]
It feels amazing.
I can't stop squeezing.
[panting]
It's like when his
power pours into me.
[BOTH moaning]
[ALL moan]
♪
[SHERA]
Anyone hungry?
[DIABLO groans]
[DIABLO]
My Magic Points
are fully recovered
in record time.
[DIABLO]
That Demon Lord is incredible.
[ALICIA'S MOM echoing]
Metal on a woman's face?
How incredibly shameful.
Take those off.
[ALICIA'S DAD echoing] I found
the books you were hiding.
They were
quite inappropriate.
So I threw them out.
It's for your own good.
[KNIGHT]
When an emergency arises,
always protect
the humans first.
Demihumans
aren't the priority.
[EMPEROR] Sometimes
sacrifices are necessary
for the prosperity
of our nation.
You must resist
selfish thinking.
[ALL]
Alicia!
It's unacceptable.
I need the Demon Lord to fulfill
her promise
to all of us.
[ALICIA]
She must do what she can
to make our
world beautiful.
She must destroy
all the mortal races.
[KNIGHT]
Saddler, are you all right?
Tell me how you feel.
[SADDLER]
Obviously, not well.
I feel quite awful.
The gods would
never approve
the existence
of an insolent man
who refuses to
believe in my power.
And I shall never forgive
those damn demihumans!
[KREBSKULM growls]
[SADDLER]
Are you saying the Demon Lord
has been revived?
[ALICIA]
Every ugly
mortal race
shall perish!
[REM]
I'm so sorry, Klem.