[whimpering]
[ADVENTURER 1]
Help me!
Somebody.
Please help me!
[grunts]
[body thuds]
♪
[ALICIA]
How ghastly.
I'll never
understand mortals.
How can they
be so atrocious?
The mortal races
deserve to be wiped off
the face of the planet.
[lightning cracks]
♪
[KNIGHT]
How truly beautiful.
Everyone who worshipped
the Demon Lord
in this village
has now
found salvation.
There's no sight
more beautiful to behold.
You can tell
a person's worth
by the color
of their exposed,
steaming innards.
[maniacal laughter]
[rain pouring]
♪
[SERVANT 1]
Oh, Alicia?
I didn't realize
you already returned.
I have.
It's good to see you again.
Well, I imagine
that you're
just as busy
as always.
But please,
don't push yourself too hard.
My devotion
belongs to the people.
That's the duty
of an Imperial Knight.
[gasps]
[footsteps approaching]
[blade scraping floor]
[gasps]
Uh. Well, then,
if you'll pardon me.
[footsteps departing]
I'll be,
valiant
Cristela returns.
I take it that you've already
reported to His Majesty
about the Greenwood
incident?
Of course.
Without issue.
[ALICIA]
It's difficult to predict
what sort of future
the Kingdom of
Greenwood will face,
but His Majesty
has informed me
that the matter
is now closed.
[SADDLER]
That's comforting to hear.
Peace is
always best.
And how about you, Saddler?
The last I heard,
you were headed
to a village
in the south.
I'm happy to say
the villagers
found salvation.
Every last one.
♪
[ALICIA]
I'm curious, Saddler.
Do you harbor hatred
for the mortal races?
[SADDLER]
What? Heavens, no!
In fact,
I love them.
They're the descendants
of those
directly blessed
by the Gods.
For that reason,
I'm incapable of
forgiving those
who worship
the Demon Lord.
♪
[ALICIA]
I'll be on my way now.
Off so soon?
Are you leaving
for Faltra?
[ALICIA] There are
a few lingering matters
I must attend to.
Actually,
it just so happens that
I'm heading to
Faltra, as well.
[gasps]
[SADDLER]
The Head Priest, Lumachina,
has revealed a prophecy.
[ALICIA]
He did?
[SADDLER]
Indeed.
Omens of
the Demon Lord's revival
in the western city.
As a Paladin,
I have no choice
but to investigate.
[ALICIA] Signs of
the Demon Lord's reemergence.
[SHERA groaning]
[gasps]
[gobbles]
Whoa, check it out!
I actually summoned it!
Duh, a complete
idiot can summon
with me teaching them.
Aww! It's so cute!
[REM]
It's called a Turkey Shot.
And to be blunt,
you've summoned
stronger things
in the bathroom.
[SHERA]
Can it fight?
Not especially, no.
It's special ability
is Synchro Sight.
It's a basic power
that allows you
to see everything
the Summon can see.
[SHERA]
That sounds useful!
[REM]
With as much magic power
as it consumes,
you can't use it
for very long.
So it really only
comes in handy
if you're lost.
[groans]
That's lame.
[REM]
There's all kinds of
summons in this world,
but it's the tough ones
with powerful attacks
that you actually
wanna control.
[SHERA]
Yeah, makes sense.
So, what do you wanna do?
Not like you
really need to perform
the Enslavement Ritual
with that gobbler.
Uh...
Well, I summoned it,
so I'll forge the pact.
[DIABLO]
Huh?
What's with the rock?
[SHERA]
I don't know what it is,
but she said
it's necessary.
It's the magic
stone required
to do
the Enslavement Ritual.
[REM]
Here, Diablo,
I'll give you one, too.
♪
[TAKUMA] These things
weren't in Cross Reverie.
I hereby command you
in the name of
Shera L. Greenwood.
You shall answer my call,
become mine alone,
and forever obey me.
[grunts softly]
♪
[kisses]
I did it!
Yeah, lucky us.
The magic
wasn't reflected again.
[SHERA]
I know, right?
I don't wanna be
enslaved to
Ms. Gobblers!
[DIABLO] Speaking of
your new spy bird...
Huh?
I have an idea.
That Summon
might just be
perfectly
suited for you.
Huh?
♪
[DIABLO]
There!
[SHERA]
Whoa!
[DIABLO]
Well?
Were you able to see
where the coin fell?
[SHERA]
No way.
All right.
Now send your
jive turkey after it.
Ms. Gobblers.
Not jive turkey.
Hey, look for that coin.
[gobbles]
♪
[groans softly]
[yelps]
[SHERA gasps]
It's amazing!
I feel like
I'm the one
soaring
through the sky!
[SHERA gasps]
Huh?
[SHERA]
I found it!
Fire an arrow at it.
Okay!
♪
[effort grunts]
Perfect shot.
Holy crap.
You see,
it's more worthwhile
than you expected.
You're able to shoot
enemies in locations
you can't see yourself.
[REM] So the elf isn't
completely useless.
[SHERA]
Me and good ol Ms. Gobblers!
[chuckles]
[TAKUMA] Good thing I
happened to read about it
on a message board.
Thanks for
showing me, Diablo!
I just figured I'd
managed to get stuck
with a real
stinker on my hands,
but I like you now,
Gobblers,
you've won me over.
Uh...
[sniffs]
[REM]
Now it's getting weird.
It's not coming
from the bird.
[SHERA gasps]
What's up?
How long has it been
since you've had a bath?
What the hell are
you trying to say?
[SHERA] Well, I can't be
the only one who's noticed!
She stinks,
right, Diablo?
Huh? What?
You sure
you're not smelling
your own
underboob sweat?
[SHERA]
Yeah!
-[SHERA] You've got a point!
-[REM gasps]
We might as well
all take a bath together!
[moans]
♪
[DIABLO screams]
If we're gonna do this,
shouldn't we have
some bathing suits?
Bathing suits?
What are those?
[TAKUMA]
Seriously?
I don't know how
you take a bath,
but most people
do it naked.
We just don't
look at each other.
[grunting]
[REM]
It's really not that difficult
to not be a creep.
[SHERA]
Come on, Diablo.
Hurry up and strip
down so we can get in.
[DIABLO
Look, I do not care for this odd
bathing custom of yours.
I'm fine here!
You two can
wash off your
stink on your own.
[BOTH] I do not smell,
you freakin' jerk!
[bird chirping]
[gasping]
[REM]
I can't believe you.
The crap that comes
out of your mouth.
It is a fact
that Pantherians'
sweat don't
smell, you know.
A "fact"?
It doesn't have a scent
and it's not salty!
[water sloshing]
[slurping]
[gasps]
What are doing,
you weirdo?
Licky, licky, licky!
Stop!
Get off of me!
[SHERA]
Yep, you're right.
-I can't taste any salt.
-[REM whimpering]
You could've just
believed me, you know!
Hmm.
[REM whimpers]
Hey, tell me what
my sweat tastes like.
What makes you think
I would do that?
Then I'll just have
to lick myself.
[REM]
What's wrong with you,
-you dumb overstuffed elf?
-[SHERA cries]
Did your brain slip
down into your boobs?
You know
that can't happen!
And that really hurts!
[REM] All their jiggling
must've shaken it loose!
[TAKUMA panting]
[grunting]
[TAKUMA]
Why am I not looking?
Yeah, sure,
I'm not brave enough to stare,
but just a quick
glimpse is all
I need to
save this sight
into my spank bank!
Maybe just a peek.
[SHERA screams]
[DIABLO gasps]
I'm sorry!
[REM]
You're a Fallen, aren't you?
[DIABLO grunts]
[SHERA]
Rem?
[footsteps approaching]
[grunts] What are you
doing here, Edelgard?
[TAKUMA]
Seriously?
Hasn't she
learned her lesson?
[DIABLO]
Speak!
Tell me
what you want!
I'm not here looking
for a fight today.
Just to talk.
We can wait
on the rest.
[REM gasps]
[water sloshing]
You want to talk?
I received
some information
that I had to verify.
And now that
I've touched her,
I know that it's true.
I detect the soul
of a Demon Lord within you.
[gasps]
[TAKUMA gasps]
Holy crap!
She can actually
sense Krebskulm's soul
inside Rem's body?
Uh, what now?
What's she
going on about, Rem?
I kinda feel
like I'm being
kept in the dark
on something here.
[SHERA]
So?
♪
You want the truth?
[REM]
Fine, here it is.
The soul of
Demon Lord Krebskulm
is sealed
inside of me.
[SHERA]
Huh?
[fire crackling]
[SHERA]
So that's what's been
going on with you.
[REM]
I'm sorry I didn't tell you,
but I thought
it was for the best.
It's just....
I didn't wanna
do that to you.
To force the burden
of my secret
onto your chest.
[SHERA cries]
Shera?
[SHERA]
I know I'm not the strongest,
but still,
that doesn't mean
I don't wanna help you
when you're in
some kind of trouble.
You're my friend, Rem.
All this time
must've been
so tough for you.
I'm sorry
I never realized it.
[REM]
Thank you, Shera.
That means a lot.
You're hoping to defeat
the Demon Lord in you,
is this right?
That's your plan?
[REM sighs]
Yeah, it's true.
Huh.
[REM]
Now that you know,
I want an answer
from you, as well.
I always figured
I'd be killed
if a Fallen found out.
So I guess
the question
I'm asking you
is, what now?
[EDELGARD]
The Demon Lord is delicate.
You can't simply
break its vessel.
There's more
to it than that.
So, no.
I won't kill you.
[DIABLO]
All right.
I'm guessing
you know a way
to completely revive
the Demon Lord?
That's correct.
Really?
[EDELGARD]
The resurrection ritual
poses zero
risk to her life.
It won't harm her.
In fact, it's
the exact opposite.
She will be treasured as
the mother
of the Demon Lord.
Hmm.
You're skeptical.
It's evident that
you don't believe me.
I should've
known as much.
[sighs]
[EDELGARD]
Fine.
I'll teach you
the ritual then.
You can conduct it yourself
and we Fallen
won't touch you.
How's that?
[TAKUMA]
What do we do?
Rem wants to release
the Demon Lord's seal
so she can finally
settle the matter.
It sucks that Edelgard
discovered her secret,
but at least we've got
the same interests
in wanting to get
Krebskulm out of Rem.
The real
question though,
is can I beat Krebskulm
after the resurrection?
[SHERA]
What do you think, Diablo?
[DIABLO]
Very well. Let's do this.
Go ahead and
teach me your ritual.
I'll gladly conduct
your ceremony
and see it completed.
I'll revive
your Demon Lord,
but only so I can
pulverize the impostor
and put him
in the ground!
The Demon Lord Krebskulm
is the real demon lord.
You won't succeed.
Have you already
forgotten my power?
♪
Hmm.
In three days,
on the evening
of the full moon.
I'll be waiting for you
at Starfall Tower.
We'll conduct
the ritual there.
Fine by me.
[DIABLO]
We've settled our terms, Rem.
We'll finally be able to
free you
from this cursed fate.
[DIABLO]
Three days from now,
I'll destroy that
parasite inside you.
[STREET CROWD chatter]
[cats meowing]
[sniffles]
Uh...
So, uh,
are you really
doing this tonight?
[SHERA]
Want some food, Mr. Meowsers?
Ow, no bite!
-[sighs]
-[SHERA giggles]
Hey, it's Alicia!
[ALICIA]
Greetings.
I've just returned from
the imperial capital.
I'm relieved to see you
had a safe journey.
Do you just love
the smell of ammonia?
[DIABLO] Or did you know
that we were here?
Please, Diablo.
Hmm?
I need you to return
to the inn at once.
Huh?
[STREET CROWD chatter]
[DIABLO] Do you care to explain
the meaning of this?
Did something happen
when you were in the capital?
There's a Paladin
named Saddler
lurking somewhere
in this town right now.
Is he dangerous
or something?
I believe his level
as a knight is over 100.
Oh?
[TAKUMA]
If this dude's over 100,
then he's on par
with Galford or better.
I've never had any
Paladins come after me
looking for battle in the game,
so I don't know their stats.
To make it worse,
if Saddler believes
there's even a chance
that you
worship a Demon Lord,
your torture
will be legendary.
-Torture?
-[ALICIA] Yes.
He'll drag it out
for as long as possible
until you confess.
[TAKUMA]
Forget the worshipping,
what's he gonna do
to someone who's
proclaimed themself
an actual Demon Lord?
[ALICIA]
We should play this safe.
The smart thing to do
is for you all
to stay indoors
until Saddler
leaves town.
[TAKUMA]
I knew being a shut-in
would pay off!
[REM]
Regardless,
I sincerely doubt
that a Paladin
could defeat Diablo.
[ALICIA] Of course,
don't mistake my words.
I'm well aware
of Diablo's strength.
However, this man,
his true power
is something else.
[gasps]
Ah, there you are.
I've been
looking for you.
You just
disappeared on me
all of a sudden.
[ALICIA]
You make it out
to sound nefarious.
I just wanted
to say hello
to some other
adventurers I know.
[SADDLER]
Is that so?
Pleasure to meet you.
The name's Saddler.
I'm a Paladin
of the imperial capital's
Orthodox Church.
And who might you be?
[ALICIA grunts]
[TAKUMA] We've gotta
perform the ritual tonight.
I don't have time to risk
provoking this guy.
Just try to
act normal,
don't say
anything dumb.
[DIABLO]
I am known as Diablo!
The great Demon Lord
from another world!
[ALL gasp]
[TAKUMA] Aw, crap.
I acted too normal!
[ALL whimpering]
[chuckles]
I've been told that
adventurers are known
for their
sense of humor,
but to claim that
you're a Demon Lord?
That is just priceless!
-[SADDLER chuckles]
-[ALICIA chuckles]
Diablo's a real prankster,
he's got jokes. [gasps]
I don't care
if he's joking,
the fact that you can
be friendly with someone
who makes light
of a Demon Lord...
I'm afraid
that's a problem
I can't overlook.
[ALICIA]
These adventurers have come
to my aid
when I needed help.
I am not ashamed
to call them
my friends.
Hmm.
So you're telling me
they have
nothing to hide?
Are you planning
to torture me
in order to find out?
I haven't decided yet.
♪
[scoffs]
[REM]
This is just ridiculous.
Do you have
some kind of issue
with us seeing
Alicia Cristela?
What the hell
is your problem?
[SADDLER grunts]
Pipe down and
remember your place, slave.
[REM gasps]
How dare you,
I am not a slave!
Maintain
this insolence,
and you'll face
divine judgment.
[gasps]
You should be the one
apologizing
for being so rude!
Can you
hear yourself?
[gasps]
[REM grunting]
[SHERA]
What's wrong?
-[gasps]
-[SHERA] Rem!
[ALICIA]
Are you okay?
[SHERA]
What's happening to her?
[SADDLER]
You're feeling the touch
of the Gods,
a power
bestowed upon me
as a result of my pure,
unyielding faith.
[SHERA] Rem!
Just hang in there!
[TAKUMA]
What the hell?
How's he doing this?
There was
no power granted
by Gods in the game!
What do I do?
[grunts]
[TAKUMA]
Wait.
That thing wrapped
around her head.
Is it...
That's just magic!
[DIABLO]
Cute little stunt
you're trying to pull, amateur!
-[SADDLER] Amateur?
-[DIABLO] Amateur!
That's divine punishment?
It's nothing
but a simple spell.
[groaning]
[gasping]
[SHERA]
Rem!
[ALICIA]
Are you all right?
[SADDLER]
It takes some audacity
for a mere demon
to insult a Paladin.
Talk to me!
Just tell me
you're okay!
I'm okay now.
Thank you.
[sighs]
Thank goodness.
You dare to question
the power of the Gods?
You must pay
for your doubt
through divine punishment.
Quit calling it that.
We both know
it's pathetic magic,
and it will
not work on me.
Yet another
foolish heretic
unwilling to believe.
I'll harden your
doubt and crack
it open like a stone!
♪
[gasp]
What... is this?
[groans]
[BOTH whimper]
[exhale]
[gasp]
[grunts]
[chuckles]
A Cement Lock, huh?
Your run-of-the-mill
negative status
Earth spell.
Was that
Magic Reflection?
[ALICIA]
So he truly was
just using spells.
[DIABLO]
If I had to guess,
he was most likely using
Subtle Chant
to cast his spells.
A skill accessible
to a level 60 Sorceror.
It allows you
to use magic
without speaking
the spell's name aloud.
Is he stuck like that?
When will
the spell wear off?
[DIABLO]
That depends on
the caster's level.
The magic will eventually
dissipate, though.
Are you
all right, Rem?
Yeah.
Although
I'm starting to get
tired of you
having to save me.
[grunts]
[footsteps departing]
Are you sure
it was a wise idea
to allow Saddler
to remain free?
Would you
have preferred
that we kill him instead?
[ALICIA sighs]
[DIABLO]
Hmm?
[TAKUMA]
Huh?
What's with the look?
[DIABLO grunts]
I couldn't care less
if a peon
lives or dies.
If he challenges me again,
there will
be no mercy
to waste upon him.
That's more like it.
I suppose
that I was worried
over nothing.
[sighs]
[TOWN chattering]
[SHERA]
Just about time to leave.
[REM]
I know.
[footsteps approaching]
You ready?
We should
get going now.
[REM groans softly]
What's the matter, Rem?
I feel like
we should
tell her the truth.
You mean Alicia?
[REM sighs]
[SHERA]
I think that'd be okay.
[gasps]
We already know
Alicia's a good person.
I'm sure that
she'd understand.
-[DIABLO] I have to disagree.
-[BOTH gasp]
Regardless,
she's an imperial knight.
Considering that,
she won't overlook
the Demon Lord's revival.
I understand
what you're saying,
but, still.
Hmm.
[REM]
Even if you're right.
I want to trust Alicia.
She's become my friend,
the same way
you and Shera have.
So I'm willing to
take the chance.
[REM and SHERA sigh]
Thank you
for telling me.
I can't imagine how much
you've had to
suffer with this.
Then to
confess to me?
It must've been difficult.
I'll help you
as much as I can.
There's no
need for you
to bear such
an awful burden
on your own.
-I'm here for you.
-[REM gasps]
[ALICIA]
We are friends, after all.
Thank you, Alicia.
Thank you so much.
[whimpers]
[cries]
[TAKUMA]
Why does this feel
so cheap to me?
Something's off here.
Seriously.
What's this
uneasy feeling
in my chest?
[grunts]
No, no, shake it off!
I'm just exhibiting what
social people
call feelings.
No reason for me to go
and freak out over it.
No.
♪
Soon,
my Demon Lord.
The time is upon us,
for your rebirth.
[KREBSKULM]
Are you the fools
who have woken me
from my slumber?
[TAKUMA]
That's the Demon Lord?
[MAN]
This incomplete Demon Lord
must die!
[REM]
Please save me from
this terrible fate.