♪
[BOY 1]
Your guy's so strong!
[TAKUMA] Nah, it's just cause
there's three of us now.
I couldn't defeat
that monster on my own.
I can give you
some of my extra gear
if you want
your warrior stronger.
-[BOY 1] Nuh-uh?
-[TAKUMA] For reals!
We're friends now,
aren't we?
-[BOY 1] Yeah!
-[BOY 2] You bet we are!
[CHILDREN playing]
[TAKUMA panting]
[BOY 1] "We're friends now,
aren't we?"
[laughs]
Man, Takuma's
such a freaky loser.
Be cool to him
so he'll still give us stuff.
[BOY 1]
Well, duh!
Did you see how strong
that equipment is?
[BOY 2] Yeah! Makes it
easy to play with just us!
[BOY 1] In that case,
can't we just ditch Takuma then?
[BOY 2 laughs] No!
He might get better stuff!
[BOTH laugh]
[DIABLO grunts]
[TAKUMA sighs]
What's up with that dream?
[DIABLO grunts]
♪
[TAKUMA] Are they
trying to suffocate me?
Too close!
[gasps]
But then again,
I, I might be into it.
[chuckles]
-[SHERA groans]
-[DIABLO groans]
[sighs]
♪
[REM]
I'm out.
Sylvie and Celes
need to know
what went
down yesterday.
With any luck,
they can help us out
with Psycho-bro Keera.
In the meantime, I'll go
and inform Lord Galford.
[DIABLO]
Good.
[SHERA]
Please be careful out there!
You're the sister
who's causing trouble.
Yes, please keep in mind
you are still being
hunted by adventurers,
which is why
this prince is coming
to hear your decision.
[ALICIA]
Don't give in to him.
Be strong.
[DIABLO]
She's not going to.
And I'm not going to
hand her over to anyone.
Keera said he'd
respect my decision.
So I'll just tell him
I'm staying here.
Then all this'll be over with.
There won't be a war
and we'll get a giant bounty!
'Kay, bye.
Well, see you soon.
-[door shuts]
-[giggles]
-Now, to work.
-Huh?
♪
[SHERA]
Whatcha doin'?
We've managed
to avert a war
for the time being,
but that doesn't mean
we shouldn't do our best
to be prepared.
I'm going to arm us
with recreations
of potions from my world!
Wow! You can make potions?
Well. They certainly
won't make themselves.
And I'm a Demon Lord.
I wouldn't be as strong
if I neglected
basic preparations.
[TAKUMA]
Why do I do this to myself?
These look
nothing like
the herb icons
in Cross Reverie,
and I can't exactly
drag and click on them.
[SHERA]
I love a good DIY!
Can I watch?
[TAKUMA] Yeah, sure.
I love pressure!
[TAKUMA yells]
And boobies!
[SHERA]
What's wrong?
[DIABLO]
Uh, nothing, why?
[TAKUMA] She's about to
spill her double lattes!
It's like eight
pounds of jelly
in a two pound bag!
Screw potions!
I need lotions for motions!
Superb!
Oversized! Orbs!
[SHERA]
Whoa!
[DIABLO]
What? You scared me!
I've never
seen anyone
who could
finish so fast!
[DIABLO grunts]
[TAKUMA]
How the hell?
I watched professionals
brew potions several times
and none of them
compare to how good you are!
[TAKUMA grunts]
I rule.
I made this while
lost in the boob-o-sphere.
If I focus,
I actually
have to do
the task myself.
But if I let
my mind wander,
my body goes
through the motions.
I have to let go
and rely
on my reflexes
to recall
the skills I perfected
as a master Combiner
in the game.
I could blink and those
things would appear.
Are you not going
to make any more?
[DIABLO] What?
Of course I am!
[DIABLO]
Now, pay close attention!
It's important that,
as an adventurer,
you know how to make potions!
Watch only my hands!
This is how
you'll learn!
'Kay! I'm watching!
[TAKUMA]
Yeah, so am I!
[SHERA moans]
[TAKUMA gasps]
Jiggle-jiggle.
I can almost
see the tippy-top
of mount boobalicious.
Keep watching my hands.
[grunts] Being a
Master Combiner is awesome!
You made so many!
[DIABLO grunts]
Of course.
I'm a Demon Lord.
[SHERA]
My mind is blown!
I can't believe that just
happened in front of me!
You can do anything, Diablo!
Oh, wow.
Are you smiling?
[DIABLO] No!
I flexed my lips!
[SHERA]
It's just your face
usually looks like
you're about to choke a kitten
[TAKUMA] Damn it!
Get it together!
But I love whatever
caused it to happen.
It looks
really nice on you.
-Huh?
-See!
There it is again! So cute!
Butt nuts!
[whimpers]
♪
[TAKUMA]
She's right.
I haven't
smiled at anyone
since coming
to this world.
Why would I?
I hope someday
I can be
as confident as Diablo,
without pretending
to be Diablo.
♪
[DIABLO]
I, uh, I was thinking.
I like these moments.
It makes me wish
they could go on for eternity.
[SHERA]
Huh?
[TAKUMA] That did not
just come out of me!
What kind of
wuss-monster
is controlling
this Demon Lord?
[SHERA]
Thank you for sharing
your feelings with me.
Actually,
I was thinking, too.
Diablo, I--
♪
[DIABLO grunts]
[gasps]
He's back.
[grunts]
[DIABLO] Shera?
What's wrong?
Listen, Diablo.
There's something difficult
I've been needing
to tell you lately.
[DIABLO]
Okay?
I realized,
I'm ready
to go back home
to the Kingdom
of Greenwood, now.
[DIABLO grunts]
What? How?
Wait! What brought this on?
[SHERA]
Nothing, really.
It just makes sense.
Things can't
stay this way.
Greenwood is my home.
I should be spending
this time with family,
who love me,
instead of questing aimlessly.
[DIABLO grunts]
Well then, see ya.
[DIABLO]
Uh, what about, uh, Rem?
I mean, don't--
don't you want to
tell her goodbye?
I've kept my brother
waiting long enough.
It's more important
that I go to him at once.
[grunts]
[door shuts]
Shera?
♪
Welcome back,
sweet sister.
I knew in time your heart
would lead you home
where you belong.
[KEERA] We agreed
we would each respect
whichever decision
she made, didn't we?
Now, we best be on our way.
[carriage doors shut]
[HORSES neigh]
[grunts]
♪
[DIABLO]
She's gone?
[whimpers]
[REM]
Hmm?
Is he okay?
[REM]
I can't tell.
Hey, is there
something wrong?
Someone's got
their pouty-pants on.
[DIABLO]
She, uh...
Shera went home
to Greenwood.
[BOTH gasp]
[REM]
She did not! Why?
I don't know.
I'm not done with you!
[REM]
What now?
What are you
planning to do?
[BOTH sigh]
[DIABLO]
Sleep.
-[gasps]
-[door shuts]
♪
[TAKUMA]
Didn't see that coming.
She lied.
I never thought
of her as the type
who would
do something like that.
Just yesterday,
she was
determined not to go.
Did I scare her
by sharing too much?
[DIABLO]
I like these moments.
It makes me wish
they could
go on for eternity.
♪
[whimpers]
[cries]
♪
He's feeling things.
[knocking]
[door opens]
[door shuts]
[footsteps approaching]
[bed creaks]
You know,
it's hard to be
productive
in a fetal pose.
How long are
you planning on
laying around like that?
She's not
smart enough
to be putting on an act.
She cared for us.
That elf couldn't lie
to a deaf and blind dwarf.
Think about it.
She's slower
than anyone,
and doesn't
learn very quickly.
Fooling us would take
a stronger skill set.
I talked to her last night.
She was fine.
She told me all about
this stupid dream
she had for the future.
[REM]
It was highly unrealistic,
but kinda cute, I guess.
Like her.
Anyway, both you and I
were part of her plans,
so it doesn't make sense.
I don't believe
she really wanted
to leave us behind.
Do you think
it's possible
someone's
controlling her?
Like, is she
under some kind of
spell or charm?
I don't think so.
I know she is.
[REM gasps]
When Keera
came back to visit,
he was playing
his flute again.
♪
[TAKUMA] Immediately,
Shera started acting strange.
I'm thinking that flute
has some sort of
brainwashing power.
But, I never saw it
in Cross Reverie,
and I don't have any proof
that it even exists.
♪
[TAKUMA]
I should have known.
This is the way
it's always been.
I told myself
we were friends because...
It was fun and convenient
to believe they liked me, too.
Constant rejection
creates hopeful delusions.
I'm the one
who misunderstood them.
That makes
the most sense.
♪
Something's wrong.
This isn't Shera.
[REM]
Even if her "decision"
wasn't affected by magic.
She's got some major
Elf Brain
happening or whatevs.
[door opens]
This is dumb.
I'm going out to find her.
I'm guessing
you'll be here?
[DIABLO grunts]
[TAKUMA whimpers]
I can't!
If she rejects me again,
I won't be
able to handle it!
I'm tired of
being hurt by jerks
who only wanna mess
with my emotions!
You're the same way, Rem.
Why? Why?
[DIABLO]
Tell me why!
Because I'm her friend,
and so are you.
-[DIABLO grunts]
-[SHERA] I'm happy here with
my new companions,
Diablo and Rem!
Diablo?
Be careful, okay?
What am I,
Chopped Orc liver?
'Cause I belong
to you, too, don't I?
I also wanted to say
thanks for saving me.
Thank you for sharing
your feelings with me.
Actually,
I was thinking, too.
Diablo, I--
♪
[DIABLO]
Just a moment.
-[DIABLO] Please wait.
-[gasps]
[DIABLO] I don't want you to
storm an Elven camp
on your own.
There's no
guaranteeing your safety.
[sighs]
[door opens]
Shera is worth the risk.
I won't
give up on her.
[DIABLO]
Isn't that ironic?
You're willing to
risk your life
for someone
who left you.
An elf who
didn't say goodbye.
Rem Galleu!
You are one of two
who summoned me.
So I ask you this.
Do you desire the power
of this Demon Lord?
Yes!
I want to have your power
more than
anything in this world!
I'd freak if
you gave it to me!
[DIABLO]
Very well!
Then, to fulfill
your fighting objective.
I shall give you
a small glimpse
of my substantial power!
I'd like to go with you, Rem.
[REM]
She gets it.
[ALICIA] I think you're
on to something
regarding
Shera's state of mind.
But you're
an imperial knight.
Won't this
affect your status?
[ALICIA]
My status is not
what I live to defend.
It's people in trouble,
this is my purpose!
Besides...
[giggles]
I don't want to leave Rem
to take this on alone.
There's our imperial knight!
[DIABLO] I told you,
you didn't always have to
find a way to be useful.
Hmm.
You ignored me.
And I have to say,
I am grateful for it.
Thanks!
[DIABLO]
All right!
Let's go get
Shera back from that
flute-blowing elf... tool!
-[ALICIA] Yeah!
-[REM] Good one...
[flute playing]
[whimpers]
-[chains rattle]
-[SHERA whimpers]
I don't know
why you're resisting,
it's pointless.
This flute is
one of the secret arts
given to our kind.
When I saw you yesterday,
I played a tune only Elves
could hear
that was imbued
with a spell
to override your thoughts.
Which means
it's impossible
for you to
defy my commands.
I can make you do
or say whatever I please.
[KEERA] The look
on that Demon's face
when you
walked away from him
was a masterpiece!
He had so much faith
in you, didn't he?
[cries]
So, why don't we
have some fun?
Are you ready to answer
some questions for me
under my command?
[SHERA]
Yes.
You can
ask me anything.
[KEERA]
Tell me what Diablo
made you do for him.
What kind of orders
did he give you?
Orders?
[KEERA] How did he use
the Enslavement Collar?
What did you do
to service him?
Tell me,
so that I can use it
to do even more
satisfying things to you.
There weren't many.
I think he only
used it on me one time.
He ordered me to shake hands
with Rem and smile.
[grunts]
Don't play dumb!
You know that's
not what I mean!
I'm telling you the truth!
That was the only
order he ever gave!
Why the hell not?
[chuckles]
His loss, I guess.
Either way,
you're done with that life.
I'm going to
enjoy teaching you
some delightful new tricks.
Just to show you
who you
belong to from now on.
[explosion]
[BOTH grunt]
There was no need
for that cacophony,
and right in the middle
of family hour.
[sloshing]
What's that stuff?
No need to be afraid.
It's just
a hungry little Slime.
[SHERA]
Please, don't!
I know what that does!
It'll eat me!
[KEERA]
Only if it were carnivorous.
This particular breed only
feeds on fabric.
Huh?
[maniacal laughter]
[SHERA]
But why would you want it
to eat my clothes?
[KEERA]
Isn't that obvious?
I'm preparing to
put an elf baby in you!
[screams]
[SHERA]
It burns!
[SHERA cries]
No!
It feels gross!
Like a bunch of
gigantic slug tongues
all over my body!
[laughs]
You like it behind the knee?
You're such a dirty girl.
[SHERA]
What do you mean?
If I'm dirty,
it's because
this stuff is sticky!
[whimpers]
♪
Make it stop!
-So gross!
-[laughs]
Why would I stop it
when you're
taking to it so well!
[SHERA]
I hate you.
I really hate you
for doing this.
I know you do.
[metal clinks]
But please
stop whining.
I don't want to kill you
before my heir is conceived.
I would rather die
than live through
that kind of sick torture!
[KEERA]
Then let's see how tough
you really are.
[sizzling]
♪
That hurts!
[cries]
[SHERA]
Stop!
[SHERA whimpers]
No!
[screams]
Help me,
please. It burns.
Those cries
are so annoying.
I suppose you
leave me no choice.
I don't want
to force you, Shera.
So I'll have to make you
offer yourself to me.
Help me,
please! Diablo!
[gasps]
Sorry for the wait.
I'm here.
I knew you would be.
Where are your manners?
You should know better than
to barge into a Prince's camp
while he's tending
to important duties.
Keera?
You're a sick elf.
Sorry all
I heard was doodies.
Release her!
Royals still
require consent!
[giggles]
What's wrong with
a little entertainment?
We're keeping things exciting.
It's mutually beneficial.
[DIABLO]
Now I see.
I was wrong
to let her go.
I knew it.
I should have
obeyed my instincts
and kept
Shera from leaving.
Even if it meant
burning down the entire city.
[grunts]
[screams]
[whimpers]
I'm sorry
I was late, Shera.
[SHERA]
Diablo. You're here.
You came for me.
[REM]
Don't worry, Shera!
[ALICIA]
We're here, too!
[groans]
They're just pretending
to be your friends.
[KEERA]
Why didn't my guards
notify me of intruders?
What are they
doing out there?
[DIABLO]
I take it you didn't hear
all the noise outside.
[KEERA screams]
How did this happen?
Where are my guards?
Are they
on a union break?
[ALL coughing]
[grunts]
Prince Keera. Help us.
[KEERA]
Look at this mess you made!
Do you know
what this is?
It's an international issue!
You want a war, don't you?
No, I only came here
for one purpose,
and that is
to find out if Shera
truly wanted to
come back home with you.
I know all about your methods,
and how you manipulated her.
[grunts]
Yeah, right!
And what kind of proof
do you have, huh?
[DIABLO]
The only proof I need
is to ask Shera once more
how she truly feels about
leaving with you.
[KEERA groans]
You're wasting your time!
Shera, tell him
you know in your heart
what must be done!
[whimpers]
I've already told you.
-I have to return to Greenwood.
-Huh?
Greenwood
is where I belong.
My family
needs me there.
This is time I could be
serving my homeland.
This isn't you, Shera!
[KEERA laughs]
Are you satisfied, Demon?
You heard her!
-That means nothing.
-[KEERA] What?
Shera!
As the owner of
your Enslavement Collar,
I command you to
express your true feelings.
Completely unbound
by other
magical influences!
-[REM] You got this!
-[ALICIA] It's working!
Don't listen to him!
I'm the one
that owns you!
Override,
override, override!
-[crackling]
-[SHERA whimpers]
Focus, Shera!
Don't listen to him!
Speak from the heart
that belongs to you!
Your heart, your mind,
and your body belong to me!
[SHERA grunting]
[DIABLO]
Shera. Tell us the truth.
What is it
you really want to do?
[grunts]
[SHERA cries]
I...
I want...
I want to be free.
I don't
want to stay here.
I want to be with Diablo
and Rem forever!
Nothing is more precious
or important to me
than the friends I've made
who are here for me now!
[growls]
[DIABLO]
You deserve to face judgment
for your actions, Keera.
[KEERA grunts]
[grunts] I don't like
this ending, damnit!
You're ruining my fun
and it's pissing me
the hell off!
[KEERA]
Have you forgotten
you're all commoners?
Maybe I should remind you!
[SHERA whimpers]
[SHERA] No, Keera!
Please don't use that!
You're all
sentenced to death!
This secret Elven
summon has the power to
destroy the entire
world with one throw!
If everything I enjoy
is going to be stolen,
then no one
deserves to live!
-As you wish.
-[SHERA and REM gasp]
[DIABLO]
If you dare to challenge me,
then I'll have to accept.
Good.
Come forth,
Force Hydra!
[REM]
What is that?
[ALICIA]
It's huge!
[SHERA]
Run, Diablo!
No one can
beat this Summon!
It's the Elven Nation's
secret weapon!
Oh, it's too late
for regrets, now!
[energy whooshing]
[growling]
Have a nice death, Demon!
[KEERA]
What the hell are you?
[DIABLO] You will pay
for your mistakes,
with your life!
-[SHERA] No!
-[CELSIOR] Keera!
[GALFORD]
It won't be good if you
decide
to spare him.