[SHERA and REM]
You figured out a way
to remove our collars?
[CELES]
Let's not be hasty.
I'm saying
it's a possibility,
but we're not
certain yet.
A slave caravan
just arrived.
They have a market
in the central plaza.
Their collars
have the same
magic level as yours.
With that in mind,
a visit might
be beneficial.
Interesting.
Are you thinking they might
have some advice for us?
If so, I agree,
since they're so
used to handling them.
I'm not so sure
about this, though.
I feel
fulfilling our quest
with the Kingdom
of Greenwood,
right now that should be
our highest priority.
[TAKUMA sighs]
She's right.
but, if there's
a way to remove the collars,
I'd like to get
that done, ASAP.
[sighs]
What do you say?
[DIABLO]
Well.
I don't think it
makes any difference.
Once I reach
the Elven nation,
the issue
will be resolved.
It would not cost us
much time at all.
If the collars
can be removed,
it's worth it.
[giggle]
I'm sorry.
You're juggling
a lot right now, Shera.
I wish I had a more
definite solution for you,
but I hope
this helps.
It does!
I appreciate it!
♪
[CROWD chatter]
I'm so excited
to get this off,
I might
cough up a hairball.
I wonder
if my neck
will feel
breezy without it!
I've just gotten
so used to having it on.
[TAKUMA gulps]
So this is a slave market?
Hmm.
Is something wrong?
Are you okay?
[DIABLO grunts]
Yes.
[TAKUMA] If these places
are anywhere close
to what they're like
in games and manga,
I'm in big trouble.
[echoing]
More master!
[TAKUMA] Yeah,
I don't know about this.
I don't feel like having
my heart explode in my pants.
I need to stay calm.
I can't let this affect
my Demon Lord game.
[groans]
[giggling]
♪
[TAKUMA grunts]
Woah.
Well, this is...
[sighs] Different.
[DIABLO gulps]
[MEDIOS]
Hello, there!
welcome to the these
Beloved Travelers!
It's not every day
I get to service
such a handsome-looking
entourage.
[DIABLO] Are you
the one in charge?
[MEDIOS]
You could say that.
I'm the owner, Medios.
Oh, my!
Your girls are stunning.
I'd gladly
pay a top rate
if you're interested
in selling today?
-[BOTH gasp]
-None of these ladies
are slaves!
Lets not get butt hurt.
The collars
around their necks
threw me off a little.
[gasps]
Well, now.
You're a powerful one,
aren't you?
I know.
[MEDIOS]
I can see it.
It's incredible.
With that
flow of magic,
not a soul would
survive your wrath.
[TAKUMA]
Flow of magic?
What the hell is
she talking about?
[SHERA]
I know, right?
You can tell how big
and powerful it is
from the moment
he walks into the room!
-Huh?
-It's true.
I take it you
have the ability
to see the flow
of magic, as well?
Yep!
Hold on, rewind.
You never discussed
any of that with us!
You never
asked me to?
[ALICIA groans]
[MEDIOS]
I think I understand.
According to this,
it sounds like
you need my help
removing
the collars, yes?
Can you do it?
I don't know yet.
I've never dealt
with a ritual
being reflected like this.
Most who come here
can't wait to put one on.
But since
it was Celes
who sent you my way,
the least
I can do is try.
Yay!
Thank you!
Yeah, what she said!
By the way, Kitty.
Your flow of magic
is also quite intriguing.
Huh?
[whimpers]
[MEDIOS] A strong power
is pent up within,
yet, aggressively
seeping from you.
Sinister.
[MEDIOS] Is it possible
you could be
carrying
a Demon child?
[screams]
[ALL]
What?
Is it true, Rem?
Do you think
you're ready for that?
When did that happen?
"My name's Shera
and I've got jokes!"
It was that night you
and Diablo went upstairs
to "tell secrets,"
wasn't it?
What?
It wasn't me!
All we did was talk,
you Dwarf muncher!
[SHERA]
I'm not stupid!
When you're on the bed
alone with someone,
you get pregnant!
[ALL]
Huh?
Logistics aside,
I'm sensing
Fallen energy within you.
-[gasps]
-Enough about that!
We're here to discuss
how we can
remove the collars!
[MEDIOS]
I'll gladly show you.
But it is
a trade secret.
I'd prefer to share it
with as few as possible,
if that's okay?
No problem,
I'll wait outside.
Me too.
I'll keep
mine for now.
I don't feel
very good.
Yeah that
happens sometimes.
Are you
cramping?
For real.
Could you
see the magic
coming out of me
this whole time?
[SHERA]
Huh? Yeah!
You're practically
drowning in it!
That's how
I knew you must be
a really
strong adventurer!
I see.
Okay.
[sighs]
[groans]
[REM] Your blindness is
my blessing, Shera.
[SHERA] And what's that
supposed to mean?
♪
My secret is...
I have the soul of
the Demon Lord Krebskulm
lurking inside of me.
[REM] I know
it's a lot to process.
My ultimate goal
is to find a way
to defeat her
while she's in me.
It's the only way
I'll be able to
get rid of her.
[TAKUMA]
That was a close one.
If she found out
about Rem's Krebskulm
demon baby,
I woulda mud striped myself.
Hang in there, Rem.
I am going to save you
from that sick
monster someday.
I promise.
Are you honestly
not feeling well, Rem?
I'm fine.
She just annoyed me.
I bet Medios has
that affect on many.
It felt like she was
staring into my heart
and judging
my insecurities.
Kinda scary when
you think about it.
Yeah, right.
Since when do
Imperial Knights
have insecurities?
All the time,
because I'm a knight.
The more you
try to live righteously,
the more you lie
to yourself daily.
[sighs]
Oh, is that
how life works?
[chuckles]
Just our secrets.
[chuckles softly]
Yeah, I know.
I was afraid
my own secret
would be
brought to light.
I know how
that feels.
You have every
right to protect it.
Oh, yeah!
I just remembered
about a charm I know!
It helps keep
secrets hidden
when they're
about to be exposed!
Unless it'd
be too silly
or embarrassing for you?
I've been
living with Shera,
I can handle it.
That's a good point!
Okay,
close your eyes
and then
hold out one hand.
In my hometown,
we would do this,
then this, and say,
"seal and conceal."
And everyone swears
it keeps secrets protected.
[gasps]
Why are you gasping?
[ALICIA]
Uh, no reason.
Uh, just gassy.
I think
I felt something.
It's like my hand
got warmer for a minute.
Did it?
That's fun.
You know,
this is my first time
ever doing it
with a Summoner.
[ALICIA]
So, maybe it works best
when there's some
actual magic involved.
Well, whatever it was,
it helped me
feel better.
[REM]
So, um, thanks Alicia.
Happy to be of service.
Even if I've
done nothing
but make you
smile for a moment.
[BOTH giggle]
[MEDIOS]
Well then,
are we
ready to begin?
♪
I mean,
I guess so, but,
the only thing
I wanted to take off
was the collar.
We're body-positive here.
[TAKUMA]
I'm positive her body
should have
some clothes on it!
Since it's
your first time,
it's best
to make contact
with the skin
while you work.
Are you sure?
[MEDIOS]
Lie down, Shera.
[SHERA]
Uh, okay.
[grunts]
[MEDIOS] I'll start
by teaching Diablo
how to see your
flow of magic power.
Once he learns
how to find it,
he'll be able to control
the strength of your collar
and use it
to release you.
Hmm. Here we go.
First, put your
hand on Shera's skin.
[DIABLO]
'Kay.
[SHERA gasps]
[gasps]
You're not supposed
to make sounds!
[SHERA]
I can't help it!
[MEDIOS] Let me know
when you're done flirting
and we can continue.
[grunts]
What?
[MEDIOS]
Welcome back.
Are you
ready to focus?
It's completely normal
if you can only
sense it at first.
♪
[SHERA gasps]
[TAKUMA]
I can't just touch
someone's skin
on command.
I need to
think of it like,
like, casting a spell.
Okay.
This isn't Shera,
it's a wand!
[chuckles]
A wand!
You're a wand!
You're a wand, damnit!
Be a wand!
[grunts]
[chuckles]
Looks like
you can see it?
[DIABLO]
Uh. Yeah.
[MEDIOS]
Good.
Now observe where her magic
is the most concentrated
and try touching her there.
[grunts]
Okay.
Here it comes.
I'm a little
scared, Diablo.
[DIABLO]
You must trust me!
[TAKUMA]
Once I figure this out,
I'll be able to
release Rem
from her collar, too.
[whimpers] Don't be a--
Don't be an idiot!
handle this!
Hurry up!
[screams]
[TAKUMA]
It's just a wand!
[yelps]
[TAKUMA]
I did it!
[SHERA pants]
Diablo, please stop!
It feels weird!
[TAKUMA grunts]
Is this the flow
of magic power?
[gasps]
[moans]
[TAKUMA]
How far does it go?
I can't see the end!
Please don't.
Don't be so
rough right there!
[TAKUMA]
Amazing!
When I change the way
I'm touching it,
the range I can
see increases!
It seems like you're able
to see most of it now.
Try going lower
to see all of it.
Lower?
[MEDIOS]
Yes, but this time,
you'll pour all of your
own magic into her.
But be gentle.
Very gentle.
As if you're
embracing Shera.
[SHERA whimpers]
Diablo, wait.
Remember, we just ate.
[DIABLO]
Her magic power
is concentrated...
Right here!
[whines] Please, no!
Not like that!
See if you can
affect her magic,
by slowly inserting
yours into her.
[SHERA moans]
[TAKUMA]
Okay, you heard her, MP.
Get in there!
[groans]
[SHERA gasps]
You've broken
past the surface
and started to
reach her core
in such an
impressive amount of time!
[DIABLO]
Hold on!
I'm almost done!
'Kay!
Do it!
[DIABO groans]
[DIABLO yelling]
[SHERA screams]
Yes, Diablo!
Give it to me!
[gasps]
[echoing]
Pour it in!
[shrieks]
[SHERA moans]
[SHERA sighs happily]
Who's hungry?
[BOTH]
What the...
Seriously?
Why would
you quit without
figuring out how to
remove the collars?
It sounded like
you were both
putting a lot
of effort into it.
Yes, we were.
I learned how to
find the flow of
magic power
but it's not easy.
It's, um, actually
pretty complicated.
♪
[DIABLO]
Finding it for these
particular collars is...
Well, it's a lot like yarn.
Countless balls of yarn
in a room tangled together.
I'm supposed
to unravel it all
thread by thread,
but the room
is filled with smoke
and I can hardly see.
And I can only
stay in this room
while holding my breath.
It's very exhausting.
I like yarn.
Doesn't seem like
it affected
you much, though.
It did!
All I did was lie there
like a sack of potatoes.
Diablo poured all his
Demon-Lord power into me,
so I'm actually full
of energy right now!
[groans]
I'm so not trying to
hear that right now.
I feel like I'm already
ready to go to bed.
[TAKUMA] I feel like
I might actually be
on my way to dead.
[groans]
[REM]
Oh, Alicia.
What about you?
Do you have somewhere
to sleep tonight?
[TAKUMA]
There's no way.
Oh, but let's say
there was a way,
it might be the best thing
that ever happened to me!
Of course,
it has to happen
when I'm
about to pass out.
Even if I had
the stamina,
I couldn't do
anything about it!
Yes, I've rented the room
right next
door to yours.
So I'm okay,
but thanks for checking.
Okay, good.
[grunts]
All right, well,
you have
a good night.
[flute playing]
Huh?
♪
[ALICIA]
Is that a flute?
Kinda late
for band practice.
[DIABLO grunts]
I know that sound.
It can't be.
[flute grows louder]
[door creaks]
♪
That's an elf.
But how?
How did you
find me here, Brother?
-Brother?
-Wait, what?
[sighs]
Pleasure to meet you.
As she said,
I'm Shera's older brother
the First Prince of Greenwood.
My name is
Keera L. Greenwood.
♪
I've finally
found you,
my dear Shera.
Are you ready
to come home?
[gasps]
[footsteps approaching]
Huh?
So you're
the idiot prince
who put that
foolish bounty on Shera?
[SHERA]
Diablo?
I was pleased
to hear reports
that the adventurers
seeking the bounty
were captured
and an appropriate
degree of justice
was administered?
Of course they were!
I am not
about to let Shera
be kidnapped
by weaklings!
♪
[KEERA]
I thank you.
For what?
You see, I wanted to
pay gratitude
to whomever
was keeping her
and protecting her.
I'm afraid they
misunderstood my wishes.
Yeah, right!
[KEERA]
I am so relieved
to find you all
alive and well.
We were told
that you were
prepared to wage war
if Princess Shera
was not handed over
within ten days?
Believe me,
I have no desire
for war
with the humans.
My father was
so worried about Shera
that I'm sure his
words came out wrong.
Please accept this
apology on his behalf.
[TAKUMA] Oh, wait.
The quest was to find
a peaceful resolution.
It never said we actually
had to work for it?
So, maybe this counts?
[SHERA]
This makes no sense!
You're not
being yourself,
I don't trust this!
[ALICIA]
Prince Keera,
if what you
say is true,
then we are
happy to hear it.
But we have to wonder
if this isn't just some
new tactic you're trying
after your
forceful measures failed.
I'm so sorry, Shera!
I've been focusing
on our country,
so much that I've
neglected your feelings.
I understand now.
When you left,
I realized the only priority
I should have is you!
Can you find it
in your heart
to forgive
your foolish brother?
What are you saying?
[REM] Look, just stop
while you're ahead, Keebler.
-[KEERA] It's Keera.
-[gasps]
I don't know
if I believe this whole
bounty-gratitude
mix-up you're trying to sell,
but I will say
you were right about
Shera's feelings
mattering most in this case.
Whether she
wants to go home
or whether she
wants to stay with us,
is up to
her to decide.
[SHERA]
Thanks, Rem.
♪
[KEERA]
Very well, then.
Shera's happiness and desires
are my highest
priorities now.
I'll happily take
my leave for today.
[grunts]
It appears that
our sudden reunion
has made Shera
quite emotional.
So, I'll come by
again tomorrow.
I hope that
will allow you
enough time
to examine
what you truly want.
Huh.
And if she
still wishes
not to leave
with you tomorrow?
You wage war?
Oh, Heavens, no!
If that's the case,
then I'll respect
her wishes!
All I want is for
her to be happy.
[TAKUMA]
He's surprisingly decent,
I guess.
[KEERA]
But what will you do?
I mean,
if Shera decides
to come home with me?
[DIABLO]
That's a foolish question.
It's not a possibility.
[SHERA]
Diablo, um...
But I want you to
be able to sleep tonight,
so I'll give you that.
Shera can do
whatever she pleases.
Then we agree.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[footsteps departing]
Thanks, Diablo.
[sighs]
[crickets chirping]
[wind blowing]
[REM] I guess you
can't sleep either?
[gasps]
Sorry.
I didn't know
you were up.
You're gonna get sick
standing in that breeze
in your nighty-nights.
Sorry, I guess I should
close the window.
-[REM] I don't mind it.
-Huh?
So, uh,
you wanna
hang out for a bit?
[REM]
Do you have any idea
what you want
to do tomorrow?
-What?
-You know.
With Keera.
Are you going home
with him tomorrow?
Or not?
I'm not going
back with him.
My mind was made up
from the moment I left.
[giggles softly]
I wasn't expecting him
to be so nice to us.
Was that even real?
[sighs]
I really don't know
his true intentions.
He could be lying
about everything.
You seem like
you're worried.
No, it's not that.
His visit just
made me think about
my homeland in general.
So you're
getting homesick?
[SHERA]
Yes! That's it!
[REM] Calm down!
You're gonna wake Diablo up!
[SHERA]
Oh! Sorry.
[snores]
[TAKUMA] Too late.
He's already up.
Shera, what's your
plan after this?
What do you mean?
You can't
live your life
being hunted
down by Elves.
I would get it
if you said
you didn't want to
keep adventuring
and moving
around all the time.
But...
That's one
of the things
I love about adventuring.
Beyond that,
I'd really like to
open up a café one day.
[REM]
A café?
[SHERA]
Doesn't it sound fun?
Just drinking coffee
and eating snacks.
Maybe petting some cats?
[REM]
That's so random
it hurts
to picture it.
[SHERA]
I've never been,
I've always
wanted to go.
There's a new one that
just opened up in Faltra.
[SHERA] Ooh!
We should visit!
[SHERA] I've thought
about this a lot, Rem!
Once I open the café,
I'll be the owner!
And then maybe you
can be a waitress,
and Diablo
can polish cups
and wear a tie!
[TAKUMA]
What kind of cups?
[REM]
Woah, hold on.
When did we
become a part of
your cats
and coffee dreams?
[SHERA]
Don't you get it?
Once I left the Kingdom,
you and Diablo were
the first friends I made!
[exhales]
Your first
non-elf friends?
That's cool.
[SHERA]
You're part of who I am.
So, wherever you are,
is part of
my new home.
You both have done
so much to help me.
[SHERA] It's not
enough to call you
my friends.
You've been
more of a family
than the rest
of the Greenwoods.
♪
I'm sorry, Shera.
But I can't be part
of your dreams
for the future,
right now.
Huh?
I, um...
I have a problem, and...
Well, I have to
focus on resolving it.
Until then,
I don't exactly
have much of
a future to plan.
[sighs]
It's not just that
it's hard
to find a solution,
it's also so
depressing that sometimes
I think that,
maybe I should just
give up, ya know?
Is there anything
I can do for you?
I don't think so.
[SHERA]
I bet Diablo could help!
[REM]
You're right.
If anyone can,
it would be him.
♪
[REM]
Okay, then.
Huh?
If I can figure
out this mess,
and if you're
still in this
mess of a head space
you're dealing with,
maybe I can be a waitress
at your cat
and coffee café.
[giggles]
[SHERA giggles]
Yay, Rem!
[REM]
Okay, that's enough!
I can't breathe!
[SHERA]
We're gonna be
café friends for life!
[grunts]
Do you know
how much I love you?
[REM]
I have an idea
and it's disturbing!
[moans]
So soft!
Okay, you're
starting to creep me out!
Stop nuzzling my tail!
[SHERA]
I've always wondered
how soft it was!
Let go!
[SHERA giggles]
[REM]
Ugh! Cut it out!
I'm not yanking
your gigantor ears!
-[SHERA moans] Watch this!
-[REM gasps]
I did not
say you could
touch me there!
This is what Diablo
did to me today
when he was
pouring his magic
inside my body!
That's great!
You don't need to
reenact it with me!
[moans]
[SHERA]
I know, right?
That's what it
made me do, too!
[REM grunts]
You're so stupid, Shera!
Stop it!
[TAKUMA grunts]
How the hell am
I supposed to sleep now?
[flute playing]
Shera.
By this time tomorrow.
You'll be all mine.
And we can plan
our future together.
[laughs maniacally]
I can't wait for you
to bear my child!
At last!
[KEERA]
You're mine!
Do you understand me?
Shera!
[REM] Because I'm
her friend, that's why.
[DIABLO]
You have to be honest.
Tell me what you
really want.