[CROWD chatter]
[footsteps approaching]
[BOTH singing] C is ‘cause
they’re super cute.
O is like
their perfect shape.
What song
are you singing?
This is our
new Cookie Song!
[singing]
K is better than cake!
[TAKUMA]
Doesn’t Cake start with a C?
E’s the way
that "cookie" ends.
[SHERA and KREBSKULM]
Let’s all sing it again.
Let’s hear
the folks in the back!
Uh, what?
[KREBSKULM singing] C is ‘cause
they’re super cute!
O is like
their perfect shape!
[singing bleakly]
K is better than cake.
[SHERA and KREBSKULM]
E’s the way that "cookie" ends!
Let’s all sing it again.
[KREBSKULM]
Come on, you know the words!
[SHERA laughing]
♪
[KREBSKULM]
So good!
I can’t get enough
of these in my face!
[KREBSKULM chews]
[sighs happily]
Yum!
[slurps]
This dirty water’s
bitter and disgusting!
Here.
Try some of this.
It’s hot chocolate.
[KREBSKULM]
Interesting.
[KREBSKULM slurps]
I assume you’ve heard
about all this?
Klem is the Demon Lord.
Without a memory.
What do you
make of it?
Hmm.
Of her being
the Demon Lord?
Or obsessing
over cookies?
Just be glad
she’s not trying to
kill the mortal races.
Oh.
[CELES]
I’m only here out of curiosity.
I had to see
this dichotomy for myself.
I think for now,
we just sit back and wait.
See how it plays.
Congratulations,
Rem, on freedom.
Yeah.
Thanks for your help, Celes,
I know how much stress
I’ve caused you.
[CELES chuckles]
[door bell jingles]
[SHERA]
Best snacks ever!
[KREBSKULM]
Let’s come here every day!
Amazing how understanding
Celes was
about everything.
[SHERA]
I’m glad she knows
Klem would never do
anything to hurt us.
Me too.
[DIABLO]
She had to be thorough
in her investigation, though.
Since she’s
the one protecting
the barrier of Faltra,
she’s not allowed
to leave the city.
She didn’t
want anyone else
to suffer that
fate unnecessarily.
[DIABLO]
At least now Rem won’t
have to lose her freedom.
I’m so happy
for you, Rem, Rem?
[SHERA]
They were right behind us
a second ago.
[grunts]
♪
What’s with the alley?
I’m not that kind of cat.
Do Shera and Diablo
know where we are?
♪
[ALICIA]
They don’t.
I’d only
planned to bring Klem.
I figured I’d
bring Shera later
when the time was right.
Then I realized,
it doesn’t really matter.
I’m not as
certain as I thought
about who
might be the key.
Okay?
[door creaks open]
Nobody’s here.
I’ll go look.
You stay here and wait.
They may still come back.
Right.
♪
[TAKUMA]
My chest is pounding.
I wonder what that means.
Do you have any idea
what could possibly
be causing the loss
of your memories?
[KREBSKULM] If I did,
I probably forgot.
[ALICIA] It’s just that
one of the Fallen priests
said it takes more
than just magic power
to completely
resurrect a Demon Lord.
A Fallen?
[ALICIA]
I want to find out
how to restore
your memories,
so that we might awaken the
Demon Lord and her bloodlust.
[REM]
Okay, time out!
I thought I just
heard you say
you wanted the Demon Lord
to fully resurrect
so that she can kill
all of the mortal races?
Your hearing appears
to be in good shape.
You are correct.
[REM gasps]
What the hell is
wrong with you?
[ALICIA]
Nothing.
I’m the same
as I’ve always been.
Except.
I don’t need to pretend
we’re all friends anymore,
thank goodness.
That got old
really quickly.
[KREBSKULM]
If anyone needs to wake up,
it’s you,
Lady Knight!
I couldn’t be
more perfectly
and completely
resurrected if I tried.
Yet, you’re refusing
to kill the mortal races?
That’s enough!
You want me to burn you?
-[ALICIA] Yes!
-[KREBSKULM whimpers]
If that’s what it takes
to awaken my lord, please do!
What an absolute blessing
that would be.
If I could become
the first mortal
who was burned to death,
I would help make
this world beautiful
by dying along with
the rest of the races!
What the crap?
[REM]
So the woman Galluk
was screaming
about that one time?
[GALLUK] I should’ve
listened to that woman
when I had the chance!
Who do you mean?
Yes, that was me.
I was doing my best
to lead him.
I even handed him
Gregore disguised
as his sword.
[scoffs]
[ALICIA]
He was a handful, wasn’t he?
Pathetic, dramatic,
and teeming with envy
and hatred,
just like the rest
of those hideous mortals.
[SADDLER]
We finally found you.
I’ve been
searching for you
for quite some
time, Lady Cristela.
You again?
I apologize, Sir.
As you see,
I’ve been a little tied up,
trying to reform
these Demon Lord Worshipers.
[scoffs]
You said you
wanted her to burn you!
Oh, no!
She’s trying to
control my mind again.
I went undercover
to expose them
as Demon Lord worshipers,
and it worked!
At least
I saved this child
they kidnapped
from her family!
So that’s the yarn
you’re spinning now?
This news comes
as no surprise to us.
I’ve suspected
that your souls
were dark all along.
What’s the deal?
I thought
you were a rock?
[SADDLER]
Oh, that.
I’ve never known
such a disgrace.
To think that anyone
would do something
so insolent to me,
one with power
granted by the Gods.
Make no mistake,
he will be punished
for that in due time.
Come forth, Asulau!
[yelps]
[ALICIA scoffs]
[growls]
Go on!
Hurry it up.
Break through them!
Form a shield, men!
[gasps]
[men scream]
What the hell
kind of idiots
would do that?
Are they trying
to get killed?
Our lives in this world
are only worth
as much as the Gods
have need for us.
Death is
a great opportunity.
It simply means we’ve
been invited into Heaven.
[grunts]
[blood splashes]
[SADDLER]
Most importantly, protecting me
is the equivalent
to protecting a God.
[ASULAU'S body thuds]
[SADDLER]
Cowards who refuse to obey
my orders out of fear
for their own lives,
could never
become squires.
♪
[gasps]
[yells]
[grunts]
Now the power
of the Gods compels you!
Bow down before us,
Demon Lord Worshiper!
[REM gagging]
Hey! Stop that!
[gagging]
The only thing she needs
is to feel true hatred.
[CROWD chatter]
[panting]
[TAKUMA]
Damn it!
Can’t help but think
something’s screwy!
Better not be some
instinctual warning about
anything.
[grunts]
[echoing]
Hey! Hey. Hey!
Are you awake?
[exhales softly]
[gasps]
What’s going on?
Are you all right?
Where are we?
I can’t tell you
how hard it is
to look at your
face after you lost
such a lame battle.
Here.
Eat this, it’ll help.
Thanks, I’m starving.
I love these.
[KREBSKULM]
Is it true you’ve been sad
for a long time
because of me?
[gasps]
Alicia was talking about it.
[KREBSKULM] She said
your life’s basically sucked
and it’s my fault.
And that your mother,
and her mother,
and her mother’s mother
were also suffering.
[REM]
Well...
[KREBSKULM]
But you still tried to save me.
And you did
the same thing
with Eulerex, too.
I gotta say,
if there was an award
for loyalty,
it would be all yours,
Rem-gnat!
[REM]
It wasn’t out of loyalty.
[gasps softly]
I don’t understand it, either.
I, uh...
I’ve spent
my whole life hating you.
At least, what I thought
was the Demon Lord,
Krebskulm.
I gave up on my dreams,
and I pushed people away.
I lived my entire life
in fear and isolation.
What the hell’s wrong with me?
[REM]
I mean, my enemy is sitting
right in front of my face,
but I can’t bring myself
to wish you were gone.
I’m sorry, Rem.
I forced you to
live your life as a prisoner.
[gasps]
[KREBSKULM]
You should allow yourself
to hate me,
it’s only natural.
Life without
freedom is not life.
[REM] You would know
after being trapped
for the same amount
of time my family was.
For several generations.
That’s a long time
to be alone in the dark.
Nah, it felt more like
a really long nap.
[REM]
Was becoming a Demon Lord
the only reason you were
imprisoned within us?
[KREBSKULM]
Yeah, but it’s how I was born.
Not what I chose.
I understand.
I think you and I
are a lot alike in that way.
[KREBSKULM]
We are?
Yes and that’s why
we need to stick together.
I’m not gonna let
Alicia have her way.
Yeah! Neither am I!
I’m fine just like I am!
Look at me
and tell me I’m not perfect,
am I right?
[chuckles softly]
Let’s get back before
the others freak out.
I don’t think you know
how ridiculously quick
we’d be out of here
if I was allowed
to use my powers.
Those mean canned soldiers
would be ash right now.
Just saying.
[REM]
I get it, but hold back.
I’m kinda into the Klem
that makes up
food songs with Shera,
laughs at anything,
and obsesses over cookies.
[REM]
Don’t ever lose that.
Don’t let your
heart become numb
to killing mortal races.
Promise me you’ll stay true
to who you are now.
Wow, that’s
a lot to take in.
But I promise you, Rem!
[chuckles softly]
[horse neighs]
Good news,
we’re finally here.
You’ll soon be saved
from your demonic desires.
♪
[door creaks open]
-[shudders]
-[PALADIN 1] Move.
[footsteps approaching]
♪
[gasps]
Seriously?
I’m no Demon Lord worshiper!
And I’m not gonna lie
and say that I am
even if you torture me!
[SADDLER]
I appreciate that.
Usually anyone who’s heard
the rumors about me
starts spewing
shallow
vows of repentance
the second
they see my tools.
Of course.
I can always see
right through their charade.
You don’t fool me.
I know the signs of a true
Demon Lord worshiper,
and you’re trying to
deceive the holy ones.
You don’t care
what I have to say,
you just wanna torture me.
I’m offering you
your salvation.
All I want is to cleanse
your tainted soul
and release you into Heaven.
Don’t you want to be free?
Gimme a break. Like you’re
a god now or something?
[SADDLER]
Not "or something."
That’s exactly what I am.
A living god who
just wants to save you.
[SADDLER] I was born
into a blessed family,
granted a blessed body,
and I boast
a blessed intellect.
What other explanation
could there possibly be
than that I am a God
who has descended
from Heaven
to save the world?
[grunts]
Why don’t you save the world
from your ass-face?
[SADDLER]
Those ears of yours.
They’re made from evil.
[gasps]
[SADDLER] That tail
isn’t very pure either.
And those hands
were used to
cast a wicked
Summon at me.
You’re judging me now?
Go to hell!
Seems your
mouth is evil too.
Perhaps we should
extract your tongue.
[REM]
Alicia!
Are you really
just going to
stand there
like a scared goat
and let them
threaten me this way?
What kind of
two-faced monster are you?
I have my own
missions to accomplish.
But if you don’t like pain,
perhaps you should ask
your friend for help?
[gasps]
Rem, you know
I can stop them now
if you need me to.
I don’t need it, Klem.
Do you understand?
Please keep your promise!
I... I will.
[REM]
This “mission” you have
is to resurrect
the Demon Lord, isn’t it?
You want her to wipe
out the mortal races!
The Demon Lord Worshiper
is trying to poison my mind
with her intentions.
You made me like you,
you tin-nipped botch!
And you went with us
to rescue Shera!
[REM] You’re saying
that meant nothing?
[ALICIA]
Lord Saddler,
may I leave this
in your hands?
Yes. It would be my honor.
[REM]
Oh, hell no. Alicia!
[doors shut]
[REM whimpering]
Now, then.
Shall we get things started?
[footsteps approaching]
[panting]
-[sighs] Damn it!
-[BAR CROWD chatter]
I’ve looked
everywhere for them.
I need a guide or something.
Any kind of clue.
[DWARF 1] You want
a piece of me now, punk?
[DWARF 2] Had a piece
of your mom last night,
smell my breath!
[DWARF 1]
You think that’s funny...
[DIABLO grunts]
That’s right!
After that,
I was surrounded
by hundreds of scoundrels
and took them out one by one!
-[door opens forcibly]
-Huh?
[pants]
There she is.
What’s with this
scorned look, my friend?
You two!
[grunts]
[EMILE]
Hmm?
[TAKUMA]
No, wait.
How does a Demon Lord
ask for a favor?
All I’ve ever done
is order people around.
And even without social skills
I know that’s not
a productive way
to ask for stuff.
If I were them
and I came at me like this,
I’d tell me to eff off.
So how do I
tone it down, though?
[DIABLO]
You see...
[stammers]
Rem and, uh, Klem are...
[blows raspberry]
[DIABLO]
Uh, uh...
[EMILE]
Huh?
[TAKUMA stammers]
French Roast!
Why can’t I just,
just talk without
snarling through everything?
Use your words.
[EMILE]
Where’s our confidence
hiding tonight, hmm?
[gasps]
[BOY 1]
Guildmaster!
Serious junk
is going down!
My friend said
he just saw a Paladin
carrying Rem somewhere!
-Huh?
-The fair maiden!
Do you know
if it’s just Rem?
-Huh?
-Anyone else with her?
[BOY 1] He said there was
some little girl with her.
[BOY 1]
They went in the church
in the North District!
[grunts]
Thank you!
Huh?
Did I just hear him
say thank you?
No, you heard him
scream thank you.
[BOTH chuckle]
[EMILE]
Well, I can’t just sit here!
Rem is in distress
and needs a rescue!
[SYLVIE]
Go get her!
[DIABLO]
I have to make it in time!
♪
[GALFORD]
What?
They’re all Fallen, you say?
Send message
to Lady Baudelaire at once!
Tell her to secure
the barrier quickly!
[SOLDIER 1]
Yes, sir!
And what, pray tell,
is happening here?
[rumbling]
♪
Stay away.
They must not enter Faltra.
This barrier
shall remain protected.
[SADDLER]
Feel free to scream
as much as you’d like.
No one will hear you,
but it might be
fun, nonetheless.
Be fun to see me in pain?
Did you sell your conscience
on the dwarf market?
Of course not.
It hurts to see
Demon Lord worshipers,
who need salvation.
[whimpers]
-[PALADIN 1] Hold still!
-[cries]
That’s it!
-[REM] No!
-[gasps]
You promised me, remember?
-Stay back!
-[KREBSKULM] But, why?
[pained whimpers]
♪
Hmm.
[chuckles]
And that’s why
he told you to sit still!
[grunts]
[gasps]
Rem, no!
[KREBSKULM]
Why do you want me
to let them hurt you?
Let me kill them!
Just say it’s okay!
[REM groans]
Don't.
I don’t want you to die!
[KREBSKULM grunts]
[SADDLER chuckles]
If you dare to interfere,
I’ll show you no mercy,
even if you are a child.
[scoffs]
♪
[growls softly]
[BOTH grunt]
[grunts]
[PALADIN 2 gasps]
She’s a Fallen!
Take one step toward her,
I’ll turn you to ash.
[SADDLER scoffs]
Damn Fallen.
Pretending to be
a human child.
How repulsive!
You’ll all pay for what
you’ve done to Rem.
It’ll cost each one of you
your pathetic lives!
[SADDLER]
Shut your fallen brat mouth.
[straining grunts]
[REM gasps]
[KREBSKULM]
Rem! Rem?
Oh, Rem! Hey!
Talk to me, please!
Go. Run away.
I won’t!
Not without you!
I’m gonna kill these men
and take you with me!
-[REM] You promised me.
-[gasps]
Yeah but, that was before.
[whimpers]
♪
Another damn demihuman.
You’re in the way!
[SADDLER grunting]
♪
[KREBSKULM whimpers]
[KREBSKULM gasping]
[screams]
What the hell?
[KREBSKULM screaming]
[REM]
That’s it.
That’s what she meant.
The only thing she needs
is to feel true hatred.
[REM]
It’s because of me.
[screaming]
[REM]
I’m so sorry, Klem.
[roaring]
♪
[ALICIA]
Finally, the true resurrection.
All the horrible mortal races
will soon be gone!
But how?
-That’s impossible!
-[growling]
[SADDLER]
The Demon Lord has resurrected?
[roars]
[SADDLER]
I am not afraid of you!
I’ll destroy you using
all the powers of the gods
that I command!
You cannot harm me,
for I am
a living god myself!
Kneel before me, Demon,
and let me see you suffer!
[grunts]
[SADDLER]
My-- my eyes!
[PALADIN 1]
Lord Saddler?
[pained groans]
No. No way. It can’t be!
[SADDLER]
Does this mean
I’m not really a god?
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[grunts]
[DIABLO]
Am I too late?
♪
[DIABLO grunts]
It’s you!
[SHERA]
Diablo!
[SHERA panting]
Shera?
What are you doing here?
I used Turkey Shot
to look for everyone,
and I saw Rem!
She’s there.
She’s hurt!
[DIABLO]
What do you mean she’s hurt?
Where’s Alicia?
[SHERA]
I don’t know!
[DIABLO]
I see.
Take these.
I’m going to hold Klem back.
It’s going to be up
to you to save Rem.
All right.
Please don’t get hurt,
and please,
please say you’ll save Klem!
[DIABLO]
Shera, do you know who I am?
I am the true Demon Lord
who was summoned
from another world!
You have nothing
to worry about!
If anyone can handle this,
it’s me!
[SHERA]
You can’t die Rem!
Not here!
Please!
[DIABLO] This attack
should wake you up, Klem!
[REM]
Let’s go home, Klem.