[clap of thunder]
[instrumental music playing]
[female narrator] Light is born from darkness.
Darkness finds it way north to become water,
while light sails south to give birth to fire.
Wind ebbs and flows between the light and the dark.
Light slips inside the darkness where it returns to earth.
Now is the time for you to show us your true nature.
Which path, light or darkness, will you choose?
[instrumental music continues]
[male narrator] All are rooted in their one true-shared trait.
And it is from that trait that they are each created.
That trait determines and influences how the Digimon
will transition into their next form.
The question is... what happens to those who were not chosen?
My Mei...
[grunts]
[surge of electricity]
[wind howling]
[sinister laughter]
[roars]
Huh.
Are you somewhere crying, my little Mei?
[voice trembling] I wish I could help you.
[train bells ringing]
Hey. You guys aren't supposed to be here.
Yeah. He's right. You guys are human, aren't you?
I can tell by your furry heads.
Whatever they are, I don't like the looks of them.
I don't know.
They don't really look all that dangerous to me.
Hey, you know, maybe that's how they act before they eat you.
Come to think of it, we don't know what humans eat.
Plus, they're so skinny, they must be starving.
Just settle down, please.
We can't understand you when you're all talking at once.
[Koromon] We are settled down!
[chuckles] You have not changed, little dude.
Huh? [grunts]
-[squeals] -Come, little Tanemon.
[laughing]
I don't want to be eaten! [screams]
Now, you stop that.
Partners don't eat each other, ever, 'kay?
What's that word mean?
-[Mimi] What word? -Partner.
[gasps] I get it.
You really don't remember me, do you?
[Tsunomon] Why are you staring at me like that?
Are you thinking that I look delicious? Is that it?
Not at all.
[Tsunomon] You're still staring.
[chuckles then gasps]
[Kari] Well, look who it is.
[Tsunomon] Yipes! She's spotted you
and now she's coming for you! Run for your life! [screams]
You didn't run off. That's brave. Thank you.
I'm Kari. You want to be friends?
I promise you can trust me, and I won't hurt you.
Hmm. [sniffing]
You smell kinda like my whistle! Mm. It's familiar somehow.
[chuckles]
Yokomon! Yokomon, where are you?
-[Yokomon] Ow! You big klutz! -Huh? [gasps]
Why don't you watch where you're going?
Sorry! Sorry! Oh, are you okay?
What do you think you're doing? Put me down!
Help! I'm getting diginapped!
[gasps] Diginapped?
[grunts] I'd never do anything to hurt you, not ever.
-Really? -Yes.
[Yokomon grumbles]
I just can't believe you don't remember me.
You and I are partners.
[Yokomon] Stop following me around!
Wait! What about all the time we spent together?
I know everything about you.
You and I have always been a great team.
I know you hate asparagus.
-[Yokomon] What's asparagus? -[Sora gasps]
[Yokomon] There's no way we were ever friends.
Yokomon...
[Izzy] I keep replying to Miss Himekawa but it won't send.
No internet and I think the gates vanished too.
Seems like the whole digital world's either offline
or got corrupted after the reboot.
-What's a reboot? -Can you eat it?
Hey, you know a lot of stuff and a lot of the grids.
Where do you keep 'em all? You have an extra brain?
I wish I had an extra brain. A reboot's for a computer.
Kind of a fresh start,
when things aren't working right.
-Can a computer make food? -[grunts]
Hey, who are you?
[TK] Your eyes are completely clear.
Not a trace of infection.
-I don't feel sick. -Nope, and you're not.
Here's the deal, Tokomon.
What do you say we become best friends for life?
-For reals? -Yep.
Absolutely for reals.
Hmm.
-Okey-dokey. -[chuckles]
So, what?
So, what are we doing?
Hmm.
Obviously, we have to find a way home
or else wait for Himekawa to rescue us, but either way,
the first thing we have to do is find food and shelter here.
And unfortunately, these guys haven't digivolved
enough yet to help us.
[Mimi] We're doomed, finished, has-beens!
[Sora] Huh? Why would you say that, Mimi?
[sobbing] Just messing with you!
I know we'll get back home just like we did last time!
Yep! Just think positive! Right?
Be chill just like you, right, Tannie?
-Yeah! [screams] -Okay.
So you forgot how to chill. That's fine.
We'll just go back to the start,
and I'll teach you again like I taught you before.
Lucky.
But right now, none of that matters.
What's important is that we're all together again.
[screams] Don't eat me!
That's enough of that nonsense.
I already told you I'm not going to eat you.
None of us is going to eat any of you.
Look, we knew this would probably happen,
that you Digimon might forget about us after the reboot.
But I believe all of you are going to remember us eventually.
We'll just have to work at it, that's all.
Like partners. Because that's what we are.
And if you've really lost all those memories,
we'll just have to make new ones.
Together.
[sighs]
[Mimi chuckling] You are such a cutie.
[TK] Poor Tanemon. [chuckles]
[Matt] Mimi does not give up.
[Mimi] I'm coming in for a snuggle!
-[rustling sounds] -[both] Huh?
[all gasp]
[Tai] All right, whoever you are.
Show yourself!
[sobbing]
Meicoomon?
Huh?
[Mimi] You guys know this Digimon?
No way! And she's still at her champion level!
Mei? Where's Mei?
[all gasp]
Whoa.
So, you remember her? Your Meiko?
Mei! [sobs]
[sobbing continues]
[all gasp]
[Matt] Tai, wait up!
[Meicoomon grunting]
[Tai] Meicoomon! Stop! We only want to help!
[grunts] No.
[surge of electricity]
The access point to the distortion port.
But why here?
[approaching footsteps]
[panting and grunting]
[sighs] Still no messages. Not good.
[grunts]
[Koromon] Look at all the goodies!
I've never seen so much food!
[all] Ah, wow!
Can we start? My mouth is watering?
-My whole body is watering. -It looks so good!
[chuckles] Well, I guess they like the food.
Sora, did you bring all this stuff with you?
Sure.
We were going to have to eat, so I just planned ahead.
Planned ahead? You're a star!
Without you, we would have been forced to eat bugs.
Well, that's a little dramatic. Now, pass out those plates.
[all giggling]
[Sora] Come on, everybody! Eat up!
[Izzy] Where were you keeping all this stuff?
[gulping] Ah, I thought I'd tried everything,
but this is the best drink ever.
Uh, glad you like it.
Uh, what was that name you called it?
It's tea. Tea is made from leaves,
and there are lots of different kinds you can choose from.
My absolute favorite is umon tea,
but there's peppermint tea, white tea,
spearmint tea, mulberry tea, herbal tea,
yellow tea, mint tea, ginger tea,
lemon tea, lemon grass tea, peppermint tea...
Oh yeah, and you can even get pumpkin tea. [laughs]
[Motimon] I think you made your point.
Oh, I'm just getting started. Then you have all your--
Sounds like there's a lot of tea in your world.
Maybe too much.
Plus, tea is not only delicious...
-We got it! -...but good for your health.
What else you got that I can eat?
Well, I do have this sandwich, but I was kind of saving it.
-Oh well. -Aww!
I hate to eat your lunch, but if you insist. [munches]
Hey, and you know, even scientists say--
Now I'm lost. What are scientists?
Do they have big brains and talk as much as you do?
Sorry. Got carried away.
Anyway, I wanted to ask you some questions about this world.
[Mimi] All right. Intermission time, Professor.
Sora made all this food. Now it's time to eat it.
Open up. Ah.
[winces]
Whoa! Would you actually refuse my special treat?
Uh, just when I can't identify it and... what are those things?
They look like jelly beans.
[Mimi] Jelly beans and whipped cream
on top of Sora's cucumber bacon roll.
I just invented it.
I know you love jelly beans, and I made enough for everyone.
[Izzy] Wow, Mimi. What an unusual topping.
[Mimi] All right, gang. Open up. Ah.
See? Sora isn't the only one who can make delicious treats.
Who wants seconds?
[nervous laughter]
They don't remember anything.
I guess the reboot deleted us entirely.
There has to be some way to restore their memories.
Well, we were warned this would probably happen.
But why didn't it happen to all of them?
Meicooman remembers.
Really? She ran from us.
Shouldn't we try to find her?
[Tai] Meicoomon.
I remember her too...
and everything she did.
What if we get her back and then find out she can't be saved?
Meicoomon and Meiko are part of us now.
We're not turning our backs on them!
I know that, but I'm still worried.
[Joe] Hmm.
Tai! Tai! It's the most amazing thing ever! [munches]
These slippery tube things make my mouth so happy!
-Say it, don't spray it! -But it's the best food ever!
I just... had to tell you.
I think I'm in love with this stuff!
You're in love all right,
with whatever food you happen to be eating at the time.
Mm. Yeah, you might be right about that.
You love hotdogs, curly fries and cheeseburgers,
pancakes and bacon.
For that matter, I can't think of a food you don't like.
-For reals? -Mm-hm.
I've never heard of any of those, but I'll try 'em!
[laughing] All right.
Now, I guess I know you better than you know yourself.
And here's something else you like. [chuckles]
Whoa! [laughing]
Hey, that looks super fun!
I want to do that too! Me next! Me next!
I want to go, too.
[Nyaromon] Kari, can you pick me up?
-Huh? -Come on. I want to fly.
-Of course. Come here. -Oh, yay.
[Kari chuckles]
[munching and grumbling]
So, do you like the meatballs?
Nah.
Oh, well how about these other things, then? Here.
I don't want anything else.
Oh, uh, my... my bad.
I'm sorry.
[phone ringing]
[Himekawa's answering machine] You've reached Agent Himekawa.
I'm sorry I'm not able to take your call.
Please leave a detailed message after the tone
-and I'll get back to you. -[machine beeps]
[Nishijima] It's Nishijima. I can't find Meiko.
She hasn't been home in several days.
If she contacts you, give me a call right away.
[train bells ringing]
[electrical crackling]
[Digimon snoring]
Anybody heard from Miss Himekawa?
[TK] Nope. Nothing.
And we won't. Without a signal, I can't contact Jenna either.
There's something really strange about this whole place.
Ugh! You guys are such downers. We'll figure it out.
Well, what's our next move then?
[Tai] We need to find Meicooman.
Yeah, we do.
Like you said before, they're part of our team.
We can't give up hope.
-Meicoomon and Meiko need us. -[chuckles]
[Tai] We have to reunite them.
Hmm. We don't know if Meicooman's still infected
or what the distortions did to her.
The reboot should have cured the infection,
but there's still a chance it didn't.
We may have to reboot again. [sighs]
Are you seriously saying
that we just went through all this for nothing?
That the stupid reboot didn't even work?
[Izzy] I hope not.
[Sora] We need a little more than hope right now!
Well, come on! Let's spread out and find Meicooman.
Then we can worry about all the rest of that stuff.
Yeah. Let's focus on one thing at a time.
I don't know how, but we'll find a way out of this jam.
And we're gonna do it together.
[Mimi] Woo-hoo! That's what I'm talking about!
Let's get this show on the road, digi-dustballs!
Uh, let's formulate a plan first, at least.
No sense going off in different directions all discombobulated.
A well-planned search is a successful search.
Now that sounds just like the Joe I grew up with.
I like to think I've matured a little bit since then.
-And even got a girlfriend. -[others giggle]
-She's not made up! -[all laughing]
Okay. Time to head out, gang.
Hey, on your feet little g--
-Huh? -[all gasp]
What's wrong? [screams] No way!
Hi. Hello.
[all gasp]
[Joe] Did they eat their way to a digiball?
[Tai] What, like too many jelly beans?
That or we're hallucinating.
[laughs] Look at me. I can fly!
[Tentomon] Yeah, me too!
-Go Tentomon! -Patamon!
[laughs]
This is way more fun than being stuck on the ground!
[both laugh]
[giggles] Wow! I'm pretty, aren't I?
Oh, you sure are. You are super pretty, Palmon.
Ha. Just like you.
-Look, I'm back! -[Kari laughing]
[Gabumon] Hmm? Well, say something, Mr. Matt.
Why are you staring at me like that?
I don't have whipped cream all over my face, do I?
Check him out. Bukamon leveled up, Tai.
How did we do that, Agumon?
We ate a ton of food until we were stuffed,
and then we took a nice long nap.
[laughs] That sounds about right.
Come to think of it, I'm getting a little hungry again.
Let's eat more and get even bigger.
-Yeah! -[TK laughs]
Well, even though the reboot deleted their memories,
looks like things are getting back to normal.
[Sora] There you are.
-I was looking for you. -Hmm?
How does it feel to be leveled up?
Why do you keep bothering me? I told you, I don't know you!
Go play with your human friends and forget you ever knew me!
But I can't. [sobs]
[train bells ringing distantly]
[Meicoomon sobbing]
Mei, why did you abandon me here?
I'm all alone and it's so scary in this place.
I don't know what to do.
I don't-- I don't know-- what's happening to me?
[growl]
[electrical crackling]
[Kari] Tai's been gone for a while.
Should we go look for him?
-[Izzy] No. Let's stay put. -[Digimon snoring]
I'm sure he's moving around trying to get a signal.
If we split up now, odds are, somebody'll get lost out there.
[Kari] Hmm?
Come here.
Hmm?
There he is. Hey, Tai.
[Joe] Took you long enough.
We're glad you're back. Have any luck?
[Tai] No bars, no signal. No nothing.
So, for now that means we're on our own.
Let's just concentrate on trying to find Meicooman.
Before, whenever there was a distortion,
it turned out Meicooman was at the center of it.
So if I can figure out a way to track the distortions
in this world, we may be able to zero in on her.
I wish there was something I could do to help you out.
[Izzy] I can do this.
[Tai] Of course. Just what are you looking for?
Hmm...
-[Izzy] An anomaly in the code. -That anomaly better run.
[Mimi] Mei-Mei, still in the DigiWorld.
Will bring Meicooman back. Send!
Sending, sending, sending...
-[failure to send alert] -[Mimi] Ugh, so infuriating!
Come on! Why won't it send?
[sighs] I guess I should have tried a little harder
to get Meiko to come with us.
Maybe. But the way things are going so far,
I think it's probably a good thing she didn't.
This could have really freaked her out.
Yeah, maybe.
[Mimi] What are you talking about? That's not fair!
Meiko's just as brave and tough as any one of us
and you know it!
[TK stammering] No. It's not that-- I didn't say--
What I meant was just--
You know, we've all been in the DigiWorld before.
You know Meiko. She's so sweet and sensitive.
Ooh.
-What does that mean? -It's obvious.
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid my heart belongs to...
-Matt. -Ah, give me a break.
Then it's true. No girls allowed.
Stop that! It's not my fault he doesn't have a girlfriend!
[girls giggling]
I'm gonna... get some more wood.
[Mimi] Great idea. I love a big fire!
[all snoring]
[Digimon snoring and muttering]
-[rustling noise] -Hmm?
[Tai] Are you going to tell us what's wrong?
[Sora] What difference would it make?
-[Tai] Well, maybe we can help. -[Matt] Yeah, exactly.
[Tai] I mean, if there's something wrong,
we should talk it out.
-Tai? -Uh, sure.
Uh, that food! That food you made was great.
[Matt groans]
Oh.
I guess this is a Sora subject then? [chuckles]
-[groans] -Go away.
[Tai] Okay. Let's try this again.
[Matt] And no bad jokes this time.
[Tai] We are not leaving here until you tell us
how we can help you.
[Tai and Matt] Huh?
-[Sora] Thanks, guys. -[Tai] Hey, Agumon!
[panting]
This is no time for rafting, pal!
What? Wait.
How'd I get here? I was having this great dream.
-I was eating fish. -Huh?
And chips.
You are just a nonstop eating machine.
Yeah.
[Tai and Agumon laughing]
[Sora] Well, at least somebody's happy.
Come on. Sora?
[Tai] I'll be right behind you.
Listen, don't move. I gotta go do damage control.
-[yawns] -[Tai] Sora! Stop already!
I'm sorry, but I couldn't let the little guy drown!
[grunting and panting]
There has to be something I'm overlooking, some clue.
[Nishijima] What else do you know?
[man] That's all the information I've got.
She's missing? She wouldn't just leave and not tell me.
[keys clicking]
[Nishijima] I'm going to find you, Hime.
I need to know what you were up to before this happened.
That's it!
Please let the old password work.
Fingers crossed.
Yes!
Now what? Should we compliment her on her meatballs?
It has nothing to do with her meatballs!
How can you be so stupid!
Well, Mr. Emotional, why don't you go talk to her
and make her feel better?
This is a job for TK.
[Sora] I can hear you, you boneheads.
[both sigh]
Can you at least tell us why you're upset?
I shouldn't have to.
If you cared about me at all, you'd know already.
-Maybe you could give us a hint. -I can't put it into words.
[both] We need TK.
I knew neither of you would understand! [sobs]
-[both gasp] -Sora, wait up!
[Sora] You're supposed to be our leader, Tai,
but you don't know a thing about us!
And you're just as bad, Matt.
Always moping around, angry at the world!
The only thing you guys are good at is fighting,
especially with each other!
But I guess that's just how it is.
Let Sora take care of everybody. She'll be fine.
Don't worry about her. Well, I have feelings, too.
Your feelings have been a mystery to me
since we were kids.
You never needed anybody's help,
and you were always ready to give out advice.
You had all the answers.
But then, the truth is, I always thought
that was one of the best things about you.
-But what about you? -Huh?
You need to take care of yourself too. Don't you?
Myself?
-Hmm. -Not an option?
Well, selflessness is one of your best traits. [chuckles]
All right. Since you're my favorite person,
I'll take care of you. Sound good?
[laughing]
[sobbing]
Please don't remind me of Biyomon. Not now.
Sora.
-[rustling noise] -Huh?
-[Tai] Something's coming. -[roars]
-[Sora] Meicooman. -[both gasp]
[explosion]
[all grunting]
[loud rumbling]
[gasps]
[roaring]
It's Machinedramon.
-[Tai] Look out! -[Sora screams]
-[all panting] -That was close.
[growling]
Hey, Matt, you go after Meicooman.
[Machinedramon growling]
[Tentamon] Is that another one of your friends, Izzy?
I'm not sure I like this one.
That's a friend? I hope he's not hungry.
I think we're safe here, you guys,
as long as he doesn't turn this way and see us.
[growling]
[roaring]
[all exclaiming]
Everybody, take cover!
But wait! Where are Matt and Tai?
Go! I'll get them. I know where they went.
We don't have time to go running around.
We have to find a hole to hide in before that thing gets us.
I'm scared. Everything's bad since you humans came.
Everybody, just relax! Panicking now won't help at all!
-Try to stay-- -[Meicooman screams]
[Joe] Huh? Is that who I think it is?
Meicooman!
Mei! Mei!
-I see them. They're safe. -[all panting]
You're all okay.
[all sighing]
[Tai] That thing is gearing up for something.
[all gasping]
[Meicooman] Mei, why did you leave me all alone?
I've never been so scared.
[growling]
[roaring]
-Agumon, time to digiball! -Uh.
Gabumon!
[Gabumon] What is that thing?
You, too, Tentomon. Time to level up!
Wait. We don't know what you want!
Whatever's supposed to happen, it ain't happening.
[Tai] How about we try it, Gabumon? Digivolve!
[TK] All right, Patamon. You know how to do this.
[Joe] Come on digivice, work.
-No dice. -Now what?
I thought these would still work,
but if they don't, it means we're stuck at this level.
Biyomon, hey, where are you?
[Biyomon panting]
Hold up. We need to stay together!
[growling]
[groaning]
[grunting and whimpering]
[Tai] Take my hand!
-[Agumon] Tai! -[Tai] Agumon!
[Nishijima] Top secret digital world data.
Current coordinates of the Digimon after the reboot?
What is all this?
-[Nishijima] Here you go. -[gasps]
[Nishijima] Sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
Still working on the reboot, huh?
Yeah. I think I might be able to contact Tapirmon
-if I get it right. -[Nishijima] Huh?
But Digieggs can't rehatch.
We both know that.
And when the harmonious ones were first born...
[Himekawa] Tapirmon was sacrificed.
[gasps]
[Himekawa] And he can never be reborn.
Not the usual way. Of course I know that.
That's why the reboot is the only option now.
I just have to keep working until I can find a way to--
[Nishijima] You need to stop.
I'm not finished.
Just stop for now. You need to rest.
Then we'll do it together.
A new team, me and you as partners.
[gasps]
-[Himekawa laughs] -Huh?
-[gasps] -[laughs harder]
You watch too much TV.
[laughs nervously]
But just the same, I appreciate you trying to help me.
[grunts]
[Nishijima] So you're telling me there's a chance?
[laughs softly]
[Nishijima] Wait, this must be from Gennai.
\"If we could harness Meicooman, a reboot might be possible.
I'll give you intel if you're willing to collaborate
with King Drasil.\"
-King Drasil? -[thud]
Who's there?
You can call me...
Hackmon.
How did I end up here all alone?
Hello? [gasps]
There she is.
Biyomon!
It's me, Sora!
-Biyomon! Wait up! -Why should I?
-Why won't you leave me alone? -[gasps]
-I'm worried about you. -You're lying!
You're just scared to be out by yourself!
You're wrong!
Find somebody else to hang out with!
I can't! You and I are partners!
Get this through your head! I do not know you!
[Sora gasps]
[grunts]
-[Sora] Couldn't we just try-- -[Biyomon] I'm leaving, and--
Uh...
[Sora] Biyomon, I finally caught up to you.
What's wrong?
[panting]
-Meiko? -[Meiko stirs]
[groans]
[Meiko] Sora? Is that you? What are you doing here?
Wait! What am I doing here?
[gasps]
And where exactly is here?
[Tai] Guys! Can anybody hear me?
-Mr. Matt! -Agumon!
Kari!
Oh. I'm all alone.
Well, what am I? Chopped liver?
I feel safer with Mr. Matt.
[chuckles]
[Salamon] Tai! Tai, is that you?
[rustling]
-[screams] -Whoa, Salamon.
[Tai] Kari, wake up, sis.
[stirs]
[Kari] I'm so glad to see you guys,
but what happened?
-Not sure, but at least... -Kari!
...you're okay.
[giggles]
[Kari] I'm fine. Just a little dazed.
[Tai] Me too.
-Where are the others? -I don't know.
Machinedramon just disappeared all of a sudden.
A big hole opened up and swallowed him.
And when I looked around, I was alone.
-Seriously? I was there. -A big hole?
-You think it was a distortion? -Sure looked like it.
-It happened just in time. -But where is everybody else?
[Tai] Hmm.
[Joe] How did we get all the way up here?
It's impossible.
Unless-- unless that distortion
zapped us all to different places!
There's no need to worry. We're fine.
And what is that?
[Mimi] Just a building. A big, creepy building.
[TK] This is too bizarre.
What happened?
[grunting]
My ankle feels like it's broken.
Huh?
I know you.
[Izzy] Welcome to the middle of nowhere.
[Tokomon] Why did we transport here?
Weren't we in the woods
with that big noisy monster thingy just a second ago?
Where did it go?
Pinch me. It's just a dream!
[grunts] Maybe, but it still hurts.
It's a painful dream.
What do you think? Got any ideas?
[Matt] Man, not a clue.
[Sora] Does this really ever work?
[Meiko] It's working now. Look.
[blowing]
[gasps then coughs]
Now, what were you saying?
My bad. I never pictured you as a camper.
My family used to go to the mountains all the time.
When I was a little girl, me and Dad would play
in the woods. We had so much fun.
[Sora] Would you like to hear some happy news?
Mm-hm.
We saw Meicooman earlier.
She's been looking everywhere for you.
Why didn't you tell me that right from the start?
Oh, I'm so glad.
I was afraid she'd forgotten all about me the way Biyomon has.
I'm so sorry.
It's all right. You were just being honest.
And even if Biyomon never remembers me,
I'll be okay.
Of course you will. You're strong.
-Huh? -[Sora] It's raining fruit.
Are those pears?
Yes. Take 'em or leave 'em.
-Biyomon, how nice! -Wow!
I've got some other stuff here, too.
-Come eat with us. -[scoffs] I don't think so.
I've got better things to do.
No problem.
Hey, stop being silly, Biyomon.
Come sit by the fire with us.
Plus, you and I have a lot to catch up on.
[grumbles]
[gasps]
[groans]
[Biyomon] Fine, but I don't know you either!
Don't get excited. I'm not here as an enemy.
I'm not here as a friend either.
I'm just a messenger sent from Homeostasis,
and I'm here to warn you about Gennai.
King Drasil corrupted him and now he's become Dark Gennai.
Gennai always kept the balance between the light and the dark.
That was his function.
Now that he's embraced the dark,
the world has begun to fall from the light.
The darkness is spreading everywhere.
[grunts]
Where's Himekawa?
She entered the Digital World on her own
in hopes of finding Tapirmon.
[gasps]
Of course, she had King Drasil's help.
He's kept track of her for years.
But Drasil has his own agenda.
And though Himekawa has joined forces with him,
her goals are unimportant.
[Nishijima] So that was the real reason for the reboot all along.
She wanted to go back.
You and I have to work together.
King Drasil's goal is to stop humans and Digimon
from interacting.
We think he's trying to use the Libra to accomplish it.
The Libra? Meicooman.
Mm-hm.
[gasps]
[Gennai] Libra is immensely powerful but volatile.
If the forces of darkness ever gain control over it,
it will be global destruction.
Huh?
[Tentomon] Izzy, where are you?
Hello? Hey, you guys!
[groans] Being lost is wearing me out.
[Tentomon] Izzy, Panomon, Gabumon, Agumon?
Oh, Izzy, where are you?
Weird. Why do I keep calling out for Izzy?
Because the two of you are partners.
You were like two peas in a pod.
Really?
It must have been a very large pod.
I wish Izzy was with us right now.
He and his big brain are so good at figuring things out.
Whatever you say, but it's your turn to yell now.
[Agumon] That's a pretty picture, Izzy,
but I don't remember it.
[Gomamon] Humans sure laugh a lot.
[Patamon] Ooh, there we are. Look how young we were.
[Izzy] And here's another picture of you and Joe, Gobumon,
and you and Tai, Agumon. See? We were all friends.
[Matt grumbles]
[Matt] Let's just stop wasting time and get going.
[Joe] That looks exactly like Mimi.
You're quite the artist, Palmon.
[all laughing]
[Meiko] Oh, Sora.
[footsteps approaching]
[groans] Meiko.
How could you leave me in this horrible place?
[Olegmon] At least it's not broken, TK.
I think you just sprained it.
These special leaves will have you all healed up in no time.
You're pretty good, Olegmon.
You're helping me babysit those little carpet crawlers,
so I owed you. Now we're even.
Like old times.
You and me and Patamon used to take care of these fellas.
Mm, yeah?
You keep saying that, but I still don't remember.
[chuckles] Yeah, of course you wouldn't remember.
We weren't part of this Digital World.
The thing is, we'll never forget you.
I'll always remember the day I meet Patamon
and the day I had to say goodbye.
You really love him, don't you, this Patamon?
I can't wait to finally meet him.
Yeah.
I hope we find him soon.
[Agumon] So, you think these tracks will lead us
-back to the others? -[Matt] It's possible.
If this is the same place I remember,
then these tracks will lead us to a lake with a trolley.
Though I can't guarantee the DigiWorld hasn't changed
I can't wait to hear more of these wild stories
about Joe and studying,
and the girlfriend he says he has and the food he eats
and the weird places he goes to study some more.
Do you even want to find them, Matt?
You haven't said a thing about Tai.
It's like you don't even like him.
-Next question. -Matt likes Tai a lot.
-Don't tell him that. -So you don't like him?
[Matt] It's just... we all expect a lot out of Tai.
Maybe... maybe more than he has to give us.
Hmm?
[Matt] Hmm.
[Izzy] Hmm.
[Gomamon] What's that? It looks like it's coming right at us.
I believe what we are experiencing is a mirage.
[Gomamon] It looks so real.
[train chugging]
[Agumon] And it sounds so real.
[chugging gets louder]
[Agumon] I'm sure glad it's not real.
-[train whistles] -[all screaming]
[train whistles]
[all groaning]
-Hey, mirage, wait up! -We need a ride!
[Gomamon] It's not stopping!
[Agumon] We'll never catch it now.
Well, I guess walking on the train tracks
wasn't the best idea we ever had.
[chuckles] Our logic was clearly flawed.
It happens.
[Gomamon] What we were talking about
before we nearly got run over?
[Agumon] Matt and Tai and how they don't get along.
[Gomamon] Oh, that's right.
[Matt] I never said we don't get along.
[Izzy] Yeah. Those two are best friends.
[Matt] No, we're not!
[others laughing]
Shouldn't we be searching for those guys?
What are we to you now, since you don't remember us?
-Huh? -I don't have any power now.
If Agumon and I are still partners,
then why couldn't I get him to do digivolve?
I'm useless here.
That's not true.
[Tai] I guess the reboot put us at square one.
And things aren't going to go back to the way they were...
ever.
[Kari] Don't be so sure about that.
There's still time, and not everything that happened is bad.
I think Salamon is actually happier now.
Let's accept our Digimon the way they are.
Their memories might all return eventually.
But either way, we'll just keep moving forward.
Huh?
Well, maybe you're right.
[Biyomon] That girl keeps saying she knows me.
Could it be true?
[Sora] What am I going to do, Meiko?
About Biyomon?
I keep trying to get closer to her,
but she just pushes me away.
I know none of our partners remember the way things
used to be, but still, all the other Digimon,
they're all happy with their partners
even without any memories of them.
So why not Biyomon?
Not only does she not know me, she doesn't want to.
Did I do something wrong
or is there just something wrong with me?
Enough of that!
There's nothing wrong with you, Sora,
and none of this is your fault!
Each of us is linked to our Digimon,
and that bond can't be broken.
You're the one who taught me that.
So stop talking nonsense already!
[gasps]
[Meiko] Sorry about that.
That came out a little harsher than I meant it to.
[leaves rustling]
I've had my doubts, too.
When Meicooman got infected, she changed.
She turned violent and dangerous.
But I'm here to find her. I'll never give up on her.
-[leaves rustling] -[both] Huh?
[gasps] Meicooman?
Mei?
-Meicooman? I'm so glad-- -[both gasp]
[Sora] Meicooman, it's us!
Oh, I know it's you,
but what I want to know is why you left me here?
How could you?
How could you leave me alone in this horrible place?
[Sora] Look out!
All alone! You hate me! I know it!
Why else would you do that? You hate me because I got sick!
[gasps] You're right.
I ran and left you because you got sick.
-You were scaring me! -[grunts] Stay away!
I thought that the evil had taken you over for good!
You left me!
But I'm here now! I came to find you!
I'll always come back for you, Meicooman, no matter what!
I know you know that because you and I are partners,
and I love you.
[Meicooman] You love me?
I will never leave you alone again.
Can you ever forgive me, Meicooman?
Please say you can.
[Meicooman] I think so. [sobs]
[Meiko] Thank you.
Let's stick together now, you and me.
[Meicooman growls]
[Meiko] Meicooman!
What are you doing here?
[chuckles and snaps fingers]
-[Meiko] Really? Again? -[Meicooman] Let me down.
No way. I'm not losing you again.
[rumbling]
[gasps]
[surge of electricity]
[Meicooman] I'll take care of this guy, Meiko.
He's here for me.
[crash]
-Come back! -Stay here. I'll go get her.
-Sora, wait! -[gasps]
[both] Huh?
[Gomamon] is that real?
[Tai] Another distortion. That's Sora.
She looks like she's in trouble.
[Himekawa] Just hold on.
I'm coming.
Hold on.
[screams]
[grunting]
[Gennai] The Libra is mine. [chuckles]
[Sora] Put her down!
The next one will hit you between the eyes!
[scoffs]
[grunts]
[grunting]
Ken, let go! What are you doing?
Don't assume everything you see is real.
Ken is just one of many forms I can take in your world.
You're Gennai. Ugh!
I have a feeling you're going to like the Gennai that I am now.
[laughing]
Does that news come as a surprise to you?
-Himekawa said it would. -Himekawa?
What does she have to do with this?
She and I made a trade for this.
-Give me that! It's mine! -It was yours.
And without it, you're nothing!
[surge of electricity]
[Gennai] Huh?
[Sora] Biyomon?
Let her go, you jerk! [grunts]
[grunts]
Biyomon!
Another little pest.
That pest is my partner!
Biyomon, are you okay?
Meicoomon, are you hurt? Say something.
Oh, man.
I guess you two are going to make me do this
the hard way after all.
[gasps]
[rumbling]
Let me go!
[screams]
What is this?
-They missed. -Huh?
[Sora] You guys are just in time.
You saved us from Machinedramon.
Nope. We just showed up.
It's true. We didn't do anything.
Then who?
-[Gabumon] How was that? -Gabumon! Nice!
-[Gabumon] Thanks. -[Agumon] I found you!
There you are. Man, am I glad to see you.
-Not so hard. -[chewing]
[Joe] Look, you guys. It's a miracle!
We're finally back together again!
[Izzy] We must have all come through those distortions.
[gasps]
Meiko.
[gasps] And Meicooman! It's a reunion, you guys.
-[rumbling] -Huh?
[Tai] Machinedramon!
[Gennai laughing] Look at the new targets.
[Tai] It's Gennai. What are you doing here?
[Gennai grunts]
I'm here for the one you call Meicooman.
But let's have some fun first. Let's see who runs and who dies.
[explosions]
I think Gennai must have gone crazy.
Maybe that's not really Gennai at all.
Oh, I'm Gennai all right,
but I've had a little change of heart.
I'm on the Digimon side.
[Matt] What are you talking about?
[Joe] So are we!
[Gennai] That's what you say, but it's a lie.
Humans and Digimon should have never met up in the first place.
You've done nothing but interfere with their lives
from the very beginning!
[panting] They all chose to be with us.
What's he mean, TK?
When Homeostasis chose you, instead of honoring them
and helping them, you enslaved them.
Then when the infection began and you started losing control,
you did just what King Drasil wanted,
and you performed the reboot! [laughing]
So the reboot is...
All part of the master plan. [snaps fingers]
[all gasping]
[rumbling]
-[Salomon grunts] -[Kari] Puppy!
[echoing screams]
-[all clamoring] -[Joe] Let's get out of here!
[low grumbling sound]
[Izzy] Machinedramon's too big to use a gangplank.
So we should be safe aboard this old ship for a while.
[TK] Can we start this wreck up and sail out of here?
[Izzy] It looks like the engines are shut.
I'll try, but it doesn't look good.
[Tentomon] It's hard to believe something this big
could ever move.
[Kari] Salamon, it was dangerous to attack like that.
[Salomon] But I had to do something, Kari.
Machinedramon was trying to hurt you.
-Mei. -What is it? Are you hurt?
You have to let me go off on my own.
That guy will never stop chasing me.
Is that what you're worried about?
Meicooman, you don't have to be alone.
You have all of us on your side, but you guys--
-[both] Huh? -This is our fault.
And I'm so very sorry you all got mixed up in it.
[Mimi] Don't be ridiculous, Mei Mei.
You heard Dark Gennai,
so now we know who's behind all this.
[TK] Mm-hm.
King Drasil.
-[thud] -[both gasp]
[all screaming]
He found us already?
-That was scary! -Is he gonna take our boat?
[TK] I'll take care of you.
Oh, great! We're trapped just like rats on this ship!
Yeah, but we can't get off!
Not with Machinedramon just waiting for us.
[Tentomon] What if we fool him into looking the wrong way
-for a minute? -Yeah.
One of us could fake him out.
Someone would have to volunteer. But who?
[Tentomon] I'll do it, Izzy.
No. It should be me and Tai.
And I volunteer too, as long as there's food.
-One-track mind. -[thud]
[screaming]
[Sora] That was even closer. He's almost found the range.
Meicooman can hide here!
The rest of us have to draw him away by getting off the ship.
[Sora] Go! I'll stay here with Meiko.
[Matt] Tai, come with me.
We'll jump off the back of the ship.
[Tai] Right. Move it, Agumon.
[Kari] I'm coming with you.
Hmm.
Decoys, huh?
Oldest trick in the book. [snaps fingers]
I'll just send them a little playmate. MetalSeadramon!
[panting]
[gasping]
[Gennai] Time to take care of the rest. [chuckles]
[all screaming]
[Tentomon] Well, we're off the ship. Now what, Izzy?
Time to destroy that thing.
I'm making a hologram to trick Gennai.
-There. -[TK] Do it.
Run!
-[surge of electricity] -[Mimi screams]
Thanks for the warning!
Come out, come out wherever you are.
[distant explosion]
-[grunts] -[Sora] It's okay, Biyomon.
[Biyomon] I don't need you to comfort me.
I'm just doing whatever I can think of to help.
You should have done what I told you.
Taking care of yourself instead of annoying me
and following me around everywhere.
That's mean.
I'm not being mean.
I just want you to face reality.
[Sora] Oh, I'm sorry.
You can't help it.
You're just a gentle spirit, Sora.
[gasps]
Biyomon, you called me by my name.
Yeah, what's the big deal?
It's just that I figured I'd better be nicer to you
if I wanted more of those meatballs.
-[Sora] [laughing] -[distant explosion]
-Oh. -Now what?
Stay with Meicooman.
I've got to make sure those guys are okay.
[Gennai] You pathetic humans are such easy targets.
It's your constant fear of death that makes you this way.
The Digimon on the other hand, are eternal.
In the form of digieggs, they can always be reborn.
Well, if they're not contaminated
by your human world.
If a Digimon's life ends in the human world,
it can never reincarnate. How sad.
[screaming]
[Gennai] That's why the reboot was such a brilliant idea.
All Digimon who died on the other side
can be reincarnated. Now, at last, the Digimon
are ready to take over the human world.
-Right, Meicooman? -Meicooman?
Yes.
She's the key to eradicating you all.
-TK, duck! -Ah!
[echoing scream]
-[grunts] -Nice shot!
So scary!
[screaming]
[grunting]
Marching Fishes, go!
[screaming]
[grunting]
Poison ivy!
-That was fantastic, Palmon. -I know, right?
Good fishing, Gomamon! That was awesome!
[Gomamon] What would you do without me, Joe?
[Sora] You guys, are you okay? [panting]
Hmm. Now, time's up.
Uh-oh.
-[screaming] -[Mimi] He's back!
Hey, ugly. Look up here.
Tentomon leveled up to giant size,
and he's about to crush you like a bug!
[Gennai] Not if I vaporize him first.
-Gabumon, can you take this guy? -You got it.
[Gabumon shouts]
[MetalSeadramon growling]
[Matt] Whoa! You did it, Gabumon!
[Gabumon] Yeah. What was that big thing?
That was MetalSeadramon. Nice job.
Thanks, little Matt. Can I call you that?
-Little? -[Tai] Yeah.
Gabumon wanted a special name for you,
and I told him you like to be called little.
-[Gabumon] Yeah. -[Matt] Tai, you are such an--
-[screaming -[MetalSeadramon growling]
[Kari] Matt, Tai! Are you okay?
[Gabumon] Little Matt. Tai! Where are you?
[panting]
[wind whistling]
[laughs]
[Himekawa] Tapirmon, I finally found you!
Hmm?
[Himekawa] Aren't you glad to see me too?
[giggles] We're together again.
I missed you so much.
[Tapirmon] Are you a human? Hmm?
Uh... I am, and I'm your partner.
-We're a team. -[Tapirmon] No, we're not.
[grunts] I don't know you, and I don't want to!
Now leave me alone!
[gasps]
[Himekawa] Tapirmon, you may not remember me yet
or believe that we're partners...
but it's true all the same and now that I've found you,
I'll never lose you again!
[screaming]
[Agumon] Tai, I need to know something.
[Tai] Agumon?
Is that you?
[Agumon] Why did you guys come back here to the Digital World?
[Tai] I had to. I had to see you again.
[Agumon] But weren't you all taking an awful big chance?
What if you didn't find us?
What if something else went wrong?
[Tai] I couldn't lose you again.
The only reason I came back to this world was to find you.
We're meant for each other.
We were all destined to be together.
-Gabumon! -Agumon!
[Agumon] Tai, I want to be more powerful .
[Gabumon] Me too, Matt.
[grunting]
Gabumon, digivolve!
[Tai] Agumon, digivolve!
[Kari] Tai, brother, where are you?
I don't know what to do!
[roaring]
[screams]
[growling]
Huh? Oh no.
Oh, what now?
-Sorry to make you wait. -Tai, you're here.
Look who's back!
[grunting]
[gasps]
[Kari exclaims]
Are we doomed?
[Kari] Salamon, digivolve too!
[Gatomon] Gatomon!
Lightning Paw!
-Hey, you okay, Kari? -Gatomon?
Man, it's good to see him.
Yeah, you got that right.
I thought it might never happen again.
[laughing
[Tentomon] Did you guys see how big I was?
Yeah, but how? Because now you're small again.
That was a hologram of a giant Tentomon,
but it fooled Machinedramon into blasting ice down onto himself.
Well done. You're amazing.
-I'd call it pro digits. -[TK] Guys.
[Kari] What is it, TK?
[TK] If Machinedramon breaks out, we'd better be ready.
I'm ready to go if you need a partner.
[Joe] It's good to have you back Gabumon.
-You're the only partner for me. -[laughs]
[Kari] The same goes for us, Palmon.
Sora, what's this partner thing again?
-What? -You know, partners?
You said we made a great team together.
That means that I--
-[thud] -[grunts]
[growling]
-[Biyomon grunts] -[Sora] Biyomon, no!
Stop it!
[Palmon] Don't worry. We'll save you guys.
[screaming]
[Sora] Let her go, you big jerk!
[Palmon] Oh no!
-Sora! Jump off! -No way!
[grunts]
No!
-[thud] -[grunts]
[Biyoman] You have to save yourself, Sora.
There's only one thing left to try.
-[Biyoman] What? -Are you with me?
Huh?
It could work. But I need you to help.
And do what?
Level up. Can you take my hand?
[grunts] Okay.
[Biyoman] Biyomon, digivolve too!
[squawking]
Birdramon!
Birdramon, digivolve too!
Garudomon!
Garudomon, digivolve too.
Phoenixmon.
[Machinedramon growling]
[Joe] Look, Phoenixmon rescued Sora.
[Sora] You did it.
[Meiko] Wow, that's Phoenixmon.
I'm glad all your friends left. This is much better.
[gasps]
Hey.
I've been waiting for this for a long time.
So much is about to happen.
Just relax. It'll all be over soon.
[Machinedramon growling]
She's digivolved.
A Mega digivolve! That's Phoenixmon for sure,
Biyomon's Mega form!
[Sora screaming]
[Joe] I'm coming, Sora. I've got you.
-[grunts] -[Mimi] Sora.
-[Patamon] What about me, TK? -[TK] Hmm?
-How can I level up? -You sure you want to?
Who wouldn't want that power? Do you know how?
[Mimi] Go for it, TK.
Hmm.
Patamon, digivolve too!
Angemon!
Angemon, digivolve too!
MagnaAngemon!
MagnaAngemon, digivolve too!
Seraphimon!
[Izzy] Another Mega digivolution.
[Tentomon] Izzy, I wanna digivolve too,
but I don't know how to do it.
-Do I have a Mega form? -Yeah, you bet!
-Can we do it? -Sure.
Come in here close to me, and I'll use this.
Oh, great.
Tentomon, digivolve too!
Kabuterimon!
Kabuterimon, digivolve too!
MegaKabuterimon!
MegaKabuterimon, digivolve too!
HerculesKabuterimon!
[Machinedramon growling]
[growling]
[Seraphimon] MegaElectroshocker!
[Machinedramon growling]
[Izzy] That'll finish him.
Nice job!
I'm worn out. That was hard. I think I need a rest.
[chuckles]
-Did I do good? -Yeah. You did fantastic.
-Tokomon. -Yay! We did it, didn't we, TK?
[laughs]
Hmm?
[Joe] I think Phoenixmon is reverting into Yokomon.
[giggling]
You were great. You okay? Was that a little scary?
I'm just glad I could help a little.
Maybe next time you can get in there too, Koromon.
Yeah, don't rush me. I will.
Palmon, we can digivolve you next time, too. Okay?
[Palmon] You got it!
[grunting]
One thing I've learned is that Digimon can digivolve
by other means than a digivice.
Another way is to use shear anger.
[growling]
And what could make Meicooman more furious
than having to watch her human partner suffer?
That's it, Meicooman, let the fury burn inside you!
Give yourself up to the transformation!
-[grunting] -[Gennai] Let the anger bloom!
Let it grow!
[straining and grunting]
[gasps]
[Gennai] Digivolve or your partner dies.
Digivolve into your true form and then destroy this world,
this world into which you should never have been born
in the first place!
Hey, are you guys all okay?
Yeah, all good.
You should have seen it, Tai!
We totally destroyed Machinedramon.
-Well, it was a group effort. -Sora.
You guys okay? Glad you're here.
[Matt] I think Tai has something he wants to say to you.
[Mimi] Well, you can talk on the way.
We've got to get Mei Mei off that ship!
[Sora] What's up?
[Tai] Uh, I...
-[Tai] I was thinking, and... -[Sora] And what?
[Tai] I'm sorry I didn't listen before,
but I really wanna help
if you'll tell me what you're upset about.
Well, that was no big whoop.
Huh? What do you mean?
Sora? You were flipping out.
[Sora] Well, now I'm not.
[both sigh]
[Sora] Thanks anyway, you boneheads.
[laughing]
-[explosion] -[all gasping]
What is that?
[screaming]
[surge of electricity]
[Gennai laughing]
[Gennai] Oh, you just wait.
[laughing]
[music]
♪ Don't look back, keep running ♪
♪ Sunshine day
♪ Can't give in to the scratches and pain ♪
♪ Adventure
♪ Stand up, there's nothing to fear ♪
♪ My future
♪ It quenches my thirst
♪ Your smile
♪ Hiding deep within my heart
♪ The weak side of me
♪ Tell it goodbye and again
♪ You can become stronger
♪ Now's the time to take courage to fly ♪
♪ Spread the wings in your heart ♪
♪ To the unseen future
♪ Now's the time to head towards ♪
♪ the endless skies
♪ It's just begun
♪ The adventure to our dreams
♪ La la la...