- ( clock ticking )
- Garius: WARRIOR
FROM LANDS UNKNOWN,
I LEAVE MY DAUGHTER,
FLESH OF MY FLESH,
TO YOUR CARE.
- Akatsuki: COME ON.
- FATHER, I DON'T
THINK I CAN DO THIS.
- ( sobs )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( door opens )
- TREAD LIGHTLY, ROGUE HERO.
MY FATHER GAVE ME EXPRESS
PERMISSION TO SLAY
WHOSOEVER PRESUMED
TO BE MY GUARDIAN
IF I FOUND THEM WANTING.
FAIL TO MEASURE UP,
AND YOUR HEAD IS MINE.
- ( gasps )
- Miu: YOU STAY BY ME,
I CAN'T GUARANTEE
YOUR SURVIVAL.
DID HE SENSE THAT DARKNESS?
- ( screams )
- TIMID BABES JUST DO IT
FOR ME, SWEET CHEEKS.
AND IT'S GOTTA BE
SAID, RED SUITS YOU.
- STOP! WHATEVER YOU'RE
THINKING I WANT NO PART OF IT!
- AW, BUT YOU'RE
SO HOT. PLAY FAIR.
AT LEAST GIMME A NAME.
- WAIT A SECOND.
HE'S SAYING ALL
THIS IN HIS SLEEP!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
I'M NOT THAT KIND OF GIRL!
YOU HAVE TO WAKE UP!
- DON'T FIGHT IT, YOU
MIGHT ENJOY YOURSELF.
- THAT'S NOT THE POINT!
WAIT! THAT'S MY
BLOUSE! GIVE IT BACK!
- ( she screams )
- NO!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THIS IS,
BUT I KNOW IT'S NOT RIGHT!
OH, MY GOODNESS.
WHAT DO I DO?
BROTHER!
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M YOUR KID SISTER,
YOU CAN'T TREAT ME LIKE THIS!
YOU SHOULD PROTECT ME,
NOT VIOLATE ME. CREEP!
DID IT WORK?
- I LIKE YOUR STYLE,
BUT THAT'S PRETTY LOW.
MY KID SISTER IS DEAD.
- ( shrieks )
STOP! WHAT ARE
YOU DOING TO ME?
I'M NOT OKAY WITH THIS!
OH, MY. IT DOES FEEL
KIND OF AMAZING, THOUGH.
- ( yells loudly )
- Akatsuki: OH! MY HEAD
FEELS LIKE A MOSH PIT.
NOT A GOOD THING.
COULD BE CATCHING A COLD.
- I'M SURE IT'S NOTHING. YOU
PROBABLY JUST SLEPT WRONG.
WHY IS EVERYONE
STARING AT US?
- OH, YOU KNOW.
"NEW KID" THING.
- (door opens )
- DON'T LET IT GET TO YA.
NEW KIDS ALWAYS FASCINATE
THE PEANUT GALLERY.
IT'S THE SAME EVERYWHERE,
STRANGER IN A STRANGE LAND,
PEOPLE ARE GONNA GIVE YOU THE
THIRD DEGREE WITH THEIR EYES.
PLAY IT OFF AND
EVENTUALLY THEY'LL LET YOU
BLEND INTO THE BACKGROUND.
- SO, SHOULD I JUST
SIT DOWN ANYWHERE?
- PARK YOUR BUTT IN
WHATEVER EMPTY SEAT YOU LIKE.
NEWBIE PRIVILEGE.
- Chikage: I'M LIKING THE
ATTITUDE, BONNIE AND CLYDE.
APPARENTLY THE RUMOR MILL
GOT IT RIGHT THIS TIME,
THE TWO OF YOU ARE
GONNA BE A HANDFUL.
ROOKIES ALWAYS GET
TALKED ABOUT, SURE.
BUT, I DON'T KNOW. MY INSTINCTS
TELL ME YOUR REPUTATION
FOR BEATING AN INSTRUCTOR'S
ASS IS RIGHT ON THE MONEY.
AND YOU, NOT JUST ANYBODY
COULD CINCH AN ENDORSEMENT
FROM THE STUDENT COUNCIL
PREZ THEIR FIRST TIME OUT.
YOU'VE GIVEN YOURSELF
A LOT TO LIVE UP TO.
BLENDING IN? GOOD LUCK.
- Miu: I DIDN'T MEAN TO...
- LOOK, I'M NOT TRYING TO MAKE
THE TRANSITION HARD FOR YOU,
I'M JUST SAYING MAKING B
CLASS YOUR FIRST DAY IS BIG.
MOST OF US HAD TO CLAW ALL
THE WAY UP FROM E CLASS,
BUT IT'S WHATEVER.
- NICE JOB BUTTERING US UP
BEFORE YOU DEAL OUT THE WARNING.
YOU GONNA TELL US A
LITTLE ABOUT YOURSELF?
OR YOU PREFER WE
USE OUR IMAGINATIONS?
- MY NAME'S IZUMI CHIKAGE.
DEFINITELY AN ACQUIRED TASTE,
BUT MAYBE SOMEONE
YOU'LL COME TO RELY ON.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
- AKATSUKI OUSAWA.
THIS, IS MY LITTLE SISTER MIU.
- I'M VERY PLEASED
TO MEET YOU.
- IF YOU TWO WOULDN'T
MIND SOME ADVICE,
THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD KNOW.
NORMALLY IT'S COOL FOR THE
NOOBS TO SIT ANYWHERE,
BUT HOW SHOULD I PUT THIS?
YOU MIGHT WANNA CONSIDER
PARKING YOUR BUTTS ELSEWHERE.
- ( both exclaim )
- Onizuka: HEY, DEAD GUY!
I SURE HOPE YOUR ASS
CAN SETTLE THE TAB
IT JUST OPENED BY
SWIPING MY SEAT!
OUTTA MY WAY, PENIS BREATH.
YOU GOT TILL I GET UP THERE
TO MOVE IT OR LOSE IT.
- I DID TRY TO WARN YOU.
THAT'D BE OUR RESIDENT
NEANDERTHAL, ONIZUKA.
HE GOT BOOTED DOWN FROM A
CLASS FOR BEING A DOUCHE NOZZLE.
- HEY, I'M TALKING TO YOU!
LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY
NEEDS A BREAKDOWN
OF THE UNOFFICIAL RULES.
- ( coughs )
WELL, AT LEAST
YOU GOT A PAIR.
YOU'LL NEED
THEM ON MY TURF.
THERE AIN'T NO FREE...
WHOA, DUDE. YOU GOT, LIKE,
A VICE GRIP. EASE UP!
- IN ANOTHER LIFE, DUDE.
WE'D HAVE HAD SOME FUN.
SEE, I HAVE THING FOR
BULLYING PEOPLE, TOO.
ESPECIALLY ONES WHO GET THEIR
ROCKS OFF ACTING ALL BOSS.
YOU KNOW THE TYPE. ALWAYS
THUMPING THEIR CHEST,
LIKE THE REST OF US ARE LUCKY
TO BREATHE THE SAME AIR?
- ( he groans in pain )
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I GOT THE RULES DOWN?
OR WAS THERE SOMETHING
YOU WANTED TO ADD
BEFORE I CRUSH THIS
EMPTY SKULL OF YOURS?
- STOP IT! YOU'VE MADE YOUR
POINT. JUST LET HIM GO!
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO
BE THE PROBLEM CHILD
BETWEEN THE TWO
OF US. LOOK AT YOU!
- UH! HERE COMES THE
JERK-WAD BRIGADE.
- Miu: WHO ARE THEY?
- DISCIPLINE COMMITTEE.
JUST A BUNCH OF CHODES WHO ONLY
ANSWER TO THE STUDENT COUNCIL.
- THIS ISN'T HIS FAULT! YOU
SAW IT, HE WAS PROVOKED!
HE HAS A RIGHT TO
DEFEND HIMSELF!
- Akatsuki: DON'T
WORRY ABOUT IT, SIS.
IT'S GOOD FOR ME.
- Girl: YOU WILL TAKE A
SEAT AND WAIT QUIETLY.
THE EXECUTIVE OFFICERS
WILL ARRIVE
TO DISCUSS THE ISSUE
WITH YOU SHORTLY.
- Akatsuki: HMMM.
TAKE A SEAT, HUH?
- Kyoya: NICELY DONE, AKATSUKI.
YOU HAVE VERY GOOD REFLEXES.
- Akatsuki: YOU SON OF A BITCH!
YOU TRYING TO DRAG MY
SISTER INTO THIS?
- Kyoya: LET'S JUST SAY,
GIVEN YOUR REPUTATION,
I DOUBTED SHE WOULD BE IN
MUCH DANGER OF GETTING HURT.
- I TRUST YOU'VE
NOT WAITED LONG?
- ( she exclaims )
- NO WORRIES. THERE ARE
WORSE WAYS TO SPEND TIME.
- I BEG YOUR PARDON!
THAT CHAIR IS NOT
FOR THE LIKES OF YOU!
KINDLY REMOVE YOURSELF TO
A MORE APPROPRIATE SPOT
AND WE'LL DISCUSS THE INCIDENT
THAT BROUGHT YOU HERE!
- OH, I'M SORRY,
AM I OUT OF LINE?
I FIGURED SINCE NO
ONE WAS HERE...
IT'S A CHAIR, RIGHT?
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL
ABOUT SITTING ON A PIECE OF
FURNITURE MEANT TO BE SAT ON?
- VALID POINT. BUT
HARUKA'S ARGUMENT
HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH FURNITURE DESIGN.
- RIGHT. THAT
CHAIR IS RESERVED.
- ( she gasps )
- ( she screams )
- WHOA! HE'S
PRETTY GOOD.
- LET'S SEE HOW GOOD!
- IF YOU'RE QUITE
DONE TESTING US,
BE ADVISED THAT FOR
NOW, WE'RE PLAYING NICE.
- Kyoya: WHAT IS THE
MEANING OF THIS, PLEASE?
- SERIOUSLY? DON'T TRY TO PULL
THE WHOLE "WHO ME" THING NOW.
YOU CALLED ME INTO
YOUR LITTLE OFFICE
TO PICK UP WHERE
WE LEFT OFF YESTERDAY, RIGHT?
- DON'T BE ABSURD.
TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST,
I HAVEN'T THE FAINTEST IDEA
WHY YOU'RE EVEN HERE.
- NO REASON YOU
SHOULD, SIR, I SENT FOR HIM.
THIS ONE IS A MENACE.
THE DISCIPLINE COMMITTEE
APPRISED ME OF HIS OUTBURST.
IT WOULD SEEM HE'S
HAVING DIFFICULTY
ADJUSTING TO LIFE HERE
WITHOUT CAUSING MISCHIEF.
NOT THAT WE'RE UNAPPRECIATIVE.
BUT YOUR INTERFERENCE WITH
THAT STUDENT WAS UNNECESSARY,
NOT TO MENTION INAPPROPRIATE.
- HOLD ON A SEC.
I PUT THAT BULLY DOWN, YOU
SHOULD BE THANKING ME.
- I AM WARNING YOU.
YOUR TENURE AT BABEL WILL
BE RIGOROUSLY SCRUTINIZED.
DON'T EXPECT LENIENCY.
IS THAT CLEAR?
THINGS WILL NOT
BODE WELL FOR YOU
SHOULD YOU STEP
OUT OF LINE AGAIN.
WHETHER YOU ACTED IN
SELF-DEFENSE IS NOT THE POINT.
WE RUN A VERY TIGHT SHIP HERE.
THOSE WHO HAVE CONTEMPT
FOR AUTHORITY,
ESPECIALLY STUDENTS
WHO THUMB THEIR NOSES
AT MEMBERS OF THE
STUDENT COUNCIL,
WILL NOT BE AFFORDED MERCY.
REMEMBER THAT.
- Kuzuha: I WOULDN'T
DO THAT IF I WERE YOU.
TRY TO GO BACK
IN THERE, I MEAN.
- WELL HEY, LOOK AT THAT.
YOU LOST, LITTLE GIRL?
- WE HAPPEN TO BE
IN THE SAME CLASS.
SO NO, THANK YOU.
MY NAME IS KUZUHA DOUMOTO.
I'M HERE TO TAKE YOU TO
YOUR NEXT PERIOD CLASSROOM.
AND I'M ALSO YOUR
CLASS REPRESENTATIVE.
- MUST BE SOMETHING. SKIPPING
SO MANY GRADES LIKE THAT.
- I DO OKAY. BUT, JUST
SO YOU'RE AWARE,
THE STUDENT COUNCIL OFFICERS YOU
PICKED A FIGHT WITH BACK THERE
KNOW WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
THEY MAKE ME LOOK
LIKE A TOTAL BEGINNER.
MATTER OF FACT, THEY'RE
PRACTICALLY MIND READERS
WHEN IT COMES TO
THEIR OPPONENTS.
- YOU DON'T SAY.
WELL, DAMN.
SO MUCH FOR TRYING TO LIGHT A
FIRE UNDER THEIR FEET, I GUESS.
- YOU MUST BE PSYCHOTIC.
- WHAT KIND OF "FIRE"
ARE WE TALKING ABOUT?
- WATCH AND LEARN, KID.
- AKATSUKI OUSAWA!
THIS CLASSIFIES AS ASSAULT!
- REFERRING TO THESE?
- OUR PRESIDENT MAY HAVE
CHOSEN TO IGNORE YOUR ANTICS,
BUT I AM NOT SO TOLERANT!
YOU'LL BE AN EXAMPLE OF
WHAT HAPPENS TO STUDENTS
WHO ABUSE THEIR PEERS, SIR!
- WHOA! OVERKILL MUCH?
- I'LL MAKE YOU RUE
THE DAY YOU WERE BORN!
THIS IS WHAT IT MEANS TO
INCUR THE WRATH OF THE WIND!
HOW DARE HE HUMILIATE ME
WITH HIS CHEAP LITTLE TRICKS?
PERHAPS THIS MOMENT
WILL TEACH HIM A LESSON.
- ( gasps )
- MARK MY WORDS, DELINQUENT.
THE STUDENT COUNCIL WILL
NOT STAND FOR THIS...
THIS INSOLENCE!
YOUR DAYS AT BABEL
ARE NUMBERED!
- SO, MORE LIKE
A BONFIRE, HUH?
- LIKE IT'S ANY FUN JUST
RUBBING TWO STICKS TOGETHER.
- ( all exclaim )
- YOU'RE FILLING OUT THAT SUIT
LIKE A PROFESSIONAL, SWEETHEART.
- WHY'RE YOU HIDING
BEHIND YOUR BRO?
- AM I THE ONLY GIRL
THIS DOESN'T FIT?
- OH, COME ON. JUST TREAT IT
LIKE YOU'RE WEARING A SWIMSUIT.
NOTHING WRONG WITH SHOWING
OFF THE ASSETS, AM I RIGHT?
- IF YOU MAKE A BIG
DEAL OUT OF THIS,
IT'LL ONLY DRAW MORE ATTENTION.
THE WAY TO PULL THIS OFF IS TO
ACT LIKE IT DOESN'T FAZE YOU.
- DOES THAT REALLY WORK?
- I KNOW A LITTLE TRICK TO
HELP YOU RELAX, IF YOU WANT.
- I'LL PASS, THANK YOU!
LAST NIGHT'S TASTE
OF YOUR RELAXATION TECHNIQUES
WAS MORE THAN ENOUGH!
- WHAT'RE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- NOTHING! FORGET I SAID
ANYTHING, JUST IGNORE ME!
- ( bell tolls )
- Miu: OKAY, SO...
THEY ALL GO IN
THIS CAGE-LIKE THING?
- YEAH. THANKS FOR THE HELP,
BY THE WAY. I APPRECIATE IT.
- Akatsuki: NO PROB. LET'S
FINISH UP AND GET OUTTA HERE.
- ( moans )
- ( giggles )
I'M SORRY, YOU WERE
JUST SO RANDOM.
- AH, GUESS THAT'S
A WORD FOR IT.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO POP THE BALL.
SOMETIMES I JUST DON'T
KNOW MY OWN...
- COULD THE TWO OF YOU FINISH
UP A LITTLE QUIETER, PLEASE?
- SORRY.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- Kuzuha: DID YOU HEAR THAT?
I THINK SOMEONE ELSE
IS IN HERE WITH US.
- ( moaning )
- MAYBE SHE'S CHECKING
HER FOR LICE?
- SHE'S SURE THOROUGH AS HELL.
- THAT'S A GOOD WAY
TO GET SUSPENDED!
THERE'S LIKE A HUNDRED OTHER
PLACES YOU COULD DO THIS.
GET UP!
- WHY YOU GOTTA BE
SUCH A KILLJOY? JEEZ.
- THIS IS AGAINST THE RULES.
- Chikage: ONLY AGAINST
THE RULES IF YOU GET CAUGHT.
- EXACTLY HOW MANY GIRLS
HAVE YOU LURED HERE?
P.E. STANDS FOR PHYSICAL
EDUCATION, NOT PERSONAL EATERY!
- CHILL. I ONLY INDULGE
ON DODGE BALL DAY.
- I'M OUT OF HERE!
- Both: WAIT, HOLD THE DOOR!
- WE'RE TOTALLY TRAPPED
IN HERE, AREN'T WE?
- TOTALLY. THE FASCISTS
WHO DESIGNED THIS PLACE
MADE IT SO THESE STUPID DOORS
ONLY OPEN FROM THE OUTSIDE.
I USUALLY WEDGE A
HANDKERCHIEF IN THE CORNER
TO KEEP IT FROM CLOSING
ALL THE WAY, BUT...
- NO SWEAT.
I GOT THIS.
- HOLD ON. TRAPPED OR NOT,
IT IS SCHOOL PROPERTY.
DAMAGE IT AND
THEY'LL MURDER YOU.
BESIDES, YOUR BICEPS AREN'T
OUR ONLY TICKET OUT OF HERE.
- OH YEAH?
- WE'LL JUST HAVE TO SIT TIGHT
TILL SOMEONE ELSE COMES IN.
LUNCH WILL BE OVER SOON,
THE OTHER REPS WILL HAVE TO
CLEAN UP AFTER THEIR CLASSES.
SHOULDN'T BE LONG.
NOT MUCH WE CAN DO ABOUT IT.
THANKS TO LADY ROMEO HERE.
- DON'T PIN THIS ON ME,
YOU COULD'VE GONE WITH
DON'T ASK DON'T TELL.
- YOU'RE NOT SERIOUSLY
HOPING I'LL IGNORE THE FACT
THAT YOU TREAT THIS ROOM LIKE
A TRUCK STOP PARKING LOT.
- OW. WAY TO TWIST THE
KNIFE, LITTLE MISS RULEBOOK.
CAN'T WE JUST
CALL IT BAD LUCK?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE TRYING
TO ARGUE WITH ME ABOUT THIS.
- OH, WOW.
NOT TO SOUND WEIRD,
BUT I'M SORTA JEALOUS OF
THE CHEMISTRY YOU TWO HAVE.
- All: "CHEMISTRY?"
- YOU'RE SHIVERING. IS IT COLD
IN HERE TO YOU? I'M SORRY.
- I'M FINE. DON'T
WORRY ABOUT IT.
- I THINK SOMEBODY
NEEDS TO PEE.
- NUH-UH!
- FINE. BE THAT WAY.
BUT YOUR EYES ARE
TURNING YELLOW.
- IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS,
BUT YOU REALLY DO
SEEM UNCOMFORTABLE.
- DROP IT, PLEASE.
- IF YOU REALLY HAVE
TO GO THAT BADLY,
I SAW SOME SANDBAGS
IN THE CORNER.
I'M NOT GOOD ENOUGH
WITH EARTH MAGIC
TO MAKE A PROPER
LATRINE, THOUGH.
- NO, THAT'S A GREAT IDEA,
WE MAKE A TOILET OUTTA DIRT!
EARTH MAGIC IS LITTLE
MISS SQUIRMY'S THING!
BOOM! BLADDER
ISSUE RECTIFIED!
- Miu: COME ON.
NO BIG DEAL.
WE'LL STAND IN THE CORNER
WITH OUR HANDS OVER OUR EARS.
IT'LL BE FINE!
- YEAH. MIGHT EVEN TAKE
YOU DOWN A FEW PEGS.
I'M SO LOVING THIS IDEA.
- SHUT UP! JUST FORGET
ABOUT IT, OKAY?
- ( squirming )
- OKAY. LOOK, I WAS JUST
BUSTING YOUR CHOPS,
BUT I HATE TO SEE
YOU LIKE THIS.
IF NATURE'S CALLING,
ANSWER! LIGHTEN UP.
MAKES YOU FEEL BETTER,
I'LL TAKE THE BLAME.
- THERE YOU GO. SHE'S
ACCEPTED FULL RESPONSIBILITY.
YOU CAN TRUST HER
NOT TO TELL ANYONE.
- Chikage: ABSOLUTELY. WE'RE
ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
ALL FOR ONE
AND ONE FOR ALL!
- YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IF I TRY TO MOVE
FROM THIS SPOT...
I'LL LEAVE A TRAIL.
- NOT DIGGING
ON THE TEARS.
- WELL, IF YOU HAVE A
SOLUTION, WE'RE GAME.
- I DO, ACTUALLY, BUT
YOU MAY NOT LIKE IT.
SEE, IN MY BOOK
WHEN A GIRL'S CRYING,
DRASTIC MEASURES
ARE IN ORDER.
IF YOU LADIES ARE
WILLING TO HELP ME OUT,
I'VE GOT JUST THE THING.
IT'S NOT AN ELEGANT FIX,
THOUGH. YOU STILL GAME?
THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
I NEED YOU TO STAND
ON EITHER SIDE OF HER.
- Miu: ALL RIGHT.
LIKE THIS?
- MMM-HMM.
- ( both gasp )
- WHAT THE HELL?
I CAN'T STAND UP.
- OH, NO!
I HAVE TO GO.
HOW IS THIS SUPPOSED TO HELP?
- I DIDN'T PICK UP ANY MAGIC
FROM THE OTHER SIDE,
BUT I DID LEARN ONE THING.
A TECHNIQUE CALLED
LINKED ENERGY MANIPULATION,
WHICH I SEEM TO
HAVE A KNACK FOR.
SEE, BASICALLY, IT ALLOWS ME
TO REDIRECT THE ENERGY
FLOWING THROUGH YOUR BODIES.
- ( both gasp )
- WAIT, BUT...
WHAT'S OUR KIDNEY'S BURSTING
GOTTA DO WITH HELPING HER?
- ( she screams )
- COME ON, LET THE
GOOD TIMES FLOW, EH?
NO NEED TO HOLD IT IN.
THERE'S NO SHAME IF
YOU ALL HAVE TO GO.
- ARE YOU OUT
OF YOUR MIND?
- IT'S HAPPENING!
- I'M GONNA BLOW!
- BE STRONG, IZUMI!
DON'T GIVE THIS JERK
THE SATISFACTION
OF SEEING YOU URINATE!
- HERE. I'LL GIVE YOU
A LITTLE KICK START.
- ( moans )
- WHAT'S GOING ON IN HERE?
I ASSUME THERE'S A GOOD REASON
THAT THIS DOOR IS LOCKED.
AND THAT YOU'RE INCREDIBLY
RUDE! INSOLENT GIRLS.
- ( sighs )
- WELL, I GUESS THIS ANSWERS
THE QUESTION OF WHETHER OR NOT
HE'S WORTHY OF BEING MY
GUARDIAN. HE'S TOTALLY NOT!
- HEY. THIS WILL NEVER BE
SPOKEN OF, EVERYONE CLEAR?
- Miu: NO WAY! I WON'T
BLAB IF YOU DON'T.
- ME NEITHER. SORRY I
GOT YOU INTO THIS MESS.
- Chikage: WHAT'RE YOU
APOLOGIZING FOR?
FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
IT'S HIS MESS.
I SAY WE LET BYGONES BE
BYGONES BETWEEN US CHICKS.
WE NEED TO POOL OUR RESOURCES
AND MAKE HIS LIFE HELL!
- OF COURSE!
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER, ALL
FOR ONE AND ONE FOR ALL!
- DO YOU MEAN YOU WANT
ME TO BE PART OF THE GROUP?
- Chikage: DAMN
SKIPPY, SWEETHEART.
- Kuzuha: COOL?
- YES! VERY COOL.
THANK YOU, GUYS!
- Chikage: SOMETHING WRONG?
- OH, IT'S NOTHING.
I JUST ZONED OUT.
IF I DIDN'T KNOW BETTER,
I'D SWEAR HE SET HIMSELF
UP AS THE BAD GUY,
SO THE THREE OF
US WOULD BOND.
NAW!
- I AM GETTING THOROUGHLY
SICK OF RUNNING INTO YOU.
AH! YOU ARE AN ANIMAL!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Valkyrie: I BELIEVE AKATSUKI
MENTIONED IN PASSING ONCE,
THAT HE WAS A
STUDENT BACK HOME.
- Listy: IN WHICH CASE I
WEEP FOR HIS ACADEMIC PEERS,
NO DOUBT HE'LL LEAD
THEM OFF A CLIFF.
- Valkyrie: DISASTER
DOES SHADOW HIM.
- Listy: THE IRONY OF IT IS,
THAT THE MAN SCARCELY INTENDS
THE TROUBLE HE STIRS UP.
- Valkyrie: I SUPPOSE FROM
A CERTAIN PERSPECTIVE,
WE MAY CALL THAT
A SAVING GRACE.
- Listy: IF WE MUST.
IF ONE IS INCLINED TO LOOK
PAST HIS TIRELESS AUDACITY!
NEXT EPISODE,
"TO BECOME AN ADULT."
- Valkyrie: UM, HOW DOES
ONE BECOME AN ADULT
WHEN STILL A CHILD?