- WHERE AM I?
- Kuzuha: BABEL'S I.C.U.
- KUZUHA.
- HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
- LIKE I TOOK A HIT.
- Miu: KUZUHA!
- Miu: I'M SORRY, I
DRAGGED YOU INTO THIS.
- DID SHE ESCAPE?
- THEN WE GOTTA GET HER.
- SLOW DOWN.
- YOU'RE NOT READY TO BE UP
AND ABOUT.
I'M SURE SHE'S ALL RIGHT,
SO, TRY TO RELAX.
AKATSUKI SHOWED UP RIGHT AFTER
IT HAPPENED, SO HE'S ON IT.
- HE'LL SAVE HER, YEAH?
- OF COURSE HE WILL. THIS IS
AKATSUKI WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
MEANWHILE, YOU JUST TRY
AND GET SOME REST.
NOW, I BETTER FIND THE DOCTOR.
THEY'LL WANNA KNOW YOU'RE AWAKE.
YOU'RE ONLY IN HERE BECAUSE YOU
PROTECTED ME. I OWE YOU ONE.
- Student 1: SO WHAT'S GOING ON?
- Student 2: WHATEVER IT IS,
THEY SAID IT'S AN EMERGENCY.
- STILL NO LUCK, I KEEP TRYING,
BUT, I JUST CAN'T REACH KYOYA.
- WE CAN'T WAIT ANY LONGER.
I THOUGHT WE COULD
AT LEAST FILL HIM IN
ON THE SITUATION HERE
BUT I GUESS NOT.
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
HOW ARE THINGS COMING
TOGETHER IN THE CONTROL ROOM?
THAT REPAIR WORK NEEDS TO BE
COMPLETED AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
- THEY'RE 60% OF THE WAY THROUGH
GETTING THE SHIELD BACK ONLINE.
- THEY'RE GOING MUCH FASTER
THAN WE HAD EXPECTED THEM TO,
BUT NO MATTER, WE MUST
ACT WHETHER IT'S ON OR NOT.
- ( building rumbles )
- ( low growl )
- Haruka: WHERE IS
IT COMING FROM?
- Minami: OVER THERE.
- WHATEVER IT IS,
IT MUST BE HUGE.
- MAN, YOU'VE GOT
TO BE KIDDING ME.
HOW DID THAT LITTLE CHUMP
EVER FORGE A PACT IN ALAYZARD
WITH AN EVIL DRAGON
THE LIKES OF ZAHHAK?
- ( roars )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( roaring )
- ZAHHAK EXISTS ON A PLANE
BEYOND THAT OF HUMANITY.
THAT PALADIN COULDN'T
HAVE FORMED A PACT WITH IT.
- I GUESS I SHOULD BE IMPRESSED
THAT HE PULLED OFF
THE IMPOSSIBLE.
MAYBE AFTER I BEAT HIM.
- NO, WAIT.
YOU CAN'T SERIOUSLY BE THINKING
OF FIGHTING RIGHT NOW.
- YOU'RE STILL WEAKENED
FROM THE POISON.
- YEAH, I'M AWARE OF THAT.
- BUT HE'S NOT GONNA SIT BACK
AND WAIT FOR ME TO FEEL BETTER,
I'LL CLEAN HIS CLOCK SOMEHOW.
- AKATSUKI, LISTEN TO ME.
YOU'RE THE ONLY
PERSON IN THIS WORLD
WHO HAS A CHANCE OF BEATING HIM,
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
ALL YOUR STRENGTH TO DO IT.
AND THAT MEANS THAT, I'M GOING
TO SERVE AS YOUR DECOY.
I'LL KEEP HIM DISTRACTED
AS LONG AS I CAN.
ONCE YOU'VE RECOVERED,
THEN YOU TAKE OVER.
- MIU, THAT'S CRAZY TALK.
YOU CAN'T FIGHT HIM.
- STUPID POISON.
- COME JOIN ME AS SOON AS
YOU'RE BETTER, OKAY?
DON'T MAKE ME WAIT TOO LONG.
I'M THE ONE YOU
CAME HERE TO KILL.
SO, COME AND GET ME.
- LISTEN UP. CRAZY REPORTS
ARE COMING IN FROM BASE CAMP.
SOMETHING ABOUT A HUGE DRAGON
APPEARING IN THE MOUNTAINS.
THEY SAY IT'S TAKEN TO THE AIR,
AND IT'S HEADED STRAIGHT FOR
THE URBAN TRAINING DISTRICT.
- A DRAGON?
- WHAT IN THE HELL IS GOING
ON OUT THERE?
- DON'T LOSE FOCUS. THE MORE WE
KNOW, THE SAFER THE KIDS ARE.
- I HOPE, YOU'RE UP TO
THIS FIGHT, AKATSUKI.
HELL OF A LOT IS RIDING ON IT.
- ( growls)
- Miu: I'M SORRY,
I DRAGGED YOU INTO THIS.
- IF YOU THINK I'D
LET YOU GO IT ALONE,
THEN YOU DON'T KNOW ME VERY
WELL AT ALL, MIU.
IS THAT AKATSUKI?
- I SEE. SO, YOUR SISTER
IS FIGHTING EVEN AS WE SPEAK?
- YEAH.
- THAT STUFF
HE POISONED YOU WITH,
WILL IT GO AWAY ON IT'S OWN
OR DO YOU NEED AN ANTIDOTE?
- NEITHER, SEE, I'VE CRANKED UP
MY METABOLISM.
IT'S LIKE A CHEAT-CODE THAT
ALLOWS ME TO PROCESS THIS CRAP.
ENERGY MANIPULATION
COMES IN HANDY AGAIN.
THE MOMENT I'M FEELING
BACK TO NORMAL,
I'M KICKING HIS SCALY ASS.
- I'M GLAD TO HEAR THAT.
BUT IN THE MEANTIME...
- ( sighs ) LEMME GUESS.
YOU WANT IN ON THE DECOY THING.
LOOK, YOU ARE A LITTLE BAD-ASS.
BUT HOW CAN I SEND A KID
TO DO MY JOB FOR ME?
- TWO OF US OUT THERE
IS BETTER THAN ONE.
MIU'S ODDS OF SURVIVAL
GO UP THIS WAY.
- Chikage: YOU KNOW, GIRL?
NOT TO ONE-UP YOU,
BUT THREE OF US
WOULD BE BETTER THAN TWO.
AS YOU WERE LEAVING
MY HOSPITAL ROOM,
YOU HAD THIS LOOK IN YOUR EYES,
LIKE YOU WERE GONNA
DO SOMETHING FOOLISH
AND WAY OUTSIDE YOUR PAY-GRADE.
- SO, I GOT OUT OF BED
AND FOLLOWED YOU HERE.
- IZUMI.
YOUR SISTER'S DAMN HOT
AND SHE'S A GOOD FRIEND.
IF SHE NEEDS HELP,
COUNT ME IN.
- WHAT IS WITH YOU
CHICKS TONIGHT?
- I HATE TO BREAK IT
TO YOU, BUDDY,
BUT WE'VE ALREADY
MADE UP OUR MINDS
THAT WE'RE GOING TO HELP MIU.
THAT SAID, WOULD
IT REALLY KILL YOU
TO GIVE US A LITTLE
VOTE OF CONFIDENCE?
- DAMN IT ALL.
FINE, KNOCK YOURSELVES OUT.
BUT DON'T DO ANYTHING
ESPECIALLY DANGEROUS,
OR SO HELP ME I WILL SPANK
THE BOTH OF YOU.
AND THAT GOES DOUBLE
FOR YOU, SHORT-STUFF.
DO I MAKE MYSELF CLEAR?
- YES. WE'LL BE CAREFUL.
LET'S HOP ON, IZUMI.
- RIGHT.
- AW, COME ON.
SHE GETS A RIDE, AND I HAVE
TO WALK TO THE DRAGON?
- YOU'RE STILL POISONED,
YOU SAID SO YOURSELF.
HOW LONG WILL IT TAKE FOR YOU
TO PROCESS WHAT'S LEFT?
- I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I'M PRACTICALLY BETTER...
- YOU NEED TO GIVE ME
A NUMBER, AKATSUKI.
WE NEED TO KNOW EXACTLY HOW
LONG WE HAVE TO HOLD OUT
BEFORE YOU'LL BE BATTLE READY.
- ( sighs )
I GUESS YOU HAVE A POINT.
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
JUST AS I THOUGHT.
LIKE ANY DRAGON,
THIS ONE HAS INBORN
PROTECTIONS AGAINST MAGIC.
- ( roars )
ALL RIGHT THEN,
HOW ABOUT THIS.
- ( groans )
IT NULLIFIED MY MAGIC STAFF
WITH A SINGLE TOUCH.
- ( roars )
- HARUKA, WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- JUST BE GLAD I DIDN'T
GET HERE ANY LATER.
- YEAH, I'LL SAY.
- WHERE'S THAT HOT SHOT BROTHER
OF YOURS, ANYWAY?
HE SHOULD BE THOROUGHLY
ASHAMED OF HIMSELF.
LETTING YOU GO HEAD TO HEAD WITH
A CREATURE OF THIS MAGNITUDE
ALL ON YOUR OWN.
I MEAN, HOW COULD
HE BE SO COWARDLY?
- AKATSUKI'S STILL GETTING OVER
A POISON ATTACK FROM EARLIER.
HE NEEDS A LITTLE MORE TIME TO
RECUPERATE SO HE CAN BE AT 100%.
I'M TRYING TO KEEP
THE DRAGON DISTRACTED
UNTIL HE'S READY TO FIGHT AGAIN.
- FAIR ENOUGH, THEN.
THOUGH I HOPE HE'S NOT OFFENDED
IF WE TAKE CARE OF THIS
THING BEFORE HE WAKES UP.
- Ryohei: HERE WE GO,
DIDN'T THINK I'D BE DOING THIS
WHEN I GOT UP THIS MORNING.
- BE CAREFUL, EVERYONE.
AGAINST A CREATURE
OF THIS MAGNITUDE,
MAGIC WON'T DO ANYTHING.
- THANKFULLY, THAT ONLY
APPLIES TO MAGICAL ATTACKS
THAT AREN'T ANCHORED
TO A PHYSICAL CATALYST,
THESE SHOULD KEEP HIM BUSY.
- ( growls )
- LET'S DO SOME DAMAGE.
- HA.
- ( roars angrily )
- LET'S SEE IF YOUR BARK
IS WORSE THAN YOUR BITE.
IT'S FOUR AGAINST ONE,
SO YOU HAD BETTER GET READY.
- OH, MAN, YOU FELL FOR THAT?
WHOA, NOT GOOD.
- IT'S MY TURN.
WAIT, KUZUHA?
AND CHIKAGE.
- HOW'S IT HANGING?
MIND IF WE TAG IN?
- DON'T EVEN BOTHER.
MAGIC DOESN'T WORK AGAINST IT.
- THEN HOW ABOUT SCIENCE?
- THAT SPELL GATHERS HYDROGEN
FROM THE AIR AROUND IT,
PACKS IT TOGETHER AS TIGHTLY AS
IT CAN, AND LIGHTS IT ON FIRE.
I'M ROCKING THAT DRAGON'S WORLD
WITH SOME NATURALLY
OCCURRING PYROTECHNICS.
LET'S HEAR IT FOR
CHEMISTRY CLASS.
- ( growls )
- THIRTY MINUTES
TILL WE CAN RETREAT.
- HUH?
- THIRTY MINUTES FROM NOW,
YOUR BIG BROTHER WILL
HAVE NEUTRALIZED
THE LAST OF THE POISON.
UNTIL HE DOES,
WE HAVE TO BE STRONG.
- SO, YOU RAN INTO HIM
ON THE WAY OVER?
- UH, HUH. THAT'S RIGHT.
HE WAS WORRIED ABOUT
US GETTING INVOLVED,
BUT HE COULDN'T ARGUE
WITH OUR LOGIC.
- THANK YOU BOTH.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
THIRTY MINUTES LEFT,
WE CAN DO IT.
- ( yells )
- HUH?
- NOT ON MY WATCH.
- I DON'T WANNA PULL MY PUNCHES.
- THEN LET'S GIVE
IT ALL WE'VE GOT.
- ( roars )
- ( grunts )
LET'S HEAT THINGS UP.
- I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN DO IT,
BUT DADDY'S SPECIAL MOVE
COULD BE WHAT WE NEED.
IT'S NOT ENOUGH,
I NEED MORE POWER.
I NEED MORE.
NOW, DIE.
- EVERYONE, ATTACK.
- IT'S A TRAP.
RUN FOR COVER.
- TOO LITTLE TOO LATE.
- WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
OH, NO, PLEASE.
- HOW DOES IT FEEL, WENCH?
HAVING VICTORY WELL
WITHIN YOUR GRASP,
ONLY TO HAVE IT YANKED AWAY
IN THE FINAL MOMENT?
NOW, THEN, YOU'VE HAD YOUR FUN.
IT'S HIGH TIME WE RETURNED
TO ALAYZARD.
- THIS ISN'T OVER.
I'LL NEVER SURRENDER TO
SOMEONE LIKE YOU.
- I ADMIRE YOUR RESOLVE.
EVEN AFTER
SUBJECTING YOUR FRIENDS
AND A SCHOOL FULL OF PEOPLE
WITH WHOM I HAD NO QUARREL,
TO MY DEADLY WRATH, YOU DENY ME.
SHALL I END MORE LIVES THEN?
UNTIL YOUR ATTITUDE GROWS
MORE TRACTABLE?
OR WILL YOU COME QUIETLY?
WHAT WILL IT BE, DARK ONE?
YOU HAVE CHOSEN WISELY.
GO TO YOUR DOOM,
KNOWING THAT YOUR SACRIFICE
PRESERVES THE WORLD
IN WHICH YOU TRIED
TO FIND REFUGE.
- WHY DID YOU FIGHT ME?
YOU COULD NOT WIN.
- NO, MAYBE I COULDN'T.
- BUT, I DON'T CARE.
I HAD TO TRY EITHER WAY.
EVER SINCE MY FATHER DIED,
I'VE BEEN RUNNING AWAY.
RUNNING FROM THE
PAIN OF LOSING HIM
AND FROM MY BIRTHRIGHT.
BUT THEN I STOPPED RUNNING,
THANKS TO AKATSUKI.
- YOUR HUBRIS IS LAUGHABLE.
WHAT COULD THAT MEDDLING
FRAUD POSSIBLY HAVE SAID
TO BUOY YOUR SPIRIT?
- YOU HAVE NO RIGHT
TO SPEAK ILL OF HIM.
FOR ALL HIS FAULTS,
HE'S MORE OF A HERO THAN
YOU COULD EVER HOPE TO BE.
HE'S GENUINE AND HE'S BRAVE,
AND HE DOESN'T CARE WHAT
PEOPLE THINK OF HIM.
EVEN IF YOU DRAG ME
BACK TO ALAYZARD
AND HANG ME FROM
THE HIGHEST TOWER,
YOU WILL NEVER BE A HERO
THE WAY AKATSUKI IS!
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT A SHAM.
A FAKER, WITH ASHES
IN YOUR HEART.
KNOW THIS, NO MATTER HOW MUCH
THE PEOPLE MAY PRAISE YOU,
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT
A THUG WITH A SWORD.
WHEN A WARRIOR RISKS LIFE
AND LIMB TO DO BATTLE
WITH A DARK LORD,
ONLY THEN WILL
THEY BE DEEMED A HERO.
IT IS AN HONOR THEY BESTOW
UPON VALIANT FOES,
FOES LIKE AKATSUKI.
BUT YOU? I'LL NEVER
ACKNOWLEDGE YOU AS A HERO.
N MATTER WHAT SORT OF PAIN
YOU PUT ME THROUGH.
AKATSUKI OUSAWA
IS ALL THE HERO I NEED.
NEXT TO HIM, YOU'RE NOTHING.
- STRANGE HOW YOU HEAP PRAISE
UPON YOUR FATHER'S KILLER
IF HE IS INDEED A HERO,
WHY HAVE YOU NOT SLAIN HIM?
I THOUGHT A DARK LORD
WOULD EXHIBIT
MORE LOYALTY TO HER KIND?
- IT'S TRUE THAT I'M
THE CHILD OF A DARK LORD
BUT MY FATHER WAS THE LAST.
THE PEOPLE OF ALAYZARD DON'T
HAVE TO LIVE IN FEAR ANYMORE.
I DON'T WANT TO FOLLOW
IN MY FATHER'S FOOTSTEPS,
I'M GIVING UP ON ALL THAT.
I JUST WANNA STAY
HERE WITH AKATSUKI
AND LIVE LIKE ANY OTHER
HIGH SCHOOL GIRL.
WHY ISN'T THAT GOOD ENOUGH,
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO DRAG ME BACK?
- DO YOU THINK YOU CAN ABANDON
YOUR PAST SO EASILY?
- I NEVER SAID IT WOULD BE EASY.
BUT I'VE MADE MY CHOICE.
- YOUR LOGIC IS THAT
OF A SOFT-MINDED CHILD.
IF YOU ARE NO DARK LORD, THEN
YOU CANNOT DEEM HIM A HERO,
NO MATTER HOW MUCH YOU
MAY WHINE TO THE CONTRARY.
- YOU MAY BE RIGHT.
BUT I DON'T CARE ABOUT
THE TECHNICALITIES.
HE'S A HERO TO ME, AND
THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS
EVEN IF NO ONE ELSE SEES IT,
HE'S MY KNIGHT IN SHINING ARMOR.
AND THE WORDS DON'T EXIST
THAT'LL CHANGE MY MIND.
- IN THAT CASE, I SUPPOSE
THERE'S NOTHING MORE TO SAY.
- YOU'RE GONNA TAKE ME BACK
TO ALAYZARD HERE AND NOW?
- TO HE WHO HAS FORGED
A PACT WITH A DRAGON,
SUCH A TASK IS SIMPLE.
I CAN'T WAIT TO WATCH YOU DIE,
TALK OF AKATSUKI'S HEROISM
DYING ON YOUR LIPS.
AS YOUR SOUL SPIRALS
INTO THE DARKNESS,
YOU'LL FINALLY REALIZE THAT
NEITHER YOUR WORLD NOR THIS ONE,
HOLDS ANY PLACE FOR YOU.
- I DON'T BELONG IN EITHER
WORLD, I KNOW THAT.
BUT I DON'T CARE ANYMORE.
BECAUSE WHEN I'M WITH HIM,
WHEN I'M WITH AKATSUKI OUSAWA,
I'M IN THE RIGHT PLACE
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOUR
INANE BLATHERING.
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
- YOU CAME FOR ME.
- YEAH.
TAKE THE OTHERS
AND GET TO SAFETY.
- YOU'VE FOUGHT MY BATTLE
FOR LONG ENOUGH.
- PLEASE, BE CAREFUL.
- DON'T WORRY. YOUR FATHER
DIDN'T MAKE A MISTAKE
WHEN HE ENTRUSTED YOU TO ME.
- I'M NOT GONNA LET
YOU DOWN, MIU.
- HMM.
- HOW DISAPPOINTING.
I WAS RATHER HOPING
YOU'D FOLLOW US BACK,
AND I'D GET THE CHANCE
TO CUT YOU OPEN
IN FRONT OF QUEEN LISTY HERSELF.
THE LOOK ON HER FACE
WOULD'VE BEEN PRICELESS.
BUT NO MATTER, KILLING YOU RIGHT
HERE WILL MORE THAN SUFFICE.
- ( grunts )
- HERE'S A LITTLE LOVE-TAP
TO GET THE PARTY STARTED.
SO, NOW YOU'RE TRYING
TO POISON MY SWORD?
FINE. I'VE GOT A FEW
TRICKS UP MY SLEEVE TOO.
LET'S SEE HOW YOU LIKE THEM.
THIS IS GETTING OLD REAL FAST.
- ( grunts )
- BASTARD!
- ( screams )
- WAS THAT SUPPOSED TO HURT?
- COME ON ALREADY.
- IT'S TIME WE BRING
THIS GAME TO AN END.
WHAT THE...
- HUH. LOOKS LIKE MY SURPRISE
IS STARTING TO TAKE EFFECT.
- SO, WHAT IF MY HITS
DIDN'T TAKE ANY OF
THE OOMPH OUT OF YOU?
IT LOOKS LIKE MY ENERGY MADE
IT'S WAY INTO YOUR BODY
JUST FINE, YOU LIKE THAT?
- DON'T DELUDE YOURSELF
INTO THINKING YOUR ATTACKS
ARE EQUAL TO MINE.
- MINE ARE BETTER,
AS YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEE.
BRING IT ON! I'M GONNA DEFLECT
YOUR ATTACK SO HARD,
IT WILL KNOCK YOUR
DAMN TEETH OUT.
- ( growls )
- ( gasps )
- GET OUT OF HERE!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Listy: SAY WHAT YOU WILL,
BUT AKATSUKI BEGRUDGED NO ONE,
WHEN HIS STATUS AS HERO
CAME UNDER DISPUTE.
HE MAY BE SHOWY,
AND LOUD AND BURDENED
WITH A SURFEIT OF LIBIDO,
BUT AS THE PERSON HERE
WHO KNEW HIM BEST,
I BELIEVE THAT AT HIS CORE
HE WILL NEVER WAVER,
NO MATTER HOW DIRE
THE SITUATION.
THERE ARE BELIEFS TO WHICH
THAT MAN SHALL ALWAYS SUBSCRIBE.
HE MUST.
NEXT EPISODE:
"THE WORLD IS WATCHING YOU."
I HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN
THE PROMISE YOU MADE
WHEN WE PARTED WAYS, AKATSUKI.