- ( shuts shower tap )
- Akatsuki: MORNING.
- ( yawning )
- HMPH!
- OKAY.
- Akatsuki: WHERE'S THE FIRE?
HELLO?
ALL RIGHTY.
PREDICTABLE REACTION.
I'M LUCKY SHE HASN'T
PUNCHED ME IN THE CROTCH.
- ( bell ringing )
- ( people chattering )
- Onizuka: SUP, TANAKA?
WAY TO RESERVE MY PLACE.
I'D DO IT MYSELF, BUT
SOMETHING ABOUT WAITING
BRINGS OUT THE WORST IN ME.
- SURE. NO PROBLEM.
- GOT SOMETHING YOU WANNA
SAY ABOUT IT, DICK WEEDS?
- Akatsuki: SUP, ONIZUKA?
THANKS FOR RESERVING MY PLACE.
I'D WAIT MYSELF, BUT
SOMETHING ABOUT LINES
JUST BRINGS OUT THE WORST IN ME.
- ( chuckling )
- YO, TANAKA.
- HEY. YOU DIDN'T
HAVE TO DO THAT.
- NOPE.
- WOW.
- MOVE OVER, ONIZUKA.
THERE'S A NEW SHERIFF IN TOWN.
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU GUYS,
BUT I SMELL LEGEND.
- ( grunting )
THAT BASTARD!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Chikage: SHRIMP, HUH?
DON'T MIND IF I DO.
- THAT'S MINE!
- MMM. MMM.
- HEY.
- WHERE IS KUZUHA?
- I BET SHE'S GETTING
THE THIRD DEGREE.
THE STUDENT COUNCIL TENDS
TO FROWN ON PEOPLE
RUNNING AMOK
ON YOUR WATCH, YOU KNOW?
YUP, POOR THING'S GONNA
HAVE TO ANSWER FOR THE HI-JINX
OF A CERTAIN DOOR-KICKING,
BULLY-BAITING, PANTY-SNATCHING
LOOSE CANNON
WHO SHALL REMAIN NAMELESS.
I'M PRETTY SURE LURING INNOCENT
GIRLS INTO THE EQUIPMENT ROOM
WAS THE FINAL STRAW.
- BUT, I MEAN,
THAT WASN'T ALL HER FAULT.
SHE'S GONNA GET IN TROUBLE
FOR THAT?
- SOUNDS LIKE IT'S
KINDA EATING YOU.
DON'T GET ME WRONG.
I'D BE PRETTY TWISTED
IF THE STUDENT COUNCIL
HAD IT IN FOR MY BIG BROTHER.
- YEAH, I'M NOT SURE
IF THAT'S REALLY IT.
THIS MAY SOUND WEIRD,
BUT I THINK THE AMNESIA MAKES IT
HARD TO SEE HIM AS A BROTHER.
- AH. WELL, NO POINT
IN FORCING IT, I GUESS.
YOUR MEMORIES ARE BOUND TO COME
CRAWLING BACK SOONER OR LATER.
I WOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
MAYBE YOU JUST NEED TO BE
AROUND HIM A WHILE LONGER.
- YEAH. MAYBE.
- OH! THERE SHE IS!
- ( door shuts )
SO. THEY PUT THE SCREWS TO YOU?
- SORRY, BUT,
WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
THAT WOULD BE NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS.
- JEEZ. FINE.
- IF THERE'S ANYTHING WE CAN
SAY TO GET YOU OUT OF THIS,
ALL YOU GOTTA DO IS ASK.
- WHAT IS THAT?
- HMM?
- YOU'RE AWARE THE SCHOOL
BYLAWS STRICTLY PROHIBIT
ACCESSORIZING OF ANY KIND.
- OH! I'M SO SORRY,
I HAD NO IDEA.
IT'S NOT HER FAULT, I GAVE
THAT DOLL TO HER AS A PRESENT
DON'T BE MAD.
- HEY, SOMETIMES A GESTURE
IS WORTH BREAKING THE RULES,
AND SHE MADE ONE FOR YOU, TOO,
SO MAYBE EASE UP.
- I ACCEPT THE GESTURE,
BUT NOT THE PRESENT.
- LOOK, DON'T
TAKE IT PERSONALLY.
SHE'D BE THAT WAY
WITH SANTA CLAUS.
- ( piano music playing )
- HO-HO.
THIS ONE IS DELICATE.
- Kuzuha: ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A LITTLE GIRL
WHO WOKE UP IN A STRANGE
WORLD ALL ALONE.
AFTER SHE'D FOUND HER WAY BACK,
SHE WAS DROPPED INTO A WORLD
JUST AS STRANGE.
ONE WHERE SHE STOOD
OUT LIKE A SORE THUMB.
I'M TOO YOUNG
TO BE HERE ANYWAY.
MAYBE I OUGHT TO
CALL THE COUNCIL'S BLUFF.
- ROOM FOR ONE MORE?
- Akatsuki: SO WHAT'LL
CALL OFF THE DOGS?
- HUH?
- YOU AND ME BOTH KNOW THE
HIGHER UPS HAVE YOU CORNERED.
I'M NOT A DOUCHE.
IT'S MY FAULT
YOU'RE IN THIS MESS.
SO LET ME HELP YOU
GET THEM OFF YOUR BACK.
WHATEVER THEY WANT TO KNOW
ABOUT ME, YOU'VE GOT IT,
FREE OF CHARGE.
LOOK, I'M NOT AN EASY TARGET
FOR SPYING.
IF YOU WANNA REACH
THE CARROT THEY'RE DANGLING
I SUGGEST WE, UH,
YOU KNOW, COME TO TERMS.
- HUMBLING THOUGHT.
AM I THAT TRANSPARENT?
THEY EXPECT A REPORT
EVERY MORNING.
YOUR HABITS,
YOUR MOOD, EVERYTHING.
THE "CARROT" IS ME NOT GETTING
SHIPPED BACK TO MY OLD SCHOOL.
- Akatsuki: AND?
- AND I'M THINKING ABOUT TELLING
THEM EXACTLY WHERE TO SHOVE IT.
- Chikage: LOOK, DON'T
TAKE IT PERSONALLY.
SHE'D BE THAT WAY
WITH SANTA CLAUS.
- HANGING AROUND
WITH A BUNCH OF OLDER KIDS
ISN'T HOW I WANT
TO GROW UP ANYWAY.
WHEN YOU GET RIGHT DOWN TO IT,
I DON'T BELONG HERE.
SEE YOU AROUND.
- NO. YOU'RE NOT A QUITTER.
DON'T PACK YOUR BAGS YET.
- Miu: I APPRECIATE YOU
WALKING HOME WITH ME.
- ( both exclaim )
- EASY, LOVE. I ENJOY AFTERNOON
DELIGHT AS MUCH AS THE NEXT GAL.
BUT, SAVE THE COME-ONS FOR
A BETTER NEIGHBORHOOD, HUH?
- LOOK, SILLY!
- HUH?
- UNLIKELY PAIRING.
OOH! THAT'S NOT
GONNA END WELL FOR HER.
- Miu: WHAT IS THAT PLACE?
"MANGA CAFE WAI-WAI: COUPLE'S
ROOMS, COMPLETE WITH SHOWERS."
- YOU THINK WE SHOULD GO IN?
- YOU BET I DO!
- Kuzuha: THIS IS
OFFICIALLY CREEPY. I'M OUT.
YOU'VE GOT A LOT OF NERVE
DRAGGING ME TO
A PLACE LIKE THIS.
GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME!
I'M GOING HOME!
- SHUT UP.
PEOPLE ARE TRYING TO UNWIND.
GIVE THEM A BREAK, HUH?
- ( Kuzuha groaning )
- LOOK.
PLEASE. WHATEVER
YOU'RE GONNA DO, JUST...
YOU WANNA FIT IN WITH THE COOL
KIDS? THIS IS HOW IT'S DONE.
- Chikage: WELL? YOU HEAR THEM
GETTING IT ON, OR WHAT?
- NOTHING. AT LEAST,
I DON'T THINK SO.
- ( she gasps )
- Chikage: KEEP IT DOWN.
YOU GET TOO LOUD AND THE
OTHER GUESTS WILL GET PISSY.
- STOP IT!
HUH? WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
THIS ISN'T WHY WE'RE HERE!
- OH, WHATEVER, YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO PICKED THIS PLACE OUT.
RELAX, EH?
I ONLY BITE IF YOU ASK.
- THIS... THIS IS EXACTLY
THE KIND OF THING I MEANT
WHEN I SAID I DIDN'T BELONG.
- AGE IS JUST
A NUMBER, SWEETHEART.
- NO.
NO, IT'S NOT.
AGE IS...
AGE IS THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN SOMEONE
WHO CAN TAKE THE
TEMPERATURE OF THE ROOM
AND SOMEONE WHO CAN'T.
- OH, REALLY?
THEN I'M SCREWED.
ESPECIALLY SINCE I'M
ABOUT TO DO THIS TO YOU
WHEN YOU'RE CLEARLY NOT ON
BOARD WITH THE WHOLE IDEA.
TAKING THE TEMPERATURE
OF THE ROOM?
IF THAT WERE TRUE,
THEN ADULTHOOD WOULD
MEAN INDULGING EVERYONE
IN EXACTLY THE KIND OF
PASSIVE AGGRESSIVE BULLSHIT
THAT KEEPS THEM FROM
BEING ABLE TO COMMUNICATE
LIKE ADULTS
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
IT'S NOT ABOUT THAT.
IT'S ABOUT BEING HONEST
WITH YOURSELF.
- Miu: I'M ASKING YOU
NICELY TO STOP.
- Chikage: YEAH, BUT,
NOT SUPER CONVINCINGLY.
NOTHING WRONG BEING
FRIENDS WITH BENEFITS.
- Miu: NO! PLEASE!
- Akatsuki: IF YOU'RE ANGRY,
BE ANGRY.
IF YOU'RE SAD, BE SAD.
- THANK YOU.
I THINK I GET IT NOW.
I HAVE TO LEARN
TO SPEAK UP FOR MYSELF.
THERE'S MORE TO YOU
THAN MEETS THE EYE.
- BE MY GUEST IF YOU WANNA
INCLUDE THAT IN TODAY'S REPORT.
IN FACT, JUST TO SPICE
THINGS UP A LITTLE BIT,
MAKE ME OUT TO BE A TOTAL JERK.
- ( Miu groaning )
- I TOLD YOU
I DON'T WANNA DO THAT.
- Chikage: LIGHTEN UP!
I WAS JUST KIDDING AROUND.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
- Akatsuki: WHAT IS
THIS ALL ABOUT?
- OH, JUST DOING
WHAT FRIENDS DO.
- MIND TELLING US WHAT YOU TWO
ARE UP TO IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
- DID HE TOUCH YOU, KUZUHA?
JUST SO YOU KNOW, IT'S TOTALLY
OKAY FOR YOU TO SMACK HIM!
- IT'S OKAY.
I'M AWARE OF WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE,
BUT ALL HE DID WAS
TEMPORARILY IMMOBILIZE ME.
- YOU BASTARD! UGH!
- SHE'S A LITTLE YOUNG TO BE
"IMMOBILIZED," DON'T YOU THINK?
- PERVERT!
- Kuzuha: HE'LL EXPLAIN
THINGS BETTER THAN I COULD.
SURELY.
- ( Haruka screaming )
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE HAS
THE AUDACITY TO BE LATE
WHEN WE MADE IT EXPRESSLY CLEAR
WHAT WAS AT STAKE SHOULD SHE
TREAT THIS ASSIGNMENT LIGHTLY!
- COME ON, SHE'S NOT THAT LATE.
LET'S JUST CUT HER SOME SLACK.
- I DON'T THINK IT'S WORTH
GETTING UPSET.
- FINE. WE'LL DETERMINE
HER PUNISHMENT LATER.
BUT AS FOR AKATSUKI,
THERE IS NO SLACK!
I WILL NOT STAND BY
AND CONTINUE LETTING HIM
MAKE US LOOK LIKE FOOLS!
- THAT GUY REALLY
GETS UNDER YOUR SKIN.
- IT'S NOT THE END OF THE WORLD
THAT HE SAW YOUR PANTIES.
- SEE THEM?
HE TOOK THEM OFF MY...
IN ANY EVENT, AS OF NOW,
I'M REFERRING HIS CASE DIRECTLY
TO THE DISCIPLINE COMMITTEE.
- ( door opens )
- ( footsteps )
- MR. PRESIDENT!
WE NEED TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT THIS, UH...
- ALL ISSUES RELATING
TO AKATSUKI OUSAWA
ARE TO BE DEALT WITH BY ME.
I TRUST YOU HAVE NO OBJECTIONS?
- LIKE THAT?
- GOOD. THAT'S AN ARMS DEVICE,
OR A.D. FOR SHORT.
WHEN PROPERLY EQUIPPED,
IT'LL MATERIALIZE
IN THE FORM OF WHATEVER WEAPON
BEST SUITS YOUR
SITUATION AND APTITUDE.
YOU CAN CONSCIOUSLY WILL IT
TO VANISH WHEN YOU'RE DONE,
OR, WORST CASE SCENARIO,
IF YOU'RE KNOCKED OUT
IT'LL DO SO AUTOMATICALLY.
- LET ME SEE.
HUH! WELL, THAT WAS EASY.
- AND HOW ABOUT YOU?
ANY LUCK THERE?
- YEAH. NOT SO MUCH.
- YOU HAVE TO REALLY
CONCENTRATE DON'T OVERTHINK IT.
THIS IS NO DIFFERENT
THAN EVERYDAY MAGIC.
- THAT DOESN'T DO US
A LOT OF GOOD.
ME AND MAGIC AREN'T
NECESSARILY BEST PALS.
- ( sighing )
YOU KNOW, I AM SINCERELY
LOOKING FORWARD TO THE DAY
WHEN SOMETHING ABOUT YOU
DOESN'T THROW ME FOR A LOOP.
BEFORE WE START
WITH YOUR COMBAT TRAINING,
I WANT EVERYONE TO SPLIT OFF
INTO TWO GROUPS.
IF YOU WANNA FIGHT AS A TEAM,
GET WITH ONE OR MORE
OF YOUR CLASSMATES
AND HIKE IT TO STADIUM ONE.
IF YOU FEEL LIKE GOING SOLO,
SCARE UP AN OPPONENT AND
STAY RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE.
- ( chattering )
- AH.
- KNOW WHAT? I THINK WE MIGHT
JUST BE THE HOTTEST TEAM HERE.
- DEFINITELY, IF YOU
LET ME JOIN.
- Together: HMPH!
IF THAT'S HOW
IT'S GOTTA BE.
- MAKE ME LOOK BAD
AND IT'S YOUR ASS.
- Akatsuki: ONIZUKA.
- WHAT THE HELL DO YOU WANT?
- YOU WANNA GO?
- YEAH, RIGHT,
LIKE I'D JUST SIGN UP TO HAVE
MY ASS HANDED TO ME.
- SAY YES OR I'LL KILL YOU.
DUDE, DON'T WET YOURSELF. I'M
YANKING YOUR CHAIN, ALL RIGHT?
I CAN'T EVEN USE
A REAL A.D., YOU KNOW.
THEY STUCK ME WITH
THIS PIECE OF CRAP
TILL WE CAN FIGURE OUT
SOMETHING LESS AWKWARD.
MAGIC ISN'T REALLY MY THING.
- WAIT, WHAT?
- SERIOUSLY.
- ( sniggering )
LET'S DANCE.
- Male Instructor: ALL RIGHT.
TODAY, YOU'LL BE SQUARING OFF
WITH CLASS FAVORITE,
THE COCKATRICE.
- ( all exclaim )
- Male student:
AW, I HATE THESE THINGS.
WE EVER GONNA FIGHT
SOMETHING LESS LAME?
- Miu: IS THIS LIKE
THEIR ENTRY LEVEL MONSTER?
- Chikage: KINDA. AT FULL POWER
HE CAN TURN YOU TO STONE,
BUT THEY'VE GOT HIM TURNED
WAY DOWN FOR US.
STAY CLEAR OF THE SHARP PARTS
AND YOU'VE GOT THIS
IN THE BAG, TRUST ME.
Kuzuha: THE CLASS HAS DEALT
WITH THEM SO OFTEN
WE GOT THE STRATEGY DOWN PAT.
IF YOU'RE A MAGE TYPE,
YOU GO WITH RANGE ATTACKS.
IF YOU'RE A FIGHTER TYPE,
WHEN THERE'S AN OPENING,
YOU STRIKE AND RUN.
- MOCK BATTLE COMMENCING,
SHOW ME SOME SPUNK,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN!
- ( cockatrice screeching )
- Male Instructor:
OUSAWA, ONIZUKA, YOU'RE UP!
- DAMN.
I WAS BANKING ON HIM
FIGHTING THIS THING
WITH HIS FRIGGING HAREM
BEFORE MY NUMBER GOT CALLED.
DOESN'T MATTER.
THE BIRD AIN'T MY ONLY WEAPON.
I CAN TAKE HIM OUT MYSELF!
- NOW REMEMBER, THE BARRIER
CONVERTS ANY PHYSICAL INJURY
TO LOW LEVEL
BIO FEEDBACK SIGNALS
THAT MIMIC EMOTIONAL
DISTRESS IN YOUR AMYGDALA.
ENOUGH DAMAGE
WILL CAUSE YOU TO PASS OUT,
SO FOCUS ON ECONOMY OF MOVEMENT.
- LET'S DO IT.
- Male Instructor:
KEEP IT CLEAN, GUYS!
- ( chuckling )
OH, MAN, THAT WAS TOO EASY!
- OBVIOUSLY, ONIZUKA HERE
THOUGHT HIS BEST CHANCE TO WIN
WAS BY STARTING HIS SPELL BEFORE
I GAVE THE OKAY TO BEGIN. RIGHT?
- HEY, IN THE REAL WORLD,
FAIR PLAY GETS YOU DIDDLY.
- Akatsuki: ALL'S FAIR
IN LOVE AND WAR, RIGHT?
NOT THAT IT MATTERS
WHEN YOUR TIMING IS CRAP.
- ( shouting )
- ( swords clang )
- SO, THAT IT FOR YOU, THEN?
BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW HOW
LONG I CAN WATCH THIS
BEFORE I KICK YOUR ASS!
- ( he whimpers )
WHOA. NAP TIME ALREADY?
- I WARNED HIM TO FOCUS
ON ECONOMY OF MOVEMENT.
HE REALLY ONLY
HAS HIMSELF TO BLAME.
- SO UNFAIR.
WHY DOES THIS THING
WORK FOR HIM?
IT'S LIKE I'VE BUILT UP A
TOLERANCE FOR THEM OR SOMETHING.
MATTER OF FACT, LET ME
JUST TEST THAT OUT.
MAYBE THESE THINGS
DON'T HAVE ENOUGH JUICE.
NO WAY!
- ( cockatrice screeching )
- WHAT THE?
IT'S NEVER BEEN THIS
STRONG BEFORE!
- Miu: COACH, THIS IS DANGEROUS!
- I KNOW, I KNOW!
I'M TRYING TO SHUT IT DOWN, BUT
THE SECURITY SYSTEM IS OFFLINE!
EVERYONE, TAKE COVER!
THIS IS UGLY, SOMEONE'S
HACKED INTO THE MAINFRAME.
- DO WHAT YOU HAVE TO
I CAN BUY US A FEW SECONDS.
- BRING IT ON!
WHEW, THAT WAS
A CLOSE ONE, HUH?
- UH, THANK YOU,
MUCH APPRECIATED.
I SUGGEST YOU MAKE A RUN FOR IT.
- HERE WE GO WITH THE
SELF-RIGHTEOUS MARTYRDOM THING.
- CAN YOU PLEASE NOT ARGUE
WITH ME FOR ONCE?
- THERE'S NO ARGUMENT.
WE'RE NOT ABANDONING
YOU AND THAT'S THAT.
- YEAH. AND DON'T GO THINKING
WE'RE DOING THIS FOR YOU,
IT'S JUST THAT WE'RE NOT GONNA
LET YOU BE THE ONLY HERO, MISSY.
- MAYBE I REALLY
DO BELONG HERE.
- CRAZY WAY TO FIND OUT.
- IZUMI? OUSAWA?
LET'S HANDLE IT.
- HEY. CHECK YOU OUT!
- YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD REALLY
SHOW THAT SMILE MORE OFTEN.
- STOP IT.
I THINK NOW MIGHT BE A GOOD
TIME TO EVACUATE EVERYONE ELSE.
- OF COURSE.
I WANT EVERYONE MOVING
CALMLY TOWARD STADIUM TWO.
- UGH! AT THIS RATE OUR
MAGIC WILL BE TAPPED
BEFORE WE CAN SUBDUE HIM.
- THEN WE'RE JUST GONNA HAVE TO
FOCUS WHATEVER WE'VE GOT LEFT
AND HIT FUGLY WHERE IT HURTS.
SOUND LIKE A PLAN TO YOU, CHIEF?
- YEAH.
THREE. TWO. ONE.
ZERO!
- BULL'S EYE!
- I WOULDN'T CELEBRATE YET.
- NOT TO BE NEGATIVE,
BUT I THINK WE JUST MADE
THINGS CONSIDERABLY WORSE.
- Chikage: HOORAY US. WAY TO
LET HIM FEED OFF OUR POWER.
- ( cockatrice screeching )
- LOOK OUT!
- IZUMI! KUZUHA, NO!
- ( cockatrice roars )
- THE BARRIER IS SUPPOSED TO
PROTECT US FROM PHYSICAL DAMAGE.
THIS SHOULDN'T EVEN BE POSSIBLE.
HOW IS IT TURNING
EVERYONE TO STONE?
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING BEFORE
IT SMASHES THEM TO PIECES.
I WON'T LET THEM DIE.
NO! I WON'T LET YOU!
- Akatsuki: SORRY IT TOOK ME
SO LONG. YOU'RE GOOD, RIGHT?
TRY THIS ONE ON FOR SIZE.
- YOU DID IT!
UH-OH.
- YOU JUST HAD TO GO
AND PUSH YOURSELF.
HEY, YOU KICKED
SOME MAJOR ASS.
HOW ABOUT YOU REST
AND LEAVE THE KILL SHOT TO ME?
- CAREFUL! EVERY TIME
YOU THROW A SPELL AT IT,
THE STUPID THING JUST SEEMS
TO SOAK UP THE ENERGY.
- OH, IS THAT ALL?
COULD BE WORSE.
I JUST HAVE TO MAKE THIS COUNT.
HEY, BIRD!
BRING IT!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Listy: EAGER TO PROVE
HIS METTLE
AS A CREDIT TO THE WARRIOR
AESTHETIC OF ALAYZARD,
THE ROGUE STOOD
AT THE FOREFRONT OF BATTLE,
LEADING THE CHARGE.
AN ARMY AT HIS BACK,
HE INSPIRED BY ACTION
RATHER THAN WORD.
EACH WARRIOR PROUD
TO FIGHT ALONGSIDE HIM.
'TIS A GIFT, ROUSING COURAGE
WITH MERELY A LOOK.
NEXT EPISODE, "THE HERO'S BACK"
HIS APPETITES ARE SUSPECT,
BUT LET THERE BE
NO QUESTION OF HIS VALOR.