- IT LOOKED LIKE MORE FABRIC
ON THE HANGER!
- Chikage: HEY, SLOWPOKE!
WE PICKED OUT OUR SWIMSUITS,
SO WE'RE GOOD TO GO.
HURRY UP, OKAY?
- Kuzuha: WE'LL WAIT
FOR YOU OUTSIDE!
- WAIT, YOU'RE LEAVING?
COME ON, SELF, YOU CAN DO THIS!
- ( rattling )
- OH, MY GOODNESS.
- Volk: SO, IT APPEARS THERE'S
NO LONGER ANY ROOM FOR DOUBT.
THE DARK LORD GARIUS
HAS MET HIS DOOM.
BUT THERE ARE THOSE
WITHIN HIS CURSED CLAN
WHO WOULD STILL DO US INJURY.
AND WE CANNOT ALLOW
THIS CANKER TO GROW.
WE MUST QUELL THIS REBELLION
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
- WELL SAID.
KNOW THAT THE SHELLFEED
KINGDOM HAS NO OBJECTIONS
TO THAT WHICH YOU
PROPOSE, EMPEROR...
FOR THE SAKE OF
PEACE IN OUR WORLD,
WE WILL PLEDGE OUR
SWORD TO THIS FIGHT.
- MMM.
AND YOU, LORD BARAM.
WHAT SAY YOU?
- I WILL STAND FAST WITH YOU
ON THIS DECISION, YOUR HOLINESS.
- BUT I THINK WE HAVE
A BIGGER PROBLEM.
THE FATE OF THE
DARK LORD'S CHILD.
SHE HAD GONE TO GROUND,
BUT I HAVE DISCOVERED
WHERE SHE'D BEEN HIDING
IN THE DAYS SINCE HIS DEATH.
WE CANNOT AFFORD TO SIT IDLE.
WE MUST SEND A SEARCH PARTY
TO APPREHEND HER IMMEDIATELY.
- WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
SINCE HIS DEATH,
MOST OF GARIUS'S CLANSMEN
HAVE KEPT TO THEMSELVES
DEEP WITHIN THE DARKNESS
OF GALEPANE FOREST.
TARGETING HIS DAUGHTER WILL ONLY
SERVE TO PROVOKE THEIR ANGER.
- YOU WOULD HAVE
US DO NOTHING?
SO LONG AS THE DARK
LORD'S HEIR IS ALIVE,
WE MUST WAIT FOR THE VENGEANCE
THEY WILL UNDOUBTEDLY SEEK OUT.
- YOU MAY BE RIGHT, BUT EVEN SO.
- YOUR MAJESTY,
IT IS TRUE
THAT GARIUS'S DAUGHTER
HAS DONE US NO WRONG.
BUT THERE IS WISDOM
IN WHAT LORD BARAM SAYS.
THE GIRL'S VERY EXISTENCE IS A
THREAT TO THE NEWFOUND PEACE
SO MANY HAVE FOUGHT
AND DIED FOR.
- I KNOW.
- WELL, ALL RIGHT, THEN. IT
SEEMS WE'VE REACHED AN ACCORD.
LORD BARAM, YOU BELIEVE
THE DARK LORD'S DAUGHTER
HAS LEFT GALEPANE
FOREST, CORRECT?
- THAT'S RIGHT. NOT ONLY
HAS SHE LEFT GALEPANE,
BUT I BELIEVE SHE'S
DEPARTED ALAYZARD ITSELF.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Haruka: HONESTLY, NOW!
- GOTTA STOP COMPLAINING
ABOUT IT EVENTUALLY.
- VERY FUNNY! YES,
THEY GAVE US SOME DOWN-TIME
BEFORE THE RANKING MATCHES,
BUT WE STILL HAVE OTHER
EXAMS TO PREP FOR!
- CALM DOWN. IT'S
OUTTA OUR HANDS.
THE FAMILY OF THE
GIRL WE RESCUED
WANTED TO THANK US
FOR OUR BRAVERY
WITH A FUN-IN-THE-SUN
GETAWAY, SO HERE WE ARE.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN RUDE TO
TURN 'EM DOWN. YOU EVEN SAID SO.
I KNOW I DID, BUT STILL.
- HARUKA, DO YOU NOT ENJOY
THE BEACH OR SOMETHING?
- NO, THE BEACH ITSELF
IS FINE. I JUST DON'T...
- HEY, DON'T FORGET,
YOU TOLD THE GIRL'S MOM OUSAWA'S
THE ONE WHO REALLY SAVED HER.
IT'S ONLY NATURAL HE'S GONNA
GET INVITED ON OUR BEACH TRIP.
FACE IT, HARUKA, YOU
DID THIS TO YOURSELF.
- HEY! SORRY FOR THE WAIT!
- AH! THERE YOU ARE!
- YOU'RE A GUY.
DO OUR SUITS MEET WITH
YOUR MANLY APPROVAL?
- YEAH! ON BEHALF OF ALL MEN,
I GIVE YOU LADIES
TWO THUMBS WAY UP.
BUT AREN'T WE MISSING SOMEONE?
- DON'T YOU WORRY,
SHE'S RIGHT HERE.
- YOUR SISTER FEELS A LITTLE
SELF CONSCIOUS, THAT'S ALL.
SHOW 'EM THE GOODS!
- HERE GOES.
UH, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- WELL, I'M SURE
NOT COMPLAINING.
BUT IF YOU'RE SO
UNCOMFORTABLE WEARING IT,
WHY'D YOU CHOOSE IT
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
- SHE HAD A BIT OF TROUBLE
PICKING OUT A SUIT.
THEN SHE JUST
CLOSED HER EYES
AND SNAPPED THIS
ONE UP AT RANDOM!
- THERE'S NO NEED TO
BLUSH. CHECK IT OUT!
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'RE
THE ONLY GIRL ON THE BEACH
WHO'S SHOWING SOME SKIN.
IT'S NOTHIN' TO BE
EMBARRASSED ABOUT.
- SO, IT'S OKAY?
- UH-HUH!
JUST LEMME KNOW IF ANY OF THE
GUYS START CREEPIN' YOU OUT.
- CREEPIN' ME OUT? HEY!
- ( laughing )
SHALL WE, LADIES?
- YOU'RE COMING WITH
US, AREN'T YOU, MIU?
- YEAH! YOU GO
ON AHEAD, I'LL CATCH UP.
UH... HI.
- OH, IT'S YOU.
- SINCE WE'RE ALL HERE,
I THOUGHT MAYBE YOU'D
LIKE TO HANG OUT WITH US!
- NO. WE DON'T WANNA
IMPOSE ON YOU.
- Ryohei: DON'T BE SUCH
A STICK IN THE MUD.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
THE GIRL'S INVITATION?
- UM, REALLY THAT'S OKAY.
RYOHEI, IN CASE YOU HAVEN'T
NOTICED I DON'T WANNA GO!
- GIMME ONE GOOD REASON WHY
YOU SHOULD BLOW HER OFF THEN.
- YOU WANT A REASON?
HOW ABOUT SHE'S OUSAWA'S SISTER?
- YOU'RE WAY TOO HUNG
UP ON THAT GUY, HARUKA.
IT MIGHT BE NICE TO IRON
OUT SOME OF THE DRAMA
BETWEEN YOU TWO.
- Haruka: HE'S BEEN NOTHING
BUT AN INSUFFERABLE SHOW-OFF
SINCE THE DAY HE...
- HE SAVED THAT LITTLE GIRL,
RIGHT?
GOING OUT OF YOUR WAY TO
AVOID HIM IS GONNA LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE JEALOUS THAT
HE STOLE YOUR SPOTLIGHT.
DON'T WANNA SEEM PETTY.
BUT YOU CAN DO WHATEVER YOU
WANNA. YOU'RE A BIG GIRL.
- FINE, THEN! I'M SO SORRY
TO HAVE MADE YOU WAIT.
IF THE OFFER STILL STANDS, WE
WOULD LOVE TO HANG OUT WITH YOU.
- OF COURSE!
- HEY, WHAT'S THE
HOLD-UP, YOU TWO?
IF WE'RE GOING TO DO
THIS, THEN LET'S GO.
ABOUT THAT. I THINK I'M GONNA
STAY HERE AND WATCH OUR STUFF.
- Haruka: HUH?
- WHAT ABOUT YOU, MINAMI,
YOU IN?
- Minami: NO CAN DO.
WORKING ON MY TAN.
- GUESS YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
- WHAT? SO I HAVE TO GO
BY MYSELF? YOU SET ME UP!
- IT'S ALL GOOD.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S HARBORING
A MAJOR BEEF AGAINST OUSAWA,
SO YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
NEEDS TO HANG OUT WITH HIM.
- ( chuckling )
- ( giggling )
- TAKE THIS!
- YOU GOT IT, MIU!
- YOU SURE THIS IS THE WAY BACK
TO THE BEACH HOUSE, CHIKAGE?
- YEAH, I THINK SO.
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- MAYBE THEY'RE ABOUT TO
HOLD A CONCERT OUT HERE.
- Motoharu: NOPE. SORRY!
IT'S NOT A CONCERT,
BUT IT'S DEFINITELY
WORTH STICKING AROUND.
- HUH?
- AKKI! HOW'S IT HANGING?
- JUST GETTING SOME SUN.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
- Motoharu: MAKING SOME COIN,
BELIEVE IT OR NOT.
CAME TO THE BEACH TODAY
ON MY PART-TIME JOB.
- ISN'T HE THE ONE WITH THE
HUGE MAN-CRUSH ON YOUR BROTHER?
- YEAH.
- LADIES, ALLOW ME TO INTRODUCE
YOU TO MOTOHARU KAIDOU.
HE'S KIND OF
A LONE WOLF, I GUESS.
- BETTER THAN WHAT I USUALLY
GET CALLED. AND TOTALLY TRUE!
YEAH, LIKE HE SAID, THE NAME'S
MOTOHARU. ME AND HIM ARE BUDS!
PLEASED TO MEET YOU!
- SO, WHAT'S THIS
PART-TIME JOB, ANYWAY?
- YOURS TRULY
IS ON THE EVENT STAFF!
- JUST WHAT IN THE WORLD
AM I LOOKING AT HERE?
- REALLY, YOU'VE
NEVER HEARD OF IT?
THEY HOLD THIS BEACH SWIMSUIT
TAG EVENT EVERY YEAR.
THEY AIR IT ON PAY-PER-VIEW
TV, AND THERE'S A CASH PRIZE.
IT'S KIND OF A BIG DEAL!
- HELL, I'D WATCH IT!
- SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
AND IT SAYS HERE THAT
THERE'S NO ENTRY FEE.
- SO WHAT DO YOU SAY?
WANNA GIVE IT THE OLD
COLLEGE TRY THERE, AKKI?
- Akatsuki: SURE. SOUNDS LIKE
A GOOD WAY TO KILL SOME TIME.
YOU FEELIN' LUCKY, GIRLS?
- HMM. IT IS TEMPTING.
- WELL, I'LL DO IT!
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
- I DON'T WANT THEM TO THINK
I'M SOME SHY LITTLE GIRL.
I CAN BE FUN TOO!
- WELL, IF MIU'S GONNA DO IT,
THEN COUNT ME IN!
- OKAY. ME TOO! BUT WHAT
ABOUT OUR VICE-PRESIDENT?
- HUH? FINE!
IF I'M GOING TO
FRATERNIZE WITH YOU
I SUPPOSE I'VE NO CHOICE
BUT TO SEE IT THROUGH
TO THE BITTER END!
WHO'S READY FOR SOME TAG?
MAKE SOME NOISE, 'CAUSE THE
BEACH SWIMSUIT TAG EVENT
IS ABOUT TO GO LIVE,
PARTY PEOPLE!
EARLIER, WE HAD YOU
FINE-LOOKIN' FOLKS
STICK NUMBER-TAGS
ONTO YOUR SWIMSUITS.
NOW WE'RE GONNA HOLD A
DRAWING TO PICK THE TARGET
AND WE'RE CHANGING THINGS
UP A BIT THIS YEAR!
WHOEVER COMES BACK
HOLDING THE TARGET'S SUIT
AT THE END OF THE
HOUR IS THE WINNER!
LADIES, IT'S ALL GOOD!
ONLY THE GUYS' NUMBERS WENT
INTO THE DRAWING, SO CHILL!
YOUR T AND A ARE SAFE
WITH US! AND HERE WE GO!
- GET READY!
- ROLLING THE GRAPHIC!
- CROSS YOUR FINGERS, FELLAS.
- WAIT. SO IT'S ME?
- CONGRATULATIONS, 88!
YOU'VE WON A FUN-FILLED HOUR
OF RUNNING AS FAST AS YOU CAN
FROM EVERYONE AROUND YOU!
- WELL, AT LEAST FOUR OF
'EM WILL BE ON MY SIDE.
RIGHT, GIRLS?
- WE'RE GONNA GIVE YOU
A TEN SECOND HEAD START!
YOU'RE ALLOWED TO GO
WHEREVER YOU WANT,
SO LONG AS IT'S ON THE BEACH!
CHANGING ROOMS, BEACH HOUSES,
THEY'RE ALL IN BOUNDS.
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH IT
AS FAR AS RULES GO.
IT'S YOU VERSUS EVERYONE, 88,
SO DO WHATEVER YOU GOTTA!
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO
TELL ME TWICE.
AND NOW THAT YOU ALL
KNOW WHAT I LOOK LIKE,
TIME TO GTFO!
- WE'RE STARTING THAT TEN-SECOND
TIMER! GOOD LUCK TO YA!
- HEY, MINAMI, HOW COME
YOU'RE SO GUNG-HO
ABOUT GETTING ALL GOLDEN
TAN ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- PEOPLE KEEP TELLING ME
THAT I'M TOO PALE.
I'M JUST TIRED OF THEM ASKING ME
IF I'VE COME DOWN
WITH SOMETHING.
- IF YOU COME HOME
WITH TOO MUCH COLOR,
THEY'LL THINK YOU
WERE UP TO SOME
CRAZY BEACH SIDE SHENANIGANS
WHILE YOU WERE HERE.
- SO EITHER WAY,
YOU'RE KINDA SCREWED.
- IT'S A CONUNDRUM.
- WHERE ARE YOU OFF TO?
- RINSING OFF MY SUNTAN OIL.
WHITE IT IS.
- OKAY, THEN.
YOU HAVE FUN WITH THAT.
HM?
- Akatsuki: THIS REMINDS ME
OF THE FUN I USED TO HAVE
WITH VALKYRIE AND THE GIRLS.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO
FOR AN HOUR?
JUST RUN AROUND AND KEEP THEM
FROM GETTING ME BARE-ASSED?
HEY, WAIT A SEC.
THE RULES ONLY SAID THAT
WHOEVER HAS MY TRUNKS
AT THE END OF THE
HOUR IS THE WINNER.
NOT THAT I HAVE TO RUN.
- TAKE THIS!
- GIVE ME THE SUIT!
- YOU HEARD HER!
- YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY.
WHAT'S GOOD FOR THE GOOSE
IS GOOD FOR THE GANDER.
IF YOU'RE GONNA TRY SOMETHING AS
BARBARIC AS SWIPING MY SWIMSUIT
I'M COOL WITH PULLING
TIT FOR TAT!
- THAT WENT WELL!
- WE GOTCHA!
- JUST KNOW THAT IF YOU'RE
GONNA GET ALL GRABBY WITH ME,
MY GRAB-FU IS STRONG!
- YOU DON'T THINK SOMEBODY'S
ALREADY GOTTEN THEM, DO YOU?
- I CAN'T IMAGINE YOUR BROTHER
RELINQUISHING HIS SWIM-TRUNKS
SO EARLY IN THE HOUR.
- ( people screaming )
- WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
- WEREN'T THOSE SOME OF
THE FOLKS CHASING AKATSUKI?
- WE'VE GOT TROUBLE.
- Baram: INDEED WE DO.
- INTO ANOTHER WORLD?
LORD BARAM, DO YOU SUGGEST
THAT THE DARK LORD'S DAUGHTER
HAS TRAVELED THROUGH
THE OTHERWORLD GATE?
AS YOU KNOW,
ONLY THOSE FROM OTHER LANDS
CAN EMPLOY THAT MEANS.
- I AGREE. YOUR THEORY
HAS MERIT, SIR,
BUT IT GOES AGAINST EVERYTHING
WE KNOW ABOUT THESE PORTALS.
- NOT AT ALL. AS QUEEN LISTY
WAS SO KIND TO REMIND US,
ONLY THOSE WHO TRAVEL HERE
FROM BEYOND ALAYZARD
CAN MAKE USE OF THE GATE.
AND MAKE USE OF IT HE DID.
- HE WHO? WAIT.
SURELY YOU DON'T MEAN...
- THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS CRISIS IS AKATSUKI'S DOING.
- ( sighs )
- THIS GAME IS CRAP. INSTEAD OF
US GETTING A PEEK AT HIS JUNK,
HE'S GETTIN' PEEKS
AT EVERYONE ELSE'S!
I DIG IT IN PRINCIPLE,
BUT COME ON!
- I DON'T MEAN TO
ALARM ANY OF YOU
BUT WE'RE THE ONLY GIRLS
WHO STILL HAVE TOPS.
- WE'VE ALL SEEN THE WAY HE
FIGHTS AGAINST MALE OPPONENTS.
HOW'S ANYONE THAT STRONG
SO QUICK WITH HIS HANDS?
- CHICKS IN A TWO-PIECE
ARE AN EASY MARK.
I COULD'VE TOLD YOU THAT.
- SO, WHAT DO WE DO?
HE'S COMING FOR US.
YOU KNOW HE IS.
LISTEN, YOU AND THE VP
GO HIDE SOMEWHERE.
KUZUHA AND I CAN TAKE
CARE OF STICKY FINGERS.
BACK WHILE EVERYONE
WAS CHARGING AT 'EM,
SHE AND I MADE
SOME PREPARATIONS,
IF YA CATCH MY DRIFT.
- ON SECOND THOUGHT,
STAY FOR THE FUN. HE'S HERE.
- FOUND YA, GIRLS. HUH?
- SORRY, PERVERT! TIME TO EVEN
THE ODDS WITH SOME MAGIC!
- LITTLE KUZUHA'S AN EARTH TYPE,
AND I LIKE TO ROCK THE H2O.
YOU'RE FIGHTIN' THE HOME TEAM.
KISS THOSE SHORTS GOODBYE!
- ( scoffs ) SHOW ME
WHAT YOU GOT!
- I'LL BE TAKIN' THAT!
- I DON'T THINK SO!
- OWW!
- TRAPS ARE ONE OF THE MANY
PERKS OF BEING THE HOME-TEAM.
- NOW ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS RUN DOWN THE CLOCK
UNTIL THE HOUR IS UP
AND OUR SWIMSUITS
WILL BE SAFE AND SOUND.
OR IF YOU'RE FEELING BALLSY,
WE COULD MAKE A GRAB
FOR THOSE TRUNKS.
SPLIT THE PRIZE MONEY TWO WAYS?
- HOW ABOUT THREE? I THINK WE'LL
NEED MIU'S HELP TO GET THEM OFF.
HE'S GONE!
CHIKAGE!
THAT WAS DESIGNED TO FALL
IN ON YOU! HOW'D YOU ESCAPE?
- Akatsuki: I CAN WALK ON WATER,
FOR CRYIN' OUT LOUD.
YOU THINK SAND'S GONNA
HARSH MY MELLOW?
NOW, THEN. THAT'S A REAL
NICE ONE-PIECE YOU'VE GOT.
- Y-YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
- HEY, WHERE'S THE FAITH?
I'VE PULLED OFF TOUGHER
ONES THAN THAT.
I'LL HAVE YOU OUTTA THAT
WITHOUT RIPPING A STITCH!
- HEY, NOW!
COOL YOUR JETS, COMPADRE!
THEY'RE GONNA AIR THIS THING
ON PAY-PER-VIEW, REMEMBER?
I KNOW A LITTLE JIGGLE
MAKES THE RATINGS GO AROUND,
BUT THEY'RE GONNA CAN US
IF YOU START GOING
FULL PEDO-BEAR.
- OH, YEAH. YOU DID SAY
SOMETHING ABOUT A TV PROGRAM.
YOU'RE PRETTY FAST FOR A DUDE
AT THE BEACH IN SANDALS, I MEAN.
- WELL, I CAN'T RUN ON THE OCEAN
LIKE SOME PEOPLE, BUT I DO OKAY.
ALL RIGHT! FORTY MINUTES DOWN,
TWENTY TO GO. WHAT'S THE PLAN?
- NOBODY LIKES A QUITTER, RIGHT?
WELL THEN, LET'S GO GET
SOME GIRLS NAKED.
MAN, IF THERE ARE ANY GIRLS
OUT THERE STILL PLAYING THE GAME
THEY'D BETTER RUN.
- HMM. SO IT'S COME DOWN
TO YOU VERSUS AKATSUKI, HUH?
AT LEAST THEY'RE HANGING OUT.
- HEY.
- HARUKA?
- MINAMI? WHAT'RE YOU DOING
IN THE SHOWERS?
- I'M RINSING OFF
THIS SUNTAN LOTION.
ISN'T THAT WHAT
YOU'RE DOING IN HERE?
- YEAH! LOOK AT THIS SAND.
I'D BETTER GET CLEAN ASAP!
- THEY DID SAY BUILDINGS ON
THE BEACH WERE FAIR GAME.
SO TOO BAD FOR HIM IF HE
DOESN'T THINK TO LOOK HERE.
- ( door opens )
- HEY. THERE YOU ARE.
THIS SHOULD BE OLD HAT
TO YOU BY NOW, RIGHT?
- HA! HOLD IT!
STATE FOR THE RECORD
WHERE YOU ARE RIGHT NOW!
- UH, IN A SHOWER-ROOM
FULL OF NAKED, WET WOMEN?
- Haruka: CORRECT!
WHICH I'M SURE IS A
DISQUALIFIABLE OFFENSE!
- OH, I WOULDN'T COUNT ON
THAT IF I WERE YOU.
THAT HOST CHICK SAID I COULD GO
ANYWHERE ON THE BEACH I WANTED
AND SHE DIDN'T SAY NO BUILDINGS.
- BUT THEY CAN'T LET YOU
DO THAT, IT'S ILLEGAL.
- SURE, AND TWENTY
MINUTES FROM NOW
IF YOU STILL SEE
ME STANDIN' HERE,
FEEL FREE TO CALL THE COPS.
UNTIL THEN, THE RULES OF
SWIMSUIT TAG SAY IT'S ALL GOOD.
- I DUNNO, MAN.
- THAT'S A PRETTY
CONVOLUTED INTERPRETATION
OF THE RULES, AKKI.
THOUGH I GOTTA ADMIT,
I'M GETTING SOME GREAT
FOOTAGE OUT OF THIS.
HEY!
- IF YOU THINK YOU'RE GETTING
MY TOP AS EASILY AS THE OTHERS,
YOU'RE IN FOR A DISAPPOINTMENT!
- THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
I'M IN THE MOOD FOR A CHALLENGE!
- MUCH BETTER.
- OOH.
- YES! VICTORY IS MINE!
- OOPS-A-DAISY.
- WELL. I'M NOT GOING TO
THANK YOU, SO THERE.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
THESE ARE THANKS ENOUGH.
- WHAT ARE?
( screaming )
- SWIMSUIT GET!
- GIVE 'EM BACK! IMMEDIATELY!
- STANDING UP JUST
SHOWS ME EVERYTHING, YOU KNOW.
- HUH? YOU DIDN'T TAKE
ANY OTHER BOTTOMS, SO WHY MINE?
- JUST FELT LIKE IT.
- ARGH!
- I HAD FUN HANGING OUT.
LET'S DO IT AGAIN!
- Haruka: YOU GET BACK HERE,
AKATSUKI OUSAWA!
- HE'S NEVER GONNA FIND ME
WAY OUT HERE.
- 'SUP.
- HUH?
YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
- I CAN SENSE YOUR ENERGY
FROM A MILE AWAY, YOU KNOW THAT.
SO, HOW THEY HANGING?
- ( burbling )
- THANKS FOR THE HELP.
- HEY, NOW, JUST BEING A HERO.
THE PLEASURE WAS ALL MINE.
- WHAT KIND OF A HERO
GRABS A GIRL LIKE THIS?
- DON'T FORGET, YOU
DID ALMOST DROWN
TRYING TO KEEP THEM
COVERED YOURSELF.
I'M MERELY TAKING
TWO FOR THE TEAM.
- YOU KNOW THERE'S
A BETTER WAY TO DO THAT!
- ACTUALLY, I THINK
YOU'RE RIGHT. VOILA!
THIS FABRIC'S WAY TOO SLIPPERY.
THE BEST WAY TO GET A FIRM GRIP
IS TO GO UNDERNEATH IT
AND OPT FOR SKIN-ON-SKIN.
- ( screaming )
YOU'RE AWFUL!
- Announcer: THAT'S IT,
PARTY PEOPLE!
THE HOUR OF TAG IS UP!
UNFORTUNATELY FOR OUR TARGET,
THE WATER ITSELF
IS OUT OF BOUNDS!
SORRY, 87 AND 88,
BUT WE GOTTA DISQUALIFY YOU!
NO ONE WINS THE
CASH MONEY THIS YEAR!
- HUH? DISQUALIFIED?
OH, NO! I'M SORRY
I MADE YOU LOSE.
- AT LEAST I'M WALKING AWAY
WITH THE BOOBY PRIZE!
WASN'T RION THE DESIGNER WHO
MADE THOSE SEE THROUGH UNDIES
THAT FREAKED YOU OUT?
- WAIT, CAN YOU SEE EVERYTHING?
- THIS OUGHT TO KEEP
YOU COVERED UP.
MAKE SURE THAT YOU
HOLD ON TIGHT NOW.
'CAUSE HERE WE GO!
- I ASK YOU TO MAKE A LIFE
WITH WHOMEVER ENDS ME.
- I'M SORRY, DAD,
BUT I DON'T THINK I CAN DO IT.
I MEAN, HE'S A HERO AND I'M...
- Miranda: THE
DARK LORD'S DAUGHTER.
AND WE'RE TO BELIEVE
THAT AKATSUKI, OF ALL PEOPLE,
SPIRITED HER
AWAY TO HIS REALM?
LORD BARAM SEEMED SO SURE,
BUT WHAT OF THAT?
AKATSUKI DEFEATED GARIUS,
THE MOST POWERFUL DARK LORD
OUR WORLD HAS EVER KNOWN,
IN SINGLE COMBAT.
TO TRY AND BRAND HIM A TRAITOR,
IT SITS ILL WITH ME.
- Listy: INDEED. WHY WOULD HE
SUGGEST SUCH A THING?
- Ludie: IF THE ACCUSATION
IS FOUND TO LACK MERIT,
HE KNOWS HE'LL BE TAKEN TO TASK
FOR HIS SLANDEROUS WORDS.
- Zechs: YET HE IS STILL
CONFIDENT, FOR ALL OF THAT.
- Baram: I HOPE YOU CAN
FORGIVE MY LATE ARRIVAL.
- Miranda: OF COURSE,
LORD BARAM.
AND NOW THAT YOU'RE HERE,
PERHAPS YOU MIGHT TELL US
HOW YOU INTEND TO SEND A
SEARCH PARTY THROUGH THE GATE.
THE OTHERWORLD
GATE ONLY RESPONDS
TO THOSE FROM REALMS UNKNOWN
SUCH HAS ITS NATURE ALWAYS BEEN.
WHO, THEN, CAN TREK
TO AKATSUKI'S LAND BEYOND
AND PROVE THE GUILT
YOU ASSIGN HIM?
- I HAVE TAKEN THAT
INTO ACCOUNT.
MIGHT I INTRODUCE PHIL BURNETT?
FORTUNATELY, HE HAILS FROM
THE SAME WORLD AS THE TRAITOR.
- I AM HONORED TO MEET YOU,
MY FAIR QUEEN LISTY.
- PHIL SHALL RETURN
FROM WHENCE HE CAME.
THERE HE WILL TRACK
DOWN GARIUS'S SPAWN
AND PROVE TO YOU SHE
IS NO HARMLESS GIRL.
I TRUST NONE OF YOU
HAS AN OBJECTION
TO THIS COURSE OF ACTION.
IF YOU DO, I SUGGEST
THAT YOU SPEAK IT NOW
OR I WILL INTERPRET
YOUR SILENCE AS CONSENT.
- DO AS YOU WILL.
- I'M COUNTING ON YOU, PHIL,
TO SEEK OUT THE
DARK LORD'S DAUGHTER
AND BRING HER BACK HERE
TO FACE HER FATE.
- AS YOU WISH, MY LORD.
- LORD BARAM! DON'T TELL ME
YOU INTEND TO HAVE THE GIRL
BROUGHT BACK HERE IN SHACKLES!
EVEN IF OUTSIDERS COULD
TRAVEL HERE A SECOND TIME,
WHICH THEY CANNOT,
I FIND THIS-
- AND WHO'S TO SAY THEY CANNOT?
- YOU'RE SAYING
THERE IS A WAY TO DO IT?
( thinking ) HE COULD
COME BACK TO ME.
- Phil: I TAKE MY LEAVE OF YOU,
QUEEN LISTY.
I ALMOST FORGOT.
SAY THIS HERO TRIES
TO PREVENT ME
FROM CARRYING OUT YOUR
ORDERS, WHAT AM I TO DO?
- IF IT SHOULD EVER COME
TO THAT, STRIKE HIM DOWN.
- YOU WOULD HAVE HIM KILLED?
IN A HEARTBEAT. THE DARK
LORD'S DAUGHTER IS A THREAT
TO THE GOOD
OF OUR WORLD.
ANYONE WHO AIDS HER IN
HER ESCAPE FROM US
IS A FOE TO US ALL.
ARE THEY NOT?
- BUT HE WOULD NEVER! AKATSUKI
OUSAWA IS OUR GREATEST HERO!
- YOU KNOW THE TRUTH
OF THE MAN, QUEEN LISTY.
HE'S NO HERO FROM ON HIGH.
HE'S A ROGUE! YOU HAVE FORGOTTEN
YOUR KINGDOM'S TRUE HERO,
MAY HIS SOUL FIND ETERNAL REST.
YOU WRONG THE GHOST
OF LEON ESPERIO.
LEON, WHO DIED PROTECTING YOUR
AKATSUKI FROM THE DARK LORD
HE WOULD EVENTUALLY
SLAY, AND THEN,
WHEN THE SO-CALLED HERO
OF SHELLFEED RAN LIKE A DOG,
YOU WERE FORCED TO
ABANDON YOUR CAPITAL,
AND MAKE FOR THE
SAFETY OF ALECLASTA.
YOUR HERO IS A COWARD.
- THE ONLY REASON ANY
OF US ARE ALIVE
TO LISTEN TO THIS
FOUL-TONGUED VITRIOL
IS THAT THE MAN YOU CONDEMN
AS A COWARD
LED THE CHARGE
TO RETAKE OUR LAND
IN THE FACE OF CERTAIN DEATH!
HE ACCEPTED THE
TITLE OF ROGUE HERO
OUT OF REMORSE FOR
LEON'S SACRIFICE,
WITHOUT WHICH AKATSUKI
SURELY WOULD HAVE DIED!
YOU WRONG A GREAT MAN
WITH YOUR WORDS, LORD BARAM.
FALL SILENT, LEST YOU DISHONOR
YOURSELF FURTHER!
- PAINT YOUR FORMER CHAMPION
IN WHATEVER LIGHT YOU DEEM FIT.
BUT DO NOT EXPECT ME
TO SHARE YOUR FAITH
IN HE WHO IS FAITHLESS.
I WILL TAKE BACK MY WORDS WHEN
HIS INNOCENCE HAS BEEN PROVEN
AND NOT A MOMENT BEFORE,
THOUGH HELL ITSELF
MAY RAGE AT ME.
THAT WILL HAVE TO SUFFICE.
- Ludie: LORD BARAM,
A QUESTION, IF I MAY.
- WHAT IS IT?
- IT WOULD HAVE BEEN BETTER
TO SEND OUT YOUR MAN
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
YET SEVERAL DAYS HAVE PASSED
SINCE OUR TRILATERAL CONFERENCE.
THIS DELAY CAN ONLY HAVE SERVED
TO MUDDY THE TRAIL.
- AH, THE BLAME FOR THAT
LIES SQUARELY ON MY SHOULDERS,
I'M AFRAID.
MY LORD BARAM
IMPLORED ME TO HURRY,
BUT MY PREPARATIONS
TOOK SOME TIME.
- I SEE. ONE LAST QUESTION THEN.
PROVIDED YOU DON'T
OBJECT TO THE ASKING.
- NOT IN THE SLIGHTEST.
ASK AWAY.
- YOU MEAN TO BEST A HERO.
CAN YOU PROVE YOU'RE ABLE?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Listy: LORD BARAM
THINKS AKATSUKI
SECRETED GARIUS'S DAUGHTER AWAY
TO THE WORLD OF HIS BIRTH,
AND NOW HE SPEAKS OF
BRINGING HER BACK TO ALAYZARD,
WHICH SHOULDN'T EVEN
BE POSSIBLE TO BEGIN WITH!
WHAT HAS INSPIRED LORD BARAM
TO ENTERTAIN THESE THOUGHTS?
AND WHY DOES HIS
CHAMPION CARRY HIMSELF
WITH SUCH AN EERIE
AIR OF CONFIDENCE?
HE ACTS AS THOUGH HE KNOWS
HE CAN BEST AKATSUKI,
SLAYER OF THE DARK LORD.
NEXT EPISODE,
BABEL'S RANKING MATCHES BEGIN.
IT SOUNDS AS THOUGH
WAR IS BREWING
ON BOTH SIDES OF THE GATE!