( loud splash )
- ( puffing and panting )
- THANKS FOR THE VOTE
OF CONFIDENCE.
SENDING A WHOLE TEAM AFTER ME,
BUT I DOUBT YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO ACTUALLY KILL ME!
- ( explosions )
- KNOW WHAT?
I TAKE THAT BACK.
I'M A LITTLE INSULTED THAT YOU
THINK A COUPLE HUNDRED ARROWS
WOULD GET THE JOB DONE.
- BULL'S EYE!
IMPOSSIBLE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- WE DOING THIS THE
EASY WAY OR THE HARD WAY?
- THE EASY WAY HAS YOU SAFE
IN SOMEONE'S BED BEFORE SUNRISE.
- Both: ANSWER CAREFULLY!
- ( both shout )
- OH, SCRUMPTIOUS LOOKING
EARLOBE YOU GOT THERE.
- ( whimpers )
- ( exclaims )
- WELL, IF IT'S THAT
IMPORTANT TO YOU.
- AKATSUKI! YOU ARE
AN ABSOLUTE ROGUE!
- BABY, YOU'VE GOT NO IDEA.
I'M KINDA LIKING THE PET NAME.
ADD "HERO" TO THAT,
AND IT'S A DEAL.
REALLY? SURE HOPE YOU FIGHT
BETTER THAN YOU HIDE, VALKYRIE.
- ( footsteps )
- I SHALL ASK YOU
ONCE MORE, SIR KNIGHT.
RETURN WITH US
TO THE PALACE,
SO THERE MAY BE
AN END TO THIS.
- YOU REALLY KNOW HOW
TO SEND A GUY OFF,
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT MUCH.
HOT DAMN, LADIES, WISH
THE MAID CAFES BACK HOME
HAD HALF THE FINE LOOKING
TAIL I SEE RIGHT HERE.
- I TAKE IT FROM THAT
COMMENT YOU TRULY INTEND
TO RETURN TO YOUR OWN REALM,
AKATSUKI THE BRAVE?
HOW UNFORTUNATE.
DAMN HIM!
- AND THE FLOWERS
ARE STILL STANDING!
- CHILDISH TACTICS!
- ( she whimpers )
- ON YOUR FEET, WARRIOR!
- WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
YOU SPRAIN YOUR ANKLES
TRYING TO CATCH THE BOUQUET?
IT'S OKAY.
MAYBE WE JUST ROLL DOWN THOSE
STOCKINGS AND PLAY DOCTOR.
- ( maids scream nervously )
- YOU LECHEROUS BASTARD.
I WAS WRONG TO
ADDRESS YOU AS "KNIGHT."
HOW CAN YOU BE CALLED SUCH
WHEN NO MAN WORTHY OF THE TITLE
WOULD LET TALES OF THIS LEWD
BEHAVIOR TRAIL IN HIS WAKE?
- YOU DON'T THINK STORIES
ABOUT WHIP-BRANDISHING,
MAN-HUNGRY MAIDS
WOULD CATCH LIKE WILDFIRE?
- MY ORDERS COME FROM
PRINCESS LISTY HERSELF.
YOU'RE NOT TO PASS THROUGH
THE OTHERWORLD GATE.
I'M TO STOP YOU BY
ANY MEANS NECESSARY.
- HER HIGHNESS IS JUST
GONNA HAVE TO BE DISAPPOINTED.
- READY YOURSELF!
- DONE AND DONE.
BRING IT ON.
- ( rapid footsteps )
- ( swords clang )
- ( birds chirping )
- CLEARLY I UNDERESTIMATED
YOUR GIFT
FOR CATCHING THE
FAIRER SEX OFF GUARD
IF YOU CAN TROUNCE
VALKYRIE.
- ( she exclaims )
- THAT WAS A COMPLIMENT,
I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW!
I DON'T DISPENSE
THEM LIGHTLY!
YOU WILL ACKNOWLEDGE
YOUR BETTER! AKATSUKI!
- SORRY, PRINCESS.
I DON'T REALLY APPRECIATE
HAVING YOUR PARTY GALS
UNLEASHED ON ME.
NO MATTER WHAT YOUR
INTENTIONS WERE.
- DO YOU REALLY MEAN
TO ABANDON THIS WORLD?
- I'VE KILLED
A DARK LORD, SWEETHEART.
IF EVER THERE WAS A TIME
TO DISAPPEAR, IT'S NOW.
I STICK AROUND, GARIUS' PALS,
HIS ENEMIES, FOR THAT MATTER,
WILL BE FALLING ALL OVER
THEMSELVES FOR A PIECE OF ME.
DON'T FORGET, I'M NOT
FROM AROUND HERE.
I'M ON MY OWN WHEN THINGS
GET UGLY. THINK ABOUT IT.
TRUTH IS, EVEN IF
I WERE FREE AND CLEAR
OF THIS SIDE OF THE GATE,
I'VE GOT OBLIGATIONS BACK HOME.
- I DON'T WANT YOU TO GO.
WHAT IS THE MEANING
OF THIS? YOU ROGUE!
- ONLY THING I COULD THINK OF
TO DO TO STOP THE WATERWORKS.
KINDA WHAT I DO.
- ONE DOES NOT SIMPLY STEAL A
KISS FROM THE LIPS OF ROYALTY!
SUCH LIBERTIES COME DEAR!
- LOOK, I'M NOT A REALLY
COMPLICATED GUY.
THINK OF ME EVERY NOW
AND THEN WHEN I'M GONE
AND THAT'LL BE
PAYMENT ENOUGH.
- YOU INCORRIGIBLE VAGABOND!
I'LL THINK OF YOU WHEN I
CHANCE TO LOOK UPON A CRIMINAL!
- AH, FLATTERY.
REALLY WISH I WAS AS GOOD AT
FARE-THEE-WELL AS YOU ARE, BABE.
BUT, YOU KNOW MY RIDE'S HERE,
SO I PROBABLY BETTER GET GOING.
- GOOD RIDDANCE, AKATSUKI!
I'D WISH YOU A
SAFE VOYAGE, BUT...
I HALF WISH YOU'LL CATCH YOUR
DEATH ON THE WAY. GET THEE GONE.
- JUST SO YOU KNOW, I STILL
MEAN WHAT I SAID THAT DAY.
IF YOU EVER NEED
ME FOR ANYTHING,
CALL ME AND I'M THERE.
ALL I'M ASKING FOR
IS A LITTLE GOOD FAITH.
IF WE HAVE TRUST,
IT DOESN'T MATTER THAT
WE'LL BE WORLDS APART.
YOU KNOW THAT.
HEY! I'M ALWAYS GONNA
BE THERE FOR YOU, OKAY?
ALL RIGHTY, THEN.
HMMM. I WONDER IF SHE'D MIND
A FRIENDLY SQUEEZE.
I MEAN, COME ON. BE GOOD.
WAKEY-WAKEY. HOW
YOU FEELING?
OH, HEY! SO, YOU'RE NOT
ALL MANGLED. THAT'S A PLUS.
- ( Miu screams )
- OKAY, FIRST OF ALL,
TRY NOT TO FREAK.
I REALIZE THIS IS
PROBABLY A SITUATION
BEYOND YOUR UNDERSTANDING,
BUT LET'S TRY TO STAY COOL.
- THEN QUIT LOOKING
AT ME LIKE THAT!
- SECOND OF ALL, THIS
IS MY HOUSE, MY WORLD.
- Akatsuki:
YOU'RE IN GOOD HANDS.
- WAIT, WHERE AM I?
AND, IF I'M IN GOOD HANDS,
WHY AM I NAKED?
- SIDE EFFECT OF CROSSING
DIMENSIONAL BARRIERS.
LOOK, MORE ON ALL
THAT STUFF LATER.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE
INTRODUCE OURSELVES?
AKATSUKI OUSAWA.
FRIENDS CALL ME AKATSUKI.
IN YOUR HOME
WORLD OF ALAYZARD,
THE LADIES USED TO SPIN YARNS
ABOUT ME BEING SOME
KIND OF ROGUE HERO
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- WELL, I... I GUESS
YOU CAN CALL ME MIU.
- ( she sighs )
- Akatsuki: THESE GUYS
DON'T MESS AROUND.
I'VE BEEN BACK JUST OVER A DAY
AND THEY'RE ALREADY
UP OUR BUTTS.
YOU REMEMBER OUR STORY, RIGHT?
YOUR NAME'S MIU OUSAWA
AND YOU'RE TOTALLY MY
LONG LOST LITTLE SISTER.
I FINALLY FOUND YOU.
- WE REUNITED IN ALAYZARD,
WHERE I'D BEEN SINCE
VANISHING FROM MY BEDROOM
WHEN I WAS A LITTLE GIRL.
- AND, AFTER WE FINALLY
RECOGNIZED EACH OTHER,
WE CAME BACK HOME THROUGH
THE OTHERWORLD GATE.
ANYBODY PRODS YOU FOR
MORE INFORMATION THAN THAT,
JUST TELL THEM
YOU'VE GOT AMNESIA.
DOWNCAST EYES ARE THE
MARK OF A TERRIBLE LIAR.
WHEN YOU WALK INTO A ROOM,
ACT LIKE YOU OWN THE
PLACE, OR THEY'LL CATCH ON.
BUCK UP. TRY STICKING
THAT CHEST OUT.
- ( Miu yells )
- Female voice: THE SUMMONING
SYNDROME AND YOU, AN OVERVIEW.
WHILE THE BEST MINDS
OF THREE GENERATIONS
HAVE YET TO FIND AN EXPLANATION
FOR THIS
STARTLING PHENOMENON,
ITS EFFECTS ARE
WELL DOCUMENTED.
THIRTY YEARS AGO, YOUNG
PEOPLE ACROSS THE GLOBE,
BEGAN DISAPPEARING
FROM OUR WORLD,
SUMMONED TO DIMENSIONS
ONLY IMAGINED
IN THE ANNALS OF FANTASY.
CURRENT ESTIMATES
PUT THE NUMBER OF
SUMMONED IN THE THOUSANDS.
THESE OTHER DIMENSIONS
CONTAIN PORTALS,
KNOWN AS OTHERWORLD GATES,
THROUGH WHICH A "SUMMONED"
CAN RETURN HOME,
THOUGH TO DATE ONLY ABOUT HALF
HAVE MANAGED TO REACH THEM.
AMONG THOSE WHO'VE RETURNED,
MANY HAVE BEEN DISCOVERED
TO POSSESS UNIQUE,
OCCULT-BASED FIGHTING TECHNIQUES
ACQUIRED WHILE AWAY.
TECHNIQUES INFINITELY
USEFUL IN OUR WORLD.
- ( she exclaims )
- MAGICAL ABILITIES, AS YOU
MIGHT IMAGINE,
ARE ESPECIALLY
INTERESTING TO US.
TO HELP RE-ACCLIMATE
THOSE EFFECTED
BY THE SUMMONING SYNDROME,
THE NEW UNITED NATIONS HAS
ESTABLISHED AN AUTONOMOUS STATE,
WHERE THESE YOUNG
PEOPLE CAN THRIVE,
GUIDED BY CUTTING EDGE SCIENCE
TO HARNESS THEIR POWERS
TO THE GREATER
BENEFIT OF HUMANKIND.
AND BECOME FINE, UPSTANDING
MEMBERS OF SOCIETY.
AS WELL AS POTENTIAL HEROES.
AS ONE OF THE SUMMONED,
YOU HAVE BEEN SINGLED
OUT FOR THE PRIVILEGE
OF ENROLLMENT INTO BABEL,
OUR STATE-OF-THE-ART
TRAINING FACILITY,
DESIGNED TO HELP YOU
FINE-TUNE THE ABILITIES ACQUIRED
DURING YOUR TIME ABROAD.
WELCOME, AND GOOD LUCK!
- SURE. "FOR THE
PRIVILEGE OF ENROLLMENT."
MORE LIKE THE PRIVILEGE OF
BEING DRAGGED OUT OF BED
AT THE ASS CRACK OF DAWN.
OH, AND LET'S NOT FORGET
BEING QUARANTINED
FROM EVERYTHING YOU KNOW
AND LOVE. THESE PEOPLE.
- YEAH, I TOTALLY AGREE.
UM, BROTHER.
OR SHOULD I SAY, BRO?
- OKAY. NOT THE WAY
TO TALK
IF YOU WANNA KEEP OUR CHARADE
UNDER THE RADAR, SIS.
- ABOUT THAT, I'M REASONABLY
SURE FROM ALL THE TESTING
THEY'VE DONE ON ME
THE PAST TWO HOURS,
THEY'RE GOING TO REALIZE
THAT I'M NOT LOCAL.
- I WOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
YOU GOTTA UNDERSTAND, IN THIS
WORLD, HAVING COLOSSAL MANGOES
ISN'T A DEAD GIVEAWAY
THAT YOU'RE A FOREIGNER.
- THOSE AREN'T THE ONLY
THINGS THEY POKED!
- SORRY TO KEEP YOU
WAITING FOR SO LONG.
THERE WERE A COUPLE OF
IRREGULARITIES I NOTICED.
- ( he clears his throat )
- Akatsuki: DON'T FREAK
OUT. PLAY IT COOL.
- WHO'S FIRST, THEN?
AKATSUKI OUSAWA, IS THAT YOU?
- YO. WHAT'S UP? GIVE
IT TO ME STRAIGHT.
- YES, WELL. YOU'RE
THE PICTURE OF HEALTH.
TAKE THIS FILE TO THE ROOM
AT THE END OF THE HALL,
AND THEY'LL DIRECT
YOU FROM THERE.
- I APPRECIATE IT, DOC.
YOU DO GOOD WORK.
- Doctor: MIU OUSAWA?
- THAT'S ME.
- ( gasps )
- DID I OR DID I NOT TELL
YOU THAT IT'D BE OKAY?
THING IS, WHEN YOU'VE HOPPED
DIMENSIONS IT'S NORMAL
FOR THEIR INSTRUMENTS
TO GO A LITTLE HAYWIRE
TRYING TO GET A LOCK ON YOU.
THEY EXPECT WONKY RESULTS.
- HOW CAN YOU
BE SO RELAXED?
- NO BIG SECRET. SEE,
I KNEW YOU'D ACE THE EXAM,
SO THERE WAS NOTHING
TO GET TENSE ABOUT.
- YEAH THANKS, BROTHER.
I MEAN, THANK YOU, BIG
BRO OR WHATEVER IT WAS.
I CAN'T DO THIS!
- JUST CALL ME AKATSUKI
TILL YOU GET USED TO IT.
YOU'LL ADJUST, I PROMISE.
- Kyoya: INTERESTING.
- Haruka: "TRUE
HERO," "OVERLORD?"
LAVISH PROSE INDEED.
MAY I ASK WHAT THE PROPHECY
MEANS, MR. PRESIDENT?
- IT SEEMS PRETTY
CUT AND DRY TO ME.
- DOES IT?
- WELL, YEAH.
I MEAN, I'M NO EXPERT,
BUT IT SOUNDS LIKE
THIS AKATSUKI GUY
IS GONNA BE THE BIG
CHEESE ONE DAY.
- Minami: SO IT WOULD BE
ACCURATE TO SAY HE'S A THREAT?
- Haruka: THAT'S ABSURD. HOW DO
WE KNOW ANY OF THIS IS TRUE?
SIR?
- I'M OFF TO GREET
OUR NEW OVERLORD.
- Instructor: EVERY NOOK
AND CRANNY OF THE SCHOOL
HAS BEEN INFUSED WITH
A MAGICAL BARRIER.
IT ESSENTIALLY KEEPS
OUR STUDENTS SAFE,
BY TRANSMUTING ANY PHYSICAL
DAMAGE THEY SUSTAIN IN BATTLE,
TO MOSTLY LOW-LEVEL BIOCHEMICAL
FEEDBACK IN THE BRAIN.
DON'T GET ME WRONG, IT'LL
STILL SMART LIKE THE DICKENS
WHEN YOU'RE ACTUALLY HIT, IT
JUST WON'T LEAVE YOU INJURED.
YOUR BRAIN WON'T KNOW
THE DIFFERENCE, THOUGH.
SO, TAKE A BIG ENOUGH WALLOP
AND IT IS POSSIBLE
TO DIE FROM SHOCK.
ALL RIGHT, KIDDOS. LET'S
GAUGE YOUR COMBAT SKILLS.
HOP TO. PICK ANY
WEAPON YOU LIKE.
NOT A BAD DECISION. YOU
GONNA TAKE ALL DAY, OR WHAT?
- I'M GOOD.
I GOT THESE.
- IF I HAD A DIME FOR EVERY
KID WHO SWAGGERED IN HERE,
EXPECTING TO WOW ME WITH
A BARE KNUCKLE BRAWL.
BUT I'M NOT GONNA TRY
TO TALK YOU OUT OF IT.
OKAY, LET'S GET THIS
SHOW ON THE ROAD.
SHOW ME WHATCHA GOT.
THAT'S RIGHT, YOU.
- PLEASE BE GENTLE.
I HAVE AMNESIA!
- Akatsuki: HOLD UP.
- OH, I AM LOVING THAT
YOU'RE A MAGE TYPE.
LOOK ALIVE, SLOWPOKE!
- ( grunts )
- EXCELLENT FORM.
LIGHTNING REFLEXES.
HOW COULD SHE
CAST SO QUICKLY
WHILE MAINTAINING A
PROTECTIVE SHIELD?
- THIS MEAN SHE PASSED?
- I WASN'T SURE
ABOUT THE RULES.
AM I ALLOWED TO DISTRACT MY
OPPONENT WITH A DECOY BARRIER
WHILE I CONJURE AN
ATTACK, OR IS THAT CHEATING?
- HE'S NOT COMPLAINING.
SO, UH, DO I GET A TURN
NOW, OR WHAT?
I MEAN, I'LL WAIT.
- Kyoya: PERHAPS YOU'D BE
BETTER MATCHED WITH ME.
- YOU THE RESIDENT BIG SHOT?
- A PLEASURE TO MAKE YOUR
ACQUAINTANCE, AKATSUKI OUSAWA.
I AM KYOYA HIKAWA, PRESIDENT
OF BABEL'S STUDENT COUNCIL.
SO SORRY IT TOOK ME THIS
LONG TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
- OUR APOLOGIES FOR
DISRUPTING YOUR DAY OFF, SIR.
- YES, YES.
GET THIS MAN TO THE INFIRMARY
AS SWIFTLY AS POSSIBLE.
- WHY'S A FACULTY MEMBER
TREATING THIS GUY
LIKE HE OWNS THE PLACE?
- WISH I KNEW.
TAKES A PRETTY
TOUGH CHARACTER
TO STAY AT THE TOP IN A
PLACE LIKE THIS, THOUGH.
JUST LOOK AT HIM. HE
KNOWS HOW GOOD HE IS.
- INDEED.
BUT I WANT TO MAKE SURE YOU
KNOW IT FOR YOURSELF AS WELL.
TAKE YOUR BEST SHOT.
- YOU GOT IT. JUST REMEMBER
THIS IDEA WAS YOURS.
- Kyoya: WHAT AN
EXCEPTIONAL GAME FACE.
WOULDN'T WANT TO MEET
YOU IN A DARK ALLEY.
FOR THE RECORD, YOU ARE AWARE
THIS IS TO BE A TEST OF SKILL
NOT A COMPETITION FOR
THE TITLE ALPHA MALE.
WE JUST WANT TO TAKE A LITTLE
SURVEY OF YOUR BATTLE PROWESS.
NICELY DONE, AKATSUKI,
YOU HAVE VERY GOOD REFLEXES.
- YOU SON OF A BITCH!
YOU TRYING TO DRAG MY
SISTER INTO THIS?
- LET'S JUST SAY,
GIVEN YOUR REPUTATION,
I DOUBTED SHE WOULD BE IN
MUCH DANGER OF GETTING HURT.
INDULGE ME A BIT FURTHER.
I'VE BEEN LED TO BELIEVE
THAT YOU SCOFFED AT THE IDEA
OF BRANDISHING A WEAPON
FOR THIS EXAM?
ARE YOUR FISTS SO IMPRESSIVE?
IF SO, I'D LOVE TO SEE THEM MAKE
SHORT WORK OF THAT ICE PILLAR.
IF YOU THINK THEY CAN.
- DUDE, SERIOUSLY?
I COULD SHATTER A GLACIER
WITH THESE THINGS.
- HOLD ON, THAT'S
NOT ORDINARY ICE!
THIS THING'S FULL OF MAGICAL
POWER. IT'S A TRICK!
IF YOU GO
AT IT BARE-HANDED,
YOU'LL SHATTER EVERY
BONE IN YOUR BODY.
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT,
I'M BEGGING YOU!
- OH, I GOTCHA. LET'S
SAY I WAS ABLE TO OBLITERATE
YOUR LITTLE POPSICLE
HERE WITH MY BARE HANDS,
THEN WOULD YOU LEAVE
THE GIRL OUT OF THIS,
SO WE CAN FIGURE THIS THING OUT
MAN TO MAN? JUST CURIOUS.
- I THINK SO. SOUNDS
QUITE REASONABLE, ACTUALLY.
- I'M GONNA HOLD
YOU TO THAT.
- Garius: WARRIOR FROM
LANDS UNKNOWN.
I LEAVE MY DAUGHTER, FLESH
OF MY FLESH, TO YOUR CARE.
- ( screams )
- WOW. HE'S SO STRONG.
- WHAT AN INCREDIBLE
PIECE OF WORK YOU ARE.
WITH RAW TALENT
LIKE THAT, MY FRIEND,
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE WE SQUARE OFF PROPERLY.
IT'S MY PLEASURE TO REPORT
THAT YOU HAVE PASSED
YOUR ENTRANCE EXAMS
WITH FLYING COLORS.
WELCOME TO THE BABEL FAMILY.
I THINK YOU'LL MAKE
EXCELLENT ADDITIONS.
- WELL IF THAT'S EVERYTHING,
I'LL BE GOING NOW, SIR.
- YES, THANK YOU.
THAT'S EVERYTHING.
- Kyoya: NOBLE OF YOU TO WANT
YOUR SISTER OUT OF HARM'S WAY.
I ADMIRE THAT YOU'D BARGAIN FOR
HER SAFETY WITH YOUR OWN SKIN.
LET US HOPE SHE'S WORTH IT.
- THAT WAS PRETTY RECKLESS.
YOU'RE LUCKY YOU DIDN'T
BREAK EVERY SINGLE JOINT
IN YOUR HAND, YOU KNOW.
- ( chuckles )
- Kyoya: A "TRUE HERO."
WELL, HE'LL SOON FIND
HIS POWER IS MINE.
- Miu: OH, WOW! IT'S LIKE
I'M AT A WEDDING BANQUET!
- ( he chuckles )
- THINK OF IT AS YOUR REWARD
FOR A WHOLE DAY AT BABEL
WITHOUT LETTING THE
CAT OUT OF THE BAG.
BETTER EAT UP BEFORE
IT GETS COLD. ENJOY!
- THANKS! YOU'RE SUCH
AN AWESOME BROTHER!
- Garius: WARRIOR FROM
LANDS UNKNOWN,
I LEAVE MY DAUGHTER,
FLESH OF MY FLESH,
TO YOUR CARE.
LET NOT HER AGE NOR
HER INNOCENCE DECEIVE YOU.
SHE IS THE SCION
OF A DARK LORD.
WHETHER SHE BE SLAIN IN
TURN, AS HER FATHER,
BY MAN, OR LAUDED
AS HIS SUCCESSOR,
HER DESTINY IS DESTRUCTION.
THUS I IMPLORE YOU...
- Miu: WHAT'S
WRONG? HEY. HELLO?
- SORRY, IT'S NOTHING.
- IT'S GONNA GET
COLD, RIGHT?
- RIGHT. DIG IN.
I'VE DONE WHAT YOU
ASKED, OLD MAN.
JUST REMEMBER, IT'S ME.
DON'T GET MAD IF THINGS DON'T
PAN OUT THE WAY YOU'D HOPED.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Listy: I CAN HARDLY BELIEVE
THE CUR HAS LEFT.
TRICKING MY GIRLS INTO SENDING
HIM OFF WITH THEIR PANTIES
AND STEALING A KISS
FROM ME IN THE OFFING!
I HAVE BUT TO CALL HIM
AND HE'LL RETURN, YES?
HE BETTER HOPE I
NEVER HAVE CALL TO!
IS IT FOOLISH OF ME TO WONDER
WHAT SORT OF HI-JINX
HE'S GETTING HIMSELF INTO
BACK WHEREVER HE'S FROM?
NO DOUBT HE'S A MENACE TO
THE FAIRER SEX THERE AS WELL!
NEXT EPISODE,
"BONDS OF HOLY WATER."
HOLY WATER? HOW CAN
WATER HAVE HOLES IN IT?