YOU MEAN TO BEST A HERO.
CAN YOU PROVE YOU'RE ABLE?
- ZECHS, NO!
- Phil: HE'S WELL WITHIN
HIS RIGHTS TO ASK ME.
THIS MISSION IS IMPORTANT,
AND THUS IT'S IMPORTANT THAT
YOU ALL HAVE FAITH IN MY SKILLS.
THIS SHOULD GIVE YOU
AN IDEA.
WELL, NOW.
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT?
IN THE BLINK OF AN EYE, I JUST
GAVE OFF AS MUCH BLOOD LUST
AS AN ENRAGED DRAGON KIN,
BUT IF ANY OF YOU STILL
HARBOR ANY DOUBTS ABOUT ME,
SAY THE WORD.
- Baram: YOU HAVE MADE
YOUR POINT, PHIL.
OUR ENEMY LIES BEYOND THE GATE.
SAVE YOUR STRENGTH.
- RIGHT YOU ARE,
MILORD. FAREWELL.
- AKATSUKI.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Motoharu: HOW'S IT
HANGING, MAN?
YOU'RE NOT SWEATING THIS,
ARE YA?
- HEY. I'M SURPRISED
TO SEE YOU HERE.
- DON'T BE TOO SHOCKED, NOW.
TAKING PART IN THE RANKING
BATTLES IS MANDATORY.
I'M A STUDENT HERE,
JUST LIKE THE REST OF YOU.
- YEAH, I KNOW YOU ARE.
IT'S JUST WEIRD HOW I DIDN'T
SENSE YOUR PRESENCE
UNTIL A MOMENT AGO.
- GUESS I'M PART NINJA.
NOW LOOK,
I'M NOT TELLING YOU ANYTHING YOU
DON'T ALREADY KNOW, AKKI,
BUT SOME OF THESE
KNUCKLEHEADS ARE GONNA TRY
AND WHUP YOU FOR
THE STREET CRED.
SO YOU MIGHT WANNA
WATCH YOUR BACK.
- I HOPE THEY TRY IT!
EVERY CHALLENGER
I LEAVE IN THE DUST
IS ONE MORE NOTCH IN MY BELT.
I'M DEFINITELY NOT ABOVE
CRACKING SOME HEADS
TO MAKE IT INTO A CLASS.
SO, YOU GIVING ME
THE HEADS UP ABOUT THIS
BECAUSE YOU AND I
ARE ALL BUDDY-BUDDY,
OR YOU GOING FOR IT TOO?
- GOOD QUESTION. LET'S JUST
SAY I DON'T LIKE TO FIGHT
WHEN THE OUTCOME IS OBVIOUS.
- THAT'S A NON-ANSWER
IF EVER I HEARD ONE.
- YEAH, WELL UNLIKE A CERTAIN
SHOW-BOATER IN B CLASS,
I'M NOT THE SORT WHO LIKES
DRAWING ATTENTION TO MYSELF.
I'LL BE TAKING THIS
BATTLE ROYALE NICE AN' EASY.
- OH! I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU!
- SORRY, HE'S ALL YOURS!
DIDN'T MEAN TO BOGART YOUR BRO!
- YOU ARE A SLOWPOKE!
I'VE BEEN LOOKING ALL OVER,
MR. "OH, I'LL FIND YOU"!
- CHILL OUT.
WHY ARE YOU IN SUCH A PISSY
MOOD ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- SHE GETS A LOT OF UNSOLICITED
ATTENTION FROM THE OTHERS.
- HOW COME?
- WELL, SHE DID JUMP STRAIGHT
INTO CLASS B LIKE YOU,
WHICH IS A RELATIVELY
UNPRECEDENTED FEAT.
BUT MIU STANDS OUT
IN OTHER WAYS.
- IT'S NOT LIKE I WANT MY BOOBS
ON DISPLAY WHEN I WEAR THIS TOP!
- IT'S MORE THAN JUST
HER CHEST, THOUGH.
THE BOYS REALLY
DIG HER LOOKS.
ACCORDING TO THEM,
MIU HERE IS THE WHOLE ENCHILADA.
- YEAH? WHO WOULD'VE THUNK IT?
THEY'RE CERTAINLY NOT TRIPPING
OVER EACH OTHER TO CHAT HER UP.
- 'CAUSE THEY WANNA LIVE.
HER BIG BROTHER'S A BAD ASS.
NO ONE WANTS TO RISK
GETTING EFFED UP.
- THAT'S RIGHT, HORN DOGS.
JUST KEEP WALKING.
- GUESS THE ONLY FOLKS AT BABEL
WHO'VE GOT THE STONES
TO TANGLE WITH YOU ARE A COUPLE
OF THE OTHER KIDS FROM A CLASS,
AND SOME OF THE BIGWIGS
ON THE STUDENT COUNCIL, HUH?
-WAIT A SECOND.
ARE THEY FAIR GAME?
- UH-HUH. I MEAN, YEAH,
THEY'RE HELPING THE FACULTY
RUN THE EXAMS BEHIND
THE SCENES AND ALL,
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY,
THEY'RE STUDENTS JUST LIKE US.
STILL, THEY'RE NOT GONNA BE ON
THE MENU UNTIL THE SECOND DAY.
- LOOK AT THAT DUMB GRIN!
THE STRONGEST FIGHTERS
IN THE WHOLE DARN SCHOOL ARE
GONNA BE GUNNING FOR HIM,
AND HE JUST STANDS
THERE LICKING HIS CHOPS!
- COME ON. WHAT'RE YOU
SO WORRIED ABOUT?
IF I SAY I CAN
TAKE 'EM, THEN I CAN TAKE 'EM.
- Motoharu: GOOD TO KNOW,
'CAUSE THEY'RE MAKING A
BEELINE FOR YA, BUDDY.
- HOW YOU DOING VP? "TOP" AND
BOTTOM OF THE MORNING TO YA.
- OH, VERY SUBTLE! THANK
YOU SO MUCH FOR THAT!
- Kyoya: SOMETHING I SHOULD
KNOW ABOUT, HARUKA?
- UM, NO. SORRY.
- GOOD TO SEE YOU, OUSAWA.
ALL SET FOR THE BIG DAY?
- Akatsuki: DON'T YOU SWEAT IT,
PREZ. I WAS BORN READY.
MATTER OF FACT, I CAN'T WAIT
TO GET OUT THERE
AND SHOW YOU GUYS WHAT I CAN DO.
- Kyoya: I APPLAUD YOUR
COMPETITIVE SPIRIT,
THOUGH I HAVE NO DOUBT
YOU'LL COME THROUGH UNSCATHED.
YOUR TEAM LOOKS STRONG, TOO.
AND I SEE YOU'VE ENLISTED
MOTOHARU TO YOUR CAUSE.
YOU'RE FULL OF SURPRISES.
- ( laughs )
- WELL, LOOK AT YOU.
MUST BE DOING SOMETHING RIGHT
IF HE KNOWS WHO YOU ARE.
- WELL, WE'RE BOTH IN A CLASS.
WHY? DOES THIS MEAN MY STOCK
JUST WENT UP WITH YOU
OR SOMETHING?
- Haruka: DON'T LOOK
SO PROUD, MOTOHARU.
GIVEN HOW MUCH WE'VE
HAD TO DISCIPLINE YOU
FOR SKIPPING CLASS, OF
COURSE WE KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
- ( laughs )
- LUCKY ME. GETTING
A CRACK AT YOU AT LAST.
ONCE THE MATCHES START UP,
EVERYBODY'S FAIR GAME, PREZ.
YOU AN' ME ARE GONNA
HAVE US A RUMBLE.
- AS MUCH AS I WOULD ENJOY
PUTTING YOU IN YOUR PLACE,
IT WILL HAVE TO WAIT.
I'M NOT SCHEDULED TO PARTICIPATE
IN THIS ROUND OF FIGHTS.
- WHAT?
- Kyoya: AS A MEMBER OF COCOON,
MY PRESENCE AT THE UPCOMING
SUMMIT MEETING IS COMPULSORY.
HOWEVER, THE OTHER
THREE COUNCIL OFFICERS
WILL BE MORE THAN HAPPY
TO TAKE YOU ON.
- Akatsuki: YOU'RE GOING
TO THE SUMMIT?
I'D ALMOST FORGOTTEN
ABOUT THAT WHOLE THING.
- Kyoya: FOR
WHATEVER IT'S WORTH,
EVERY COCOON MEMBER
WILL BE IN ATTENDANCE.
- Haruka: IT'S VERY IMPORTANT
THAT HE BE THERE, YOU SEE.
- FAIR ENOUGH,
BUT HE'S NOT GONNA BE IN
MEETINGS THE WHOLE TIME, RIGHT?
- COME ON, AKATSUKI,
CAN'T YOU GIVE IT A REST?
IT'S NOT LIKE THIS IS A
CLASS REUNION, YOU KNOW?
HE CAN'T JUST SLIP OUT WHENEVER.
SORRY, MAN,
BUT YOU'LL HAVE TO HAVE YOUR
SPARRING MATCH ANOTHER TIME.
- WITH THE MEETING IN JAPAN,
HE'S KIND OF LIKE THE HOST.
THE PRESIDENT HAS
A LOT ON HIS PLATE.
- CHICKEN, FROM THE SOUND OF IT.
- Haruka: WHAT? WHY, YOU LITTLE!
- Kyoya: I ONLY NEED BE AT THE
SUMMIT UNTIL TOMORROW NIGHT.
ASSUMING THINGS
END AS SCHEDULED,
THERE SHOULD BE PLENTY OF TIME
AT THE END OF THE BATTLE EXAMS
FOR ME TO OBLIGE YOU.
I TRUST THAT'LL SUFFICE?
- OH, HELL YEAH.
WHERE DO WE MEET?
- VERY FEW OF OUR
PEERS WILL ENDURE
TO THE END OF THE FINAL
DAY OF FIGHTING.
WHEN THE TIME IS RIGHT,
I HAVE NO DOUBT ONE OF US WILL
HAPPEN UPON THE OTHER.
- SPEAKING OF CHICKEN,
YOU SHOULDN'T COUNT YOURS
BEFORE IT HATCHES, AKATSUKI.
A LOT CAN HAPPEN
BETWEEN NOW AND THEN.
THE THREE OF US CAN PARTICIPATE
STARTING TOMORROW MORNING,
AND THE MOMENT WE'VE SUITED UP,
I'M COMING FOR YOU.
YOU'LL BE ELIMINATED LONG
BEFORE THE PRESIDENT GETS BACK.
- BETTER DOUBLE DOWN ON BRAS!
- UGH! PUMMELING YOU INTO THE
GROUND IS GOING TO BE A VICTORY
FOR ALL WOMANKIND, YOU SAVAGE!
- WELL, THEN. I WILL
LOOK FOR YOU TOMORROW.
- Haruka: UH, MIU?
CAN I TALK TO YOU?
- YEAH, UM, SURE!
- HEY, MAN, I'M GONNA GO
MAKE MYSELF SCARCE.
YOU KICK SOME ASS.
AND IF THE ASS IN QUESTION COULD
MAYBE NOT BE ATTACHED TO ME,
YOU'D BE DOING ME A BIG FAVOR.
- I'M NOT MAKING ANY
PROMISES EITHER WAY.
- YOU'RE A REAL GIVER.
- SO, WHAT DID THE V.P.
WANNA TALK ABOUT?
- SHE, UH... IT WAS NOTHING
IMPORTANT, REALLY.
- ( bells dinging )
- Male Announcer: ALL RIGHT.
TIME TO EXPLAIN THE RULES
FOR THE RANKING BATTLE.
THE EXAM PERIOD
WILL LAST 48 HOURS.
YOU'LL BE EVALUATED ON HOW LONG
YOU REMAIN IN THE RUNNING,
AND HOW WELL YOU FIGHT.
YOU'RE ALLOWED TO SLEEP DURING
THE EXAM IF YOU SEE FIT,
BUT BE AWARE THAT
YOUR FELLOW STUDENTS
ARE ALLOWED TO ATTACK
YOU AT ANY MOMENT,
INCLUDING VULNERABLE
ONES SUCH AS THAT.
IF YOU DEFEAT SOMEONE WHOSE
RANK IS HIGHER THAN YOUR OWN,
YOUR RANK WILL BE
INCREASED IN ACCORDANCE
WITH THE GRADING METRIC.
EVERY STUDENT IS CONSIDERED AN
ACTIVE PARTICIPANT IN THE EXAM
UNTIL THE POINT AT WHICH
THEY'RE KNOCKED UNCONSCIOUS
BY AN OPPONENT,
AT WHICH TIME THEIR FINAL SCORES
WILL BE CALCULATED.
ANY UNSPORTSMANLIKE CONDUCT
WILL RESULT IN DISQUALIFICATION.
THE FACULTY IS MONITORING
THE BATTLE AREA CLOSELY
TO KEEP THINGS ON THE UP AND UP.
STAY TUNED FOR A SUBSEQUENT
BROADCAST IN WHICH I'LL EXPLAIN
THE CONCEPT OF A.D.
POWER DELIMITING.
- WHAT'S "A.D.
POWER DELIMITING" MEAN?
- OH, YEAH. I FORGET YOU
AND AKATSUKI ARE NEW
TO THIS WHOLE BATTLE EXAM DEAL
SO I PROBABLY SHOULDN'T ASSUME
YOU GUYS KNOW WHAT'S UP.
- "POWER DELIMITING"
DOESN'T MEAN
OUR WEAPONS GET ANY STRONGER,
SO DON'T GET TOO
EXCITED ABOUT IT.
ALL IT MEANS IS THAT OUR A.D.
BRACELETS ARE GOING TO SYNC UP
WITH THE FABRIC OF
OUR GYM UNIFORMS.
- Chikage: EACH OF OUR BRACELETS
CONTAINS ORICHALCUM.
IT'S THE GOOD STUFF THAT MAKES
OUR WEAPON SUMMONING POSSIBLE.
TODAY, IT'LL RESPOND
TO YOUR MENTAL STATE
AND TURN YOUR CLOTHES
INTO COMBAT THREADS.
- ( gasps )
- ( smirks )
- LOOKS LIKE OUR OUTFITS ADAPT
TO OUR PERSONALITIES,
JUST LIKE OUR
WEAPONS TEND TO DO.
- YEAH, THAT'S THE IDEA.
THOUGH IT DOES CHECK
YOUR SUBCONSCIOUS, TOO,
SO SOMETIMES YOU GET
SOME UNUSUAL...
- WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
WHAT THE... WHY AM I
WEARING THIS THING?
- Akatsuki: CUT IT OUT,
YOU GUYS!
OR DO I HAVE TO START
BUSTING HEADS ALREADY?
SHOW SOME COMPASSION!
SHE MAY WATCH KINKY ANIME
AND WEAR ITTY BITTY SWIMSUITS,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN SHE WANTED
TO BE SLUTTED UP LIKE THIS!
- HUH?
- EH?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- Male Announcer: THIS
YEAR'S RANKING BATTLE EXAM
WILL NOW BEGIN!
- ( all yelling )
- MOUNTING A FRONTAL ATTACK!
- WAS A BIG OLD MISTAKE!
- ( grunts )
- SORRY, BUT HERE IT COMES!
- MAN, I DIDN'T GET
TO HIT ANYBODY.
- WELL, THAT'S ONE GROUP OF
CHUMPS WE SHUT DOWN IN A HURRY,
NOW EXACTLY HOW MANY TEAMS ARE
THERE DOING THIS THING AGAIN?
- THERE ARE 39 TEAMS IN ALL,
RANGING FROM CLASS
A DOWN TO CLASS E.
- THIRTY SEVEN TEAMS
SOUNDS LIKE A LOT TO BEAT,
BUT IF WE WORK TOGETHER,
I'M SURE WE CAN DO IT!
- BETTER GET STARTED, THEN!
- ( both gasp )
- YOU'RE TELLING ME THOSE GUYS
WERE HIDING IN THE GROUND?
- ANOTHER TEAM BITES
THE DUST, LADIES.
OH, AN' BY THE WAY, I KNOW
YOU JOKERS ARE OUT THERE,
SO DON'T EVEN TRY IT.
- HUH?
- IF YOU KEEP HIDING
IN THE BUSHES
LIKE A BUNCH OF 'FRAIDY CATS,
I'M GONNA KICK YOUR ASSES EVEN
HARDER THAN I WAS PLANNING ON.
AND THAT WAS PRETTY
DAMN HARD TO BEGIN WITH!
- OH, NO! THEY'RE EVERYWHERE!
I THINK WE SHOULD
START TO WORRY NOW!
- I DIDN'T THINK WE'D HAVE
TO FIGHT SO MANY OF 'EM
BACK-TO-BACK!
- THERE'S NO TIME TO RECOVER.
- YOU GIRLS HAVE NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
THESE GUYS ARE ABOUT AS
THREATENING AS A STUBBED TOE,
SO CHILL.
WE'LL FLATTEN THEIR ASSES
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
- HEAR THAT, FELLAS?
HOTSHOT WITH THE
OVER SIZED SWORD
THINKS WE'RE GONNA
BE AN EASY MARK!
- ( laughing )
- HE'S IN FOR A BIG...
- WOW, AMAZING!
- YA SEE? THAT WAS TOTALLY
DOABLE... WHAT'D I TELL YA?
NOW LET'S PUT THESE
REJECTS TO BED!
- KICK HIS ASS ALREADY!
- Male Operator: THE FIGHTING AT
DELTA POINT HAS CEASED FOR NOW.
ONE TEAM HAS ELIMINATED
14 OTHERS SO FAR
FOR A TOTAL OF 51 PARTICIPANTS!
- NO WAY! IT HASN'T EVEN BEEN
AN HOUR YET, THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
WHICH TEAM ARE WE
TALKING ABOUT HERE?
- TEAM 8, WHICH IS
NOTHING BUT B CLASSERS.
IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S THEIR CLASS
REP KUZUHA DOUMOTO
AND THREE OTHER STUDENTS.
- IT'S KUZUHA DOUMOTO,
CHIKAGE IZUMI, MIU OUSAWA,
AND AKATSUKI OUSAWA.
THEY'RE ALL GOOD, BUT THAT LAST
ONE'S A CERTIFIED SHOW STOPPER.
WE'LL BUMP HIM TO A CLASS, BUT
HE'S REALLY BEYOND EVEN THAT.
THIS GUY COULD DEFINITELY
GIVE THE STUDENT COUNCIL
A RUN FOR THEIR MONEY.
- Haruka: GUESS THIS EXPLAINS
WHY MY EARS WERE BURNING!
I WILL BE THE FIRST TO ADMIT
THAT AKATSUKI'S A HIGHLY
SKILLED COMBATANT.
BUT SUGGESTING HE'S ON
PAR WITH THE FOUR OF US
IS TO GIVE THAT GRINNING
DELINQUENT FAR TOO MUCH CREDIT.
- I DUNNO.
THINK ABOUT IT.
THE FOUR OF US VERSUS HIM
WOULD BE A PRETTY GOOD FIGHT.
- OH, COME ON!
WE DON'T NEED TO GANG UP.
ANY ONE OF US COULD
TAKE HIM OUT!
- THERE'S MORE TO AKATSUKI
THAN I THOUGHT AT FIRST.
HE TALKS A BIG GAME,
WHICH LED ME TO BELIEVE THERE
WAS NOTHING TO HIM BUT EGO.
BUT HE HAS THE SKILL
TO BACK UP HIS WORDS.
- MINAMI!
- BUT, GUESS YOU'D KNOW BEST.
I MEAN, AFTER ALL THAT TIME
YOU GUYS SPENT
TOGETHER AT THE BEACH.
- NOT FAIR! I WASN'T WITH
HIM BECAUSE I WANTED TO BE!
- NO NEED TO GET UPSET.
- NO! JUST STOP IT!
I'VE HAD ENOUGH!
IT'S WAY PAST TIME WE PUT
AKATSUKI IN HIS PLACE
ONCE AND FOR ALL!
LISTEN UP, YOU TWO.
WE'RE GOING TO FINISH UP OUR
WORK AS FAST AS WE CAN
AND JOIN THE RANKING
BATTLE TONIGHT!
I'M SICK AND TIRED OF PEOPLE
GLORIFYING AKATSUKI,
AND THE SOONER WE PROVE
THEM WRONG, THE BETTER!
LEST YOU'VE FORGOTTEN, WE ARE
OFFICERS OF THE STUDENT COUNCIL!
WE MAINTAIN ORDER
WITHIN BABEL.
IF WE CAN'T DEFEAT A GUY FROM
CLASS B, WHAT GOOD ARE WE?
- Akatsuki: ( sighs ) COULDN'T
EAT ANOTHER BITE!
- Miu: ARE YOU SURE THIS
IS A GOOD IDEA?
HAVING A FIRE OUT
IN THE OPEN LIKE THIS?
THE OTHERS WILL
KNOW WHERE WE ARE!
- THE OTHERS ARE
PROBABLY JUST THANKFUL
WE HAVEN'T GOTTEN AROUND
TO BEATING THEM UP
AND TAKING THEIR LUNCHES YET.
AFTER THE SHOW WE PUT ON TODAY,
I REALLY DON'T THINK ANYONE'S
GONNA COME LOOKING FOR TROUBLE.
- YEAH, PROBABLY NOT.
- WE DID KICK A LOT OF ASS.
- NOW, THEN. TIME TO STRIP DOWN
AND HAVE OURSELVES A GOOD SOAK.
- Girls: HUH?
- KUZUHA USES HER EARTH MAGIC
TO WHIP US UP A BIG TUB,
CHIKAGE USES HER WATER
MAGIC TO FILL IT UP,
WE TOSS IN SOME HOT ROCKS
TO KEEP IT NICE AND TOASTY
AND BAM, OPEN AIR BATH!
- YOU WANNA BATHE WITH US?
- Akatsuki: THIS IS GONNA ROCK
AFTER THE SWEATY DAY WE ALL HAD.
- I AGREE WITH YOU
IN THEORY, BUT...
- PEEL 'EM OFF, LADIES,
THIS LESBIAN DIDN'T DIG
A HOLE FOR NOTHING.
- FAIR ENOUGH!
YOU HEARD HER, GIRLS.
MAKE YOURSELVES AT HOME.
- WAIT, YOU'RE SERIOUS?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU DON'T THINK I'M GONNA PEEK
AT YOUR NAKED BODIES, DO YA?
LOOK, YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY.
I GIVE YOU MY WORD I'LL BE GOOD.
- YEAH? YOU REALLY DO MEAN IT?
I'VE GOT A BAD
FEELING ABOUT THIS.
- Chikage: THE MAN
AIN'T PERFECT,
BUT HE DID GIVE US HIS WORD
THAT HE'D BEHAVE.
- ( Miu screams )
WHAT THE...
- ( Kuzuha grunts )
- YOU TOTALLY LIED TO US!
- HEY, I DIDN'T PEEK!
COME ON, YOU'RE SO TENSE!
- WHY ARE YOU TOUCHING ME?
- AW, NOW, YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT.
AFTER ALL THAT FIGHTING
YOU DID, YOU NEED MASSAGES!
- HUH? I DON'T WANT ONE!
LEMME GO!
- DON'T BE SHY!
WHO WANTS A GOOD RUB DOWN?
- Girls: NO!
- NO BATHING!
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS!
WHAT IF SOMEBODY ATTACKS US
WHILE WE'RE IN THE WATER?
WE'D BE AT A HUGE DISADVANTAGE!
- YOU THINK SO? WE WOULD GET
TO SOAK IN THE MEANTIME.
AND WORST CASE SCENARIO, WE
COULD JUST FIGHT 'EM OFF NAKED!
- Girls: WE COULD WHAT?
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- SOUNDS LIKE SOMEBODY BROKE
THROUGH MY WIND BARRIER!
- Haruka: YOU'RE NONE THE WORSE
FOR WEAR. LUCKY YOU.
- Chikage: WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
- HEY, YOU GUYS!
WHAT HAPPENED TO NOT
BEING ABLE TO MAKE IT OUT
FOR THE FIRST DAY?
I FIGURED YOU WOULDN'T
ROLL IN ON MY CAMPFIRE
UNTIL 12:01 AT THE EARLIEST.
- Ryohei: WE WERE GONNA TO WAIT
UNTIL TOMORROW MORNING
TO CHALLENGE YOU,
BUT HARUKA GOT IMPATIENT.
- YEAH, SHE COULDN'T
HOLD HERSELF BACK.
- UH, MINAMI, CAN YOU NOT
MAKE IT SOUND SO SEXUAL?
- All: AW...
- Haruka: A THOUSAND
PARDONS, AKATSUKI,
BUT COULD I BOTHER YOU FOR
A MOMENT OF YOUR TIME?
I TRUST I DON'T HAVE
TO EXPLAIN MYSELF.
- 'COURSE YA DON'T, AND LUCKY
FOR YOU I'M A REAL SUCKER
FOR AN INVITATION
FROM A PRETTY GIRL.
- WAIT A SECOND! YOU CAN'T
FIGHT HER BY YOURSELF!
- THE OTHERS ARE FREE TO HELP
IF YOU DON'T THINK YOU'RE
UP TO THE TASK, AKATSUKI.
- NO NEED TO BRING 'EM INTO IT.
TOMORROW'S GONNA BE
A FULL DAY OF FIGHTING,
AND THE LAST THING I WANT
IS FOR THESE LOVELY GIRLS
TO GET KNOCKED AROUND
TONIGHT ON ACCOUNT OF ME.
- YOU CALL THAT LOGIC?
IN CASE YOU FORGOT, YOU HAVE
TO FIGHT TOMORROW, TOO!
- WE BECAME A TEAM SO WE
COULD DO THIS TOGETHER.
JUST BECAUSE SOMEONE
CALLS YOU OUT FOR A FIGHT
DOESN'T MEAN YOU HAVE
TO FACE THEM ALONE!
- AND YOU GUYS!
YOU STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBERS ACT
LIKE HE'S GOT A TARGET
ON HIS BACK ALL THE TIME!
WHY DO YOU WANNA
DEFEAT HIM SO BADLY?
- UH, IT'S BECAUSE OF
THE THINGS HE DOES.
- WAIT A MINUTE. THAT LOOK ON
HER FACE. I KNOW THAT FEELING.
- HE TOOK A LITTLE EXTRA FROM
HER DURING SWIMSUIT TAG.
- THAT'S ENOUGH!
- TOOK A LITTLE EXTRA
DURING TAG?
( grunts )
GROSS!
I HOPE SHE KICKS YOUR BUTT INTO
NEXT WEEK, YOU SLEAZE BALL!
- Haruka: HOW'D YOU LIKE
YOUR FIRST TASTE
OF THE RANKING BATTLE?
- Akatsuki: I DUNNO.
DIDN'T REALLY LIVE UP
TO THE HYPE, I GUESS.
I HOPED IT'D BE TOUGHER.
THOUGH, I GOT A FEELING
I MAY GET MY WISH
ONCE THE COCOON SUMMIT WRAPS UP.
- YOU DON'T NEED TO WAIT
FOR THE PRESIDENT.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR A CHALLENGE,
I'M SURE THAT THE THREE OF
US CAN OBLIGE YOU!
- Akatsuki: WHAT WAS
THAT HOODOO?
- Ryohei: WE PUT UP A BARRIER
TWO KILOMETERS ACROSS.
BASICALLY, IT KEEPS THE SOUND
AND VIBRATION OF US FIGHTING
FROM LEAVING THE AREA
AND BEING A NUISANCE
TO ANYONE AROUND US.
- WE CAN FIGHT TO
OUR HEARTS' CONTENT,
AND NOBODY WILL
INTERFERE WITH US.
- NOT GONNA LIE, I DIG THE WAY
YOU'RE SETTING THE STAGE.
JUST, ONE QUESTION
BEFORE WE ROCK THIS OUT.
IS THIS GONNA COUNT TOWARDS
MY RANKING EXAM RESULTS,
OR IS THIS BATTLE OFF THE BOOKS?
- Ryohei: OH, IT
DEFINITELY COUNTS.
BUT I DOUBT THAT SORT OF THING
SHOULD BE MUCH OF A CONCERN
FOR YOU GUYS ANYMORE.
- NO?
- LOOK, YOU AND YOUR
TEAMMATES EARNED
EXCEEDINGLY HIGH MARKS DURING
TODAY'S PORTION OF THE EXAM.
ANY WAY YA SLICE IT,
YOU AND THE OTHERS ARE GETTING
BUMPED UP TO A CLASS.
IN OTHER WORDS,
THIS LOSS WON'T HURT YOU.
- GOOD TO KNOW.
LOOKS LIKE OLD KYOYO AN'
I WILL BE CLASSMATES.
THAT SHOULD MAKE FOR SOME FUN.
THAT SAID, IT IS KIND OF A
BUMMER THAT WINNING THIS
WON'T NET ME
ANYTHING, BUT HEY...
AT LEAST I'LL BE READY WHEN
KYOYA FINALLY GETS HERE.
NO POINT IN LOOKING A GIFT WARM
UP IN THE MOUTH, AM I RIGHT?
MAKING THAT BARRIER
WAS A BIG MISTAKE, PRINCESS.
NOW THAT I CAN WHUP ON
YOU WITHOUT INTERRUPTION,
THIS BATTLE IS AS GOOD AS OVER.
- SUCH ARROGANCE!
MINAMI! UESAKI!
THIS IS MY FIGHT!
I'LL BE THE ONE
TO TAKE HIM DOWN.
AKATSUKI OUSAWA!
PREPARE YOURSELF FOR DEFEAT!
WHERE'D HE GO?
- Akatsuki: YOU MISS ME?
COME ON, WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE MESSING WITH?
- NOW I'VE GOT YOU!
HUH?
HE'S A GOOD FIGHTER,
BUT AS LONG AS WE'RE AIRBORNE,
THE ADVANTAGE IS MINE!
- Akatsuki: YOU READY?
'CAUSE HERE IT COMES!
- ( screams )
- THIS WOULD BE A GREAT TIME
TO WAVE THE WHITE FLAG.
- WHAT THE...
WHY DID YOU INTERFERE?
DIDN'T I TELL YOU BOTH THIS
WAS MY FIGHT TO WIN?
- MAYBE YOU SAID SOMETHING
TO THAT EFFECT,
BUT I DON'T REMEMBER AGREEING.
- YOU'RE LETTING YOUR PERSONAL
FEELINGS GET IN THE WAY
OF YOUR RESPONSIBILITY
AS A STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBER,
WHEN YOU SHOULD BE LOOKING
AT THE BIG PICTURE.
- THIS GUY IS POWERFUL.
ALL THERE IS TO IT.
AND YOU'RE OUR VICE
PRESIDENT, HARUKA.
WHAT HAPPENS IF HE DEFEATS YOU?
CAN YOU IMAGINE IT?
ONCE WE'RE NOT TOP OF THE HEAP,
THE ORDER WE'VE
WORKED HARD TO MAINTAIN
GOES RIGHT
OUT THE DAMN WINDOW!
- AND NOW? IT TOOK THREE OF US
TO BEAT HIM ISN'T THAT JUST AS-
- AKATSUKI ISN'T UNBEATABLE!
AND HE'S BEEN ACTING LIKE HE IS.
YOU SAID YOU'D
PUT HIM IN HIS PLACE.
THAT'S ALL THE THREE
OF US DID RIGHT NOW.
WE SHOWED A JACKASS WHO'S BOSS.
- Akatsuki: SURE YEAH,
LESSON LEARNED.
I FIGURED YOU THREE
WOULD GANG UP ON ME,
SO IT WASN'T MUCH OF A SHOCK.
- Ryohei: HOW IS HE
EVEN CONSCIOUS?
- Akatsuki: I CAN PUT UP
AN ANTI MAGIC FIELD
WHEN THE MOOD STRIKES
ME, YOU KNOW.
- GOOD TO KNOW. SINCE
THAT'S THE CASE,
I GUESS WE'LL HAVE TO DO THIS
THE OLD FASHIONED WAY,
WITH WEAPON BASED ATTACKS.
- Haruka: THERE ARE
TIMES TO WORRY ABOUT
THE FAIRNESS OF A FIGHT,
BUT THIS ISN'T ONE OF THEM.
- Akatsuki: INFUSING YOUR
WEAPONS WITH MAGIC! I DIG IT!
YOU'RE FINALLY STARTING
TO TAKE THIS SERIOUSLY!
IN WHICH CASE I AIN'T
GONNA HOLD BACK!
- WHETHER YOU HOLD BACK OR NOT,
YOU'RE GOING TO LOSE
TO US EITHER WAY!
- HA!
- WHAT'S HE DOING?
NO, THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
BUT IT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
- SAY GOODNIGHT,
STUDENT COUNCIL!
COME ON, MAN, I WAS ABOUT TO
PULL OFF AN EPIC TRIPLE K.O.
WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA, MOTOHARU?
- HEY, YOU KNOW I
WOULDN'T SPOIL YOUR FUN
UNLESS IT WAS IMPORTANT, RIGHT?
WE'VE GOT A BIT OF AN
EMERGENCY ON OUR HANDS.
I'M SURPRISED HARUKA HASN'T
ALREADY PICKED UP ON IT.
I TAKE IT YOU HAVEN'T
NOTICED THAT LITTLE CUT
ON YOUR CHEEK, AKKI?
- Akatsuki: NO, BUT IT'S
JUST A SCRATCH. SO...
- SO IT SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
POSSIBLE TO RECEIVE IT
IN THE FIRST PLACE,
THANKS TO THE BARRIER
OVER ALL OF BABEL
THAT CONVERTS PHYSICAL
DAMAGE INTO MENTAL TRAUMA.
YET, THERE IT IS ANYWAY.
- WAIT, THE CONVERSION
FIELD IS GONE?
- AND SO FAR,
THE FACULTY MEMBERS
HAVEN'T SAID SQUAT ABOUT THIS
RATHER IMPORTANT DEVELOPMENT.
SOMETHING IS GOING DOWN,
YOU GUYS.
PROBABLY SOMETHING SINISTER.
- ( heavy crashing )
- THAT CRASHING SOUND!
IT CAME FROM WHERE MIU WAS!
( gasps )
AKATSUKI! NO!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Listy: I TOOK STOCK OF PHIL
BURNETT BEFORE HE LEFT,
AND IN HIM I SEE A MAN WHO WILL
SACRIFICE WHATEVER IS NECESSARY
IN ORDER TO CARRY THE DAY.
GARIUS'S DAUGHTER AND
AKATSUKI ARE IN DANGER,
BUT HE MAY WELL BRING HARM
TO ANY WHO STAND IN HIS WAY.
OF COURSE, IT REMAINS TO BE
SEEN IF GARIUS' DAUGHTER
HAS INDEED FLED TO
THE OTHER WORLD.
I HOPE NOT. BUT IF WHAT
LORD BARAM SAID IS TRUE...
NEXT EPISODE. "ON SUCH A
BEAUTIFUL MOONLIT NIGHT."
THIS WILL NOT END WELL.