Akatsuki: BAD MOVE.
REAL BAD.
A PRETTY YOUNG THING CRYING
ON A BEAUTIFUL MOONLIT
NIGHT LIKE THIS?
THAT'S WHEN I STEP IN.
UNDERSTAND THIS,
YOU HURT HER AND
YOU ANSWER TO ME!
( yells )
JUST SIT TIGHT.
BIG BROTHER'S GOT
SOME ASS KICKING TO DO.
( grunts )
( yells )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Akatsuki: NICE OUTFIT.
OFF THE RACK OR WHAT?
- Phil: I HAPPENED ACROSS
SOME VERY GENEROUS DONORS.
MY LUCKY DAY, REALLY.
- OH, YEAH? AND WHO HELPED
YOU TAKE DOWN THE BARRIER?
- BARRIER? OH YES, THAT.
NO ONE, MORE DUMB LUCK.
THE BRAT RESPONSIBLE DID
IT OF HIS OWN VOLITION.
COINCIDENCE. THOUGH I'M
THE FIRST TO ADMIT
I COULD NOT HAVE
PLANNED IT BETTER.
MERCENARY HEAVEN.
ONE SCARCELY MOVES
TWO FEET IN THIS PLACE
WITHOUT STUMBLING
ON SOMEONE USEFUL.
- WHAT DID YOU DO?
- Phil: THEY RESISTED
AT FIRST, AS PEOPLE DO.
BUT THEY HAD NO HOPE IN THE END.
NOT WITH ALL THAT I
HAVE LEARNED IN ALAYZARD.
- YOU BASTARD!
- OH, DEAR. IS MY
PREDECESSOR TROUBLED?
COME!
SURELY YOU'RE NOT ANGRY.
THE IRONY?
HERE WE ARE, BOTH BORN
OF THE SAME NATIVE SOIL.
YET YOU FIGHT TO PROTECT HER.
DAUGHTER OF A DARK LORD
KILLED BY YOU LANDS AWAY.
AND WHY?
WE'RE THE BALANCE OF
EACH OTHER, REALLY.
OUR FULCRUM POINT, THE GIRL.
ASK YOURSELF, IS SHE REALLY
WORTH DEFENDING TO THE DEATH?
WORTH KILLING A
VERITABLE KINSMAN OVER?
- NONE OF THAT CRAP MATTERS.
AND DON'T EVEN TRY TO
TALK TO ME LIKE THE FACT
WE'RE BOTH FROM HERE MEANS A
DAMN THING, 'CAUSE IT DOESN'T.
GET THIS.
I NEVER IGNORE A
GIRL'S TEARS. EVER.
IT'S MY THING. MY AESTHETIC.
SO'S DECORATING THE GROUND
WITH THE INSIDES OF
BASTARDS LIKE YOU!
- IS THAT A FACT?
WELL, I'LL MAKE IT A POINT
OF BEATING YOU TO THE PUNCH.
THUS IS MY AESTHETIC.
- ( grunts )
ENOUGH OF THIS!
( grunts )
- YOU DISAPPOINT ME.
COME ON! STEP UP!
YOU CAN DO SO MUCH BETTER!
- YOU MEAN LIKE THIS?
( yells )
HA! WHAT'S WRONG, BLONDIE?
NOT AS EASY AS YOU
THOUGHT IT WAS GONNA BE?
- Phil: LINKED
ENERGY MANIPULATION.
I APPLAUD YOUR LEVEL OF MASTERY.
STILL, WITHOUT PROPER
MAGIC I FEEL YOUR CHANCES
IN THIS FIGHT ARE NEGLIGIBLE.
BLOCK THIS WITH YOUR CHI!
- ( yells )
I HAD GOOD REASON
FOR TURNING MY BACK
ON HOCUS POCUS TO STUDY
ENERGY MANIPULATION, DUDE.
SEE, IT'S HANDS DOWN
THE BEST WAY FOR MAKING
ANTI MAGIC BARRIERS
WITH WHATEVER'S AROUND.
IF I USE IT ON ME, I CAN MAKE
MY BODY A SHIELD AGAINST YOU.
COMES IN A HELLUVA LOT HANDIER
THAN RELYING ON SPELLS
TO DO THE HEAVY LIFTING.
FOR EXAMPLE, I CAN
DO STUFF LIKE THIS.
TELL ME WHATCHA THINK.
- YOU'RE A LIGHT MAGIC WIELDER?
- THIS AIN'T MAGIC.
IT'S AN ENERGY BOMB!
AND IT DOESN'T FEEL
GOOD, I PROMISE.
YOU MIGHT WANNA FIND SOME COVER!
AND HE'S TOAST.
- ( screams in pain )
- DUDE, YOU TOTALLY USED AN
ANTI MAGIC BARRIER, DIDN'T YOU?
DON'T YOU LISTEN?
I TOLD YOU IT WASN'T MAGIC.
I GOTTA HAND IT TO YOU, THOUGH.
YOU TOOK IT LIKE A CHAMP.
NO WAY! WHAT WAS THAT ENERGY?
- DEAR, OH, DEAR.
SEEMS I'VE UNDERESTIMATED YOU.
HEH, TO THINK YOU'D GO TO SUCH
LENGTHS FOR A DARK LORD'S ISSUE.
QUEEN LISTY WILL BE
HEARTBROKEN, I FEAR.
- S'CUSE ME?
- SHE'S NOT FAR
FROM IT EVEN NOW.
HEAVY IS THE HEAD
THAT WEARS THE CROWN.
- BULLSHIT.
WHAT THE HELL HAVE
YOU DONE TO HER?
- OH, TO HER MAJESTY?
NOTHING DIRECTLY.
JUST, AN IMPISH BIT OF
VANDALISM, ONE MIGHT SAY.
THE GRAVE OF LEON ESPERIO
IS NOW SO MUCH RUBBLE.
EVEN IN DEATH, THE MAN
WHOSE END YOU BROUGHT ABOUT
STYMIED MY CLAIM
TO THE TITLE HERO.
YOUR OWN GLORY IS TOO DISPUTED
TO THREATEN MY ASPIRATIONS
IN ANY REAL WAY.
GALLANT LEON, HOWEVER,
HE PERSISTED IN THWARTING
ME FROM BEYOND THE GRAVE.
HIS GLORY LIVED ON AFTER HIM.
HIS GRAVE WAS A
BLIGHT ON MY ATTEMPTS
TO WIN A SHARE OF IT FOR MYSELF.
AN ATROCITY!
- YOU DESTROYED
ANOTHER MAN'S GRAVE?
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- NOW, NOW. ALL IS NOT LOST.
I'M SURE SHELLFEED HAS
PUZZLED ME OUT AS THE CULPRIT.
JUSTICE WILL BE
NO DOUBT BE SERVED.
OF COURSE, SHOULD I
SUCCEED IN DISPOSING OF YOU
AND DRAGGING YOUR LITTLE
WHORE BACK TO ALAYZARD,
MY REPUTATION
WILL FAR OUTSTRIP
ANY CHARACTER ASSASSINATION
THEY THROW AT ME.
IN THE END, A GOOD NAME IS ALL
THAT REALLY MATTERS, ISN'T IT?
- I DUNNO.
- ( Phil grunts )
- IS A GOOD NAME
WORTH DYING OVER?
- YOU ARE INCREDIBLY FAST.
ALAS.
AS YOU CAN CLEARLY SEE,
A GIFT FOR SPEED IS SOMETHING
I HAPPEN TO POSSESS, AS WELL.
NOW, THEN.
IF YOU WOULD BE SO KIND
AS TO DROP YOUR WEAPON.
DID YOU NOT HEAR ME?
DROP YOUR WEAPON.
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
I MUCH PREFER YOU DISARMED.
OH, AND, THE A.D. WILL
HAVE TO GO AS WELL.
DON'T WANT ANY MORE TOYS
APPEARING OUT OF THIN AIR,
DO WE?
- SOMEBODY'S INFORMED.
- Phil: ANOTHER PIECE
OF INTELLIGENCE
I OWE TO YOUR
GENEROUS CLASSMATES.
FOR WHATEVER THE CONSOLATION
MAY BE TO YOU, YOUR DEATH,
LIKE HERS, WILL SIGNAL AN
END TO ALAYZARD'S STRIFE.
- Akatsuki: YOU MEAN ONCE ITS
ENEMIES ARE OUT OF THE WAY,
DISDIA WILL BE FREE TO DO WITH
ALAYZARD WHATEVER IT WANTS.
- PERHAPS. BUT HONESTLY
THE POLITICAL MACHINATIONS
INTEREST ME VERY LITTLE.
MY FIRST AND ONLY REAL CONCERN
IS ATTAINING MY RIGHTFUL TITLE.
- WHAT ABOUT YOUR "NATIVE SOIL?"
YOU JUST GONNA LIVE OUT THE
REST OF YOUR DAYS IN ALAYZARD?
- IS THAT SO WRONG?
YOU CAN'T BLAME ME, CAN YOU?
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS WORLD HOLDS
IN STORE FOR PEOPLE LIKE US.
LOOK AROUND YOU.
THE QUARANTINE,
THE COMPULSORY TRAINING,
THE MILITANT IDEALISM DRIVEN
BY THREADBARE CLICHES
OF THE WORST KIND.
AND THE ONLY THING THAT
BAFFLES ME MORE THAN THOSE
WHO ACCEPT A LIFE
OF SUBSERVIENCE
IS THE IGNORANCE OF THOSE
WHO THINK TO SWAY THEIR
WARDENS THROUGH TERRORISM.
BETTER TO LIVE IN
ANY WORLD BUT THIS.
- FOR THE RECORD,
I SEE YOUR POINT.
MATTER OF FACT, I AGREE.
NO DOUBT THIS WORLD
IS AN INSANE MESS.
STILL, I HAVE WHAT
YOU MIGHT CALL
UNFINISHED BUSINESS WITH IT.
I'M NOT READY TO TURN
MY BACK ON HER JUST YET.
- THAT IS A SHAME.
- Akatsuki: I TOTALLY GET WHY
YOU SEE PEOPLE LIKE ME AND LEON
AS OBSTACLES TO
YOUR LIFE'S AMBITION.
TROUBLE IS, I'M NOT
REALLY FEELING YA
ON WHY YOU'VE GOT TO KILL HER.
- OH, IT'S QUITE SIMPLE, REALLY.
YOU SEE, IF I'M
TRULY TO SURPASS YOU,
THERE'S A CRUCIAL
STEP I DAREN'T IGNORE.
SOMETHING EVERY HERO REQUIRES.
A NEW DARK LORD TO VANQUISH.
BEING OF THE PROPER BLOODLINE,
THIS LITTLE DARLING
FITS THE BILL.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON.
NO MORE, NO LESS.
- ( laughing )
- WHAT DO YOU FIND SO AMUSING?
- I'M LAUGHING 'CAUSE I EXPECTED
TO BE THROWN FOR A LOOP.
DUDE, PLEASE!
AFTER ALL THE BIG TALK,
THAT'S WHAT MAKES YOU TICK?
WHAT A DISAPPOINTMENT.
I FIGURED YOU'D BE IN THIS
FOR A BETTER REASON
THAN PETTY JEALOUSY.
I SAW IT COMING FROM A MILE
AWAY, YOU'RE ALL THE SAME.
TRUTH IS YOU'RE JUST A PEON
WHO THINKS PUSHING PEOPLE AROUND
WILL GIVE HIM THE RIGHT
TO CALL HIMSELF A HERO.
-( grunts )
( gasps )
IMPOSSIBLE!
- TOO BAD SO SAD, CHIEF.
I KNOW YOU DON'T
WANNA ACCEPT IT,
BUT ENERGY MANIPULATION
TRUMPS MAGIC AT EVERY TURN.
IT'S CALLED BEING AT
HOME IN YOUR OWN SKIN,
NOT SOMETHING LEARNING AN
INCANTATION BY HEART CAN TEACH.
( grunts )
( yells )
DUDE, TALK ABOUT NOT
KNOWING YOUR LIMITS.
YO. COAST IS PRETTY MUCH CLEAR.
MIU! WHY THE HELL
ARE YOU RUNNING?
THE BAD GUY'S GONE NOW!
DOOFUS.
YOU'RE NOT S'POSED
TO RUN AWAY FROM ME.
DO YOU MIND TELLING ME
WHAT THE BIG DEAL IS?
- Miu: I'M SORRY.
- HA?
- I DON'T BELONG
HERE ANYMORE.
I DON'T BELONG ANYWHERE.
- EXCUSE ME?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- LISTEN, THIS WHOLE THING
IS BETWEEN ME AND ALAYZARD.
I'M SORRY.
BUT AS LONG AS I'M ALIVE, THE
PEOPLE I LOVE ARE IN DANGER.
I'M THE DAUGHTER
OF A DARK LORD.
THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
IF I STAY HERE, PEOPLE LIKE HIM
WILL JUST KEEP COMING FOR ME.
IF I GO BACK HOME, THE
SIMPLE FACT OF MY EXISTENCE
WILL GUARANTEE THAT EVERYONE
GOES ON KILLING EACH OTHER.
THERE'S NO OTHER
WAY OUT OF THIS MESS.
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
- I HAVE NOWHERE TO GO.
PLEASE UNDERSTAND.
FORGIVE ME.
WHEN HE AWAKENS, TELL THE
MERCENARY WHAT'S BECOME OF ME.
THAT WILL BE AN END TO IT.
LET IT BE DONE.
NO! WHY?
- ( Akatsuki grunts )
- WHY DID YOU SAVE ME?
- WHY ARE YOU SUCH AN IDIOT?
YOU'RE GONNA LET SOME
SMARMY BASTARD'S GIBBERISH
GET TO YOU LIKE THAT?
- HE'S RIGHT! WHAT WOULD
YOU HAVE DONE IN MY POSITION?
YOU WANT ME TO KEEP DRAGGING
OUR FRIENDS INTO THIS?
YOU WANT THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD TO SUFFER BECAUSE OF ME?
ANIMALS LIKE HIM ARE NEVER
GOING TO GIVE UP THE HUNT.
THEY WON'T REST UNTIL I'M
HAULED BACK TO ALAYZARD!
DON'T YOU GET IT?
I HAVE TO DIE!
BY LIVING, I BRING RUIN
TO MY WORLD AND YOURS!
I DON'T WANNA BE THE
REASON PEOPLE PERISH!
SACRIFICING MYSELF IS THE
ONLY DECENT THING TO DO!
- ARE YOU DONE?
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
DEATH IS THE EASY WAY OUT.
IT'S NOT A SOLUTION, IT'S YOU
BEING A SPOILED LITTLE PRINCESS!
HELLUVA LOT SIMPLER TO JUST WALK
OFF A CLIFF THAN TURN AROUND
AND FIGHT LIKE THE PEOPLE
YOU LOVE DESERVE, RIGHT?
YOU THINK DEAR OLD DAD JUST
THREW HIMSELF ON MY SWORD?
YOU THINK THE MAN
JUST HANDED YOU OFF
WITHOUT MAKING ME PROVE MYSELF?
OR THAT HE DIDN'T CARE
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN
TO HIS ONLY DAUGHTER?
ANSWER ME!
OR BETTER YET, KEEP THAT TRAP
SHUT AND THINK ABOUT THE FACT
THAT HE LET HIMSELF BE KILLED
TO GIVE YOU A BETTER LIFE!
EITHER WAY, HE SURE AS HELL
DIDN'T THINK THAT YOU
DYING WAS THE BEST OPTION.
YOU HEAR ME?
IF YOU EVEN THINK
ABOUT KILLING YOURSELF,
YOU'RE INSULTING HIS MEMORY,
AND I'LL NEVER LET
YOU SINK THAT LOW.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
YOU'RE HIS VALIDATION!
HIS SURVIVAL!
THE LEGACY OF AN INDOMITABLE
SOUL WRITTEN IN FLESH AND BLOOD!
- YOU COULD'VE DIED
TRYING TO RESCUE ME.
IF YOUR CHI HAD BEEN EVEN
THE TINIEST BIT WEAKER,
THAT MONSTER WOULD'VE HAD YOU
AND THERE WAS NOTHING
I COULD'VE DONE ABOUT IT.
- I DON'T DIE.
I MEAN, COME ON, IT'S
ME WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
HE DIDN'T HAVE A CHANCE.
- I COULD'VE BEAT HIM
WITH MY EYES CLOSED.
- YEAH?
AND WHAT ABOUT THE NEXT
GUY WHO COMES AFTER ME?
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN HE TURNS
OUT TO BE STRONGER THAN YOU?
NO. I WON'T LET YOU!
DYING ISN'T THE EASY WAY
OUT, IT'S THE ONLY WAY OUT!
- YOU KNOW THAT ISN'T TRUE.
THAT'S THE MONSTER TALKING.
BESIDES, THINK ABOUT IT.
WHO SAYS YOU HAVE
TO HAVE A WAY OUT?
STICK AROUND AND FIGHT
FOR THE PEOPLE YOU LOVE.
- I CAN'T.
- I GET IT, OKAY? REALLY.
FINE, I'LL DO THE
FIGHTING FOR BOTH OF US.
IF I'VE TOLD YOU ONCE I'VE
TOLD YOU A THOUSAND TIMES,
THAT'S WHAT I'M HERE FOR.
IF THIS MESS IS ANYONE'S FAULT,
IT'S MINE FOR BRINGING
YOU HERE AT ALL.
IF I'D HAVE KNOWN THIS WOULD
COME TO YOU JUMPING OFF A CLIFF.
I'D HAVE TOLD YOUR
FATHER TO SUCK IT
AND LEFT YOUR ASS IN ALAYZARD.
WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY, I GUESS,
IS THAT NONE OF THIS
IS YOUR FAULT.
IT'S NOT THAT BLACK
AND WHITE, OKAY?
I KILLED HIM, AND
I BROUGHT YOU HERE,
SO IT'S MY PLACE
TO FIGHT FOR YOU
WHICH IS WHAT YOUR FATHER
WANTED IN THE FIRST PLACE.
THIS IS THE PATH
I CHOSE FOR MYSELF
AND I'M NOT GONNA LET
ANYONE KNOCK ME OFF IT.
NOT EVEN YOU, SWEETHEART, SO
YOU MIGHT AS WELL GIVE IT UP.
YOU CHOSE THIS, TOO.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO REACHED
UP AND TOOK MY HAND.
HAVE A LITTLE FAITH IN ME.
HAVE FAITH IN YOUR DAD'S
VISION, HELL, IN YOURSELF.
YOU'RE NOT ALONE HERE.
SO GET THAT THROUGH
YOUR THICK SKULL.
WE'RE IN THIS THING
TOGETHER, YOU AND I.
- GET AWAY FROM ME!
STOP BEING SO NICE!
NOTHING ABOUT YOUR
ATTITUDE MAKES SENSE!
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST FORGET ABOUT
ME AND GET ON WITH YOUR LIFE?
IT'D BE SO MUCH EASIER!
JUST STOP ACTING LIKE MY
GUARDIAN AND LEAVE ME ALONE!
- NOT USED TO BEING TREATED
WITH LOVING KINDNESS, HUH?
YOU SAID EARLIER THAT
YOU DON'T BELONG ANYWHERE.
PERSONALLY, I KNOW
THAT'S A BUNCH OF CRAP,
BUT, BEAR WITH ME A SEC
AND WE'LL BREAK IT DOWN
FOR THE SAKE OF ARGUMENT.
IF YOU ASK ME,
THE WHOLE IDEA THAT YOU NEED
TO BELONG ANYWHERE IS BUNK.
SEE, YOU'RE THINKING IN TERMS
OF A PLACE, A PHYSICAL PLACE,
LIKE ALAYZARD OR HERE,
AND THAT'S MISLEADING.
IT'S NOT ABOUT "WHERE".
IT'S ABOUT WITH "WHO".
IN YOUR CASE THE
"WHO" HAPPENS TO BE ME.
- ( gasps )
- LISTEN, IF YOU EVER
NEED A REMINDER,
JUST LOOK INTO MY EYES AND
YOU'LL KNOW WHERE HOME IS.
AND HEY,
IF THE NICE GUY PART CONFUSES
YOU, I CAN ALWAYS BE A JERK.
EASY-PEASY.
- WHA... WHAT ARE YOU DO...
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
TRYING TO REINFORCE
TODAY'S LESSON
WITH A LITTLE SENSORY
AUGMENTATION.
- WELL, CUT IT OUT ALREADY!
- HA! THE MOUTH ON YOU.
LET'S GIVE IT
SOMETHING BETTER TO DO.
BRACE YOURSELF, SWEET CHEEKS.
- MAYBE HE'S RIGHT.
MAYBE THIS IS HOME.
- Akatsuki: COME ON.
HOW YOU DOING, YOU OKAY?
- UM, YEAH.
LISTEN, ARE YOU...
ARE YOU ABSOLUTELY
SURE ABOUT THIS?
- HUH? ABOUT WHAT?
- COME ON. YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
ALL THE DRAMA,
THE TROUBLE THAT'S BOUND
TO FOLLOW US FROM NOW
UNTIL THE DAY WE DIE.
- YOU THINK
I CAN'T DEAL WITH IT?
MIU, TRUST ME,
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED
YOUR OLD MAN'S
LEGACY WASN'T A CURSE.
IT WAS LUCK.
WELL, WE PROBABLY OUGHTA BE
HEADING BACK RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
IZUMI AND THE OTHERS
WILL BE WORRIED,
AND I'VE GOT ME A MERCENARY
TO INTERROGATE, SO...
( grunts )
- WHAT IS IT? WHAT'S WRONG?
( gasps )
HE POISONED YOU!
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I JUST NEED TO LAY DOWN.
NOTHING MY BODY HASN'T
DEALT WITH BEFORE.
- DON'T BE A MORON!
THAT'S NOT HOW IT WORKS!
COME ON, DON'T DO THIS.
STAY WITH ME.
OH, NO! HIS BODY
TEMPERATURE IS DROPPING!
OKAY, YOU JERK!
IT'S MY TURN TO HELP YOU.
HIS CLOTHES ARE DRENCHED.
HE'LL FREEZE IF
HE STAYS LIKE THIS.
IT'S OKAY. I'M JUST
GONNA WARM YOU UP.
WHA... WHAT AM I DOING?
THIS ISN'T ME.
AH!
OKAY, NOW THIS IS GETTING
A LITTLE OUT OF HAND.
( screams )
DEFINITELY NOT WHAT
I MEANT TO HAPPEN!
OH, MY GOD! WHAT IS THAT?
WAIT, HOLD ON.
THIS ISN'T... WE CAN'T.
( screams )
- EASY.
- WAIT, YOU'RE AWAKE?
- THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE, HUH?
WHEW, GOOD JOB
GETTING THE POISON OUT.
GLAD YOU'RE ON TOP OF THINGS.
- ( gasps )
( grunts )
YOU PROUD OF YOURSELF?
YOU PROUD OF WHAT YOU JUST PUT
ME THROUGH, YOU SON OF A BITCH?
YOU'RE SUCH A PERVERT.
HOW MUCH OF THAT WERE
YOU CONSCIOUS FOR?
- EVERY SECOND OF IT.
I HAD TO KEEP THE
POISON FROM SPREADING
TO THE REST OF MY BODY, RIGHT?
YOUd KINDA NEED TO BE AWAKE AND
FOCUSED TO MANIPULATE YOUR CHI.
HEY, DON'T GET ALL TICKED.
I TOLD YOU I COULD HANDLE IT.
I'VE BEEN POISONED
HUNDREDS OF TIMES.
NOT THAT I DON'T APPRECIATE
YOU TRYING TO HELP.
- YOU'RE A TERRIBLE PERSON.
MAYBE YOU CAN TAKE IT EASY
WHILE SOMEONE'S GOING
THROUGH WHATEVER THAT WAS.
BUT I'M NOT AS
CALLOUS AS YOU ARE!
UGH! YOU'RE HEARTLESS!
EXPLOITING MY SYMPATHY
TO COMPROMISE MY VIRTUE
BEFORE I KNEW
WHAT WAS HAPPENING!
- LOOK, I'M SORRY.
HMM.
I'M NOT MADE OF STONE, YOU KNOW?
THERE'S ONLY SO MUCH
"CUTE" I CAN TAKE.
FORGIVE ME.
- WHY AM I FALLING FOR THIS?
- NOW, THEN.
LET'S GET GOING, HUH?
- UH-UH. YOUR BODY
ISN'T READY FOR A HIKE!
- GOTTA STAY ON THE MOVE.
POISON'LL GET IT'S HOOKS
INTO ME AGAIN IF I DON'T.
HEY, I'M GONNA BE FINE.
THE TRICK NOW IS TO STAY ON
THE OLD FEET, WALK IT OFF.
- I DON'T BUY IT!
YOU NEED TO SIT DOWN AND REST
BEFORE YOU EVEN THINK
ABOUT GOING ANYWHERE!
- REALLY WISH I COULD.
TIME'S JUST NOT ON
OUR SIDE RIGHT NOW.
- ( gasps )
- Phil: I REALLY LET
MY GUARD DOWN.
IN MY DEFENSE, IT'S NOT
EVERY DAY YOU MEET SOMEONE
WHO CAN WIELD SUCH
POWER BARE HANDED.
OR WHO CAN SURVIVE A VENOM
DESIGNED TO FELL
A MAN INSTANTLY.
YOU'RE ALMOST
INHUMAN, AREN'T YOU?
- FUNNY, I WAS GONNA
SAY THE SAME TO YOU.
I WASN'T AT FULL POWER
BACK THERE, BUT STILL.
YOUR ENERGY FLOW SHOULD BE
ALL OVER THE MAP RIGHT NOW,
I'M AMAZED YOU CAN STAND.
I'M KIND OF AMAZED
YOU'RE EVEN CONSCIOUS.
IMPRESSIVE STUFF, MAN. RESPECT.
- YES, WELL, IF YOU'RE
IMPRESSED, NOW, JUST YOU WAIT.
I WAS HOPING NOT TO
RESORT TO THIS, BUT,
IT WOULD APPEAR YOU'VE
LEFT ME PRECIOUS LITTLE
IN THE WAY OF OPTIONS.
- ( Miu screams )
- ( Phil screams )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Listy: I KNOW NOT WHY,
BUT DESPITE MY
STEADFAST CONVICTION
THAT AKATSUKI WILL PREVAIL,
MY HEART IS ILL AT EASE.
PHIL BURNETT IS
NOT THE SORT OF MAN
TO ENGAGE WITHOUT A
TRUMP CARD READY IN HAND,
AND ONE SHUDDERS TO IMAGINE WHAT
THAT WILL BE IN THIS INSTANCE.
IF THE WEDDING OF
BLOODLUST AND CUNNING
HE DISPLAYED AT THE OTHERWORLD
GATE IS ANY INDICATION,
HE MAY WELL TRANSCEND
HUMAN LIMITS ERE LONG.
IN WHAT STATE WOULD
SUCH A TRANSFORMATION
LEAVE A MAN LIKE HIM?
NEXT EPISODE. "BEFORE DAYBREAK."