[TOUKA]
Go, on eat it!
[KANEKI muffled grunting]
[KANEKI retching]
[KANEKI] How could
you do that to me?
There's no way I could eat
someone's flesh!
You're not gonna turn me
into a cannibal! I'm human!
I'm not like you monsters!
[KANEKI groans]
[KANEKI grunting]
[TOUKA]
So. If I'm a monster,
then what the hell does
that make you?
Please, you have to help
me. I dunno what to do.
My whole world has been
turned upside down.
That day has ruined
my entire life!
Yeah, I bet it's rough.
I can't really say that
I pity you though.
You see, I've always wondered
why humans love cake.
It tastes so disgusting to me
that it makes me wanna puke.
But you guys sure
seem to enjoy eating it.
It must've been nice to
live such a peaceful life.
One where you didn't live in
fear of the CCG or other ghouls.
[KANEKI sobbing]
[TOUKA] You think
your life sucks now?
Gimme a break! This
life is all I've ever known,
so how do you think
that makes me feel?
Well, buddy? Answer me!
[KANEKI whimpers]
[KANEKI screams]
[stomach growling]
No! I'm telling
you, I'm a human!
[KANEKI grunting]
[TOUKA sniffing] Well you're
not a ghoul, I know that much.
But you're not human, either.
A half-breed like you
isn't gonna last five
seconds out here!
[KANEKI]
But I, I'm not..
If you wanna be
a human so badly,
then let's see how long
you last 'til you starve.
But I should warn you.
Starvation is utter
hell for a ghoul.
[YOSHIMURA]
That's enough, Touka.
Leave the poor boy alone.
[TOUKA]
But, sir!
This must be hard on you.
Please, come with me young man.
[TOUKA] Are you
gonna take him in?
Of course I am. Remember,
it's our policy
to help our fellow ghouls
in their time of need.
[YOSHIMURA]
Sorry that took a while.
Here you go, son.
[YOSHIMURA] What's the matter?
You don't like coffee?
I do. It's just...
[YOSHIMURA] Kaneki, take a good
look at the cup in front of you.
Does it look strange?
[KANEKI]
No, sir. It looks delicious.
[YOSHIMURA] Then why
don't you give it a try?
[KANEKI gulping]
Oh wow! It is delicious!
[KANEKI] But every time
I try to eat something,
it tastes horrible.
[YOSHIMURA] Through the ages,
coffee is the only thing
that ghouls have been able
to enjoy the way humans do.
However. Drinking coffee is not
enough to satisfy our hunger.
Take this.
What is that?
[YOSHIMURA] When you need more,
don't hesitate to come back.
There's plenty where
that came from.
[KANEKI gulps]
[TOUKA] I don't get why you
decided to help that kid.
[YOSHIMURA] I know you're upset.
But do you remember the story
on the news about an
emergency organ transplant?
Some steel beams fell
and crushed two students
who were standing beneath them.
The doctor took it upon himself
to transplant the organs
from the deceased girl
into the surviving
young man's body.
[TOUKA] But the girl who
died in that accident...
It was Rize.
Wait, he was the guy?
[YOSHIMURA] Yes. He's had ghoul
organs transplanted into him,
and as a result, his life
has been forever changed.
[TOUKA]
You gotta be kidding me!
[YOSHIMURA] This is the first
time I've encountered
this situation. But I have
a feeling that his body
may be changing to
become more like ours.
[stomach growling]
[KANEKI whimpering]
[KANEKI]
Flesh.
Flesh...
[TOUKA] You're not a ghoul,
but you're not a human either.
A half-breed like you
isn't gonna last five
seconds out here!
[RIZE] Who cares if
you're a "half-breed"?
I don't see why
it really matters.
So you're not a human.
Well, you're not a ghoul either.
All that matters
is you're still you.
I say you make the most
of being a "half-breed".
There's delicious flesh out
there just waiting for you.
Watch.
You're gonna love
it. You'll see.
Once you start eating it,
you won't be able to stop.
Yes, it's so good.
It'll put any steak to shame.
[KANEKI screaming]
[KANEKI panting]
Go ahead and eat it.
You know you want to.
It's extra rare just for you.
[stomach growling]
[KANEKI grunting, panting]
[phone ringing]
[KANEKI gasps]
[KANEKI panting]
[phone ringing]
[KANEKI grunting]
[KANEKI]
Hide.
[COLLEGE GIRL] Hey, have you
ever been to the bakery
that's in front of
the train station?
They have the yummiest
stuff in there!
[HIDE yelling]
[HIDE]
Dang it, Kaneki!
How long are you gonna
skip class, you jerk?
Do you know how hard
it's been for me?
If you don't come back soon
I'm gonna die of loneliness.
Whoa, easy! Sorry, man.
[HIDE] What's with
the eye patch?
Is that some new trend
I'm not hip to? Anyway...
[KANEKI]
You know, it's funny.
All these years, and Hide
hasn't changed one bit.
[YOUNG KANEKI sobbing]
[YOUNG HIDE yelling]
[YOUNG HIDE]
Dang it!
How long were you gonna
stay home, you jerk?
Do you know how hard
it's been for me?
Hey, are you even listening
to me? Earth to Kaneki!
Oh, uh. I'm Sorry.
What'd you say?
[HIDE groans]
[HIDE] I've gotta go pick up
some materials from Nishio.
He's an upperclassman.
Kinda snarky but he's okay.
You wanna come with me?
[KANEKI]
Yeah, Sure.
[HIDE] Hey Kaneki. I don't mean
to pry but are you eatin' right?
You're lookin' a little pale.
You're gonna have to eat better
if you wanna stay healthy.
Uh. Right. Okay.
[KANEKI] You can't get
anything past, Hide.
I should've known that he'd be
able to see right through me.
He's hypersensitive.
It's like he knows what
I'm feeling before I do.
But he pretends that
everything's cool. For my sake.
What upsets me the
most about all this,
is if I were to
stop being human,
I couldn't hang out
with him anymore.
[HIDE]
Thanks for coming along.
I think you're really
gonna like him.
[KIMI giggling]
[KANEKI]
Who? Nishio?
[HIDE]
Yeah, who else?
Like I said, he can be
snarky but he's cool.
He's got this dark, mysterious
vibe. It's hard to explain.
This is it. Hey, Nishio!
[KANEKI] Geez, you
could've knocked first!
[KIMI shrieking]
[HIDE, KANEKI]
Uh...
[BOY] Do you always
barge into places
without any warning, Nagachika?
[HIDE] Sorry about that,
I wasn't thinkin'.
Yeah, no kiddin'. Y'know,
nothing pisses me off more
than people disrespecting
my territory.
So, anyway.
This is my friend Kaneki I was
telling you about before.
[KANEKI gasps]
[BOY]
Hm...
[NISHIKI] Nishiki Nishio.
I'm a second year
with the School of Pharmacy.
It's nice to meet you,
Kaneki.
[NISHIKI] You wanted last
year's numbers, right?
[HIDE] Yeah, but I'm only
interested in the retail data.
[NISHIKI] Wish I could
remember where I put it.
Oh, wait. It's prob'ly at home.
Aww, seriously?
I don't live too
far. If you want,
we can walk over
there right now.
Walk over where?
To your house?
That okay?
[HIDE sighing] I need that
data. I'm sorry, buddy.
I hate to ditch ya
but it looks like
we'll just have to hang
out some other time.
Okay.
[KANEKI]
Hide.
'Scuse me.
You mind if I tag along?
[HIDE grunts]
What's gotten into you?
[NISHIKI]
Yeah sure, that's fine.
It's not like I'm gonna
let him in or anything.
[HIDE] Totally understandable.
[phone ringing]
[NISHIKI] But I gotta work
this out before we go.
[HIDE] Why're you actin'
weird? What's up?
[KANEKI] Nothing, I'm fine.
[HIDE] You sure about that?
[NISHIKI] What'd you see?
[HIDE] Who, me?
[NISHIKI]
Yeah, you.
How much of her did
you see earlier?
[KANEKI] Why are
all of these ghouls
suddenly popping up around me?
[HIDE] They were very pretty.
[KANEKI] No, it's not them.
[KANEKI] They've always been
here, I've just never noticed.
'Cause I wasn't a
part of their world.
[NISHIKI] You want one?
[HIDE] Yeah, sure!
[HIDE]
Thanks, man!
[MALE CLERK] You're in luck.
I just made a fresh batch.
[NISHIKI]
Here ya go.
[KANEKI grunting]
I think I'm gonna puke.
[NISHIKI]
Here's yours.
Awesome! Thanks again.
[NISHIKI] So, are you
in any clubs, Kaneki?
Uh, no. I'd like to join one
but I don't do so great
with large groups.
Oh, yeah?
You're the exact opposite of
your buddy, Nagachika.
[KANEKI] No way. He can't
eat that, he's a ghoul!
[NISHIKI munching]
[KANEKI gasps]
This is the best
one I've tasted.
Me too, it's nice
and crispy!
Hey, aren't you gonna
eat yours, Kaneki?
[KANEKI]
I will. Later.
It's crazy.
He has no problem blending
in 'cause he acts just like
any other college student.
It's kind of impressive.
I'm sure nobody even
suspects that he's a ghoul.
[HIDE grunts]
[metalic bang]
I don't think that
he needs to see this.
[KANEKI]
Hide!
[NISHIKI] I thought I was
the only ghoul on campus,
but I guess not.
Whoa, you reek, buddy.
You smell just like
a female ghoul!
[KANEKI grunting]
[NISHIKI] Y'think I
don't know your plan?
You were gonna try to eat
Nagachika, weren't you?
[NISHIKI] There's nothin' like
the sense of power you get
from turning on some idiot
who trusts you wholeheartedly.
Dontcha just love the look of
anguish that crosses their face
when they finally give up
hope? Well, dontcha, Kaneki?
You, you're a monster.
I'm not like you.
[NISHIKI]
Oh, yeah?
[KANEKI groans]
[KANEKI retching]
[NISHIKI] You better
watch your mouth
'cause you're startin'
to piss me off.
You're supposed to
respect your elders.
That was too easy.
You don't even have an ounce
of muscle on your body.
I punched right through you.
[NISHIKI groaning]
I'm gettin' queasy.
How can humans eat that
stuff? It's disgusting.
It tastes just like I'm eatin'
a pile of horse crap.
[NISHIKI gagging]
[NISHIKI]
Uh-oh, I'm sorry about that.
I'm afraid that I've
just ruined your meal.
You two have known
each other for a long time.
He calls you his best friend.
So tell me, just when
were you going to eat him?
Don't you think you've
waited long enough, Kaneki?
Which part of him do
you wanna eat first?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Stop it. Hide is not food.
Get your foot off of him!
What did you say?
[NISHIKI cackling]
[KANEKI yelling]
You heard me!
[NISHIKI] You're attacking
me with your bag?
What are you, an old lady?
[KANEKI grunting]
[KANEKI groaning, coughing]
[NISHIKI] You just don't
seem to get it, do you?
Humans aren't your "friends",
they're nothing but food to eat.
It's no different than the way
they'd think of a cow or pig.
It's rude to play
with your food.
You should probably just
go ahead and eat him.
Quit pretending
you're his friend.
But I'm not pretending!
I see.
Dontcha think that hangin'
out with Nagachika is risky?
He's pretty smart. Having
somebody who's as perceptive
as he is by your side is bound
to get you into trouble.
And this.
[KANEKI whimpering]
[NISHIKI] You can't even
control your own eyes.
[KANEKI grunting, coughing]
[NISHIKI]
Aw c'mon, get up!
Or do you want me to
kill Nagachika first?
You kiddin' me?
That all you've got?
Let's see ya dodge this!
[KANEKI groaning]
[NISHIKI]
I could release my kagune
and put you out of your misery,
but where's the fun in that?
[KANEKI] I can't beat him.
I'm not strong enough.
But I have to try! Hide!
[NISHIKI] Aw. You
worried about your buddy?
Well, you should be.
Are you ready to hear
him scream in agony?
Aw. He's unconscious?
[KANEKI] I've never been
happier to hear those words.
Say your prayers. Nagachika.
[KANEKI]
No.
No!
[YOUNG HIDE]
I Don't mean to intrude.
But why're you always reading
books by yourself at school?
Is that wrong?
[YOUNG HIDE] Nah, you're fine.
Lemme shoot straight with ya.
I just moved here and I haven't
made any pals yet, so...
I was wondering if
you'd be my friend.
Yeah. Sure thing!
Wow, really? I'm
Hideyoshi Nagachka,
but that's a mouthful,
you can call me Hide.
Okay. My name's Kaneki.
[KANEKI]
He changed my life.
I was always the outcast.
Until Hide came along
and reached out to me.
I have to do something.
I don't want my best friend
[KANEKI screaming]
to die!
No. I won't let that happen!
[NISHIKI grunts]
[NISHIKI chuckles]
[KANEKI grunting]
Nice try!
[NISHIKI groaning]
[NISHIKI] Stop, you dumbass!
Keep this up and you'll kill me!
[NISHIKI groaning]
That's Rize's kagune.
But how can that be?
[dripping]
[KANEKI]
Hide.
[RIZE]
He sure looks delicious.
[KANEKI gulps]
What a savory aroma.
It's making me hungry.
So what do you think, Kaneki?
Doesn't he look tasty?
No way! I can't eat
him. He's my friend!
Forget about that for a sec.
And take a closer look.
Well? Can you see it now?
Yeah. I can.
[KANKEI panting]
He does look tasty!
[KANEKI cackling]
No! What the hell am I doing?
[RIZE]
Aw, you poor thing.
You want to eat him so
badly you can't stand it!
Don't beat yourself up.
I mean, it's not like you're
doing anything wrong.
[KANEKI whimpering]
[RIZE]
What're you waiting for?
Quit fighting yourself and
give in to your instincts.
[KANEKI]
What instincts?
The primal ones.
He's all yours, Kaneki.
He's all mine?
[RIZE]
Go on.
[KANEKI panting, cackling]
You're right!
Maybe I should follow
my instincts for once.
He's like a special
treat just for me!
'Cause Hide is my...
[RIZE]
He's your friend!
Yeah!
Hide's been my friend for years.
So I should be the one
who gets to eat him!
[TOUKA] It looks like you're
becoming more like us,
half-breed.
You're so hungry you've
lost your sense of reason.
Move it!
I don't give a crap
about your friend,
go ahead and kill
him if you want.
[TOUKA]
But I'm warning you.
You're gonna be sorry
if you gobble him up.
You'll be left with nothing
but a sea of blood,
entrails, and regret.
Do you think you could
live with that guilt?
Knowing that you killed
your best friend?
[KANEKI growling]
I didn't want it
to come to this.
I'll try to go easy
on you, Kaneki.
But I can't promise anything!
[KANEKI panting]
[KANEKI gasps]
[YOSHIMURA] Touka found you
and brought you back here.
[KANEKI]
Where's my friend?
[YOSHIMURA]
Please follow me.
[KANEKI]
Hide!
[HIDE grunts]
[KANEKI]
This hunger.
It seems to be getting
worse and worse by the day.
I couldn't control it. And
I completely lost myself.
I was so hungry that I
thought I was going to die.
So I went after Hide.
Now that agonizing
hunger's gone.
But there was blood in my mouth.
I want to know where
it came from.
What did you do to me
while I was sleeping?
[YOSHIMURA]
As you know,
there's only one way to
satisfy a ghoul's hunger.
I'm afraid that we
had no choice.
If we hadn't stepped in, you
would've devoured your friend.
[KANEKI sobbing]
[YOSHIMURA] Don't be ashamed,
you're one of us now.
[KANEKI]
I know that.
And as a result, I'm gonna
lose my best friend.
Because...
...I care too much about
Hide to put him at risk.
What now? It's
not like I can just
join the ghoul world. You
guys don't want me around
'cause I'm a half-breed.
I'm alone.
I'm not a human or a ghoul.
There's no place for me!
[YOSHIMURA] I can assure
you that's not true.
Don't you see, you are both
a human and a ghoul, Kaneki.
Therefore, you are
the one and only person
who has a place in both worlds.
I promise you,
you're not alone.
Why don't you join
us at Anteiku?
I'm sure we can help
you find your way.
It'd be good for you.
It'll give you the opportunity
to better understand us.
Then you can judge for yourself
whether or not we're
just ravenous beasts.
Well, how about it?
I'll start off by teaching you
how to make one of our
delicious cups of coffee.
Yeah. Sounds good. I've
never made coffee before.
[MADO]
Isn't the rain lovely?
You know, precipitation
dulls their senses.
Which makes this the perfect
weather to work in.
[AMON] According to the
20th Ward Branch's report,
there was a predatory
incident involving
a binge eater in this
building three months ago.
What's interesting is
eyewitnesses claim
to have seen Jason
in the area as well.
A binge eater and Jason?
[AMON]
2 S-rated subjects interacting?
Well, it's hard to say. But
I think it's safe to assume
that they weren't
cordially sharing a meal.
[MADO gasps]
[AMON]
Everything alright?
Mr. Mado!
[MADO]
What'd I tell you?!
I knew the weather would
work in our favor.
As far as I'm concerned,
there's only one drawback
to this downpour.
It's a shame we're
not able to hear
the scumbag's throes of death.
[MADO cackling]
Tastes like I'm eatin'
a pile of horse crap.
[KANEKI]
May I ask how you know
what horse manure
tastes like, Nishio?
What are you, an idiot? I've
never actually eaten crap!
It's just a figure of speech!
[KANEKI]
Oh, Yeah?
[KANEKI cackling]
[KANEKI whispering]
[HIDE] What?
Nishio has eaten horse dung?
And cow patties, too!
And every other kind of feces!
Whoa, for real?
[NISHIKI]
Damn you, Kaneki!
So, how's that poop
taste, buddy?
Oh, Nishiki, you smell like poo!
You are a disgrace to ghouls
everywhere, young man.