[helicopter humming]
[CCG RADIO]
CCG Base to 203.
Intruders reported at the
Aqua Building in the 20th Ward.
[WOMAN sighs]
[CCG RADIO] Intruders believed
to be ghouls-- I repeat, ghouls.
Proceed to location immediately.
[WOMAN chewing, heavy breathing]
[WOMAN]
More! I want more!
[WOMAN laughing]
[WOMAN gasping, gulping]
[knuckle cracks]
[YAMORI]
My, my, what a mess.
They weren't kidding when they
called you a binge eater.
All I want to do
is enjoy my meal.
Why must you interrupt me?
[YAMORI] You don't know
who I am, do you?
[WOMAN chuckling]
Of course I do.
You're a miserable wretch
who gets a kick out
of pestering others.
[YAMORI chuckling]
[YAMORI] I've got
orders from above.
They've asked that
I take you alive.
However, Before I do that,
I don't see the harm
in taking a finger or two,
maybe an arm or leg,
or perhaps all four?
Surely you wouldn't mind.
[WOMAN]
I should've known
a big man like you would
carry a small weapon.
If you think I'm going
to go down easily...
...you're mistaken.
[YAMORI] Watch it, or you'll
lose more than just limbs.
[YAMORI grunts]
[YAMORI]
How dare you! Those are mine!
Give them back, you thief!
[WOMAN] I don't want
to play with you anymore.
[metal clanging]
[NEWSCASTER A] Early this
morning, authorities discovered
several unidentified male bodies
inside the Aqua Building,
a commercial center located
in Tokyo's 20th Ward.
Investigators found what is
believed to be ghoul saliva
on the bodies of the deceased.
As a result, the incident has
been labeled a ghoul crime.
[HIDE laughing]
[KANEKI]
Aw c'mon, it's not that funny.
[HIDE]
Man, you're hopeless!
Ya can't take her to a
bookstore on the first date!
Why not? She might think
it's an awesome idea!
Look, don't do it. Trust me.
She'll think you're lame.
Then I'll take her...
to Big Girl for hamburgers.
[HIDE snorting]
[KANEKI] I'm being serious,
Hide! Quit laughing!
[HIDE] I know! That
makes it even funnier!
You can't take her to
a place called "Big Girl".
Since when are you the expert?
Fine, then where would
you take a date?
[HIDE]
That's easy!
I'd pay attention
to what the girl's into
and then pick a place
I think she'd enjoy.
[KANEKI]
Such as?
[HIDE]
Uh, Y'know. Girly places.
[KANEKI] You don't even
have a clue, do ya?
[HIDE] If I did I'd be out
with a hot chick right now
instead of sittin' here
lookin' at your ugly mug.
[KANEKI] Yeah, you've
got a good point.
[NEWSCASTER A] prompted
officials to call in the CCG
to investigate. Their 20th Ward
Branch is concerned that--
They're hittin' close to home.
So? Who is she?
Which one of these chicks
is your special lady friend?
[HIDE gasps]
Is that her?!
[KANEKI]
No!
But she's pretty cute, too.
[HIDE]
Excuse me, Miss?
Can I get a cappuccino?
You want one, Kaneki?
[KANEKI] No, I'm still
working on mine.
[HIDE] Oh, and
what is your name?
Hide!
I'm Touka Kirishima.
[HIDE] Lemme just cut to the
chase. Are you seeing anyone?
Cut it out, idiot!
Man, what a hottie.
If you get me kicked outta
here I will never forgive you!
[KANEKI] This coffee shop is the
only place I ever run into her.
[KANEKI gasps]
[HIDE] Huh?
[KANEKI] That's her.
That's the girl.
[KANEKI sighs]
You don't have a chance.
You and her would be like
"Beauty and the Bonehead".
You mean "the Beast"?
Whatever.
Now that I've seen you lovesick
I've got blackmail for days.
[HIDE]
I'm gonna jet.
What? You're leaving?
[HIDE]
I'll see ya later, Touka.
[bell rings]
[HIDE] Good luck, Kaneki!
You're gonna need all
you can get, buddy!
[KANEKI gasps]
[RIZE] Huh?
[HIDE muffled] Man, you are one
lucky bastard, you know that?
[KANEKI]
No joke.
Who'd've thought she'd like
the same author that I do?
[HIDE]
For real.
What's the girl's name
again? Sen Takasaki?
Sen Takatsuki!
And get this, we made plans
to go to the bookstore
together on Sunday.
[HIDE]
Seriously?
That sounds about as exciting
as watching paint dry to me.
But you kids have fun.
[KANEKI]
Thanks, man.
[NAKAJIMA]
We got another one.
Man, it's startin' to get
real ugly 'round here.
Yeah.
Here's the part I don't get.
[NAKAJIMA] Eating one person
is supposed to last them
a month, right? So what's the
deal with these binge eaters?
[KUSABA] This is why we have
to treat them like equals.
If we were to treat them
like the animals they are
they'd kill us all.
Yeah, they're nasty creatures.
If only they could
make themselves useful
and go after the bad guys.
[NAKAJIMA chuckling]
Ain't that the truth.
[RIZE]
So tell me Kaneki,
out of all Takatsuki's novels,
which one is your favorite?
Guess I'd have to go
with her first book.
Well, that's understandable,
it was her breakout hit.
It's my favorite. Her
writing just speaks to me.
Yeah, I feel the same way!
It's so good and to think
she wrote it when she
was just a teen!
[KANEKI coughing]
Are you all right, Kaneki?
[KANEKI gasps]
[KANEKI]
Yeah... I am now.
I'm fine, so anyway...
How's your food? You didn't
eat very much, did you?
Actually, I'm, uh...
I'm on a diet.
[RIZE] I need to go
powder my nose.
Wow, she's such a lady.
[RIZE] Thank you. I had
a great time today.
[KANEKI]
No, thank you! It's been fun.
Uh--
[RIZE] I hate to
ask this of you,
But I live in the area
where all of the attacks
have been happening.
[KANEKI] You mean,
with the ghouls?
[RIZE grunts]
[RIZE] I don't want you
to think I'm weak or anything,
but I'm scared
to walk home alone.
The very thought
of it terrifies me.
[KANEKI]
I'll walk you home.
I mean, what kinda
date would I be
if I didn't at least
do that much?
[RIZE giggles]
Crazy, right? So then Hide asks,
"Do you like me
or novels better?"
[RIZE]
Which one did you pick?
[KANEKI]
Novels, duh.
[RIZE giggling]
He sounds like a funny guy
[KANEKI]
Yeah, he is.
[RIZE] Have you always
been into reading
or is it more of
a newfound passion?
[KANEKI]
I grew up around books.
My dad had a ton in the house.
He passed away
when I was little.
I barely even remember
him. It may sound weird
but when I read his books
I felt closer to him.
My mom had to work
a lot to make ends meet
so I spent most of my
time home alone reading.
Then, ever since my mom died...
[KANEKI gasps]
Hide's the only person
I've talked to about this.
[RIZE] Thanks for
sharing it with me.
[RIZE]
It's this way.
[KANEKI]
Oh, okay.
[YORIKO humming]
[YORIKO] Is there
something wrong, Touka?
Nuh-uh. It's nothing.
[RIZE] Well, I'm right
over here, so, Goodnight.
Rize, um...
[KANEKI] I'd like to
see you again. I mean,
only if you want to.
[RIZE]
Oh, I see.
Well, we have similar
taste in books.
And we're both the same age.
I suppose we do have
a lot in common.
[train rattling]
[RIZE]
Kaneki.
[KANEKI]
Uh, yeah?
[RIZE] The truth is,
I've had my eye on you, too.
I'll admit, I love the
way you look at me.
[KANEKI] Does that mean
you feel the same way?
[RIZE]
Yeah. I want you,
Just as much as you...
...want me.
[KANEKI laughs]
[KANEKI whimpering]
[RIZE gasps]
[train rattling]
[KANEKI whimpering]
Ah! Tasty!
[KANEKI grunting]
[RIZE] You see,
here's the thing.
There's something I like
even more than reading.
Know what that is?
Ripping the organs
out of someone
who's too terrified
to run away from me.
Oh, how I love the
look on your face!
So what do you say, Kaneki?
Will you let me have my fun?
[RIZE cackling]
[KANEKI]
No way!
[KANEKI screams]
[RIZE]
You can't run from me, silly!
[KANEKI grunting]
[RIZE] I'm coming
for you, Kaneki!
[RIZE cackling]
[KANEKI grunting]
[KANEKI gagging]
[RIZE cackling]
What fun!
Wow, I've really made
a mess of you, haven't I?
Uh-oh, it looks like
you died on me.
[RIZE]
Aw, that's too bad.
I was hoping you'd
last a little longer.
You've got just the right
amount of fat on you.
And your flesh is so
tender and tasty.
[RIZE weakly] How could...
...this happen?
[sirens blaring]
[KANOU] His abdominal organs
ruptured! [KANEKI] Where am I?
[KANOU] We need to
operate immediately!
[KANEKI]
What is this place?
I thought...
...I thought I was
on a date with Rize.
[KANOU] Prepare for
organ transplantation.
[MALE NURSE] We need
consent from the next of kin!
[KANEKI]
"Transplantation"?
"Next of kin"?
What the hell are
they talking about?
[TAGUCHI]
You can't, Dr. Kanou!
[KANOU]
I'll take full responsibility!
He needs her organs to survive!
[KANEKI]
It's so warm.
But why?
[heart monitor beeping]
[KANEKI gags]
[KANEKI]
I can't do it.
As much as I want to,
I just can't eat it.
[TAGUCHI]
Hello, Mr. Kaneki.
[door rolling]
[TAGUCHI] You barely even
touched your food.
[TAGUCHI] Oh yeah, your
friend stopped by again.
You know, he seems really
worried about you.
[door rolling]
Oh. Hi, Dr. Kanou.
[KANOU] How are you
feeling today, Kaneki?
[KANOU] Hm. So, the nurses
tell me you haven't eaten
much of anything since
you were admitted.
But there doesn't seem
to be anything wrong with you.
I know. I feel okay.
It's my sense of taste.
[KANOU]
Care to explain?
[KANEKI] Well, everything
tastes disgusting to me.
Hm. Probably
psychological trauma.
It was a serious accident.
You're lucky to be alive.
Don't rush yourself.
As they say,
"time heals all wounds".
I'll stop by later.
[KANEKI]
Nothing wrong with me?
Then why do I feel this way?
[KANEKI] Everything that
happened that day with Rize.
It doesn't feel real. It's
almost like some strange dream.
But one thing's for
sure. Ever since then,
I haven't felt like
the same person.
I'm different somehow.
[HIDE] "Kaneki! Congrats
on getting discharged!
I thought you could probably
use some high-quality
leftovers from my place.
I even got you your
favorite hamburger!
I know, I know,
I'm the best ever.
P.S. Hurry and come
back to school, dude.
It's rough out here on my own."
[KANEKI]
Hide...
Thanks, but, I can't right now.
[OGURA] Here's what I don't
understand about these attacks.
There's no need for
a ghoul to eat this much
in such a short amount of time.
We know that consuming
one dead body
is enough to keep them
alive for a month or two.
[FEMALE TV HOST]
Let me ask you this Mr. Ogura,
why can't ghouls be satisfied
eating the same food
that humans do?
[OGURA]
Well, to put it simply,
they can only derive
nutrition from human flesh.
Eating anything else can
actually be detrimental to them.
Our food tastes
disgusting to ghouls.
Because their tongues work
differently than ours do.
[OGURA] Our food tastes
disgusting to ghouls.
Because their tongues work
differently than ours do.
[KANEKI whimpering]
[KANEKI panting]
[KANEKI gulps]
[KANEKI panting, grunting]
[door slams]
[KANEKI retching]
[KANEKI coughing, retching]
Oh, no!
[KANEKI retching]
[KANEKI yelling, coughing]
[KANEKI sobbing]
[HIDE] I even got you your
favorite hamburger!
[KANEKI]
Hide...
Did you go out and
buy this just for me?
[KANEKI]
This can't be happening.
[phone buzzing]
[phone beeps]
[NISHIKI]
Worried about your friend?
Yeah.
They released him
from the hospital.
But I can't seem to reach him. I
went to go see him a few times.
But he didn't want any visitors.
[NISHIKI] Sounds kinda
rude, if you ask me.
I'd cut ties with him.
[HIDE] Kaneki and I have
been pals since we were kids.
He's my best friend.
Isn't that sweet?
[phone beeps]
[HIDE] What's up, Kaneki?
You feelin' any better?
Anyway, just wanted to let you
know Takatsuki what's-her-name
is doing a signing
at the bookstore
in front of the station.
Gimme a call when you
feel up to it, dude. Later.
[KANEKI sighs]
[stomach growls]
[KANEKI sniffing]
[KANEKI]
People.
Children.
Women. Flesh.
Girl. Flesh.
Man. Flesh.
Family. Flesh.
Children. Flesh.
Girl. Flesh.
Woman. Flesh.
Boy. Flesh.
Man. Flesh.
Flesh.
Flesh!
[GIRL]
Huh?
[KANEKI gasps]
[CROWD murmuring]
Whoa. What's wrong?
Come on! Don't get us involved!
[KANEKI sputtering]
[KANEKI panting]
[KANEKI whimpering]
[KANEKI]
What's happening to me?
[KANEKI gasps]
[KANEKI yelling]
[KANEKI]
I know what's causing this!
[KANOU]
He needs her organs to survive!
[OGURA] Ordinary blades such
as hunting knives or kitchenware
can't cut their flesh.
[KANEKI]
Let's see.
If that's true
and I'm a ghoul...
This won't hurt!
[KANEKI panting]
[metal clattering]
[KANEKI screaming]
[KANEKI grunts]
[KANEKI sobbing]
No.
What the hell am I
supposed to do now?
[KANEKI]
Kill a person.
Take their flesh. And eat it!
What's gotten into me?
What am I saying?
[KANEKI sniffing]
[KANEKI]
What is that scent?
I've never smelled it before.
But there's something
familiar about it.
It's got a sweet aroma to it.
Almost like my
mom's home cooking.
[KANEKI]
Who cares what it is!
I've finally found
something I can eat!
Where is it?
Where is-
[KANEKI grunts]
It's so close.
[KANEKI panting, grunting]
[KANEKI]
A ghoul. A human!
The sweet smell that lured
me here was a corpse?
[KAZUO gasps]
[KANEKI sobbing]
[KAZUO]
You're a ghoul... aren't you?
What's wrong? Are you all right?
Don't cry. It's okay, I'm Kazuo.
I haven't eaten in a while
so I'm afraid I can't
share too much with you,
but here, you can have some-
[NISHIKI]
Good riddance.
You should know better
than to trespass
on my feeding grounds.
[NISHIKI]
I've never seen you before.
Whoa, how come only
one of your eyes is red?
That looks pretty nasty.
[KANEKI groans]
[NISHIKI] Did you think
you could hunt for food
on my feeding grounds
and get away with it?
No, I--
I didn't do it.
[KANEKI]
Look, I swear!
I just happened
to be passing by.
[NISHIKI]
You think I believe that?
Imagine this, your girlfriend is
naked and lying on the ground.
A guy standing over her with his
pants around his ankles says,
"I didn't do it! I swear!
I was just passing by!"
That's basically the same
as what you're telling me
right now. If someone did that
to my girl, I'd kill him.
So that's what I'm
gonna do to you.
If you trespass on
my territory, you die-
[TOUKA]
This isn't your territory!
Which means he wasn't
trespassing, Nishiki.
So let him go.
Touka.
[KANEKI gasping, coughing]
[NISHIKI] I don't see
what the problem is,
I know that binge
eating bitch is dead.
[TOUKA] How does that make
this your feeding ground?
You don't have any say in how
the territory Rize stole
in the 20th Ward gets
distributed among
the weaker ghouls. Just leave it
up to those of us at Anteiku.
Huh? Y'know, I still don't
understand why we've gotta run
every little thing by a bunch
of fence-sitters like Anteiku!
I'm just reclaiming what's mine.
This was my feeding ground--
[TOUKA]
Yeah, because you were weak.
[NISHIKI] I don't
appreciate being insulted
by a punk kid with
a smart-mouth.
Watch it, you're
starting to piss me off.
Think I'm scared?
[NISHIKI]
You should be!
[TOUKA yelling]
Is that all you've
got, Touka?
[TOUKA]
Wait for It.
[NISHIKI groans]
Do you want me to go
harder next time?
[NISHIKI panting, grunting]
You don't wanna take
your corpse with you?
[KANEKI panting]
[KANEKI gasping]
Do you want this?
[KANEKI grunting]
[TOUKA]
You're not eating?
[KANEKI panting]
Oh wow, only one of your eyes
has changed, that's crazy.
Wait, you're the guy
who was with Rize!
[TOUKA]
Why didn't she eat you?
And what's with your eye?
[KANEKI grunting]
Please Miss, you
have to help me!
[KANEKI] I know you might find
this hard to believe this, but,
I'm actually human.
And yet I wanna eat that!
Part of me wants to shove it
in my mouth. But I know I can't.
'Cause if I do, I
won't be a human!
If you're in that much
pain, then just eat.
[KANEKI grunting]
No way! No way! No way!
No way! No way!
There's no way
that I could ever
eat another person's flesh!
[KANEKI] I can't be a ghoul.
Not if this is what it's like.
I've never even hurt a fly, so
how am I supposed to fight?
And I have to kill to eat?!
Well, I won't!
'Cause I'm a human!
This is ridiculous. Why don't
you just give in, already?
If you don't have the nerve
to eat it on your own.
[TOUKA]
Then let me give you a hand.
[KANEKI grunts]
[KANEKI swallowing]
Yoshida Kazuo, age 41 "Ghoul"
Occupation:
aerobics class instructor.
On his day off,
he visits Anteiku
and takes over a feeding
ground from Nishimura.
Once he's home,
he selects his target.
He kills them and then
prepares to eat.
All of a sudden a
young ghoul shows up.
The kid starts screaming
and trembling
and sobbing uncontrollably
Before he can help he gets
whooped by Nishiki.
Yoshida Kazuo, one-time
aerobics class instructor,
dead at just 41 years old.