[KANEKI screaming]
[KANEKI]
Somebody help me! Please!
[KANEKI sighs]
Tsukiyama!
I'm so glad you're here!
You have to save me.
These people, they're--
[KANEKI gasps]
[TSUKIYAMA]
Sweet Kaneki.
Bon appétit!
[KANEKI screams]
[KANEKI panting]
[MALE CUSTOMER A] You hear the
news? Another dove's moved in.
[MALE CUSTOMER B]
How many does that make now?
The way things are heading,
I'm scared to go out alone.
[MALE CUSTOMER C]
Remember the good ole' days,
when the 20th Ward was safe?
[YOSHIMURA] That'll be
all for today, Kaneki.
I've asked Kaya to take
things from here.
[KANEKI]
Oh, alright.
But, sir, where is Touka?
[IRIMI] She called in sick,
so I'm filling in for her.
[YOSHIMURA] Hey Kaneki. Why
don't you pay her a visit?
[KANEKI] I don't
know if I should.
It won't be too much trouble.
After all, she's just upstairs.
[KANEKI]
Ayato Kirishima?
Kay, I'm leaving. Thank you
for keeping an eye on her.
Hinami, be a good girl and
do whatever Touka says, okay?
Bye!
[RYOKO gasps]
Oh. Hi there.
[TOUKA]
Well?
So what are you doing here?
[KANEKI]
Oh, uh.
I heard you were sick so
I thought I'd check on you.
That's all.
[TOUKA] Mm-hm. So
what'd you bring me?
[KANEKI]
Nothing. Sorry.
[HINAMI] Hey Kaneki,
what is this word?
[KANEKI]
Uh. Let's see.
That word is "orange osmanthus."
[HINAMI] Is that another flower?
[KANEKI] Mm-hm.
I'll get some
coffee started.
Hey, wait a second
and I'll do it.
[TOUKA]
Nah, you're good.
You're helping Hinami
with her reading.
But if you're not feeling
well, then you should rest.
[TOUKA] I'm fine,
I just ate too much.
[KANEKI gasps]
Ate too much of what?
[KANEKI]
Do I really wanna know?
[doorbell rings]
[TSUKIYAMA]
Non!
[TOUKA]
Yoriko? Why's she here?
Yoriko.
Hey, what's up?
I'm sorry. I should've called.
But you weren't at school
so I wanted to make
sure you're alright.
[TOUKA] You came by
to check on me?
Yeah. And also--
[YORIKO gasps]
Touka! Don't tell
me that you two--!
[TOUKA] Oh no,
that's just Kaneki!
I get it. I made you
these dumplings.
Share them with him!
Listen, I think you've
got the wrong idea.
Hey! Yoriko, wait!
[YORIKO grunts]
[KANEKI]
So. Did I--
do something wrong,
or am I okay?
[TOUKA groans]
[KANEKI] Geez. Seems
like such a waste.
[TOUKA]
I'll eat it!
It must've taken her hours
to make this for me!
Wait. You've been making
yourself sick eating human food?
Yeah? So what?
[TOUKA chewing, gagging]
[KANEKI] Wow, she's
a really good friend.
[TSUKIYAMA] What should
I do? What should I do?
The partaking of Kaneki
must be savored, but how?
[TSUKIYAMA gasps]
Yes, That's it!
[TSUKIYAMA whimpers]
[TSUKIYAMA inhales]
The perfect meal requires...
...not just two but three!
A maestoso locale!
Him reaching a crescendo...
[TSUKIYAMA moaning]
Until finally I...
...Fortissimo!
My sweet Kaneki!
[KANEKI]
Man that hurt.
Yomo's gonna break my
arm one of these days.
[MEN grunting]
[GHOUL A] C'mon, cry
like the bitch you are.
[KANEKI]
It's Nishio!
[GHOUL A] So how 'bout
we start with his arm?
[GHOUL B]
Sounds good to me.
[KANEKI] I dunno if I should
help after everything he's done.
[NISHIKI screaming]
[GHOULS laughing]
[KANEKI] Hey, uh, sorry
to interrupt, but,
Don't you think that you
might be overdoing it a bit?
No, don't do it, kid.
Not really. What,
is this piece of shit
a friend of yours or somethin'?
[KANEKI] Well, no.
I wouldn't go that far.
[GHOUL A]
Then be a good little boy
and get the hell outta here.
'Cause we're about to
dig in to the bastard.
[KANEKI]
You're gonna eat him?
[KANEKI grunts]
Well? You wanna try
your luck, kiddo?
[GHOUL A grunting]
[KANEKI] His speed's
pathetic compared to Yomo's.
Looks like my training
actually paid off.
Why, you!
[GHOUL A groaning]
Whoa, I hit him!
[NISHIKI weakly]
It's called a grudge, kid.
You should try it sometime.
[KANEKI]
Is this your place?
[KIMI gasps]
[KIMI]
Nishiki! What happened?
It seems like every time you
leave you come back hurt!
[NISHIKI] Sorry, my hunger is
driving me completely insane.
[KANEKI grunts]
Don't Kimi, he's okay.
But he's the one who
hurt you last time.
Yeah, He's the guy. Allow
me to introduce you
to the kid who tore that
hole in my stomach.
[KANEKI] Excuse me, Kimi?
You're a human, right?
So why do you choose
to be with a ghoul?
[KIMI]
I'm in love with him.
[KANEKI] You know that
he kills other people.
Doesn't that affect
your feelings for him?
[KIMI]
Well, of course it does.
But as long as he doesn't
hurt anyone I care about.
I'll just do my best
not to think about it.
Besides, if he didn't kill
them, then he would die.
Well, yeah. That's true.
Please help me.
There's got to be something that
I can do to save Nishiki.
The thing is, if he
doesn't eat, he'll die.
But how am I supposed
to help him with that?
[KIMI sobbing]
[KANEKI]
Hey, Kimi. Listen.
I'll see what I can do, okay?
[KIMI]
Thank you so much.
[KIMI] I've done everything
I can for Nishiki.
I'll just have to trust Kaneki
to take care of the rest.
[KIMI muffled screaming]
Bonsoir, sweet mademoiselle.
Please forgive me.
But I require your
assistance tonight.
[KANEKI]
It's locked, but why?
[KANEKI] Strange. Even
knowing that he's a ghoul,
she's decided to
stay by his side.
[tap]
[KANEKI gasps]
[KANEKI]
A note with a rose?
Only one person would do this.
[TSUKIYAMA]
"My Sweet Kaneki.
Won't you join me for
supper this evening?
How's midnight sound?
I've already brought
that charming woman you were
speaking with at the park.
But to be honest,
it's your company that I'm
really looking forward to."
[KANEKI gasps]
Kimi!
[loud knocking]
[KANEKI]
Nishio!
[NISHIKI] Kimi. She
never made it back.
Damn it! Tsukiyama,
you son of a--
This can't be happening!
Why would he do this?
I'm the one he's after
so, that means
It's on me to make this
right. I'll bring her back!
[NISHIKI]
I'm comin' with you.
But in your condition that would
be suicide! He'll kill you!
[NISHIKI] Do you honestly
expect me sit at home
while Kimi's in this mess?
I have to do something.
[organ playing]
Ah Kaneki. Tell me, are
you a fan of Beethoven?
[NISHIKI panting]
Tsukiyama!
[TSUKIYAMA]
Well, This is awkward.
I don't recall
inviting you, Nishio.
[NISHIKI] Give Kimi
back, you sick freak!
[TSUKIYAMA] Apologies, but
I simply cannot do that.
I'll be needing her to add
spice to tonight's entrée.
It is essential that she
remain as fresh as possible
for sweet Kaneki's pleasure.
Huh?
Do allow me to explain.
I shall feast upon sweet Kaneki!
But even as I do, I want
him to feast upon her!
You son of a bitch.
But that's so disgusting.
Disgusting? You wound me.
But still, if that's how
you really feel about it...
Then Kaneki, I think it's
important that you realize
it is your flavor, which
has driven me to this.
And You sure as
hell better realize
just how delicious you will be.
[NISHIKI groans]
[KANEKI]
Nishio!
Why don't you take
a load off for a bit?
[KANEKI grunting]
Oh my, you're rather
clumsy aren't you?
Tottling about like a
freshly hatched chick.
Pay attention.
This my friend...
[KANEKI groaning]
...Is what real
punch feels like.
[KANEKI grunting]
[TSUKIYAMA]
Oh, and this...
[KANEKI groans]
Is what a real
kick feels like.
[KANEKI gasping]
[TSUKIYAMA] Well, my darling,
[TSUKIYAMA]
what sort of attack
would you like to see
demonstrated next?
[TOUKA]
How about that one?
It's a regular sneak attack.
[TSUKIYAMA grunts]
[KANEKI] Touka, it's you!
[TSUKIYAMA] I must admit,
this is rather embarrassing.
It's been quite a while
since I've been scratched.
When I'm done, you'll
be picking up your teeth
with broken fingers,
ya creepy bastard.
[TSUKIYAMA] You have
such a filthy mouth.
Miss Kirishima.
He's not hurt!
[TSUKIYAMA] I remember a time
when you had that lithe body
of yours honed like
a sharpened blade.
You must've weakened
considerably over the years,
or that scratch would've taken
more than seconds to heal.
[TOUKA] That was just
my way of sayin' hello.
Wouldn't be any fun if it was
over as soon as it started.
Oh my goodness, such
a feisty little girl.
But still...
that's always been the heart
of your charm, my lovely.
[TOUKA grunts]
Do you really think that's
enough to beat me?
[TOUKA grunting]
[TSUKIYAMA]
Remember when you were 14,
and I was 18?
[TSUKIYAMA] Those cold,
piercing eyes of yours
that shone like crystal shards.
I will never forget
their beauty.
Tryin' to win me over with
words? Well, forget it!
I'm not ashamed to admit,
I was quite smitten
with you back then.
[TSUKIYAMA groans]
[KANEKI] I'm leaving and
I'm taking Kimi with me.
Tonight, you're going hungry.
That was a good kick. I mean it.
[TSUKIYAMA laughing]
Oh, brother.
Where were we?
Oh yes.
[KANEKI screaming]
Now then. Let's have a taste.
[KANEKI groans]
[KANEKI coughing, groaning]
[TSUKIYAMA gasps]
[TSUKIYAMA]
Tres bien!
So exquisite!
A symphony of flavor
played in perfect harmony!
Ah, yes! It's even
greater than I imagined!
But now that I've had a taste,
I want something even
more extravagant!
I can't allow my morsel
to die like this!
No.
Not before he's feasted
on my offering!
[TOUKA grunts]
Once upon a time, your cold,
dark heart set mine a flutter.
Sad to say that's
no longer the case.
Something's lit a
fire in your eyes,
and you grow softer as you melt.
[TOUKA gasps]
[TSUKIYAMA] It's truly
a shame, Miss Kirishima.
You see. Softness is the
last thing that you need.
Touka, no!
Stop interrupting my meal!
No, wait! I'm the one
you wanna eat, right?
Don't tell me you forgot.
I want to eat you as
you eat her, remember?
How can you kill people so
easily? Don't you care at all?
It's only natural.
Ghouls are equal-opportunity
carnivores.
Think of life on this
planet as a whole.
Mankind eats every beast
that squirms or crawls.
Since human's are all we eat,
we level the playing field
for other creatures.
What is this?
Such a repulsive scar.
Kimi.
Hey, Nishiki.
I'm sorry. It's just that
I don't want to eat
people anymore, Sis.
[NISHIKI'S SISTER]
But we don't have a choice.
Humans eat animals like cows and
pigs the same way we eat them.
[YOUNG NISHIKI]
But I don't wanna kill anyone.
It's okay. You don't
have to hurt anybody.
[YOUNG NISHIKI]
You're gonna work?
Yep. You don't want us to
live like stray cats forever,
now do you?
[YOUNG NISHIKI]
Well, no.
Nobody's gonna find out about
us. Don't worry, little bro.
[NISHIKI'S SISTER]
Okay, I gotta go!
[YOUNG NISHIKI]
Be careful out there.
[NISHIKI'S SISTER]
Okay, I gotta go!
[YOUNG NISHIKI]
Be careful out there.
[NISHIKI'S SISTER]
Well, guess who got fired today?
[TEEN NISHIKI]
Not again.
What's up?
I didn't realize how much
taller you've gotten.
You look just like dad now!
[TEEN NISHIKI]
Who was that?
[NISHIKI'S SISTER]
He's the manager at work.
Now butt out.
[INVESTIGATOR A]
Which way did they run?
[INVESTIGATOR B]
Search over that way!
[TEEN NISHIKI]
C'mon Sis, please!
You've gotta stay
with me, you have to!
Little bro. Take
care of yourself.
You're on your own.
No, Sis! I need you!
Stay strong! Don't die on me!
[NISHIKI'S SISTER]
You have to live.
[TEEN NISHIKI screaming]
[TEEN NISHIKI]
Yup, you're the one
who turned her in, all right.
[MANAGER] No, d-don't
do this. Spare me.
I'm begging you!
[TEEN NISHIKI]
You've reaped what you sowed.
Both you and my sister.
[TEEN NISHIKI]
Not me though.
'Cause I'll never trust a soul.
Hey. You forgot your change.
[NISHIKI]
Here ya go.
Thanks, that was nice of you.
[NISHIKI]
She's a pale looking girl.
But who knows? She might
be useful for something.
[NISHIKI]
I really like your name.
[KIMI]
Why?
'Cause "Kimi"
means "noble future".
So who came up with it anyway?
Your mom or your dad?
[KIMI sobbing]
What's wrong?
[NISHIKI] What the hell?
Was it something I said?
[NISHIKI coughing]
[NISHIKI]
Kaneki, you son of a bitch!
How come this wound won't heal?
Dammit! I need to
eat some flesh!
Hey, Nishiki?
[KIMI gasps]
[KIMI] Oh my goodness!
What happened to you?
Are you bleeding?
[NISHIKI growling]
[KIMI screaming]
[NISHIKI] You're a real
lifesaver Kimi, do ya know why?
'Cause otherwise I'd be
shit outta luck right now!
[NISHIKI coughs]
[NISHIKI] It's no use.
I don't have the strength.
Nishiki, you--
you're a ghoul?
[NISHIKI panting]
This is just great.
Now she's gonna report me
and it'll be game over.
I'll end up dead
just like my sister.
Ah well, it's been
a lousy life anyway.
[KIMI]
Here you go.
[NISHIKI snarles]
[KIMI gasps]
[KIMI] If we're being honest,
then I should let you in
on a secret I've been
keeping from you.
The day that I met you
I had lost my mom, dad,
and little brother in a car
accident. I was crushed.
I felt like I had nothing
left to live for in this world.
Then you came along and
gave me a reason to live.
You see,
I owe you my life.
[NISHIKI yelling]
[NISHIKI]
That's all I need.
[NISHIKI yelling]
[NISHIKI shouting]
What are you, stupid?
[NISHIKI groans]
[NISHIKI] I always knew
that trusting a human
would get me killed.
And nothing's changed.
I've just found one
who's worth dying for.
[NISHIKI grunting]
You're wearing at my patience.
[NISHIKI shouting]
You don't stand a chance
if you can't use your kagune.
It is the source
of our strength!
The most powerful
weapon we possess!
If your kagune
is an engine,
Human flesh is the fuel.
If a ghoul has a poor diet,
he'll find his kagune's
strength severely diminished.
[TOUKA] Yeah, I know
that all too well.
[KANEKI]
Whaddya mean?
I didn't expect Yoriko's cooking
to make me so much weaker.
[TSUKIYAMA]
Well, enough of that.
Now, for tonight's main event.
You're becoming quite
the pest, Nishio.
Let her go!
[TSUKIYAMA] Damn you!
Stop annoying me!
[TSUKIYAMA sighs]
See?
That's what happens when
you get me all riled up.
[NISHIKI] I've got nothing.
I'm alone in this world.
Except for Kimi,
she's all I've got.
Lay a hand on her
and I'll kill you.
I swear.
Even if it kills me.
What can we do?
[KANEKI] If we want
to use our kagune,
we have to eat.
Hey, Touka. So who's stronger
when at full strength?
You or Tsukiyama?
The last time I fought
him, we were about even.
Okay. Here's the plan.
[NISHIKI groans]
[TSUKIYAMA sighes]
There. That should do it.
You're lucky I didn't
kill you the first time.
[KANEKI]
Tsukiyama!
Huh?
Here goes.
Look away.
[TSUKIYAMA gasps]
[KANEKI grunting]
[TSUKIYAMA gasping]
He belongs to me!
[TSUKIYAMA grunting]
[TOUKA]
You think he's yours?
No way.
[TOUKA] I hate to break
it to you, Tsukiyama.
But nothing here belongs to you.