[TOUKA]
Here goes.
[TSUKIYAMA gasps]
[KANEKI grunting]
[TSUKIYAMA gasping]
He belongs to me!
[TSUKIYAMA grunting]
[TOUKA]
You think he's yours?
No way.
I hate to break it
to you, Tsukiyama
But nothing here
belongs to you.
[TOUKA grunting]
Calmato, my dear.
[TSUKIYAMA grunting]
Amazing.
I've never seen Touka's kagune.
[TSUKIYAMA gasping]
[TSUKIYAMA laughing]
Ah! Bravo, Miss Kirishima!
[TSUKIYAMA] Who'd've thought
I'd take on this much damage?
Your kagune is no more
powerful than mine.
My, my. And here I thought
the fire within you was dead.
But it appears...
...your passion has reawakened!
I was wondering how I
could dress up my meal
and I think your organs will
make the perfect garnish!
Such an unexpected
hors d'oeuvre!
What do you say?
[TOUKA, TSUKIYAMA grunting]
[TOUKA yelling]
[TSUKIYAMA grunting]
[TSUKIYAMA groaning, chuckling]
[TSUKIYAMA]
Impressive, Miss Kirishima.
I'm afraid you've
left me no choice.
To be honest, I was hoping this
would play out more elegantly.
But now I'm desperate...
...for flesh!
[TSUKIYAMA grunts]
[TSUKIYAMA]
How dare you, Nishio?
Insolent fool!
What the hell are you, a zombie?
Let me go!
Let go of me, you bastard!
[NISHIKI]
Ki... mi...
[TSUKIYAMA panting]
Damn it!
I've had enough of you--
[TSUKIYAMA hysterical laughter]
Look at what you've
done to me!
This is going to take...
an awfully long time...
...to heal.
Kaneki, please,
just this once...
[TSUKIYAMA] ...give me a bite.
[KANEKI whimpering]
That's all I need.
[TSUKIYAMA grunts]
[TOUKA]
If you wanna live,
you'll have to eat your
own flesh. Filthy gourmet.
[KANEKI sighs]
[crash]
[NISHIKI gasping]
[NISHIKI]
Ki... mi.
[KIMI]
You okay, my love?
[NISHIKI]
Yeah, don't worry.
Just hold on.
I'll get you free.
[TOUKA]
Nishiki.
Step aside.
Touka...
No.
[TOUKA] I realize you care about
her but she knows too much.
She's a danger to us.
So I have to kill her.
[thump]
[KANEKI]
Don't do it!
You can't kill her.
It's not fair.
We've all got a
human we care about.
I've got Hide and
you've got Yoriko.
Just think.
What if it was her up there?
What would you do then, huh?
Touka, please.
Would you be able
to kill Yoriko?
Shut up!
[TOUKA] That's exactly
why I have to do it!
To protect the people
that I care about!
[NISHIKI groaning]
Nishiki?
How pretty.
[TOUKA gasps]
[KIMI gasps]
I'm sorry.
[TOUKA]
What does that mean?
Oh, no, Nishiki!
[KIMI]
Please, wake up!
[NISHIKI groaning]
[KIMI]
Thank goodness!
[TOUKA]
How am I...
...pretty?
[KANEKI sighs]
[KANEKI]
The incident at the church
was kind of a turning
point for us.
There were some major changes at
Anteiku after that fateful day.
Sorry, manual labor
isn't really my "thing".
[KANEKI]
Hey! I just cleaned that!
[HIDE]
What're you doing here?
That's a stupid question.
Do you really think I'd
wear this silly get-up
just for the hell of it?
[KANEKI]
The biggest change of all?
Nishio came to work with us.
[KANEKI] Do it for Kimi's sake.
If you keep taking human lives,
you're not only putting
your life in danger,
but hers as well.
[YOSHIMURA] With the way that
we go about gathering our food,
Anteiku allows you
to live a relatively
guilt-free life as a ghoul.
However, there is something
that we ask of you in return.
You must work in
our coffee shop.
Is that understood?
[HIDE] Man, I hate to
break it to you, Nishio,
but a guy like you
doesn't really fit in
at a classy place like this.
[NISHIKI] What's that
s'posed to mean?
Better watch what you
say or I'll throw you out.
[HIDE]
Alright, alright.
So, what made you
wanna work here?
A good woman. Now butt out.
Hold up! Don't tell me
that you're after Touka!
[NISHIKI] Gimme a break! I said
"good woman" not "dumb girl"!
[HIDE] Speaking of,
how's she doing?
Is she feeling any better?
Dunno.
[KANEKI] I wish I knew
what was bothering Touka.
She hasn't been back
to work since that day.
[clatter]
[HINAMI]
It's not fair! I just--
I wanna see Daddy!
[HINAMI sobs]
[HIDE]
What was that about?
[NISHIKI]
She's a kid.
They throw temper
tantrums all the time.
Oh crap, I'm gonna be late!
Here, this should cover me.
[KANEKI]
Hey, Hinami?
[RYOKO] It's my fault
she's acting out.
Without my husband, I
have to be both parents.
Turns out that's a lot
harder than I thought.
[KANEKI] You don't have to
tell me if you don't want to.
But, um, why is she so upset?
[RYOKO] It's been a while
since we've heard anything
from my husband. She's
worried, and rightfully so.
But now she's insisting
that we go see him.
[KANEKI]
And that's bad?
Where is he right now?
[door creaks]
[ASAKI gasps]
[ASAKI]
Yamori.
Looks like business has been
slow for you lately, eh Doc?
[ASAKI] Here, take this
and get out of my office.
Hm...
Oh yeah, this'll be perfect.
Gotta hand it to you, this
craftsmanship is impressive.
She doesn't stand a
chance against this!
[ASAKI] Now that I've
finished that for you.
Please leave me alone.
[YAMORI] What, you
don't like my company?
[ASAKI] I just want to
live my life in peace.
[ASAKI] Please.
[knuckle cracks]
[YAMORI]
As you wish.
[ASAKI]
Hinami, Ryoko,
We'll be together again soon.
[YAMORI]
Oh hey Doc,
I don't wanna be a nuisance
so I'll get out of your hair.
But before I go I gotta ask ya,
when did you become a
flunky for the humans?
[ASAKI grunts]
[RYOKO]
Well, you see,
My husband used
to be involved
with some dangerous
business in the 13th Ward.
But then, when Hinami was born,
he chose to leave
that life behind him.
I don't worry about his past.
He's a wonderful
husband and father.
That's all that matters.
Well. See ya.
[KANEKI]
Uh, you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I can take it from here. I'm
going to have a talk to her
and maybe even spoil
her a little bit.
[ASAKI groaning]
[ASAKI]
A box-carrier?
Why are the doves here?
Well, well, look who it is!
It seems our patience
has paid off.
See? What'd I tell you?
As long as we use
the peons as bait,
we're bound to reel in a trophy.
or a bottom feeder in this case.
[AMON]
Mr. Mado, is that?
[MADO]
Jason. Funny seeing you here.
What's a big fish like you
doing in a small pond
like the 20th Ward?
You didn't honestly
think you could
wander around
undetected, did you?
He's S-rated.
The 13th Ward's Jason.
[RYOKO]
Open up.
Please, Hinami. I
want to talk to you.
[HINAMI] No! I'm
not letting you in!
Leave me alone!
I know that you're
angry with me but--
[HINAMI] I just wanna see daddy
and you won't let me! Why, Mom?
Why won't you let me
see him? I hate you!
You need to calm down, Hinami!
[RYOKO]
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have
raised my voice.
This is has been
hard on all of us.
I'm sure your dad misses you
just as much as you miss him.
I'm sorry. I wish
I could take you
to see him but I don't
want us to get in his way.
I hate that I'm putting
you through all this.
[lock clicks]
[MADO cackling]
Jason!
[MADO]
Jason! Jason!
I've got you now!
[AMON grunting]
[YAMORI]
You guys aren't half bad.
Sure. I'll entertain
ya for a minute or two.
[AMON] I'm sorry about that.
Guess I didn't get close enough.
No worries. Just be sure to
nail him with the next one.
[AMON]
Yes, sir.
[AMON gasps]
[AMON groaning]
[YAMORI]
Pathetic.
[AMON groans]
Did you really think that tough
guy act was gonna fool me?
How're ya doin'
over there, Amon?
[AMON grunts]
Fine, sir!
Good, then sit back
and catch your breath.
[weapons clanging]
[MADO gasps]
[YAMORI]
What a shame.
[MADO]
Yeah, For you.
[MADO grunts]
[YAMORI laughing]
Are you kidding me?
That all you got?
No! Get away!
[YAMORI] Your time's up.
Better luck next time.
[AMON]
Dammit! You all right?
[MADO] Yes. But that
bastard broke my quinque.
[ASAKI grunting]
[MADO] Well, what
do we have here?
I wonder what kind of fish
we'll be able to attract
with this little worm.
[RYOKO]
Hinami...
[ASAKI grunting]
You're not alone.
Believe me, I miss him too.
[ASAKI grunting]
[MADO gasping]
I'm so sorry, mama!
[RYOKO]
Me, too.
[ASAKI yelling]
Okay, that's enough.
[RYOKO] Are you still
angry with me?
[HINAMI] Mm-mm. So don't
cry anymore, okay?
I can't promise anything
but I'll try my hardest.
Oh, Hinami. I love you.
[RYOKO] We have to try
to stay strong for Daddy.
We'll be together again soon.
[AMON] I still can't believe
we let Jason get away.
[MADO] There's nothing we
could've done to stop him.
Not after he broke my quinque.
[AMON]
Even so.
There's no need for you
to be so hard on yourself,
we're bound to run
into him again.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Oh... I think that
we can use this.
All right.
You've been such a trooper
through all of this, Hinami.
I want to make it up to you
so I'm going to get
you a little present.
Can you think of
anything you want?
[HINAMI]
Hm...
Well. Give it some
thought, okay?
[HINAMI]
Thank you so much, Mama!
[RYOKO] I'm the one who
should be thanking you.
[doorbell rings]
[TOUKA sighs]
[TOUKA]
What do you want?
[KANEKI]
Sorry to bug you.
I was wondering if you're gonna
work your shift tomorrow.
[TOUKA]
I don't wanna.
Hey, listen--
I'm a complete failure.
I couldn't kill that woman.
[KANEKI gasps]
You know, uh,
[KANEKI] I saw Hinami and
her mother fighting earlier.
Thankfully they were
able to patch things up.
But as I was watching
them, I couldn't help
but think to myself, it must
be nice to have a family.
I realized that familial
bonds and relationships
are the same whether
you're a human or a ghoul.
I hate to admit it, but, I never
even thought about that
before I ended up like this.
If only everyone else would
come to that realization.
Then maybe Nishio and
Kimi's relationship
could serve as a guidepost
for the way things could be
between humans and ghouls.
[TOUKA]
Well? Is that it?
Uh. Well, yeah.
And also, I,
I wanted to apologize to you...
About Yoriko,
I shouldn't've mentioned her.
[KANEKI]
I'm sorry.
Um, I'll let the manager
know you need some time.
[KANEKI] I'm sure Touka agrees
with my way of thinking.
Especially after she
saw how Kimi, a human,
instantly accepted
her. But I know
that if it had gone the other
way and she had been rejected,
there would've been
no going back.
The same goes for Hide and me.
[HINAMI] Is Touka feeling
any better today?
[KANEKI]
Uh, that's a good question.
Do you think she'll be
back to normal soon?
[KANEKI]
Hm.
I've got another word for you.
How do you read
this one right here?
Lemme see.
That's a tough one,
it's "cloudburst".
[HINAMI]
What does that mean?
[KANEKI] It's a sudden rainstorm
that doesn't last verylong.
[RYOKO]
What's going on here?
[HINAMI]
Oh, hi Mom!
[RYOKO] Is this another
reading lesson?
[HINAMI]
Mm-hm!
[RYOKO] You're so sweet
to do this for her.
[KANEKI]
It's no big deal.
Well, I should go.
[HINAMI]
Thanks again, Kaneki.
[KANEKI] I'll see you tomorrow.
[HINAMI] Okay!
[HINAMI]
Hey Mama, look!
I've already learned all of
the words inside this book!
Really? I'm so
proud of you!
[HINAMI] Thanks. Can
I ask you something?
[RYOKO]
Sure, dear.
Well, now that I know
everything in this book.
[RYOKO]
Yeah?
[HINAMI]
Can you get me a new one?
I wanna learn even more
words so I can surprise Dad!
[HINAMI]
Also, his birthday's coming up
and I still need to get him a
present. So, I was wondering...
Let me guess, you want
to give him a book?
[HINAMI]
Mm-hm.
This calls for a trip
to the bookstore.
No, sorry.
[KUSABA]
Thank you, ma'am.
Excuse me.
[HIDE] Looks like
there's a storm coming.
Wow, you were right!
It is raining!
See? Does this mean that
you'll believe me next time?
Yeah!
Mom! You know what this is?
It's rain.
[HINAMI] No, a sudden storm
like this has a special name!
[RYOKO]
I didn't know that.
[HINAMI] Uh-huh! It's
called a cloudburst!
But don't worry, they
don't last very long.
At least that's what
Kaneki told me.
Goodness, he sure
is smart, isn't he?
You think Daddy knows
what a cloudburst is?
We'll have to ask him
when we see him.
It'd be so cool if I knew
something that he didn't.
That'd make me super smart, huh?
It would, indeed.
[HINAMI humming]
[RYOKO] What's gotten
into you, silly girl?
It's been a long time since
we've gone out, Mama!
Stay under the umbrella
or you'll get wet.
[HINAMI humming]
[RYOKO] Come on.
We have to go home.
[HINAMI]
But why?
[HINAMI] But I thought
we were gonna go
to that other place, Mama!
[KUSABA inaudible]
Is something wrong?
No, dear. There's just
something I need to do.
[HINAMI gasps]
Why did you stop?
[HINAMI inhales]
I smell Daddy!
[RYOKO]
Huh?
That's his scent! He's
gotta be somewhere nearby!
No way.
[HINAMI giggling]
He came to get us, Mama!
[RYOKO]
Hinami!
[HINAMI]
Come on, he's this way!
[RYOKO] No, you come
back here right now!
It's Daddy!
Wait! Hinami!
Where is he?
No, stop! Hinami!
It's Daddy! It's him! I know it!
[RYOKO]
Hinami!
[HINAMI]
I've missed you so much!
You're not my Daddy.
[RYOKO]
Hinami!
Mama. That's his scent.
[MADO] Don't you
just love the rain?
[MADO]
Although I have to admit
I'm glad it's not raining any
harder than this. Why, you ask?
Because it dulls ghouls' senses,
so you wouldn't have been
able to pick up his scent.
I don't suppose that I could
have a moment of your time.
Mrs. Fueguchi?
Mama...
[HINAMI]
I'm scared.
Oh...
[HINAMI gasps]
Run, dear.
Run fast.
But, Mama...
No...
Don't be scared. Just go to
Anteiku and I'll meet you there.
You don't have to worry,
I promise I'll be
right behind you.
Mama! I can't!
[HINAMI]
I wanna stay here with you!
[NAKAJIMA] Now Kusaba!
Use your Q-bullets!
[KUSABA]
Right!
Hurry, go!
[HINAMI gasps]
[HINAMI sobbing]
[KUSABA]
Hold it!
[MADO] Was that little display
meant to tug at my heartstrings?
'Cause it made me sick!
Just leave us alone!
[HINAMI]
Somebody, please! Help me!
Kaneki!
Touka!
[HINAMI sobbing, panting]
[HINAMI sobbing]
Mama!
Hey, guess what Nishiki?
What?
I got you a
little something.
What's this?
[KIMI] It's called
a bangle bracelet.
See? I've got one too.
[NISHIKI] Does she
seriously want us
to wear matching jewelry?
[NISHIKI] Well, I'll wear
it since it's a present.
But man, these bangles are
about as ugly as horse crap.
[KIMI] Huh? What do you
mean they're ugly?
Oh, did I say that?
I'm sorry, Kimi.
I didn't realize I said that in
my outside voice, don't hurt me!