[AMON] Kotaro Amon. I've been
assigned to Division One.
It's an honor to meet you
and join your ranks.
[ARIMA] I see the new blood's
looking strong this year.
[AMON]
Special Investigator Arima!
I've heard great things
about you from the Academy.
It's a pleasure, Amon.
Thank you. It's an honor, sir.
[ARIMA] You'll be under
Mr. Mado, one of our best.
Yes, sir!
[INVESTIGATOR A] You're
stickin' the rookie with him?
Whelp, I guess
them's the breaks.
[INVESTIGATOR B]
Don't let him
talk you into anything
crazy and you'll be fine.
There you are.
Mr. Mado, meet your new
partner, Kotaro Amon.
[MADO]
Hmm. Yes, he'll do nicely.
Well we have our orders.
Shall we shake
hands, seal the deal?
[AMON] It's a pleasure
to meet you, sir.
This ghoul's
codenamed Applehead?
Yeah. And she's had her fill
of forbidden fruit lately
50 victims in
the past year.
What do we have to work
with so far, any suspects?
Well, there is one.
[MADO]
Kie Muramatsu, age 68.
She's been spotted at a
few of the crime scenes.
Her?
What, are you surprised?
Didn't realize ghouls get
old like the rest of us?
[AMON]
No, sir.
There's not a
doubt in my mind
that this little old biddy
is our wolf in disguise.
[AMON] What makes
you think that, sir?
Instinct.
Uh. Excuse me?
[MADO] Instincts are nothing
to sneeze at, young man.
I mean, take a look at me. I
trust mine and I'm still alive.
[AMON] Of all the investigators
I could've been partnered with.
[MADO]
Good afternoon, Ms. Muramatsu.
[MURAMATSU]
Oh, hello Investigator.
Isn't the weather lovely today?
Goodness, who is this handsome
young man you've got with you?
Allow me to introduce
my new partner, Amon.
Nice to meet you, ma'am.
[MURAMATSU giggles]
[AMON] Does he really think
this sweet old lady's a ghoul?
Anyway, I Just wanted to
stop by and say thank you
for sending me your
medical certificate.
I took some time to
look over your results,
paying special attention
to your RC Factor.
Your RC cell count is 231,
which is good news
because that means you're
definitely not a ghoul.
I apologize for the
inconvenience ma'am,
you have a lovely day.
[AMON]
Why didn't you tell me
you had a medical certificate
from her, Mr. Mado?
Do you know how easy it is to
forge a document these days?
A scrap of paper
doesn't prove anything.
Even so...
I only asked for the certificate
to lure her into a false
sense of security.
You could learn a thing
or two from me, Amon.
After all, I'm a seasoned pro,
and you're still wet
behind the ears.
Whatever you say, sir.
Well, if it's whatever I say.
Why don't you pop open
that briefcase for me?
[AMON]
Why?
I'd love to see what
kind of quinques
they're giving to the
rookies these days.
C'mon, let's have a peek.
[AMON] Forgive my impertinance,
Senior Investigator,
but I take my
job very seriously.
I'm not playing show
and tell with you.
Not when there are
lives at stake!
Now if you'll excuse me.
[MADO]
Hm...
[AMON]
Crazy old, fool.
He doesn't seem to be
taking the job seriously.
How did he even become
a Senior Investigator?
[AMON]
Ms. Muramatsu?
[MURAMATSU]
I can't thank you enough
for helping me, young man.
[AMON]
It's my pleasure.
You protect us from ghouls and
help old ladies with their bags.
Your mother must be so proud.
[AMON]
Really, it's nothing.
Nonetheless, I'm very grateful.
[AMON] I can't believe he'd
suspect this sweet old lady.
He's definitely
got a screw loose.
I have to admit, this is heavy.
How'd you get as far as you did?
[AMON gasps]
[AMON grunting]
[MURAMATSU] Since you asked so
nicely I'll tell ya' my secret.
I eat well.
[MURAMATSU yelling]
[AMON groaning]
[MURAMATSU chuckling]
[AMON]
So this is how it ends.
[MURAMATSU yelling]
[AMON gasps]
[MADO] Ya see? What'd
I tell you, Amon?
Anyone can be a ghoul,
even a sweet old lady.
[MADO giggling]
Mr. Mado...
[AMON sighs]
[AMON]
I'm sorry, Sir. Thank you.
[MADO] Don't be,
you were perfect.
Seriously, you were the best
ghoul bait I've had in years.
At least your heart's
in the right place.
Now if you want
to keep it there,
and not in some granny's
gullet, keep this in mind.
When the foe is before
you, you fight!
Even if it costs you your life!
That's what it means
to be an investigator.
Yes, sir.
[SHINOHARA]
Well, if it isn't Amon!
How ya doin'?
[AMON]
Mr. Shinohara!
Hey! It's been a while.
How've you been holdin' up?
[AMON] Not too bad.
So what brings you out here?
[SHINOHARA]
Actually, I came to see you.
Whatcha got there?
[AMON]
They're for Mr. Mado.
[SHINOHARA] Oh, of course.
Sorry, I should've known.
[AMON]
It's okay
You know he really was
one of the best we had.
I still can't believe he's gone.
[AMON] Anyway, what
can I do for you, sir?
Oh. Don't worry about
it now, we can talk later.
[AMON]
Are you sure?
Yeah, you go see Mado.
[SHINOHARA]
By the way.
You should know...
he was very proud of you
and what you've achieved.
Thanks. That's good to hear.
I felt the same way.
He was a great partner.
[NEWSCASTER A] In a gruesome
scene uncovered late last night,
several bodies were found in
the 11th Ward. The CCG is now
treating the incident as
a ghoul related crime.
[HINAMI]
Hey, Kaneki!
[KANEKI]
Hinami, is that you?
Yep, you guessed it!
That's quite the
disguise you got there.
[HINAMI] Pretty cool, right? I
borrowed most of it from Touka.
Yomo's gonna take
me shopping today!
Shopping for what?
[HINAMI] We're getting
a bird house for Hetare!
Oh.
[HETARE]
Hetare! Hetare!
All right then, Yomo. Keep
a close eye on Hinami, okay?
[HETARE]
I'm a cat! Hetare!
[HINAMI]
See ya later!
[KANEKI] After she
lost her family,
Hinami ended up
living with Touka.
We thought we'd lost
her for a while there,
but she's slowly getting
her smile back.
[HINAMI gasps]
[HETARE coughing]
[HINAMI sobbing]
[KANEKI]
Oh, uh, hey, Touka.
You seen the bird?
Yeah, he's with Yoshimura.
[TOUKA sighs]
[TOUKA] It pukes, it molts, and
it haunts my dreams. I hate it.
[KANEKI]
Touka isn't one to share,
but I can tell that
she's distracted.
Quit starin' if you
like that eye!
I'm sorry.
[KANEKI] Our wounds
are starting to heal.
In fact, there are times
when it feels like things
are almost back to normal. But
I don't know if that's possible
after everything
we've been through.
[HINAMI whimpering]
[KANEKI] We were hit by
a tragedy and none of us
have fully recovered from it.
But we're resolved
to go on living.
For those we've lost and
the child they left behind.
We're going to continue to fight
until we get our old lives back.
[dishes clattering]
What the hell is the matter with
you? You're useless, woman!
[TOUKA] Excuse me? You
better shut your mouth
before I shove it full of
glass, you misogynist pig!
Oh, Yeah? You
would try that,
'cause you don't know
where the trash can is!
"Ha! I've been here
too long to bus tables".
Well, that's the least
you can do, you dick!
Because you suck so hard
at everything else!
So Screw you and your lazy ass.
Do us both a favor and quit.
[NISHIKI] You'd love that,
wouldn't you? Y'know what?
We have a business to run,
guys. So is there any chance
you could cut back
on all the cursing?
[NISHIKI] Try it, bitch!
[TOUKA] Bring it, dumbass!
[NISHIKI] Look, I'm a gentleman,
[KOMA sighs]
[KOMA] You're a brave pair
to ignore me like this.
Impetuous even.
It's like you've never heard
the legend of the Devil Ape.
I'm not lazy!
Oh, hell yeah, you are!
[NISHIKI] If I were lazy I
wouldn't have gotten into Kamii!
[NEWSCASTER A]
Among the casualties,
was a CCG investigator--
[AMON]
I failed you Mr. Mado.
I should've fought harder,
gotten to you sooner.
Then the rabbit would be dead.
And you'd still be with us.
[ITORI]
So what, you were like,
possessed by Rize's
ghost or something?
[KANEKI] That's not exactly
how I would describe it.
I don't remember much.
I must've blacked out.
When I came to,
I'd impaled Yomo.
Damn. You ran him through?
Most ghouls aren't
strong enough
to pierce through a
chiseled body like Ren's.
[ITORI] I know who to call
if I ever need a hit man.
But Itori I--
Oh, relax, I'm only kidding!
What is it with you and Ren?
Everybody else thinks
I'm freakin' hilarious.
[KANEKI]
Sorry, I'll work on that.
What's got me worried is that
this has happened once before.
Just like last night,
I could feel Rize's presence,
as she took control.
[ITORI] And here I thought
you came to hang out with me.
You want the scoop
on Rize, don't ya?
[KANEKI]
Yeah.
[ITORI] Well, I'll do
what I can for ya.
You've disarmed me with
that boyish charm of yours.
Rize, huh?
To be totally honest with you...
[KANEKI]
Yeah?
[ITORI] I don't know much
about her. I can tell you
the life story of anyone
else in this ward,
but she was a mystery.
It's the weirdest thing.
One day she just popped
up outta nowhere.
[KANEKI]
Whaddya mean?
[ITORI] Nobody knows
where she came from
or what she was up to
before she showed up here.
But, mysterious as she was,
she had to come from somewhere,
that girl had a past.
The info's out there, it'll
just take some work to find.
[KANEKI]
Yeah, I guess you're right.
You could start by
going to the 11th Ward.
[KANEKI]
What makes you say that?
Because I asked her
where she'd moved from,
and that was her answer.
I'd start there if I were you.
Thanks for the tip.
[JUZO humming, giggling]
[KANEKI] Maybe I should check
it out when I get a day off.
[KANEKI grunts]
[KANEKI]
Oh, excuse me!
[JUZO]
Oh no, excuse me!
I mean, you weren't the one
who was dancin' around
with your eyes closed.
Anyway, I'd love to stick around
and chat but adventure calls!
[KANEKI] I dunno what it is,
but something about that kid...
...smells delicious.
[JUZO] Let's see, insurance
card, and here's a library card,
Ahh, here we go.
I found his student ID!
Ken Kaneki, 19 years old.
Whaddaya know, he's
the same age as me!
Alright, it's time
to make it rain!
It kinda feels like
he robbed me.
[HIDE]
You got pickpocketed?
[KANEKI]
Mm-hmm.
Do you remember what
his face looked like?
Nah, I'm not even
sure that it was a he.
[HIDE] Did you file
a police report?
[KANEKI] It's not like
there was any money in it.
[NISHIKI]
Dude, you're pathetic.
Those creeps wouldn't
mess with you
if you didn't ooze "pushover"
with every fiber of your being.
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER A] Breaking
news: this just in from the CCG.
[KANEKI]
Uh. I'll work on that.
[NEWSCASTER A]
Chairman Washu Tsuneyoshi has
announced an unusual
change in CCG strategy
Due to recent events, a large
numer of investigators will be
sent to the 11th and 20th Wards.
[HIDE] Weird.
[HIDE] Is the 20th Ward really
given' 'em that much trouble?
[KANEKI]
Beats me, man.
[HIDE] I wonder if the
balance has shifted.
What?
[HIDE]
Hm? Oh.
It might sound silly, but
I have this theory that
there's a ghoul organization
that monitors this ward.
[KANEKI] Okay. What
makes you think that?
Well, we haven't had as
many predatory cases
as the others,
that is, until now.
I figured it's because
the 20th Ward's ghouls
have some kinda
pact or somethin'.
[KANEKI gasps]
Um...
As soon as their predation
began to attract attention,
both the binge-eaters and
the gourmets vanished.
It seems conceivable that this
ghoul organization would want
to clean house to avoid
a crackdown by the CCG.
[KANEKI gulps]
Hey, Are you alright? You're
lookin' a little pale, man.
Uh... Yeah, I
feel fine, really.
I'm just surprised. Ghouls, huh?
I never knew you had
an interest in them.
Yeah. We need
to talk, Kaneki.
About this new book I got,
it's friggin' amazing!
[KANEKI]
Huh?
[HIDE] Okay, Check it out! So
there's this badass ghoul gang
and they all wear clown
masks. They call the shots
in the 3rd Ward, at least
until this ghoul named Matsubara
dips out of Wakayama
and heads for Tokyo!
[HIDE] I gotta jet.
See ya later, man!
[STAFFER] Investigator Amon,
reinforcements from
the head office are
waiting for you upstairs.
[AMON] Thank you.
I'll be right there.
[AMON] I wonder
who they've sent us.
I doubt it's a veteran officer,
they don't have any to spare.
[elevator dings]
Hey!
[AMON]
Mr. Shinohara!
Don't tell me that they've
assigned you here.
[SHINOHARA]
No, I'm headed elsewhere.
But you get these
two fine officers.
[AMON]
Hoji!
Hello, Kotaro. It's
been far too long.
[AMON]
You can say that again.
[SEIDO]
Um. Mr. Amon, sir?
It's an honor to meet
you! Seido Takizawa,
Investigator Second Class,
Control Division One, sir!
He's been talking about
meeting you all day.
Looks like you've got a fan.
[SEIDO] Assistant
Special Investigator Hoji,
you're embarrassing me!
I mean, not that
that's a problem, sir.
[AMON] Nice to meet you,
Investigator Takizawa.
[SEIDO]
It's such an honor, sir!
Amon,
these two are gonna keep an
eye on the 20th Ward for you.
At least, until you get back.
You and I have been assigned
to a special task force.
A task force, are you
sure about this?
[SHINOHARA] Heard it
from Marude himself.
The 11th Ward. There's
something brewing.
Yeah, so I've heard.
[NISHIKI] Are you for real?
Sounds like shit's really
hittin' the fan
in the 11th, huh?
[KOMA] Yeah. I was
talkin' to Yomo.
Apparently a buncha'
ghouls've teamed up down there
to hunt the investigators.
Now the whole damn ward's
like a slaughterhouse.
[NISHIKI]
Man.
Things get any worse. it'll
mean big trouble for all of us.
What do you mean
by "big trouble"?
Could be a war.
That's right. You guys
might get the chance
to see how I earned
the nickname, Devil Ape.
Anyway, where's Touka?
I'm not sure, but she
could with Hetare.
Seriously? But I thought
she was scared of birds.
Exposure therapy, maybe? I'll
go and check on her real quick.
[HETARE]
Hetare's a cat!
[TOUKA]
He had a family.
And I took him from them.
Hey, Touka?
[TOUKA] Do you think this little
guy's got a family out there?
[KANEKI]
Huh?
I mean...
Everybody has one, right?
Ayato!
[YOUNG AYATO]
Yeah, Sis? What's up?
[bird chirping]
[ARATA]
Poor little guy.
He must've fallen from the nest.
Whadda we do Dad?
Well, would you like to
take care of him at home?
Uh-huh!
Hey look, I
caught a worm!
[YOUNG AYATO shrieks]
You're a boy, you're
s'posed to like worms!
I know, but...
[YOUNG TOUKA]
C'mon! Do it for Chunta!
[YOUNG AYATO]
Okay.
That's a lot of
worms you caught.
[YOUNG TOUKA]
Mm-hmm.
Yeah!
You've turned into
such a tomboy, Touka,
you're just like your mother.
[YOUNG AYATO] So does that
mean I'm like you, Dad?
[ARATA] That it does,
my boy. I hate bugs, too.
So if you see one, you'll
have to call for your sister.
Whew! It looks like you
two could use a bath.
[YOUNG TOUKA]
I don't like baths,
but a hug might change my mind.
[YOUNG AYATO] I want one, too!
[ARATA] All right, deal.
[ARATA] I can't believe
how fast you're growing!
[ARATA] Touka, as the oldest
you're going to have to teach
your brother all
sorts of stuff.
And you're not off
the hook, Ayato.
You're going to have to
keep your sister safe.
'Kay!
Is that a promise?
[TOUKA] I never asked you.
What's your family like?
Well, uh--
My dad's been dead for about
as long as I can remember.
And my mom...
[KANEKI] She died while
I was in grade school.
Sorry.
It's dinnertime, Hetare!
[HINAMI]
Hi Kaneki!
[KANEKI] Hey, Hinami.
Did you get a haircut?
[HINAMI] Yeah, I did!
Do you like it?
[KANEKI] It really suits you.
Did you go to a hair salon?
I didn't have to!
Touka cut it for me right here!
[TOUKA] You surprised?
[KANEKI] Well, yeah.
[TOUKA] Didn't think I
had it in me, or what?
[KANEKI] It's not that. I'm just
impressed that it looks so good.
You've got talent.
It's no big deal.
[HETARE] Shut your
yap, stupid bird!
Don't peck me,
you son of a bitch!
[TOUKA] Are you tattling
on me, you stupid bird?
Better shut your yap before
you end up in a deep fryer!
[HETARE]
Asshole!
[BOTH giggle]
It's so bitter.
[NICO] You've met her
before, haven't you?
[MAN]
Who, Rize?
Yeah, but I don't exactly
have fond memories of her.
[knuckle cracks]
She won't get away
from me this time.
[can thudding]
[ICHIMI]
So this is the 20th Ward?
I've never been here before.
[JIRO] For some reason, it feels
like time moves slower here,
know what I mean?
[BANJO] Idiots. Don't
let your guard down.
We've got a job to do,
let's get moving.
[SANTE] We've got a lot
of ground to cover, Banjo,
where should we start?
[BANJO] There's a coffee
shop here called "Anteiku,"
that's run by some old ghoul.
Let's move. Rize's
been there before.
I just know it.
[screaming]
[thudding]
[MAN] These guys were
weak, even for humans.
Heard from that
dumbass, Banjo yet?
[SUBORDINATE A]
Not a word.
[MAN] Damn, he's
useless. At this rate,
Yamori and his fairy friend'll
get the jump on him.
Fine then. We'll head
to the 20th Ward ourselves.
And then secure
Rize, at all costs.
[SUBORDINATES]
Yes, sir!
[SUBORDINATE A]
Hey, wait a minute,
isn't that the ward
you grew up in?
[MAN] Yeah. But I don't
remember much about the place,
except that it's full of
human-loving cowards.
Ha ha. Come to think of it,
I still have some family there.
She's one of those
cowards I mentioned.
Ha! Are we in a
western or what?
Looks like that handsome
white-haired ghoul's
about to get a
thrashing from Uta.
Heard someone's makin'
waves in my part of town.
That you?
What's with those goofy
glasses you're wearin'?
[UTA laughing]
[UTA] Hey guys. wanna watch
me make this pansy cry?
[MAN A]
Whoa, he means business!
[MAN B] They're gonna
smash up the 4th Ward!
[YOMO] On second thought,
I'm outta here.