[KANEKI whimpering, gasping]
Is that you?
Momma?
[KANEKI gasps]
[KANEKI]
Rize...
But how?
[RIZE]
Long time, no see, Kaneki.
Wow, you look awful. Been
through the ringer, huh?
Sucks to be you.
[KANEKI whimpering]
[click]
[RIZE giggling] Sounds like
the Master is home.
[KANEKI gasping, screaming]
[YAMORI laughing]
[KANEKI screaming]
[YAMORI] How far did
you manage to count?
[KANEKI gasping]
To 500...
...59!
[YAMORI]
I've got a bucket here.
I want you to fill
it to the brim.
[KANEKI screaming]
[KANEKI] Since the first cut,
Yamori told me to count
backwards from 1,000, out-loud,
in increments of seven.
I didn't understand
why, at first.
Then I realized he was
trying to keep me sane.
so I'd be aware of every
single cut that followed.
I was clinging to every number.
[KANEKI gasps]
[KANEKI] Meanwhile, he
took my fingers and toes.
over and over, and over, and
over, and over, and over...
Every time my fingers and toes
grew back, it was a reminder.
I'm not human anymore.
I'm a monster.
[RIZE yawns]
Good Morning.
[KANEKI]
Rize, are you still alive?
[RIZE] That depends on
your definition of 'living',
I suppose. New topic!
Tell me about your mom. What
kind of person was she?
Earlier, you thought
I was her, right?
She's over there.
[KANEKI gasping]
[KANEKI]
Are you still alive?
[KANEKI gasps]
[YOUNG KANEKI]
Hey, Mom, I'm home!
[KANEKI'S MOTHER]
Welcome home, sweetie!
[RIZE]
I barely recognize you.
[YOUNG KANEKI]
I found another one!
[RIZE]
You were so full of energy.
What's that you're doing?
[KANEKI] When I had
trouble with reading.
She'd carefully write
out the pronunciations.
We'd drill over them until
I could do it on my own.
Is she leaving you all alone?
[lock clicks]
[KANEKI]
She had to go to work.
[RIZE]
Now where are we?
[KANEKI]
My Dad's Study, at home.
[RIZE]
Tell me about him.
[KANEKI]
I never got to know him.
When he passed away, I
was still just an infant.
These books...
They were the only real
connection I had to him.
I fell in love
with reading here.
[RIZE] Weren't you
lonely, all by yourself?
[KANEKI] I had a
kind, caring mother.
And all the books I
could ever ask for.
My mom really was
a wonderful person.
She worked so hard, but
our home was always tidy.
She was a joy to be around.
She got along with everyone.
And she never, ever
lost her temper.
I loved her dearly. I'm
very proud to be her son.
[KANEKI'S MOTHER] Ken, It's
okay to feel sadness from loss.
As long as you remember to stay
kind, you'll find joy again.
[KANEKI, YOUNG KANEKI]
'Kay.
[KANEKI] "It's far better
to feel pain yourself,
than to inflict it on others.
As long as you remain kind,
you will find joy again."
That's what my mom
always told me.
[RIZE] Yeah, she was a
wonderful person, alright.
She's the reason you're
living this hell now.
[KANEKI screaming]
[YAMORI] I'm tellin' ya, kid.
You're really somethin' else.
So, have you figured out
the reason you're here?
Why you're special?
It's your regenerative ability.
That kind of power
doesn't come standard
in your run-of-the-mill ghoul.
All thanks to Kanou's
science project.
[YAMORI sniffing]
He sewed in Rize's bits
and presto! Instant ghoul!
With that one eye, and
the stank of the glutton.
You're a goddamn collector's
item, and you're all mine.
[YAMORI] The
Chinese Red-headed Centipede.
Nasty little shit.
I'm gonna let him run around in
your ear for a little while.
You don't mind, do you?
[KANEKI]
No, please. I'm begging you!
D-Don't do it!
Please, have mercy.
No! No, please! Stop!
Don't come near me!
[static]
[KANEKI laughing maniacally]
Oh, boy!
He popped! Look at him go!
That's the way, maggot!
Dance!
You want me to cut out your
heart and eat it, don't you?
You want it to be all over?
'Cause that's the only way out!
Beg me for death!
[YAMORI cackling]
Please, kill me. Eat me alive.
Just end it, I'm begging you!
[KANEKI whimpering]
[RIZE] "It's better
to feel pain yourself,
than to inflict it on others".
You bought in to that
masochistic crap?
[KANEKI] Of course I did.
It's how Mom raised me.
Is that bad?
[RIZE] You chose to blindly obey
your mother's "words of wisdom"?
Yeah, that is bad.
Are you sure she
was all that great?
Because, from where I'm
standing, it seems her lessons
haven't brought you
anything but misery.
[RIZE]
What's that, there?
[KANEKI]
An allowance.
[RIZE]
For whom?
[KANEKI]
My aunt. Mom's sister.
She always claimed to
be struggling financially.
Mom felt bad for her,
so she'd give her money.
She had a part-time
job during the day.
She collected garbage at night.
Mom never stopped working.
Even her free time was
devoted to work.
You're exhausted.
Take care of yourself.
[KANEKI'S MOTHER]
I'm fine, Ken.
[RIZE]
Then what happened?
[KANEKI sighs]
What do you think?
[KANEKI] She worked herself
to death. I lost her.
Suddenly, I was all alone.
I was just a little
kid and I had no one.
[YOUNG HIDE yelling]
[YOUNG HIDE] Dang it!
How long were you gonna--
[KANEKI] Then again,
I wasn't completely alone.
One person was always
there for me.
[HIDE]
Okay, serious question,
if you were a ghoul would you
eat that hottie from Class 2?
The one you keep starin' at?
[KANEKI]
Who, Yoshikawa?
I don't stare at her
that much, do I?
[KANEKI] Hide wasn't just
my friend, he was all I had.
[RIZE] I can see why
he means so much to you.
Too bad. The way
things are going,
you'll probably end
up losing him, too.
[KANEKI gasps]
And it'll be all your fault.
[muffled grunting, screaming]
[YAMORI] "All the drawbacks
and detriment in this world
stem from a lack
of individual ability."
The person who told me that
was a real sack of crap.
but, that doesn't make
his words any less true.
It's an important lesson
to learn. You'll see.
Now, I've been thinkin',
and I realized, I've been going
about this the wrong way.
Ripping off your digits
has been fun and all,
but what I really want to
rip apart is your mind.
So I devised a little game
that should do the trick.
Oh...
...yeah!
A couple of love birds.
Let's play!
[muffled grunting, screaming]
You're gonna pick
which one I kill,
him or her!
[YAMORI] What's the matter?
You don't owe them anything.
Just choose.
Say. You weren't
holding out hope
that they'd get you outta
here, were you, kid?
These weaklings? They're your
knights in shining armor?
[knuckle cracks]
Well? Pick one.
Choose.
Keep me waiting and
I'll kill both of them.
Let me rephrase it for ya.
[knuckle cracks]
Which one of them
do you want to save?
[KANEKI whimpering]
[muffled grunting]
No, I can't. I can't
do it. Please.
Why do I have to be
the one to choose?
Hurry. Time's a wastin'.
No! If I choose,
I might as well be
killing them myself!
Just pick one! C'mon!
Choose!
Brat! It's easy!
The guy? The girl?
Right! Left!
Pick one!
Didn't you hear me? There's
no way I'm doing that!
You'll have to kill me first!
Fine. Have it your way.
[YAMORI] I'll show
you how it's done.
[YAMORI]
See? It's easy!
Do you like my pick?
Well? Speak up!
You can still save
her if you want to!
C'mon! She's dying,
here, Kaneki!
Choose!
Look at them! The guy?
Or the girl?
[KANEKI gasping]
[YAMORI] Well?
[YAMORI]
This is your last chance!
Do it!
[YAMORI yelling]
Please, Kaneki, pick me!
[SHU]
Haru's going to die!
Dammit, hurry!
[SHU]
Kaneki, I'm begging you!
No! Please!
[HARU gagging]
[SHU screaming, sobbing]
[YAMORI]
Too late. She broke.
[KANEKI whimpering, gasping]
[SHU growling]
Now, they'll both rot in hell.
[SHU groans]
[KANEKI]
But, It's not my fault.
No. It is.
I'm the one to blame.
[RIZE] It took a lot of blood
for you to learn that lesson.
[RIZE]
Do me a favor, 'kay?
Don't just sit there
wallowing in your own guilt.
That's not going to
change anything either.
You've got a problem
with that, you know.
You're complacent.
You never change or adapt.
That's why you're at fault.
Did you think you could
blame it on something else?
Coincidence? Tragedy? Fate?
Sorry, but destiny doesn't
exist in this world.
It's all just one
person's circumstances
colliding with another's.
And, who creates
those circumstances?
Would you care to guess?
It's you, Kaneki.
"All the detriment
in this world
stems from a lack of
individual ability."
Jason sure nailed that one.
If you were smart to
the ways of the world.
You and I may never have
come together like this.
Aw, you were
such easy prey.
You practically begged
me to devour you.
Then the doctor had his way.
And we were turned
into a Grade-A freak.
All because you
were such a fool.
But you're supposed to take
the moral high road
and suffer, right?
Do you think the loves
birds would agree?
You had everything you needed
to kill the son of a bitch.
and all you did was watch him.
Or, you could have
picked one of them,
and the other would
still be alive.
But you failed them both.
Just like you failed
her that day.
[KANEKI]
Ryoko...
No.
[KANEKI grunting, screaming]
No! Stop it!
[RIZE] And she won't
be the last one.
[KANEKI]
Touka...
Hinami...
[RIZE]
You'll lose everything again.
[KANEKI]
I'm here, Hide!
[HIDE]
You're a monster.
No, I'm not...
I swear.
Why didn't you tell
me about any of this?
You had a choice to
make, and you failed.
That's why this--
[HIDE]
...is-is happening.
[KANEKI screaming]
[RIZE]
You see?
You have no right to play
the victim, Kaneki.
This is the life and
the future you chose.
Why are you crying?
This is your doing.
You said you'd rather
feel pain yourself,
than inflict it on others.
You choose to be neutral.
But, you know what happens
when you play both sides?
In the end, everybody loses.
You saw what happened
with your mother.
If she'd had the guts to tell
her lazy sister to get a job,
she wouldn't have worked
herself into an early grave.
[KANEKI]
Shut up.
[RIZE] Not much of
a mother, was she?
If she loved you, she would've
abandoned her sister
and focused on raising her son.
[KANEKI]
Please stop it.
Be honest with me.
You wanted her to choose
you over your aunt.
[KANEKI]
It's not true.
[KANEKI sobbing]
[KANEKI]
Mom...
Oh, Mom.
I wish...
I wish that you were
still here with me.
I hate being all alone.
I miss you so much it hurts.
Why?
Why couldn't you
just live for me?
You had a choice!
Why didn't you choose me?!
Even if it meant
forsaking your aunt?
Yes, if she'd be here now!
Even if it meant hurting her?
[KANEKI]
If it had to be done.
[RIZE] Even if it
meant killing her?
[KANEKI]
Whatever it takes!
Good boy!
[RIZE]
Now you've got it, Kaneki.
You've learned the lesson your
mother couldn't seem to grasp.
That, sometimes,
to protect one thing,
you have to have the resolve
to let go of another.
Her actions didn't make her
kind, they made her weak.
She didn't have the
resolve, the strength
to turn her back and
focus on what's important.
[RIZE] But you're not
weak like she was.
You have the power to
break this chain of grief.
Or will you die at
the hands of Yamori?
[KANEKI]
No. No, I won't!
[RIZE] If Aogiri continues
to get stronger, it's only
a matter of time before they
attempt to seize the 20th Ward.
[KANEKI]
I won't let that happen.
[RIZE] Good, otherwise your dear
friend, Hide and your pals
at Anteiku might have
to endure the same hell
you've just been through.
[KANEKI] Anyone who tries
to take them from me
will get no mercy.
[RIZE] Are you sure you have
the strength to back that up?
[KANEKI]
Yes.
Does this mean you'll finally
stop holding me back?
'Course not. That'd be foolish.
[chains clattering]
[KANEKI] I'm never going
to let you have control.
And what if your decision
ends up being the wrong one,
in the end?
[KANEKI]
That won't happen,
because I'm not wrong.
[KANEKI]
What's wrong...
...is this messed up world!
[RIZE] That will do,
Kaneki. At least, for now.
To live is to devour others.
That's part of who you are now.
[KANEKI swallows]
[RIZE]
Go eat.
[KANEKI]
I am a ghoul.
[YAMORI]
Bad news, kid.
It's been fun but I'm afraid our
play time has to come to an end.
Apparently, the doves are
about to swoop down on us.
It's my job to go out
and clip their wings
with extreme prejudice.
[YAMORI]
Aogiri won't hesitate
to slaughter anyone
who gets in our way.
Obviously, that's mostly humans,
but ghouls aren't exempt either.
That includes your adopted
family of coffee drinkers.
What do they call that
café of theirs again?
Anteiku, right?
Yeah, that's the one.
Aogiri's got their
eye on them.
They're targeted
for elimination.
[YAMORI]
Kaneki!
Let me take from you!
Let me devour you!
Every last bite!
[YAMORI gasping]
[RIZE laughing]
We meet again.
[RIZE] Poor, Yamori.
All that brawn and no brain.
[YAMORI laughing]
[YAMORI] I knew there was
something special about you!
[knuckle cracks]
[YAMORI yelling]
[YAMORI]
I'll swallow you whole!
[YAMORI grunting, gagging]
Why don't you chew on this?
[YAMORI growling]
[YAMORI panting]
You taste foul.
[YAMORI growls]
What'd you do? You bit me!
[KANEKI] Yeah, and your
flesh is disgusting;
it tastes just like rotten meat.
[YAMORI]
I've got you now!
[YAMORI grunts]
After everything you've done,
you think that would hurt me?
[YAMORI] I'll kill
you. I swear it.
I'll kill you! Kill you!
Kill you dead!
You're dinner!
I'll rip you to pieces!
[YAMORI yelling]
[knuckle cracks]
[YAMORI] I'll chomp
your head off!
[YAMORI panting]
[YAMORI growling, grunting]
[YAMORI grunting]
[YAMORI growls]
[YAMORI grunts
[YAMORI panting, cackling]
[YAMORI gasps]
[KANEKI]
Not too bad...
...but I can do better.
[knuckle cracks]
[YAMORI growling]
[YAMORI yelling]
[YAMORI grunting, growling]
[YAMORI groaning]
[YAMORI screaming]
[knuckle cracks]
1,000 minus seven.
[YAMORI grunting]
[YAMORI screaming]
I'm waiting for an answer.
[KANEKI]
What's 1,000 minus seven?
[YAMORI screaming]
[KANEKI] I can keep
this up all day.
[YAMORI panting]
[YAMORI screaming]
993!
986!
900...
900 and...
70...
...9!
900...
70...
...2!
900...
...65
[KANEKI] Remember, you're the
one who tried to eat me first.
[knuckle cracks]
So you'll get what's
coming to you...
...when I eat you instead.
[KANEKI gasps]
[chomp]
[KANEKI swallows]