[AMON] I can't let it
end here. Not like this.
[AMON grunts]
[AMON growling]
[KANEKI screaming]
[KANEKI] What is this?
I don't understand.
What am I doing here?
[TOUKA]
Like hell he's tagging along!
Whatever his reasons, they
aren't for our benefit.
I know how you feel,
but, the hard truth
is that we're short on
allies at the moment.
With his help, we
might save Kaneki.
[TOUKA] How are you even
alive? We left you for dead.
Oui, Mon cheri!
But in desperation,
I heeded your advice.
And, to my surprise,
it actually worked!
Not only did I fully heal,
I also discovered
I'm quite tasty.
You really think he
plans to help us?
He's only in it for
a chance at Kaneki.
[YOMO] He won't get one.
I'll make sure of it.
So put it out of your mind.
[YOSHIMURA] Has there been any
movement from the CCG yet?
[YOMO] It looks like they'll
be going for a full assault
once the civilians are clear.
[YOSHIMURA]
That's when we'll move.
If we use their attack as cover,
we'll have the best chance
of getting Kaneki out.
Are there any objections?
No, sir.
[YAMORI]
Oh, good. You're awake.
This is my room.
Make yourself comfy.
[YAMORI] Tatara decided he
didn't need you, after all.
But one man's garbage
is another man's hobby.
I'm glad you're here.
I've wanted to invite you
over for a while now.
Since the moment
we met, in fact.
[knuckle cracks]
[YAMORI]
Or maybe,
since even before we met.
So please,
do your best not to
disappoint me, alright?
[KANEKI whimpering]
[YAMORI]
RC inhibition fluid.
You know what that does once it
gets into a ghoul's bloodstream?
It suppresses all
kagune activity.
When that happens, their flesh
might as well be
construction paper.
'Least as far as my
scalpel is concerned.
Slice's right through it.
Just like a human.
[KANEKI gasping]
[YAMORI]
The only problem is,
hypodermic needles
can't break your skin.
So I'll have to stick you in
the one spot it will go through.
The mucus membrane.
Right in here!
[KANEKI screaming]
[MABUCHI]
Here's the situation, everyone.
Two months ago, the
shopping mall in question
was occupied by a
large force of ghouls.
Over the last week,
they've increased their
numbers substantially.
So far, we count
500 ghouls inside.
[MABUCHI] As you can see--
[AMON] Mr. Mado...
[SHINOHARA]
Here.
What is it?
[SHINOHARA] Mado told
me to give it to you.
He said you should use it
when the time was right.
[SHINOHARA]
Take it.
[AMON] I'll make sure
it's put to good use.
[SHINOHARA] The civilian
evacuation has been completed!
Let's kick some ass!
[INVESTIGATORS]
Yes, sir!
[NEWSCASTER A] At this moment,
a joint force of over 1,000 CCG
and Law Enforcement
officials are standing-by,
waiting for the word
to storm the 11th Ward.
The leader on the scene is the
man responsible for locating
the ghoul base, Special
Investigator Marude Itsuki.
We've staked our
lives on this op.
And we guarantee the safety
of up to 99% of the population.
As for the remaining one,
their lives hinge on the rest
of you working together.
[MARUDE]
With your cooperation,
I know we can bring peace and
order back to the 11th Ward!
[NEWSCASTER A] That was
Special Investigator Marude.
[HIDE]
Kaneki...
[KANEKI screaming]
[YAMORI]
How many was that?
I lost count, again.
[KANEKI]
500...
50...
...9.
[YAMORI]
Take some time to recover.
I'll be back in a little while.
[KANEKI]
500...
[YAMORI]
Clean that up.
[HOODED MAN]
Yes, sir.
[KANEKI gasping]
[HOODED MAN]
I'm sorry.
[KANEKI]
Banjo? Is that you?
The moment I see an opening,
I'm gettin' you outta here.
So don't you quit on me, okay?
[KANEKI]
Why me? What did I do?
[BANJO] I heard, you know.
About Rize's death.
You could've just told
me from the start,
but you were trying
to spare my feelings.
You're a good guy, Kaneki.
The next shift
is Shu and Haru.
They're friends of mine.
If something comes up,
find a way to tell them.
Hang in there.
We'll get you out.
[KANEKI sobbing]
Is everybody ready to move?
[TOUKA] Uta, hey!
Are you coming with us?
'Course I am. I can't leave a
valued customer to such a fate.
[YOSHIMURA] It looks like
we're all here. Let's go.
[AMON] Is something
wrong, Shinohara?
[SHINOHARA]
Hmm? Oh, no.
I was just thinking, when
you and Mado fought the guy,
did you get manage to get
any sort of read on him?
Definitely unique,
as far as ghouls go.
He had a weird vibe about him,
but it's hard to put into words.
That helps. And the
only photo we have
was taken before he even
started going by "Jason."
[YOUNGER YAMORI screaming]
[SHINOHARA] After his initial
[SHINOHARA]
arrest by CCG,
he was sent to the
Cochlea Ghoul Internment Center.
The investigator who
was posted there...
Well, let's just say he
was a little "disturbed".
[YOUNGER YAMORI]
559.
552.
[INVESTIGATOR]
There's still so much left.
[INVESTIGATOR panting]
[YOUNGER YAMORI sobbing]
[INVESTIGATOR cackling]
Let me take it!
[SHINOHARA]
He was tortured in ways
you only hear about in fiction.
It was so brutal, his mind
did the only thing it could
to protect itself.
It created another personality.
After that...
...he busted out.
Ever since then, he's favored
acting like the brute, himself.
And he employs the same torture
he endured on his victims.
He started calling himself
Jason after that, too.
Crazy shit, huh?
[ETO] They got here
sooner than we thought.
[TATARA]
Yeah.
Bin Brothers, you're
in the main building.
[BIN BROTHERS]
Right.
[TATARA]
Kirishima, take the annex.
You got it.
[TATARA] Let's get going, Eto.
You can take it from here, Noro.
Where's Yamori?
[NICO] Beats me. Probably
in his little play room.
Now, of all times?
That's just perfect.
[YAMORI] The weak should
be trampled underfoot.
Crushed!
Violated!
Tormented.
[YAMORI laughing]
Please, no.
[KANEKI]
Don't do it. Don't!
[KANEKI scraeming]
You could hear a
pin drop out there.
[KANEKI gasping]
223...
200...
[CCG TROOPERS groaning]
[MARUDE] How the hell
are they picking us off?!
Enemy forces are employing
kagunes and scopes, sir.
So, the ghouls fancy
themselves soldiers, do they?
C'mon, men! Don't let
these bastards show us up!
[MARUDE]
Gimme that gun!
[GHOULS groaning]
Did ya see that?
That's how you take out
a goddamn sniper's nest,
you sack-less clods!
Hop to it!
[CCG TROOPER]
What a badass.
[MARUDE]
What's going on?
[MABUCHI] Your bike. It was
brought over from headquarters.
[MARUDE]
Hold it, stitches!
What do you think you're
doing with my bike!
Aw, don't worry! 'Kay?
[JUZO yelps]
[MARUDE] Hey!
[JUZO laughing]
What are you doing? No, no
no no no, not that way!
Change direction, you
psychotic little ape!
They'll turn my baby
into Swiss cheese!
Why are you doing this to me!
[JUZO]
Woo-hoo!
Eeny...
Meeny...
Miny...
...moe!
[GHOUL groans]
[GHOULS groaning, yelping]
[MARUDE sobbing]
Give 'em hell!
[CCG TROUPERS shouting]
[footsteps tapping]
[GHOUL] Hold it!
Which team are you with?
[GHOULS groaning]
Team Anteiku.
[CCG TROOPER E] Incoming, 3
o'clock! I count ten targets!
Deploying Emerio.
[GHOULS grunting, groaning]
[CCG TROOPER F] Ten more!
9 o'clock and closing!
Hirako!
[GHOULS grunting, groaning]
[CCG TROOPER G] Southern
entrance block is secured!
[SHINOHARA] I want
eyes on the perimeter!
[SHINOHARA]
This is Shinohara.
We've taken control of the main
building, second floor entrance.
Awaiting orders.
Split up into three units,
move in from below,
then secure the parking
lot and the interior.
Then you should be able
to rendezvous top-side.
[SHINOHARA]
Copy.
By the way, I haven't
seen Suzuya around.
[MARUDE] I can't let that
patchwork psycho die
until he pays for my bike.
Send someone to snag him!
You got me!
Copy that.
[JUZO cackling]
[weapon slicing]
[JUZO]
Hang in there!
You can't die yet, we're
not through playing!
Don't give up!
Aw, he broke.
[SHU]
This is barbaric.
[KANEKI weakly]
Thank you both.
Hey, Kaneki.
Just so you know, Banjo
still hasn't given up on you.
[HARU]
He sent a message,
"I'll get you outta
here, bro. Count on it."
[SHU] We'll come back when
we can. You stay strong.
Trust Banjo.
If anyone can help
you, it's him.
[YAMORI growls]
[GHOULS groaning]
[TOUKA grunting]
[TOUKA] Dammit Kaneki,
where are you?
[GHOULS groaning]
[AMON grunting]
You're kidding.
[AMON]
Hold it!
[AMON] Thought you
could slip past me?
Well, think again, Rabbit!
[TOUKA] Is he that
dove from before?
For Mado!
[CCG TROOPER H]
Empty your clips!
[rapid beeping]
[CCG TROOPER H]
What the hell! There's no way!
[CCG TROOPER screaming]
[CCG TROOPER I]
Holy shit!
[CCG TROUPERS screaming]
[CCG TROOPER L]
Heads up!
[CCG TROOPERS gasping]
[CCG TROOPERS groan]
[CCG TROOPER N]
It's not working!
[CCG TROOPER M] Keep firing!
[CCG TROOPERS groaning]
Not bad, they've actually
made some headway.
[IRIMI] I lost their
footsteps. Wait, got them!
It sounds like they
all made it inside.
[HINAMI] Wow, you can
hear them? That's amazing!
[IRIMI]
With a little practice,
I'm sure you'll be able
to do it someday.
[YOSHIMURA] Focus, Kaya. Give
me an update on the CCG.
[IRIMI]
They've split their forces.
They have the advantage,
at the moment.
[YOSHIMURA]
Then there's little choice.
[YOSHIMURA] We'll have to buy
our team some extra time.
Kaya, look after
Hinami while I'm gone.
[IRIMI]
Yes, sir.
[AMON] You're mine, Rabbit!
I've got you now!
[TOUKA]
He's totally going berserk!
[TOUKA grunts]
[AMON yelling]
[TOUKA] I don't get it,
what'd I ever do to him?
He wants revenge.
[TOUKA, AMON grunting]
[TOUKA] Dammit! I don't have
time to deal with him right now!
[AMON]
You can't run forever!
[YOUNGER BIN] Who was that?
I don't think I know 'em.
[OLDER BIN] Whoa. He shrugged
off a number three combo.
[YOUNGER BIN]
Not bad, for a human.
The Bin Brothers?
They're S-rated ghouls!
[UTA] Well, well.
What do we have here?
[TSUKIYAMA laughing]
[TSUKIYAMA] I follow my
nose and who do I find
but Mister High C himself.
Simplement merveilleux!
Shall we share a table together?
[YOMO] Keep your guard up.
This is no ordinary ghoul.
[TSUKIYAMA] My, what a
charming mouth you have.
I believe a passionate baiser
may be in short order.
Take him out.
[TSUKIYAMA cackling]
[AMON grunting]
[AMON] Can I take down
two S-rated ghouls?
Do I have what it takes?
I know Mr. Mado did.
[MADO] Here's a question for
you. How can a human being
overcome their physical
limitations and prevail against
a ghoul in an
all-or-nothing brawl?
Any thoughts?
[AMON groaning]
[AMON] I suppose building up
muscle mass and stamina
would do the trick.
[MADO giggling]
It certainly wouldn't hurt.
But, no. You can't
depend on brute strength
in a fight
against a ghoul.
You'd never be able
to overpower them.
[AMON grunting, gasping]
[MADO] Now think. When
all the training in the world
can't save you, what can
you do to close the gap?
Got any ideas?
[AMON]
I don't.
[OLDER BIN]
Number one combo!
[YOUNGER BIN]
Got it!
[MADO] You have to be wily.
Guile is your weapon, Amon.
As long as it's for the
right cause, fight dirty.
And don't you dare
feel guilty for it.
[MADO] In my collection, there's
a quinque I like to call "Kura".
I think it would
suit you nicely.
[MADO] I'm not going to
be around forever, Amon.
When I die, I want
you to use it.
[AMON]
Yes, sir!
[AMON yelling]
[YOUNGER BIN screaming]
[OLDER BIN grunts]
[AMON yelling]
[OLDER BIN groaning]
[AMON] I can't let it
end here. Not like this.
I won't give up until
I've avenged you!
[TOUKA]
Kaneki.
[NISHIKI groans]
Be a little more
careful, would ya?
I don't like playing the hero.
[TOUKA]
Nishiki!
[AYATO] Well, If it
isn't my dumbass sister.
What the hell are
you doin' here?
You and me, bro.
[CCG TROOPER P] Squad A
has secured the annex,
third floor, and north exit.
Squad B has secured
main building, second
floor, and west exit.
[MARUDE] Shinohara.
how're we looking?
[SHINOHARA] Parking level
and fifth floor are secure!
En route to rendezvous!
[MARUDE]
Copy that.
Kind of reminds you of the
good old days, now doesn't it?
[SHINOHARA]
Sure does.
[SHINOHARA] They were
good men. Every one of 'em.
[SHINOHARA] This is Shinohara.
We've arrived at the roof.
Doesn't look like
anyone's up here.
I don't like this.
[AMON]
Shinohara!
[SHINOHARA]
You alright?
[AMON] No, far from it. The
ghoul who killed Mr. Mado--
What's happening?
[SHINOHARA]
Maru...
It's him.
[SHINOHARA]
The one-eyed Owl.
Listen closely.
Only those who are willing
to die should stay behind.
'Cause you probably will.
[MARUDE] If you guys can't
hold him off, then no one can.
Don't go throwing lives away.
We both know it's not going
to slow the bastard down.
Challenge him with as
few men as possible.
Good luck.
[MARUDE] Even on the roughest
days, riding clears my head.
When the good-for-nothing peons
and the ball-busting
higher-ups get me low.
[MARUDE] Going full-throttle
down the Big Slab takes me high.
I couldn't ask for
a better partner.
I know I had my keys.
[JUZO]
Yahoo!
[MARUDE yelping]
[JUZO laughing]
[MARUDE sobbing]