[chirping]
[LEON]
Chenho...
Is this a judgment of blood?
[CONTROLLER]
Your entry permit number please.
[VOICE] C338. Cargo delivered
to Ride Transport.
We have requested
an Angel Links escort.
[CONTROLLER]
Instructions received,
you'll embark tomorrow.
Please complete your
inspections at C Gate.
[VOICE]
Thank you.
[KOSEI] So this is the
shipment cargo manifest
and the contract between
Ride Transport and us.
Ah...
[LAWYER] The contract stipulates
the route to be taken,
details of the escort,
and a contingency agreement.
[gasps]
Please read it carefully,
and sign there at the bottom.
Yeah... It's amazing
there are pirates
who will come after
us small fish.
I can't afford to
hire a security firm
for such small merchandise so
we're very thankful for you!
[yawns]
[MEIFON]
Give me a break, you worry wart!
The planet Dela route
is a walk in the park.
I'm tired of babysitting
cargo for these stiffs.
[yawns]
[MEIFON] There's never
an attack! It's so boring.
[MEN scream]
[ALL]
Hm?
[RIDE PRESIDENT gasps]
There's trouble!
[RIDE PREZ, MEIFON]
Huh?
The cargo was stolen
while being brought in...
Just right before it entered
into our security zone!
And the culprits?
[CONTROLLER]
They've escaped!
Looks like the "Outside" Gang.
You mean the beggar pirates?
[KOSEI]
Great. She's thrilled.
Please tell me! What was taken?!
[CONTROLLER] Ride Transports.
Containers 2 and 3.
No! That's ours!
[RIDE PRESIDENT]
I knew it!
Container 3 has the client's
priceless artwork!
And we can't pay it back!
Counselor! Please tell me
the responsibility
was handed over to
the Angel Links!
Tell me they're liable, please!
No! We haven't signed yet.
So? There's my signature!
I'm telling you it's
already a done deal!
Wait just a minute.
It was your responsi--
It certainly was not!
The deal is done!
Angel Links has to compensate
for all the stolen cargo!
It's part of the
contingency agreement!
It didn't reach our safety zone,
so therefore it wasn't
on our property!
You should have arranged
for other security.
Altair is a dangerous place.
You should be responsible for
the shipment in your territory!
Counselor, it's a contingency!
Well, it did actually happen
outside of the gate...
[RIDE PRESIDENT] I beg you.
Consider it a contingency!
No, it isn't.
[RIDE PRESIDENT]
But you drew it up!
Not valid!
--[RIDE PREZ] Deal is done!
--No it isn't!
--Yes it is!
--It is!
--It isn't!
--It's not!
--It's done!
--No! Not done.
--Done!
--No way!
[MEIFON]
It's done!
Meifon!
She signed it!
So we have a case! We have a
binding contract with you!
Hurrah! Ha, ha!
Why did you sign it?
Haven't you heard
what's been going on?
I heard.
Once signed, it's
our responsibility.
So, let's go get
that shipment back.
Huh?!
Get it back?!
Actually, I don't mind if you
reimburse me with cash.
We have our own
way of compensating.
The contract doesn't specify
how we do it,
that's our business.
Huh?!
[MEIFON]
Next time...
...you should read
the fine print.
[RIDE PRESIDENT]
Y-Yes, ma'am...
[KOSEI]
They call this is the "Outside."
A Skid Row for vagrant pirates
who've lost their ships
or were injured in space.
[ANNE, AIHARA laughing]
[KOSEI]
They use the Outside as a base,
and emerge onto
the surface to plunder.
This incident is
definitely their doing.
[KOSEI] This underground world
is controlled by one man...
...Cyrus.
A former pirate--
the one who built
the Outside up
to what it is today.
[KOSEI]
Please take a look at this.
It's a map of the airline route,
and one of the subway system.
As you can see, they both divert
around this empty space here.
The Outside.
Cyrus owns the land surface,
the underground,
and air rights too.
The railway department
of the Links Group really
wanted to purchase the land
and build a subway system,
but it was to no avail.
Ooh. I see now...
I always wondered why the subway
took such a roundabout route.
The diversion makes my
commute twice as long!
Me, too! Commuting
drives me crazy!
Does this Cyrus drag queen
have that much power?
It's rumored he uses Tao.
Tao... Magic.
We don't know the exact
extent of his power,
but nobody who has
crossed into his territory
has ever returned alive.
So, my conclusion is...
Let's just compensate
the client with cash.
'Cause it's not worth the risk.
[MEIFON]
We'll head out in 30 minutes,
so be prepared.
W-W-Wait a minute!
What about Valeria and Duuz?
[MEIFON]
Well. They're not required
under contract to do
any surface duty.
We're on our own!
Meifon.
It's not required in my
contract either, you know.
Ya got enough guns in here?
I don't feel like dying today.
[AIHARA] The commander
sure likes a fight.
I suppose. But maybe
there's more to it.
Huh?
[ANNE] One of the containers
plundered was filled
with personal belongings
like letters and gifts,
children's toys. You know.
That kind of thing.
[AIHARA]
So?
[ANNE]
Probably reminded her.
Apparently, her grandfather sent
her some birthday presents
right before he died, but
she never received them.
The ship was
plundered by pirates.
So, the commander makes a point
of protecting shipments that are
worth more than just money.
Oh, wow! She has
such a great heart!
I think she also just likes
to have a good scrap.
[KOSEI coughs]
Bad pavement kicks up the dust.
Oh, I'll have to wash
my hair when we get back.
[KOSEI]
If you still have a head.
[GANG chuckles]
Huh?
[MEIFON]
Can ya spare a moment?
I'll spare you anything,
babe. Come home to Papa.
That's sort of what
we're after here.
We want you to take
both of us to home base.
To see Cyrus.
But... why?
A shipment of ours was
taken by the Outsiders.
And we're here to get it back.
You came here to get it?
Just you?!
Ha, ha! You waltz in
and expect Cyrus to give back
the shipment that they took?
You either gotta be naive
or a freakin' lunatic!
[MEIFON]
Make... my... day!
[screaming]
[MAN 1]
Ow...!
Captain Cyrus!
There's someone here
who wants to see you!
Captain Cyrus!
Ah!
Captain?!
Captain Kangaroo maybe,
he's got no ship!
--[KOSEI] Shhhhh!
--Huh?
Who dares to disturb me?
Uh, this guy's a slime.
You've got some
company--Circus Boy!
There's no need
to raise your voice.
I know everything
that happens here.
Well since you're
such a know it all...
This will be quick.
Give back my stuff!
Do you think that
I'll hand it over
just because you asked me to?
Neither you nor your shipment
can expect to ever return again.
Oh, good.
I'm really glad that you're not
going to surrender right away.
Because I look forward to the
fun of cleaning this dump up!
This world is my ship!
You defile its sanctity, so I'm
feeding you to the sharks!
Fire upon them now!
[KOSEI]
Meifon, hurry!
[MEIFON, KOSEI grunt, scream]
[MEIFON, KOSEI panting]
[MEN grunting]
Once you set foot on my Outside
ship, you never get back in.
[KOSEI, MEIFON panting]
[GANG yelling]
Taffei!
Time for some fun!
[MEIFON]
Ha, ha!
[MAN 2]
[BOTH yelling]
[MAN 2 screams]
[MAN 4 yells]
[gasps]
[GANG yelling]
[MEIFON yells]
[MAN 5 groans]
[GANG screams]
[MEIFON yells]
[MAN 9 groans]
[MEIFON]
Ha!
[MAN 11 laughs]
[MEIFON grunts]
--[MEIFON grunting]
--[MAN 11 groaning]
[MEIFON pants]
Hey, Kosei...
I'm sorry to make you wait.
You took such a long time
I was just about to go
home without you.
[CYRUS]
Bakwa Sanfa...
[MEIFON] Oh, come on.
We came all this way...
[CYRUS]
Bakwa Sanfa...
[MEIFON]
Why rush home?
Well, if you enjoy this
so much, then do it alone.
[CYRUS]
Bakwa Sanfa...
Bakwa Sanfa... Bakwa Sanfa...
[CYRUS inhales]
Feigaa!
[KOSEI gasps]
What the...?!
Watch out for my foot!
My foot, Meifon! Ah!
[KOSEI gasping]
--[gasps]
--Cyrus!
[CYRUS]
Feigaa!
[MEIFON, KOSEI groan]
He controls...
soil with his Tao!
[CYRUS]
Feigaa!
[MEIFON]
Goodnight, Mr. Sandman!
[CYRUS]
Feigaa!
[KOSEI]
Huh?
Let's split up!
[MEIFON gasps]
[KOSEI]
Huh?
We'd better get
away from this soil.
[CYRUS]
Bakwa Sanfa...
Bakwa Sanfa... Bakwa Sanfa...
[MEIFON, KOSEI panting]
[CYRUS]
Feigaa!
I'm sure we should be safe here.
[MEIFON]
Yeah. He's gone.
[KOSEI, MEIFON yelp]
[MEIFON]
Watch your head!
[MEIFON screams]
[KOSEI groans]
[KOSEI]
Meifon!
[CYRUS]
It's all over.
[MEIFON yelling]
[KOSEI]
Huh?
[MEIFON yelling]
[KOSEI]
Meifon!
[MEIFON yells]
[CYRUS]
Your confidence will wane.
I'm absolutely
impossible to defeat.
Kosei, you know you can get out
of here if you really want to.
No! I won't leave you
all by yourself.
Ya didn't wanna come
in the first place.
[KOSEI]
There's no turning back now.
Besides... when you
hit that wall...
[KOSEI]
...didn't you get hurt?
No. Guess not.
[MEIFON screams]
[BOTH groan]
[CYRUS]
Like I said, it's over now.
[KOSEI groaning]
[VALERIA panting, yells]
Huh? V-Valeria...?!
You're here?!
Why not?
Duuz, too!
Well, the occasional
surface battle
isn't such a terrible thing.
Say what?
[MEIFON]
All right everyone...
Show 'em what we've got!
[CYRUS]
Bakwa Sanfa... Bakwa Sanfa...
[MEIFON yells]
[DUUZ growls]
[KOSEI grunts]
[VALERIA]
It'll never end this way!
We're gonna lose all
our strength soon
and that's going to
be the end of it.
I know it. Huh?
I'll give it back.
Uh...
Duuz, it doesn't have
much energy left.
[CYRUS]
Stop that!
I'm right.
What? What do you mean?
I've encountered a Tao
like this once before.
Its power comes from all of
the seams in the ground.
[MEIFON]
"Seams in the ground"?
[VALERIA] No wonder he
didn't want a subway
running through here,
disturbing his power.
Oh, that's right...
So how do you think we go about
disturbing the seams right now?
[MEIFON]
Huh...
Hey, I've got an idea!
[CYRUS] To think they
knew about the seams...
Well, let them have
their final revelation!
They won't live long enough
to do anything about it.
[VALERIA]
There it is!
Good!
[DUUZ]
Now! Run!
[KOSEI panting]
[VALERIA, MEIFON panting]
Huh? This way everyone!
And hurry!
[CYRUS] You can run as much
as you want, but it's useless.
I see your every move.
No! Don't end this way!
[CYRUS]
It is time to admit defeat.
I've won.
[laughing]
[laughing continues]
[KOSEI]
Uh...
[MEIFON grunts]
Cherubim fire!
That's it!
[CYRUS]
What's that above?!
A spaceship, Captain!
[CYRUS]
A... Spaceship?
[AIHARA] Isn't it a breach
of the TS Military Treaty
that I fired the Links cannon
onto the surface like that?
It's fine. Pinpoint accuracy.
Besides, what's done is done.
You're right!
So, let's give them another one!
[CYRUS whimpering]
[MEIFON]
Get a load of this!
[CYRUS] What are you...
What are you doing?!
[CYRUS whimpers]
[CYRUS]
What's goin' on here...?!
Hey boss, have we been cleared
to start building
the subway yet?
Hm? That's what everyone wants!
[CYRUS]
Subway...?!
That's right. The Links Group
is building a subway.
Right through your ship.
Stop it!
[CYRUS groaning]
Cyrus may be a criminal,
but he does still legally
own the land.
He'll be compensated.
As for the people who live here,
I have a little work
project for them.
Huh?
[MEIFON] If they behave,
they can run the subway line.
[KOSEI]
What?!
[DUUZ]
That is, if it suits them.
My Outside ship...
Oh, my ship...
[cries]
Now, I want my shipment back.
Curses, on you! You are
destroying my ship!
What do you mean your ship?!
You're nothin' but a
grounded old pirate!
No more suckin' all
the power from the Earth
for your stupid Tao!
I bet you were a third-rate
pirate in space,
you Pippy Long Stockings.
You're lucky to be stuck
in this soil, you bad weed.
How dare you insult me!
How dare you! I am a captain!
[CYRUS yells]
[CYRUS groans]
You can spend some time
behind bars on the Inside now.
[KOSEI] Meifon! I just
found the shipment!
[MEIFON]
Hmph.
[KOSEI] They were getting ready
to sell off the container
with the artwork, but this
one was going to be dumped.
Someone is going to get
their birthday present.
Thank goodness.
You all right? Hey,
what's wrong? Meifon!
[ADMIRAL] So... you want
data on Angel Links?
[LEON]
That's right.
I need this favor from you,
your excellency.
Well, since it's you
requesting it... I'll do it.
Special Forces III.
Will that do?
Thank you, Admiral.
I would like to send
those armaments to you
as a token of my gratitude.
[ADMIRAL laughs]
[ADMIRAL]
May we always be good friends.
Yes.
[MEIFON] Next time on
Space Guardian: Angel Links,
"A Pheasant
Chooses its Nest."