[KOSEI] This amazing
battleship was designed
by Lord Hiraga Dynecourt.
It's the only one of
its kind in space.
And it's so deadly,
it makes me shudder.
That's why I love it!
'Casue this ship and I must
be perfect for each other.
With both Duuz
and Valeria on board,
we're going to be invincible.
Ha! It's almost cheating!
Sounds good.
There's only one person who
can handle "the dragon"
and "the dragon lady"...
...both together on one ship.
And that's me!
You're confident.
I have to be.
Who's going to follow an
unconfident leader, Kosei?
[COMPANY MAN 1] The president
was a real dictator.
Things should slacken
up a bit now.
[COMPANY MAN 2] I wish! Maybe
in your faction, not mine.
[PRIEST] I wanted to ask
you a question, Meifon.
Why did you not even shed a
single tear at the funeral?
I know you were close
to your grandfather.
[PRIEST]
I think you're still in shock.
I'm concerned about you.
You're going to need some
good friends you can trust.
No. I don't need any friends.
I need a professional
and a superior staff!
[PRIEST]
Hmm...
Huh?
And so, are you Meifon Li?
I was told that I should offer
my support to you when needed.
I made a promise to your
grandfather before he died.
Pleased to make
your acquaintance.
[LAWYER] I shall now read
the last will and testament
of the late Chenho Li.
Firstly, all ownership of the
Links Group will be passed on
to my granddaughter, Meifon Li.
[DIRECTORS chattering]
Secondly.
[LAWYERS] In addition to
current communication
and transportation
business operations,
she will initiate a space
security enterprise.
The services from this operation
will be offered free of charge.
Thirdly, full control
of said enterprise
shall be granted to Meifon Li.
A free pirate fighting service?
What is this, a charity?
That's the most lame-brained
excuse of an idea
I've ever heard of.
Who wants to be a part
of this company--?
This is Chenho's
last will and testament.
All rights to the company
have been granted to me.
[MEIFON]
I ask you to respect my,
or rather, my
grandfather's wishes.
As to these modifications...
[MEIFON] The Angel Links will
be completed in three months.
You will be trained to
be a superior crew.
Next up.
[RECRUIT]
Yes, sir!
Firing range scores at 90%.
Well, it looks like we
got ourselves a crew.
[CREW shouting]
Grappler ships have
just penetrated
the very last defense line!
Why, those pirates are from a
frontier 20 light years away!
[GUNNER]
They're Ashid B types!
How dare they mess with us!
I don't really care
who they are!
They're just grappler ships.
Now tell me what's
takin' you so long.
Relax! Shut up! I'm doin'
the best that I can!
You idiots! Do something fast!
[RADAR MAN]
Commander!
We're going to make contact
with the Grappler
ships in 30 seconds!
[growls]
Here's the Oracle Cannon!
Wh-What's happening?!
I've lost control!
[CREW yelling]
[GUNNER]
We did it!
[PILOT]
Wow!
[RADARMAN]
Commander, there's a problem!
My screen is showing
several merchant vessels
that caught in
behind the pirates!
Seventeen vessels in total!
[ANALYST]
The Oracle Cannon is a weapon
that disturbs the flow of ether,
robbing a ship of its
power and control.
It creates a violent
wave in space
and all ships in
range are affected,
both civilian and enemy.
Sufficient care
must be exercised
when using this weapon
because the Oracle Cannon not
only affects normal flight
but it makes control under
ether drive impossible.
Yeah. Go ahead and
shut 'em down, boys!
Good riddance to the
free pirate fighters!
With this recent accident,
the TS Military Treaty will most
certainly be put on review.
There're some hungry pirates
who're just drooling
to get their hands on this.
I just wanna thank you
so much, Mr. Goryu.
[ANNOUNCER]
The Links Group new...
Oh, I forgot, you
don't go by that name.
[REPORTER 1] President Li,
as commander of Angel Links ,
it's said that you personally
ordered the use
of the Oracle Cannon that
damaged 17 merchant ships.
Is that true?
[REPORTER 2] There are rumors
that the Angel Links group
may lose its certification.
Any comments, President?
[KOSEI] The recent incident has
been handled very discreetly.
Although, it did cost us.
Thank you, Kosei.
And in order to handle
this wild horse,
we're gonna need some
professionals on board.
I agree. So fire the
entire present crew.
[KOSEI]
Huh?
[DIRECTOR 1] Chenho Li sure
left a mess behind him.
And bequeathing the company
to a 16-year-old girl...
Can that be legal?
Well, you know, she's had
a really rough time of it.
You don't actually feel sorry
for that arrogant little twerp?
Huh?
[crying]
Goryu, please. Stop it!
You know we're allies!
You spineless fools.
[CHEN]
Traitor!
No, you're the traitor, Chen!
You call yourself a pirate,
but you just want the
cushie life of a civilian
in your old age.
[gasps]
[MEIFON]
A dream?
[CHEN]
Now, you must go, Meifon.
[MEIFON]
Okay!
[CHEN] Some people believe
they can be re-incarnated.
and when they come back,
it's not always in human form.
For instance, your parents may
re-appear someday as an animal.
[laughs] Then I wanna
turn into a little kitty-cat!
[CHEN] So what kind of
cat do you wanna be?
A hungry cat that
lives free in the wild,
or a tame cat that's well-fed?
Well, let's see...
A free cat that can eat a lot!
A spoiled child. A free cat.
[MEIFON]
I won't let anyone get hurt.
Hear me, Grandfather?
I vow to carry out your will.
[KOSEI] Commander, I've found
some interesting candidates
for your consideration.
Look, I did not ask
you to help me.
I know, your grandfather
asked me to help you
but now you need to decide
whether you can trust me or not.
We begin operations shortly.
I've arranged for
you to meet them.
[KOSEI]
One of them is Valeria Vertone.
A former strategist with the
Einhorn Imperial Forces.
[VALERIA] I never waste my
time working with amateurs.
[MEIFON]
Hm.
[VALERIA]
I understand your situation.
I'm just not interested
in the position.
Please let me by.
Forget it.
Listen, I appreciate your offer,
but you aren't
even in my league.
I know I am young, but
I know my own strength.
[VALERIA]
You're naïve.
[MEIFON]
Three months.
[VALERIA]
Move.
[MEIFON]
Just give me three months!
[VALERIA]
Why?
[MEIFON]
Because with or without you,
this project will happen.
I have total faith in it.
This work will be done, so
please have faith and follow me.
If three months pass and you
still don't believe in me,
then leave.
[gasps]
Okay. Luck is half the battle.
So I would like to
see if you're lucky.
[click]
[chuckles]
[KOSEI] Of all the Dragonites
in the known world,
Duuz Delax Rex is considered
the finest commander of
hand-to-hand combat.
He'd be an excellent
addition to our personnel,
or should I say, Dragonnel?
So you want to
employ me, do you?
[yells]
If you want me to
submit to you,
come at me with your
sword, young girl.
[DUUZ]
I'm surprised.
You're quite skilled
for a mammalian girl.
But you're useless
without a sword.
[MEIFON]
I wouldn't move.
Girl, I'm really impressed
with your courage.
But you definitely
need more than courage
to win in barehanded combat.
Barehanded? My battle sword
is directly above your head.
What?
Girl, I submit.
Not bad.
It's all right.
[MEIFON] While you are
on this assignment,
you must set your
personal feelings aside
or they will interfere
with your judgment.
In space, the smallest loss
of judgment can be fatal.
You may feel resentful taking
orders from a young girl
and I don't care
if you dislike me.
But while we're on board,
I ask that you set
your feelings aside.
And let us all work
as a unified team,
together as professionals.
You're late.
I'll sign for three months.
As soon as my nails are dry.
All crew have now reported.
Good! Then let's
prepare to launch!
[ANNE]
Grappler ships sighted ahead!
All stations report status!
They-They just won't respond to
our identification calls at all!
[gasps] The enemy Grappler ships
are approaching really quickly!
Commander! What should
our course be?
We could shoot them
any time now!
[gasps]
Oh, brother. A little
performance anxiety?
[BOWIE]
Uh.
Oh, relax, boys,
and think of baseball.
These lousy pirates will
simply be target practice.
And if it comes to
hand-to-hand combat,
I'll gladly take them on.
Anne, keep me informed
of our status!
[ANNE] Grappler ships
approaching at eight o'clock!
In 20 seconds, we'll
be in range of firing.
Serge, what's the output
of the Links Cannon?
Output is at 30%!
Maintain it there.
The surrounding area?
I detect that there
are no merchant vessels
within firing range of
the Links Cannon.
[SERGE]
All firing data is in.
[MEIFON]
Links Cannon! Prepare to fire!
We're all ready.
Cherubim! Fire!
[sighs]
[DUUZ] The first battle
is always like this.
President, congratulations
on your magnificent success!
[KOSEI]
There's a hornet on your face.
Look out!
Got it.
Oh, Commander! Hey, Commander!
[MEIFON]
Huh?
[ANNE]
Are you free tonight?
[MEIFON]
Why?
[AIHARA] Anne found a great
little Chinese place!
Really? I'm starved, let's go!
Okay, sounds good!
Hey, do they have ginger beef?
I could go for tofu dim sum now.
[MEIFON]
Right, you're a vegetarian!
[KOSEI] Yeah, and he
eats like a whale!
[DUUZ]
She eats more than me.
[VALERIA]
If Meifon eats more than Duuz,
Kosei picks up the tab.
Wh-Wh-Why me?
[MEIFON] Hear that, Taffei?
Kosei's treating tonight!
[TAFFEI chirping]
[KOSEI] A volunteer
pirate fighting service?
Why would you send
your granddaughter
into a dangerous
business like that?
She's so young
and... beautiful...
Oh, hey there, Meifon.
[KOSEI yelps]
[MEIFON] I know,
my name's on the grave.
A joke, I guess.
Y-Yeah, I suppose so...
When the time comes,
maybe I'll be reborn as a cat.
Huh?
Meow!
[MEIFON]
Grandpa.
I am a free cat that
can eat a lot.
[MEIFON] Next time on
Space Guardian: Angel Links ,
"The Angel and
the Fallen Angel."