[MEIFON]
Huh?
"Dear Meifon Li.
I'll present you with
a song of mermaids."
Song of mermaids?
[gasps]
[SERGE] Accept your defeat,
you little cockroach!
Now!
I think one Prelude-class ship
should be sufficient
against them.
Uh-huh.
We still have to get
the client back home.
At this rate, we'll barely
make it for dinner.
Aww. And we had to book ahead an
entire month for reservations.
The legendary crab leg
special of Casa de Galicia!
And bottles of very
fine red wine
pressed from their
own vineyards!
C'mon! C'mon! Die! C'mon! C'mon!
[growls]
Aww.
We are never get to that seafood
restaurant if we don't hurry!
[KOSEI]
Hmm...
[ANNE, AIHARA]
C'mon, Kosei!
No frivolous use of our weapons!
[AIHARA]
What do you mean frivolous?!
The whole crew was
looking forward
to this dinner for
a long, long time!
[KOSEI]
Do you know how much it costs
to fire the Links
Cannon even just once?
We will not waste it
on small-fry pirates!
No exceptions!
[AIHARA]
Kosei.
[ANNE]
But come on!
[KOSEI] Professionals
do not let their appetite
do their thinking!
Kosei!
[KOSEI]
Yes?
Links Cannon! Prepare to fire!
[KOSEI]
What?!
[CREW]
Aye-aye!
[AIHARA] Way to go, Commander!
Cut right to the chase!
Uh... But hold on.
[ANNE] It looks like
we'll make it after all.
[AIHARA]
What are you going to have
for the main course, Commander?
The prawns or the crab?
I hear the lobster
is excellent, too.
Commander?
[MEIFON]
Huh?
So what will you order?
The prawns or the crab?
[MEIFON] Actually, I have
a business engagement.
What?!
Do you know how hard it was
to make a reservation
for that place?
[AIHARA]
What's that, Commander?
[MEIFON]
Huh?
[AIHARA]
You're hiding something there!
[ANNE] Oh, how intriguing!
An invitation!
[AIHARA] It's looking more and
more suspicious than ever.
[MEIFON]
That's ticklish!
[AIHARA, ANNE laughing]
It says, "My dear Meifon Li.
I'll present you a
song of mermaids."
What's this?
Oh, my!
[AIHARA] It's a love note!
A romantic invitation!
Let go! Give it!
You mean, you used
the Links Cannon
so you could make it in
time for a rendezvous?
Valeria!
So are you saying we always make
frivolous use of our weapons?
Yes. That's right!
Duuz!
[CREW cheering]
[sighs]
Ta-da! Grandpa, how do I look?
Dress makes the
woman, you think?
[MEIFON]
All set!
Let's go, Taffei!
[MEIFON]
Huh?
Hey. I'll give you a lift.
[KOSEI] Hm. Never seen
this side of you before.
What side? So what do you mean?
The softer side.
Well, like any other girl,
I'm happy to be
invited on a date.
Especially a date with Leon Lau,
the big corporate tycoon.
At least, I think so.
What do you mean?
[horn honking]
Oh, look, the light's
turned green.
Right.
But isn't that letter from Leon?
There was no return address.
Huh? I wonder why...
Well, I don't know.
But it must've been him,
'cause it was sent by
someone close to my heart.
Let's just call it...
a woman's intuition.
Well, even an ordinary guy
like me can figure out
that a pretentious
letter must be from him.
Now, now, are you jealous?
Not at all. Unlike Lau, I'm
not obsessed with women.
Hey, it's red.
[MEIFON] Right here's
fine. Thanks, Kosei.
[KOSEI]
Meifon.
[MEIFON]
Hm?
I just want you to be careful.
I think that Leon
might be dangerous.
Let's just call it
a man's intuition.
A man's intuition
is hardly objective.
Huh?
[MEIFON]
But thanks anyway!
Lau, I'd really like to know
how you rose to prominence
in only a couple of years.
[KOSEI] That insignia...
I'm sure I've seen it somewhere.
[horn blares]
[LEON]
Meifon.
[gasps]
[MEIFON]
I'm sorry I'm late.
Oh, thank you. That is so nice.
Meifon, I've only ever seen
you wearing your uniform.
You know, those flowers go so
beautifully with your dress.
I, uh, I wanted to
thank you so much...
[YAYOI]
Meifon!
...for inviting me out today.
Oh. Yayoi.
[LEON]
She insisted on coming along.
My Uncle Leon tried to
keep your date a secret.
But that just isn't fair, is it?
I want to play with you too!
[LEON]
Sorry about this.
[YAYOI]
Don't you wanna play with me?
[MEIFON] Of course I do!
It's great to see you!
[YAYOI]
Really?
Yes. Let's have
lots of fun today.
So what should we do first?
Well, uh... Let's see.
[stomach growls]
[gasps]
Your tummy says
it's time for lunch!
Let's go eat some
lunch, lunch, lunch!
[chuckles]
[LEON]
Yayoi, remember your manners.
Uncle, no.
So do you want something else?
[YAYOI]
Nope. I'm full.
[LEON]
Don't be picky.
[YAYOI]
I'm full, really.
Okay, Yayoi.
What do you wanna
do after lunch?
Let me see...
I know! Let's go on a boat!
[MEIFON]
A boat ride, huh?
But you're gonna get sea-sick,
unless you take the cure.
[YAYOI]
What's that?
Carrots!
They will help you build up
your sea-legs, you know.
[YAYOI]
Really?
[MEIFON]
Mm-hmm.
[chuckles]
[MEIFON] Yayoi, now you'll
be strong as a sailor!
[YAYOI]
Really? Yay!
[chuckles]
Well, you're on a roll,
Daddy Warbucks.
[YAYOI screams]
[MEIFON]
Don't worry, Yayoi.
That's a twin tail dragon
and he looks scarier
than he actually is.
You mean there are dragons
even scarier than that?
[MEIFON]
Oh, yeah.
You should see Duuz
with his sword.
He's even scarier at dinner!
[DUUZ sneezes]
[NIKOLA]
Hey!
Bon appetit.
[YAYOI chuckles]
[MEIFON]
Uh, oh.
[MEIFON] Where do you
wanna go next, Yayoi?
But why don't we go where
you want to go now?
She's right. So tell me,
what would you like to do now?
Well, let's see.
[gasps]
I wanna hear a
song of mermaids.
A song of mermaids.
[KOSEI]
It's not a corporate insignia.
But I'm sure I've
seen it somewhere.
[YAYOI]
Oh! They're so cute!
[BOTH laughing]
[LEON] Those are the cries
of the Oracian Jugon.
Some call them
the "Grey Mermaids."
They mate with their
partner for life
and this is the song they sing
to find their true love.
So that's...
a song of mermaids.
[gasps]
I haven't had a nice relaxing
day like this in a while.
[LEON] I've never seen
Yayoi so happy before.
She's very fond of you.
I know you saved her life,
but it's more than that.
You two have a special bond.
She really loves you.
A song of mermaids.
I really appreciate your
wonderful invitation, Leon.
[LEON]
Invitation?
[MEIFON]
Yes.
I knew it was you right away,
even without the signature.
I knew it was someone
close to my heart.
Leon?
[gasps]
Leon. What?
[LEON]
What's this about?
Huh?
[LEON]
Who in the world...?
Hey. What's the matter?
[LEON]
It wasn't me.
I was not the one who
sent you that invitation.
What?
You see, I thought it was you
who asked me to come here today.
[gasps]
What about... the, uh,
invitation that I got?
[gasps]
Just look at mine.
It's exactly the same.
[gasps]
Who would do such a thing?
I think someone is trying to
bring us together, Meifon.
Where are you going?
That's insane. How could it be?
Marin? But why would such
an ancient pirate be...?
[LEON]
Meifon. Meifon!
[MEIFON]
I know this place.
[laughing]
[MEIFON]
Grandpa! Hurry up!
[CHENHO]
Meifon! Don't go there!
Meifon! Come back! Meifon!
Meifon!
[MEIFON]
This way, Grandpa! This way!
Huh?
What's your name, mister?
[CHENHO]
Don't do it! Goryu!
A pirate shouldn't
pretend to live the life
of a respectable citizen.
[MEIFON] That day...
I was standing right here.
Go... ryu...
[MEIFON]
[LEON gasps]
[growling]
M-Meifon?
Go... ryu...
[gasps]
Goryu!
I'm going to take a
piece of that angel.
[MEIFON]
Goryu!
You... will...
...die!
[MEIFON yelling]
[MEIFON]
Destroy... Goryu. Destroy!
[roars]
[yells]
[YAYOI]
Meifon...
Meifon. I'm awake now.
It's you.
[gasps]
[YAYOI]
I'm glad.
Meifon!
[KOSEI]
Oh, no!
Are you all right?!
You! What did you do to Meifon?!
Just stop. Don't you see?
There's a little girl.
[KOSEI]
Why--!
Leon Lau.
I don't know who you really are,
but I promise,
I will protect her.
Go... Goryu...
[KOSEI]
Meifon.
[MEIFON]
Huh? Where am I?
I must have just
dozed off, I guess.
How embarrassing.
And in front of Yayoi.
You're just exhausted.
I think you've been pushing
yourself too hard lately.
I guess.
But today... I had
a good time today.
I really did.
[LEON] Meifon.
Granddaughter of Chenho Li.
Oh, Meifon...
[LEON]
It must have been you.
It must have been you, Chenho,
who brought us together.
[LEON chuckles]
[LEON]
I accept your challenge.
[MEIFON] Until next time on
Space Guardian: Angel Links ,
"My Ship."