Morning!
[crying]
[screams]
Strange memory.
[gasps]
[sighs]
Roses!
[KOSEI]
Yes.
Leon Lau sent those.
Leon Lau. Oh.
[MEIFON]
Morning!
[ANNE] We've received
10,072 security requests
in the past 24 hours.
File 1231 please.
Hey, doll, I'd love to leave
my assets in your hands.
[laughs]
Eww. What a creep!
Next.
We request that you
provide security
for our illustrious mayor.
[MEIFON]
Presumptuous squid. Pass.
We really need your help.
Hey, I think I
recognize that guy.
He's the actor from that show,
The Young and the Relentless .
And he has an export
business on the side.
[MEIFON growls]
That Slime Ball!
Acting like he's poor so that
he can get free security!
That's enough!
Two lefts and then turn right?
Huh?
[GORDON growling]
Our sales are down again!
Curse Angel Links! They're
stealing all our business!
[door opens]
Hey.
What is it?
This is the president's office.
Bookings are the first floor.
[MARCOTTE]
Oh, uh, sorry.
Our service isn't cheap.
Well, yeah. I figured as much.
And that's why I'm
looking for Angel Links.
Can you tell me where to go?
[GORDON]
Hm?
Yeah. I would love to, buddy.
Huh? Oh. I see it.
Ciao .
[GORDON]
Hey. Wait!
[sighs]
President, it's time to go.
Oh, right.
This job is going
to be a hassle.
We'll be hauling a dangerous
load, but we need the business.
[MAN 3]
Meifon, baby!
I want your security
for the rest of my life.
Please marry me!
[growls]
Don't we have any real calls?!
[KOSEI] There's bound
to be some crackpots.
[MEIFON]
Hmph!
Meifon, where are you--?
Out to lunch!
[RECEPTIONIST] Security?
I'm sorry, we're booked solid.
[sighs]
[BOTH sigh]
[MEIFON]
Hm?
[MARCOTTE]
Huh?
Hey. Check it out.
I just got this picture
of my daughter Emma.
Wow! She's so cute!
Yeah, she's great.
One more job and I can
finally go home to see her.
Bet you can hardly wait.
She's beautiful.
Looks just like my wife.
She's got big ears, like you.
Hey, whaddaya mean "big"?
[BOTH laugh]
When I realized we were
going to have a baby,
I took a space transport job to
better provide for my family.
But it's dangerous
work for little money.
And I fly from planet
to lonely planet
with my family worlds away.
She's growing up so fast.
I wonder if she'll remember me.
Just one more job left and I can
have them in my arms again.
[MARCOTTE]
What? You're Meifon Li?
You know, I'm pretty lucky
to have Angel Links escort me
on my very last transport.
And for free! Thanks!
[MEIFON] Wow. You're bringing
more gifts than cargo!
[MARCOTTE]
Ha-ha. Could be!
And speaking of cargo,
what are the contents?
Um... I don't know if they
told me. Wheat or beans.
How on earth could ya not know?
I'm only contracted to ship it.
They never, ever give
me the details.
Secondo, this is going
to be a sweet, little job.
Think. All those guns
and military cannons.
We can use them for our ships,
or we can sell them
on the black market.
[SECCO] Primo, I'm not
doing it. Forget it!
Perche no ?
You numb your head
with too much gelati.
Che cosa ?
Vero! We hacked into
Gordon's system.
They changed the ship.
Secondo, you think
you're hot stuff!
You lie to me, to my face!
My sources are better
than yours, stupido !
You should be thankful.
Thankful? I taught you
everything that you know!
You're just like Papa.
You can't even eat
without making a mess!
How dare you speak of
Papa with disrespect.
You're just like that
fat pig of a woman.
[growls]
That's my mama!
I'm going to get
you for saying that!
[DOLCE]
Try it, you little bastard!
[VALERIA]
Huh?
Empty?
[VALERIA]
Commander,
for a passage to
Metanoia on Oracion V,
we have three escort ships
available right now.
All others are in maintenance.
Well, that leaves
us a bit short.
[GORDON]
Well, well...
Gordon Hoi.
[GORDON] I'm honored
you remembered my name.
So where are you off to then?
It's rare to see the celebrities
actually working, huh?
[growls]
A confidential route?
Good. You just never know
when pirates may appear.
[LEON] Or greedy contractors
who leak information to pirates
and have their own ship attacked
so that they can collect
the insurance money.
Leon Lau.
Oh. Present company
excluded, of course.
Who would think
to do such a thing?
Well, I was just
downtown on business.
It is a real pleasure to bump
into you like this, Meifon.
[MEIFON]
Huh?
[KOSEI] In remembrance
of our beloved...
...Meifon Li, died at age 17?
[MEIFON chuckling]
[MEIFON]
Hey!
You're such a little rascal!
[KOSEI] What sick joker would
write that on a grave?
[BOWIE]
Gravity cycle unit! Activated!
[DOC]
Interior bridge inertia control.
[NIKOLA] General controls,
commence control transfer.
Dock draining, complete.
[NIKOLA]
Advance flying unit,
launch preparation complete.
Three, two, one.
Take-off!
[NIKOLA] Advance flying
unit, launch confirmed.
All right then!
Angel Links ! Launch!
Advance flying unit
surpassing Mach 1.
Spreading the sound barrier.
[ANNE]
Unmanned escort ships, Prelude ,
String , Rhapsody ,
linking up with Angel .
[AIHARA]
Receiving ship identity codes.
It's a Marcotte cargo vessel,
positioning to link up with us.
We will approach in
spherical formation.
[MARCOTTE] I'm going to
see you, Emma. Soon!
So how are you doin'?
[MARCOTTE yelps]
[MEIFON]
We'll have ya home in no time.
I'm in your hands.
You're safe and sound.
[MARCOTTE]
Meifon.
Yeah?
You get so many calls,
so why'd you pick me?
[MEIFON]
Well, maybe it was the way
you looked at the picture
of your daughter.
Uh?
You must really
love your family.
I'm a lucky man.
Hey, you think she's
cute in the picture,
you should see her in real life!
I guess in a few
hours, you will!
You stupido Secondo.
[SECCO]
Stupido Primo.
He's got the wrong space ship.
The real treasure
is with Gordon!
[WOONO] The Gordon squadron:
Accelerating steadily.
Estimated time of
arrival: 47 minutes.
Good.
It looks like we'll
arrive without a glitch.
But it sure is quiet out there.
That's a rare luxury for us.
So don't count your
chickens just yet.
Valeria, you're
such a pessimist.
[alarm blaring]
Attack vessel! We're under fire!
[MEIFON]
All hands, prepare for battle!
Guard the cargo vessel!
Let's give 'em a warm welcome!
[ANNE]
Enemy! One Striker ship!
Ether drift, plus 0.01 degrees!
Commence attack!
[ANNE] We're 10,000
kilometers off course!
Do the idiots dare to strike
us head on with one ship?
[ANNE] Enemy Striker
ship is retreating!
[MEIFON]
Hm!
No doubt, the fools.
Wait.
That was a decoy!
Here come the others!
Others? Where?!
Attack!
[SECCO]
Vittoria!
What are you so
jumpy about, Susie?
[yelling]
What's going on?!
[ANNE] Six Grappler ships
approaching fast!
[MEIFON]
Very clever...
They lured us here because
it's tough to maneuver.
[MEIFON] We'll blast them
with the Oracle Cannon!
We can't use it here.
Oracion V is too close.
[MEIFON growls]
[DOLCE]
They got the Angel Link escort,
proof that this is definitely
the ship with the guns.
I was right!
And we have the advantage.
The Angel 's too big to do
battle in an asteroid field.
Sorpressa !
Hurry up! Return fire!
We can't! All
gun-ports are damaged!
[laughing]
Prelude has been damaged!
Blast! That's the only
weakness of the Angel .
Close range battle!
[VALERIA]
We've lost formation!
Move the Angel forward now!
We can't let them
get close to us!
[grumbles]
Grieco bastards.
Ah! The ship can't hold
out that much longer!
[VALERIA]
Think, Valeria.
Serge, Nikola!
Put the ship into retreat
and fire Missile 6!
[SERGE, NIKOLA]
Aye-aye!
Meifon! Prepare the
Angel Links Cannon!
Right away!
[laughs]
Ah! Your Angel ship is sinking
and all the treasure is mine!
[MARCOTTE]
Oh, no. Ah!
[MARCOTTE] We've got to
make it, we've got to!
I'm sorry Emma. I tried.
[MEIFON]
I'll protect you, Marcotte,
for the sake of your daughter!
[VALERIA] Marcotte, come
in, this is Angel Links .
Jettison your containers!
Hurry! It's your only hope!
Ah. I know.
Containers are released.
[VALERIA]
Good.
The containers! Vieni qui !
Now!
[SERGE]
Locked-on!
[DOLCE laughing]
[MEIFON] We got 'em now!
Cherubim, fire!
[laughing]
[DOLCE]
Huh?!
[screams]
Fretta!
Huh? What's that?
[screams]
The guardian's ring. I see.
[MEIFON] I'm so sorry
you lost your cargo.
Oh. Well, at least we're
alive. That's what counts.
Yes, but you...
[MAN IN SUIT] Good work,
Marcotte. Job well done.
[MARCOTTE]
What do you mean, sir?
I blew up your cargo.
[MAN IN SUIT]
You never had cargo.
[MARCOTTE]
Hm?
What are you saying?
[VALERIA]
The weight readings didn't match
between the ship
and the containers...
...because they were empty.
[MEIFON]
Huh?
Valeria, how is
the Einhorn Empire?
I don't believe my past
is any of your business.
[MEIFON]
Why were the containers empty?
Marcotte's was a decoy ship,
meant to fool the pirates.
Bet you didn't know
that, did you?
Yes. They keep them in the dark
to avoid any information leaks.
Then where's the real cargo?
[GORDON] Ohh... Susie...
Where's my Susie?
[MAN IN SUIT] Gordon Hoi decided
to transport it himself.
The transaction is complete,
so please sign here.
I can't believe you!
You could've had this man
killed out there playin' decoy!
Marcotte has a wife
and child, you know!
Huh?
It's okay. I'm used to this,
and at least I get paid for it.
And thanks to you, I made
it home safe this time.
How can you be so foolish
as to take on this kinda work?
And what about your baby Emma?
[MARCOTTE]
Meifon!
You really...
You really have no
idea how hard it is
for a person like me
to raise a family.
This is the only kind
of work I'm offered.
And if it means risking my life
for the sake of
my daughter, I'll do it.
[MARCOTTE]
Huh?
[EMMA laughing]
[MEIFON]
Stay tuned for next time
on Space Guardian: Angel Links ,
"The Proud Dragon."