[chirping]
Meifon
[MEIFON] I am an android
built by my grandfather
for the purposes of revenge.
[MEIFON gasps]
[gasps] M-Meifon!
[yells]
[panting]
Goryu!
[KOSEI]
Stop it!
[MEIFON yells]
Goryu!
[KOSEI groaning]
[gasps] I did this?
I... I can't...
I... I can't stand it.
I hate it!
[MEIFON]
Angel Links will be dissolved.
You have all followed
me... faithfully.
I thank you.
[AIHARA]
Commander...
[MEIFON]
This is a lie!
And this too!
And this! And this!
And this... They're all lies!
[MEIFON cries]
[LEON] Meifon, you do
love me, don't you?
[MEIFON panting]
[MEIFON]
No!
Oh, it already looks like all
of our clients have been
transferred to another
security firm.
I guess that it's over.
[BOTH sigh]
I feel wretched.
[DOC] If I could switch places
with Meifon, I gladly would.
Huh? D-Duuz...
[DUUZ] I got some information
out of Gordon Hoi, in exchange
for dropping our complaint
and protecting him.
And so?
[DUUZ]
A long time ago,
before he became a corporate
tycoon, Chenho Li was a pirate.
Among his subordinates
in the group,
Chenho favored Goryu the most.
[PIRATES groan]
[DUUZ] And Goryu treated
Chenho like family.
[PIRATES groan]
[DUUZ] Chenho and Goryu were
like father and son,
but the close bond between
them broke apart when they
encountered an alien spaceship
full of rare metals.
Chenho decided
to use the treasure
as seed money to
build a new life,
give up pirating and become
a corporate tycoon.
However, the young hot-blooded
Goryu could not accept this,
so he betrayed Chenho.
So, you call yourself
a pirate, Chen?
You're the traitor,
getting soft in your old age!
[GORYU groans]
However, Goryu survived,
and then he claimed revenge
against Chenho Li.
[DUUZ] He proceeded to kill
Chenho's family one by one.
And then...
[MEIFON cries]
No!
[gunshot]
[GORYU]
Chenho, if you can give me up,
you can give up the
rest of your family.
[DUUZ]
After carrying out his revenge,
Goryu underwent bio-surgery
and re-invented himself.
He emerged into society as
the young tycoon, Leon Lau.
On the surface, he's known
as a philanthropist
and the "Top Gun of Travel."
But behind the scenes,
he's an arms merchant.
Now, Goryu seems interested
in Meifon as a weapon.
[KOSEI]
An invincible bio-android...
He wants to mass-produce
and trade killer robots.
[KOSEI]
So, you built a bio-android
that resembled your dead
granddaughter, Meifon Li,
and you had her start the free
pirate fighting business
all to flush out Goryu
who was in hiding.
Chenho...
Now I understand what the date
on the grave stone means.
You gave your killing
machine a time limit
just in case she falls
into the wrong hands,
regardless of whether she
accomplishes her revenge or not.
If that date passes,
then Goryu wins without a fight.
However, as an arms merchant,
he has a vested interest in her.
So he'll pursue her until
the last possible moment.
[KOSEI gasps]
She has only one more month.
She won't even live to
see past her 17th birthday.
[MEIFON]
Maybe I should just jump.
Won't work, I'm not human.
[MEIFON] All of this sorrow
and not one tear.
When I grow up, I want to be the
president of grandpa's company.
Then I'm gonna fall
in love and get married!
I'm gonna be a wild cat that's
free and can eat a lot!
Ha! I'm starting to
look like Mother.
[VALERIA]
I still can't believe it.
To think she's bio-android.
I say that she's human no
matter which way you look at it.
It must be the hardest of
all for her to believe.
[MEIFON]
My name is...
...Meifon Li...
Born June 30th
in the year 142.
Only 16,
and the President of
the Links Group...
I'm the commander
of Angel Links .
Only 16...
[gasps]
Meifon! Meifon! Don't do it!
Don't you touch me!
Huh?
[MEIFON]
I don't know who I am.
I don't know what's
living inside of me.
Or when it'll go on a rampage.
I might end up killing
you for interfering.
[gasping]
Then why don't you kill me?
Uh!
If you can't do it,
then you must listen to me!
[gasping]
I wonder what a real human girl
would do at a time like this?
Fighting pirates... revenge...
I don't want to be
programmed that way.
I just want...
to live my own life.
Then, let's go.
[MEIFON]
Huh?
[gasps]
You can fight the program,
and live your own life.
[LEON laughs]
Meifon.
I am the only one--the only
one who accepts you.
[LEON] Seku, Letaly,
is the plan in place?
Yes.
It is now in place, sir.
I've just sent you an
invitation, dear Meifon.
It will likely arrive
in two or three days.
You'll come running to my side.
We're going to go
and see Meifon now!
Hooray! Hooray!
Look! We're gonna
ride in that!
From today on,
this is your new home!
This is my new home...
[KOSEI] You did say you wanted
to live your own way.
You can start a new life
for yourself here.
And forget all about
pirate fighting, okay?
Hey, you were the one
who said you just wanted
to live a normal life.
First of all, let's start by
getting you out of uniform.
We'll buy you some new clothes.
[LADY]
Oh, that really suits you!
You simply must get it,
you remind me of me
when I was young.
I was a lot slimmer back then!
Ah.
Come back anytime, my dear!
It'll need a spot
of oil sometimes.
[MEIFON]
All right. Thank you!
[gasps]
Didn't know you could cook.
[MEIFON] The girl at the store
gave me the recipe.
I'm glad you thought to bring
all the utensils from the ship.
Jee. It's funny how one can
forget all about the essentials,
at a time like this.
[MEIFON]
I know.
Bit of truth to that.
I am always coming across
things that I'm still missing.
[ANNOUNCER] We interrupt this
program now to bring you
an important news flash.
Pirates attacked today
an Oracion V.
It was in the vicinity of...
I thought that I would buy
a tablecloth tomorrow.
To match the color
of the curtains.
[KOSEI]
And don't forget the sugar!
[MEIFON] Right! So you
can drink your tea! Ha, ha!
I really hope I'm doing
the right thing.
[screeches]
[gasping]
[screaming]
[MEIFON]
Goryu...
[MEIFON gasping]
[MEIFON laughs]
[laughing continues]
[MEIFON]
No!
Miss Aihara!
Oh. Hi, Anne!
[exhales]
[SERGE] Huh? What are
you guys doin' here?
[ANNE]
Huh?
We're all thinking the
same thing, aren't we?
Nikola! Serge! Hi, guys!
I knew you'd all show up.
Ha, ha! Well, hello
there everyone!
Hello Yayoi!
But where's Meifon?
[KOSEI]
Kosei Hida...
What's a simple man like
you to do now, huh?
Wha...?!
Meifon?
[MEIFON] I can't accept this
reality so easily, Kosei.
I just can't.
But I have learned
something here.
Nothing will ever be
resolved if I avoid it.
I wanna live the way I choose.
If I have to fight
for it, and I will...
For my own sake,
I will defeat Goryu!
[sighs]
Let's go.
Are you sure that's
really what you want?
Is this what you want, Meifon?
I've decided... I will fight.
[KOSEI]
I understand.
I promise I won't stop you
if that's the way you
choose... to live.
[MEIFON]
Kosei...
Yes, Meifon?
[MEIFON]
Thank you.
Sure.
[MEIFON gasps]
What's up? [gasps]
[AIHARA] Commander, please
reconsider your decision.
We understand...
We do understand that you
are deeply suffering.
And we have no illusion that
we can resolve it for you.
We're just not able to.
But... But we've worked
together all this time,
and we've supported
you all along.
Commander, we're professionals!
Whatever the situation,
we've always followed you.
So please, please
come back to us.
Oh, Commander...
Please come back!
Oh...
[NIKOLA, SERGE, BOWIE]
Commander...
I'm so sorry everyone.
Listen carefully, crew.
I have decided to
go back into battle.
This time, I won't be
fighting for someone else.
I will simply be
fighting for myself.
Alone.
I can't ask you to follow me.
But I... want to tell you this
while I still remain myself.
That I am very grateful...
...to have... known all of you.
I feel just like a human.
With human tears and all...
Why are you so sad, Meifon?
Don't cry now, don't cry!
Oh, thank you, Yayoi.
It's okay; it's all
right... to cry today.
[gasps]
Yayoi... Yayoi?!
--Oh... Meifon...
--[MEIFON] Yayoi!
[ANNE]
She has a high fever!
This is... [gasps]
What's this?
Oh, Commander!
This was in her bag!
Leon...!
Dear Meifon...
This is your invitation
to a final battle.
If you wish to save Yayoi's
life, you should come to see me.
If you refuse to come to me...
...I'll release the same
virus onto Oracion IV.
[gasps]
[LEON] I am sure you can
figure out where I am.
I'll be waiting. [laughs]
[MEIFON] Next time on
Space Guardian: Angel Links,
"All My Soul."