[TOKACHEV] Finally, after 178
years, you have appeared!
My elusive LiEF.
You will soon be in my grasp
and I will have eternal life.
Commander, you're right.
It's a remarkable creature!
I've never seen
anything like it.
You mean the LiEF?
Actually, its full name
is "Living Ether Flier."
It generates ether energy
through Dragon Stones
stored in its body.
And it's the biggest
living creature in space!
Lots of hype.
[KOSEI] It says here that
because the Lief lives so long,
some people think they can
actually gain immortality
by eating its liver.
Well, I suppose we better be
on the look-out for poachers.
Furthermore, his notion of
immortality is perpetuated
through both legends
and the occult.
You know, I do remember
my grandfather tellin' me
about the nutcase weirdos
who actually believed
in all of that whole liver
eating immortality nonsense.
It's very important to
many people out there
that we do our absolute
utmost to protect the LiEF.
The LiEF is safe with us.
[VALERIA]
I suggest we put Jaeger on this,
we need all the
hands we can get.
And convert the Angel
into Carrier Dress .
Speed won't be an issue.
The LiEF likes to take
her own sweet time.
Probably why she's
lived so long.
Yup.
And it'll be good to put
Jaeger's unit to work
so they don't get rusty.
[NIKOLA]
Three, two, one.
Take-off!
All right then.
Angel Links ! Launch!
Advance flying unit
surpassing Mach 1.
Spreading the sound barrier.
[ANNE]
Confirm Carrier Dress Base,
commence with
conversion operation.
We're now commending the
adjusting of the orbit velocity
between the dock
and Angel Links .
Darlings, time for wardrobe!
The Angel will be the
lady in red tonight.
Angel Core , all
compartments sealed.
[BOWIE]
Gantry arm, making contact.
[BOWIE] Positioning of Carrier
Dress to conversion point:
Complete.
Angel Core ,
commencing docking.
[ANNE] Dress conversion
operations: Complete.
We're headin' out now!
Let's go meet the LiEF!
Ready to launch.
Welcome to the Carrier
Dress , Commander.
There's no need to salute
little 'ole me, Captain Jaeger!
This isn't the military.
[JAEGER]
Aye-aye.
Nice to see you again,
but let's cut the formalities
and get down to business.
[TOKACHEV]
Well, my lady LiEF,
you don't look a day
over 10,000 years old.
Do tell me your secret.
You are like a wizard who
lives on nothing but air,
but somehow, you've
gotten awfully fat.
Not that I'm complaining.
Every pound I carve out
of your round belly
earns me a small fortune,
then I'll have wealth
and eternal life!
[laughs]
[ANNE]
We have sighted the LiEF.
[MEIFON]
Adjust speed and stay astern.
[NIKOLA]
Aye-aye.
[ANNE]
Monitor screening of LiEF.
[MEIFON]
What's that?
[ANNE]
That's the LiEF child.
I'll have to zoom
out for the mother.
There she is in all her glory.
Wow. I don't believe it.
The LiEF is so totally huge.
Do you think that thing is
actually a real living creature?
So they say.
Yes, because the LiEF converts
space ether into energy
by using the Dragon Stones
stored within its body.
So poachers are on the prowl for
her famous liver of immortality
and also for those
Dragon Stones.
You know, I'm thinking our space
ship uses ether for fuel
just like the LiEF.
So do you think that mean that
the Angel 's a living organism?
And to think that
you passed Biology.
[ANNE]
Commander!
There appear to be several
ships approaching the LiEF.
What should we do?
What kinda ships?
[ANNE] Private sightseeing tour
ships. Registration's confirmed.
They're getting awfully close.
Well, I bet that those
tourists paid mighty big bucks
to get a first-hand look
at the real LiEF.
Well, they better back off
quickly, or they might get hurt.
That LiEF baby is one
very agile creature.
Oh, c'mon, what's
a baby gonna do?
I'll go out and
warn them anyway.
Nikola, keep Angel Links
at this position.
Yes, Captain.
Captain Jaeger.
Yes?
Come along for the ride.
We could use a few more ships.
Sir! I mean, Commander!
I'm ready when you are.
[MEIFON]
He really needs to get out more.
[OPERATOR 1]
You're required to use a hood!
And mess up my hair? Bah!
Now, you be careful, Commander.
I just wanted to warn you,
this thing may look small,
but it's extremely powerful
and sometimes even kind of wild.
[MEIFON]
I've heard that one before.
Look, I know what I'm doing.
These ships were ordered
to my specifications.
[OPERATOR 1] Well then, I'm glad
your investment isn't wasted.
And good luck.
Man, I really should give
these guys more to do.
They're so uptight.
Just chill out, boys.
[OPERATOR B] Captain Jaeger,
you're cleared to launch.
Launching!
[OPERATOR A]
Catapult set!
Launching!
[sighs]
[chirping]
[ANNOUNCER] The sounds
that you hear right now
are the communications
between the LiEFs.
They are actually
transmitting energy signals,
but we've converted them to
sound so that you can hear them.
Wow. What's going on?
Hello. My name is Meifon
Li of the Angel Links .
We're here today
to safeguard the LiEF
against any pirate attacks.
Just in case of trouble,
we'd like you to withdraw
from the danger zone.
[CREW MEMBER] Understood,
Commander. We will withdraw.
Thank you for your cooperation.
You all have a safe passage now.
What?!
Hey!
[yells]
[MEIFON]
Get off of me, you little twerp!
Stop that! I'm not
a punching bag!
What on earth is she doing?
Deputy, I see an
approaching ship.
[KOSEI]
Huh?
[ANNE]
It's headed for the LiEF.
I can't identify
its registration.
[KOSEI]
Looks like a labor barge.
[ANNE]
I don't know. It's huge.
Hmm...
Seems very odd.
[JAEGER] We're alongside
the unidentified ship,
but there seems to be
no response from them.
[TOKACHEV]
They're blocking my view.
Get rid of them!
Oh, no!
Look! The ship has
just opened fire!
I knew it!
The approaching ship
is considered hostile,
so let's prepare to attack!
Fire!
Wh-What is happening?
We're jammed!
[ANNE]
We've lost the Jaeger unit!
Their controls have been jammed!
[gasps] A trap?!
[SUBORDINATE A]
The LiEF is now in range!
[TOKACHEV]
All right! Let's shed our cover!
[ANNE]
The enemy ship has separated.
It's approaching the LiEF!
There's no time for
confirmation! Attack and fire!
Huh?!
[ALL screaming]
Idiot! There's a retreating
cruiser ship here!
Hold your fire!
[KOSEI]
Huh?
[MEIFON]
Ridiculous!
[TOKACHEV]
Go after the LiEF child!
Capture it at once!
Huh?
Move the cruiser ship!
[TOKACHEV]
Give the tourists a ticket home!
Huh? I thought I told
them to withdraw!
[screaming]
[wailing]
[TOKACHEV]
There it is! Capture it!
Immortality is in my grasp!
Oh, no! They've captured
the LiEF child!
They're making an
escape to nine o'clock!
Do your Angel squadron proud
and do not let them escape!
[gasps]
[MEIFON]
The main reactor's dead.
Oh, no!
[MEIFON gasps]
[WORKERS]
Whoa!
[MEIFON]
Where am I?
You crashed into our ship!
So who are you anyway?
[MEIFON]
Huh?
[MEIFON] So you were repairing
a relay broadcast satellite?
[WORKER A]
Yeah, but we took cover here
when the attack started.
What do you mean attack?
[MEIFON gasps]
Angel Links !
Come in, Angel Links !
I'm recieving a transmission
from the commander!
Status report!
[KOSEI] Well, Meifon,
we're pursuing the pirates
who captured the LiEF child.
Deputy! The mother LiEF is
suddenly changing her direction.
What?!
She's following
the transmissions
being sent out by her child.
[ANNE] There's a space
station in her course!
And if she keeps going,
she will collide with it.
What do we do?
[VALERIA]
The LiEF is two miles long
and weighs millions of tons.
That's a catastrophe!
The only possible way to make
the LiEF change her course
is to re-capture the child
and move it away.
[MEIFON] What should I do?
There must be a way.
[gasps]
[MEIFON]
Is that a Newton Reactor?
[WORKER A] Yeah, it's
for satellite propulsion.
[MEIFON]
Great!
Oh, no, you don't!
That one's a brand
new replacement.
[MEIFON]
Hmm.
Kosei!
Deploy the Angel Links fleet
onto the LiEF's course
at full battle speed.
If it looks like she'll
penetrate the safety zone,
force her to change course,
even if you have to fire!
[KOSEI]
Roger!
That's easy for her to say.
I'm going to be the one burnt at
the stake if I hit the LiEF.
Ah! That was close!
[WORKER A]
You can't take it!
We need it for work!
I promise I'll buy you a new
one! Just name your price!
What? Hey, look here, lady,
we got a job to finish!
[MEIFON]
I don't have time for this!
Just send the invoice
to Angel Links.
Ya got that, smarty-pants?
[TOKACHEV] If we can just get
in there, we'll be home free.
[MEIFON]
The signal.
I can only hope they
don't change course now.
Ignite!
[yells]
[SERGE]
All gun-ports ready for firing!
Hold your fire till it crosses
the safety barrier zone.
Then fire all at once!
[ANNE] There's a heat
source fast approaching.
I've identified it.
It's the commander! No!
[yelling]
[ANNE] The commander
is on a direct course
for the enemy ship.
She's equipped with a
satellite propulsion reactor!
Why, she's ramming it into
the ship to change its course.
She's gone insane! What happens
if she misses her target?
There it is!
[TOKACHEV]
She dares to follow?
Destroy her!
And here I come!
We must make a path
for the commander
and do not let any
craft near her!
You're such a good man, Jaeger!
Yeah!
I've got you!
Huh?
No! This is supposed to be new!
Oh, no! The commander's craft
is now going off course!
It's headed into the station.
The reactor is out of control!
How much worse can this get?
The LiEF. Look!
[KOSEI gasps]
Nothing can stop it!
[TOKACHEV]
We've outrun them! We win!
[laughing]
Here I go!
[TOKACHEV]
What?!
All right then! Time to
face your immortality!
[TOKACHEV]
Move!
[yells]
[TOKACHEV]
Get out of the way!
[screaming]
[yells]
[ANNE] There's a heat source
fast approaching from astern.
[gasps] It's Meifon!
Is she with the baby?
Yes!
And now, I want the child back!
All right.
[groaning]
Oh, please, LiEF...
give me your immortality.
And so, the collision
between the LiEF
and the space station
has been averted!
[KOSEI sighs]
Oh, good.
Whew. We made it, baby.
Well, you sure are
a bundle of trouble.
No! Not again! I gotta
get the reactor going.
Oh, no! Too late!
I hate babysitting.
[LiEF chirping]
[MEIFON] Until next time on
Space Guardian: Angel Links ,
"The Rain upon the Stars."