[LEON]
Dear Meifon.
This is your invitation
to a final battle.
[gasps]
[LEON] If you wish
to save Yayoi's life,
you should come to see me.
If you refuse to come to me,
I'll release the same
virus onto Oracion IV.
Goryu... Goryu!
[MEIFON yells]
[LEON laughs]
[YAYOI]
Meifon...
[gasps]
Me... ifon...
[MEIFON gasping]
Yayoi!
Why would he go after Yayoi?!
Goryu!
Goryu...!
[KOSEI]
Hm?
[MEIFON]
Stay away!
Huh?
Don't you dare come near us now!
But what are you going to do?
Sorry... I know you wanna help
but this is something I need
to resolve all on my own.
Thank you, my friends.
Come back! Meifon!
[MEIFON grunts]
Meifon! Come back here!
Meifon! [groaning]
[DUUZ]
Stop it!
Will you let go!
Let me go, Duuz!
Meifon!
Angel Links !
Ready to launch!
Just takes off on her
own like that?! [growls]
She's crazy!
Kosei!
Where do you think you're going?
Take a guess!
I'm going after her!
--Aw. yeah!
--Let's go!
[LEON] I'm sure you can
figure out where I am.
[MEIFON]
A place that only I know.
[gasps]
[MEIFON]
The asteroid Mystel...
You want to use the
B Configuration?
[VALERIA]
It's an emergency.
Equip the Carrier Dress
with the Dummy Core.
[JAEGER] That requires
Commander approval.
Let's not quibble
over details here.
The commander--didn't she say
that Angel Links was dissolved?
Never mind that!
Make the preparations!
Get on it!
Yes, Officer. I understood you.
[JAEGER]
Hm? Huh?
[JAEGER] You said emergency.
May I ask what it is?
We'll explain later.
It's time to launch!
Well, we should
be able to manage this.
Yeah.
[NIKOLA] The B configuration
gives us five times the output,
we'll catch up to the commander.
Can you pick up Meifon's course?
Too much time has
passed, impossible!
And she hasn't filed
a flight plan yet, either.
Check the registers of each
planet and space station.
Yes, sir.
[TAFFEI chirping]
[KOSEI]
Taffei...
Can you please tell us where
Meifon might've gone, huh?
[chirps]
That's right, Taffei.
You know Meifon better
than anyone else does.
Huh?
[NIKOLA]
Taffei seems to think
the course is in the
north-eastern rim.
All right. Assault
Carrier Dress! Launch!
[MEIFON]
I'm getting closer...
...to where I was...
as my real self.
My place of origin...
My birth place?
What real self?!
No!
In order for me to
remain myself,
I must destroy Goryu
using my own free will.
For my own sake!
Yes...
[LEON laughs]
How strange
that I have awakened the one
who was created
specifically to destroy me.
But I don't regret it.
In fact, it gives me
a certain sense of perverse joy.
Do you think I'll be able
to acquire Meifon?
Yes, Master Goryu.
As you wish, sir.
[laughs] Soon enough we will
have the answer to it all.
[MEIFON]
All right.
I will fight the program and
defeat Goryu of my own will.
That will prove that
I am truly alive.
He has entangled innocent people
into this battle between us.
I will never let him
get away with it!
[growls] Goryu!
No!
[MEIFON] As long... as
I can remain myself...
...no one else will get hurt.
So Doc, what do you think?
So far, it doesn't seem like
there was any viral contagion
along the route the girl took.
I see.
It has, however, recently
come to my attention
that an experimental virus
was stolen 3 weeks ago.
What about the vaccine
for the virus?
There was a vaccine
stolen with the virus
and it's the only
one that exists.
So it all lies in
the hands of Goryu.
Found it! Identity confirmed!
It's the Angel Links ,
in its normal dress.
[VALERIA, KOSEI]
Huh?
Where's it heading now?
[ANNE]
Towards an asteroid.
[KOSEI]
What's there?
According to the data,
there's nothing at all
but an abandoned
resource station
down there. [gasps]
[KOSEI]
What's the matter?
It's registered under...
under Chenho.
Chenho?!
[VALERIA] Probably a
secret weapons plant
disguised as an abandoned mine.
Can we catch up?!
I doubt it.
Even with the Assault speed...
But there is one way.
This route here.
We can't!
The ship won't be able to bear
the heat from the star.
Besides, we could get
caught in its gravity field,
causing us to crash.
Certainly the ship
may get damaged.
But given the considerable
power of the Assault Dress--
we'll be able to break
through the gravity field.
[JAEGER]
Let's go.
I am not afraid of my own death
as long as it protects
our commander.
I believe that I speak
for everyone present.
Everyone...
...let's... go!
We might not be able
to do anything
even if we catch up to her,
but we've gotta try!
Set course for the
north-eastern rim!
[CREW]
Aye-aye!
[MEIFON] I'm so sorry
you got drawn into this.
I will make sure
you're saved soon.
Even if I have to
give up my life.
So hold on, Yayoi.
[YAYOI wheezes]
[MEIFON] Please, I know
I don't pray very often,
but please let me be who I am
now for a little bit longer.
If only to save Yayoi, I don't
care what happens to me.
There is no time!
I'll take the shortest
route possible!
Links Cannon! Cherubim! Fire!
[beeping]
[gasps]
Assault Carrier Dress?
Huh?
[NIKOLA growls]
Just keep going,
straight ahead.
We've gotta catch up to her!
[NIKOLA]
Spreading the laser sail.
Output, 150%!
[VALERIA, JAEGER grunting]
[SERGE growls]
[MEIFON]
I thought told you not to come.
[KOSEI] Jettison all three!
Maximum reactor output!
Aye-aye! [yells]
All right. Somehow we
made it through that.
Huh?
Why did you come?
Why did you...
Why did you come, you fools?!
Who's the fool here?!
[gasps]
[KOSEI] We can't let you go
alone in your current condition.
[MEIFON] But this is something
that I must do on my own.
I don't want to entangle anyone.
I don't want to hurt
anyone else anymore.
[KOSEI]
What are we to you then?
Huh?!
[KOSEI] Never mind worrying
about us so much!
Do you think you
can single-handedly
protect the lives of
everyone in this system?
If you're determined to fight,
we're with you on this!
No arguing.
We're with you all the way.
You're all... foolish.
That's right. We're all fools!
[chirps]
[KOSEI] If we weren't,
we wouldn't be fit
to be Angel Links crew members.
[CREW screams]
[MEIFON growls]
Where did they... come from?
[LEON] That ship operates
with a mechanism
that is far beyond your
understanding.
Destroy Goryu...
[LEON laughs]
Just as I told you,
you must come only with Yayoi.
The vaccine is here.
I'm waiting for you, Meifon.
[MEIFON growls]
[SEKU]
Sights adjusted to plus 0.3...
[LITALY] Convergence
inclination, rising to 120%.
[SEKU]
Target, locked on.
[SEKU, LITALY]
Main guns... Fire.
Retaliate!
We can't! With the last hit,
most of our weapons
just went down!
[MEIFON]
Kosei! Everyone!
Ah! Links Cannon,
prepare to fire!
[MEIFON groaning]
[MEIFON]
Why is...
...the Angel Links
moving on its own?
[LEON] We have a pest.
I'll have it exterminated.
Goryu...!
Come quickly,
Meifon. To my side.
[KOSEI] We can't allow
ourselves to get stuck
in a place like this!
If we don't hurry,
Meifon will...!
Kosei!
Huh?
[VALERIA]
Our only choice is to distract
the enemy ship with
Jaeger's unit.
At the same time, use
the Assault cyclone blade
to cut a path through.
[OPERATOR] Captain Jaeger,
you're free to launch!
And launch!
Kosei. You go, too.
We can't leave Meifon
alone right now.
[DUUZ]
I'll go with you.
[OPERATOR] Deputy Commander,
you're free to launch!
[KOSEI]
And launch!
[MEIFON]
Goryu...
[growling] Goryu!
Goryu!
[LEON laughs]
Go ahead, Meifon. Make my day.
In time you will find that your
hatred will be only a delusion.
[LEON laughs]
[SEKU]
You will not...
[LITALY]
...interfere.
What?!
[DUUZ, KOSEI groaning]
[KOSEI]
Uh. What is that?
Are you all right?
[KOSEI]
Jaeger?
Stay on the current course
in the shuttle if you can.
Don't worry, we'll do the rest.
[KOSEI]
Thanks.
Useless! Can't put
a scratch on 'em!
What a monster!
Back off, you creep! Huh?
[VALERIA]
Good job, Jaeger!
Yeah, right.
[SEKU, LITALY]
Approaching.
Nikola! Commence cyclone
blade system now!
[NIKOLA] Commencing
cyclone blade system!
[SEKU, LITALY]
What is it.
[VALERIA]
Don't hold back! Just ram it!
[JAEGER]
I can't believe it!
Even the beam guns
don't work on it.
What are they doing?
A Kamikaze attack?!
[NIKOLA]
Yeah!
The reactor!
We must blow the connecting
bolts and disengage the Core!
Aye-aye!
[SEKU]
All for...
[LITALY]
...Master Goryu...
[CREW groans]
Attack plan, accomplished.
Goryu! Goryu!
Goryu!
I'll destroy... you!
[MEIFON gasps]
[exhales]
Yayoi...
[MEIFON]
Just a little longer, Yayoi.
Goryu!
Come on out and fight!
[LEON laughs] Meifon, you
yourself should know where I am.
Me know... Myself...?
[LEON]
Very soon...
Very soon, the answer
will become apparent.
Come to me, Meifon.
And then, you will be able
to give me the answer.
[MEIFON panting]
It will be of my own will--
it will be for myself.
The asteroid Mystel.
[MEIFON] Next time on
Space Guardian: Angel Links,
"Fragment of an Angel."