[DOC] I was checking Meifon's
clinical chart the other day.
[KOSEI]
Hm...
The problem is?
She has no medical problem.
Do you know
anything about Goryu?
[VALERIA]
The Goryu?
You mean the famous
pirate who disappeared
there awhile back?
[AIHARA]
Commander!
During this trip, when we
get to our destination
we get a half day off
at the station, don't we?
You have a hot
date or something?
[AIHARA]
No! A hot plate!
That station serves
the most amazing crab!
Did you say crab? Let's all go!
Perfect! Serge, I will
second that motion!
Now this is the problem
with omnivores...
We're not off yet,
so get to work, please.
Yeah.
Right. Get to work.
[ANNE gasps]
What Anne? See something?
[ANNE] Well, something
flashed on the radar.
But now it seems
like it's disappeared.
Oh, it's probably
just interference.
Let's check it out,
just in case.
'Cause we don't want
to be caught off-guard.
Aye-aye.
[ANNE]
No trace of laser reflections--
ether density is flat.
Trace detected!
It is the size of an 800
meter-class battleship!
The distance: 5,000 miles!
There are definitely no
identified flight plans
currently filed for this region.
Alert status!
[alarm blares]
What is going on up here?
It's an unidentified battleship!
Commander!
Now the ship is sending
a transmission to us.
Really?!
All right. Let's view monitor.
[gasps]
[LAWRENCE]
This is Brigadier General
Lawrence McGuire of
the 3rd Special Force
of the 1st Mobile Battle Group.
of the Einhorn
Imperial Space Force.
The Einhorn Empire?
The Space Force?
[CREW chattering]
Oh, Lawrence...
[chattering continues]
[LAWRENCE] It looks as
though we spooked you.
Sorry. We are headed towards
our current base station
at Oracion 3.
We have no intention
of interfering with
any other fleets.
There is no reason
to be alarmed.
[sighs]
[LAWRENCE] I'll have what
the lady's having.
I'm having scotch on the rocks.
This is where to get it,
it's the only place
in the station
that serves a
decent single malt.
It's been 5 years and you
haven't changed a bit.
Oh, I don't know, just try me.
I really like the long hair.
[LAWRENCE] A toast, to the
youngest tactical officer
in the Einhorn Imperial Space
Forces, Valeria Vertone.
[VALERIA]
Thank you.
[gasping]
[SUPERIOR] Your actions were
clearly a breach of orders.
Because of you, our fleet has
been dealt a severe blow.
My mission was simply
to destroy the enemy.
It was certainly not to
protect a misguided fleet
that held on to faulted views.
I obeyed, even if it meant
ten thousand casualties.
Officer, you incriminate
yourself further
with that answer!
Defendant, refrain from making
statements out of order.
After that, you disappeared
from the Forces and from me.
Do you ever regret it?
[VALERIA]
Why? Should I?
By the way, how is your boy?
[LAWRENCE]
He's already in junior high.
I can't believe it.
[LAWRENCE] Actually,
encountering Angel Links
was not a coincidence.
[VALERIA]
Huh?
Do you have any desire to
return to the Einhorn Forces?
[VALERIA]
Einhorn? Me?
[LAWRENCE]
Yes.
Despite the past, your tactical
skills are highly regarded.
[VALERIA] If General McGuire's
here just to tell me that,
then I'm flattered.
[LAWRENCE]
But that's not all.
Einhorn is also looking for
information on Angel Links.
[VALERIA]
"Angel Links"?
[LAWRENCE]
It's a peace-keeping,
private para-military
organization.
We want to know about
its establishment,
battle capabilities
and crew data.
[VALERIA]
So, the Angel Links has become
a thorn in the side of
the Einhorn Empire, hm?
If we can obtain that data,
then you will be re-instated
to your former position.
[VALERIA]
So, that's the bait?
[LAWRENCE] I don't think it's
a bad proposal, frankly.
Information on Angel Links
and Valeria Vertone.
If the Empire had to choose,
one or the other,
which would it be?
[LAWRENCE] I would do anything
to start over with you...
[gasps]
...get back together again.
[LAWRENCE] As for the Forces,
if they had to choose one
or the other, you'd
be the first priority.
I'll give you time
to think about it.
[VALERIA]
A return to the Einhorn.
[VALERIA] A return to
everything I left behind.
[DUUZ]
That you, Valeria?
[VALERIA]
You alone, Duuz?
Where is everybody?
[DUUZ]
They're eating crustaceans
but I don't dine
on bottom-feeders.
When you put it that way...
Hey, Duuz, do you plan on
staying with Angel Links
for a little while?
Well, it's a pretty
comfortable place.
So I'll at least finish
off my contract.
[VALERIA] I guess.
And the chairs are comfy, too.
The first letter is a "P."
A smart bird who chooses
the tree to nest in.
Huh?
[DUUZ] "Smart bird"
who choose its tree.
Oh, you're doing the crosswords.
It's a pheasant. A pheasant
chooses its tree.
P-H-E-A-S--
I can spell. Pheasant.
A pheasant chooses
its tree, huh?
[DUUZ]
Valeria.
[VALERIA]
Yes?
[DUUZ]
Four letters begins with "J."
"One for every Jack."
Uh, Jack and Jill.
Jill. So, what kind of
crossword is that?
It's called "Words of Wisdom."
[CREW chattering]
[AIHARA]
You know the crab is good
when everybody stops talking!
[VALERIA] All I have left
to get is the data
about the founding
of Angel Links.
Huh? What's this?
[VALERIA]
"June 30th... Chenho Li and wife
Lifon killed in a flight
accident at Oracion IV.
July 1st, award offered in the
amount of six million folleys
for the whereabouts of first
degree murderer, Goryu."
So, the day after
Meifon's parents died
a huge price was put on
that one pirate's head.
Do you know anything
about Goryu?
[VALERIA]
They must have suspected him.
Why... What's their
relationship with Goryu?
There's something I'd like
you to check out for me.
[LAWRENCE] I found it in
an old file on Chenho Li.
[VALERIA]
Chenho?!
[LAWRENCE]
According to the documents,
Chenho and this Goryu were
suspected of working together
in the pirating business.
[VALERIA]
Pirating? Chenho?
[LAWRENCE] Yes. And somehow
he managed to become
the head of a major
conglomerate.
[VALERIA] And Goryu
killed Chenho's daughter
and her husband.
[LAWRENCE] As to how Chenho
built up the Links Group,
or why Goryu went after his
daughter and husband,
and whether that
has anything to do
with the founding
of Angel Links--
that's what the information
department is interested in.
[VALERIA] It's certainly
an intriguing story.
[LAWRENCE] Intriguing enough
to have you stay on
with Angel Links as
part of their staff?
Now honor our agreement.
In exchange for
information on Goryu
the data on Angel Links.
[VALERIA] Agreed,
I'll hand over the data.
[LAWRENCE]
But you aren't coming back.
I'm sorry, but it doesn't
suit my purpose
to build a nest in
the Einhorn tree.
That's crazy!
You could have a fleet of
thousands in the Empire
You'd rather grub it out
here in the frontier?
[VALERIA] I'd rather have
a small tree and fly free
than have a big tree
in the Einhorn cage.
[LAWRENCE]
Someday someone's gonna
clip your wings, Valeria!
[VALERIA]
No Jack for this Jill.
All right! Now that
we're all here... Launch!
Yes, Captain!
Valeria... at least I
tried to save you.
Stubborn woman.
[OPERATOR] Analysis of Angel
Links' data, complete.
[LAWRENCE]
Right, give me a report.
Yes, sir. The maximum
firing range
of the Oracle cannon is
approximately 20,000 kilometers.
And there is a dead angle
to the cannons on board.
Dead angle?
[OPERATOR]
In this configuration,
it's at 6 o'clock, low.
Below and directly astern
is the dead angle.
Ah, yes. So I see.
[OPERATOR]
Are you sure about this?
We haven't received orders.
[LAWRENCE] Using the same
degree of battle strength,
we sink the fleet which Valeria
Vertone has embraced.
I think that's a very
appealing prospect.
But General!
[LAWRENCE] The Einhorn has had
their eye on Angel Links for
a while. They won't object
if we leave no witnesses.
[NIKOLA] We're about to
reach the point at which we
can commence sub-ether drive.
[BOWIE]
Munchenhauser reactor is green.
Ether density, 102%.
[MEIFON]
Huh?
Hey, what are you
doin' there, Valeria?
I'm programming course
settings for the missiles.
Wh-What? Why are
we doing that?
Well, I wish it were
just my imagination.
Anne, I would like you
to keep a good watch
on the surrounding space.
[ANNE] Hm? Yeah, sure,
whatever you say.
Valeria, what's up, huh?
[MEIFON]
Uh. Hey?!
But it can't be! Because there's
nothing at all on the radar!
[VALERIA]
It's the Einhorn Ziedlitz.
[MEIFON]
Huh?!
[MEIFON] The Ziedlitz...
Then you mean...?
Yes. I'm sure of it.
[NIKOLA] We're in battle
with the Einhorn?
[CREW muttering]
[AIHARA]
Can't be?!
Stay calm, everyone!
I doubt they'd be bringing
a major fleet into
the Oracion system.
I bet it's only Lawrence's
single squadron.
Valeria...
There's no way...
Valeria and... Einhorn?
[DUUZ]
Hm...
[VALERIA]
Relax and remember,
Einhorn attacks knowing
that I'm on board
They are by no means
any friends of mine!
Oh!
Retreat from enemy fire!
Yes, Captain!
Bowie! Don't use the radar.
You have to calculate their
position based on their barrage.
Aye-aye, Captain!
[LAWRENCE] I'm impressed.
They have determined that
the use of radar will
help us to detect them.
[ANALYST] Should we proceed
with standard tactics?
[LAWRENCE] Launch the sensor
pods, find their exact position.
[ANNE] Something's been
launched by the enemy ship!
It's probably some sensor pods!
Nikola! Retreat!
[NIKOLA groans]
[MEIFON] At this rate we'll
end up taking a direct hit!
Isn't there something
we can do?!
There's one strategy
that might work.
Huh?!
[MEIFON]
Valeria?
The movement is technically
illegal, it's really up to you.
You're an acquaintance
of the enemy commander...
I know, but I am also a crew
member of the Angel Links .
All right. Then you're on.
I hereby hand over
command to Tactical Officer,
Valeria Vertone!
Angel Links will now
separate from the fleet
and withdraw on our own!
Set direction to 1 o'clock, low!
Yes, Captain!
[ANALYST] The enemy command
ship is making a move!
What do you mean by that?!
[ANALYST] It doesn't seem
like they know our position.
The command ship's
moving alone?
It couldn't be. What's their
distance from the escort fleet?
[ANALYST]
Around 21,000 kilometers!
They plan to use
the Oracle cannon?
However, we won't
be falling for that.
All right!
Position ship at
enemy's 6 o'clock, low.
At a distance of
20,000 kilometers!
[LAWRENCE] No more flying
for you, little bird.
[VALERIA]
One, two, three, four...
Angel Links ! Come
about 180 degrees!
[ANALYST] Enemy ship,
at 0 o'clock, high!
Distance, 20,050 kilometers!
[LAWRENCE]
All guns! Prepare to fire!
Too far, Oracle Cannon!
We're out of range.
Prepare Oracle Cannon!
[VALERIA] Aim sights to
enemy command ship!
[LAWRENCE] Aim sights
to enemy command ship!
All guns fire!
[ANALYST]
Oracle cannon approaching!
No way?!
[EINHORN CREW scream]
But how?!
She lied to me!
Oracle cannon has
made a direct hit!
[CREW cheering]
Too soon to celebrate!
[LAWRENCE growls]
[LAWRENCE]
What are the other ships doing?!
Get in front and retaliate!
Oh, no! The enemy fleet
is returning fire!
[CREW grunt]
[KOSEI]
Retaliate!
[VALERIA]
Never mind their fleet!
Aim for the command ship!
Ready Links cannon!
[SERGE]
Energy charge-up, 30%!
Activate, ship-wide
anti-shock system.
[VALERIA]
Links cannon! Fire!
[LAWRENCE groans]
[OPERATOR 1]
Number 1 gun turret destroyed!
[OPERATOR 2] Number 1 and 4
turrets aren't functional!
[OPERATOR 3]
Missile ports destroyed!
[OPERATOR 4]
Power output down 50%!
How could this be...?!
[gasps] Valeria!
We do not have any desire
whatsoever to sink you.
If you leave the battle
theatre immediately,
we will not give chase.
[LAWRENCE] Y-You mean
you're letting us go?!
[VALERIA] If we were
to sink your ship
we would have to fight against
the Einhorn Forces proper.
Even Angel Links
has no desire for that.
How did you know
our exact position?
[VALERIA]
It was the best position
from which to attack us.
So, you intentionally...
[VALERIA]
An able commander
never misses the enemy's
unguarded points.
I know you, you always attack
my greatest... weakness.
[LAWRENCE gasps]
[LAWRENCE]
My ship is damaged,
but my squadron is still
capable of attack!
Convert this to Imperial.
The real firing range
of the Oracle cannon
is 30,000 kilometers.
Your entire squadron is
within our firing range.
Our escort ships are
surrounding you as we speak.
[LAWRENCE]
Huh?!
So, that data you
gave us was fake?
[VALERIA] The truth is
for you to figure out.
You lied to me from the start!
Perhaps I did lie to you.
I really wish it didn't
have to be this way now.
[LAWRENCE]
You're not the woman I knew.
[VALERIA] No, I'm not. You
however, are exactly the same.
It's disappointing.
[LAWRENCE]
What do you mean by that?
End transmission.
Valeria!
[LAWRENCE sighs]
[growling]
[OPERATORS gasp]
[LAWRENCE]
Little vixen!
[VALERIA]
Commander.
I leaked information about
Angel Links to Einhorn.
A clear violation of contract.
I expect you'll have
to discharge me.
[MEIFON]
Hm...
But, Valeria, do you think that
you acted on your best judgment
as a tactical officer
in this situation?
Under the circumstances.
Very well. It's understood.
[ANNOUNCER]
The Einhorn Empire Forces
officially announced today
that the accident was caused
by cosmodust impact
during exercises.
However, a full investigation
is still underway.
[LEON] The Einhorn people
should have been satisfied
with simply obtaining
this data. Hm...
[MEIFON] Next time on
Space Guardian: Angel Links,
"The Ones Who Were Left."