[CAPTAIN]
This is cargo vessel Octopus ,
currently transiting
the Southwestern rim
of the Oracion Planetary System,
approaching in Newton Drive
and headed for ascension.
All systems prepare to enter
the orbit of Planet 3.
Well, looks like our
ship has no escort!
[CREW cheer]
Yeehaw! Blast 'er, but
don't damage the goods!
[CAPTAIN]
Pirates! Defenses up.
We're being attacked!
Send an SOS!
Alert sent, Captain!
[BOTH yell]
Octopus , you're
deep-fried calamari!
That's what you get for
not wearin' protection!
You'll never hit us
with your little toys!
[laughing]
What the--?
What was that?
Oh! Angel !
We're here!
[chuckles]
Commander, enemy Grappler
ships are in retreat.
Another third rate pirate.
Wake me when it's over.
Even a third-rate pirate
deserves my full attention.
[KOSEI] I just put the
tea on, Commander.
You've got two minutes
while it steeps, 'kay?
Well then, let's send
off our guests in style
before it gets bitter.
Links Cannon! Prepare to fire!
Systems output: 20%.
Confirming cargo
vessel escape path!
Cherubim!
[screams]
[MEIFON]
Oh! He turned a pretty color.
[CAPTAIN]
Ahh.
That must be the famous...
[NARRATOR]
The Oracion Planetary System
is considered one of the richest
areas in the frontier of space
due to its valuable
mineral deposits.
Huge unarmed cargo vessels are
left to haul valuable minerals
through this wild territory,
where pirates prey upon the
weak like a pack of hyenas.
The police are out-maneuvered,
and companies have no choice
but to seek out
other protection.
To their rescue come
private security firms
with the most advanced ships,
staffed with professional
pirate fighters.
One of these firms,
the Links Group,
fights pirates free of charge
to help smaller businesses
who have limited resources.
[NARRATOR] Acting as the
leader of the Links Group
is a young 16-year-old
girl called Meifon Li.
This is spaceship Angel .
We're now preparing to
return to Oracion IV.
Configuring for touch down.
[TACO]
Commander, my gratitude to you
for escorting our ship recently!
No problem. Anytime, sir.
So if you need us again,
just call and we'll
be there right away.
Okay!
Gosh, Miss Meifon, you truly
are such a beacon in the dark
for all of us small
security firms.
Ah, Miss Meifon Li!
Please allow me to express
my sincere gratitude
for escorting the
president recently.
Yes, yes, yes.
And I do appreciate your
help in handling security
for the transport of
our death row prisoners.
[MEIFON]
Ahh!
Hm.
A free pirate fighting service
was my grandfather's dying wish.
If you wanna thank someone,
you can visit my
grandfather's grave.
Ah, yes. Well put, my lady!
I just don't see why I have
to come to these things.
[VALERIA] Schmoozing at
sponsorship receptions
is part of your Angel
Links contract.
And besides, it's an open bar.
Y'know, Meifon takes all those
diplomats right off guard.
She doesn't buy into
any of their politics.
They have no idea who
they are dealing with.
She's a regular Joan of Arc, eh?
I'm impressed. Reptile Boy
knows his human terminology.
[DUUZ]
Hmph. Bottoms up.
Well, well. if it isn't the
spectacle of the evening.
And so who're you?
[growls]
Such naïveté. How quaint.
[GORDON]
Allow me to give you my card.
[MEIFON]
Hmm...
Gordon and Company?
Security Service.
Who would've thought
that the leading firm
in the transportation and
information services industries
had such a beautiful girl as
the head of their corporation?
It seems to me that you are
much better suited for a...
...softer kind of
escort service.
Especially now that
you've volunteered
to fight pirates
for certain clients.
We'll see about that.
You know, leadership
skills have nothing at all
to do with gender.
The Commander's reputation
speaks for itself,
and as for pirates,
well, we try to protect those
who can't afford an escort.
Forgive me, but you're
creating a false economy.
It costs money to fight pirates,
and not many
businesses can afford
to play Guardian Angel
to clients for free.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[chuckles]
[YAYOI screams]
Feeding your anger?
Look, he'll say anything
to get your goat, Meifon.
You fight pirates better
than he does, and for free.
Why can't they accept
that a beautiful young girl
runs her own company?
Can I help it if they're
jealous of little ol' me, huh?
Ha. A little modesty
wouldn't hurt.
What did you say?
[ANNE]
President?
[ANNE whispering]
[EXIADE laughs]
[EXIADE]
Listen up!
My name is Exiade Leego.
I'll only say this once.
I wanna trade these hostages
for 100 kilos of Dragon Stone.
So Leon Lau's ship
was attacked by pirates.
Leon Lau.
I'm sure he was planning
to attend today's reception.
The attack occurred
on his journey here.
[VALERIA] WEll, didn't he
have an escort ship with him?
[ANNE]
He did. But they...
Who's "they"?
[ANNE]
Ashid B-type.
Nice doing business with you.
[VALERIA]
Ashid B is a band of pirates
made up of
degenerate mercenaries.
They're a nasty bunch.
[MEIFON] Well, my guest
is missing a good party!
I better assure
his safe arrival.
After all, I'm the host!
[BOWIE]
Gravity cycle unit! Activated!
[DOC]
Bridge inertia control.
[NIKOLA] General controls,
commence power transfer.
Dock draining: Complete.
[NIKOLA] Advance flying unit,
launch preparation complete.
Three, two, one.
Take-off!
[NIKOLA] Advance flying unit,
launch confirmed.
We're good to go.
So, Angel Links ! Launch!
Advance flying unit
surpassing Mach 1.
Spreading the sound barrier.
Well, as long as you
pay them enough,
those guys will do
anything for money.
Including kidnapping!
[KOSEI]
Exiade Leego.
Mercenary gang boss.
Will do anything for money.
Two months ago, he caused
50 fatalities on Metanoia.
He also takes credit
for the airport bombing.
Mr. Leon Lau owns a
private airline company,
and in a few short years,
has managed to establish himself
as the Top Gun of Travel.
He's also well known
for his charity work,
such as building a
school for orphans.
Ah. Now I see.
You know, you've got a lot
of nerve picking a fight
with Angel Links of Oracion.
[EXIADE] I would worry about
yourself more than anyone else.
[crying]
[EXIADE]
Ugh! Shut up, you stupid brat!
[LEON]
Don't you dare touch Yayoi!
Why, if you end up hurting her,
then I'll kill you
with my own hands!
What?!
[SUB A]
Boss! Our treasure's arrived!
[ALL gasp]
The escort ship is in pieces!
This is so awful.
We request the release of
the hostages, as you promised.
[EXIADE]
All right.
Bring the goods, leave your
weapons, and come aboard.
And don't try anything stupid!
[MEIFON]
Understood.
Well, the rumors were
right about you being
a nice little piece of work.
Can't believe a beauty like you
would be working
as a pirate fighter.
[EXIADE]
I'm gonna have to frisk you.
Hey, let go!
Duuz! Let go of him!
[DUUZ]
As you wish.
[chuckles]
[growls]
[KOSEI]
Meifon.
[EXIADE chuckles]
[EXIADE yelps]
[growling]
These jewels are not
part of the bargain.
Ugh. Ungrateful wench!
Then what about
the Dragon Stones?
[EXIADE chuckles]
Gotta hand it to
you, Links Group.
Only you could come up with
those priceless Dragon
Stones so quickly!
I've held up my end. Release
those two hostages now.
[EXIADE]
First, I want you and Pretty Boy
to escort us to a safer region.
And the "iguana" stays.
[growls]
[VALERIA]
Awaiting orders.
All hands on combat
alert, and stand by!
I'm extremely sorry you got
involved in all of this mess.
It's not your fault so
don't blame yourself.
I hope...
[crying]
[gasps]
[MEIFON]
What's wrong? Cheer up a little!
There you go again!
If you keep that up, I'm just
gonna burst into tears.
[MEIFON crying]
[MEIFON]
Peek-a-boo!
Did I surprise you?
There now. That's better.
Don't be afraid, Yayoi. No way!
Those pirates are no match
for this Angel Links bear!
Rawr! Rawr!
Rawr!
Ow!
[giggles]
Okay now?
You gotta trust me. Deal?
Deal.
Heh!
[MEIFON]
You have a beautiful daughter.
[LEON] Actually, she
lost both her parents
shortly after she was born.
[KOSEI]
Oh, that's right.
You support a
school for orphans.
Yes. Some people say it's
just a publicity stunt.
Well, maybe my reasons
are selfish, but...
When I see her smile
and hear her laughter,
I don't care what anyone says.
It's wonderful to
give a child joy.
[MEIFON yowls]
[chuckles] It's time to
say your good-byes.
Get up. You're in
our territory now.
Your services are
no longer of use.
It's time to throw
out the trash.
I agree!
[KOSEI]
Huh?
Take him away!
What the--?!
Excuse me.
[KOSEI]
Meifon!
[MEIFON]
Hurry up! This way!
[EXIADE]
Don't let them get away!
Come in, Angel Links !
This is Meifon!
Do you read me?
We have the two hostages!
Hey, we've got a transmission
from the commander!
Let's go get them!
Charge!
[CREW]
Aye-aye!
There's an escape capsule
in the hangar! This way!
Stop them!
Huh? My Bear!
[MEIFON]
Yayoi! Where are you going?
Yayoi, get back here!
Yayoi!
[YAYOI]
Huh?
[MEIFON gasps]
[YAYOI screams]
[EXIADE]
Hold it right there.
Let her go!
[LEON yells]
Step right up. Who
would like to be next?
The lady or the tramp?
Maybe I'll knock off the brat.
[YAYOI gasps]
[wailing]
[crying]
[gunshot]
Now, Taffei!
[yells]
[yelling]
[EXIADE groans]
[VALERIA]
This is Angel Links , Commander.
Ready for transport!
[CREW MEMBER] Quick!
Let's get the heck out of here!
Kill the shepherd and
the sheep will scatter.
Cowards.
Angel Links Cannon!
Prepare to fire!
[CREW]
Aye-aye!
[SERGE]
Position gun!
Set!
Energy charge-up...
Seventy.
Ninety.
One hundred.
One fifteen.
Remove safety!
Activate ship-wide
anti-shock system.
[MEIFON]
Adjust sights!
Locked on target!
Try this on for size.
Cherubim!
[growling]
Useless pirate idiots!
[MEIFON]
Grandfather...
It's been six months since
Angel Links was formed,
according to your dying wish.
In that time, we've had
all sorts of reactions
for running a free
pirate fighting service.
I don't pay much
attention to them though.
We've got a good team,
Grandpa. You'd be proud.
Huh?
[giggling]
Leon Lau! Yayoi!
[LEON] This little one insisted
on coming to thank you.
Thank you, Miss Meifon.
[BOTH laugh]
[chuckles]
[KOSEI]
Huh? Where did she go?
Hmm.
In remembrance of..
our beloved...
...Meifon Li?
[KOSEI]
This can't be!
[MEIFON]
Stay tuned for next time
on Space Guardian: Angel Links ,
"A Wasted Fairy Tale"