You seek your vengeance
even in death, Chenho.
But you miscalculated,
didn't you?
Because your assassin does
not even recognize me.
How unfortunate for you.
I will take Meifon before
she remembers anything
[KOSEI] Chenho and Goryu
were both pirates...
But Chenho put a price on
Goryu's head... why?
What does it mean?
[KOSEI]
Meifon!
[MEIFON]
Goryu...
[knocking]
[KOSEI]
Hm?
A client is here to see you now.
[KOSEI]
All right.
[MEIFON laughs]
[MEIFON gasps]
[MEIFON cries]
[CHENHO]
Don't!
[MEIFON growls]
[TAFFEI yelps]
[MEIFON] Something's strange.
I just know it.
[TAFFEI chirps]
Something inside me is not me.
[KOSEI]
Meifon.
[MEIFON]
Wh-What is it, Kosei?
A client who's scheduled for
embarkment tomorrow morning
is here to say hello. But if
you're tired, then I can tell--
[MEIFON]
No, I'll come.
[MEIFON yawns]
I think I think too much!
Time for to work!
Meifon!
[gasps] Uncle Ulgen!
It's been a while, Meifon.
You look well.
You, too! Oh, I've missed
your growly voice!
Well, I see you
know each other.
Yes, he's an old friend
of my grandfather's.
Correct. We were
"blood brothers"!
Master Chenho's?
But you have yet
to meet my Marcia.
My one and only grandchild.
Nice to meet you. I'm Meifon.
I'm Marcia.
And this is her first
time to Altair.
Do you think you could show
her around, Meifon?
I can discuss matters
about tomorrow
with this fellow I suppose?
Sounds great!
I'll take Marcia around
all my stomping grounds!
Well then,
where should we go?
It's okay. if you're busy...
Oh, I'd rather do this
than dreary office work!
[KOSEI] This is the first
time I've seen Meifon
spend time with
someone her own age.
[inaudible]
[MEIFON, MARCIA laugh]
So, I understand that you
lost both your Mother
and your Father...?
Yeah. Since then, I have always
been with my grandpa.
Huh. Seems like we've
got a lot in common.
Right down to stubborn
grandfathers!
Let's have a toast--
here's to our meeting!
What? Did I say something?
This is the first time
that I've ever been
out with anyone
other than my grandfather.
Huh? Don't you go to school?
So ya don't?!
These days, I don't go either.
But it was fun.
Lots of friends and stuff.
Huh...
Yeah!
[GIRL 2
I'd love to go.
[GIRL 3
Oh, he is so cute.
[MEIFON]
Friends... Strange...
I can't recall even one
friend I used to have.
[MEIFON]
Not even one...
Is something wrong?
Huh? Mm! Mm-mm.
[MEIFON]
What's wrong with me?
Meifon, thank you for
taking the time.
[MEIFON]  My pleasure!
See you tomorrow!
[MARCIA]
Meifon!
Huh?
Can we be friends
from now on?
Of course!
[MARCIA]
No matter who I am?
Huh?
Marcia, you're a...
That is right, Meifon.
Marcia is an android
[gasps]
[ULGEN] When I lost my son
and his family in the accident,
I simply couldn't bear
the sorrow of it.
So I had an android made to
look like my granddaughter.
Now she's my family.
But Marcia has no memories
yet, and no friends, either.
No friends?
I appreciate your help.
[gasps]
[MARCIA]
Meifon!
You will be my friend,
won't you?
My first friend?
We have so much in common,
you said it yourself.
We understand each other.
We are not the same!
I was not manufactured!
[MARCIA whimpers]
[gasps]
I'm so awful.
[GORDON]
Why, this is...!
I can't believe this is the
escort route of Angel Links.
How did you get a hold of this?
[LEON]
Hmph.
Do you really need to know?
No. Not at all, I'm not nosy.
[LEON] We'll fire a barrage
when we get into orbit
around Oracion V.
With your ship.
Uh. What?! Wait a minute...!
You're going to use us again,
and I'm trying to run a
respectable business here.
This will be a
hand-to-hand battle.
And you are going to handle it,
a small favor between friends.
Anything for you, my friend.
[NIKOLA] Advance flying unit,
launch preparation complete.
3...
...2... 1...
Take-off!
[NIKOLA] Advance flying unit,
launch confirmed.
All right! Angel Links! Launch!
[NIKOLA] Advance flying unit
surpassing Mach 1.
[NIKOLA]
Spreading the sound barrier.
[ANNE] We will be entering the
orbit around Oracion V shortly.
No suspicious vessels sighted.
Let's maintain our
current formation
and continue our course.
Yes, Captain!
And how is my uncle's group?
They seem just fine.
That's good.
[GORDON]
How much longer
till we intersect the
Angel Link 's route?
About 300 seconds.
Well, isn't it time to
send them a signal now?
It's been done.
Tell me, why is it that you're
going out of your way
to do all of this yourself, eh?
I thought you said
that you weren't nosy.
No. Just curious.
[LEON]
You can relax.
I don't intend on
making you fight.
[ANNE] There's a ship ahead
intersecting our course.
The registration search says...
Gordon and Company.
And they have a space
bureau flight permit.
Gordon And Company? Creepy...
They're getting a bit
too close for comfort now.
Let's caution them.
Signal them, Aihara.
Sure.
[DOUE] There's a transmission
in from Angel Links .
[LEON]
Ignore it.
We'll launch the assault ball.
Not on Angel Links,
but on the ship it escorts.
They have not responded.
Really! I'll threaten them!
Look out! It's an assault ball!
[MEIFON gasps]
They fooled us.
Attacking with a legitimately
registered ship.
Launch an assault
ball back! Hurry!
Grandpa, wait!
Don't worry now. Please,
stay where you are, Marcia.
But...
It's going to be all right.
Oh...
[CREW groaning]
[MEIFON yells]
All troops, secure area!
[TROOPS groaning]
Just leave it to us.
[DUUZ growls]
[TROOPS whimper]
I'll finish them all off.
[CREW 3 groans]
[CREW 4 groans]
[ULGEN growls]
[TROOPS groaning]
[ULGEN] This battle has
the hallmark of Marmin,
our pirate group...
Can't be! Goryu!
[MEIFON yells]
[TROOP 3 groans]
Uncle! Marcia!
Uh! Where are you?!
Where did you go?!
[VALERIA] Kosei! These
aren't just any pirates!
[DUUZ]
Yes. They're very well trained.
And, extremely organized.
Well, what do they
want with us, anyway?
Valeria, Duuz, I'm
going after Meifon!
All right! But be careful!
[MARCIA whimpers]
Marcia!
Marcia! This way!
Grandpa!
Watch out!
[BOTH gasping]
[ULGEN groans]
[MARCIA]
Grandpa!
[yells]
[TROOPS groaning]
[MEIFON]
Uncle!
[ULGEN grunting]
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Are you all right, Marcia?
Uh. Yes...
Uncle... You shielded Marcia...
Does that seem strange to you
just because she's not human?
[MEIFON]
Mm?
I do love Marcia. I love her
even the way she is now.
I'm just the same as
your Grandfather, Chenho.
[gasps]
The same as my grandfather?
Uncle! But what do you mean
"the same as my grandfather?"
Tell me what you mean!
Meifon, dear...
your grandfather...
Chenho was... Chenho was...
[ULGEN, MARCIA groan]
[MEIFON]
Uncle...
Marcia...
[screams] No!
[gasps] Leon Lau...
Uh. What could you
possibly be doing here?
[MEIFON]
Did you shoot them?
[LEON]
They were dangerous to you.
They'll remind you
of unfortunate things.
They will remind me?
They'll remind me of what?!
[LEON]
Meifon, you think too much.
[gasps]
I would like you to come with
me now. Come here.
There's nothing to
worry about now.
I want you to come
with me, Meifon.
You do love me,
don't you, my dear...?
[gasps]
No! Meifon!
[KOSEI]
Stay away from him, Meifon!
No!
[KOSEI yelps]
Oh, Lifon...
Meifon!
No!
[CHENHO]
Goryu must die...
You must destroy Goryu
during your limited lifetime.
Must destroy... Destroy Goryu...
[LEON growls]
I have finally found
you, Goryu...
[LEON groaning]
[MEIFON]
I have found you, now, Goryu.
You mean Leon Lau is Goryu?!
[MEIFON]
I have found you, now, Goryu!
Curse Chenho!
He's made me the switch that
turns on a murder machine!
Meifon!
[LEON]
Hmph.
There's nothing to cry over.
She's just an android
that Chenho built
for the purposes
of killing me.
[KOSEI]
Meifon...?!
[MEIFON]
Stay out of it!
[MEIFON yells]
[LEON]
Incredible...
[LEON] To think that he
perfected this angelic jewel,
even surpassing the most
advanced military robot.
[laughs] I'm impressed.
Someday, I will have you
for my very own purposes.
[MEIFON yelling]
Goryu! Goryu!
Goryu! Ah! Uh.
[KOSEI growls]
What's going on?
[KOSEI]
Stop it, Meifon!
[MEIFON grunts]
Meifon, no!
Kosei!
Stop it, Meifon!
Now settle down!
[MEIFON panting]
Settle down. Goryu
isn't here anymore.
That's right.
It's all okay now, Meifon.
[MEIFON]
Kosei...
I was the same...
The same as Marcia after all.
Everything's gonna be all right.
[MEIFON sobs]
I'm the same! Why, why?!
[ULGEN] I love Marcia...
Yes, I am the same as Chenho.
That's wrong. Grandfather...
He never loved me.
Why would he...?
[MEIFON] Next time on
Space Guardian: Angel Links,
"At the Binary Interval."