[MEIFON panting]
I pray that the Commander
remains safe.
Poor Meifon...
Oh, Commander...
And this is all for the
sake of not hurting us.
I know that the commander
will not lose...
She'll beat the program!
I do believe in miracles.
[DOC]
Hmph. Yes.
Oh, Commander...
[KOSEI, DUUZ panting]
[MEIFON]
My name is...
...Meifon Li...
I am... I am...
[screeches]
[FEMALE ANDROID 1 laughs]
[FEMALE ANDROID 3 laughs]
[KOSEI]
Huh?
[FEMALE ANDROIDS laughing]
[hisses]
Go ahead of me.
[KOSEI]
Huh?
You are simply no match
for these gals!
[FEMALE ANDROIDS laughing]
[DUUZ growls]
[KOSEI grunts]
[DUUZ]
Kosei!
Get to Meifon, quick!
[KOSEI]
Huh?
[FEMALE ANDROID 5 groans]
Go witness the destiny she's
about to carve out for herself!
I will!
[ALL FEMALE ANDROIDS laughing]
Why, this is...
[gasps]
[LEON laughs]
[MEIFON]
From within me...
...I am ceasing to be myself.
[LEON]
Come to me, Meifon.
[MEIFON gasps]
[MEIFON]
Goryu!
[MEIFON growls]
[MEIFON]
Goryu!
[MEIFON gasps]
[music plays]
[VALERIA panting]
[MEIFON]
I know this place.
Why? I've never
been here before.
How strange... I feel so calm.
Ever since I walked in here
my body feels totally at ease.
[gasps]
Why this is...
[LEON laughs]
[growls]
Goryu!
[LEON]
Welcome home, Meifon.
So you have come to kill me just
as Chenho programmed you.
Don't be stupid!
I'm here of my own free will!
[LEON] Either way,
I'm so glad you've come.
I'm sure you have a special
fondness for this place, hm?
[gasps]
[LEON] Yes. This is
where you were born.
It is also the place where the
fates turned for Chenho and I.
[LEON] And so, that is why you
instinctively know this place.
[MEIFON grunts]
[LEON] Meifon, let's have
a nice long heart to heart.
There's nothing to talk about!
[screams]
Meifon, my love, you are simply
the most advanced bio-android
that I have ever heard of. Yes.
You are the ultimate
killing machine.
Let go!
Do you think I'd face you
without improving
--my odds of victory?
--Huh?
Normally, you would be
able to throw me off
of you with such ease.
However, while you are here,
in this place, you are
totally helpless in my arms.
[MEIFON]
Huh?!
[LEON]
You were born on this ship,
and a fragment of you
is super-human.
If you had free reign
of your power,
I'd never be able
to defend myself.
But I've discovered that your
power is controlled by a system
installed in your body
that deactivates while you
are on this ship.
And here, you are
not any stronger
than an ordinary young girl.
[MEIFON whimpers]
So you see,
you will finally be able to
escape from Chenho's program.
With all of its suffering
and the time limit he
put on your life. So,
Meifon, won't you please
stay with me now?
[FEMALE ANDROID 5 laughs]
[FEMALE ANDROIDS laughing]
[FEMALE ANDROID 6 groans]
Got girl trouble?
Thanks, Valeria.
[FEMALE ANDROIDS laugh]
Oh, Meifon...
I am the only one
who can accept you--
because we're two of a kind.
You and I, we have
both been reborn.
When I became Leon Lau,
I changed...
...every single part of my body.
I even changed both my
fingerprints and my corneas.
So Chenho searched long and hard
but he could never find me.
However, I just opened
a Pandora's box
with my own two hands,
didn't I dear Meifon?
I was able to fool
everyone on the surface...
But in the end,
you were able to
sense my DNA make-up
through our physical touch.
It acted as a trigger to awaken
you as a killing machine.
But, I have no regrets.
Even if it was a trap,
I am grateful to Chenho
for bringing the two
of us together.
And the feelings I had for
you then were sincere.
Here, we could both make a
future for ourselves together.
But Meifon.
You will not create my future!
You wanna use my data
to create killer androids,
and profit from it.
Fine then. You are right.
Liar!
Meifon!
[TAFFEI screeches]
[LEON grunts]
[MEIFON grunts]
Meifon!
Kosei...
[KOSEI sighs]
[LEON laughs]
--Huh?
--Stay back!
This is something that I alone
must bring to an end.
Meifon!
Duuz, Valeria!
[MEIFON growls]
[MEIFON groans]
Taffei!
Meifon, this is the end.
I beg that you reconsider.
I want us to be together!
I am my self!
And I will create my own future!
Your future is limited.
You only have a few days
left to live, you see.
Meifon. Let's see just how
badly you really want to
kill me. I will even
lend you the sword.
Let's see how far your
"own self" will take you.
Cut my head off,
rip out my heart.
Do what you want.
But, the moment you
cross over that red line
by even one step, a laser will
rip your body apart regardless
of my will or yours.
However, there's a minute chance
that your sword will
reach me before you die.
What do you think?
Do you want to try?
This is your last chance.
[MEIFON growls]
[LEON groans]
[KOSEI grunts]
[gasps] Goryu...
But I'm... Wh-- Uh. Why?!
I don't know.
I'm surprised at myself.
I guess I didn't want to lose
you for the third time.
[groans]
[LEON]
When I was reunited with you...
...I felt true joy... for the
first time in a long time.
In the past I-I betrayed Chenho,
killed Lifon with my own hands
and even you, an orphan.
Fearing revenge, I changed my
appearance, my name...
I still wanted to survive.
So I decided to live
a new life. Start over.
However... I was never
able to truly run away.
It was never supposed to happen,
from the very beginning.
And so this is... This is...
...the answer.
[MEIFON gasps]
Meifon... If you had never...
made your appearance...
...I would have...
remained... as Leon... Lau...
[MEIFON gasping]
[screams]
Hey, Meifon...
[MEIFON whimpers]
[MEIFON sobs]
[MEIFON cries]
[DUUZ, VALERIA gasp]
[KOSEI]
Huh?
[ANNE] The energy pressure
in the alien spaceship
is really building up!
[AIHARA] It's going to explode
at any moment!
[SERGE]
How... How can that be?!
[JAEGER]
Haven't they responded?!
[AIHARA]
No, not yet!
[JAEGER growls]
Commander!
[DUUZ grunts]
[AIHARA]
This is Angel Links !
Please respond! Commander!
Deputy Commander!
Tactical Officer!
Platoon Commander! Anybody!
[gasps]
[DOC]
It's... It's collapsing...
[AIHARA cries]
How can it be?
Hey, Aihara...
[AIHARA cries]
Oh!
[AIHARA] This... This is a
terrible way for it to end!
I can't accept it, I won't...
[KOSEI]
Angel Links ! Come in!
This is Kosei! Do you read?!
Deputy?
[CREW gasp]
[KOSEI] Do you read?!
Returning to ship!
Prepare to launch!
Everyone's safe!
And we have Meifon!
[CREW cheering]
[MEIFON]
Thank you... everyone.
Well, good morning, Yayoi.
Where am I?
[gasps]
Where has Meifon gone now?
She's gone far, far away, Yayoi.
"Far, far away"?
[KOSEI]
Yes, far away.
[YAYOI]
Oh...
[KOSEI]
She's finally attained it.
A future that is hers, alone.
[LADY] All right then,
I'll see you tomorrow.
[MEIFON]
Great! Thanks for taking me on.
Ooh! What do you think?
Here. Thanks for comin'.
This is one's on the house.
[gasps] Thank you!
[gasps] Ow!
[OLD LADY] Your stories are
always so fantastical!
I like the dragon that does
crossword puzzles.
Don't you find the company
of an old woman tedious?
No. I used to live
with my grandfather.
[OLD LADY]
He must have loved you.
Huh?!
After all, you turned out
to be such a wonderful girl.
Oh. Uh... Hm.
Yes!
[OLD LADY]
Well?
What story do you
have for me today?
Huh. Let's see...
It's about a young girl
who has a pet cat that
turns into a sword
and they go on a wild
space adventure!
[OLD LADY] When I'm
re-incarnated, I'd like to go
on an adventure like that.
What about you?
[MEIFON]
Huh?
[OLD LADY]
Hm?
If I'm re-incarnated,
I want to be...
[gasps] Oh...
...a free cat.
A wild, free cat that
can eat a lot!
[clock chimes]