The warp of a loom is like the flow of time.
It changes seasons,
dyes the sky anew.
The weft comprises a man's deeds,
their tread upon the earth,
the shift of their heart
and the morph weave the days together.
Weaving the story of their world
through the many long centuries of their life.
Maquia!
Leilia!
What are you doing down there?
We're never going to finish with you playing around.
Jump in, Maquia!
You can do it, just fly!
I... I can't.
You're scared.
It's all right. Better not to
get caught up in her mischief.
You're right.
That Leilia,
she will never learn.
Those that make a life of weaving this cloth,
far from the lands of man, have a name...
"the Clan of the Separated".
Is something the matter, Lady Racine?
Nothing.
Just you wait, next time you're going in, too.
Mother!
Welcome home.
Leilia you mustn't treat the cloth like that.
Sorry, Mama.
Now why exactly are you all wet?
Did you find any good flowers, Father?
Indeed, these will make a rich violet.
See you later! Bye, Maquia!
See ya later.
See you later.
A tear.
Why are you crying, little one?
Because I'm alone.
Alone?
Even with me beside you?
No, elder, that's not what I...
You always were quick to tears.
Maquia, do you know why we call
ourselves "the Clan of the Separated"?
Hmm?
To outsiders, we are but fairytales,
we are longer lived than any other race,
but despite that fact, we
seemingly remain eternally youthful.
Only a few centuries past, an existence
such as ours would be commonplace,
there was a clan that unfurled wings like a bird's,
there were flowers that would sing at daybreak,
leviathans would carry cargo across the seas.
But now, all of that magic,
that wonder, has departed the world.
That is why the Separated must
always weave the Hibial cloth.
You will never be alone here.
Memories dwindle and fade with the passing of years,
the Hibial will always remember.
The people who enter and depart our lives,
they weep within its fabric with you.
They are weeping with me?
Maquia...
if ever you must leave the lorph behind...
Huh?
...if you should ever meet someone from the outside,
you must never fall in love.
For if you fall to love, you'll be truly alone.
Oh, but if ll meet someone,
then how could I be left alone?
Such is our fate,
why we must always remain the Clan of the Separated.
Goodnight, elder.
Sleep well, Maquia.
And be sure not to forget to weave your Hibial for today.
Of course.
Oh...
They're blooming.
Maquia?
The Renato!
Mezarte's attacking?
Maquia, get the elder quickly!
Elder Racine?
Elder Racine!
Elder?!
Anybody!
The Renato are attacking! Protect the Hibial!
It looks like the rumors are true.
They really do look like children.
Yeah, this must look great to a deviant like you.
Silence.
Commander Izol.
Who leads this village?
You're the elder?
It is an honor to meet you.
You may look like a young girl, but I know what you are.
The stories say you are a monster over 400 years old.
You will find no monsters here, Commander, only weavers,
who bind the cloth of days.
Such is our fate and I shall not permit you...
I am afraid you have no choice in the matter.
It is by order of the king you shall
accompany me to the palace of Mezarte.
You won't lay a hand on Lady Racine.
Take the women!
You have your orders!
Kill any that try to resist!
Forget the Renato, the lorph are all that matter!
Let me out!
Please, let me out!
Maquia!
No!
Jump in, Maquia!
You can do it, just fly!
A baby?
You know what I love about tear liquor?
It's got that extra salty kick to it.
Huh?
You were that girl with the elder.
You're Maquia, right?
I came to buy some Hibial but...
...that didn't work out.
This place was a drifter's settlement.
Got raided by bandits. This little guy was only hours old.
That's pretty amazing. I guess that's what mothers do.
Even in death, she tries to protect her child.
Well, leave the kid here.
They'll meet up again in heaven.
The Hibial of this child's life will end here,
little more than a frayed thread that was never woven in.
Better than being alone.
He's... he's really alone?
Oh, she's...
She's so strong.
Come on now, don't do that.
You're really going to take him with you?
He's not a toy.
I know he's not a toy.
He's my...
He's my Hibial.
A lone child meets another lone child,
and so they set off into the world.
Are you cold?
You smell funny.
You smell like the sun.
Maquia: When the Promised Flower Blooms
You'll never take me alive!
Get back here!
Lang, Deol, that's enough now.
You didn't watch your back, Lang!
Get back here!
I'm gonna get you!
Those boys just never listen.
Hm?
What's wrong, Anora?
Huh?
I don't understand.
What?
How do these... I don't know how these work.
I can't...
What a mess.
A child is not meant to raise another child.
Is that baby even yours?
They say you can't tell how old
lorphs are by how they look. Is he yours?
Hey, off with the both of you.
I'm-I'm 15.
But the baby, he's... I don't know.
What's his name?
I don't know.
Super weird and she's weird And the kid's weird
Leilia!
Leilia.
But that's a girl's name. He should have a boy's name.
Leili, Elli,
Elia...
Erial!
Huh?
Let go of me!
Well, I suppose that'll do.
She's a distant relative.
She knows how to weave.
Mmm...
There's a loom that's gone unused in the back of the shop.
She's welcome to that.
Take him outside.
She's an lorph, isn't she?
I never could trick you, Darel. I'm sorry.
Lorph cloth fetches quite a high price.
She'll end up making me a fair bit of coin.
Don't worry, I won't say a word.
Thank you, Darel.
However, you've taken in an lorph girl,
trouble will be finding you soon enough.
Maybe so, but no one can say
what the future will bring to us,
such is life, with or without her.
Here you are, this week's freshest.
Thank you as always, Mido.
Mm! Your cheese has the most wonderful flavor.
Oh, who's the new girl?
I'll be back next week, thanks so much.
Just a good, solid, cheesy taste, you know?
And the week after that. Farewell now.
You know, raising a child is never easy.
Even I couldn't do it alone.
You do understand that?
Mm.
My husband passed on some time ago,
killed by a Renato with the red eye.
I don't know.
There's nothing wrong with that.
I don't know what it means to be a mother.
I never...
had one.
Well, it's all about guts.
He's doing it!
He can walk!
Erial.
Erial's walking!
Erial can walk!
Whoo-hoo!
It looks like someone's become quite the mama.
Am I really a mother?
If you were a mother, I think you would know it.
Did you boys clean up the goat
barn or spend all day fooling around?
Lang, Mom's coming!
We gotta go. Come on run!
I'm sorry, Mom.
We meant to do it.
Oh, you will be sorry.
Ow.
Say "mommy", I know you can.
Sorry, you don't have to.
Mama.
Erial, did you just say...
Say it again.
Say it one more time.
Another Renato has been stricken with the red eye.
We shall put it down and
incinerate the body in quarantine,
then bury it deep beneath the earth.
Only five remain to us.
Oh, what fresh hell is this?
We need a cure and we need it now, my liege.
The strength of the Renato is the symbol of Mezarte,
it's the only force we can afford to deploy.
When the last of the Renato falls,
the other kingdoms will not hesitate.
Hmm... if they cannot be saved, we
will need a power to replace the Renato,
something of equal wonder and
might that will keep them at bay.
Yes, of course!
We have been granted the chosen blood.
It will keep us safe.
Commander, what of the lorph girl that you captured?
How does she fare as consort to Prince Hazel?
Tell me, please.
If you all have wings...
tell me, why you don't fly away?
You're afraid
you will wither and die here.
All the emotion you trap inside will burn away,
your heart will catch fire and you will burn to cinders.
Lady Leilia, the king has summoned you.
One moment more.
Lady Leilia, why are you drawn here?
It reminds me of the Hibial tower.
So it does.
It's done. Does it say anything?
Yeah, it says, "Anora, feel better soon."
Perfect!
You know, back where Mama was born,
we'd use cloth to say how we felt instead of using words.
Where were you born, Mom?
Is it the same place I was born?
Dida's mom says you're different from
everybody else, but I don't think so.
Where you were born, little Erial,
everybody would talk with their tummies
before the tickling bug would get them.
Tickle, tickle, tickle. Tickle, tickle, tickle.
But, Mom.
Then we'd fly away.
Anora!
Be gentle with him, OK?
Aren't you a lucky puppy?
Anora's been here ever since Mom and Dad got married.
That puppy is almost 90 years old in dog years.
Hey, Erial, why's your mom so weird?
Why's she always sneaking around the village?
She is not weird! My mommy.
I mean, my mom is...
She's just...
The baby can't talk.
And then he needs to run home to his mommy.
You're the one who's weird, Erial.
Huh?
Boy's aren't supposed to like their moms, stupid.
That's not true. You don't know.
Dita, I hate you!
I like my mom.
Oh, shut up, you.
I hate you! I hate you!
Hmm.
Wait, are you crying, Dita?
Hmm, impressive work.
Here, this month's pay.
Thank you so much, Darel.
Actually, I'd like you to take a look at something.
A customer of mine brought in some true Hibial, here.
Maquia?
"Held within the castle. And to be wed to-to the prince.”
It's beautiful.
Leilia!
Don't worry, Darel will look into it.
If anyone can get you on a ship, it's him.
Quiet, it's that Maquia girl.
Maybe it's for the best. For now at least.
What are you going to do with Erial?
Huh?
The journey won't be easy, ever
more so with a young child in tow.
Besides, you have more than a journey ahead.
You know I'd gladly watch over him.
Mom! Mommy!
Erial!
Don't dig too deep, OK?
Just in case Anora wants to come back and...
Dummy. You don't want wild animals to dig her up, right?
It's time.
I won't be able to see her in the ground.
You can see her anytime you come here.
But we won't be able to play together.
Tell her she's a good dog.
She died in peace without any pain.
And everybody is going to die, eventually.
Anora was born into a life where it
happens faster than it does for us.
Maquia!
I'll go after her.
Does... does everybody die?
Yes.
Even moms?
Maquia! Hey, please wait.
Erial.
Everyone, it's not fair.
You'll all have to...
You'll leave and I'll-I'll still be here.
Maquia...
I knew it would happen, I knew
it, but it's not fair, it's not.
It doesn't matter that it isn't fair.
Stop crying!
You'll be gone, too.
Come on, you are Erial's mother, aren't you?
Moms don't cry, you hear me?
My mom wouldn't.
So I know for sure that moms don't cry.
OK.
Don't cry.
I promise.
Me too.
Good night.
Sleep well.
Erial!
You tried to wait up for me.
Let's get you to bed, OK?
You're getting big now, Erial,
but you still smell like the sun.
I won't cry, OK?
I will always be your mother.
We will always be together.
I promise.
I'm really sorry, I didn't mean it. I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry about everything. I really didn't mean...
I'm really, really sorry and I wanna be friends again.
Um, Erial and his mom had to leave.
You're sure you don't wanna say goodbye?
I wanna see the ocean.
Erial, come back! You can't!
You told me you would be a good boy.
Come back and stay with Mom.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to...
Maquia, is that you?
Oh, I can hardly believe you're alive.
I never thought I'd see you again.
It was our blood.
Mezarte attacked to discover the secret of our long life,
that's why they came.
Stole Leilia.
Hey, Mom, who is he talking about?
You have him calling you his mother?
No, it's not like that, I just...
I'm not angry, you're not wrong to.
It's just hard to forget what the elder used to say.
I know, I haven't forgotten.
As long as you know, Maquia.
Items for sale.
There's going to be a parade,
a massive festival to celebrate the prince's wedding.
Two different processions, one
with the prince and one with Leilia,
will leave from separate palaces,
both of them crossing this bridge.
Here, we'll stage an attack on the prince and his Renato,
cause all the chaos we can, and when the guard
protecting Leilia weakens to support the prince,
we take Leilia back.
I wanna see the parade, too.
I'm sorry, sweetheart, maybe next time.
Mom, I wanna go home.
Erial.
You don't act like the mommy I know when we're here.
Erial, the tickle bugs are coming.
Tickle, tickle, tickle. Tickle, tickle, tickle.
People of Mezarte, today the blood of
the lorph is bonded to the royal family.
The Renato and the lorph,
these legends that endure unto our era,
can join their power with Mezarte!
We are the chosen people. Our dominion shall be infinite!
Today will be a day to remember with
the marriage of my son Prince Hazel
and the lorph Princess Leilia, a new
legend shall be born unto us, unto Mezarte!
That boy.
What's happening?
An assassin?
They tried to kill the prince.
Leilia. Leilia.
Hm?
Sorry, sir.
I've missed you.
Maquia, what are you doing here?
Not just me, Krim, too.
Krim is here in the city?
We came to save you.
Come on, everybody's waiting for...
Leilia?
I'm sorry, I can't just leave.
But why not?
I can't escape.
You can, you were the fastest of anybody.
You can just fly over these
castle walls and be gone, Leilia.
I can't... I can't see Krim again.
But then you...
Leilia, you...
Your Highness!
You have to run, Maquia, now!
But I... Leilia, no.
Go now, I'll be OK. After all, I can fly, right?
Hold fast!
My lady.
Get them.
Hold! If you lay a finger on her...
As you wish, my lady.
I can fly, I know it.
So, how big's the kid now?
He should be about six or seven, yeah?
So, how's the world treating ya?
You're one of us. You're an lorph.
Only about half.
Racine, the elder, there's a reason she made
it taboo for any lorph to leave the village.
She knew what would happen.
She knew the fate of those that are different.
Humans always play the same part,
first they stare, then they taunt.
One day, they hate, eventually, they Kill.
So, the Clan remains separated,
and always just out of step with the rhythms of the world.
Try to live an ordinary life.
Krim, you're hurt.
Would you take off the cloak for me?
What does it mean to be a child?
What?
What does it mean to be a mother?
I wonder if I even know.
At times, Mido would try to explain it.
She'd help me out so much,
sometimes I felt like a little sister,
but that's not quite it.
I know that I'm really happy
whenever Erial laughs or smiles
and when I look at him, everything
else in the world just falls away
and I just wanna hold him...
That makes no sense.
Erial will die long before you.
It's the truth.
Erial is going to leave you alone.
Don't make my mom cry!
Erial, no! He's just...
I'll make you cry.
Erial, please stop it.
Can you protect him?
Can you? When it really matters?
Huh?
We will stay in Mezarte, we will save Leilia.
You and your child will only get in the way.
I am sorry, Maquia, this is goodbye.
Are we gonna go home?
No, we're not going home.
But why not?
We are going somewhere new, just the two of us.
Somewhere brand new? You mean without
Mido or Lang or anybody from home?
I'm sorry, Erial,
I don't think you'll be able to see them again.
Well, as long as I'm with you, I'm OK.
Me too.
I'm happy, as long as I'm with you.
No chance, girlie. I know trouble when I see it.
Can't have you running off when
whatever trouble it is comes knocking.
Ohh!
Erial!
I'm so sorry!
You brat! You'd better run!
Don't come back!
Mom's gonna try a few more places, all right?
You wait at the inn for me.
Aww, I don't want to.
Please, Erial, will you wait?
I really can't thank you enough.
The bar does all its best business at night.
You'll probably be working pretty late.
You don't mind?
How late do you mean?
Got a problem?
Just, my son is... He's young.
I'd rather not leave him alone if I don't have to...
We just had another girl take off
with the same problem, you're too young.
You'd better think about this.
But you don't...
Don't what?
Tell me, you need to be a better
example than this to your child!
Go on then, I don't have any work for someone like you.
Welcome home, Mommy!
Hello, sweetie.
Mom, come here. Look! look!
I made you some Hibial.
Why'd you give me more to do?
Hm?
Why did you take all this out?
Because I wanted to show you what I made.
Can't you just listen to me for once, Erial!
Huh?
Always! You're always making problems.
If I don't work then we can't eat,
we cannot survive like this.
Mommy...
You make everything so hard.
Why, Erial?
The tickle bugs are coming.
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle.
I bought some dinner, come and eat.
Erial, wait!
I... I'm not a mother
I don't have a right to be.
I don't deserve it.
All this time, I've just been pretending.
Mido was always there to catch me.
You must never fall in love, for if
you do, then you shall truly be alone.
Truly alone.
Elder.
"My mommy".
My mommy.
Erial!
Erial, where are you?
Erial, please!
Mommy!
Erial!
I tricked you.
You thought I shed my skin, right?
You shed your skin.
I made you laugh.
Wha... Oh.
I got you!
Silly boy.
Mommy?
I wish... I wish that you could stay like this forever.
Nuh-uh.
If I don't get bigger, how will I protect you?
I didn't want you to cry.
Then I won't cry again.
After all, I'm a mom.
You promise me?
Uh-huh.
You promise, too. OK, Erial?
Yeah, I promise.
Mom, I'll always protect you.
Keep going, slowly now.
All right, order up! Maquia!
Coming!
And this one's on you, you're
paying me back for the other day.
It takes a lot of experience to get it perfect like this.
And that's why I told you, you had to cut it out.
I kinda thought it was all going to turn out OK.
Welcome, there's a table at the back.
Maquia, three kelbi, yeah?
Sure.
I'll take that, sweetie.
Right away.
I'll take another one, too.
Your sister's got quite a butt on her.
I never noticed.
The two of them hardly look alike at all, right?
Yeah, very suspicious how you just came out of nowhere.
Where'd you say you moved from again?
Huh?
Maybe you two ain't brother and sister at all,
just two crazy kids who went and eloped together.
Sorry for the wait.
Oh, yes!
Let me know if you need anything else.
Welcome.
Hmm...
They keep getting new recruits.
How many guards do they actually need on watch?
Iron's the most important resource we got.
Mezarte keeps making cannons and we keep getting fed,
wouldn't call it a terrible deal.
You don't think it's all a bit suspicious?
It's almost like they're just
waiting for another war to break out.
Do you think that idiot prince can command our military?
Not a chance.
It can get a tad raucous in here, sorry it's so loud.
Here's what we're serving from the kitchen today.
Maquia!
Lang, it's you!
I can't believe it's you!
You haven't aged a day, makes sense.
Well, what about you, Lang?
Look how tall you are, like you could touch the sun.
Come on, I'm not a stalk of wheat.
Erial! Hey, Erial!
Look up here! It's Lang! Lang is here!
Hey, Erial!
Huh?
Are you sure it's all right for me to be here?
Of course. Sorry about the mess.
Tell me more.
Are Mido and Deol doing well?
Yeah, except cities like Durell
are the only ones with an economy.
All the old rural areas are dying out.
Deol left as well. Ah, thank you.
Deol's looking for work too?
Well, can't live without it.
OK, I'm gonna take off.
Ha-ha, what's that? Got yourself a date tonight?
Sure, deep in the mines.
Be safe, OK? I'll see you later.
I'll make some dinner when you get back.
He got a job when we first arrived here,
and he works incredibly hard.
Of course.
And we can't just keep selling the Hibial.
Plus, because of me, it's hard
to stay in one place for too long.
I see. Makes sense.
So he finally realized you weren't bound by blood.
How'd he take it?
Five years ago,
he told me he didn't want me sleeping next to him anymore.
Not too long after, he stopped calling me "Mom", too.
"Hey"” or "Come here", that's it. That's all he says.
I did the same thing. It's just a phase.
Lang, have you heard anything about Leilia?
Another lost to the red eye.
Burn it to the bones. Bury it deep.
Scary.
There's nothing to fear, Princess Medomel.
Um, where's my father?
His Highness Prince Hazel is currently occupied.
And Mother?
What about your mother?
Sorry, it's nothing.
Hair the color of a dawning moon,
golden rings within the cornea,
and, allegedly, a low body temperature
are the signs of the lorph people.
I regret to say, Princess Medomel shows
almost none of these traits, Your Majesty.
So, if she won't live a long life or bear a
son, then why have I kept that monster in my home?
Hmm. I feel it will be difficult
for Leilia to produce another child.
Not to mention, Prince Hazel seems
to have grown tired of her as well.
Oh, my poor, beloved Hazel.
Do something! At least go find my son another woman.
My liege, we are currently seeking survivors of the lorph.
No doubt they will produce a better heir.
Enough!
Princess Leila!
If he has no desire to speak to me
until I'm weighed down with all this filth,
then just be rid of me!
Her Highness is...
I will speak with her alone.
Another Renato has died?
Yes.
I have been locked in this tower
since the day I gave birth to Medomel.
And I am never allowed to see either of them.
The same...
the Renato and I are the same.
We're vapors, things only meant
to exist and live in memory.
The clan that flew the skies,
flowers that sung at day break,
they were not meant for this world.
There must be a way to resist.
A way for the legends to survive the night.
To survive?
You dare say those words?
You murdered them.
My lady, I beg for your forgiveness.
You can burn!
Let me see my daughter!
Why can't I see her?
I brought her into this world.
I...
I've almost forgotten her scent.
How soft she was when I held her.
Izol, how much must you take
from me before you are satisfied?
You take everything and I am alone.
If you won't let me see Medomel, then bring me Maquia.
Please, bring me Maquia.
I...
I don't want to be alone anymore.
You never cleaned like this before.
It's been you and me for so long,
we've never had any company over before.
Hey, help me?
You've gotten so tall.
I guess so.
Maquia, I need to talk to you.
Will you have time when your shift is over?
Yeah, I think so.
I'll be around once you finish then.
Maquia, got an order coming up.
OK.
Man, I thought she was your girl, so I never made a move.
Same here.
Come on, lads, there's plenty of fish in the sea.
But why does that jerk get this fish?
She's not like that.
Oh... Yeah?
Hey, when life's got you down, you gotta drink up.
I'm not...
What you're not is a kid anymore.
He kept it down! Nice.
Now you gotta try the real stuff.
Down this and you're a real man, Erial.
Drink, drink, drink, drink, drink it down, drink it down,
burn and pound, burn and pound,
bottoms up and pound it down.
Erial, Erial, Erial, Erial!
The trick is keeping it down.
Fill it to the brim, lads! One more!
We'll make you a man yet.
You're sure they're looking for me?
We're gonna have to leave the city again.
Wanna come back to the farm with me?
But Lang...
It'll be perfect!
The price of goat milk has gone up.
You can bring Erial.
We'd just bring you trouble.
Maquia.
Lang, if something were to happen to
your mom or your brother, I just couldn't.
Maquia, I want you to be trouble.
Huh?
Ever since I was little, I
would do anything for you, Maquia.
Just think about it.
A future and...
being with me.
I can't do that. I'm so sorry.
Huh?
I spend every moment thinking about my Erial.
Thinking "How can we stay together?",
"How can I become a true mother to him?"
I've never been able to find answers to those questions.
And I don't see myself finding the answers anytime soon.
I've never had that kind of wisdom
but that's all I want,
forever, to think about my son.
I understand.
Listen, let me at least help you find a new home,
some place you and Erial can be safe.
You don't have to do this alone.
Huh?!
Erial?
Are you all right?
You smell like...
I'm home.
But you never drink!
Are you all right?
No welcome home kiss?
You always used to...
You used to always kiss me hello.
Erial, are you all right? Can you stand?
They thought...
everyone thought we had eloped together.
Huh?
And he thought Lang was gonna take you away.
What are you saying?
Erial, come on.
I'm gonna get you to bed and you can...
Be careful.
Don't step on that!
You...
you wove this Hibial for me.
I hate this.
Why do you still keep this thing around?
How long are you gonna treat me like a kid?!
You are always going to be my child.
That's something that will never change.
Erial!
I spoke to Lang and we have to find a new home.
Is there somewhere you want to go next?
I'm happy to go anywhere, as long as I'm with you.
Right.
I don't think I can be your son anymore.
I have a favor to ask.
Would you consider hiring me as a castle solider?
I need this, Lang.
Your mother's going to be sad.
She's not my mother.
Did you say that?
Huh?
Did you say that to her?
I may have.
How dare you?!
Maquia raised you since you were
nothing but an infant! Stop being a brat!
She worked every day, she was
no older than you are right now.
How could you?
You think I don't know that?!
Why does she care about me? Why did she stay with me?
Erial...
She's always with me.
She worked so hard for me.
I always thought that's what a mother does,
that's... that's why I called her my mother.
I wanna protect her.
But I can't, not like this.
I'm just...
I'm hurting her.
I need to protect her.
I'm just not strong enough.
If you cry like that, you're no
different from when you were a baby.
Are you sure you wanna do this?
It's OK, I can do it.
You were gonna leave too, right?
Right after I see you off to the castle.
I'll miss you. Be safe.
I'll see you soon.
Stop crying.
Moms don't cry.
He promised me.
Erial, you promised.
You said you would protect me.
You said...
Please don't go.
Aww, I thought we'd get to see a real Renato.
Sorry, sweetheart, there used
to be a whole flight of Renato,
but now there's only one still alive at the castle.
That's sad.
I really hope they don't expect that us marching behind
this ridiculous Renato doll will actually raise morale.
Hey, did you guys hear about Biaira?
They got themselves an lorph too.
Wait seriously? Like, for real?
Come on, Commander, what did the lice do to deserve that?
Shut it.
Division Commander Lang?
Hmm?
Yup, I heard it too.
Supposedly, it's a girl about
the same age as Princess Leilia.
That doesn't mean it's Maquia.
You worried?
No, she's strong.
Maquia would be so happy to hear that from you.
She was always so afraid she wasn't strong,
that she couldn't protect you.
She worked so hard to be a mother to you.
To be a mother you could always depend on.
She's still a child.
Yeah, maybe she is a child.
So this time...
this time I'll be a father to her.
Huh?
Mezarte has become nothing.
They defiled the ancient power they held.
Turning myths to nothing but tools for politics.
The nation of Biaira shall commit all we can to your aid.
Maquia, the time has come.
Your hair's gotten so long.
Back in the village, we were only permitted
hair past our waist if we had a child.
Come, Maquia, we're going to rescue Leilia.
Will there be war?
Only a moment of suffering for people like us.
Nothing to the pain you must have known these years.
Abandoning the lorph, wandering the world with nothing.
Lost and alone, as if you'd died alive.
So... you know how we feel, don't you?
The Clan of the Separated,
the elder must be long gone and passed into shadow.
Everything we have ever known has faded away.
And you, you left it all behind for your own world.
The lorph work as one, the lorph weave one cloth.
You and me and Leilia,
we cannot weave different histories.
Congratulations, Maquia, you're home,
we have severed the final thread.
We begin anew, weaving one future.
Dita!
Huh?
Erial, welcome home!
You're home pretty early today.
I'm sorry I'm so busy right when you need me the most.
Don't you worry, we still have plenty of time.
I know, but I still worry anyway.
I'll get dinner started.
No, no. I got it, you should be resting.
It's better if I move around a bit.
I'm fine. Sit down, sit down.
OK.
Do you think it's odd how we came together?
Sometimes.
I was looking for work. Came here to Mezarte.
Who could have imagined I'd meet you again?
And now...
Hey, Erial, was I truly the right one for you?
Hmm? What did you say?
Is it Biaira?
Not just Biaira, Hugh and Endora ships are with them.
Erial, wait!
Keep our child safe, I'll be back, I promise.
It's about damn time.
Sorry, sir.
Biairan soldiers have crossed the
mountains in an attempt to close off escape.
Split into two...
Was that...
Cannon fire?
How ironic.
Mezarte exploited ancient powers
as a show of unstoppable might
and now the nations that surround us have
forged alliances and furled condemnations,
all to tear down Mezarte's abuse of those ancient powers.
Where is my High Minister?
He's already fled the castle,
along with many of your retainers, Your Majesty.
Has he abandoned me in my time of need?
What must I endure?
It's all over, the kingdom falls.
Majesty, you have to move.
Go. I'll return and find Princess Medomel.
Silence, you fool, I have no daughter.
We don't need that monster!
Maquia, come on!
Erial!
My Leilia.
I found you.
Krim?
How are you?
You're alive?
No, it's not real.
You're a ghost.
I came to save you.
I swear to you,
I am going to make them suffer,
I'm going to make them pay for hurting you.
Then I'll wipe it all clean, everything.
Wait.
I want to see her first.
My daughter, please.
What are you saying?
They forced you to bear them a child.
You didn't want her, Leilia.
She, she is still my daughter.
Forget about her!
The name of that child forced upon you
will never be entwined in your Hibial.
That's not true.
I thought you were...
I thought everyone who cared for me...
you were dead.
Everything...
I thought I had lost everything.
She was the only thing that mattered.
My beautiful daughter.
All I could think of was holding her...
pressing her close to my chest and...
those thoughts were what kept me alive.
I had nothing else.
Leilia.
My angel...
Medomel.
I understand, I do.
Let's greet the dark.
Let's end it together.
Krim!
I will not...
...allow anyone...
...to harm our Hibial
ever again.
Krim?
Princess Leilia!
It never stops.
Leilia and Maquia.
But why?
Why does time always...
The same fires as that day.
Huh?
Erial.
Commander Lang.
Word came down,
there were two lorph aboard one of the Biairan ships.
You came upon them, didn't you?
Yes.
Just go, leave this to us.
Find Maquia...
I'm willing to fight, Commander!
You didn't join up out of loyalty to Mezarte, Erial.
You signed on just so you could get away from your mother.
That's not true!
Maybe that's why I joined up at first,
but now... now I have Dita and my friends.
I have a baby on the way.
Mezarte is the first home that I made,
the first home that was mine without my mother.
I want to protect that.
Hmm.
Are you all right?
It's you.
I'll get help.
Wait, no!
But I...
It's Erial's.
It's his child.
Fire!
Dita...
stay strong, almost there.
Soon you'll hold your baby.
Keep pushing, Dita!
Keep pushing.
That's right, Dita. Almost there.
Just a little further.
Dita!
Hold on!
It hurts!
Dita!
Please, make it end!
Dita, it'll be OK...
You have to save the baby.
Please, Maquia, please!
I will, Dita.
I swear it.
Someone is coming! Get out!
Your baby's coming.
You're so strong, Dita.
You and my Erial,
you're going to be parents soon.
You were wonderful, really... Mommy.
You're really going to take him with you?
He's not a toy.
I know he's not a toy.
He's my...
He's my Hibial.
Beautiful.
I see now.
Erial, it's time to come inside.
Mommy, I'm home.
Look at you, you're covered in snow.
Welcome home, my Erial.
Welcome home...
my Erial.
A dream.
No... I'm here.
But, Mom, the snow.
It's not snow, it's ash.
Dita gave birth during the invasion.
You'll hurt yourself.
It's OK, they're waiting for you.
And they'll keep waiting, you're a father now.
When your mother gave birth to you,
she must've gone through the same thing.
I remember her holding you,
holding you so tight
and you were so very small.
Her arms wrapped around you
as she protected you.
I could barely get you out,
I had to pull away one finger at a time.
That's enough.
I...
I wasn't able to be a mother to you, I'm sorry...
That's enough!
You've taught me everything, Mom.
To be kind
and strong
and brave.
You taught me what it means to love someone.
I tried to do all I could for you,
but you were the one who ended up caring for me.
When I first laid eyes on you that night,
I thought you would cry with me,
share my sorrow.
I thought that you would be my Hibial,
but then, every moment I spent with you,
all the sadness, all the pain,
it all went away.
Still, I...
I left, I failed you.
You could never, ever fail me, Erial.
Despite what you think, you did keep your promise to me.
You've been here,
protecting me this entire time.
Even alone, even if we were separated,
whenever I didn't know what to do with myself,
you were there, I would always think of you...
and everything was OK.
So if you call my name,
even if it isn't "Mom"...
whatever name you choose,
I swear to you, Erial,
that name will become mine.
You wove me together, Erial...
all that I am.
Maquia!
Lang!
Please, I need you to take Erial with you.
His wife and child are waiting for him.
It's time for him to go back home.
Don't go.
Please, don't go.
Please, Mom!
It's almost time to head down, Princess Medomel.
My father and the others?
Well, don't worry, it's quite all right.
When I reach the city,
it will be a completely new life that awaits me.
But, even so I...
Huh?
Who are you?
Princess Leilia.
Leilia...
you're my mother.
I am Leilia of the lorph.
I am wild, strong-willed.
I am reckless.
I am free.
I'll always be free.
Fly, Leilia!
I can fly, I can fly.
Mother!
Maquia?
Yes, you can fly too.
Goodbye!
Forget me, Medomel!
I promise I will, too.
I won't weave these years, my life in
the castle will never be in my Hibial!
My mother.
The long, long memories will fade away.
I will forget every moment,
because it will be just a tiny tear.
A tear.
Yes.
That's my mother.
I've never seen anyone so beautiful.
I'm sorry, Medomel.
Princess Leilia.
We don't need the Renato,
we don't need the lorph.
If the legends are so fated to fade away,
then let them live of their own accord up to the end.
Leilia, don't cry.
You're afraid, but I promise you will never forget.
That was so hard...
and it hurt so much.
But how is the world still beautiful?
I could never forget.
I made it home.
You're really here.
I promised I'd be back.
That's our baby.
Yeah.
She's softer than I could have imagined.
She's perfect. We need to choose a name.
Mm-hm.
Dita?
I'm so sorry.
When we were little kids,
you liked your mom and I said...
I said you were weird.
I'm so sorry.
I swear, I didn't mean it.
Your mom was so...
so beautiful and so kind.
She came and...
She was here and she...
I love you, Dita.
I love you too, Erial.
I was so foolish.
I used to be so jealous of her.
I wanted you to love me too.
My mother raised me to be the man I am,
just so I could love you.
And our daughter...
she'll love someone, too.
So we'll raise her, you and I,
we'll raise her well,
together,
so one day she'll know how to love,
just like us.
The Clan of the Separated.
You are destined to say many goodbyes,
to see so much that will change.
Time will march on, never ending.
You'll meet someone new, an endless stream of new faces.
You meet someone and you weave.
Hello, little one.
I'm here to see your grandfather.
Would you take me to him?
You know Grandpa?
Lily.
What are you doing out here?
Aren't you...?
Mom passed away a few years ago.
They really were a perfect couple.
After the fall of Mezarte,
Lang helped to move them back here.
It wasn't an easy life,
but I think they were incredibly happy.
Come on.
Just wait, it's coming.
They spoke of you all the time,
they were so happy together.
I'm glad you made it in time.
Father is, well...
I'm home.
Erial.
You did so well, my son.
Such a life.
You lived with all you had,
a truly wonderful life, my little boy.
But I won't cry.
I'm a mother and I promised you.
Huh?
Mom.
Welcome home.
I am home.
Hm.
I'll see you soon, my Erial.
Make sure you're home for dinner, OK?
These are for you.
Thank you.
Mom! Mommy!
Welcome home, Mommy. I know, I know.
Mommy, I'm home! Good morning, Mom.
I tricked you!?
You thought I shed my skin, right?
Is it the same place I was born?
But, Mom, time to start the party.
Dita's mom says you're different from
everybody else, but I don't think so.
'Cause I wanted to show you what I made.
Mommy, but why?
You don't act like the mommy I know when we're here.
I make you cry.
As long as I'm with you, I'm OK.
Mommy, I'll always protect you. Hey, Mom.
Even moms? Mommy.
Oh, hey there. See you soon.
It'll be fine, I promise.
I guess so. Don't worry about it.
I hate this. I'm home!
I don't think I can be your son anymore.
You think I don't know that?
I wanna protect her, but I can't, not like this.
I'm just not strong enough.
Why does she care about me? Why does she stay with me?
You've taught me everything, Mom.
Please, don't go.
Please, Mom!
I'm sorry, Erial.
Mommy?
I'm sorry.
Then I won't cry again, after all, I'm a mom.
You promise me?
Your mother has to...
...break her promise.
Mom!
I love you so much!
I love you!
Erial.
My Erial.
Done already?
No.
As long as I'm alive,
Erial's Hibial will still be woven.
It's not funny.
It's just the elder would laugh
if she saw your face right now.
And you know why?
She'd be happy to have taught you
that leaving someone isn't all sad.
Hop on, let's go.
Time to meet the next person you'll have to leave.
Elder...
I am happy that I met him.
I'm happy to have been his mother.
I am happy that I loved him.