[CARTA]
I am truly sorry, Lord Iznario.
I know failure is unacceptable
for a member of the Seven Stars.
Well, you needn't
apologize to me.
But I wonder. What would
your father think?
Carta, your actions have
tarnished the Issue family name.
[gasps]
[IZNARIO] But having taken the
place of your ailing father
and agreeing to
become your guardian,
I cannot simply sit
back and watch.
[IZNARIO] So I shall give you
a chance to redeem yourself.
[gasps]
Which is...?
[IZNARIO]
Makanai...
[CARTA grunts]
[IZNARIO] I've received word
that he's headed for Edmonton
with some group calling
themselves Tekkadan.
We must stop him,
no matter what it takes,
in the name of Gjallarhorn.
[CARTA] Lord Iznario. Please
give me this opportunity.
I'll crush Makanai's plans and
destroy every last one of them.
You have my word.
[IZNARIO]
Actually...
[gasps]
[IZNARIO] I felt it was
too heavy a burden
so soon after your defeat.
But McGillis insisted
you should carry it out.
[CARTA]
I-Is that so?
He's been tracking their
movements for some time,
and will provide you
with more details soon.
[CARTA grunts]
[CARTA gasps]
It's been quite a while,
hasn't it, Carta.
I must say I'm surprised.
Never thought that
you'd want to help me.
I do appreciate this, McGillis.
You're perfect for the mission.
Stop it! You know
damn you've come just
so you can laugh
and call me a failure.
That little patronizing smirk
of yours never changes,
even after all these years.
It's funny. I noticed
you haven't changed, either.
The only daughter of the Seven
Stars most powerful family.
So strong, so beautiful...
Enough. How dare you say--
[MCGILLIS]
Carta.
From the first day that we met,
I knew that you would always be
somebody I looked up to.
[gasps]
[CARTA]
McGillis...
[CARTA pants] So, this is
where you've been, huh?
I came over so you
can play with us.
How's it goin?
[CARTA] I lost the last time,
but it won't happen again.
Let's see who can
climb these trees fa--
[SERVANT A]
Miss Carta!
Please! You children shouldn't
be doing such dangerous things.
Besides, that young man
may be a Farheed by name,
but he's really a...
[CARTA]
A what?
Well...
[CARTA gasps]
[CARTA]
You're just gonna run away?
[MCGILLIS] Look, uh...
I think I'd better go now.
You should play
with someone else.
Why's that?
[gasps]
[MCGILLIS]
Hm?
Have a little confidence.
[MCGILLIS]
Huh?
[CARTA] I mean, you can climb
all the trees out here
in half the time it
takes me to do it.
And you learned to read
faster than anybody
that I've ever seen.
You even eat fast.
It's pretty cool!
[CARTA] Anyway, stop moping
around and pitying yourself.
'Cause it's getting
really annoying.
[MCGILLIS]
You never minced words
or looked down your nose at me
the way so many others did.
When I was with you,
I felt like an equal.
It's fine, you can spare
me the gratitude.
In my eyes, you were always
confident, always so noble.
And I can't bear the thought
of your feeling disgraced.
Which is why I want
you to let me help
in any way I
possibly can, Carta.
M-McGillis,
♪
[SHINO]
Just look at that.
It's pure white.
So cold out there,
you can see your breath.
[SHINO] Yeah, but since
we've been here,
I can hardly even feel it.
'Cause lately, I'm only
gettin' warmed up.
So they better
be ready to fight.
We're coming to you from
Parliament in Edmonton.
With the election deciding
Arbrau's new prime minister
approaching in only one week,
Togonosuke Makanai is
rumored to be running again.
[MAKANAI] Mm. Seems the
word's gotten out.
Yes. Mr. Alesi's really
been working hard.
It's quite impressive.
[ALESI]
It's been too long.
So good to finally meet
with you in person, again.
And of course, I'm always
happy to be of service.
But I wish I could escort you to
the Parliament Hall, myself.
[MAKANAI]
Nonsense, Lasker.
If the two of us were together
and headed in that direction,
we'd play right into
Gjallarhorn's hands.
As I said, I need you
to get there earlier
and lobby for me till
the election starts.
Well, with all the political
enemies Henri Fleurs created
over the years,
that should be no problem.
So it looks like all you're
gonna have to do now
is make it out there in time.
I'm sure I will. These young
men seem up to the task.
[ALESI]
I was worried, at first.
When you told me the
soldiers taking you were
basically children,
I just couldn't believe it.
But I can see the
determination in their eyes.
[TROW]
This is a battle for revenge.
[ALESI]
Huh? What did he say?
[MAKANAI]
A catchy slogan, isn't it?
"This is a battle for revenge".
I don't understand, sir.
It seems to me that people
are always looking
for some sort of excuse.
But those kids have one desire;
destruction itself.
[AIDE A]
I-I see...
[ORGA]
How's it lookin', Old Man?
Well, so far, the five
machines we brought with us
are all ready. And, uh...
[MERRIBIT] They're working
on the 20 units we bought in
Anchorage through Teiwaz,
right now.
[YUKINOJO] Those're newer
models than we're used to,
but none of em' came with
Alaya-Vinyana Systems,
so I'm not too sure how
effective they're gonna be.
Still. It sounds
better than nuthin'.
From what I've been told,
Earth has rules against
bringing Ahab Reactors
into urban areas.
So if we're not allowed to
use Mobile Suits out here,
then I guess were just
gonna have to get by
on the vehicles we've got.
[MERRIBIT] Are you going to
have the younger children
fighting in those things, too?
[ORGA] Hell of a lot better than
facing the enemy unarmed.
[MERRIBIT]
Hold on, Boss.
[ORGA exhales]
Yeah, what?
It seems like Biscuit's death
has driven you all crazy.
Your point is?
The members of Tekkadan
are really sweet kids.
But at this rate, they may
never be able to return.
Oh yeah? To where?
[gasps] I-I uh...
P-Please, Boss...
At least, promise me
you aren't going to drag
the little children
into this, too!
[TAKAKI]
Ms. Merribit.
[MERRIBIT]
Uh?
Hey, you two.
W-What's wrong?
[RIDE] That's enough. You should
just stay out of this.
Huh?
[TAKAKI]
Believe me.
Nobody here's getting
dragged into anything.
Every choice that we've made
so far has been our own.
[MERRIBIT] I understand that,
but... I just think...
It might be difficult for you
all to see any other options,
right now.
You've been so
blinded by this situa--
If they don't pay for
what they've done,
we couldn't live
with ourselves.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[GAELIO] Seriously?
Ein's regained consciousness?
[ENGINEER-A] Yes, sir. We were
waiting for you. This way...
[GAELIO] Why are
we stopping? Where is he?
[EIN]
Specialist Major Bauduin.
[gasps]
Wait! It can't be! Is that you?
[EIN]
Yes, sir.
[GAELIO gasps]
Ein...
[sighs] So it was a success.
That's Wonderful.
I'm glad. Really...
[ENGINEER A] Please.
Have a look, Specialist Major.
[GAELIO]
Hm?
[ENGINEER A] This is the
Second Lieutenant, now.
[gasps]
[ENGINEER A] The Alaya-Vinyana
integrated perfectly.
[EIN] Thank you so much
for what you've done.
Now I'll finally be able
to avenge Lieutenant Crank.
[GAELIO]
I see.
[EIN]
Throughout my entire life,
I've only met two people
who've earned my respect.
I don't think I've
ever been so happy.
I'll be indebted to you
till I take my last breath
for this gift you've given me.
[GAELIO]
Of course... Ein.
[MCGILLIS]
That was his greatest wish.
As his senior officer,
you were able to offer him the
opportunity to fully realize it.
All that's left now, is for
you to assist him by
setting the stage and taking
him to face the enemy.
Gaelio. With Gjallarhorn in
such a dark state of corruption,
It's truly a wonder
that your heart
has managed to remain so pure.
You're mocking me now,
is that it?
[MCGILLIS]
I'm serious.
And not just you. Ein as well.
I sincerely believe that the
two of you have what it takes
to utterly reform
that organization.
Even Ein, huh?
Indeed. If this mission
proves successful,
his contribution to Gjallarhorn
will be quite immeasurable.
And regardless of
his appearance,
the battle he's about to
enter could make him a hero.
[GAELIO exhales]
[GAELIO] Thanks so much.
I appreciate this
[MCGILLIS]
Gaelio... Carta...
You were always
dear friends to me.
I never lied to
you about that.
And I believe the two of you
will change Gjallarhorn forever.
[ORGA]
I dunno, Mika.
I'm startin' to think
I really am losin' it.
[MIKAZUKI]
How come?
Tellin' all you guys we're
fightin' to get our revenge,
putting everybody's
lives in danger...
This is exactly the reason why
Biscuit said he wanted to quit.
That night. He talked
to me about that.
[gasps]
[ORGA]
He did?
[MIKAZUKI]
Hey, Biscuit.
[BISCUIT]
Uh... Mikazuki?
Gjallarhorn's on their
way to the island
[BISCUIT]
Are you serious?!
Yeah. I'm gonna need
you to follow me.
Orga's making a plan
and he wants you there.
Uh... You sure?
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
Well, yeah.
Did Something happen?
[BISCUIT]
Uh... You could say that.
We argued about what
we're gonna do next.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
Mikazuki, I'm not gonna quit.
[MIKAZUKI]
W-What are you talkin' about?
[BISCUIT]
Oh... it's Nothing.
Biscuit. Are you sayin'
that you wanted to leave?
[BISCUIT]
No... Well, uh, maybe.
Guess I was just afraid.
Orga makes the decisions.
And he has led us this far,
but I started to realize
that he's only giving us
what we've been wishing for.
That's why I'm not gonna leave.
I'm staying right here.
Only way I'll go, is if
we all head home together.
[grunts]
Hey, uh, it's my turn
to be on lookout now.
[ORGA] If we can all
go home together, huh?
Well, in that case...
...there's no way that any
of us can go back now.
Biscuit...
[LAFTER] Mikazuki? Are you
ready to switch off again?
On my way.
--[gasps] What's that?
--[radar beeps]
[gasps]
An Ahab Wave?
[ELITE GUARD A]
We now have visual contact
with their freight train.
Listen up. Retreating is not
an option, do you understand me?
[ELITE GUARDS]
Yes, ma'am.
[CARTA] What doesn't kill you
only makes you stronger!
And no matter what happens,
they won't take my dignity.
I promise, McGills.
We won't leave here
untill we are victorious.
Our fleet's reputation
is at stake.
[CARTA] That's right. So let's
show them what we can do.
Hey Boss, we've got three
Mobile Suits dead ahead.
They look like the
ones from the island.
[SHINO sniffs]
Aww, man!
I was just in the middle
of an awesome dream, too.
[AKIHIRO] What? I can barely
sleep ridin' in this thing.
Dammit!
[MAKANAI] But I was assured we
were traveling on a safe route
that Gjallarhorn's surveillance
wouldn't be able to detect.
[KUDELIA] It doesn't make sense.
How did they find us so quickly?
There's only one person I know
who could've tipped them off.
[gasps]
[ORGA]
I can't believe he stabbed us
in the back like that.
So you're saying you
have somebody in mind?
Yeah. But we'll talk later.
Yamagi, stop the train!
[YAMAGI]
All right!
[ORGA grunts]
Sure there's only three of 'em?
[YAMAGI]
Yeah, at least so far.
[YUKINOJO] Mikazuki. Make sure
Barbatos is ready to launch.
Got it?
Yeah.
[gasps]
Is that her?
No way.
[CARTA]
I represent Gjallarhorn's
Earth Headquarters.
I'm commander of the Outer Earth
Orbit Regulatory Joint Fleet,
Carta Issue.
I challenge you to
a duel, Tekkadan!
Three of our Mobile Suits
against three of yours!
[SHINO] Hang on a minute.
You ee that red cloth?
It's a challenge.
[CARTA] ...hand over
Togonosuke Makanai
and Kudelia Aina
Bernstein immediately...
[ATRA] Who are those people?
What's that woman talking about?
[CARTA]
And of course,
all members of Tekkadan shall
surrender themselves to us.
If we're vanquished, however,
you may continue to pass,
as you wish.
Well, it sounds
pretty good to me.
Are you ready to show 'em
what we can do, Akihiro?
[AKIHIRO]
Yeah.
[AZEE] Forget about it, guys.
Now don't even waste your time.
[LAFTER]
That's right.
I mean, we have 'em
totally outnumbered.
So why don't we go out there
and beat 'em senseless!
Thirty minutes.
That's what we'll give you
to choose your best fighters
and prepare for combat.
As soon as you're ready, you--
[gasps]
How dare you!
Lady Carta wasn't finished
speaking yet you bastard!
[ELITE GUARD B shouts]
Mikazuki...
[ORGA grunts]
What are you doin', Mika?
Unbelievable. Ma'am, we're
gonna need to regroup and...
[yells]
That's brutal.
Great. Thanks a lot, Mikazuki.
Now there's no one
left for us to fight.
[ELITE GUARD A] Dammit! I can
still take out the track.
What?
How despicable. Look what you've
done to my proud elite guards!
[gasps]
[groans]
So gross...
I've never seen
anything like this.
[MAKANAI]
It seems perfectly fine to me.
But staying out
here in the snow
can take quite a toll on
an old body like mine.
So the sooner this
is over, the better.
We really need to
get moving along.
[CARTA grunts]
So you like to
fight dirty, huh?
I don't approve!
Boss, have you seen
what he's doing?
[ORGA]
Just like I told ya.
We're gonna crush anyone
who gets in our way.
[gasps]
[ORGA]
Aren't we, Mika?
[grunts]
[ATRA screams]
[TEKKADAN BOY]
Awesome!
[TEKKADAN BOYS chatter]
Those kids.
[yells]
[CARTA] I'd been waiting
for this battle...
[CARTA grunts]
...but I wanted to
confront the enemy fairly!
Otherwise, it would
be dishonorable!
My name is Carta Issue!
[MIKAZUKI] I don't care
who the hell you are.
[grunts]
[MIKAZUKI] Cause right now,
you're my enemy.
That's all that matters.
[MERRIBIT grunts]
You guys, it's dangerous
out here. Head inside.
I must win.
There's no other option.
I ruined my reputation
and humiliated my family.
[shouts]
The little girl he
once looked up to
shouldn't have to feel like
such an insignificant fool!
[CARTA shouts]
[MERRIBIT]
Get in the train, everyone!
You could get hurt!
[TAKAKI]
You have to stop this.
We're not leaving.
We've gotta see this ourselves.
Right.
[gasps]
We need to look at our enemy.
And watch what Mikazuki does.
[MERRIBIT]
W-What?
He's right.
We're stayin' right here till
we know he brought her down.
'Cause this is our revenge.
For Biscuit and every
friend we've lost.
[sobs]
[CARTA] I can't. I can't
afford to lose. Not now.
He believes in me...
and I can't betray him.
I won't let it end here!
[CARTA yells]
[MIKAZUKI]
You're not gonna escape.
[grunts]
I've got to win this.
I'm not afraid of anything!
If I don't kill you right now,
you'll only get
in our way again.
[CARTA] I won't be disgraced
for a second time.
[MIKAZUKI]
But more than that,
I can't forgive
what you did to us.
[CARTA]
I won't...
[CARTA gasps]
[CARTA]
Help me... Please... McGillis.
[LAFTER] Hold on!
Another Ahab Wave reaction?
[gasps]
Mikazuki!
[grunts]
Reinforcements?
[gasps]
You're goin' down.
[ORGA]
Wait, Mika. Come back.
Orga?
[ORGA] There's no time
to chase 'em down.
We need to get out of
here while we can.
[MERRIBIT gasps]
We have no place to go back to.
But now, we do have
a destination.
And I swear...
...we'll get there together.
[gasps]
[sniffs]
[grunts]
[MAKANAI]
Hm...
[MERRIBIT exhales]
[CARTA pants]
McGillis...
You came all this
way to rescue me.
Didn't you?
[GAELIO sniffs]
Yes. That's right.
[gasps]
I failed...
I failed again, didn't I?
[GAELIO] No. That's not true.
You fought honorably, Carta.
[CARTA gasps]
[GAELIO] When we get back,
things'll be better.
Don't worry.
[CARTA]
Really?
Thank... you...
...McGillis.
[gasps, sobs]
[GAELIO] It's all right, Carta.
Get some rest.
[grunts]
[GAELIO] We'll take care
of everything from here.
[train whitsles]
I think we made it.
[ORGA]
We're here, Mika.
And so are they.
♪
[MIKAZUKI] Till now, I never
really thought about who's
with us and who's against us.
I just followed the orders that
Orga gave me and fought
anybody he needed me to.
But from this point on,
it's different.
Anyone who tries to get in
Tekkadan's way is my enemy...
...and they're gonna go down.
Next time on Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
Episode 24
"A Future Reward."