[breathes deeply]
So, what do you want
me to do next, Orga?
[chuckles]
[ORGA]
All right, Mika.
[gasps]
[ORGA]
I've got a job for you.
One that no one
else here can do.
[YAMAGI]
Right!
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
I'm here, Old Man.
[YUKINOJO]
Hey, there you are...
[MIKAZUKI gasps]
--What's going on?
--[YUKINOJO] Yamagi take over.
[YAMAGI]
I'm on it.
[power tools humming]
[MIKAZUKI] What're you
gonna do with this?
[YUKINOJO] Maruba kept
it stored back here,
hopin' that one day he could
sell it for some cash.
There was no need for the
area around the cockpit,
so it was all
taken out years ago.
We're gonna fill it
in with this, instead.
So are you sure this'll
work in that thing?
[YUKINOJO] Yeah. We'll use the
system that's already in place.
Here, you should read this.
[gasps]
Oh. That's right...
All we need is the interface
from the Alaya-Vijnana.
These Mobile Suits
from the Calamity War
should be compatible--
[KUDELIA]
Alaya-Vijnana...
[YUKINOJO]
Hm?
[KUDELIA] That system uses
special nanomachines,
and can only fuse with
children because they haven't
finished growing. It's highly
dangerous and some have--
[YUKINOJO] Once those
nanomachines go into the body,
they create a
kind of "brain lobe"
that controls spatial awareness.
Then, through that, it connects
to an external device,
making a system that allows
the brain to directly
process all of the
Mobile Suit data.
[MIKAZUKI]
Got it.
Okay.
And if we didn't have it, a kid
like him with no education,
could never operate this thing.
You mean...
Look, Mikazuki, the feedback
from a Mobile Suit is
a whole lot different
than a Mobile Worker's.
It could damage your
cerebral nerves.
It's all right. I mean,
I never use 'em much anyway.
C'mon, now...
[KUDELIA]
How could you?
How could you say
something like that?
I mean, doesn't your own
life matter to you at all?
[MIKAZUKI]
'Course my life matters to me.
[YUKINOJO grunts]
But not just mine. Everyone's.
[gasps]
[KUDELIA]
That's not what I meant.
[YUKINOJO]
Seems all right.
How's that?
Good. Feels fine.
[YUKINOJO]
I'll start it up.
[MIKAZUKI gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
How do you read this?
[YUKINOJO] Huh?
Uh, Gundam Frame Type B-Bar?
Baro? What?
[gasps, shouts]
[YUKINOJO gasps]
Hey, Mikazuki!
[BISCUIT]
Old Man! Are you ready?
We can't hold 'em, anymore!
[YUKINOJO] Just hang on.
I think he's in trouble up here!
[BISCUIT]
What's wrong?
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
Barbatos...
[YUKINOJO]
Huh?
[MIKAZUKI]
That word from before.
It's this one's name.
[YUKINOJO] Hey, man.
You feelin' all right?
Yeah. So let's hurry.
[YUKINOJO gasps]
In that case...
He's ready! Yamagi, lift it up!
[YAMAGI]
Done!
[BISCUIT] Yamagi. You should
bring him out on Number 3.
[YAMAGI] What?! The exit's
completely blocked that way!
[BISCUIT] Yeah, but it's
closest to the battlefield.
Begin retinal projection.
[YUKINOJO]
Okay!
Tell me. You think he can win?
Maybe?
[KUDELIA]
Huh?
[BISCUIT]
We're outta options.
Our only chance now, is to
fight with all we've got.
[KUDELIA grunts]
[MIKAZUKI]
Let's go, Barbatos.
♪
[SHINO]
Oh, man!
He really took
that thing down!
Unbelievable!
[EUGENE]
Mikazuki's in there?
[EIN]
Wait. It can't be!
Captain Orlis has...
We were never told anything
about Mobile Suits
being out here.
[CRANK]
Orlis...
[EIN]
Lieutenant!
[CRANK]
Ein! Cover me!
Yes, sir!
[EUGENE gasps]
Here they come again.
[MIKAZUKI]
Orga, order them to fall back.
[ORGA]
You got it!
[CRANK]
You're not getting away!
[grunts]
What's this?
[EIN]
I'll stop him right here, sir.
[CRANK]
Wait, hold your fire!
[gasps]
[EIN]
Hold on!
Are those retreating Mobile
Workers from our side?
Just try and shoot me now.
[grunts]
[EIN]
Come on!
Only a coward would try to
bring down Mobile Workers!
Seriously? Look who's talkin'.
[CRANK]
Hold it, Ein. Wait for me!
He's mine.
Even without a rifle,
I know I can take him down.
[EIN grunts]
Did he just throw his weapon?
[gasps]
Where'd he go?
Did I get him?
[gasps]
[CRANK] I don't know
where you got that thing,
but do you really believe
you can take down a
Graze of Gjallarhorn with an
old Mobile Suit like that?
[MIKAZUKI] Yeah. Well, so far,
one of you is already dead.
[CRANK]
That voice...
It can't be!
Are you... only a child?
[MIKAZUKI]
That's right...
So was every soldier
you killed out here.
Remember that.
[CRANK grunts]
How is this happening?
[MIKAZUKI] We're gonna be the
same ones who take you out!
[EIN]
Lieutenant!
[CRANK, MIKAZUKI gasp]
[EIN]
Dammit
Amazing reaction speed.
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
Am I outta gas?
[YUKINOJO yells]
You okay?
He's in trouble, Yamagi.
I forgot to refuel the
Mobile Suit's thrusters.
Huh?
[YUKINOJO]
This is bad!
[YAMAGI]
Is he gonna be all right?
[YUKINOJO] Oh, man. I was too
busy startin' it up to remember.
Wonder how much longer he's got?
At this range,
I can still take aim.
[Crank]
Under you!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[CRANK]
You all right?
Yes, sir. But I...
[CRANK]
Good. We need to fall back.
[gasps]
[EIN]
What do you mean?
Looks like his thrusters
are malfunctioning.
The remaining Mobile Workers are
safe and have cleared the area.
It's time to retreat.
[MIKAZUKI]
I'm not done.
[EIN]
But why, sir?
[CRANK]
You heard me!
[gasps, grunts]
[MIKAZUKI]
I'm not done yet.
[grunts]
I'm not...
[HAEDA growls]
[ORGA grunts]
[engine rummbles]
[ATRA] Something's not right.
Is everything okay?
[COOKIE, CRACKER]
Hey! Hey!
[ATRA gasps]
[COOKIE, CRACKER]
Hey!
Now stop! You're speeding up.
You gotta slow down!
[COOKIE, CRACKER yelp]
[CORAL]
You what? How could you fail me?
And, there's more, sir.
Captain Orlis died in battle.
We lost a third of our
soldiers as well as a Graze.
Our only choice was to retreat.
[CORAL]
Don't give me that!
How could this happen?
I wanted the leader of the
Martian independence movement
to be destroyed on that base.
Kudelia Aina Berstein
should've never
made it out alive.
With her gone forever,
it would've caused an
upheaval on Mars and only
strengthened their hatred
toward the people of Earth.
It would've worked perfectly!
[CORAL] Now, we'll never get
any funding from Nobliss.
And if we lost a Mobile
Suit out there, too...
When is Specialist Major
Fareed due to arrive here?
Sir, two days.
All right By the time he's here,
I want Kudelia captured.
All evidence of the battle is to
be erased. I want them all dead!
[CRANK]
But, sir...
What?
[CRANK]
We were fighting...
...against children.
[CORAL]
Children?
So you went out there and
allowed some little punks
to defeat you?
[CRANK]
Did you hear me?!
I can't, in good conscience,
fight soldiers who're so young.
Especially when I know they're
fighting against their will.
You need to man up! Who cares
how old the fighters are?
I'm giving you a direct order.
Exterminate them.
Failure is not an option.
Do you hear me?
[grunts]
[SOLDIERS chattering]
Yeah, that's it!
Good! Keep going...
[SOLDIER B]
Hey! Just a little higher.
[CORPSMAN B ] Some of them
might be buried down underneath.
Try and be careful.
--[SOLDIER E] Dammit!
--[SOLDIER F] Does it hurt?
[SHINO]
No... This can't be.
[CHAD]
Yeah, I'm sure.
This is all that's left of
his Alaya-Vijnana System.
[SHINO] Danji. We used
to talk about this.
You always said
you wanted to die
smothered between huge boobs.
They'd be really soft, you know?
Not rock hard like this
old busted cockpit.
Hey, Danji. Answer me...
[AKIHIRO] Hey. It looks like the
First Corps survivors are back.
[ORGA exhales]
[HAEDA] Dammit. Where have
all those space rats gone?
Hurry up, guys. Just bring
them all out here.
[SOLDIERS]
Yes sir.
[SASAI]
Haeda. What're we gonna do now?
We're all being targeted
by Gjallarjhorn. Maruba's gone!
Look, I don't know.
Let's take what we can,
then get the hell outta here.
I'd better come up with
my next move, quick.
[CRACKER] Hurry and get
my brother. Now let's go!
[ATRA]
I came down to make delivery.
So where are all the usual
people who work around here?
[BISCUIT]
Cookie! Cracker!
--[CRACKER] It's Big Bro!
--[COOKIE] Brother!
[BOTH whimper]
[BISCUIT] Really, guys?
You had to come out here now?
[COOKIE]
I-I'm sorry.
[CRACKER] I was getting
so worried about you.
[CRACKER] We came all this way!
Think you need to thank us.
Yeah. Guess you're right.
[CRACKER giggles]
[COOKIE]
Me too!
Okay. Really sorry, Atra.
Kinda crazy right now.
Sure. So, have you
seen Mikazuki?
[MIKAZUKI gasps]
[YUKINOJO]
Hey, are you awake?
[grunts]
[YUKINOJO]
Just hold on a minute.
I wasn't able to cut the
link with this suit
while you were sitting in
the cockpit, unconscious.
[MIKAZUKI]
How many died?
[gasps]
[YUKINOJO] There were
42 from Third Group
and 68 from First Corps.
But just so you know,
you and this one here...
...did a good job.
[ATRA grunts, gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
Atra? What're you doin' here?
Makin' deliveries, huh?
Oh... Yeah. Hey... Mikazuki?
[MIKAZUKI]
What's up?
I, uh... You okay?
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah. Thanks for askin'.
I'm kinda in a hurry, though.
See ya later.
Oh... Sure.
[ATRA] I'm so stupid.
Why'd I ask him that?
I knew he wasn't all right.
[KUDELIA] Many years
after the Calamity War,
Mars was completely divided
and then governed
by the four different
economic blocks.
As a result of this, poverty
spread across the planet.
And, sadly, most of these
victims were only children.
Even to this day, with all
the time that's passed,
so many lives are being lost.
They're innocent little
ones who suffer each day.
And, something must be done.
[KUDELIA]
So many died today...
[sobs]
[KUDELIA]
And it's all because of me.
[FUMITAN]
Miss?
[KUDELIA gasps] Fumitan!
Where were you? I was worried.
[gasps]
[FUMITAN] Oh. I'm quite
all right, Miss.
It's just a scratch.
Anyway, I'm sorry about
what happened.
When there's an emergency,
I've been given strict orders
to contact Mr. Bernstein
before anybody else.
[gasps]
What did father say?
[FUMITAN] Well, he was
very worried about you.
And he wants you back
home right away.
[gasps]
Sorry. Not yet.
[FUMITAN]
Huh?
[KUDELIA] I requested
that this trip to Earth
was to be done
in total secrecy.
And yet, It's quite clear to me
now that I was the target of
Gjallarhorn's attack. But for
some reason My father,
who's completely against
the freedom movement,
gave his full support.
I don't want to believe he's...
What's that, Miss?
[KUDELIA]
The way things are, now,
I don't know that I'll be able
to return to my father,
unless I can confirm
I'm wrong about this.
I understand. But, Miss...
...there's no point
in staying here now.
It just seems...
[MIKAZUKI]
So, you're still here?
[KUDELIA]
Uh, Mikazuki. Well, uh...
Thank you so much. I really
appreciate your protecting me.
[MIKAZUKI]
You don't have to thank me.
Uh...Yes, but because
of me those people...
[MIKAZUKI]
You gotta stop this, all right?
[MIKAZUKI] You really
think all those people died
'cause of something you did?
Don't disrespect my
friends like that.
[gasps]
[KUDELIA]
He's right.
I didn't know what
I was saying.
Completely ignorant
of what was going on.
I just wanted understand,
yet the whole time...
[KUDELIA]
Those eyes...
[KUDELIA] It felt like he
could see right through me.
[KUDELIA]
Like he was laughing at me.
[CRACKER giggles]
[COOKIE] Whoa! See this?
It looks like a butt!
[ATRA]
Hey. Stop that!
You shouldn't play
with your food?
[grunts]
Just put it down.
[KUDELIA]
Um. S'cuse me...
[CRACKER]
So, who are you?
Is she your friend, Atra?
[ATRA]
What? No...
Need some help?
Oh, I'm sorry.
My name is
Kudelia Aina Bernstein
Kudelia?
[KUDELIA] I heard you talking
back here, so I just...
Hold on! Aren't you the
one who's on the news?
[CRACKER] Wait. Are you
saying she's a celebrity?
[COOKIE giggles]
I want an autograph.
[CRACKER]
Yeah! Could I get one too?
[BOYS whisper]
[HAEDA]
You fool!
[ORGA grunts]
[HAEDA]
You made us look like idiots.
Using us for your own gain--
Well, I heard that
when First Corps
went in for their
surprise attack,
all of you guys ran
into a little situation.
[scoffs]
So how is that our problem--
[grunts]
Kid, I've heard enough
outta you. You got it? Huh?!
What the hell are
you looking at?
Do you all want
some of this too?
[ORGA]
No. This is between...
...you and me.
Come on. Let's do it.
[chuckles]
[thudding]
[ALL grunting]
[HAEDA]
Just leave him.
Figure out the damage from
the battle and report to me.
[SASAI]
And hurry up!
[ORGA grunts]
Orga!
Dammit! I won't forgive them.
Me either. We can't.
[ALL gasp]
Who knows? Might be our chance.
[EUGENE]
Wait. Are you sure?
You said you wanted to do
this before, Eugene.
It's time to take over.
[EUGENE] Yeah, I did.
But in a situation like this?
We've already lost
so many out there.
Listen. Maruba was a
good-for-nothin' bastard,
but those guys in
First Corpse are worse.
To them, we'rejust human shields
who can go off and fight
their battles for 'em.
It won't take too much
longer before their business
goes south. Then the jobs'll
get even more dangerous for us.
No way we'll make
it out in one piece.
And if we leave,
kids like us'll never
be able to find jobs.
Looks like we don't
have any other choice.
What do you think about this?
Are you in or out?
We're nothing but
human debris.
Each one of us are
here against our will.
So I'll follow
whoever's in charge.
Whether it's the
other guys, or you.
[ORGA shuckles]
[EUGENE]
Okay. Let's have a meeting
and figure out our next move.
[BISCUIT] Hey, wait.
What about Mikazuki?
Ah. Guess I forgot.
[BISCUIT]
Are you serious?
If Mika's against me on this,
that's it you guys.
I'll call it off.
What?
Orga...
Eh... That won't happen.
[ORGA] I'm sure he'll
have my back on this one.
If he knows I'm serious,
he won't even hesitate.
[EIN] You're not gonna
take the troops?
[CRANK]
No. I'm going alone.
[EIN] But, sir. Even three
of our Mobile Suits
weren't any match
for those guys.
[CRANK]
I underestimated them,
but I won't make the
same mistake twice.
[EIN] In that case, sir.
I want to go with you and--
[CRANK] You got banged
up pretty badly,
so you'll only slow me down.
[gasps]
But... I have to.
[CRANK]
Fighting against children...
[EIN]
Lieutenant?
Please, Ein. I'm going alone.
I have a plan and
I don't want to
drag the rest of
you down with me.
No, of course not.
I don't want to fight them.
But if there's no choice,
I'll have to engage.
[CRANK]
Ein...
[gasps]
[ORGA]
Mika.
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
[chuckles]
Really improved your looks.
Yeah, thanks.
[ORGA] Don't you want
to say goodbye?
A lot of our boys
went down, back there.
[MIKAZUKI]
Nah. That's okay.
It's like you said,
years ago...
"You'll have plenty of
time to see the dead
when it's your
turn to join them.
So just try and keep
the living alive.
And give everything you've
got to protect them."
I said that, huh?
Maybe so...
Heh.
Hey.
Huh?
[ORGA]
I want you to do somethin'.
And, it's kinda important, so--
That's it? You're just gonna
accept before hearing it?
Of course I will.
'Cause it's you.
If you wanna do something,
that's good enough for me.
[ORGA chuckles]
Knew I could count on you.
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
[ORGA]
It's nothing. Thanks.
[CORAL]
Well, well!
Specialist Majors Fareed and
Bauduin Wonderful to see you.
Thank you for coming
here gentlemen.
It's been quite a while
hasn't it, Major Coral?
It's rather cramped in here,
but I've prepared a
little party for you two.
Though, you must be tired
after all that traveling.
Please, get some rest.
Thank you so much. Indeed.
If I can be of any assistance,
then please don't
hesitate to ask me.
We'll prepare any necessary da--
If you don't mind, sir,
we'll do the inspection
at our discretion.
But, we do appreciate
your offer.
Y-You're quite right. You should
be allowed to do as you please.
Well, then This way...
You! Make sure
everything is ready!
[ADJUTANT A]
Sir!
[GAELIO scoffs] So much
commotion around here...
I can tell they're
hiding something.
It's obvious.
[MCGILLIS]
Hm.
[CORAL]
Damn those two idiots!
Crank, you better
be doing your job.
♪
[CRACKER] Hey, Cookie.
Miss Kudelia is so beautiful!
Like really pretty!
But, I couldn't help noticing...
She's kinda clumsy, isn't she?
[COOKIE] C'mon, now.
Don't say that, Cracker.
I can see she's
workin' pretty hard.
Maybe it's up to the two
of us to teach her stuff.
[CRACKER] Sure! And we should
tell her she's awesome
if she acts
like a good girl
[COOKIE, CRACKER]
Yeah!
Next time on Mobile Suit
Gundam: Iron Blooded Orphans,
Episode 3:
"Glorious Demise."