No! Masahiro!
[grunts]
[gasps, screams]
[gunshots]
[BOTH gasps]
[BOYS whimper]
Nothing but kids in here too.
Hey, It's all right.
Don't be afraid.
Nobody is gonna hurt you.
Let's go.
Jeez...
[gunshots]
[TEKKADAN MEMBER A]
Hey... Neriya!
[BOYS whimpers]
[DANTE]
Damn it.
[SHINO]
Dante!
[BOYS scream]
[AKIHIRO grunts]
Masahiro! Can you hear me?
Big... Brother?
Don't move. Tell me,
why'd you protect me?
Don't know. This feels
pretty strange.
It's supposed to hurt,
but it doesn't.
Right now, I don't feel
any pain at all, Akihiro.
[AKIHIRO gasps]
Is it the Alaya-Vijnana?
It really is strange, you know?
I guess I'm not human after all.
[grunts] Stop... Please.
You don't have to talk anymore.
[MASAHIRO] I remember someone
telling me a story once.
[gasps]
He said... when humans die,
their souls... are reborn.
And they can start life over.
Sounds too good
to be true, huh?
[KUDAL yells]
You damn space rats!
You're so useless!
Ya can't even be a proper decoy!
At least now you'll
rot in the void
along with the rest of
this space garbage!
I won't let you get in the way!
[AZEE] Akihiro needs time...
to say his goodbyes.
[MASAHIRO] I guess that
story has nothing to do with
Human Debris like me, though.
So, Brother, understand?
This is how you die.
if you're Human De--
[AKIHIRO]
I don't get it.
[MASAHIRO]
Huh?
There's no way I
could accept that!
If you die here you'll
be reborn. I swear it!
You hear me?
You'll be reborn and
come back to me!
Back to our home!
[chuckles]
That sounds really nice,
Not sure whether it's true,
but I'll know in
just a few moments.
I'll go first and
check it out for us.
Akihiro... Brother.
M-Masahiro!
[SHINO]
Damn it.
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
Give it up! End this already,
you bastards!
[KUDAL grunts]
What is he doing? Aiming for the
gaps between my armor plates?
What the hell is up
with this freak?!
[MIKAZUKI] I like this thing.
Not bad at all.
[MIKAZUKI] What? That's strange.
Why do I feel like this?
[KUDAL screams]
[MIKAZUKI]
I don't understand.
Stop fooling around
with me! Hey!
You're enjoying this,
aren't you?
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
[KUDAL]
The killing of men!
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
[groans]
Why?! Why won't you just die?!
[MIKAZUKI]
Am I... really enjoying this?
[grunts]
Well, whatever.
This one doesn't
deserve to stay alive.
[KUDAL screams]
♪
[PARTYGOERS chatter]
[GUEST A]
Congratulations.
[GUEST B] Good news
like this has been rare.
[GUEST C] Lord Bauduin
must be quite relieved.
Relax. Enjoy your
time here tonight.
I will.
Lord Iznario. Using the child
of his mistress like that.
[GUEST E] Hmph. But If he
takes the hand of the
Bauduin family's daughter,
his position in the Seven
Stars will be even stronger.
Hear that? The guests are
even more vulgar than usual.
Let them say what they want.
[YOUNG LADY A]
Mr. McGillis.
[MCGILLIS, GAELIO]
Hm?
Um, if it's possible,
could I talk to you?
You won't be a bachelor
much longer. Go on.
I'll pretend I
didn't see anything.
[GUEST F]
Oh, my. She's so adorable!
Just like a little doll.
[ALMIRIA sighs]
[ALMIRIA gasps]
Macky!
[gasps]
[sighs]
[GUEST H]
Even if it's for the family,
he's definitely rushing it.
She looks like she barely got
out of her diapers yesterday.
[GUEST H gasps]
[ALMIRIA whimpers]
Miss, wait!
May I have this dance?
Sure.
[MCGILLIS gasps]
[exhales]
[whimpers]
You're not dancing?
[ALMIRIA]
I can't. I'm just a child.
Nothing more.
[ALMIRIA]
As it is,
I can't even dance with
my cheek against yours.
[ALMIRIA gasps]
Eh? Macky...
[gasps]
Now, let us dance, My Lady.
I can't.
If someone sees us,
they'll just laugh.
[MCGILLIS]
Almiria.
If someone does laughs at you,
I'll never forgive them.
Huh?
Because to me,
out of all the ladies here,
you're the most beautiful.
[whimpers]
[ALMIRIA]
Macky.
Tonight is supposed
to be special.
Forget all your worries.
Don't think about what fate
may have in store for us.
Dance with me.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER B] There are
still some old idiots hiding,
so be careful.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER c]
Ok. I'll keep my eyes open then.
Dante, is that all of them?
Think so. But boss,
these kids...
[BREWER A grunts]
[DANTE gasps]
[ORGA] Mars might not
be the greatest place,
but it beats staying here.
And we've got a stable
base set up there too.
You can have a
hot meal everyday.
[BREWER A,D]
Huh?
Wait, what?
[ORGA]
I talked it over with Naze.
[gasps]
[ORGA] We're gonna take
care of these guys.
[BREWER BOY A]
What? Take care of us?
[DANTE]
Boss...
[BREWER A]
Hold on.
[ORGA]
Huh?
Until just a while ago,
we were trying to kill you.
So why?
[ORGA]
That was your job, wasn't it?
What choice did you have?
[BREWERS gasp]
[ORGA]
Following orders.
Unless you were doing it
because you wanted to.
No!
In fact... I didn't give
it any thought until now.
It was never up to me.
[DANTE gasps]
I couldn't... Because we're...
[ORGA]
Human Debris.
[gasps]
[ORGA] Born in space and you're
not afraid to die there, either.
You're the chosen few,
and proud of it.
[BREWER BOYS gasp]
We're Tekkadan.
Welcome the family
[BREWER BOYS sob]
Thanks boss. I'm truly grateful.
[ORGA grunts]
[SHINO sobs]
[MIKAZUKI]
Shino.
[SHINO] I was the one
who gave the order.
And because I
wasn't good enough...
...these guys...
[SHINO]
In a place like this.
It would've been so much better
if I had died instead of them.
No, you are wrong.
Saying that would
disrespect these guys.
[SHINO grunts, yells]
[NAZE]
It's quite simple.
You will pay any
reparations we ask for.
Got it, Brooke Kabayan?
Naze Turbine.
[NAZE]
Hm. Well, you first, Brother.
Now, let's see.
I'll take one of your ships.
And all the mobile suits.
What?! Hey, that's
asking too much.
[grunts]
If you don't like it, I can sell
pieces of your flesh instead.
They're loaded with fat,
but we can feed
them to the dogs.
[BROOKE yelps, screams]
[NAZE] As planned, we'll he
heading to the colonies next.
[MERRIBIT]
The Brewers' assets consist of
two ships and ten Mobile Suits
we should be able to fix.
That's not bad at all.
These things are beasts.
Every one of them are equipped
with an unusually thick
amount of armor plating.
And most of them are
undamaged inside.
The one called Gusion
is especially valuable.
What should we do?
Will Tekkadan be
keeping the machines?
No... We'll be
selling all of them.
[CREW]
Eh?
Akihiro's brother is dead.
No way we could ever pilot them.
Not if they killed
one of our own.
You're right. Where is he?
Who knows. He could
be up in his room.
I mean, his brother
just died after all.
[MERRIBIT]
I know...
[ORGA]
Hm?
Why don't we have a
funeral for the boys.
A funeral?
That's right. Where I am from,
it's the very old tradition.
It's the way my
colony honors the dead.
The ceremony allows
the soul to be free.
That way, it can be
safely reborn.
I don't know about that.
Sounds strange.
[NAZE]
I'm all for it.
[ORGA]
Huh?
Apparently, funerals were
a fairly important tradition
for much of Earth's history.
By going through
these ceremonies,
they say the soul of the dead
forgets the pain they had
when they were alive and move
into a state of total peace.
Is that true?
Who knows.
I wanna do it.
What?
I'm serious. If it were up
to me, I think we should.
I want to help them
forget their pain,
Even for just a little while.
[door hums]
It's the right thing to do.
[ORGA]
Akihiro.
Well, if that's the case,
then we'll lend you a hand.
We should tell
everyone else.
[YUKINOJO]
Yeah. Good call.
[EUGENE] Okay, then I'll
go back to the Isaribi .
[SHINO]
Yeah, me too.
[MERRIBIT] Gues you are not
that interested it, are you?
To be honest,
I don't really get it.
All that talk about the
soul being reborn...
We'll be able to see the dead
when its our turn to die.
This funeral is just
a waste of time.
We should be more concerned
about staying alive,
than worrying about
the after life.
[MERRIBIT] Well , I suppose you
are entitled to your opinion.
[ORGA exhales]
[MERRIBIT] But not everyone
here accepts the deaths
of their friends
quite so easily.
These funerals... They're just
as much for the living.
It allows people to move on...
...and accept the absence
of those they've lost.
So, like talking down to
all the people, huh?
Old Woman...
[MERRIBIT]
I can still hear you.
Little Boy.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[KUDELIA]
A funeral?
Yeah. I don't really
understand it, honestly.
But tell the others, okay?
[ATRA]
Oh! Mikazuki.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
Uh... Mm-mm.
Mikazuki made it
back in one piece.
But it feels weird
telling him I'm glad.
[KUDELIA sighs]
I know what you mean.
[ATRA] Still... I am just
happy he is back with us.
[KUDELIA]
Right.
[yawns]
So, we're having
a funeral, huh?
I sure wish we had some
flowers or something
to make it look better.
[YAMAGI]
Old Man.
Huh?
I think I might have an idea
on that. Can you help me?
Uh...?
[YUKINOJO]
What is it?
[TEKKADAN BOY A]
Can I put this in too?
[NAZE]
Sure.
It feels strange just
standing here.
Know what I mean?
[SHINO]
Yeah.
There. We should get started.
Orga?
Yeah.
Takaki, it doesn't
hurt anymore?
No. I feel fine.
[ORGA]
Okay.
Everyone bow your heads.
[MERRIBIT]
Mm?
So the souls of those
who have fallen,
will go to where they belong.
And be reborn.
I wish all of you
a safe journey.
[sighs]
Prepare salute shots.
[ORGA]
Fire.
[gasps]
[AKIHIRO]
This is...
Whoa! Amazing!
Like blooming flowers!
--[RIDE] Wow!
--[CHAD] Whoa...
[TAKAKI]
Incredible.
[RIDE]
What's going on?
[EUGENE]
D'you do this, old man?
Yeah. I messed around with the
hydrogen in the propellant.
Makes a hell of a show.
Right? It was all Yamagi's idea.
Ha!
[SHINO]
Are you serious?
They're fading.
[EUGENE]
Yeah.
[EMBI]
Oh, no...
[ELGAR]
Already?
[RIDE]
Well that was lame.
They should just stay
in bloom forever.
Yeah...
[gasps]
You know, it's seem so short.
When we're alive,
we really make a racket.
We fight sometimes,
and we laugh too.
But then, just like that,
we're gone.
[SHINO grunts]
[NAZE]
You can cry.
[gasps]
That's what a funeral's for.
It allows the living to remember
those who've gone and say
their good-byes one last time.
It's all right. You can
let all out now.
--[SHINO] No, sir.
--[NAZE] Huh?
We've gathered here to send
off our brothers in style.
And I don't want us to
look lame in their eyes.
--[YUKINOJO exhales]
--[YAMAGI whimpers]
[AMIDA] These kids.
They can be so foolish.
It seems really quiet, tonight.
[ATRA]
Mm.
[TEKKADAN BOY A sobs]
Come on...
[ATRA]
Ride? What's wrong?
I can't get him to stop crying.
And rest of us
can't get any sleep.
[TEKKADAN BOY A]
Mom...
[ATRA, KUDELIA sigh]
Come here. Let me hold you.
[TEKKADAN BOY A]
No! You chest is too flat, Atra.
[ATRA gasps]
[TEKKADAN BOY A]
I want Fumitan.
Come on!
Fumitan?
[FUMITAN]
It's all right.
[KUDELIA, ATRA gasp]
[TEKKADAN BOY A sobs]
[SHINO]
Oh! There you are, Yamagi.
[YAMAGI]
Shino. Give me a second.
Thank you. For all
those ice flowers.
[YAMAGI]
Are you kidding?
What? It was beautiful!
You better make
blossoms like that
when I kick the
bucket it someday.
[YAMAGI exhales]
Forget it.
Huh?
No. 'Cause they take
a lot of work to make
and it cost too much.
I'm not going to be able
to hold funerals
all the time.
[laughs]
You're right.
Sorry to bother you, man.
Just wanted to say thanks.
[sighs]
Alright. All the sales
procedures have been completed.
Yeah, good job.
Thank you for everything.
And... I'm not just talking
about the loot either.
The funeral was...
[NAZE] Please, Brother,
don't mention it.
Now then, Amida.
[AMIDA]
Hm?
Hey, why are you
kissing all of a sudden?
[NAZE]
Huh?
Don't you know?
Years with high death rates
have high birthrates, too.
Huh?
Being around death makes you
start thinking about life.
Next thing you know,
the woman beside you
starts looking pretty good.
[AMIDA]
I thought I always look good.
[NAZE]
I meant even better than usual.
[BISCUIT]
Is that so...
[ORGA] So, Akihiro,
what'd you wanna talk about?
Can you give this to me?
[ORGA]
What? Are you gonna pilot it?
[AKIHIRO]
At the funeral,
I kept thinking about
the one's who died.
I have memories
of each of them.
Even the ones I never
really talked to.
But the memories
I have of Masahiro
are only from my childhood.
And now the last one
that I have of him,
is the moment when
this suit took his life.
If it's mine,
At least it will be something
always connect the two of us.
[ORGA]
I see...
[KUDAL] You're enjoying this,
aren't you?
The killing of men!
[KUDELIA]
I wonder what's wrong.
They're usually so happy
and fully of energy.
They were so excited
about the ice flowers.
[FUMITAN] They can't help it.
They're only children.
Unconsciously, they keep their
problems buried down inside.
But sometimes the
strain shows.
Unconsciously, huh?
[FUMITAN] Miss, you should
get to sleep now.
[KUDELIA] I'm okay. I can
stay a little longer.
[KUDELIA]
Tekkadan.
They were named, "the flowers
that never wilt and die."
[MIKAZUKI]
Oh, hey.
Mikazuki. You can't
get to sleep?
No. It's just...
Hungry?
[KUDELIA]
Uh. Okay, sure.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
What's the matter?
You're hands are shaking.
Huh?
You're right. I wonder why.
Something feels strange today.
[KUDELIA]
Maybe Mikazuki has them too.
Strong emotions that he
keeps inside... unconsciously.
Huh?
[KUDELIA]
Uh. It's just that, uh, Fumitan
was doing this to
the little kids earlier
and they seemed to
calm down afterwards.
S-Sorry. I guess
I wasn't thinking.
[sighs]
[KUDELIA]
Uh.
[KUDELIA gasps]
W-What? What are you doing?
[MIKAZUKI]
I thought you were cute.
[MIKAZUKI blows]
[MIKAZUKI]
Sorry. You didn't like it?
U-Uh. Whether I like
it or not isn't the issue.
These things take time.
You should ask...
[gasps]
♪
[ATRA]
Mm!
[ATRA sneezes]
[NOBLISS]
There are a lot of people being
oppressed by Gjallarhorn
these days.
They're all anxiously
awaiting the appearance
of a beautiful revolutionary.
[NOBLISS]
Mm.
I've decided.
The stage for the death of
Kudelia Aina Bernstein
will be... the colony.
[RIDE] Argh! That's it.
I've had enough of this.
The boss needs to
stop calling me a kid.
I don't start missing
my mom and go cryin'
like the other guys
do around here.
And there's a lot of sad
stuff going on, believe me.
Still, you won't
catch me cryin'.
Then, again. Guess I wouldn't
mind getting a hug from
Ms. Fumitan once in a while.
Next time on Mobile Suit
Gundam: Iron Blooded Orphans,
Episode 14,
"Vessel of Hope."