[gunshot]
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
[MIKAZUKI]
Ow...
[ORGA gasps, grunts]
So, what do you want
me to do next, Orga?
[MIKAZUKI]
Orga...
[grunts]
[ORGA]
Hey. Mika...
[MIKAZUKI] C'mon, man. You can't
keep slackin' off like this.
Think of what'll happen if they
catch us back here again.
Yeah, I know. You're right.
[YUKINOJO]
Mikazuki! Did you find him?
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah.
[ORGA grunts]
What's up, Old Man?
[YUKINOJO] Now, don't
gimme that. Maruba's callin'.
[ORGA]
The president?
[YUKINOJO]
Look, guys,
I thought we've already
been through this before.
[ORGA] Come on. It's the only
place that warm around here.
[YUKINOJO]
Gimme a break...
--[ORGA] Hey Mika! Time to go.
--This engine room's top secret.
[MIKAZUKI]
Right.
[MARUBA]
We've received word
from the Chryse
Autonomous Region.
Their representative's
daughter's going to Earth,
along with her escort.
You boys in the Third Group
are gonna take her.
[BOTH gasp]
S'cuse me, but are you referring
to Kudelia Aina Bernstein,
by any chance?
[MARUBA]
Have you heard of her, Biscuit?
[BISCUIT]
Indeed, sir.
She's involved in the
freedom movement, isn't she?
[MARUBA] Right. And her trip to
Earth is about that very thing.
The independence of Mars.
Noble, isn't it?
But, why do you want us
to do a big job like this?
Well, actually she
handpicked you guys, herself.
[BISCUIT]
What? You mean--
Regardless of the assignment,
just make sure that you
remember one thing.
You little punks are to do
exactly as we say. Understand?
[TAKAKI grunts]
[DANJI]
This sucks!
Can you believe all these
landmine setting drills?
[RIDE] It's like
they're torturing us.
Tomorrow, we've
got removal drills.
[DANJI]
Oh, man...
[explosions]
[DANJI]
Hm?
[grunts] Damn that kid.
How does he do it?
[gasps, grunts]
[AKIHIRO] Mikazuki Augus.
You know how to dodge, don't ya?
I gotta pilot those things.
I hope that some day...
[SASAI]
What's going on!
[grunts]
Pick up the pace, kid!
Todo, you're suppose to be
keeping 'em in line!
[chuckles] All right, brats!
You've got work to do!
Oh, jeez... Hmph. These space
rats better settle down.
Takaki, you gonna be okay?
[TAKAKI]
Yeah... I'm fine.
[grunts]
[SOLDIERS chatter]
[EUGENE] They put us in
charge of escorting her?
You know a girl like that has
to smell pretty incredible!
Right, Mikazuki?
Yeah, whatever. She's just
human like the rest of us.
Doubt she'd be any different.
[SHINO]
Huh?
[DANJI] He's clueless
when it comes to girls.
Trust me, you're wasting
your breath.
Takaki.
Hey. You need some water?
Why are you wearing
that bandage?
Oh, it's no big deal.
Happens all the time...
[EUGENE] The president knows.
He sees we're strong.
When an outfit like
ours pulls together,
we're unstoppable. Unlike all
of his brown-nosing employees.
I'm tellin' you guys.
We're gonna breeze past
those smooth-talkin' jerks
and take their place
as First Corps!
[ORGA] Listen, no matter
how senile Maruba gets,
he's always gonna
see us as expendable.
So I wouldn't get your hopes
too high if I were you.
[grunts]
Oh yeah?
Well, if that's true, did ya
ever think maybe the reason he
sees us that way is 'cause we've
got you for a group leader?
Now, that's enough, Eugene.
[EUGENE]
Aw, shut up, Biscuit.
Let's not forget
he's the one who--
[groans]
Tryin' to start a
fight out here?
Don't make me do this.
Hey, let go!
You're tearin' it off!
[ORGA] Nah, we're just having a
little disagreement. That's all.
Y-Yeah, right.
That's all it is.
[EUGENE]
C-Come on, Mikazuki!
Really sorry, Akihiro.
They're a little rowdy.
[AKIHIRO]
Same as always.
[KUDELIA]
The time's come, Mother.
I'll be leaving now.
[TOMOMI] So soon, Aina?
I had no idea.
Please remember to
mind you manners
around the peolpe out there
[KUDELIA] I always thought
Father didn't like that
I was so involved in
the freedom movement.
But, this time he's being so
supportive and allowing me
to go to Earth as a mediator
between our two sides.
[TOMOMI]
It's in your nature
to take things
so negatively, Kudelia.
Your father's always kept
your best interests at heart.
He truly cares about you.
[KUDELIA] My mother would
rather ignore these things.
She's never made any
effort to understand
what's going on out there.
I refuse to live like that.
I want a better understanding
by experiencing
the truth myself.
[FUMITAN] Is that why you chose
Third Group as your escorts?
[KUDELIA] Yes. Because these
children are precisely the kind
of soldiers born out of the
Earth Sphere's oppressive rule.
They embody the problems
burdening each one of us.
By getting to know them
on a more personal level,
I hope to share
some of their pain
and let them know that
they are not alone.
[CORAL]
It's beautiful, isn't it?
The delicate nature of youth
and wide-eyed innocence.
The Bernsteins are a family
deeply involved with Earth,
yet their daughter's seen
as the leader of the very
Independence movement
against it.
Ironic, isn't it?
Norman Bernstein.
[grunts] My daughter's
been quite foolish.
[CORAL] But, when foolishness
goes that far,
it's rather magnificent.
Which is the reason
that Chryse--
No-- It's the reason those
bastards all over Mars
support what she's trying to do.
Now, then. I'm sure she'd
like nothing more
than to live eternally in the
hearts and minds of the people.
So, in a way, you might
say we're helping her.
[grunts]
Of course, Sir Coral.
But, please, promise
me you'll be kind.
[CORAL] He sells out his
daughter for his own gain,
then asks me to be "kind"?
What a pathetic coward.
I think he could learn
something from her.
[ADJUTANT A]
Sir.
[CORAL] But, now that
inspection from Earth
is a golden opportunity.
To receive Nobliss's support,
we need to do everything in our
power to ensure this plan works.
All right, Orlis,
The mission's been finalized.
You take command, this time.
Yes, sir.
[CORAL] Crank!
Support your former student.
Sir.
[CORAL]
Ein!
[gasps]
Yes, sir.
[CORAL] This is your
first official assignment.
Do your best!
[EIN]
I will, sir.
[GAELIO]
Mars? Seriously?
As a colony, that planet's
resources are all used up,
if you asked me. And that
place is out in the boonies.
Do we really need Gjallarhorn
inspectors out there?
I've just confirmed it.
Are these frontier operations
boring you, Gaelio?
As if. I'll work hard
as an officer
of the inspection division,
Major McGills.
You can count on me,
as always, Sir.
Well, whether we
like it or not,
Earth Sphere's economy depends
on that used-up colony.
To succeed, it's imperative
that they can continue
making significant
contributions.
So it's of utmost importance
that the Mars Branch
clean up their act and become
proud members of Gjallarhorn:
the true keepers
of the world order.
I kinda feel bad for
those guys down there.
[MCGILLIS]
The push for independence
is spreading across Mars
at an alarming pace.
[GAELIO]
Hm?
[MCGILLIS]
Before much longer,
we may be too busy to
worry about anybody else.
[YOUNG SOLDIER A]
We're supposed to start heading
down to the south
route to Block D.
[Young soldier B]
I'm tired.
[Young soldier C]
Let's get goin'.
[SOLDIERS snoring]
[MIKAZUKI, AKIHIRO grunt]
[AKIHIRO]
Muscle weighs more.
M-My body's just heavier
than yours, all right?
[MIKAZUKI] Yeah, keep tellin'
yourself that.
[AKIHIRO grunts]
Hey!
[YUKINOJO] Okay Just finished
checkin' the equipment
for your trip.
[ORGA]
Good job, man.
[YUKINOJO] So, she's supposed
to come down tomorrow, huh?
[ORGA] Yeah. And, then we'll
get goin' the day after.
I figure it should take
us about five months
to make it to Earth and back.
[YUKINOJO] It's gonna
be quiet around here.
I heard she picked
you herself. Not bad.
You gotta be kiddin' me.
We're just being used.
Same as always.
Maruba thinks we're
nothin' but a buncha rats
runnin' around this place.
He just knows we can
move a little faster
thanks to our "Whiskers".
Yeah, those things...
The old Man-Machine Interface,
the Alaya-Vijnana System.
They're just 's awful.
[ORGA] Yeah, but ...
having it implanted
is the price you pay
if you wanna work here.
[YUKINOJO]
Well, guess it's better than
not having a job at all.
[chuckles] I still remember
back when you got yours.
They didn't give
you any anesthesia,
but you didn't cry once.
Then you got punched
for being a wise ass.
[ORGA] If I cried,
I would've been punched, too.
Anyway, Third Group
doesn't mean crap here.
They either smack
us for a few laughs,
or use us as human shields.
But... I won't let 'em
take away my pride.
I can't show any weakness.
To Mikazuki, you mean?
[ORGA chuckles]
It must be tough, Captain.
[PROTESTERS shouting]
[PROTESTER 0A] We demand
independence from Earth
for the Chryse
Autonomous Region!
[PROTESTERS]
Independence!
[PROTESTER A] That's right!
No more colonial rule!
[PROTESTERS]
No more!
[PROTESTER A]
Protect the autonomy of Mars.
[ATRA hums]
[HABA]
You're in a good mood.
[ATRA gasps, grunts]
I-I'm sorry.
[HABA] It's fine. With the
protest going on outside,
I don't think we'll have
customers anyway.
I know. It's for
that boy, isn't it?
[ATRA gasps]
Oh, uh...
[HABA]
I understand.
He's got a big job and
you're gonna miss him
while he's gone, aren't you?
Make sure you finish it by
tomorrow's deliveries.
[ATRA]
Yes, ma'am.
[MARUBA] It's truly an honor
to have you here with us.
I've admired your political
activism for quite some time,
Miss Kudelia.
--[MARUBA chuckles]
--[knocking]
[MARUBA]
Come in.
Hello, sir. Third Group
reporting in, as requested.
[MARUBA] All right.
These are the young men
who'll be escorting
you to Earth.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kudelia Aina Bernstein.
Hey, there.
What's up? My name is--
[HAEDA] Don't you even know how
to greet someone properly?
Unbelievable!
[MARUBA] Now, where were we?
About tomorrow's schedule...
[KUDELIA]
And, you...?
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
[KUDELIA]
What's your name?
I'm Mikazuki Augus. Hello.
[KUDELIA] Would it be
possible for you to show me
around this place?
--[MIKAZUKI] Huh?
--[MARUBA] What?
Fumitan? I'll leave
the rest up to you.
Of course, as you wish.
[MARUBA]
Uh...
Okay then, Mikazuki.
[FUMITAN]
I hope you don't mind.
I believe you wanted to
discuss our schedule?
[MARUBA]
B-But...
'Kay, follow me.
[MARUBA]
I, uh...
[KUDELIA]
Hey! Wait! Come back!
[MIKAZUKI] So, behind this
is the engine room.
[KUDELIA]
S'cuse me--
[MIKAZUKI] And we have our own
Ahab Reactor down here too.
[KUDELIA]
Um... Hold on!
[MIKAZUKI]
Uh?
[KUDELIA pants]
[KUDELIA]
Um...Let's shake hands.
It's nice to meet you.
[MIKAZUKI]
Uh...
Is everything all right?
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
[KUDELIA]
I hope this is okay.
I just wanted you to show you
that I see you as an equal.
I can't do it 'cause my hands
are really dirty right now.
[gasps]
Of course. I only...
[MIKAZUKI] Oh well. I guess
that means the two of us
weren't on equal
terms to begin with.
[gasps]
[BISCUIT]
You can't get to sleep, Orga?
[ORGA] And it looks
like you can't, either.
Something just
doesn't seem right.
[BISCUIT] Indeed. I mean, to me,
Kudelia's just some naïve girl,
but I know how
important she really is
and what she represents.
Even Gjallarhorn could act
against somebody
like that influential.
So what does she want with a
little outfit like ours, anyway?
I don't know. It's not like we
have a choice now, anyway.
But, if this whole
thing's a trap,
we'd better be ready
to crush 'em.
[SUBORDINATE A] The transmission
with headquarters
is finished, sir.
[MCGILLIS]
Good.
[GAELIO]
Depending on the relay point
for our communications
is pretty annoying.
I'll probably never
get used to this.
[MCGILLIS] The Ahab Reactor
creates the kind of energy
that not only powers the ship,
but also makes it possible
to sustain life in space.
We have no choice but to
ignore some of the downsides.
[GAELIO] But that's the
very reason why Earth
has trouble seeing this far.
It only makes more work
for all of us inspectors.
This was practically the cause
of the war 300 years ago,
wasn't it?
But it isn't always easy to
let go of a power like that,
once you obtain it.
I suppose it's human nature.
We'll stop at nothing,
even if it's a power that
could destroy us all.
[sighs, grunts]]
[YOUNG SOLDIER B]
Come on, let's go.
It's time for us to be
heading back,
It's almost dawn
and we've gotta--
[YOUNG SOLDIER B]
Huh? Did you--
[GJALLAHORN SPOTTER]
Clear. Okay, next target...
[BOTH gasp]
Those two are
completely useless.
I'll throw those pathetic
snipers in the brig!
--[CRANK] Hold on, Orlis--
--[ORLIS] Okay. All forces.
Let's begin! Attack!
[gasps]
What's that?
[KUDELIA]
Fumitan!
[FUMITAN] I'll find
out what's happening.
Wait here 'till I
come back, Miss.
[gasps]
I'm going with you!
[EUGENE gasps]
[ORGA]
What's goin' on?
[EUGENE]
You're a little late!
Mikazuki and Shino's team have
already headed out there!
Akihiro and the others
used the second hangar.
[HAEDA]
What do you think you're doing?
I want everybody
in the Third Group
attacking the enemy, head on!
[ORGA] One question.
Who are we fightin' against?
[grunts]
Th-They're, uh...
[SHINO] Damn! They must
be rich, firing all that ammo.
They're trying to kill us
and we don't even know
who the hell they are!
[MIKAZUKI]
Hold on.
They're here.
[SHINO]
Huh?
[SHINO] Wait a minute.
Those Mobile Workers are...
[MARUBA]
Gjallarhorn?
Those guys're a bunch of idiots.
Why're they attacking us?
We don't even keep a lotta
loot around this place.
Damn. Forgot the
password again.
Think it was about that
female dog I had as a kid...
[gasps] Wait, the loot?
A female dog? Sasai!
[gasps]
Sir?
[EUGENE]
Why's Gjallarhorn doing this?
[HAEDA]
How am I supposed to know?
[TODO]
Never mind that! Just deploy!
And First Corps.
We'll coordinate with
you guys. Won't we?
We'll sneak up on them.
And combat them from the rear.
A surprise attack!
But until then, you're job
is to hold off the enemy.
[TODO]
You got that?
[EUGENE]
Great. I guess we have to go.
Hey, Orga.
We've been picking up
Ahab Wave signals,
but it isn't from
our own reactor.
[ORGA gasps]
If the enemy's Gjallarhorn,
you know what that means.
[ORGA grunts]
[EUGENE]
Orga! Hurry up!
Hey, Biscuit.
I need a favor.
[grunts]
[SHINO]
You saved us, Mikazuki.
[MIKAZUKI]
No problem.
But there's just so many
of them. And our ammo's low.
[ORGA]
Shino's team! Fall back!
Dante's coming. Go reload.
[SHINO]
Orga! Where are you?
Yeah, sorry,
Mika, Akihiro, fall back.
[DANJI] Orga! Hey, if you're
shorthanded, you can put me
out there. I think I saw a
Mobile Worker that's free.
[TAKAKI]
You can't, Danji.
Report to Shino when he
gets back. Be careful.
Yes!
Huh?
[SASAI grunts]
Damn! The Third Group's job
should be doing this. Not me!
Maruba's a fool.
Excuse me, but...
[SASAI gasps]
[KUDELIA]
Where are you taking me?
I have to wait for
Fumitan to get ba--
[BISCUIT] If you stay here, you
won't live through the night.
[gasps]
You... You mean...
There's a chance
I could die here?
I'm doing everything I can to
make sure that doesn't happen.
[YUKINOJO]
Yamagi! Cable 5.
[YAMAGI]
Right!
[BISCUIT]
Hey, Old Man!
[YUKINOJO]
We've already started.
Are you sure about this?
[BISCUIT] Yeah, positive.
I've still have some things
I've gotta do around here.
You think you can handle it?
[YUKINOJO]
Look. It's right under there.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[ORGA] Team 3,
your reinforcements are coming.
Just hold tight 'till then.
Step it up, Team 5.
Watch your ass!
Eugene, go!
I can move out if you want,
but it's only gettin'
worse out here.
[SHINO]
They're still comin'.
Focus your fire!
[SHINO]
Hey! What're you doin', Danji?
That armor's thicker
than I thought.
I'll have to get in
a little closer.
[DANJI screams]
[SHINO] Keep goin'!
If you stop now, you'll die!
[DANJI gasps]
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
Sorry. I'm here.
[DANJI]
Mikazuki!
[MIKAZUKI gasps]
[AKIHIRO] Stop hoggin' all
the glory. It's my turn now!
[ORGA] All right.
Mika and Akihiro have engaged.
Those two are unstoppable
in close combat.
Time to show them what we
"space rats" can do.
Get the wounded outta there.
We're gonna need to regroup.
[EUGENE]
Yeah, all right.
But this'll only buy us
a little more time.
It's gettin' pretty bad.
Where're the Main Forces?
Why isn't First Corps
here already?
Those guys had better
get out here soon!
[BISCUIT]
Orga.
Is that you, Biscuit?
How's it look?
[BISCUIT] Our worst case
scenario came true.
First Corps and the President
are fleeing the
battlefield from the rear.
We're all alone out here!
[gasps] So, what in the hell
are we supposed to do, now?
There's no way
I'm gonna die for this!
[ORGA]
And you won't have to.
[EUGENE]
What?
[ORGA]
Time for us to change the game.
Right, Biscuit?
So true.
[beeping]
[TODO]
Huh?
[TODO shouts]
[YOUNG SOLDIER E]
What is that?
[YOUNG SOLDIER F]
A signal flare?
[EUGENE gasps]
Who did that? First Corps?
[ORGA] Yeah. Looks like those
guys are gonna help us out
and be our decoys after all.
[HAEDA] All right! What were
you thinkin', Todo? Tell me!
C'mon, I didn't do anything.
You've gotta believe me!
[HAEDA growls]
Those little brats!
[SHINO]
Whoa! The enemy is moving!
I bet they are.
[EUGENE]
Huh?
If I'm right about this.
They're gonna make sure
that nobody gets
outta this base alive.
[YUKINOJO]
Yamagi! Number 12!
[YAMAGI]
Yeah--
Hold on! You guys,
I can try and help, too.
[YUKINOJO]
It's too dangerous, Miss.
Just stand back!
[KUDELIA sighs]
Aren't those...?
[BOTH]
The landmines we buried!
Awesome!
Okay! Let's take
'em down, you guys!
[gasps]
[ORGA]
What?
Is that artillery?
[BOTH grunt]
No way!
[YOUNG SOLDIER G]
What's goin' on?
[YOUNG SOLDIER G gasps]
[ORLIS] Can anyone explain
why it's taking so long
to neutralize a
facility like this?
Wait what?
[ORLIS] All of you Mobile
Workers are gonna get
a cut in pay.
[CRANK]
Orlis!
Why did you open fire?
Our objective here is--
You keep your mouth shut, Crank,
I'm the one in charge now.
[grunts]
[ORLIS] If the objective
is so damn important,
why don't you go
find her, yourself?
Ein, you too.
[gasps]
Y-Yes, sir.
[EUGENE] Impossible! We can't
win against Mobile Suits.
What are we supposed
to do now?
L-Let's go.
We're trapped.
[ORGA]
We are.
There's no place we can run.
There never was...
...right, Mika?
Yeah. So, what do you
want me to do next, Orga?
[chuckles]
[laughs] I'll squash you
all like little bugs!
[EIN] Lieutenant Crank,
Captain Orlis--
No use stopping him.
If we could've
deployed here sooner,
we wouldn't have had so
many casualties laid out
all over the battlefield.
[ORGA] Hold your positions.
We just need to stay put
till Mika gets back here.
And,when he does,
we'll deliver the final blow.
We can all get outta this
rotten place. Are we clear?
The base! Stop it!
My friends are still inside.
Danji! No! Danji!
Gotta keep moving. Just a
little longer. Just a little--
[EUGENE]
Orga! It's looking this way.
[ORLIS] So, tell me.
Are you the one in charge here?
[EUGENE]
We're all gonna die!
[ORGA] We're not gonna die.
We'll never die.
Not like this.
[ORGA]
Not fighting out here.
This is not the end!
[laughs]
[ORGA]
Is it, Mika?!
[ORGA grunts]
[MIKAZUKI] So, what do you
want me to do next, Orga?
[ORGA]
It's clear to me now.
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
[ORGA]
We're going.
[MIKAZUKI]
Where?
[ORGA]
Anywhere but here.
[ORGA] To a better place.
Where you and me belong.
[grunts]
[MIKAZUKI]
Let's go.
All of us...
...together.
♪
[ATRA] I really hope
he likes the bracelet
that I made for him.
I wonder if he'll
always wanna wear it.
Ew... It'll probably
start to smell bad.
Well, maybe he should try
and air it out in the sun
once and a while.
But, he won't be able to
if he goes out into space.
What am I gonna do?
Next time on Mobile Suit
Gundam: Iron Blooded Orphans,
Episode 2: "Barbatos."