[ANNOUNCER A] The clash between
the protesters and Gjallarhorn
erupted into an intense shootout
that momentarily
got out of hand.
But the garrisons'
quick response
put the main street under
control in a matter of minutes.
However, there are still
sporadic terrorist activities
caused by the protesters.
The situation
remains unpredictable.
Mr. Navona Mingo, believed to be
the leader of the protesters,
has been confirmed dead.
Mr. Navona.
They got him.
I'll never forgive them...
Death to the entire company!
It should be clear.
Negotiations were useless
from the very beginning!
[UNION WORKER D] There's no
need to hold back now.
Let's do it.
[UNION WORKERS cheer]
[gunshots, explosions]
[UNION WORKERS shouting]
[PROTESTER B]
There they are.
[PROTESTER C]
Okay, let's take them.
[PROTESTER D]
Where are the weapons?
[PROTESTER E]
Locker 5!
[STAFFER A]
Can you do this?
Of course I can!
I use these every day
for building walls.
All right. Look out,
you company fools.
[DISPATCHER A]
Do the thrusters need to refuel?
No need. The tank's
completely filled up.
[DISPATCHER A]
Okay, start moving the ones
that're ready into the airlock.
[OFFICERS scream]
[PROTESTER G]
Any weapons?
[PROTESTER H]
Debris missiles.
[PROTESTER I]
Load 'em.
[UNION WORKER C]
Come on! We're going to Dort 3!
[UNION WORKER D]
But why aren't we running into
any Gjallarhorn
soldiers here?
[UNION WORKER C] They're busy
with all the rioting going on.
Let's just hurry.
[OPERATOR A] Incoming from
Dort Space Ports 1, 4, and 5.
We have confirmation that
Mobile Suits and armed launches
are heading out now.
Calling all forces.
Eliminate the dissidents.
They're gone.
[BISCUIT]
We'd better hurry.
The number 3 elevator
is still moving.
Okay, let's get outta here.
Miss Kudelia? Are you all right?
Yes, of course.
Let's go.
[ORGA]
Mika.
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah.
♪
[UNION WORKER E]
Hey.
Here come the garrison forces.
No problem. They're severely
outnumbered. Kill them all!
Look at all of them out there!
D-Did they deploy the
main Arianrhod fleet?
No way!
Hurry and shoot already!
Or they'll murder us!
Okay! Huh?
[UNION WORKER F]
What's wrong? Come on!
[UNION WORKER G]
I can't! It won't fire!
What? You've gotta
be kidding me!
What is the matter?!
I don't know.
The system seems fine,
but nothing's firing!
[gasps]
[UNION WORKER H]
Dammit! How dare you!
What?
The thruster! But the
gauge says it's normal.
[UNION WORKER H] What the hell?!
Why won't the bullets fire?
[DISPATCHER A]
T-The number two machine...
The number two machine's
been shot down.
[CAPTAIN A]
It looks like the counterattack
on the armed group has begun.
Counterattack? It looks
more like a massacre to me.
What do you mean?
They provoked them
into violent actions,
and then they'll wipe them out
all in the name of peace.
They even gave the union workers
useless weapons to fight with.
That's always been how
the Regulatory Bureau
handles things.
[CAPTAIN A] Specialist Major,
I have a feeling
there shouldn't be a problem
launching your Mobile Suit now.
[GAELIO]
Don't be stupid.
It's just as McGillis
said it was,
this is the true nature
of today's Gjallahorn.
The very definition
of corruption.
I want no part of it.
[SOLDIER A]
I'm sorry.
But with all the
fighting going on,
it's too dangerous
outside the colonies.
So the Space Port's been
completely closed off.
Are you out of your mind?
It's dangerous here, too!
If we stay any longer,
who knows when the
protesters will attack?
[SOLDIER A]
Please, just be patient.
We'll guide you all
to a safe place
as soon as we possibly can.
The Space Port is closed?
What do we do now, Orga?
'Cause even the Isaribi
is out of our reach.
[REPORTER A] In many of the
colonies, armed union groups
are now escalating
their violent activities.
Dort 1, 4, and 5 have all
suffered sizeable damage
and casualties from
terrorist bombings.
Multiple weaponized
launches and Mobile Suits
have been reported stolen.
Armed groups have begun taking
off from each Space Port.
It appears that they're
attempting to support
the protesters in
Dort 3 with force.
Gjallarhorn's Arianrhod
fleet, patroling nearby,
has begun quelling the
situation as fight intensifies
around the colonies.
The following is a quote
from Fleet headquarters
on the matter.
"We have an enormous
advantage in firepower.
At the present time,
there is little chance
of any further damage.
Peace will return to
the colonies very soon.
We ask that our citizens
try to remain calm."
We now return you to the
situation unfolding in space.
So the armed union guys
they're talkin' about,
those're all Navona's
guys, aren't they?
Yeah.
It's not a fair fight.
Those people are
being slaughtered.
Come on, Orga. Isn't there
anything we can do to help?
I think it's time.
What do you have
in mind, Eugene?
[EUGENE]
I don't know, like,
maybe try and give 'em
a little backup or--
[ORGA] Forget it.
I told you that's not an option.
I realize we've got orders,
but we can't ignore this; it's
happening all over the place.
Remember what those
union workers told us?
We're the band of knights.
The heroes. We bring them hope.
[ORGA]
I said drop it.
Our job is to try and escort our
client to Earth in one piece.
[BISCUIT]
He's right.
After all we've been through,
we can't stop now.
Not like this...
I can't.
I can't go to Earth with
things as they are.
[ATRA]
Miss Kudelia...
The sole purpose for my going
there was to try and create
a better world for
all the people of Mars.
But now I've seen
so much more...
The people here
are also suffering.
They've been oppressed,
and beaten down.
Even murdered.
If I can't save them...
If I can't stand up...
...nobody will
listen to my words.
None of it will matter.
[KUDELIA]
So I'm gonna fight.
Alone, if I have to.
I won't run. Not again.
It's like Fumitan told me.
I wanna be...
...like the girl in the book...
I want to become hope.
Did you hear that?
See? Even Kudelia thinks we
should join in the fight.
It'd be kinda lame if
we don't do somethin'.
Uh, hold on a minute!
It isn't that easy!
Mika, what do you think?
I'll do whatever you
want me to do, Orga.
But... I don't wanna keep
watching them lose like this.
Mikazuki...
You guys are wearin' me out.
Well, guess it won't do us
any good standin' around here.
Let's do this.
[EUGENE]
Sounds good!
[SHINO]
That's more like it.
[BISCUIT] Well, guess
we'll just get arrested
if we wait out here.
[REPORTER A] Reporting live
from the center of Dort 3.
The chaos has died
down considerably,
and the town has
become eerily quiet.
But still, distant gunfire
can be heard at times,
and it seems the resistance
against Gjallarhorn rages on.
What? Stop broadcasting?
But people are dying over here.
Don't you care about that?!
Fine. I got it.
Dort Company headquarters has
taken this situation seriously.
[PRODUCER A]
Hey, that's enough. Pack it up.
Huh?
[CAMERAMAN A]
What do you mean?
[PRODUCER A]
They don't want any more reports
about how bad
things are out here.
They said it damages
the image of the colonies
as a place of peace
and opportunity.
[REPORTER A]
Are you serious?
I guess reporting the truth
isn't important to them now.
Hold on...
Uh. I-It's her.
She was at the protest before.
None of the civilian transport
elevators are running now.
What about the maintenance
ones? Maybe we--
[PRODUCER A]
Hey, you guys!
Who's that?
Wait, isn't that the
reporter we saw on the news?
[PRODUCER A]
Excuse me, but you were with
the protesters earlier,
weren't you?
Uh. Are you talking to me?
[PRODUCER A]
Can I have a word with you?
I'd like to intervie--
Sorry, but we're kinda
in a hurry here.
You'd better clear the area.
Please. It'll just
take a minute, okay?
Personally, I feel
that our story
is a little one-sided
this time around.
I wanna report the voices of
you workers as much as possible,
even though I'm not sure
how far I can go with it.
[ORGA] You got a hearing
problem or somethin'?
[KUDELIA]
Please, wait.
If you're able to deliver
my message to the people,
then it'll be worth it.
That's the whole reason
I came here from Mars.
From Mars?
Who are you?
[KUDELIA] My name is
Kudelia Aina Bernstine.
Kudelia?
Are you outta your mind?
[PRODUCER A] Bernstein?
Of the independence movement?
A crew like this should have
their own private vessel.
And a special signal
line for news feeds.
[beeping]
[MERRIBIT]
This is the Isaribi .
[ORGA]
Merribit.
Boss, it's you.
Are you all right?
How's everybody else?
[ORGA] There's no time. I'll
tell you what to do from here.
Listen carefully.
[CHAD]
S'that the boss? What's up?
[YUKINOJO] Top off the Mobile
Suit propellants. Hurry!
[RIDE]
Connect from line 5.
[NAZE]
Are you serious?
[ORGA]
Yeah. Sorry bout this, Brother.
At request of our client,
we're gonna make some noise
before headin' to Earth.
We don't intend to turn back.
[NAZE] I'm afraid this
is too big a deal now.
We're so well known as Teiwaz,
we won't be able to join you.
We'd be causing too much
trouble for the old man.
Understood.
[NAZE] Well, if you're
really this determined
to go through with it,
then show 'em what
you're made of.
[ORGA]
Right.
Have you heard about this?
What're ya thinkin'?
[LAFTER]
Akihiro!
Are you going, too?
[AKIHIRO]
Of course I am.
Then maybe I should ask darling
to let me go with you again.
Don't, Lafter.
Come on! There's too
many of 'em out there!
Look, it's hard for Naze, too.
So let's not make things worse.
Azee!
[AKIHIRO]
By finishing this up alone,
the Turbines have done
more than enough for me.
It's our first fight. I'll make
damn sure it's a good one.
[LAFTER groans]
[AMIDA]
Now, now,
what kind of face is that?
It's ruining your
handsome features.
[NAZE] Guess I'm just
not cut out for this.
Well, you're still
amazing to me.
Don't worry. Those kids
are strong enough.
Yeah.
Gonna be chaos, down there.
The weapons should--
Hey, what are you doin', Dante?!
We have to deliver
this first, right?
I'll take it to
Mikazuki, myself!
--[YUKINOJO] Wait a minute!
--Are you gonna be okay?
I've done plenty of simulations.
It's just a delivery.
[groaning]
Dante!
[YUKINOJO]
You idiot.
The Alaya-Vijnana in Barbatos
has its limiter
off for Mikazuki.
What are you thinkin'?
You can't withstand
that much data!
And Mikazuki can take
all of that? Whoa...
[SECURITY GUARD A]
Wait, it's off limits from here.
Huh?
[CAMERAMAN A]
We're the camera crew.
Here to grab equipment
from the launch.
[SECURITY GUARD A]
All right.
[PRODUCER A] You sure
he's all right by himself?
[ORGA]
Don't worry about it.
[PRODUCER A]
Yeah, but--
We can't just fly out in
an unarmed launch, okay?
[KUDELIA]
Excuse me.
But I was wondering if you could
tell me everything you can
about the people who're
working in these colonies.
Huh?
[KUDELIA]
It's important.
Please. I need to know as
much as possible about them.
She's amazing. Really.
But I...
[MIKAZUKI sighs]
[MIKAZUKI] But I can't
help feeling frustrated.
No, please! Stay away!
[GRAZE PILOT A]
Wh-What was that?
[GRAZE PILOT B]
I-It's coming this way!
[OPERATOR A]
An unidentified Mobile Suit
has entered into combat
around Dort 3.
There are 3 Grazes
immobilized.
[COMMANDER A]
The numbers?
[OPERATOR A]
One, sir.
There's only one?
Send the Dort 5 and 6
forces in to support.
Isn't that the Mobile Suit
you were looking for?
[GAELIO growls]
This isn't how I wanted it,
but I can't miss this chance.
Let's go, Ein.
Sir!
[ORGA]
All right!
Now make for the rendezvous
point, and step on it!
[EUGENE]
You got it!
Orga's taking off.
I'll work just a
little more then.
[GRAZE PILOT C]
I got you.
Try dodging!
[GRAZE PILOT C] He blocked
with the manipulator?
[beeping]
That Mobile Suit...
[GAELIO]
This power.
The performance.
It's more than I expected.
Then again, I wouldn't
have pulled this antique
out of our family treasury
if I didn't think it was good!
[MIKAZUKI]
Damn!
[GAELIO]
That Gundam Frame,
it's too much for
someone like you.
Know your place, brat.
[MASKED MAN]
ASW-G-66. Gundam Kimaris.
Gaelio...
He's brought out the Bauduin
family's prized machine.
They're a forgotten legend.
I'm rather amazed
seeing the suits
that once protected the world
as symbols of Gjallarhorn
fighting each other now.
Irony at its very finest.
He took the shots? Why?
That's...
Now I understand
[MIKAZUKI]
You're not getting near it!
No! The launch!
You're not gonna get away!
Your timing couldn't
be better, Chad!
Thanks, Boss.
Home at last.
Sorry to make you worry.
[MERRIBIT]
Just glad you're safe.
For a minute there, I thought
they'd shoot us down
before we even got close.
Well, if it wasn't for Mikazuki,
they might've just succeeded.
Here. You can go right in.
[REPORTER A]
Uh, sure...
Who are they?
[BISCUIT] Oh...
There's a reason they're here.
Hey, what's the big idea?
You guys don't
expect us to help you
fight against
Gjallarhorn, do ya?
No, of course not. Now I
have preparations to make.
Please wait here
until they're finished.
Preparations?
Yeah, I think I have an idea.
[ATRA]
Uh. Wait...
--[explosion]
--[ALL yelp]
They're already here.
Shino, are you ready?!
Yeah! Just say the word, Boss!
Be careful, all right?
[SHINO chuckles]
[SHINO]
Don't worry.
You won't be making ice flowers
bloom for me just yet, Yamagi.
Norba Shino, Ryusei-Go!
Heading out!
[RIDE, YUKINOJO]
Ryusei-Go?
[beeping]
That machine code is from
Lieutenant Crank's Graze.
[SHINO] But it doesn't have
such a lame name anymore!
This suit belongs to me now.
And it's called the Ryusei-Go!
How dare you defile his machine
by painting it with
such a vulgar color!
I won't forgive you!
He moved so fast! Does he
have an Alaya-Vijnana too?
I'm no good against
suits like these.
[GAELIO]
What's wrong?
Can't track me with
your Alaya-Vijnana?
This is the end.
What?!
[MIKAZUKI]
I got you. Now...
[GAELIO]
Let me go, you space rat.
That voice.
Chocolate guy's friend.
I'm Gaelio Bauduin.
[MIKAZUKI]
Gali Gali?
Are you mocking me now?
[MIKAZUKI]
What does it matter?
It's a name that
will disappear soon.
Not so fast.
[GAELIO yelling]
[yelps]
[NOBLISS] I don't understand
what's gotten into McMurdo.
After all, the girl
isn't that valuable.
[beeping]
[NOBLISS]
Hm?
[RECEPTIONIST A]
Mr. Nobliss, you have a message.
Yeah, who is it this time?
[RECEPTIONIST A]
Actually, it's from
Kudelia Aina
Bernstein, sir.
[NOBLISS]
What?
Hm...
[NOBLISS laughing]
[GAELIO] I know that attack was
probably too much for you,
so I'll make it quick!
[AKIHIRO]
Sorry for the wait.
Akihiro? They already
finished it?
Yeah.
Say hello to Gundam
Frame Gusion... Rebake!
Crap. Reinforcements?
[MIKAZUKI] You saved me.
But that Gali Gali is fast.
[AKIHIRO]
Gali Gali? Yeah. Whatever.
I'm not used to
the Alaya-Vijnana yet,
so let's get him together.
He's here.
[growls]
[SHINO yells]
[GAELIO]
Agh! Dammit!
Specialist Major!
No! Sorry, Mikazuki!
It got away!
[EIN]
Major Bauduin!
Ein!
[SHINO]
I don't think so!
[ALL yelp]
[SHINO]
Sorry, you guys.
[EUGENE] You idiot! Quit playin'
around and finish him off!
[SHINO] It's my first time in
this thing. I can't help it!
Um, are they okay?
Well, uh...
[KUDELIA]
They're fine.
[ATRA]
Miss Kudelia!
[REPORTER A]
Are you sure?
[beeping]
[MERRIBIT]
A quantum encrypted message.
Do you know who it's from?
[KUDELIA]
Nobliss Gordon, correct?
Uh... Yes.
The hell'd you do?
[AKIHIRO]
I got ya!
[groans]
Ein!
[EIN] Forgive me. I did
something I shouldn't have...
Look, just--
[GAELIO]
What?
[CAPTAIN A] The main Arianrhod
fleet is coming your way.
Is that?
Mikazuki...
[CAPTAIN A]
You may be a Seven Star,
but if you keep interfering like
this, there will be trouble!
[growls]
Is that right?
[MIKAZUKI]
Shino, are you okay?
[SHINO]
Yeah. For now anyway.
Those're a whole lotta ships.
What do ya say we take off?
Yeah, I have a feeling
they're not gonna let us.
[beeping]
[KUDELIA] My name is
Kudelia Aina Bernstein.
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
Kudelia?
Right now, I am calling out
to every one of you
who can see me on your
television screens.
Is my voice reaching you?
If so, then I beg you to listen.
Because I need to
tell each one of you
what's happening at
the Dort colonies.
And I want you to know
the truth about their people.
[COMMANDER A]
What's going on?
Doesn't the Regulatory Bureau
control all of the
outgoing news content?
Yes, sir. It's supposed to.
Somebody must've pulled some
strings behind the scenes.
[NOBLISS] It took some
guts to try and use me.
Looks like that girl
still has the potential
to turn into something
even greater.
♪
[YAMAGI] When you repair
machines after a battle,
you start smelling all
kinds of things.
There's sweat, blood, and even
some animal-like orders, too.
'Course, I only wait for those
who risk their lives fighting,
so I know that I'll
never smell that way.
And though I'm not
out there with 'em,
when I get a sniff of what
they've gone through,
I realize I have to do my best.
Welcome back, Ryusei-go.
Next time on Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
Episode 18: "Voice."