[YUKINOJO] Move the launches
as soon as they get full.
and make sure to check
the loading order.
[SOLDIER A]
All right!
[SOLDIER B]
Here it comes!
[SOLDIER C]
Headin' your way!
[yelps]
[YUKINOJO]
Careful. Are you all right?
[ATRA]
Thank you, Mr. Yukinojo.
Now, don't force yourself, Atra.
Isn't that too heavy?
No, I'm fine. I carried
a lot heavier stuff
when I worked at
the manager's place.
Jeez, you're pretty
pumped up, aren't ya?
Yeah, you got that right!
Get used to it!
Along with Miss Kudelia,
I'm gonna "do revolution."
[CREW]
Huh?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER A]
What about personal stuff?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER B]
Just the bare minimum, okay?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER C]
Seriously?
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
[KUDELIA grunts]
Uh...
I-I'm sorry.
What's up? You in a hurry?
[gasps]
Yes.
We're getting close to Earth,
so I have things to do.
When we're not even sure
if we'll make it down there
in one piece?
[KUDELIA gasps]
I know we will.
This is Tekkadan.
I'm not worried about that.
I see. Guess you're right.
[KUDELIA]
Um... Uh...
[gasps]
Let's shake hands. Alright?
But it looks like my
hands are dirty again.
[gasps]
It's no problem.
Mine are dirty too.
Dirty with blood
and expectations.
But still. I'm proud
of these hands.
[KUDELIA gasps]
[KUDELIA]
Hm.
[ORGA] All right.
I guess we're ready now.
[MCGILLIS] Good. So let's
proceed as planned.
[ORGA] By the way,
Montag Company, isn't it
about time for you to let us
know what your real name is?
[MCGILLIS]
Montag is fine.
I mean, after all,
it is my last name.
Huh?
[MCGILLIS]
Now, good luck in battle.
--[grunts]
--[door hums]
[KUDELIA]
Boss?
[ORGA]
Hm?
Hey, what's goin' on?
[KUDELIA]
I wanted you to know.
If wasn't for Tekkadan, I would
never have come this far.
So, thank you very much.
Yeah, sure. But this thing
isn't over just yet.
[KUDELIA]
It was such a big hand.
But his body is so small.
Yet, somehow he...
Yes. As we get closer,
I'm sure things aren't
gonna get any easier.
But even so, I ask that
you take me to Earth.
And once we've made it there...
...I will make everyone happy,
no matter what.
I promise you that.
All right. We'll be counting
on you, Kudelia.
[KUDELIA]
You have my word, Fumitan.
♪
[OPERATOR A]
Reaction on Ariadne.
Confirming Ahab Wave.
It matches the
reported ship.
[CARTA] I can't believe
they really came here.
But, I'm glad they did.
[GAELIO]
Carta.
[gasps]
It's Commander Carta.
[GAELIO]
Hm.
[CARTA] Gaelio, we allowed
you to join us,
so try not to get in our way.
Make sure you do
your part, all right?
Well, yeah, of course
I will... Commander.
[CARTA] Oh, by the way, do you
know what happened to him?
[GAELIO]
Who're you talking about?
How can you handle
this operation
when you are so incredibly slow?
I'm talking about
that blonde, arrogant one.
The one who got
engaged to a bed-wetter
to further his status!
The man who's always fiddling
with the front of his hair.
Sounds the same as
she always did.
McGillis is still out
on vacation leave.
He's on Earth with
his fiancée, right now.
[CARTA] On Earth? Then why
didn't he report that to me?
Huh? Well, why would
he think to do that
when you're not his
direct superior?
You have the gall
to make fun of the
Outer Earth Orbit Regulatory
Joint Fleet, too, Gaelio?
What? No. I wasn't
trying to make fun--
[CARTA]
Listen up.
You better get results,
or you'll be severely punished.
You understand?
Wait, punishment?
What're you talking about?
[CARTA grunts]
The Regulatory Bureau says our
fleet is just around for show,
and nothing more.
But soon they'll know
our true strength.
Then, they will never
mock us again.
For we are the Outer Earth
Orbit Regulatory Joint Fleet!
[GUARDS] We are perseverant
and fortitudinous!
[CARTA]
Second from right, too slow.
S-Sorry, forgive me, Commander!
All right. Let's crush
these space-rats!
[CHAD] We've been caught by
the Ariadne like we planned.
Yeah, so far so good.
[EUGENE]
Hey!
Are you guys ready
to kick some ass?
[CHAD]
Huh?
[DANTE]
What's up, Eugene?
[CHAD]
Man, you're fired up...
Damn right I am.
[SHINO hums]
[sighs]
[humming continues]
[EUGENE groans]
Look. Could you please knock
off the pity-party, Eugene?
You're really killing
my mood, here.
Can't help it.
If I mess things up,
everyone in Tekkadan could die.
Huh? No way. Are you nervous?
[EUGENE grunts]
What do you think?
I mean, I am human.
Hey, we all know you
screw up sometimes.
So if worse comes to worst,
we'll just smile and say,
"Oh, it's just Eugene again."
We won't blame you
for getting' us kill--
Don't mess with me!
Uh...
Don't get mad.
Sorry, just seems like you
were getting too worked up.
[grunts]
Yeah, I'm sorry too.
Guess it's kinda funny.
'Cause all this time...
...I've been thinking
about changin' my ways.
Becomin' a real man.
And now's my chance.
Huh?
[EUGENE] I've been entrusted
with Tekkadan's lives.
I've... I've always dreamed
about taking on this role.
There's no room for failure.
That's why...
[SHINO laughs]
[EUGENE]
Why're you laughing?
Sorry, but I never
knew you wanted
to be like Orga that much. Pft!
Huh? What made you think this
has anything to do with him?!
Gimme a break.
[SHINO]
Know what?!
[EUGENE grunts]
[EUGENE]
What was that for?
[SHINO]
Maybe you're right.
You wanna play it cool, huh?
Let's give it a shot.
[EUGENE grunts]
[EUGENE]
Whatever.
I don't need to
hear that from you.
All right, boyss, let's do this!
[DANTE, CHAD]
Yeah!
[GAELIO]
Are you ready to go, Ein?
[EIN] The Maintenance
Chief worked hard.
I see. Looks like this one
made it in time, too, somehow.
Soon, it'll be the
end of those rats.
[EIN]
Yes, sir.
[GAELIO]
By the way.
That woman hasn't
changed at all.
I thought her promotion to a
position like Commander of that
"just for show" fleet would
calm her down a little,
but I guess I was wrong.
How do you know Commander Issue?
We've known each other
since childhood, sadly.
Same with McGillis.
[CARTA]
Come on up, Gaelio.
Carta, we have to go back right
now or Father's gonna be angry.
Who cares about
the stupid party?
You're just a coward,
aren't you, diaper boy?
[gasps]
I do not wear diapers anymore.
But you should,
you bed-wetter!
[CARTA gasps]
How dare you say that to a lady!
The other day at school you...
[CARTA gasps]
Oh?
[GAELIO]
Who's that?
He looks so dirty.
Uh?
[CARTA gasps]
What is it?
[gasps]
[GAELIO]
Hm?
Yeah...
And ever since then...
[EIN]
Specialist Major?
[gasps]
It's nothing. Forget it.
--[alarm blares]
--[EIN, GAELIO gasp]
[CAPTAIN A] The Ahab Wave of the
target ship has been detected.
[GAELIO] Hmph. All right.
Let's go, Ein.
[EIN]
Yes, sir.
To grasp another
person's heart,
and to control their future
actions is rather easy.
Just unveil their past.
By doing so,
you limit their choices,
and make it easy to
predict their next move.
[MCGILLIS] Jealousy, hate,
disgrace, shame...
We are endlessly harassed
by days long gone.
And our supposedly
bright future is wasted
on cleaning up the mistakes
of our foolish past.
[MCGILLIS] It's something
I know all too well.
So, Tekkadan...
...do you think that
the step you're taking
will lead to progress?
Because if you truly believe
in your hearts that it will...
Then show it to me.
Here and now.
[OPERATOR A] Communication
from the commando ship.
Jutland 1 has set up a blockade.
Jutland 2 is also on guard.
[CARTA grunts] It feels like
overkill to dispatch such a
large welcome for one
measly assault ship.
--[radar beeps]
--Contact! They're here!
Send the halt order.
[OPERATOR A] We aren't
receiving any response!
[CARTA]
Give them a crushing blow.
[OPERATOR B] Calling all forces.
Prepare to engage!
Fire!
[CARTA sighs]
All too easy.
[OPERATOR A]
Ahab Wave increasing!
They're closing in!
[CARTA]
What?
[OPERATOR B] Wait. There are now
two Ahab Wave reactions, ma'am.
No way! It can't be!
Are they crazy?
[yells]
[CARTA] Using the ship as
a shield? How barbaric.
Move the flank forces
to the front at once!
Use the Crane Wing Formation
and take them down! Fire!
[grunts]
The Brewers' ship won't be able
to take much more of this!
Then it'll be us next.
All right, we'd better
make the move!
Not yet. We need to get closer!
Come on, we can't
let Orga down!
This isn't the time to
act cool, man, do it!
Chad! Turn control of the
front ship over to me!
Don't be stupid.
You can't control two ships at
once with the Alaya-Vijnana.
Heh. Stop arguing with me.
This is my chance!
[CHAD] Okay, but I'm
not takin' the blame!
[groans]
[CHAD]
Eugene!
[EUGENE grunts, pants]
Now watch this, you bastards!
[gasps]
[growls]
Concentrate! Focus your attack!
[OPERATOR A]
Enemy ship still approaching.
[CARTA grunts]
For we are the Outer Earth
Orbit Regulatory Joint Fl--
[OPERATOR A]
Rear ship changing course!
[OPERATOR B]
Which one do we shoot?
It doesn't matter,
fire at them both!
What are you waiting for,
you fools?!
Shoot them down!
[OPERATOR A gasps]
What?
[OPERATOR C]
Monitor lost!
Data link cut with
friendly ships!
[CARTA] Come on.
What are you looking at?
Just shoot!
[OPERATOR A] Optical Sight
has lost the target.
[OPERATOR B] The LCS is cut.
We can't communicate.
[OPERATOR D] They deployed
Nano-Mirror chaff!
[CARTA gasps]
But I thought that wasn't suited
for use in a combat situation!
Keep your heads!
Now, all ships with
light signals...
...irradiate the whole
area with maximum LCS.
Fire missiles with
time fuses, simultaneously.
Burn away that ancient Chaff.
[OPERATOR B]
The LCS has recovered.
How annoying.
Now reconfirm the
targets' positions.
Hurry up!
Optical Sight has
caught the target again.
Well. It would appear
that even the quickest rats
can't do anything in
this short amount of time.
Where are they?
[OPERATOR B gasps]
They're...
That little trick gave us
all the time we're gonna need
to finish this!
[OPERATOR B]
Gladsheimr.
[gasps]
[EUGENE]
Here we go!
All hands, prepare for impact!
[CREW grunts]
[grunts]
[OPERATOR B] Rescue signal
from Gladsheimr 1.
Orbit negative 2.
At this rate,
it'll fall to Earth!
[CARTA grunts] After the
Mobile Suit forces launch,
head to their rescue.
[EUGENE grunts] I'll leave
the rest to you guys.
Eugene, you did it!
[EUGENE]
Can I ask you one thing?
[CHAD, DANTE]
Huh?
[EUGENE grunts]
Am... I cool?
[DANTE, CHAD gasp]
E-Eugene!
You were awesome
out there, Eugene.
Way to kick ass.
[gasps]
[ATRA]
Are you okay, Miss Kudelia?
Really, sorry. I'm so clumsy.
It's all going as planned.
At least, so far.
Yeah. We shoul--
[BOTH grunt]
[KUDELIA, ATRA scream]
[BISCUIT]
An attack?
[ORGA]
From where?
You found them! Great work!
I've seen how these damn rats do
things ever since I was on Mars.
I'll end it here,
once and for all!
[SHINO yells]
Just leave him to me.
[chuckles]
It's time for a little payback!
[grunts]
[SHINO shouts]
Shino!
[gasps]
[ORGA]
Crap. They're here again!
Akihiro, can you go?
You have to ask?
I have no choice!
Those suits're fast!
[AKIHIRO]
There're so many of 'em!
[grunts]
[AKIHIRO gasps]
You guys!
Sorry for making you wait!
Took us a little while
to change out the armor.
But we'll be sure to make
up for the lost time.
[AKIHIRO grunts]
What 're you two doing here?
[LAFTER] Darling asked us
to lend you boys a hand.
Brother asked you?
[AKIHIRO]
Then that machine is...
If we tried using
Hyakuren out here,
then it'd be the same as
announcing we're in Teiwaz.
[LAFTER] So we gave it brand new
armor and renamed it Rouei.
Not bad, huh?
A-Amazing...
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
It's even faster than before.
[GAELIO] I prepared this
just so I can finally
bring an end to you.
Die with some gratitude!
Yeah, well, I've prepared
something special for you, too.
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
[gasps] It can't be!
Reactive Armor?
[MIKAZUKI] Once we know your
patterns, we can counter them.
[MIKAZUKI]
Thanks, Yukinojo...
[GAELIO]
You damn filthy space rat!
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
[ORGA] Okay. Mika and the
others are doing all right.
Now let's get into
re-entry orbit.
[BISCUIT]
Wait! Shino...
[ORGA gasps]
[SHINO grunts]
[EIN]
This'll make your Alaya-Vijnana
completely useless.
Don't ever underestimate me!
I know Lieutenant Crank must
have offered you a helping hand,
and you turned it away,
didn't you?!
You just brushed it aside
and murdered him!
[SHINO]
Dammit!
[shouts]
[EIN]
You damn brats!
--[radar beeps]
--[EIN gasps]
I've got pride too!
Is that so?
[GAELIO grunts]
[gasps]
[EIN groans]
[grunts]
Gali, Gali...
[ORGA] Sorry Mika,
enemy reinforcements.
[grunts]
[GAELIO]
Ein!
Why?! Why'd you help?
[EIN] I... I'd lost
my pride. But you...
...you gave me the confidence
to come back again.
[GAELIO gasps]
[EIN groans] I couldn't
just leave you to die.
[gasps]
[GAELIO]
Ein!
[OPERATOR E]
Ship 3, you're late.
[OPERATOR 1F] Re-calculate
direction of thrust!
[CARTA] You will pay for
making a fool out of me.
I will teach you,
you space rats,
who's really in charge here!
That's it.
[ROYAL GUARD G]
Straight Snake Formation!
[ROYAL GUARD]
Sturm und Drang!
[ROYAL GUARD G grunts]
[gasps]
You can actually keep
up with me. Not bad.
You kinda remind me of...
Huh?
[MCGILLIS chuckles]
[MIKAZUKI] Wait. You're the
Chocolate Man, aren't you?
[MCGILLIS laughs]
[MCGILLIS]
You noticed it just like that?
Your senses are
quite formidable.
Actually, they're pretty normal.
[SHINO screams]
It's too heavy!
[BISCUIT]
Whose suit is that?
Well it doesn't matter now.
This our last chance.
Get Shino and the others!
We're already caught by gravity.
And they're not going to
be able to break free!
[ROYAL GUARD F] It's too
dangerous to pursue any further.
We'll get burned up!
I can't leave like this.
This is Lady Carta's territory.
They can't be
allowed to escape!
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
You'd better go now.
There are still some things
we need you to do.
[MCGILLIS]
I see.
If you're sure it's gonna be
all right, I suppose I will.
[grunts]
[YUKINOJO] Akihiro, hurry and
lock up the machine now.
You'll be thrown off!
But Mikazuki hasn't boarded yet!
Mikazuki!
Mika! Come back!
[yells]
[ROYAL GUARD G grunts]
[ROYAL GUARD G] We will
not let a bunch of Martian
space rats onto
our glorious Earth!
[groans]
[KUDELIA]
Can't we do something?
[BISCUIT] No! Communication is
cut off during re-entry!
[ATRA]
Mikazuki!
I'm ready for you to show me...
...everything you're capable of.
Your true potential.
So this is Earth's gravity.
Impressive...
[grunts]
[ORGA]
We're going.
[MIKAZUKI]
Where?
[ORGA]
Anywhere but here.
To a better place,
where you and me belong.
[ORGA chuckles]
[MIKAZUKI]
Oh yeah?
[gasps]
What kind of place is that?
[ORGA]
Huh? Well, I'm not sure.
But it's gonna be amazing!
There'll be plenty of food.
And we'll even
have our own beds.
And, uh...
And there'll be, um...
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
[ORGA] But we won't
know till we're there.
Till we can see it
with our own eyes!
Till we see it?
[ORGA]
That's right.
I mean, we've gotta leave
this place, anyway.
Okay. So if I follow you, Orga,
I'll see all kinds
of new things?
[ORGA]
Yeah, so let's go!
[MIKAZUKI gasps]
[MIKAZUKI] That's right.
And I'm ready to see that place.
How about you, Barbatos?
[gasps]
[ATRA sobs]
[KUDELIA]
Mikazuki, this can't be the end.
Those hands of yours
are meant to do
so many more important things!
It's Earth! We made it!
Mikazuki!
[growls]
[gasps]
[gasps, sobs]
[ATRA]
Mikazuki!
[AKIHIRO]
[YUKINOJO]
He made it!
[KUDELIA laughs, sobs]
Thank goodness!
Don't scare us like that,
you stupid jerk.
[MIKAZUKI]
So this is Earth, huh?
The crescent moon... Mikazuki.
♪
[AZEE]
Alright, Naze. I'm taking off.
You took a Sakazuki oath
to be sworn brothers,
so I see them all as
my little brothers, too.
Besides, I'm used to backing
up naughty, reckless guys.
Huh? Don't cheat on you?
Heh. I'd never
do that, you idiot.
Next time on Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
Episode 20: "Brother."