[SHINO grunts]
You gonna be all right?
[SHINO] Yeah, but this is
gonna be really tough...
What if it's impossible?
I mean, maybe we
won't be able to import
the Alaya-Vijnana System the
Brewer's used into this thing.
[SHINO]
Don't give up yet, Yamagi.
But I...
[SHINO] I'll test it out
just as often as you need.
[gasps]
I want it too, you know...
The power to protect
the people I care about...
[YAMAGI]
Shino...
[KUDELIA] I couldn't
get to sleep at all.
Then again...
[KUDELIA] There's no way I could
after something like that...
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
[gasps]
Hey. Good morning.
[KUDELIA]
Uh...
Seriously?
♪
[FUMITAN]
"Everything has been arranged.
Enter port at Dort 2
along with Kudelia."
[sighs]
[KUDELIA]
I want to know.
I need to learn all I can
about the people of Mars.
It's important.
Fumitan, please, I could
really use your help.
Tell me everything.
[doorbell rings]
[FUMITAN]
Miss Kudelia.
Do you have a minute to talk?
What's wrong?
Did something happen to--?
Fumitan. Have you ever--?
Um...
H-Have you ever gone out on
a date with a man before?
[FUMITAN]
Huh?
I've heard that sometimes...
young men will ask women out
even if they don't have
romantic feelings for them.
Is that really true?
But, what if they...
...k... kiss you?
Does that mean
they're serious?
I-Is it okay to think that
maybe they really like you?
Are you saying that
someone kissed you?
[KUDELIA]
No, no! No! Hypothetically.
You know, just as a "what-if."
But if something
like that did happen,
does it mean I should consider
marrying that person?
[FUMITAN chuckles]
Hey, why are you laughing?
Come on. What's so
strange about that?
[FUMITAN clears throat]
[FUMITAN]
My apologies.
If you're curious,
I might suggest
that you simply ask the man
what his true feelings are.
Yeah. Yes, you're right.
[sighs]
I'm sorry. I know this
was kinda sudden,
but I've always felt like
I could talk to you about
anything, you know?
[doorbell rings]
Huh?
Oh, excuse me, Fumitan.
I was just wondering
where Miss Kudelia was.
Is that Atra?
[ATRA]
Oh, hey!
Would you like to go out
to the bridge with me?
Why? What's going on?
We're finally able
to see the colonies now!
[ATRA gasps]
[ATRA]
Is that it straight ahead?
[CHAD]
Yeah, should be.
[ATRA]
Whoa!
We're goin' to the one closest
to us, in the middle, right?
Yeah.
Is it just me or do they
all look exactly alike?
[ORGA] Apparently, these
colonies are a public enterprise
run by the African Union...
They all belong to the
same company called Dort.
[EUGENE]
I see the number up ahead.
We're headin' to Dort 2, huh?
What about that one?
That's, uh...
[BISCUIT]
It's Dort 3.
That's where a lot of factory
owners from Earth live in luxury
inside beautiful homes.
It's also where quite a
few commercial facilities
are located.
[SHINO] Whoa! You really
know your stuff, Biscuit!
Commercial facilities...
Hey, Mikazuki. Uh...
Hm?
[ATRA gasps]
[ATRA]
Wait a minute. That planet.
Is it Earth, guys?
Yeah. Sure is.
It's blue. A lot prettier
than I thought it'd be.
[ATRA]
Yeah. It looks like a jewel.
[SHINO] Really?
'Cause it looks tasty to me!
[EUGENE]
How can a planet look tasty?
Sorry we've gotta make a little
detour before we can get there.
But once we drop off
this cargo from Teiwaz,
we'll be on our way.
Yes, of course. That's a
very important job as well.
Which reminds me. Um, I have
a small favor to ask you.
[ORGA]
What's that?
While all of you are out
there working over on Dort 2,
do you think that it'd be
possible for Fumitan and me
to go to Dort 3?
For what reason?
[ORGA]
Dort 3?
[KUDELIA]
Yes.
If there are commercial
facilities there,
I'd like to get a
little shopping done.
Young Miss, I don't think that--
That's okay with you, right?
I only wanted to
pick up a few thing.
And it's been a long time since
I went shopping anywhere.
Well...
[FUMITAN]
I understand.
Then I will accompany you.
[ATRA]
What?
You're shopping? I'm jealous.
[KUDELIA]
Why don't you join us, Atra?
[ATRA gasps]
Can I really go?
That's fine,
but I don't think you girls
should take off by yourselves.
[ORGA]
Mika, can you go with 'em?
No problem.
Oh, Mikazuki, why's that?
Anything could happen out there,
and I'm not willing to risk it.
'Course, if you're
there with her,
I know she'll
be in good hands.
[BISCUIT]
Hey, Orga.
[ORGA]
Yeah?
You think it'd be okay if
I went with them as well?
[ORGA]
Uh. Sure, why not?
Hey, thanks a lot.
Let's buy a whole bunch
of things, okay, Miss Kudelia?
Uh. Sure...
[ATRA]
Ooh! I can't wait.
Oh, I know. I should wear the
clothes I bought on Saisei.
Th-That'd be nice.
[AZEE] Detailed maintenance
will start up
when we get to the colony.
In the meantime,
looks like you'll be
staying here for a while.
Hey, you're not really gonna
pilot that one, are you?
That's the suit that killed
your little brother, right?
[AZEE]
Lafter.
[AKIHIRO]
It's all right.
I've already made up my mind.
Were there any problems
with the cargo?
Uh-uh. We double-checked
all the containers;
everything seemed
to be accounted for.
Sounds good.
Now, it's your first job
so I'd like to come along
and make sure that all is well,
but unfortunately,
we still have to sell off
the Brewers' stuff.
So we're goin' to the
Teiwaz branch on Dort 6.
Don't let me down, all right?
Just leave it to us.
Well, remember not to mess
around with Gjallarhorn
while you're down there.
Keep your eyes open
around those guys.
'Cause the soldiers they've
got are much better trained
and far more motivated
than the ones in the Outer
Spheres like Mars or Jupiter.
Huh...
Come on. We're not gonna know
anything until we fight 'em.
[AMIDA]
You really don't get it, do you?
We're inside the
Earth Sphere now.
In the Outer Spheres you're used
to, they're basically no rules.
But law and order are
strictly enforced out here.
If you kill someone, you'll
be charged and punished.
[NAZE] Teiwaz may be respected
in the Outer Spheres,
but on Earth, it's no different
than any run-of-the-mill
corporation.
So if you don't
wanna be crushed,
then I would suggest you
behave yourselves.
Got it? Don't cause
any trouble out there.
[EIN]
They're at the Dort colonies?
[GAELIO]
Yeah.
Apparently, they got a call from
the Mustache Man on watch.
Now I'll finally get my
chance to settle things
with those brats.
But, sir, are we allowed
to deploy ships
without receiving prior orders?
We're just using
them for a drill.
I don't see any problem with it.
Besides, we won't have
any other missions
while McGillis is off
on vacation anyway.
It's a chance to get
revenge for your superiors.
Get ready.
Sir.
[ATRA] Oh! I'm really
looking forward to this.
[KUDELIA]
Me, too.
[ATRA] Oh, can we withdraw
money when we get there?
Teiwaz has an affiliated bank
so I think you guys
should be just fine.
[ATRA]
Awesome!
[FUMITAN]
Why? Why did I...?
They're fine. The launch is
safely in route to Dort 3.
Thanks a lot. For helping
us out with this, I mean.
Of course.
All right, let's get movin'!
Contact the
controller for Dort 2.
[beeping]
What is it?
It looks like another ship.
A what?
It's getting closer.
[UNION MEMBER A]
You're Tekkadan, right?
Welcome to Dort 2. We're happy
to have you as our guests.
Please follow our guide.
[ORGA]
Hold on. Do you know us?
[UNION MEMBER A]
Of course.
We've been anticipating
your arrival.
And we're looking
forward to seeing
all the young heroes
face-to-face.
Heroes?
What's that about?
All right, then. Guide us in.
[UNION MEMBER A]
So you're really Tekkadan!
[ORGA]
Uh, yeah.
I'm kinda surprised.
You're a lot younger
than I thought you'd be.
You're only kids.
[EUGENE]
What about it?
Don't underestimate us
just 'cause we're young.
Please don't get the wrong idea.
Can't tell ya how much we were
looking forward to your arrival
and finally getting to
meet you in person.
[UNION MEMBER C] Wait, are
you Kudelia Aina Bernstine?
Huh? No, I'm afraid
I'm not. Sorry, uh--
Kudelia's gone to a different
colony for other matters.
She won't be here.
Oh, really? Ah, that's too bad.
I did think you looked
old for a teenager.
[MERRIBIT]
Uh. Old?
[SHINO] Wait, you know
about Kudelia too?
Oh yeah, of course we do.
Well, I-I mean, after all,
she is the Maiden of Revolution
for the Mars movement.
She's the star of hope
for all of us workers
in the Earth Sphere.
[UNION MEMBER B] Just like
the young band of knights
who're so bravely protecting
her on her journey to Earth.
What's a "band of knights"?
Beats me.
Is it just me, or is
this a little weird?
Thanks so much for coming.
We wanna welcome you
all to Dort 2.
Yeah, thanks for
the hospitality.
With your permission,
would it be all right
if we begin unloading our cargo?
Sure, go right ahead.
Now listen up, guys.
You understand that this is our
first job as members of Teiwaz
so let's some
kick some ass!
[GROUP]
Yeah!
[BISCUIT] This is what
you meant by shopping?
[KUDELIA]
Let me ask you two a question.
When was the last time any
of you washed properly?
Do you remember?
Uh, I think it was maybe...
four or five days ago.
Ew!
To be honest, I've
been kinda concerned.
Inside the ship, there's
a very distinct odor.
[ATRA] Now that you
mention it, it does stink.
When everyone's together,
sometimes I gag a little.
[MIKAZUKI]
Uh...
[BISCUIT]
Do we smell that bad?
[ATRA]
You really do.
In fact, when I go
near Mr. Yukinojo,
it totally makes
my eyes burn.
[KUDELIA]
Hygiene is very important.
So let's buy detergent, cleaning
tools, and clothes for everyone.
How about we clean up
around the ship, too?
[ATRA] Okay, count me in.
I'd be glad to help!
So, what're you lookin' at?
Huh? Well...
When I was a little kid,
it was always a dream
of mine to come here.
What are you talkin' about?
Well, I've never
told anyone this,
but I'm actually from these
colonies originally.
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
[BISCUIT] But it wasn't here.
I lived in the slums of Dort 2.
Mom and Dad used to break
their backs in the factories
day and night.
Guess you could say
we were kinda poor.
Even in the Earth Sphere,
our life was the same as the
people who lived down on Mars.
[UNION MEMBER A] Only a
small handful of the people
who transferred from
Earth have any real money.
Those of us born and
raised in the colonies
might as well be
expendable tools.
We're made to work
for next to nothin'.
And if we ever get injured
and slow down a little,
we get the boot.
And we don't get
any insurance, either.
So we can't afford to get sick.
[UNION MEMBER A]
While the people on Earth
lead their fancy lifestyles
and suck up all the profits.
We've been enduring this
injustice for decades now.
So you're nothin'
but expendable tools...
Sounds a lot like
the time we spent
back in the CGS, doesn't it?
No matter what planet
you're on, it's the same.
The pompous ones are
always scum bags.
Then, a ray of hope came
out of the darkness
and shone down upon
each one of us.
We heard about
Kudelia Aina Bernstein
and the incredible things
she's been doing.
[ALL gasp]
A young woman who's
not only leading
the Mars independence movement,
but also influenced
a powerful magnate
of Earth's economic bloc.
Could there be anything
more exciting than that?
Because of her, we realized
that if we rise up,
we can change this world.
[UNION MEMBER B]
Then we were surprised to hear
that the ones who are
escorting her to Earth
are a group of young men
who're still in their teens.
So that means...
We're the "band of
knights," bro!
[UNION MEMBER B]
That's right.
There's Miss Kudelia,
the Maiden of Revolution,
and Tekkadan,
who fight to protect her.
You guys are a symbol
of hope to all of us.
[EUGENE] I see. Guess that
explains the warm welcome.
[SHINO]
Hope, huh?
Heh. I could get used to this.
In any case, I find it
more than a little strange
that a new company
like Tekkadan's
already known all
the way out here.
How'd you find out about
us in the first place?
Oh, our supporter told us.
Who might that be?
[RIDE] Hey, Boss, I finished
unloading everything.
Good work. Now go ahead
and get back to the ship.
[RIDE]
Will do.
Can you please confirm that
all cargo is accounted for?
Okay, I'd be glad to.
[MIKAZUKI] You've got an
older brother, Biscuit?
[ATRA]
Huh?
[BISCUIT]
Yeah.
But it's been a long time
since the two of us
have seen each other.
Back when our mom and dad
got into an accident and died,
Cookie, Cracker, and I were
adopted by our grandmother,
and went to go live
with her on Mars.
My big brother was
going to school
when all of this happened.
He was smart and taken in
by a company executive.
We haven't kept in touch since.
Wonder if he's still in Dort 3.
Why don't you try
givin' him a call?
Uhh...
Yeah, but if I were to call him
up all of a sudden like that,
it might freak him
out, you know?
Now stop making excuses!
Huh?
[ATRA] You need to let him
know that you're here!
He's your big brother. I'm sure
he wants to see you again too.
A-Atra...
[KUDELIA]
I think she's right.
If you don't at least try to
see him before we leave here,
you might end up regretting it.
[ATRA]
Like Mr. Akihiro.
I'm sure he wishes
he could've spent
more time with his brother.
Please contact him.
All right?
[phone ringing]
[SAVARIN]
What is it?
[SUBORDINATE A] We just
received a call for you.
Somebody saying
he's your brother.
My brother?
Put him through.
[BISCUIT]
Um, hey, Savarin?
I-It's me, Biscuit.
You're kidding.
Is it really you, Biscuit?
[BISCUIT]
Y-Yeah. That's right.
I'm working for an organization
called Tekkadan now.
[SAVARIN]
Tekkadan?
[BISCUIT]
Um, Yeah.
And I'm actually
out here on Dort 3
taking care of some business.
So, uh... if it's not
too much trouble,
could we maybe meet
up for a little while?
Savarin, you still there?
[SAVARIN]
Uh. Uh...
I'm sorry. I was just surprised
because this is so sudden.
How 'bout this?
[BISCUIT]
Mh-hm. Mh-hm.
Okay, I got it.
I'll see you later then.
He agreed to meet with me.
[ATRA]
Oh, that's great!
[BISCUIT]
Mh-hm.
You don't seem very
happy about it.
No, I'm happy. It's just...
The two of us live in
such different worlds now.
I'm not sure how
to talk to him.
I'm sorry. Hope I didn't
cause you any trouble.
No, not at all. I'm probably
thinking about it too much.
[ATRA]
Want me to come along?
Huh?
[ATRA] Wouldn't that make things
easier for the two of you
if I'm there?
Uh, well, maybe, but...
Mm! Okay, let's do it.
That way it might not feel
quite as awkward... Oh...
[KUDELIA]
Hm?
[ATRA]
I'm sorry, Miss Kudelia.
Would you mind if I left the
rest of the shopping to you?
Uh. No, of course not.
[UNION MEMBERS gasping]
[UNION MEMBER A] After all this
time, it's finally gonna start.
[UNION MEMBER B]
I can't wait.
Our years of endurance
are finally paying off.
[EUGENE]
Hey, isn't that...?
A Mobile Worker?
What's going on here?
This was the cargo
we were transporting?
[MERRIBIT] Uh, I-I thought it
was only industrial supplies.
[UNION MEMBER C]
Whoa! Amazing!
This is even more
than I expected.
[SHINO]
Okay, this is crazy.
Why didn't they tell us
about this stuff?
[MERRIBIT]
I'll check the order form.
Hey, what're you guys
plannin' to do here?
[UNION MEMBER B]
Hm?
Haven't you heard?
Surely our supporter told you
that we needed your help.
I mean, that's why you brought
us all this firepower, isn't it?
Supporter? We were only
doing what we were--
Nobody said anything
about weapons!
Who have you been talkin' to?
I-I don't know the name.
They just told us they
were Kudelia's proxy.
What?
[UNION MEMBER A] They said
she's ready to get going
and start a rebellion.
Not just on Mars
as we once thought,
but in every other sphere, too!
[UNION MEMBER B]
Then we were assured
that all of the necessary
arms and ammo we'd need
to help see it through would be
provided by her via Tekkadan.
Doesn't make any sense.
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
[UNION MEMBERS shouting]
Now what?
It's Gjallarhorn!
[SOLDIER A]
Nobody move!
Drop your weapons and raise
both hands so we can see 'em!
[SOLDIER A] Mobile Workers
for combat, arms, and ammo.
Looks like the
report was true.
[UNION MEMBER B]
Report?
[SOLDIER A] An illegal
transaction's going on here.
Hey, wait a minute,
we were only--
[SOLDIER A]
I don't want your excuses!
How in the hell are we
gonna out of this one?
[ORGA grunts]
[SOLDIER A]
Did you hear me? Hurry up.
[ORGA]
This doesn't look good...
[SOLDIER A]
You too!
[SOLDIER B]
Now, let's get movin'!
[SOLDIER A]
Damn you.
This is something
we have to do!
Crap, the fighting
already started!
Why're they doing this?
Dammit. Let's go!
Where are we going?
Keep your head down!
You Gjallahorn bastards!
Those bastards!
Don't shoot.
Remember what Naze told us.
Come on, Orga.
We can't just sit here.
[beeping]
[MERRIBIT]
Boss? What's going on?
[ORGA]
Get the ship out now!
What?
[ORGA] We're caught in
the middle of a skirmish
with Gjallarhorn.
Tekkadan's ship cannot be here.
Is that the boss?
What's wrong?
[ORGA]
Now, move it.
Understood.
Oh, and I have
something to report.
The client for the shipment
appears to be a company
called GN Trading.
Don't think I've ever
heard of them before.
Gotta go. I'm leavin'
the rest up to you.
[MERRIBIT]
Yes, Sir.
[MIKAZUKI]
You're buying more?
[KUDELIA]
Y-Yes. But I'm almost finished.
M-Mikazuki.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
What is it?
[KUDELIA]
Well... the... the k...
Huh?
K-- Clothes. We need
to buy some more.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm? Then let's get it over with.
[FUMITAN] "Kudelia will become
central to the rebellion
within the colony, and be shot
by a Gjallarhorn assassin.
We have already
laid the groundwork."
What's the matter with me?
Why did I disobey my orders?
Kudelia...
To me... she's nothing, but...
[MERRIBIT]
Hammerhead , please respond.
This is the Isaribi .
Come in, Hammerhead .
[NAZE sighs]
What's wrong, darling?
Those Tekkadan idiots have gone
and caused problems already.
Can you believe it?
[SOLDIER A]
Pull back, men!
[SOLDIERS]
Retreat!
[UNION MEMBER B]
Look! We got 'em on the run!
We beat them back!
[UNION MEMBERS cheering]
[ORGA]
This thing isn't over yet.
[UNION MEMBER A]
Huh?
They'll be back
before you know it.
And they'll bring even more
troops than you can count.
I know you're
right about this,
but it's far too late for
us to turn back now.
We have to fight them,
head-on, and win.
You've got that right.
Let's go for it.
We can do it.
Are they all out of
their minds?
Look at 'em...
What're we gonna
do now, Orga?
Don't know
But it better be good.
♪
[MASKED MAN]
Nicely done.
Heh. I now have a toy I can
play with as often as I want.
The moment I put
on this mask,
I will assume the role
of a completely different man.
Maybe I should change
the way I talk, too.
Hmm...
Um... never mind...
Next time on Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
Episode 15:
"Trail of Footprints."