[MIKAZUKI grunts]
[AKIHIRO] Hey. I'm gonna
get outta here, okay?
[MIKAZUKI]
All right.
You working tomorrow?
Yeah. Early.
Strange... huh?
[AKIHIRO]
Hm?
That we're all working
together again.
It's routine.
There's nothing strange
about it to me.
Right.
If you say so.
[BOY SOLDIERS grunting]
[RIDE grunts]
[SHINO] Come on!
Quit movin' like old ladies!
[BOY SOLDIERS] Yes sir.
[TODO sighs]
Damn brats.
[TODO] Pickin' a fight
with Gjallarhorn?
Yeah, you might as well
dig your own grave.
They've controlled this
world for centuries
and you think we can take 'em?
How stupid can you be?
Man! This is it! We're dead!
[BISCUIT] Oh hey.
How's it goin', Todo?
[ORGA] Weren't you gonna
go to the meeting, too?
Oh! Sure! I'll be right there.
You cocky bastards
[ORGA]
We need to find a guide.
[BISCUIT] Do you think there's
a company that would accept us?
[TODO]
Heh.
There might be a way
to use these idiots.
♪
[BISCUIT] First, we'll go
to the low-orbit station.
That's where we'll meet
up with our guide ship.
Then we'll transfer
to our ship
in geosynchronous orbit and
proceed onward to Earth.
But, why do we need
a guide there?
Well, normally,
all the main routes to
and from Earth are under
the strict control
of Gjallarhorn.
And since you're
their target,
it wouldn't be smart to
transport you in plain sight,
so we need a backdoor.
Our plan is to use a
route that doesn't cross
with any paths the Gjallarhorn
are watching over,
but it's gonna be
kinda complicated.
Plus, none of us
have been to Earth,
so a guide's our only option.
These routes are
divided territories,
so we might have to deal
with those civilian outfits.
[TODO clears throat]
I think the safest and surest
bet would be the Orcus Company.
As a matter fact,
I've known the CEO for years.
I can contact him any time.
Now, don't tell me you
actually trust this scumbag.
[TODO] That's harsh!
We're brothers! Comrades!
[grunts]
Hey, Don't sweat it.
If he screws up, he knows
what'll happen to him.
Don't you?
[whimpers] I hear you, boss.
Loud and clear.
You say you have
your own ship?
[BISCUIT] That's right.
We have the CGS ship
Will-O'-the-Wisp ,
Docked at Hakobune.
Hakobune? I-I've heard of it.
Isn't that one of the
civilian space ports?
[BISCUIT] Yeah. But legally,
we can't use it yet,
so we need to register the ship
as Tekkadan property, asap.
Well, I've got Akihiro and
Dexter takin' care of that.
What else?
Mikazuki and Yukinojo are
running maintenance and
repairs on the Mobile Workers
and Mobile Suits now,
but the actual departure
date will depend entirely
on the negotiation
with Orcus.
At this point, we can't afford
to wait much longer.
It gets real
from here on out.
It's Tekkadan's
first official job.
[TODO chuckles]
I gotta admit,
your subordinates looked like
they were pretty run
down out there.
Is that so?
[GAELIO] I think they
were having a hard time
keeping up the pace,
to be honest
I suppose that's the
problem with having
an excellent
superior like you.
I'll be careful.
[GAELIO] Hm. I'm sure it'll
surprise "you-know-who"
after all the steps he
took to buy more time.
[CORAL] I see the two of
you have gotten up early,
Specialist Major Fareed,
Specialist Major Bauduin.
Speak of the devil.
I hope the morning is
treating you well, Major.
So, how is the
work progressing?
Oh, that's right!
Our blunder made it impossible
to organize the data for you.
I'm sorry. It must've been
a chore to even look at it.
[MCGILLIS] No. Our examination
has gone on without a hitch.
We should be
finished soon enough.
[gasps]
[MCGILLIS]
No need to worry.
We'll report our
findings on schedule.
[CORAL] O-Oh, I see.
That's good to hear.
[MCGILLIS] By the way,
there was one piece of data
that caught our attention.
[gasps]
And what would that be?
[MCGILLIS] Apparently,
one company was sent out,
but failed to
return to base.
Ah, yes. They're out
subduing a riot as we speak.
[GAELIO] A riot?
The independence movement?
It's just the citizens
venting their frustrations.
There've been so many,
it's hard to keep up.
I heard rumors of
the riots on Earth.
But, I had no idea a full
company was required.
They must be quite a handful.
[gasps]
Yes, well...
I should get out of your way.
I have duties to return to.
[GAELIO chuckles]
[CORAL] By the way, is there
anything I can do for you?
[GAELIO]
Such as?
[CORAL] I could make your
stay more pleasant.
This may not be much,
but it could make
your trip worthwhi--
Is this a bribe? If so,
I'll arrest you where you stand.
[gasps]
[MCGILLIS] Watch yourself,
Major Coral Conrad.
You're so mean.
[CORAL grunts]
How dare they
make a fool of me!
This is all Crank's fault.
If he hadn't disobeyed my orders
and failed the mission...
Tsk. That useless,
good for nothing fool.
[YUKINOJO]
Hm?
[ORGA]
Mika! How's it lookin?
Well, I think it's okay. Probly.
That good, huh?
Can we take the
Mobile Suit with us?
[YUKINOJO]
I don't know for sure.
[BISCUIT]
What?
[YUKINOJO] I'm a Mobile
Worker specialist,
not an antique dealer, guys.
And this machine's
several hundred years old.
A relic from the Calamity War.
That one's newer and it
runs better. Take it.
[ORGA] Come on, Old Man,
don't make me beg ya.
All right, fine. I'll do
as much as I can with it.
I wonder if
Akihiro's all right.
[ORGA] Talk to me.
Why are we out here?
So, you found this?
Uh-huh. It's the info
about your work contract.
You can thank Biscuit.
And you're just
giving it to me?
You know what
it represents, don't you?
Human Debris.
It's legal proof that you're
all the property of Maruba.
But, if it's gone,
you're free, aren't ya?
Do you even know what
handing that over--
[ORGA] It means you guys
don't belong to anybody now.
I'm not lookin' for gratitude,
so do whatever you want.
But, if you're stayin',
I'll protect ya'.
You will? You'd do that
for garbage like us?
[chuckles]
[ORGA]
'Course I would.
So you ready to make our mark?
We'll see.
Hey! Let's do this.
[DANTE, CHAD]
Sure.
I think someone
needs to calm down.
It's just paperwork.
I managed to get
ahold of Orcus.
It took some doing, but he
agreed to guide us to Earth.
Yeah? How much do they want?
[TODO sighs] Forty-five percent
of what we're getting paid.
That's one hell of
a service charge.
We don't have much
of a choice, do we?
You've got to be kiddin' me!
Forty-five percent for
guide work's a rip off!
Todo, your sorry ass better
not be takin' a kick-back.
If you don't like it,
you handle negotiations.
What'd you say?
Now, now...
We still need to decide who's
gonna go to Earth with us.
[EUGENE] What's everyone
else supposed to do?
Orga and I talked it over.
We can still sell the stuff
from the battle. And there's
always the usual farming work
to float us--
I shoulda known
this would happen.
How boring...
I'm sorry, were you
expecting some excitement?
Legitimate jobs are
always dull. You know that.
[EUGENE]
Well, don't you think escorting
Kudelia will be kinda risky?
Yeah, but that's different.
After all, she's a celebrity.
If we can manage to
get her to Earth safely,
the Tekkadan name will
spread like wild fire.
Maybe it'll bring
in some more jobs,
We might be able to
lead a decent life
instead of
just scrapin' by.
There's definitely some risk
involved, but it's worth it.
But, we've got more ridin'
on this than money.
Our whole future
depends on it.
Think so, huh?
[TODO] Hmph. I wouldn't bank
on that future just yet, boy.
Yummy!
Hey, keep it down, Shino!
[SHINO]
Huh?
So, whatcha drawin'?
Wouldn't you like to know?
[TAKAKI]
Come on. Show me.
[RIDE]
Back off! It's a secret.
[TAKAKI]
You're so lame.
[RIDE]
Now, go bug someone else.
Why aren't you eating, Miss?
'Cause I've realized how
weak I am... and helpless.
[NOBLISS]
The funds you requested
have been wired to the
designated account.
Please confirm it.
It's there. Thank you.
[NOBLISS]
My pleasure.
Though I must say,
I'm surprised.
Your decision was
not an easy one.
You're quite brave, my lady.
[KUDELIA]
You're too kind.
[NOBLISS]
Her young warriors in tow,
the war goddess rushed
into the jaws of death,
ready to build an eternal
paradise atop their corpses.
[gasps]
[NOBLISS] It's like a tale
from mythology, isn't it?
I knew my confidence in you
wasn't misplaced, my young hero.
[SHINO]
Another bowl, please!
Those boys...
I'm afraid I'm gonna rob
them of their happiness.
[SHINO] Eat up! It'll put
some hair on your chest!
But despite that fear,
I still...
[MIKAZUKI]
You're lookin' upset again.
[KUDELIA]
Mikazuki. It's nothing...
I think I'm gonna go out
after I finish eating.
Do you wanna tag
along with me?
[KUDELIA]
Huh?
[GAELIO] It doesn't get
more barren than this.
Is there a reason
we're in this dump?
Kudelia Aina Bernstein.
No one knows where she is now.
I know that name.
The one responsible for the
Noachis July Assembly?
[MCGILLIS] That's the one.
Just before we left Earth,
I heard rumors that she
was negotiating with
the Arbrau government
on her own.
[GAELIO]
What? I can't believe that.
Negotiating with Earth's
economic bloc
should be impossible for someone
who's from the Outer Sphere.
[GAELIO]
Hm?
What am I looking at?
[MCGILLIS] I've received reports
that a battle took place here
a few days ago.
And, before that occurred,
Kudelia's father,
Norman Berstein went up and
paid our friend Coral a visit.
I see...
[gasps] You think Major Coral
had her targeted, don't you?
Then, that means the missing
company must have come out here.
Capturing her would put
them in some good graces.
Especially with the
Regulatory Bureau.
And our little inspection
wouldn't even make them
break a sweat.
[RIDE grunts]
[sighs]
[ORGA]
Hey! Be careful up there!
Yeah, I know!
What's up?
I'm not really sure.
It's something Orga
asked him to do.
[KUDELIA]
So... Where are we?
Sakura's cornfield.
And, who's that?
She's my grandmother.
But I still don't understand
why you wanted to bring me here.
[ATRA]
Mikazuki!
It's good to see you!
[KUDELIA]
Oh, hello, Atra!
I didn't know you were here.
[ATRA] Yeah. So...
What brings you here?
[COOKIE]
Brother! Mikazuki! Hi!
Hey!
[COOKIE, CRACKER giggle]
[CRACKER gasps]
Kudelia's here too.
[COOKIE]
Oh, yeah...!
[CRACKER]
Can you cut vegetables now?
Eh? Well, yes... Sort of.
[SAKURA]
About time.
Hey, Sakura.
Is this all of you?
Yeah.
Fine. Then let's get started.
The days a wastin'.
Right.
[BOTH grunt, giggle]
[BISCUIT] Follow me. We have
some extra clothes you can use.
So you brought
Kudelia along, too, huh?
[MIKAZUKI]
Mm-hm.
[ATRA sighs]
Hey... That's...
Huh?
Oh! That's right.
This is the one you
made for me, isn't it?
Um... Yeah.
It's supposed to be
a good luck charm.
Just like mine.
Yeah. Thank you, Atra.
[gasps]
[sighs]
Look, why don't we just
interrogate Coral?
It'd be a lot less boring.
It would also be
a waste of time.
We need strong
evidence on our side.
[GAELIO]
Fastidious as usual.
Well, it is my duty.
[GAELIO] It's not easy
being an inspector, is it?
By the way, I'm gonna get
in touch with my sister
later on tonight.
You should join.
Almiria?
She hasn't seen you in a while,
and it's driving
her crazy, ya' know?
Come on. She might
be nine years old,
but she's still your fiancée.
Even though you
didn't choose her.
[MCGILLIS] It's fine.
She's my friend's sister.
[GAELIO]
Don't fool yourself...
[MCGILLIS] I wouldn't dream
of it, "big brother".
[GAELIO gasps]
[gasps]
[COOKIE, CRACKER]
Yay!
[BISCUIT] Hey! Watch where
you're going, okay?
[gasps]
[KUDELIA giggles]
[CRACKER]
Look, there's another one!
[gasps]
[COOKIE]
I got it!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[yelps]
[gasps]
Watch your step.
[KUDELIA]
Right. Sorry.
So, um...
...Thank you.
What a lovely place.
When I'm outside
and working with my hands,
It really helps clear my mind.
It's so refreshing.
Great. Glad to hear it.
[gasps]
Then, is that why I'm here?
So I can feel better?
How much do you think that
crop in your hand is worth?
[KUDELIA]
Uh...
For one ear of corn?
Ah, about 200 galars?
50 galars a bunch.
[KUDELIA gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
Cheap, right?
They're mostly used as
raw material for biofuel.
Without Biscuit's salary,
Sakura wouldn't be able to
keep this place running.
It's the same for just
about everyone here.
They have debts to pay
and mouths to feed,
so they get pretty desperate.
They put their bodies
on the line to live.
You ever heard of Human Debris?
[KUDELIA]
Yeah, I think so.
They're people who've been
traded for money, right?
Yeah, for next to nothing.
Do you remember Akihiro
back at the base?
He and the other guys he hangs
out with are just like that.
And even if they become free,
getting a decent job
would be hard.
Well... I guess we've
got that in common.
But, we're back
in the game now.
And that wouldn't be the case
if you hadn't come along.
Means a lot. Thanks.
[gasps]
[grunts]
Aren't you worried, Atra?
She'll take Mikazuki away.
[gasps]
[CRACKER, COOKIE giggle]
[ATRA]
Now hush!
[CRACKER, COOKIE giggle]
[BISCUIT]
Hey, Cookie, Cracker.
Can you take Kudelia's
basket to Grandma?
Sure! No problem.
Then we'll take it away!
Jeez.
[CRACKER]
We're gonna get a basket!
[COOKIE]
Think fast!
--[metalic screech]
--[COOKIE, CRACKER scream]
[BOTH gasp]
What was that?
[GAELIO] Oh, no.
Are you two all right?
--[MIKAZUKI growls]
--[GAELIO groans]
What the...?
[BOTH whimper]
Mikazuki!
[CRACKER]
Stop! It's not what you think!
[COOKIE]
Let him go! Please!
He... Help me!
[SAKURA] That's enough of
that you boneheaded oaf.
What happened?
We ran in front of them
without thinking.
They turned to make sure
we wouldn't get hit.
--[MIKAZUKI gasps]
--[GAELIO coughs]
[MCGILLIS] We were careless too.
Let me apologize.
[BISCUIT]
Hey! Is everyone all right?
[ATRA] Are you okay?
What happened, Mikazuki?
I was so worried.
[CRACKER]
Sorry...
[COOKIE]
We're okay.
[ATRA]
Oh, thank goodness.
Come with me. Now.
Huh? But...
[GAELIO coughs]
Guess I... was wrong.
Hey, you all right?
Your temper's out
of control. Be careful.
Right. My fault.
I'm not the one you should
apologize to, Moron.
Um... Really sorry 'bout this.
Not yet, but you will be!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[GAELIO grunts]
What's your deal, farm boy?
And what's that on your back?
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
An Alaya-Vijnana System.
[GAELIO]
A what?
[MCGILLIS]
A bio-organic device
that's surgically implanted
into the human body.
I'd heard that they were
still being used out here.
You put that thing
inside your...?
[gags]
Uh, what's up?
[MCGILLIS] I'm terribly sorry I
put you through such a scare.
This isn't much,
but I do hope you can
accept it as an apology?
[BOTH gasp]
[COOKIE]
Apology...
[CRACKER]
...accepted!
Thank you.
[MCGILLIS] You should see
a doctor, just in case.
If there's an
outstanding bill,
feel free to call the
Gjallarhorn Mars Branch.
Give them my name.
Major McGillis Fareed.
Uh... Okay.
[MCGILLIS] Before we go,
may I ask you something?
Sure, what is it?
There was a battle here.
It occurred within
the last few days.
Have any of you noticed
anything unusual?
Now that you mention it,
I remember hearing some
pretty intense shooting
two or three days ago.
But there's a paramilitary
organization nearby,
so it might have been
them training, right?
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah.
[MCGILLIS] I see. Thank you
for your help. You.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
[MCGILLIS]
You have some amazing moves.
Did you train somewhere?
Yeah. Here and there...
[MCGILLIS]
Interesting.
You'd make a great soldier.
[grunts]
[FUMITAN]
They're finally leaving.
You alright?
[KUDELIA grunts]
[sighs]
Close one. They didn't
seem to know too much
about our fight the other day.
Well, maybe Gjallarhorn
has factions?
Guess we got lucky.
Uh, Mikazuki...?
[DEXTER] You're positive this is
the name he wanted registered?
[AKIHIRO] Yeah. 'Cause the
boss named it himself.
From now on, he doesn't want
anything to do with the CGS.
I rather liked
Will-O'-the-Wisp .
What a shame.
[AKIHIRO]
It's Isaribi now.
[MCGILLIS] The farmhand
was telling the truth.
There's a group.
Paramilitary. Called CGS.
They used to run this place.
I noticed the past-tense.
The companies' name
and ownership
changed hands recently.
They're Tekkadan now.
So I've heard.
[GAELIO]
What are you thinking?
Was it just the name
they wanted to erase?
Or something more?
[BISCUIT gasps]
[gasps]
Hey! Great timing!
What do you think?
[BOY SOLDIERS chattering]
[gasps]
[BISCUIT gasps]
What is it?
It's the symbol of Tekkadan.
I've been sketching
different ideas for it
since this morning.
Hey, not too shabby, kid.
It's a fish, huh?
Huh?!
It's a flower, dumbass!
[SHINO]
What? I don't see it.
It's pretty damn good, right?
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm.
[ORGA]
Mika.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
[ORGA] It's ours. So let's
make sure we protect it.
[SHINO, RIDE shouting]
[TODO] Right. Yeah.
Don't you worry,
I can handle it.
Just make sure you
don't leave me hanging.
Heh.
Adults are terrifying, kids.
And when I'm done,
you won't ever forget it.
♪
[BISCUIT] I trust those
Gjallarhorn guys
about as far as I can throw 'em.
Cookie! Cracker! Cut it out!
If you keep eating all
of that chocolate,
you won't have any room
for dinner tonight!
Do you wanna get cavities?
Too much of that stuff'll
just make you fat!
Then again, I'm not
really one to talk, am I?
[BISCUIT chuckles]
[BISCUIT]
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron Blooded Orphans,
Episode 5:
"Beyond the Red Sky."