[NAZE] Sorry about this.
I kept talkin' a big game,
but then we ran
into some pirates,
and look at the
state we're in now.
Ah, cut it out, Brother.
It's just a cheap fight
some thugs picked with us,
that's all.
So what do ya you think
we should do about it?
Well, they might be thugs,
but that doesn't mean
I wanna let 'em slide.
Yeah. Same here.
Guess it's settled, then.
It's time to teach all those
little punks a lesson about
goin' up against us.
[TAKAKI]
Oh, great.
I can't believe I'm so
useless at a time like this.
Don't talk like that.
Right now, your job is to
focus on getting better.
She's right, man. Just relax
and get some rest, okay?
But I...
The boss says they're gonna
deal with it, so stop worrying.
[MERRIBIT]
I think that's best.
You can't rest properly
if you're on edge.
[RIDE]
Hey, ya hear that?
Even Miss Merribit
agrees with me.
[TAKAKI]
Ride I really--
[RIDE] Look. Wouldja go
back to sleep already?
[NAZE] I didn't think
finding the Brewer's ship
would be this hard.
We've sent our extended
range Hyakuri out on patrol
several times already,
but we haven't seen so
much as a shadow.
You mean they can see us,
but we can't see them?
But how is that
even possible?
And how are they
keeping track of us?
Our ship is carrying
Ahab Reactors.
Without any Adriadne signals,
it should be impossible
to locate us.
And the fact that they demanded
Kudelia raises more questions.
They know things
about our ships,
and even the path we're taking.
Smells like a rat to me.
Only Teiwaz knew our route.
At least, that's what I thought.
Is that right?
Our own navigation officer
came up with it by herself.
Of course, we logged it in to
Teiwaz before we left Saisei.
Then if our info was leaked,
it would have to have come
from someone back there.
[BISCUIT] Could something
like that really happen?
Once an organization gets
as big as we are,
it's not that easy to monitor
everything that goes on.
So the Brewers could be
waiting to ambush us
at any point along
our flight path.
Then why don't we just
change our course?
We could do that,
but then we'd miss our
chance to get back at them.
[BISCUIT]
So what do you suggest?
If that bloated freak
is lying in wait for us,
there are several ways
we could handle it.
[YUKINOJO] Okay. I'll take
a look at it for ya.
Thanks, Old Man.
[exhales]
It's too late, Akihiro.
♪
[BISCUIT]
According to Ms. Amida,
the point where the Brewers
are expected to spring
their ambush on us is
somewhere around...
...here.
I see. The Debris Zone.
[BISCUIT] Yeah. After the
Calamity War came to an end,
the remains of Mobile Suits
and other military ships
collected there.
A passage runs through it
almost like a secret corridor.
[CHAD] Why has all the debris
clumped together like that?
[BISCUIT] Ahab Reactors have
a fairly long shelf life.
Many of them are still
perfectly operational.
[CHAD] So the gravity
from the reactors
is attracting the debris.
I can't believe they still
work after hundreds of years.
I don't get it. Why are the
reactors creating gravity?
For real?
The reason we're able
to maintain gravity
aboard this ship is,
because of our Ahab Reactor.
--[EUGENE grunts]
--[KUDELIA] Huh?
Wow! I had no idea.
Seriously?
Forgive me, Miss Kudelia.
I should have explained things
to you in much greater detail.
[KUDELIA]
Oh, no...
Anyway the unstable gravity
that's created by the reactors
is what keeps ordinary ships
from attempting to pass
through the corridor.
[ORGA] Well, obviously, the Ahab
Wave interference is huge.
It's impossible for anyone to
detect the enemy's position
in that.
But why would we incorporate
such a dangerous spot
into our flight path?
Because Teiwaz are the
ones who first discovered
and mapped out the
route to begin with.
Not only does it serve
as a shortcut to Earth,
but it's also incredibly useful
for highly secretive jobs
like the ones we have.
Look, if we know they're
hiding out there,
then why don't we just
attack them first?
[CHAD] Wait. Head on?
That's what they're hoping for.
No. We shouldn't do that
even if we wanted to.
Average ships can't fly
through the Debris Zone.
It'd be like trying to hit a
bullseye with our eyes closed.
[gasps]
But it shouldn't be a problem
for space rats like us.
You've got a point there.
Okay, but... how can you
be sure that the Brewers
are really gonna be out there?
Yeah, good point. the enemy may
think that we'd never try it
and completely avoid the
Shoal Zone all together.
So we'll have Lofter's Hyakuri
with extended flight range,
and Mikazuki's Barbatos
equipped with a booster,
fly in first, and act as scouts.
They'll think the Isaribi
and the Hammerhead will be
following closely behind,
and that's our advantage.
By using a long-range machine,
we'll confuse them.
Their sense of distance
will be thrown off.
[BISCUI] While they're
distracted by what's behind
Mikazuki and Lofter's Suits,
we should be able
spring our own ambush.
[door hums]
[AKIHIRO]
You're goin' first, right?
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah.
[AKIHIRO]
When they come out...
...and if my younger
brother is with them...
[grunts]
If Masahiro's there...
I want you to...
[MIKAZUKI]
I know.
I'll go easy on him and
try to buy a little time
until you can
get there, all right?
--Mika--
--[MIKAZUKI] But...
...if I'm in a bad situation,
I can't make you any promises.
I'm sorry...
...but I'll try.
Alright.
Thank you.
[ATRA]
Oh! Mikazuki.
[MIKAZUKI gasps]
Thank goodness.
We made it in time.
Here..
[MIKAZUKI]
What is it?
It's your lunch. Kudelia and
I made it for you.
I-I helped a little.
But honestly, it was Atra
who did most of the work.
I'll be waiting here with
even more, later on.
So make sure to come
back in one piece.
Be careful out there.
[MIKAZUKI]
Okay.
[YUKINOJO]
Hm...
Docking with booster, completed.
[LAFTER] Gonna be just the
two of us for a while.
Now, let's do this.
[MIKAZUKI] Sorry to get you
involved in all uh this, Lafter.
[LAFTER]
Hey, don't worry about it.
Besides, aren't you rescuing
Akihiro's brother?
Once I heard that,
there's no way I could just
sit back and let you go solo.
[FUMITAN]
Barbatos and Hyakuri
are on their
second acceleration.
Good. Then it's
our turn to move!
[CREW]
Yes, sir.
[MASAHIRO]
Hm? Where'd you get that?
[BREWER A grunts]
No way. We had extra?
It's Pedro's. Guess the staff
left it here by mistake.
I see... Sorry, man.
Yeah, I know it sucks...
...but maybe Pedro's been
reborn somewhere better.
What're you talkin' about?
Well uh...
I heard that's what happens
whenever humans pass away.
They don't stay dead.
They get to come back.
[BREWER A]
But, how does that work?
[BREWER D] They're born
from their mom's belly
and then they become
babies all over again.
They forget everything and get
a chance to redo their life.
But that's only for humans,
isn't it? Not us Debris.
We die. That's all there is.
[BREWERS sigh]
We don't know for sure, though.
If I'm reborn, I'll be rich and
get to eat steak every--
[KUDAL]
So you want to be reborn, huh?
[BREWER A gasps]
[KUDAL] No problem! We can try
it right now, if you like.
--Well?
--[BREWER A grunts]
[KUDAL] You need to
stop talking nonsense,
and finish up in here, brats!
There's a lot of
work to be done.
[BREWER A grunts]
[KUDAL]
Hey.
Yes, sir?
Try not to screw things
up next time, kid.
If you fail again, it won't
just be you who get punished.
I'll throw all of you naked into
the cold, dark, void, got it?
So don't test me.
[MASAHIRO]
Sir.
[LAFTER]
We'll enter the corridor soon.
Oh. So it isn't a tunnel
like I thought it was, huh?
[LAFTER] You can't see
it with the naked eye,
if that's what you mean.
Uh... what are you doing?
[MIKAZUKI]
Studying.
[LAFTER]
Oh, I see.
Oh, communications with
the ship will be cut soon.
[SHINO] You're out here
pretty early, Akihiro.
[AKIHIRO]
Hm?
You've still got plenty
of time before dispatch.
Shouldn't you rest up a
little before heading out?
No. I'm fine here.
[SHINO]
Hmph. If you say so...
[FUMITAN] It seems
data links with Barbatos
and Hyakuri have been severed.
It's almost time, then.
Look at that. There's even
more debris around us.
Eugene, take the helm.
Huh?
Times like this,
it's gotta be you.
You're the best choice here.
[gasps]
Jeez! No pressure, right?
Fine. I'll babysit
you guys again.
[OPERATOR A] I'm linking
our navigation system
with the Isaribi's .
That's it, boys.
Now we're completely dependent
on you to get us through this.
We'll have our eyes closed
until then, so be gentle.
[ORGA]
Got it.
[FUMITAN] We'll be entering
an area of dense debris.
Any impacts could
cause the ship to shake.
All crew should be on alert.
It's finally starting.
[sighs]
[gasps]
Mikazuki will be all right.
I know it.
[KUDELIA exhales]
[KUDELIA]
Yeah...
[ORGA]
All right.
Tsk.
[ORGA]
Let's go.
[LAFTER] Okay, we should be
getting closer to the point.
[MIKAZUKI]
I can't see anything.
Stay sharp. They could
find us at anytime now.
[BREWER OPERATOR] Man Rodi
on patrol, reporting:
We've spotted enemy
Mobile Suits approaching.
The rats are trapped.
[chuckles]
Send out our Mobile Suits.
They're here.
[BREWER B] That white one!
I'll avenge Pedro.
[KUDAL] They can't use long
distance communication here.
You need to cut
their numbers. Quickly!
Just don't forget
the main target
is the hunk of junk
that's following them.
Surround them and don't let
them get back to their ship.
[BREWERS]
Yes, sir.
Think I'm gonna head out too.
You're gonna pay!
[grunts]
[BREWER A] Don't rush.
Block their escape route.
Drive them towards our ship.
[LAFTER] Whoa! It's so cramped
out here, I can barely maneuver!
Yeah, no kidding.
My booster's so hard to handle,
that I that can't dodge any--
[radar beeps]
This Ahab Wave reaction.
Is it him?
[BREWER OPERATOR]
Two enemy units
are approaching fast.
[BROOKE] Tell me, have you
seen their ship yet?
[BREWER OPERATOR]
No, sir.
[growls] Damn it. They'll be
here sooner or later.
And won't stray far
from their scouts.
Until they arrive,
make them suffer!
Isn't my darling here yet?
[grunts]
What the hell?
It's just two machines.
Has there been any
sign of their ship?
[BREWER OPERATOR] N-No, sir.
Nothing from our scouts yet.
--[alarm blares]
--What's going on, now?!
[BREWER OPERATOR]
Ahab Wave on the port side!
[BROOKE]
Huh? It can't be!
Ah! They came cutting
through the Debris Zone?
Are they crazy?!
O-Orga!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
You're late, My Darling!
[OPERATOR B]
Enemy ship dead ahead.
Let's show these sorry
bastards why we call our ship
the "Hammerhead".
Whaddya say?
Yes, sir! All crew,
prepare for impact.
Reactor output to max!
Full inertial control enabled!
Give them hell!
[gasps]
Don't let the
Turbines show us up!
[EUGENE yells]
Now, what the hell?!
[SHINO]
Let's do this!
[KUDAL yelps]
Impossiblle!
How'd we let them ambush us?
Now what are we gonna do?
We can't afford to back
down on this job.
Gjallarhorn doesn't hand
them out to just anyone.
This is our golden ticket.
If we pull it off,
we'll gain their support!
Hey, you don't have
to tell me that, boss.
I know what's at stake here.
We can still turn this around
if we manage to get ahold
of that Kudelia girl.
We'll take care of the
pests that boarded us.
I want you to get out there
and smash up their ship good!
Fine by me! 'Cause I
get the fun part.
Kudal Cadel.
Gusion, heading out.
Go! Go!
[BREWER OPERATOR] Enemy
intruders in the upper decks.
Come on! You just get
rid of them already!
[ORGA]
Sorry to make you wait, Akihiro.
There's no need to apologize.
Not to Human Debris
like me, anyway.
You're still on
that debris crap?
Well, knock it off.
I'm sick of hearin' it.
[gasps]
[ORGA] We can't change
our past, either.
Don't forget,
we're all space rats.
All of us. But we can
change the future.
Best we can,
in spite of our past.
But don't take my word
for it; learn it yourself.
Right here and now.
Yeah.
Akihiro Altland.
Graze Custom, heading out.
[AKIHIRO]
They're coming.
Wait, that's...
[AMIDA] Your fight
is with us now, boys.
We won't let you near Akihiro.
[AZEE]
Hurry, Akihiro.
[grunts]
Got it!
[MIKAZUKI]
Okay. Let's go too, Lofter!
[LAFTER]
Roger.
Now! Come at me from
any angle you want!
[BREWER B]
Hey! What's goin' on?
[BREWER A]
Where'd they come from?
[BREWER D]
They're attacking our ship!
Wait, reinforcements?
[KUDAL] You brats!
Don't just sit around.
Numbers one through five,
you need to follow me.
The rest of you stay here
and stop these Mobile Suits.
[AZEE]
They're attacking your ship.
[MIKAZUKI]
I'm on it.
[AMIDA] I'll provide cover
for the Hammerhead .
Lofter and Azee, I want
you to stay with Akihiro.
[AZEE]
Roger.
[LAFTER]
Leave it to me.
Take this!
--[ALL grunt]
--[ORGA] The hell?
[FUMITAN]
We've been hit by a Mobile Suit.
What? A Suit has
that much power?
[BREWER SOLDIER E gasps]
[BREWER SOLDIER E groans]
That suit... I know it.
Thanks, Mika! All right,
let's regroup and finish this!
[BREWER SOLDIER F groans]
[SHINO grunts]
[SHINO] Thought Brewers
were supposed to be tough!
[BREWER SOLDIERS yell]
Ya coulda fooled me!
Your defense is one giant hole!
[BREWER A]
Oh, no you don't!
I gotcha!
You can't do that alone!
Thanks, guys.
I'm coming, Masahiro!
[MASAHIRO grunts]
[gasps]
That machine is...
[grunts]
[MASAHIRO]
It's too late now...
[grunts]
[gasps]
[MASAHIRO]
What's he doing?
[BREWER A]
Masahiro?
Wait, where are you headed?!
[LAFTER]
I said you can't go that way!
[MASAHIRO]
Wh-What do you want?
[AKIHIRO]
Sorry for the wait, Masahiro.
I'm here for you now.
[MASAHIRO]
Here... for me?
That's right. I promised you.
Brother... Why?
Pedro will be avenged!
[BREWER B]
What?!
[BREWER B grunts]
[BREWER D]
No! Vito...
[BREWER E]
How did he...?
Quit gawkin' and put all you've
got into taking this guy out!
[MASAHIRO]
Why talk about this now?
[AKIHIRO]
What do you mean?
I... I waited so long
for you, Big Brother.
But one day, I realized...
...that having hope
brings nothing but pain.
The more you hope,
the more you suffer.
That's why I've come here for--
[MASAHIRO]
Don't you see it's useless?!
[gasps]
[MASAHIRO] Even if you win
and take me with you...
Even if I leave
all this behind...
What exactly will that change?
Masahiro...
[MASAHIRO] Sooner or later,
we'll all die. Isn't that right?
We're nothing more
than Human Debris.
We can't die peacefully.
[SHINO]
Hey! Don't go out there!
[DANTE]
Dammit it all to hell!
I told him he
needed to stay back!
[DANTE] I wish I could punch him
for leavin' us here like this.
[SHINO]
Let's move.
[MASAHIRO] Debris die
in space like garbage.
[AKIHIRO]
You know...
That's what I used
to think, too.
[MASAHIRO]
What?
[AKIHIRO]
As Human Debris,
I thought it didn't
matter what I did.
That nothing was ever
gonna change.
And to be honest, I even
gave up on finding you again.
Then one day,
I found people who treated
me like a human being.
No... I've found people
who call me family.
[MASAHIRO]
Huh?
Family?
That's right. And they're
waiting to meet you, brother.
Let's go.
[MASAHIRO]
What?
What's a family?
[AKIHIRO gasps]
[MASAHIRO chuckles]
[MASAHIRO] For me, it was
only ever you, mom, and dad.
That's it. That's the
one I remember.
Masahiro...
[MASAHIRO] So... while I was
waiting for you to save me,
You were out there having
the time of your life?!
You abandoned me.
No, that's not true! I didn't!
Soon, you'll find
out... how it feels!
Brother!
[KUDAL]
How annoying.
Annoying! Annoying! Annoying!
I've had enough of this!
Why won't you die?!
Where the hell are you
stupid rats, anyway?!
Somebody back me up! Hey!
Dammit! You guys're useless!
[gasps]
Not good!
Ah! I'll use him as a hostage,
and finish off the
white one right now!
[MASAHIRO] You've got
this all wrong, Akihiro.
You think we're human?
[chuckles]
You're a fool.
It's time for you to
find out first hand
what death for Human
Debris is really like.
So, are you ready?
[KUDAL]
Masahiro!
[gasps]
[KUDAL]
Just like that!
Hold him tight and don't let go!
[AKIHIRO]
No!
[gasps]
What are you doing?
[chuckles]
No! Masahiro!
♪
[NAZE]
Listen close, kids.
I'm about to teach you the
basics of good business.
First, "Quickly and Carefully,"
that should be your motto.
Now, this next part
is really important:
No matter what happens,
you should never mix
business with pleasure.
Understand?
If you can do that,
then you've got it made.
So go for it!
Next time on Mobile Suit
Gundam: Iron Blooded Orphans,
Episode 13,
"Funeral Rites."
I love you.