[NAZE] Now, listen up. We're
about to have a meeting with
one of the most feared men
in the entire Outer Sphere,
so you guys better be
on your best behavior.
--[EUGENE grunts]
--[BISCUIT gasps]
[NAZE]
Hey! It's been a while.
[MAN IN BLACK A]
Indeed it has, Mr. Turbine.
What brings you out
here today, if I may ask?
Well, I came to
see the old man.
[EUGENE gulps]
All right... I hope
you're ready.
♪
[MCMURDO]
Hm?
Ah, so you made it, Naze.
Well, well, well...
It's you guys, huh?
I've heard about you.
A very promising group, indeed.
Yes...
Hey, bring out some
cannoli for our guests.
And fill 'em with
lots of cream.
[SUBORDINATE A]
Yes, sir.
[BISCUIT] So this guy,
McMurdo Barriston,
is really the head of Teiwaz?
[EUGENE] He's a lot different
than I thought he'd be.
Now, Naze, what is it
you want to do?
As you know, these guys aren't
afraid of taking chances.
Well, I want to swear a Sakazuki
blood oath to their leader.
[gasps]
Oh, is that so?
That must mean you hold
this man in high regard.
This is a rare
occasion, indeed.
[NAZE]
Hm.
[MCMURDO]
Very well, then.
I'll agree to hold a
ceremony for the two of you.
When it's finished, the Turbines
and Tekkadan will be brothers.
The two of us are
gonna be brothers, huh?
So, what's his share?
[NAZE]
Fifty-fifty.
And that way,
nobody's above the other.
[MCMURDO] Hm. Even if you
think that's reasonable,
the others may not. It could
be a little too much for them,
so why don't we
make it sixty-forty.
[gasps]
[LAFTER]
That guy is unbelievable!
No matter what happens,
he doesn't give up.
A night with Naze
is tamer than this!
[MECHANIC A]
What? Seriously?
[MECHANIC B]
No way!
Alright! Ready for
another one.
[gasps]
Gimme a break, huh?
[AZEE] Sorry 'bout this, but I
really needed your help.
That's fine. I love
cooking new dishes.
Atra, why didn't you
go to that big meeting
with Orga and all the others?
Huh?
It's 'cause she's just a girl.
They're weak and just get
in the way of
important stuff like that.
[ELGAR yelps]
[AZEE]
Why don't you say that again?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
[EMBI]
But, Kudelia's a girl,
and she still went with
the rest of them.
[ATRA]
Uh...
[AZEE]
Enough, Embi...
[EMBI] Y-Yeah, but it's
the truth. Isn't it?
[sighs]
[AMIDA]
Only one way to measure a man.
It's by the amount
of love he gives.
I-It is? What do you mean?
Well, among all
the men out there,
some have more to
offer than others.
And even if he shares his love
with lots of different women,
it's still quite a bit more than
others could ever hope
to provide. That's what
really satisfies the soul
right down to the
core of your being.
Huh...
Honestly, would you rather eat
gritty old cornbread alone,
or share the most delicious
meat you've ever tasted
with everyone? You know?
Meat, huh?
[AMIDA]
Hm?
[gasps]
Oh sorry,
but you were talking about
having real meat, weren't you?
Cause on Mars, nobody eats
things like that.
But the bread my manager bakes
at her store is really amazing.
[giggles] You'll make
a great wife, Atra.
Do you really think so?
[ATRA giggles]
Just make sure you don't
pick the wrong man.
[MCGILLIS]
Three more points.
By following the Ariadne,
we'll reach Earth soon.
[GAELIO] That job was
incredibly annoying.
Can you believe all
those space rats?
[MCGILLIS] They should be
heading to Earth, also.
Tekkadan and Kudelia...
But if they're not
using the Ariadne line,
then we'll never find them.
[GAELIO]
Hmph.
The lower the creature, the
faster they can slither away.
They won't escape.
Trust me.
There's a man investigating
for me, as we speak.
Of course they won't. The great
Specialist Major McGillis...
Wait, I can't call
you that anymore.
When we get back to Earth,
you'll be promoted.
[MCGILLIS]
Well, before that,
There's still the engagement
party for Almiria and me.
[GAELIO] I feel bad for him.
I know that she's my sister,
but I still think it
must be pretty awful
to have a little
kid as a fiancée.
Ein. Tell me, do you have
a girlfriend back home?
No, sir. There's nobody
at the moment.
You're boring, Ya know that?
I agreed to make
you my subordinate,
So the least you could do
is have a few stories
to kill the time up here.
[CRANK] Ein. Forgive me
for acting so selfishly.
But, I refuse to take the
lives of innocent children
on the battlefield.
[EIN] He cared about every one
of those soldiers so deeply,
but they slaughtered
him without mercy.
We shouldn't murder
innocent children.
But the guilty ones
need to be punished
for all that they've done.
Right, Lieutenant?
[EUGENE]
Oh, man! These are great!
Um, Mr. Naze, what did he
want with Kudelia, anyway?
In spite of his reputation,
he doesn't do anything
that's unreasonable.
And she does have
a bodyguard, doesn't she?
Uh, yeah...
[NAZE] Oh, by the way.
We got an offer
on all that merchandise
you guys handed over to us.
[ORGA, EUGENE]
Hm?
[NAZE] If the prices look good
to you, just give me an invoice.
H-How much?
Are you sure?
Some items went for
more than others,
but the Graze reactor sold
for a really high price.
'Cause now, the only
organization left that can
still manufacture Ahab
Reactors is Gjallarhorn.
[EUGENE]
We did it, Orga!
Yeah, right.
We really appreciate this.
Thanks, Naze.
I mean... uh... Brother.
It's a little too
early to call me that.
[ORGA gasps]
By the way. You can have a
good time here with some cash.
And with all the fighting
and the traveling,
I'll bet those kids are pretty
stressed out these days.
Maybe it's time to let
'em have a break.
Oh yeah? Is that somethin'
you do for your wives, too?
[NAZE]
Hm?
Uh... I mean... It's part
of having a family, right?
Sure! If women don't
get the chance
to let out steam sometimes,
they just explode.
As head of the family,
I try to provide that for
'em once and a while.
Guess that makes sense.
Okay. Let's take our
profit and party tonight.
Ha, ha! All right!
Hold on just a minute, Orga.
We need to try thinking ahead
and using our money
a little more wise--
[ORGA] Let's get goin'.
We've gotta spread the word.
[EUGENE]
Yeah Awesome!
Ah... Forget it.
[thudding]
[MCMURDO] So, you're the
activist who wants Mars
to have its independence.
It's a pleasure to meet
the girl in the limelight.
E-Excuse me, sir?
As a plan to begin rejuvenating
the sagging Martian economy,
you demanded that the rulers
of Earth deregulate all
half-metal
resources indefinitely.
And, to spearhead the autonomous
distribution on Mars,
you're going to Earth yourself.
That right, Ms. Bernstine?
Yes, sir.
[MCMURDO] From all of the
information we've gathered,
The head of Arbrau, Makanai,
is doing everything in his
power to see that it happens.
[KUDELIA gasps]
That's such wonderful news.
[MCMURDO] Though, worst-case
scenario, this could mean war.
[gasps]
I don't understand.
[MCMURDO] Well, anytime you want
more rights, organizations come
out of the woodwork
and start scheming.
Using whatever little dirty
tricks they can think of.
[gasps]
[MCMURDO] And the wounds
can take a while to heal.
'Cause even if you win
the rights you fought for,
the friction between the
opposing parties will remain.
But why? How could they?
[MCMURDO] Young lady, how would
you feel about appointing
Teiwaz for this?
[gasps]
[MCMURDO] By allowing us
to work alongside you,
as your direct appointees on
these matters, we can do
something about the immediate
problems that you'll be facing.
Though, there might be some
things even we can't avoid.
Well, I...
May I have a little time
to think everything over?
It seems clear. Can't decide?
[KUDELIA grunts]
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
[MIKAZUKI]
Kudelia...
[gasps]
This is all up to
you now, okay?
[KUDELIA grunts]
Either way you choose, people
are gonna still gonna die.
[MCMURDO grunts]
[MIKAZUKI] You know from
what you've seen already.
[gasps]
Yeah, you're right.
[MIKAZUKI] I guess this is kinda
like that day I took somebody's
life for the first time.
Just like me,
our entire future depends
on the decision you make.
And no one can
choose it for you.
So you're gonna have
to rely on yourself.
[KUDELIA exhales]
[MCMURDO]
The boy's right.
It's not something
to be taken lightly.
But just know. I'm not the
young man I used to be, Miss,
So I'll need an
answer soon.
Yes, I understand, sir.
Please Excuse me.
Hey, kid.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
[MCMURDO]
What's your name?
Mikazuki Augus.
[MCMURDO]
Mikazuki... Right.
You're the one who pilots
that Mobile Suit.
Well, we'll be sure and
take good care of it
while you're here.
[MIKAZUKI]
What?
Our engineers are
some of the finest.
You don't have to worry, kid.
I won't take it away.
[ORGA]
Looks pretty good, huh?
[BOYS cheer]
Would it be okay if
I have this one?
Hell. You can try all of 'em.
--[ELGAR] This is awesome!
--[EMBI] Great, let's dig in!
Come on! Now be fair and wait
for your turn, all right?
Hey, Ride!
Shouldn't you be setting an
example for the other kids?
Shut up, okay?
Atra, dig in.
Uh, sure! I wonder if
I can make these myself...
[ORGA]
Hey, you two. Break it up.
[SHINO]
Yo, Boss!
You got anything
for the rest of us?
Yeah... You bet your ass.
[OLDER BOYS cheering]
[MERRIBIT] Mm. It's really
starting to get busy tonight.
[BARTENDER A]
Yeah, sorry, Merribit.
A rowdy bunch from Mars came in.
They're here from Mars?
All right, guys, order whatever
you want and have a good time.
Man. The food and
drink are okay,
but what we need
are some women!
What?!
I'm feelin' all wound up after
being around the Turbines.
Busty women everywhere and
we can't even touch 'em?
It just isn't fair!
Am I right, Eugene?
I-I don't really care
about stuff like that.
You are so lame.
[ORGA] Hey, what're you
doin' sittin' around here?
We're gonna party 'till
the sun comes up!
[OLDER BOYS cheer]
[MERRIBIT]
Mm...
[ORGA coughs, groans]
You hangin' in there, Orga?
[ORGA groans]
[MERRIBIT]
Here.
It's all right. Take it.
[ORGA]
Huh?
Wanna act like an adult, huh?
Then, you've gotta deal with
the consequences. It's just
a part of growing up.
It's part of growing up.
[ORGA grunts]
Who was that?
Don't know.
[ORGA sniffs]
[ORGA]
Smells like a woman.
[SHINO] Fine. We'll leave
you guys here, then.
I don't really want to go,
but Shino won't shut up--
Hey, it's all right.
I'll see you two later.
[groans]
[Akihiro grunts)
[MIKAZUKI] I've never seen
Orga like this before.
It's gonna happen...
[MIKAZUKI]
Mm?
I promise... We're gonna
be a real family.
[ORGA]
And, you guys...
...will all have a place
that you can call home.
And be proud.
Orga...
[MIKAZUKI]
Hmph.
[AKIHIRO]
A family... huh?
[FUMITAN]
And those were the conditions
Mr. Barriston gave you?
[KUDELIA]
Yeah.
I'm well aware that by
moving forward on this,
more bloodshed is inevitable.
What should I do?
As a maid, I'm not qualified
to offer such advice.
[gasps]
Fumitan!
[FUMITAN] However, It would seem
that after crossing Gjallarhorn,
we can't risk going
back to Mars now.
And with that in mind...
[KUDELIA]
There's only one answer.
[FUMITAN]
Mm.
I always knew that.
But I didn't have the
strength to admit it.
I'm sorry. Thank you
so much, Fumitan.
Well, I...
Oh, yeah!
[FUMITAN]
Hm?
What's this?
Do you think it's pretty?
It's just a little something
I picked up when we all
went out shopping earlier.
[KUDELIA giggles]
[KUDELIA]
They're a matching pair.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[exhales]
[MIKAZUKI] Now, Orga,
If you go to sleep out here,
you're just gonna
catch a cold. Come on.
[ORGA grunts]
[BISCUIT] I see. So what you're
saying is that essentially,
Kudelia would be under
Teiwaz's care, then.
Do you think I should've
spoken against it?
Why would you?
Well, if Teiwaz
comes in on this,
there's gonna be
a lot less profit.
And Orga hasn't even been told
about what's going on yet.
If all this ends up leading
us to some kinda war,
we'll be in big trouble.
He knows we couldn't
handle something like that.
Fact is, it's only been
a matter of luck so far.
Seems like we've been in over
our heads most of the time.
And going up against people
way out of our league.
[MIKAZUKI] Maybe. But if it
weren't for what Orga's done
for us, then we wouldn't
have come this far.
You're right, Though, sometimes
I wish he'd try relying on us
a little more, ya know?
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah.
--[ORGA grunts]
--[clattering]
[ORGA]
Huh?
[RIDE grunts]
[ORGA]
Hey!
[gasps]
[ORGA] What're you doin' out
here this time of night, Ride?
[RIDE]
I Uh...
[ORGA]
Huh?
Is that food?
You didn't feel like eatin'
this stuff with everybody else?
What's goin' on here, buddy?
[RIDE grunts]
I'm just keeping it
for when those little
brats complain.
Like you?
No! It's for all
the younger kids!
Thought it'd be a good idea to
have something sweet around
when they start crying.
So I figured...
[RIDE] They all...
--[ORGA laughs]
--[RIDE] Hey Come on!
I thought I told ya
I'm not a kid, anymore.
[RIDE]
Huh?
[ORGA gags]
[gasps]
You okay? B-Boss!
[TAKAKI]
I wonder if those engineers
have already gotten started.
What's the matter, Yamagi?
It's nothing.
Ah, yeah. I understand.
Believe me. I wish I could
go to the ceremony, too.
[CHIEF MECHANIC gasps] I never
thought I'd get to touch the
Barbatos with my very own hands!
[TAKAKI] Woah! They really
took it apart fast.
[YUKINOJO] When I got here,
it'd already been disassembled.
[YAMAGI] Excuse me, but what's
so great about this suit?
[CHIEF MECHANIC]
Are you kidding?!
This is one of the 72 Gundam
frames that brought an end
to the entire Calamity War!
But after all these years,
the information was lost.
So now, it's called a
phantom machine!
And now I get to tune it up
without any budgetary
limitations at all!
They're allowed to do this?
Well, apparently,
the boss of Teiwaz
has taken a liking to Mikazuki.
[CHIEF MECHANIC]
Just you wait and see!
All expendable parts
will be replaced!
The frame and the reactor
will be readjusted for
optimum performance, and I'll
gather the research to
create the perfect
version of the Barbatos.
Think it's just
what she needed.
[SHINO] Hey, what's up guys?
You need any help down here?
[YUKINOJO] Hey! So what
about the ceremony?
Yeah, sorry. I guess
I overslept a little.
You're gonna need some
more people, right?
We will, but uh,
are you okay?
Why do you look so shiny?
Oh! Yeah, well, I worked up a
pretty good sweat, last night.
[YUKINOJO]
What do you mean by that?
[SHINO laughs]
[AMIDA ] You're just too big.
I'm afraid it doesn't fit.
[BISCUIT]
Uh...
Uh, what am I supposed
to do with this?
[LAFTER]
Come on. Give it to me.
There. Clothes make the man.
You're lookin' good.
[gasps]
You're right. I am a man, now.
[LAFTER]
Huh?
[BISCUIT] Akihiro, I'm a little
surprised to see you here.
This doesn't seem like
it's your kinda thing.
[AKIHIRO]
'Course it is.
[gasps]
[AKIHIRO]
'Cause this is for our family.
Yeah.
[KUDELIA]
Sorry about this, Atra.
Thanks for all your help.
Sure...
Kudelia, you don't look
so good. Do you feel okay?
Is something's wrong?
Mikazuki... Know I understand
how he's felt all along.
What do you mean?
Those're strange pictures.
These are letters. Together,
they spell "Orga Itsuka."
Really?
[NAZE]
It's for the ceremony.
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh...
Are there any letters
for my name, too?
[NAZE]
Lemme think.
Hm...
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
So this is me, right?
Yeah! Like it?
Well. Kudelia's been teaching
us some different ones,
but I'd rather learn these.
They really look beautiful.
[knocking]
[ORGA]
Sorry guys.
I know you've been waiting.
[NAZE]
Nice! Lookin' good, Orga.
Ah, thanks.
Did you make these
for the ceremony?
Yeah.
Hey, look! We've got
the same letter.
Huh?
He's right!
That's the "g" from Orga
and the "g" from Augus.
[NAZE]
It can also be read as an "I."
"I"?
[NAZE]
Yeah, meaning "oneself".
Through the years, your position
is gonna change a lot.
So don't lose yourself
along the way, all right?
Or you can't
protect your family.
[gasps]
[KUDELIA]
Excuse me.
[ORGA]
Hm?
[NAZE]
Wow! You look great.
[MIKAZUKI]
What's the matter?
Thanks to you, Mikazuki,
I've made my decision.
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
[KUDELIA]
And boss?
[ORGA]
Hm?
No. Orga Itsuka.
We need to talk.
[ORGA]
Hm.
[MCMURDO] Well. I 'm glad
that you've made up your mind,
Miss Kudelia
Aina Bernstine.
As I see it, I've already
got blood on my hands.
Ah.
And it's the blood of Tekkadan.
If I were to stop fighting now,
it would betray every
single one of them.
[MCMURDO]
Hm... I understand.
But, what do they think?
If we agree to all this and
Tekkadan joins with Teiwaz,
will we still be
allowed to escort her?
Of course. But wouldn't
aligning yourself with us
hurt your pride as a
leader to those men?
[ORGA]
Tekkadan's what I--
No.
It's something that
we built together.
[KUDELIA gasps]
Orga...
[MCMURDO]
Hm...
[ORGA] This isn't about
my pride. It's about us.
And we're not gonna change,
no matter what happens.
We're a family.
Tekkadan means everything to us.
[ORGA]
And, we'll protect it.
♪
[EUGENE] I can barely
keep my eyes open.
[ATRA] Be careful or your
clothes will get wrinkled.
[EUGENE]
Aw, shut up.
You were really cool, Orga.
[ORGA]
Yeah.
I'm sorry I made
you worry, Mika.
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
[ORGA]
All right.
Think all those
ritual behind us now.
Ready?
[ORGA]
Let's go to Earth.
♪
[AKIHIRO grunts, pants]
[AKIHIRO] Man. Why am
I training so hard, anyway?
Well, I guess If I can't protect
what's important to me,
then I can...
Nah, that's not it.
I train hard 'cause when
I focus on working out,
All my problems just
kinda fade away.
Next time on Mobile Suit
Gundam: Iron Blooded Orphans,
Episode 10:
"A Letter from Tomorrow."