[MERRIBIT]
Bring me the bandages.
Got it!
[MERRIBIT]
Thanks, Atra.
[groaning]
[MERRIBIT]
Sorry, this may hurt a little.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER 24C]
All right. Thank you.
Stay down; you still
need to rest.
But our troops
are shorthanded.
I have to go back.
Don't be ridiculous.
--[ATRA gasps]
--[glass breaks]
[ATRA]
I-I'm sorry!
[MERRIBIT]
You should rest too, Atra.
You didn't sleep
at all last night.
No, I'm fine.
I'm used to working
long hours now.
[MERRIBIT]
But still...
[TEKKADAN MEMBER 24D]
What's wrong, Atra?
Nothing at all.
Okay. I can't see very well.
[ATRA]
Don't worry about a thing.
It'll be all right.
[MERRIBIT] Gjallarhorn
started attacking Tekkadan
to try and block them
from entering Edmonton.
It's already been three days.
Despite Gjallorhorn's strength
and being severely outnumbered,
Tekkadan continues
to push forward.
Never resting, never stopping.
Every time they get pushed
back, they get up again.
Gjallarhorn has to be terrified.
With Tekkadan's frantic attacks,
they must think those boys
have gone completely insane.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER 24E] Quick!
Take him to Ms. Merribit.
Over here.
Hey, you! Can you help me?
Huh?
[MAKANAI]
You still can't get through?
Unfortunate,
considering the election
for Arbrau's prime minister
begins this afternoon.
Only six more hours
until the deadline.
Perhaps it was just
too much of a burden.
Hurry. You need
to prep him first.
[KUDELIA] If you don't mind,
I'd prefer it if you didn't
speak that way
in their presence,
because they're fighting for
us and putting each one
of their lives on the line.
And when you say those things,
it's no different than
stabbing them in the back.
Trust me, I have no
doubt they're capable.
And I believe they'll make
it to their destination.
What I am worried about
is the amount of blood
they'll shed until then.
[MERRIBIT] Orga said the boys
in Tekkadan had nowhere to go.
No home that any of them
could come back to--
That all they have
now is a destination.
But after living
through this hell,
I can't imagine anywhere
they could go now.
♪
[GATT]
Ugh. Still no good
Orga, the front line
can't hold on.
We don't have time for this!
We need to get into
the city ASAP!
Hey, boss!
I'm really running low
on ammo here!
Ah, great.
Let's fall back. Alaya-Vijnana
forces take the rear.
[GATT, DIOS]
Roger.
[ADJUTANT 24B]
Captain.
Don't you think we should
go and back them up?
[CAPTAIN 24B]
We have one mission,
and that's to protect
this area; nothing more.
[ADJUTANT 24B] But if we
attack, we could defeat them
all at once, couldn't we?
[CAPTAIN 24B]
Of course we could,
but it sounds to me like
you've forgotten our orders.
This is a political issue.
[ADJUTANT 24B]
You're right, sir.
[CAPTAIN 24B]
Now remember.
Gjallarhorn isn't supposed
to interfere with any
internal affairs.
At least that's
what they told us.
[SOLDIER 24A]
I'm sorry, Captain.
They've broken our formation.
Retreat and regroup, then.
Damn, they ran away again!
[AZEE] They've learned they're
at a disadvantage in a skirmish.
Not bad.
[LAFTER]
Are you kidding?!
We're doing pretty well
ourselves, though.
We've held on here
for three days.
--[MIKAZUKI] I can finally eat.
--[SHINO] Huh?
Are you serious?
Food's the last
thing on my mind.
[AKIHIRO]
What is with you, man?
[ECO]
Come on, hurry up.
We got a lot to do!
Refuel and maintenance time!
[BOY SOLDIERS]
Yes, ma'am!
They're pushing
us to the limit.
[YUKINOJO] Reloading and
refueling has top priority,
understand?
Focus all repairs
on the legs first!
[BOY SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
We've lost a
whole lot, boss...
[ORGA]
Yeah.
Mikazuki and the other
guys should be able
to break their defensive line
without any problem, right?
Yeah, but the whole reason
we can keep on fighting now
is because they've been
holding up the rear for us.
Besides...
[ORGA] There's no way we can
bring an Ahab reactor out there.
The entire city would shut down.
If the public turns against
Makanai for any reason,
all of this would
be for nothing.
So how're we looking?
[KUDELIA]
Even after we enter the city,
there's still quite a way
to the Parliament hall.
We don't have
any time to waste.
[RIDE]
Boss!
[ORGA]
Ride. You're back. Talk to me.
[RIDE] The river's water level
has gone down a lot.
I think a Mobile Worker
could probably cross it now.
Good work.
Please, boss,
let me fight this time.
There should be some machines
that aren't being used.
You sure you understand
what you're askin' me?
[ORGA]
All right.
[RIDE]
Yes!
[TAKAKI]
That's great, Ride!
[RIDE] Huh! Now let's see who
can really kick some ass
on the battlefield.
[TAKAKI]
Stop kiddin' around.
We've gotta go out there
and do our best for Tekkadan.
[RIDE]
Oh, come on. Boring.
What's wrong with
a little competition?
[ORGA]
Mika? You read me?
Orga?
[ORGA] We'll go out
for a final attack.
[MIKAZUKI]
Okay, got it.
But it's gonna
be a big gamble.
And uhh...
There could be
a lot of causalities.
It's lookin' like I don't
have a choice this time.
[MIKAZUKI]
I've already bet it all on you.
Ever since that day...
But I'm not the only one.
It's all of us.
We've got your back, Orga
So you can always
count on us. Understand?
Everyone in Tekkadan.
[ORGA] All you guys
are behind me... huh?
[NEWSCASTER 24A] The election
for prime minister is coming up
this afternoon, and Edmonton
has been completely shut off
by Gjallarhorn.
Throughout the city,
there's a growing sense
of unease as security forces...
[MEMBER 24A] Alesi, this
is not what you told me.
[MEMBER 24B] Will Mr. Makanai
really make it or not?
[ALESI]
He's very close.
Don't worry.
He'll be here, gentlemen.
But Gjallarhorn's
forces are on the move
at this very moment.
And I've been told
that Iznario Fareed
has just come here as well.
[ALESI] Then it appears
we have the perfect fodder
to put Henri's faction
at a disadvantage.
If Gjallarhorn were to infringe
upon Arbrau's sovereignty,
I don't think the people
would look favorably on it.
[MEMBER 24B]
But he still has to get here.
Of course. I'm aware that if
Makanai doesn't make it in time
this election will
have been for nothing.
Now calm down.
[HENRI] You told me
to leave this up to you.
[IZNARIO] I know of
Makanai's faction's plans.
Then why aren't--
It's all taken care of.
No matter how hard
they may struggle,
it will be to no avail.
[ORGA]
Listen up.
We're just about out of time.
So whether it all works or not,
this will be our
last operation, guys.
Now, Merribit.
Yes, boss?
[ORGA] I want you to
take all the wounded
and leave right away.
Understood?
Huh? But if I...
[ORGA] And I'll have the
rest of you act as decoys
to try and draw in Gjallarhorn.
[MAKANAI]
Hmm...
I know it sounds risky.
But if we're gonna
pull this thing off,
then we have to do
anything we can to win.
If you don't agree to this plan,
no one will stop you
from going with Merribit
and the wounded.
But if you'll
join me on this...
Take whatever
you have left in you
and bet it all on Tekkadan!
[MERRIBIT]
You're insane!
Acting as decoys?
Betting away their lives?
Do you want these
kids to die out there?
[ORGA]
Now look...
We lived by risking
our lives for money.
Ever since we started
this damn job.
In fact, it was ever
since we were born.
But know this:
Our lives aren't disposable.
Who we are doesn't fade
once we're dead and gone.
Not as long as Tekkadan exists.
Some died before we
ever made it to this place.
But their deaths
were not in vain.
It's time for all of us to be
our chips on the battlefield.
The more lives we gamble,
the bigger our reward.
And the brighter our future.
Every person that we lose
will carve out the destiny
for those of us remaining.
--[MERRIBIT] But you can't...
--[RIDE] Boss is right.
For the longest time now,
I always thought we'd die
sooner or later... You know?
But even if one of
us loses our life,
that'll make Tekkadan's
future even greater
than it was before.
[TAKAKI] And the survivors
will only grow stronger
after the sacrifices
every one of them made.
Yeah, that's right,
Takaki. You tell 'em.
[ORGA]
Exactly.
It doesn't make a hell
of a lot of difference
who lives or who dies.
We are all one.
We are all... a family.
[MERRIBIT gasps]
[ORGA] For the fate
of Tekkadan itself,
risk everything you've got!
[BOY SOLDIERS cheering]
[MERRIBIT]
You're wrong. You're so wrong.
A family isn't a...
I can't take this anymore!
Biscuit... Fumitan...
I know they wouldn't want this.
[crying]
It just isn't right...
[YUKINOJO]
Yeah. Have to say I agree.
[MERRIBIT]
If it's the wrong thing to do...
...then why are they...?
It's useless. It's useless!
[crying]
Eh? Wait, Atra?
Why are you--?
Our troops are kinda busy,
so I'm gonna be your driver.
[KUDELIA]
You what?
Boss already gave
me the okay on this.
[KUDELIA]
Hold on... I, uh...
Mikazuki can't be here.
But I'm gonna make sure
that you're still protected.
[ATRA]
That is my revolution.
Okay.
I'm counting on you.
[KUDELIA] Guess this isn't
just my battle anymore.
It's all of ours.
I'm ready to bet everything.
All right, let's go!
[MIKAZUKI]
And I know we can win.
[siren]
[CORLIS]
What's going on?
Enemy attack?
[SHINO]
All right, let's do this.
Come on! It's our last one!
[AZEE] While they're in a
panic, we'll take them down.
[LAFTER]
Got it!
[CORLIS]
They're on the offensive?
[MIKAZUKI]
All right, I'll end it all here.
[beeping]
Gali-gali's back.
[GAELIO]
Carta, leave this to me.
I'm gonna make sure
he pays for what he did.
And then we can seize
the future of Gjallarhorn!
[CAPTAIN 24A]
What are you doing?
Push them back.
[ADJUTANT 24A]
We can't.
No matter how much we fire,
they keep charging.
They're crazy.
[CAPTAIN 24A]
Concentrate your shots.
Take good aim,
one by one...
[CAPTAIN 24A]
...and kill them!
What the hell?
I'll draw their attention
try to make it to...
[GATT]
Dios!
Everyone is...
[radio chatter]
[ORGA grunts]
[ORGA]
You guys...
Now! Follow me!
Damn! Damn!
[ORGA] I will not let your
sacrifice go to waste!
[RIDE yells]
[GATT]
The enemy's moving!
A little more...
Just a little more!
[CAPTAIN 24B] I can't just stand
here and watch our men die.
[ORGA]
Okay.
The enemy's gathering
on the bridge.
But our team's
firepower is so weak
they won't last by the time
we've crossed the river.
Get ready to move.
Because there's no way
I'm gonna let everything they
sacrificed go to waste!
--What in the--?!
--[EUGENE] 'Ey, Orga!
Your hero has arrived.
[ORGA]
Wait a minute...
Eugene!
Thought you could use a hand.
Right, Dante?
[DANTE] Yeah, so we
brought a few friends.
I'm gonna make sure I
never lose my home again.
I hope I can still
get paid for this.
The Brewers?
[EUGENE] We'll take on
the enemy from here.
Go for it!
All right, head out!
Corlis Stenja.
I want you guys to support
the Mobile Worker forces.
With all due respect, Major,
one Kimaris isn't
gonna be enough.
It's not a problem. Just go.
[CORLIS]
Y-Yes, sir.
[AKIHIRO]
I won't let them get away.
[LAFTER]
Akihiro! You can't go alone!
[beeping]
Now what?
[AZEE]
Lafter!
[LAFTER]
A giant Mobile Suit?
Where'd it come from?
That machine's
not in the database.
Let's go!
[LAFTER]
Okay!
You're dead!
[LAFTER yells]
Alaya-Vijnana system?
It must be.
What the--?!
[AZEE gasps]
[SHINO]
Azee!
[EIN] I can feel it.
The pure instinct.
Now I understand...
...that this... is my true form.
[MAKANAI] So they actually
managed to break the siege
and enter the city.
Properly rewarding
them is gonna cost me.
But I suppose those
kids deserve it.
There's not much
security in the city.
Takaki, we're charging through!
[TAKAKI]
Yes, sir!
[LAFTER yelling]
[LAFTER]
Azee!
Come on, answer me!
What the hell is this thing?!
[LAFTER] It's so creepy.
I can't read its moves.
Oh, man...
It might be stronger
than Mikazuki.
Hey, Lafter,
you be careful!
Huh?
[LAFTER screaming]
[MIKAZUKI]
Lafter!
Your fight is with me!
[GAELIO] This is where
you meet your end.
Did you see that?
It's the Alaya-Vijnana's
true form.
Ein's become one
with the Mobile Suit
because of his determination.
And he can destroy
imposters like you!
[GAELIO growling]
[SHINO]
Damn you!
[yelling]
[SHINO yells]
No way...
[ECO]
Lafter... Azee... No...
[EIN] Look, Lieutenant
Crank! I did it!
I got your machine back.
I hope you're somewhere...
watching me.
For I will carry out your will.
[YUKINOJO] Mobile Suit
forces, do you hear me?
[EIN] I will take revenge
and fulfill your commands.
[YUKINOJO]
Someone, come in!
Orga and Kudelia
have entered the city.
Just a little more...
You just have to
hold out a little more!
[EIN]
Kudelia Aina Bernstein!
[GAELIO yells]
[GAELIO] I will make sure I'm
the one who takes you down!
[GAELIO yelling]
[AKIHIRO]
Sorry, Mikazuki.
One of them
made it past us!
[MIKAZUKI gasps]
[ALESI] The session's
about to get underway.
We're out of time,
Mr. Makanai.
What did you just say?!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[SOLDIER 24B]
Unbelievable!
They brought those
things into the city?
[SOLDIER 24C]
Hey! Where's the backup?
We don't have enough
weapons out here...
[SOLDIER 24D] The troops at
the bridge are all tied up--
[SOLDIER 24C]
What?
Hey! Where's the
Parliament building?!
A right at the next light.
[ATRA]
Huh? The lights!
What's goin' on?
[TAKAKI]
Boss!
All communication
besides the LCS is cut off.
Looks like the radar is out too!
That means...
[ORGA]
You're kidding me...!
They're coming into the city...
...with a Mobile Suit?!
[EIN]
That's right, I remember now.
I'm sorry, Lieutenant Crank.
I was so overcome
with revenge that I forgot
to obey your orders and capture
Kudelia Aina Bernstein!
[ATRA]
Miss Kudelia!
[KUDELIA]
I am Kudelia Aina Bernstein.
If there's something
you want from me,
tell me now!
[EIN]
Well, well...
So you were here all along.
I tried to take you
from the CGS.
[ORGA]
What's that idiot doin'?
Takaki, be ready
to move at any minute.
[TAKAKI]
Right!
[EIN] ...come with
me from the beginning,
Lieutenant Crank
wouldn't have died.
He would still be with us.
Miss Kudelia!
[TEKKADAN PILOT 24A]
If I can create an opening,
she can escape...
[EIN]
That's right.
He's not here anymore
because of you.
There were many lives
that have been lost
as a result of my actions.
But... that's precisely
why I can't stop.
[EIN]
Such foolish pride!
I'll teach you a lesson!
[ATRA]
Look out!
[GAELIO]
Wha--What just happened?
Who the hell are you?
Get out of my way!
[MCGILLIS]
Can't do that.
I'm your opponent now.
[ORGA]
Of course...
I should have known you
weren't going to let us die.
Not in a place like this.
Were you, Mika?
[ATRA, KUDELIA]
Mikazuki.
Now let's go, Barbatos.
♪
[KUDELIA] From the first moment
we met, I was afraid of you.
It was as if you were able to
see through all of my arrogance,
ignorance, and doubts,
like looking into
some kind of window.
Mikazuki, I will not be
frightened by your eyes anymore.
Now I'm in this with you.
Let's reach that
destination... together.
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans :
Episode 25, "Tekkadan."