[BISCUIT]
Shoot now!
Any day, Eugene!
Would you get off
my back?! Dammit!
[MARUBA shouts]
[MARUBA]
Stop it! No, no, no!
My poor ship!
[MARUBA shouts]
♪
What's goin' on?
Shouldn't you be
in bed, Gaelio?
I told you it was
just a scratch.
Have you decided what
our next step is yet?
I'm ready whenever you are.
This time I'll get
that little fool.
[MCGILLIS]
We won't pursue.
[GAELIO]
Why not?
Calm yourself.
Coral's death left a lot of
work for us to take care of.
Have patience, my friend.
So, what? Are we just
gonna let 'em go, then?
Course not. Thanks to the
care package they sent,
I'm certain Kudelia Aina
Bernstine is aboard that ship.
And that means one thing...
They'll head for Earth.
No doubt about it.
We'll see them again, soon.
[GAELIO grunts]
[ORGA] Well? Do we
still have a tail?
[CHAD] So far, I'm not seeing
an Ahab Wave reaction.
And our patrols haven't
reported anything for a while.
Guess we're in the clear.
But we can't afford to
let our guard down.
[YUKINOJO] Jeez. No rest
for the weary around here.
Hey, Old Man. Is this armor
reinforcement the same kind
that's on the Mobile Worker?
Are you kidding me?
Mobile Suits are protected
by Nanolaminate armor.
It's a completely
different kinda material.
Then, how do I fix it?
[YUKINOJO]
Give me a second, wouldja?
[grunts] Dammit. These records
are practically worthless.
[YAMAGI]
Old Man.
[YUKINOJO]
Huh?
Want me to check
the reactor--
[YUKINOJO] Would you
cool your jets already?
I haven't even touched
one of these suits
since I was a little kid.
I was trained as a
Mobile Worker Specialist.
Well, I guess this machine was
made a pretty long time ago,
wasn't it?
Yeah. This thing
should be in a museum.
But, it was brand new
during the Calamity War.
In fact, other than the
ones Gjallarhorn uses,
most Mobile Suits
are antiques.
[TAKAKI]
What was the Calamity War?
[YUKINOJO] A massive
conflict that happened
on Earth 300 years ago.
Back then, there were
enough of these things
to destroy it entirely.
And they nearly did...
A Gundam Frame, you said?
Yes. And only 72
of them were made.
They were quite
prominent centuries ago,
near the very end
of the Calamity War.
This unit's name was Barbatos.
A Gundam... I know
I've heard the name.
You sure it's not a mistake?
The proof is in the
pattern of the reactor.
It has two Ahab Reactors;
both of which were specially
designed for that machine.
They're like a fingerprint.
[GAELIO] Hm. So despite its age,
it's still got some punch, huh?
No wonder it put up
such a good fight.
True, it is very powerful,
but it's the pilot
that really matters.
It's not your fault.
The Alaya-Vijnana System
was developed during
the Calamity War
as a way to maximize the
abilities of the Mobile Suits
by granting their pilots
acute spatial awareness.
[GAELIO scoffs]
Those filthy space rats.
You must be hungry, huh?
[MIKAZUKI] Yeah, piloting always
makes me work up an appetite.
Uh, about that... Are we
gonna be fighting a lot?
Probably so. 'Cause there're
still a bunch of people
who're coming
after Kudelia.
Mikazuki... Aren't you afraid?
Not really.
Why not?
I mean, if you're not careful,
you could die out there.
[MIKAZUKI]
Mm?
[sighs]
[MIKAZUKI]
I'll be fine.
[gasps]
'Cause I have this.
Yeah...
[BISCUIT] So. What should
we do from here on?
We're gonna need another guide,
but we can't afford to hire a
scumbag like Orcus again.
Agreed.
But are we certain that a guide
is absolutely necessary?
Sorry, those're the breaks.
If you want to get to
Earth safely, then we
don't have any choice.
It won't be easy with
Gjallarhorn gunnin' for us.
And run-of-the-mill isn't
gonna quite cut it.
We need someone strong enough
to watch our backs, and crazy
enough to take care of things
on Mars while we're away.
Sorry, but I got nothin'.
Who'd be willing to do that?
[ORGA]
Teiwaz.
[SHINO, BISCUIT]
Huh?
That's our ticket.
Wait, who?
Teiwaz. A large conglomerate
that operates out of
the Jupiter Sphere. Based on
the rumors I've heard,
they're actually
more like the mafia.
And that's exactly why
we need to contact them.
[BISCUIT]
They do have some influence
among Earth's economic blocs.
If they were escorting us,
Gjallarhorn might think twice
about attacking us again.
[SHINO]
That sounds great,
but how are supposed to
negotiate with them?
[EUGENE] Good point. What makes
you think they'll even want
to talk to kids like us, anyway?
We got nothin'
to offer those guys.
[BISCUIT]
I wish we had a connection.
Goin' to Earth is off
the table for now.
And we can't go back home.
We either go to Jupiter
or we rot out here.
As far as finding someone to
set a meeting, I don't know.
Might have to do it ourselves.
You're out of your mind.
[CHAD]
Amazing. How'd you do it?
What's goin' on?
[CHAD] I've been having trouble
contacting the guys on Mars,
but she got me through
without any problem at all.
What'd you do?
I simply utilized the Ariadne
that Gjallarhorn controls.
The Ariadne?
Never heard of it.
Even when the effects of an
Ahab Wave hinder their ship's
radar systems, the Ariadne
acts as a guidepost
and allows them to
navigate properly.
By using the
relay points, or cocoons,
that it's composed of,
long distance communication
is possible.
That's great, but won't
Gjallarhorn know
we're using their system?
All of the communications
are encrypted,
so it shouldn't be any issue.
You can really do that?
[FUMITAN]
If you're interested,
I would be willing
to help from now on.
Provided that Miss
Kudelia approves.
[gasps]
Of course. Go ahead.
[ORGA]
Glad to have you.
You can help
with Communications.
Welcome aboard.
[KUDELIA gasps]
Understood, sir.
[CHAD] I look forward
to it, Miss, uh...?
Fumitan Admoss.
[CHAD]
I never knew. It's pretty.
[MIKAZUKI]
Mm?
[ATRA]
Oh! Hey, Kudelia.
[KUDELIA gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
What are you doing?
Catching my breath. I just
discussed our next plan
of action with the
boss and the others.
Uh huh.
I was kinda surprised you
weren't there to participate.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm...
[ATRA]
Hm?
It's just not my speed.
I don't like stuff like that.
I wouldn't understand it anyway.
[KUDELIA]
Mm, but...
What's that?
It's our lunch.
Everybody's busy, so we're
delivering them ourselves.
[KUDELIA]
Oh, I see.
[ATRA]
Later.
[KUDELIA]
H-Hold on.
[ATRA]
Huh?
I-If it's not too much trouble,
I'd like to help you guys out.
Huh?
[ATRA]
Uh...
[CREW chatters]
[ATRA] Great work!
Take a break, guys!
It's lunch time!
[CREW cheers]
One for you...
[BOY A]
Thanks, Mikazuki!
Don't worry,
there's plenty to share.
Okay, here you go.
Hey, thanks a lot, Kudelia.
[AKIHIRO grunting]
Akihiro. Lunch time.
[AKIHIRO]
Kinda busy.
[MIKAZUKI]
I'll leave it here.
[AKIHIRO]
Mikazuki.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
[AKIHIRO] Let's train with
the simulator after this.
[MIKAZUKI]
Okay.
[ATRA] So, are we gonna try and
meet with that Teiwaz person?
Hold on, I thought Teiwaz
was a company, not a person.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
But unfortunately, we don't
know who to mediate with,
so even having a meeting
will be pretty difficult.
[MIKAZUKI]
I see.
You "see"?
This is really important.
Aren't you interested?
Not really. Orga will make
sure everything's all right.
And to be honest, I still
have no idea why you're
even goin' to Earth
in the first place.
[gasps] I didn't know that
we were gonna go to Earth!
Wait, didn't I tell you?
Oh, great. What am I
supposed to do?
I don't have any clothes that're
cool enough to bring there.
What's the matter with
what you're wearing?
[ATRA] We're going to Earth!
If I wear this, they'll think
I'm just a poor girl
from the country!
Freedom for the
Martian people.
Winning that is the reason
I decided to go to Earth.
In the Calamity War,
300 years ago,
the subdivided nations
of Earth were united
into four economic blocs.
Did you know that?
[MIKAZUKI]
No, I didn't.
[KUDELIA]
Oh, I see...
Well, following that,
all of the Outer Spheres,
like Mars and Jupiter,
were divided among the
different economic blocs
and then put under
their administration.
The Chryse Autonomous Region
came under the jurisdiction
of the Arbrau economic bloc.
But thanks to the unfair
Trans-Planetary Economic Pact
from the pioneer days,
people living there were
unjustly exploited
for many years.
I've been negotiating with the
Arbrau government of Earth
in the hopes of reforming
this unfortunate reality.
And the other day,
Togonosuke Makanai,
the leader of Arbrau,
agreed for the first time to
hold talks on this issue.
If all goes well,
we'll have won economic
independence for Mars.
That is my goal, and I
truly believe it will lead
to the happiness of
everyone who lives there.
[clapping]
That's amazing, Miss Kudelia.
[KUDELIA gasps]
Okay... So you plan
on goin' to Earth
because you want
to make us happy?
[KUDELIA]
Uh...
[gasps]
Yes. That's my intention.
[elevator beeps, doors clatter]
[CREW MEMBER C] This thing
really took a beating out there.
[CREW MEMBER D] I'm surprised
he made it back alive.
[YUKINOJO] Alright, stop moving
your mouths and move your hands.
[CREW MEMBER C]
Yes, sir.
[ATRA] Thanks for your
hard work! We brought lunch.
Ah, great. I appreciate it.
Hey! Stop what you're doin' and
come have some food, you guys!
Yes, sir!
Nice! I'm starving!
[ATRA]
There's no need to rush, boys.
Here now, don't be shy.
[gasps]
Thanks a lot, Miss.
Do you want me to
help out here?
Yeah. When it's time
for the heavy lifting.
We're still doing some fine
tuning right now, though.
And you'd... need to
know how to read.
Yeah, okay, I understand.
Mikazuki. You really
don't know how to read?
[MIKAZUKI]
Mm.
How could that be? I mean,
you operate this complicated
machine all the time.
[MIKAZUKI] Well, it's not
like I move it by reading.
It's basically the
same as a Mobile Worker.
The rest is instinct.
[KUDELIA gasps]
Really?
Yeah. I don't know why
you're so surprised.
[KUDELIA] Hold on.
Didn't you go to school?
No I didn't.
I think the ones who did
are a minority around here.
[YUKINOJO] Well, a lot of them
were desperate just to survive.
So there wasn't much
time for an education.
A few of 'em are from
slightly better facilities,
so they might
have learned some.
I had no idea.
I finished the deliveries.
[MIKAZUKI] Do you know
how to read, Atra?
Yeah! The shop
keeper taught me.
Mikazuki. I was just wondering,
would you maybe like to
learn how to read and write?
[MIKAZUKI]
What?
I would be glad
to show you.
'Cause knowing how can
be a really useful skill,
as well as a great tool.
By reading books or
writing letters and essays,
you can expand your own
world like never before.
[ATRA]
Uh.
No kidding.
So I'll be able to read
different types of books, huh?
Yes! Exactly.
[YUKINOJO]
Hmm.
[MIKAZUKI]
I guess it's worth a shot.
[EMBI]
Me too!
I'd like to learn,
if you wouldn't mind
having another student.
Think we could join Mikazuki?
Please! Come on!
Yeah, I wanna learn how!
Will you be our teacher, too?
Me? A teacher? I uh...
[ATRA giggles]
[KUDELIA]
Uh.
[YUKINOJO grunts]
Sure. If you're okay with it,
then let's all study together.
Awesome!
This is so cool!
We're gonna study!
Yeah! That's the
right attitude, you guys!
All right... I can
teach you too,
so if you have
any questions, just ask.
[EMBI]
Wait. You, Atra?
[ELGAR]
Think I'd prefer Miss Kudelia.
Huh? Hold on! What's that
supposed to mean?
[TROW]
It's nothin'!
[ATRA]
I can do it too. Ugh...
Connection. Think...
[FUMITAN] Is there something
I can help you with, sir?
Uh. Yeah, uh...
Actually. Would you mind
watching things here for minute?
[FUMITAN]
No. Not at all.
Thanks. I'll be right back.
[NOBLISS] I see. Coral bit
the big one, huh?
I didn't expect that
idiot to be this useless.
Those kids seem more
capable than he ever was.
[grunts] The young knights
protecting their new princess.
This might be even more
interesting than I thought.
[MCGILLIS] All right.
Second Lieutenant Ein Dalton?
Sir!
[MCGILLIS] We know that you
engaged a civilian organization
outside Chryse under
Coral's orders.
Your company planned
to defeat them
with your overwhelming power,
but that plan went
south rather quickly.
I want to know
why that happened.
Was it due to the
enemy's Mobile Suit?
[EIN]
Yes, sir.
I want to hear your
honest impression.
How would you gauge
his abilities?
Well, at first...
I was surprised
a civilian organization
even had a Mobile Suit.
But then, once the
battle started,
it turned into a different
kind of surprise.
A little more specific.
It was... something I never
experienced in training.
The mobility,
the reaction speed...
Their tactics caught us off
guard and that's when we...
[MCGILLIS] I see.
This certainly helped.
That's all for now.
You are dismissed.
[EIN] Specialist Major, sir.
I have a favor to ask.
Go ahead.
I wasn't good enough out there
and my superior officers
paid the price.
I can't return to Mars
in disgrace like this.
And therefore...
...I request permission
to join the pursuit force.
Please give me
this chance, sir.
I understand what you're saying.
I'll think about it.
[EIN]
Thank you, sir.
You'll have orders later.
You can go now.
Sir!
[MCGILLIS]
Gundam, huh?
[KUDELIA]
Okay.
Learning how to write your name
is the perfect way to start.
Try making it as
neat as you can.
[EMBI] Miss Kudelia!
Look at my writing.
Me too!
[EMBI]
Did I do it okay?
[KUDELIA]
Let's see.
Huh. You both
did a great job.
[EMBI, ELGAR]
We're awesome!
[grunts]
[EMBI, ELGAR]
Huh?
[EMBI, ELGAR laugh]
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
[KUDELIA]
[KUDELIA giggles]
Not too bad.
But a couple of your letters
are kinda backwards.
See? And this one too.
Huh?
[EMBI, ELGAR laugh]
[MIKAZUKI] Okay I knew there
was something wrong with it.
I think you should stick
to piloting, Mr. Mikazuki.
Writing isn't your thing.
I can't wait to tell
all the other guys
how I beat you at handwriting.
[TAKAKI] Embi, Elgar! You need
to quit running your mouths
and start focusing on practice!
Fine.
[ELGAR]
I'll race ya!
Things are different now that
the adults are all gone!
We're gonna need to man up,
and do our best to
contribute to Tekkadan.
Do you understand me?
[EMBI, ELGAR]
Yeah.
Takaki is strict.
He has to be.
He's the leader of all the
younger children here.
He's doin' his best so he can
catch up to the rest of us.
Wait, isn't that
spelled with a "d"?
But it's pronounced
with a "z", right?
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
Orga?
[BOY SOLDIER A]
Come on, let's go!
[BOY SOLDIER B]
Okay!
[BOY SOLDIERS grunt]
Hey, kids. Watch where
you're runnin'.
[BOY SOLDIER A] I-It won't
happen again, Boss.
Fine. Just be careful.
[BOY SOLDIER A]
Right!
[BOY SOLDIER B]
Sorry, sir.
Way to go, dummy!
[BOY SOLDIER A]
Shut up!
[BISCUIT]
Orga.
[gasps]
[BISCUIT] I'm sorry. But without
some kind of connnection,
it'll be almost impossible
to negotiate with Teiwaz.
What should we do?
[BISCUIT] I don't know,
but we should be careful
about this before we
make any rash decisions.
I've been thinkin'.
Goin' over it again and again,
but I can't find a better way
to get us outta this mess.
Try not to take this
the wrong way,
but this job may be a little
too much for Tekkadan right now.
I mean, none of us have
any work experience.
[ORGA]
So what, then?
[BISCUIT gasps]
Should we break our promise,
give up on Kudelia,
and hand her over to the first
Gjallarhorn ship we find?
No. That's not what I'm saying.
Maybe we could subcontract
another company
to take the job over for us.
[ORGA]
Out of the question.
We made a commitment.
We're gonna move forward.
[BISCUIT] Don't you feel like
you're kinda rushing things?
[ORGA]
Hm?
To be honest with you, it almost
seems like you're trying
to take the most
dangerous path on purpose.
[ORGA]
Hm. Maybe.
I don't get it.
Why are you so stuck on
moving forward, Orga?
Because I'm bein' watched.
[BISCUIT]
Huh?
Whenever I turn around,
I see his eyes locked on me.
[BISCUIT]
Whose eyes?
[ORGA]
Mika. That kid's amazing.
Through the years,
he's always been so brave.
Mastered a Mobile Suit
in his first battle
and now he's learning
to read and write.
I know that when
he's looking at me,
it's like he's asking, "Orga,
what are we gonna do next?
And what are some
of the new things
that you're gonna
show me, today?"
I can't let him down.
I can't betray those eyes.
[BISCUIT gasps]
As far as he's concerned, I need
to be completely fearless.
It's because of him that
I've gotta keep my cool.
[gasps]
We head to the Teiwaz
headquarters. No changes.
[MIKAZUKI]
So, you are here.
[ORGA]
That's right.
[MIKAZUKI]
You were watching us, earlier.
[ORGA]
You knew, huh?
Question: Why'd you wanna
learn to read and write
all of the sudden?
Because Kudelia said that
she'd teach me, I guess.
And all of the others, too.
Ah.
Plus, if I can't
read and write,
I can't help out with
Mobile Suit maintenance.
Also, I can't do it yet,
but some day I want to
read all kinds of books
and try to learn everything
that I can about vegetables.
Forgot about that.
You did tell me you wanted
to run a farm, didn't you?
Just like Biscuit's
grandmother, Sakura.
[MIKAZUKI]
Mm.
Orga, aren't you tired yet?
Aw, nah, this is nothin'.
And, you?
Figured the battle the other
day would've worn you out.
Don't worry. I'm fine.
Glad to hear it.
'Cause Earth is still far away.
But you've decided
to go, huh?
[ORGA]
Yeah. The die's been cast.
It's up to us to keep going
'till the bitter end, right?
[MIKAZUKI]
Right.
'Cause we finally found a
place where we belong.
As it stands now,
everyone's lives and future
depend on Tekkadan.
[EMBI]
Um, excuse me, Miss Kudelia.
Did I spell all
these words right?
[KUDELIA]
Hm.
Uh. The first
two are. Not these.
Can you see the difference?
[EMBI]
Um...
[KUDELIA]
An Alaya-Vijnana System...
On such a small child.
[EMBI]
Hm? Oh! It's cool, isn't it?
Huh? It is.
I can do all kinds of work
thanks to this little baby.
The operation hurts, but I
think I'll have it done again.
[gasps] Once was enough for me.
It's way too painful!
I knew you were a coward, Elgar.
Huh?
[EMBI]
If you can't learn to take it,
you'll never be like...
[KUDELIA] I can't believe this
is a reality for these kids.
We have to protect her.
Yeah, I know.
You don't change, huh?
And you?
What do you think?
I am who I am.
Got that right.
We're gonna succeed.
I promise you.
Tekkadan will be unstoppable
and you'll be able to live
that dream of yours.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm.
[alarm blares]
What the hell?
Someone talk to me!
Another ship's
ordering us to stop.
A ship? Position?
[FUMITAN]
Unknown, sir.
Do you think it could
be Gjalllarhorn?
I don't know.
I can't identify it!
You give me back my ship,
you little twerps!
Him?!
[MARUBA]
How dare you--
Wait, that's President Maruba!
I'll have your heads,
you thieving rats!
You had better give
back my Will-O'-the-Wisp !
Dammit. What's he doin' here?
♪
[YUKINOJO] You know,
when I first met Maruba,
the two of us were
pretty young and cocky.
But, he wasn't such
a jerk back then.
He liked dogs. He even
took in two puppies.
What were their names again?
Hmm... Ken-Ken and Wan-wan?
Ah, whatever.
Who the hell wants to hear my
stories about Maruba, anyway?
Next time on Mobile Suit
Gundam: Iron Blooded Orphans,
Episode 7: "Whaling."