[YUKINOJO]
Well, there they go.
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah.
What's wrong? Is being away from
them makin' you feel lonely?
[MIKAZUKI]
Eh. Somethin' like that.
[YUKINOJO]
Hm. Don't worry about it,
you'll catch up to them soon.
Once Barbatos is overhauled.
[MIKAZUKI]
I guess so.
[YUKINOJO] He may be strong,
but sometimes I forget
he's still a kid, too.
[CHIEF MECHANIC]
Hey! Mikazuki!
Let's begin the
Alaya-Vijnana System check.
Yeah, okay.
[chuckles]
[TAKAKI] Alright!
That's good. Steady now.
Careful, Ride! Don't treat
it so rough, okay?
We have to deliver this one
to the industrial colony intact.
It's just a bunch of
minerals right?
They'll be just fine.
[TAKAKI] Moron! Teiwaz trusted
us with this cargo.
If it's banged up
when we deliver it,
they could lose
faith in Tekkadan.
[RIDE]
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
That little brat.
Okay. Whaddya say we
finish this work
before lunch, guys?
[TECHNICIANS]
Yes sir.
[TAKAKI] Hey! Don't get
so close to the crane!
[RIDE] What's up with him?
He's extra annoying today.
[ATRA]
Mikazuki and Miss Kudelia...
Guess they looked happy.
[BISCUIT pants]
Atra?
Strange to see you here.
What are you doing?
Me? Nothing.
So... what are you doing?
[gasps] Actually, we just
got messages in from Mars.
[gasps]
♪
[DEXTER] Everything's going
pretty smoothly here.
The support we received from
Teiwaz arrived without a hitch.
Thanks to you,
we have enough money
to keep running for a
while now. On top of that,
we haven't heard so much
as a peep from Gjallarhorn
since you left.
Hopefully it stays that way
so business can continue.
[SHINO] Everybody on Mars
seems to be doin' okay.
And now that Teiwaz has
our backs, Gjallarhorn will
think twice about sticking
its nose in our business.
Yeah, no kidding. Gotta say,
they're pretty awesome.
Right, Biscuit?
Huh? Yeah. Pretty awesome.
Hey, it's all right.
Don't worry about us. Get going.
Oh. Sorry. See you, guys.
[EUGENE]
What's with him?
He got a message from
his sisters back on Mars.
[SHINO] Oh yeah? Why doesn't
he watch it out here then?
He's just trying to
be considerate, Shino.
Lotta the guys out here
don't have anyone back home,
so he thought it'd be better if
we got our messages separately.
You know him.
[SHINO]
Guess so. Classic Biscuit.
Who cares about family messages?
I'd rather get one from a woman.
"Oh, I miss you, Eugene. When
will you come back to me, baby?"
[SHINO] Well, you have
fun with your dream girl.
I'll settle for
chasing the boobs
I actually can get my hands on.
You're so dumb! Those are
nothing but skin bags.
Don't you know that love and
kindness are what's important?
Oh, I had no idea.
You know a lot for someone who
just had his cherry popped.
[EUGENE]
You... Shut up!
You know what I'm
talking about, right?
Huh? Sorry. I don't really
care about that stuff.
[chuckles] Oh? Our leader
is inexperienced.
If you want to be a real man,
you should at least
know a woman or two.
[SHINO] Yeah, Orga. Listen to
Mr-Know-It-All-Cherry-Boy.
Ah! I'm gonna punch
your teeth in.
[SHINO mockingly]
Don't, Eugene!
Will you guys just
shut up, already?
The only thing that matters
to me is Tekkadan.
[CRACKER] Um, are you
sure it's recording?
[COOKIE] I think so.
Hi, Biscuit! Cookie here!
And Cracker, too! What's up?
[COOKIE] We already
finished harvesting!
Isn't that great? There were
a lot of sandstorms this year,
so there were less crops,
but we're still A-Okay.
We worked hard, so you can
praise us when you're home.
I hope it's soon!
[COOKIE]
Wherever you are, Biscuit,
you better take care
of yourself for us!
[CRACKER]
And buy lots of souvenirs too!
[COOKIE] Um... what else do you
think we should we talk about?
[CRACKER]
Well... Oh!
We can tell him about...
[BISCUIT] Hey, Takaki.
Is something wrong?
No. It's just that
I got one too.
[BISCUIT] Really? A message
from your family?
Yeah, it's from
my little sister.
Hey there, Big Brother.
Hope you're doing okay!
Everything's going
great back home.
But it'd be even better if
you were still here with us.
I miss you a lot.
She's very mature.
How old is she?
Six years younger than me.
Just turned seven.
That makes her close
to my sister's age.
Come on! Let's play
another game!
Okay! One second! Talk to
you soon, Takaki. Bye!
Is she in an orphanage?
Yeah. That's right. Fuka's about
as smart as they come, too.
Much smarter than I am.
And now that Tekkadan's
paying me, I can help.
She's safer, now.
That's what I care about.
But I really want to
send her to a school.
Though, at the moment,
it's just a dream.
It's not just a dream. Now that
we're a subsidiary of Teiwaz,
our earnings should
go up considerably.
And if we succeed
on this job,
Tekkadan's name will
get even bigger.
[TAKAKI]
You think so?
You and I are a
lotta like, Takaki.
I want to put my twin
sisters, Cookie and Cracker,
into school too.
I had no idea.
Well then. In that case,
I'll work even harder
to make sure that
my dream comes true.
[BISCUIT]
Hm, That sounds good.
[TAKAKI] Now, I'm pumped!
Let's do this!
These days, all I hear
about you are rumors.
It's dangerous work.
You're putting yourself
at too great a risk.
Your father is even
more worried than I am.
Why don't you stop this
and come home now?
For the sake of the
Bernstine family and--
[beep]
My father is scared of me.
It's as if I were
his worst nightmare.
If he learns we've
joined up with Teiwaz,
he'll probably lose his mind.
[KUDELIA] I know it's late.
And I'm sorry, Fumitan.
I shouldn't have gotten you
involved in any of this.
[FUMITAN]
Being by your side is my duty.
[KUDELIA]
Thank you.
[NAZE] As long as we're using
the Ahab Reactor for power,
radio waves are
completely useless.
Our only checkpoints will be
the network of Ariadne beacons.
Sadly, all of them are under
the control of Gjallarhorn.
If we're gonna be using
these as guideposts,
it'll take some skill to secure
a path and avoid being detected
by their surveillance system.
But, lucky for you,
that is our specialty.
All I'm gonna need you guys
to do is to steer the ship
exactly as I tell you.
[ORGA grunts]
Ok, that shouldn't be a problem.
What is, are the other
scoundrels in our line of work.
Exactly.
I don't follow.
[AMIDA] The path around
the Ariadne Network
is effective for
avoiding Gallerhorn.
But, there are pirates who're
known to prey on ships
passing through there.
[NAZE] The Turbines are known
for being a militant group,
So, unless they're
some kinda daredevils,
I doubt anyone else would
pick a fight with us.
[TAKAKI]
Okay, we're all done here.
[RIDE] Hey, hold on.
Where are you goin'?
[TAKAKI] The simulator.
I wanna get some training in.
We might be asked to work
outside one of these days.
[RIDE sighs] That guy has
way too much energy.
[NAZE]
Oh, that's right.
We left Saisei in such a hurry,
that I forgot to tell you.
We've decided to station a
representative from Teiwaz
on board the Isaribi
from now on.
Are you serious?
Yeah. Serving as an
overseer for the old man.
[ORGA]
I see...
[EUGENE, BISCUIT gasp]
[ORGA]
Funny.
I thought becoming blood
brothers meant we were trusted.
[NAZE]
Don't jump to conclusions.
We need a liaison for both
sides to work well together.
Anyway, she's a pretty
versatile woman to have around.
Wait. What?
You can come on in.
[gasps]
[MERRIBIT] Nice to meet you.
My name's Merribit Stapleton.
She used to work in
the banking division
of the Teiwaz organization.
When it comes to business,
she's the best there is.
Lucky you. You're inexperienced
in that department, am I right?
She can teach you
everything you'll need.
Yeah. I bet.
There's nothing but guys here.
Might be a bad idea.
Hello again.
Huh?
Huh? You two already
know each other?
Yes. I met him a few
days ago on Saisei .
Well, then. That makes
things easier.
[ORGA]
But, I-I don't...
[MERRIBIT sighs]
[ORGA]
Hm?
[gasps]
[grunts]
[NAZE]
What?
[gasps]
I uh... don't really remember.
[NAZE] Well, whatever.
That's the deal.
This is an order straight from
the old man, so play nice.
Yes, sir...
[gasps]
Looking forward to
working with you.
[ORGA grunts]
Yeah. Same here.
[BOY C] Look, there she is!
It's Ms. Merribit.
That's how adult women
are supposed to look.
Hey, hey! Wouldja quit
staring like creepers.
Don't you kids have work to do?
[MERRIBIT]
Hey!
Eugene, right?
I could use your help.
Uh... Sure, what is it?
I'll help with
whatever you want.
Just say the word and I'll--
[MERRIBIT] Have you seen
your boss around recently?
[EUGENE] Ah, no.
You should try the bridge.
Great. Thanks a lot.
[EUGENE]
Yeah, sure...
[grunts]
[BOYS chuckle]
Get back to work!
[BOYS laugh]
[MERRIBIT]
Boss.
[MERRIBIT grunts]
Sorry!
[ORGA]
Yeah.
Whenever you get a chance,
I'd like to see the food
and supply list.
[ORGA]
What?
[MERRIBIT] I need it to
prepare the balance sheet.
[ORGA]
'Kay, no problem.
I'll have Biscuit
get it for you.
[MERRIBIT]
Thank you.
This is a great ship.
I was surprised.
Hard to believe it's
run by children.
[ORGA] Can you please not treat
us like we're a bunch of kids?
[gasps]
My apologies. I didn't
mean it like that.
Oh, by the way.
About your handkerchief...
So you did remember
after all.
Sorry. I kind of lost it.
I was pretty wasted then.
Please, don't worry about it.
Wasn't expecting to see
it again, anyway.
Were you spying on us? Is that
why you were there that night?
No, of course not! It was a
coincidence that I was there.
You don't have to hide it.
If watching us is your job,
it's your job. But remember,
This is our house, so you're
gonna need to play by our rules.
Got it?
You don't like me,
do you? Be honest.
[ORGA] Doesn't really matter.
I have my orders.
[EMBI]
Gimme a break.
Fumiton is nice, but Miss
Merribit is way sexier.
[ELGAR]
Right? Adult women are the best.
And boys are all idiots.
[KUDELIA]
Excuse me, Atra?
Uh, yes?
I was just wondering
if you could use
another pair
of hands in here?
Uh, yeah. Sure!
[KUDELIA] It's nice to
actually move around.
Kinda helps me forget my
troubles for a little while.
[ATRA]
What do you mean?
[exhales]
Sorry, it's not a big deal.
[ATRA]
Hm...
[ATRA blows]
Hey, Atra? Where are
your parents?
Long gone.
[KUDELIA gasps]
I'm sorry.
[ATRA]
Don't be. Mikazuki was there.
And there were other ones, too.
So have you known the people in
Tekkadan for a long time, then?
[ATRA]
Hm...
Well, I first met them
when I was 10 years old.
Seems like a long
time ago, now.
It was after I worked for a
place that only employed girls.
Compared to the older
ones who made the money,
I was still young and small,
so I took care of
all the chores.
Unfortunately, I wasn't really
that good at doing them well.
[ATRA yelps]
[WOMEN laugh]
[ATRA] I messed up a
different way each day
and I got scolded
for it every time.
I got bullied and
beat up a lot, too.
If I made a mistake,
they wouldn't give me
any food for days.
I got so hungry that
I couldn't sleep.
So one night,
I decided to run away.
[gasps]
[MAN grunts]
[ATRA yelps]
[PEDESTRIAN A] Is it
your first time today?
[PEDESTRIAN B]
Uh, yeah...
[PEDESTRIAN A] Then we'll
celebrate with drinks later.
[ATRA groans]
I'm not gonna share with you.
I don't want it.
Good. I worked hard
just to get this much.
[ATRA ]
I'll work too.
Nobody's gonna hire
someone your age.
And girls aren't
allowed in the CGS.
[ATRA ] I can work.
We're about the same age.
--[ATRA whimpers]
--[stomach growls]
[sighs]
[door clatters]
This is all I got.
[HABA]
Hm?
[MIKAZUKI] I don't care what
it is, just sell me some food.
What's wrong?
It looks like she's too hungry
even to stand up anymore.
[HABA sighs]
[ATRA] He saved me.
Once the manager heard all
I'd been through, she hired
me right on the spot.
After that, I started to help
make deliveries to CGS.
I'm here 'cause
Mikazuki saved me.
I have so much to
be grateful for.
I see. You went through
some hard times, huh?
No. It's not like that.
Ever since I met Mikazuki
and the others,
things have been great.
[KUDELIA] You know what, Atra?
I'm kinda jealous of you.
Huh?
[KUDELIA] You may not
have siblings or parents,
but you have an entire families'
worth of people you can trust,
and I know there're so many out
there who aren't as fortunate.
I have parents, but I don't feel
that I can trust them at all.
In fact, my father
hates everything I do.
And wants me dead.
[ATRA gasps]
[whimpers]
Sometimes I...
[ATRA]
Excuse me, but... Um...
Maybe it's a misunderstanding.
I-It has to be, right? I mean,
a father wouldn't do that.
They're supposed to love their
daughters, no matter what.
When Mr. Ivan, who lived
next to me, had a daughter,
she was all he could talk
about for months at a time.
I-I'll just shut up. Sorry.
I-I don't know even
what I'm saying.
[KUDELIA sobs]
It's fine.
Don't worry.
Kudelia?
Please don't forget that you're
one of our friends, too.
You're part of our family now.
Seriously? You mean that?
[grunts]
Oh?
[KUDELIA] Thank you.
That makes me very happy.
[ATRA giggles]
[gasps]
[ATRA]
Wait.
If Miss Kudelia and I are
part of the same family.
[ATRA]
That means... That means...
That means...!
Oh, wow! We could be
just like the Turbines!
Yes! That way everyone
gets what they want!
[KUDELIA]
Atra?
Let's hang in and
do our best, Kudelia!
Uh... Sure.
[AKIHIRO grunting]
[LAFTER] Oh! Hey, you finished
faster than usual.
Wanna go another round?
[AKIHIRO] No... I can't.
It's almost time for my patrol.
[LAFTER] Bummer. Wait... Are you
sure everything's all right?
[AKIHIRO]
Hm?
You were so different.
I've never seen
you fight like that.
It was a lot less
reckless and suicidal,
but still pretty persistent.
Well... Keep it up, Akihiro.
[AKIHIRO grunts]
Right.
[AKIHIRO]
I changed, huh?
[FUMITAN] Please come
in from the cargo hatch.
Your patrol duties will
be starting in 15 minutes.
Roger that.
Hey, Akihiro, are you
about to go on patrol?
[AKIHIRO]
Yeah.
Awesome. Would you mind
if I tagged along, too?
I've been hittin' the
simulator pretty hard.
I won't be any trouble.
I promise.
Well, I guess two pairs of eyes
are better than one out there.
[gasps]
[TAKAKI]
Sorry. Hope I wasn't too pushy.
Hey, it's all right.
What's goin' on?
[TAKAKI]
I got a message from my sister.
See, I've always
had this dream about
letting her go off
to school some day.
So, I want to learn
a few other jobs.
And, if I can do that,
I can make more money .
I really want to work hard
for her. I-I'm sorry.
[AKIHIRO]
Hm. What?
You can't talk about your
family to Human Debris?
[TAKAKI]
Uh, no. I just...
Forget about it.
I could see you were tryin'
hard for your sister.
Nothing wrong with that.
You know. I've never told
anyone about this, but...
...I had a younger brother.
Are you serious?
[AKIHIRO]
His name was Masahiro.
We were part of a family that
owned a merchant ship fleet.
And we used to travel between
spheres for weeks at a time.
Here you are.
[AKIHIRO grunts]
You too, huh?
[MASAHIRO]
Yeah!
Okay. Try your hand at this one.
[MASAHIRO grunts, yelps]
Are you all right?!
--[MASAHIRO groans]
--[AKIHIRO laughs]
Don't push yourself
too hard, Masahiro.
Hey, don't laugh at me!
It isn't funny!
Ah! I'm not gonna fall behind!
[AKIHIRO]
Then one day...
[gunshots]
[AKIHIRO]
We were hit by pirates.
All the adults were killed,
Including our parents.
[MASAHIRO, AKIHIRO whimper]
[AKIHIRO] After that, we were
treated as Human Debris.
We were separated
and sold for dirt cheap
to anyone who would take us.
Let go! Give him back to me!
Big Brother! Please, help me!
I'm gonna find you!
[PIRATE A]
Shut up.
[MASAHIRO]
Brother!
[AKIHIRO] Since that day,
I haven't seen any sign of him.
Then again, I've been
busy taking care of myself
all these years. Truth be told,
I'd forgotten all about him.
Now that I've joined Tekkadan,
they're just as important
as any brother to me.
But it makes me think.
I had a real family
of my own once.
If he's alive, he'd be about
as old as you, Takaki.
No kidding.
[AKIHIRO] But, he's probably
long gone now.
[gasps]
Don't say that, Akihiro.
I'm sure if you keep
going down this path,
you'll see him again.
I hope you're
right about that.
Well. I think we've
come far enough.
Let's go home.
[TAKAKI]
Sounds good.
[TAKAKI gasps]
Hold on.
[AKIHIRO]
What is it?
[TAKAKI] Look. 2 o'clock.
That star is moving.
[AKIHIRO]
Wait a minute...
That's an Ahab Reactor signal!
Dammit!
Those are Mobile Suits!
We need to leave!
[TAKAKI]
Yes, sir.
[grunts]
[AKIHIRO]
Takaki, hold on tight!
Right!
[FUMITAN]
Communication from our Graze.
They're being attacked
by unknown fighters.
Three have been spotted.
[grunts] You've gotta be
kidding me. Distance?
[BISCUIT]
About 1,600.
[growls]
Crap!
[grunts]
Takaki. What?
[gasps]
Whoa...
[sighs]
[AKIHIRO]
Mikazuki...
♪
[CHAD]
Yeah, I know. You're right.
The sleeve is completely frayed.
But it's okay.
Just leave it like that.
Before I came here, all I
ever had were clothes
that were worn out,
ripped, or tattered,
so it feels better
when they're dirty.
What? Who am I?
I'm Chad! Chad Chadan!
You know, I'm always
on the bridge!
Next time on Mobile Suit
Gundam: Iron Blooded Orphans,
Episode 11:
"Human Debri."