[CRACKER] I wonder if
Brother is on that thing.
[COOKIE]
Kinda doubt it.
He's still on
Earth working, isn't he?
Well, I sure hope he
comes back home soon.
Yeah, then we can
all play again.
Hey, Cookie, do you think they
have corn on Earth like we do?
[COOKIE]
I don't know why they wouldn't.
[CRACKER giggling]
Earth corn!
[COOKIE]
That sounds weird.
[CRACKER]
No it doesn't!
[BISCUIT] Listen to me!
If you do, I'll...
I'll quit Tekkadan.
[BISCUIT] I need to go back
and have a talk with him.
[BISCUIT] I wonder if it's seed
planting season on Mars now.
I sure hope Cookie and Cracker
aren't causing Grandma
any trouble back home.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hey, Biscuit.
[BISCUIT]
Uh?
Mikazuki?
Gjallarhorn's on their
way to the island.
[BISCUIT]
Are you serious?
Yeah. I'm gonna need
you to follow me.
Orga's making a plan
and he wants you there.
[BISCUIT]
Uh?
You sure?
[MIKAZUKI] Hm? Well, yeah.
Something happen?
[BISCUIT]
Uh... You could say that.
We argued about what
we're going to do next.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
Mikazuki? I...
♪
[TECHNICANS chattering]
[YUKINOJO]
I want to see some hustle!
Stop standing around and start
assembling the Mobile Workers.
Wait! who's going
to check Gusion?
[ECO] Hey! Don't worry,
I can handle that.
I just finished with Rouei.
[YUKINOJO]
You're an angel! Get to it!
[ECO]
Okay!
One, two...
[RIDE] Holy crap! How'd they
get out here so fast?
[ORGA]
Just got confirmation.
Gjallarhorn ships are
within sight of the island.
[MAKANAI]
Hm.
[KUDELIA] Even if they're
under different command,
how could a unit of
Gjallarhorn act on their own,
without approval?
Well, well, well. It appears
that you've managed to ruffle
some not so ordinary feathers.
You've aroused the ire of the
Issue family's daughter,
and their the most powerful
of the Seven Stars.
Now, she's a woman
with a lot of pride.
She must be burning for
the chance to repay you
for the shame she felt after
you escaped her in orbit.
You mean,
even the Oceanian Federation
government cant stop them?
[MAKANAI] Remember.
This is a desert island.
It's not at all like the
cities where Ahab Reactors
are prohibited. Information is
easier to control here.
[KUDELIA grunts]
[MAKANAI] So, what will
you do? I'm quite curious.
We won't be safe even
if we hand over Kudelia.
That's probably the only
thing that you said
I actually agree with.
Oh! Did I really
say such a thing?
[grunts]
The way I see it,
we've only got one choice.
[BISCUIT grunts]
I've decided.
We'll take you and Kudelia and
escape this island together.
[KUDELIA]
Orga...
[ORGA] Don't worry.
This is what's best for us.
[KUDELIA]
O-Okay.
But this job'll cost ya.
Hear me, Old Man?
Don't forget it.
Very well. All you have to
do is drop me off at the
Arbrau Parliament in Edmonton.
Now, how are we going to handle
this current situation?
I'll make arrangements for
the ship to transport us.
[ORGA, BISCUIT gasp]
Do you have any idea
where you can get one?
Because, unless you can get a
ship to the island carefully,
Gjallarhorn won't
hesitate to strike.
Now you just let Tekkadan
worry about that, all right?
I like your confidence, Orga.
In this situation,
that's all we have left.
I'm gonna need you to
take care of the ship.
Sure, you got it.
Heh. Okay, then.
it looks like we'll be business
partners from now on.
[KUDELIA gasps]
Guess so. I know
I can count on you.
[TEKKADAN MEMBERS chatter]
[ATRA]
Here.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER A]
Thanks.
[ATRA] There's still a
lot more left, you guys.
[SHINO]
Hm?
[SHINO] Come on eat up,
this stuffs good for ya.
[YAMAGI]
Oh? Right. Thanks.
[SHINO]
Whatcha looking up at there?
[YAMAGI] I was just
wondering if we're gonna
make it back to Mars.
[SHINO]
Yeah! Of course we will.
But if we wanna do that, we need
to get off this island first.
[YAMAGI]
And then what?
[gasps]
Hm?
[YAMAGI] I mean, Gjallarhorn
will still come looking for us
even after we leave
this place behind.
[SHINO] Then we can
just take off into space.
[YAMAGI] Well, whether we're
up there or back on Mars,
we're still gonna be on the run.
Okay, lets go.
[YAMAGI]
From now on, nights like these
may start happening
more and more.
And I'm scared.
[SHINO]
Aw, don't worry about it.
We'll blow all our enemies away.
Whether it's Gjallarhorn
or anyone else.
Right, Mikazuki?
[MIKAZUKI]
Mm-hm.
We'll take down anybody who
tries to get in our way.
And we can start worrying about
the future after we leave.
Cuz if we stay,
there's nothing that we
can do, Kudelia either.
[MAKANAI] I take it you've
secured a ship for all of us?
[KUDELIA]
Yes. Don't worry about a thing.
[MAKANAI]
Good. Very good.
What kind of man is wrapped
around your little finger?
[MAKANAI chuckles]
The Maiden of Revolution
seems to be in high
spirits this evening.
[TODO] So what did that
annoying blonde want this time?
Apparently, she needs a mode of
transportation while on Earth.
And rather quickly at that.
Let that spoiled
brat find her own.
[MCGILLIS laughs]
Don't tell me you already
accepted the request.
She uses me like
I'm her servant.
I must say, it's far more
amusing than I expected.
Eeh! Boy you're
easily amused, aren't ya!
[MCGILLIS]
I should be going down soon.
Take care of the rest.
Yeah, yeah.
It's not as if I want to go
to Earth too, or anything.
[ORGA]
Quitting Tekkadan... huh.
[BISCUIT]
Orga.
[ORGA grunts]
[ORGA]
Hey, Biscuit.
You worried about
our battle plan?
No. It's not that.
[BISCUIT]
Hm?
I was just thinking about the
future and where we're headed.
Actually, I've been wanting
to talk to you about that.
I uh...
Not right now.
I wanted to sit down and
sort things out with you.
But considering this situation,
can it wait until after
we leave the island?
Sure.
[ORGA]
Ever since we were kids...
[BISCUIT]
Hm?
...you never complained about
any of my reckless ideas.
Not even one time.
I did complain, actually,
but you just didn't
bother to listen to me.
[exhales] Well, maybe. Guess I
haven't grown up at all, huh?
Now, cause I'm being
hard headed, you want to leave?
Am I really such a bad guy?
[BISCUIT] Maybe we should
discuss this a little later.
We've got more urgent things
to deal with anyway.
[ORGA]
Alright. That's a promise.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER B]
Hand me the wrench.
[BISCUIT]
Old Man, How's it going?
[YUKINOJO] Hm? Hey!
We've got three ready so far.
But I should ask you
the same question?
Are you holding up all right?
[BISCUIT] Hey, even I can
operate a Mobile Worker.
You know what I mean.
You and Orga okay?
[BISCUIT]
Yeah it's fine now.
We've promised to talk
more about everything
after we leave the island.
[YUKINOJO]
Hm.
Glad to hear it.
Here, I'll help you put that on.
[gasps]
[MERRIBIT] So far it looks
like everything's ready.
[ORGA] I wanted to ask
Biscuit to stay in Tekkadan,
but I couldn't bring
myself to say it.
[BISCUIT] I just think that
if we want to survive,
we gotta keep thinking
one step ahead.
We have to.
Oh, "We" have to, huh?
Well, I'm happy to hear
you talking like that.
[gasps]
[YUKINOJO]
As far as Orga's concerned,
I think he needs
someone like you around.
[MERRIBIT] I suppose even you
have a hard time telling him
what you're feeling.
[grunts]
[MERRIBIT] But, you still have
plenty of chances to say it.
[ORGA]
Guess you're right.
[OPERATOR A]
Captain Stenja.
It's past the deadline
for their surrender.
[CORLIS] Hmph. Well, well.
That's more like it.
At last. I can avenge
the death of my brother.
These space rats will rue the
day they crossed Corlis Stenja.
Attention all ships!
Commence the clean-up operation!
Glory to Lady
Carta's battlefield!
It's started.
You better Hurry, Mikazuki.
Right.
Is this really all
we've got left?
'Cause I'm not really
sure how to use it.
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
Wait... That'll work.
Alright. Huh?
What is that?!
[MIKAZUKI] Found it next to
one of those containers.
[SHINO]
Woah!
[SHINO gasps]
[SHINO] A saturation
attack, huh? So typical.
[LAFTER] It's useless
against Mobile Suits.
I guess when you're rich, you
don't care about wasting ammo.
[ORGA] Akihiro, can you aim for
the ship from your position?
[AKIHIRO grunts]
[AKIHIRO]
I'll try.
What the...?!
[OPERATOR A] We're being
attacked by the Mobile Suits.
Those Martian space rats
think they know battle theory,
do they?!
Fine, then! send out
our Mobile Suits too.
[grunts]
I missed.
[LAFTER]
Aim it right, idiot.
Do you want Amida
to yell at you?
[AKIHIRO]
But... I, uh...
[ORGA] What in the hell are
they doing out there?
Biscuit! Move it!
[AKIHIRO] Hang on.
How am I supposed to--
[MIKAZUKI] Akihiro, you still
have that sensation, don't you?
[MIKAZUKI]
Just follow that and shoot.
[grunts]
Now I get it.
[CREW grunts]
There's a direct hit on
the starboard hangar block.
We're taking in water
from the impact area.
I want you to send in
the landing troops first.
Once it's finished,
all hands abandon ship.
Looks like he was able
to correct his aim
just by using his senses.
The Alaya-Vijnana?
That is so cheating.
[gasps]
[ORGA] The Mobile Suits
are coming this way.
[LAFTER giggles]
[ORGA] Try to get rid of them
while they're over the water.
[AZEE, LAFTER]
Roger that.
If they can keep this up,
they're not even
gonna need our help.
[SHINO]
The hell was that?!
Wait a minute.
Are those...?
Lafter and Azee, need you
to focus your fire
on the suits over the ocean.
[AZEE, LAFTER]
Got it!
Now, you guys take
care of the rest!
[SHINO] Oh, we're on it.
Come on, lets go!
You have gotta be kiddin' me!
[SHINO gasps]
[gasps]
Huh?
It's time for you to pay the
price for humiliating us!
[ORGA] Damn it, looks like
they got onto the island
a lot sooner than I
thought they would.
[CARTA] Remember!
We are the Outer Earth
Orbit Regulatory Joint Fleet!
[ROYAL GUARDS] We are
perseverance and fortitudeness!
[ROYAL GUARD A grunts]
[CARTA gasps]
[AKIHIRO]
It was okay to shoot, right?
[MIKAZUKI]
'Course it was.
Barbarian! Where are
your manners?!
[CARTA] It's judgment day
for these savages,
so dont show them any mercy!
[ROYAL GUARDS]
Iron-fisted punishment!
Spearhead Formation. Charge!
[ROYAL GUARDS]
Single point breakthrough!
[SHINO] Time for a
little target practice!
[CARTA]
Bring it on.
What the...?
[gasps]
[SHINO]
Mikazuki!
[shouts]
I'm gonna squash you!
Huh?
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm...
[gasps]
[ROYAL GUARD A] Lady Carta.
Our formation's been disrupted!
What have you done?!
[ROYAL GUARD F grunts]
[SHINO]
Come on!
Unless you wanna die,
keep moving!
Space rat...!
[groans]
[grunts]
We're all using
an Alaya-Vijnana,
so you don't stand
a chance against us!
[ROYAL GUARD B]
I got you!
Didn't think Gjallarhorn would
be so easy to take down,
here on Earth!
[ROYAL GUARD A]
Lady Carta!
[grunts]
What are you doing?!
Now, spread out and take them
down one by one if you have to!
[ROYAL GUARDS]
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Where are the naval forces?!
[ROYAL GUARD A] They're in
combat with unknown machines.
Dammit. Stop moving.
[grunts, gasps]
[LAFTER grunts]
They got through.
Akihiro, two coming your way!
Oh well, I didn't have
many shots left anyway.
But that's alright.
It doesn't matter!
[grunts]
It's too powerful!
This style suits me better!
[TAKAKI]
Well?
They're here. And it's a
bunch of landing troops,
just like boss said.
Let's see what we're
up against. Come on.
All right.
[ORGA] Mika and the others
are putting up a good fight.
[ORGA gasps]
We got company?
[TAKAKI]
Confirmed.
Landing troops just hit
the northeastern shore.
Heading towards
Makanai's place.
Figured as much. How many?
[TAKAKI] Six Mobile Workers
and about twenty soldiers.
[ORGA] Copy that. The two
of you can leave there now
and join up
with Kudelia. Got it?
[TAKAKI, RIDE]
Yes, sir.
Looks like you were right.
They've taken the bait.
As much as they hate our guts,
I just knew there'd be no
way they could ignore
Kudelia and Mr. Makanai.
And I figured they'd land here
if we made the back of
the island look weaker.
But, I didn't expect them
to drop forces from the sky.
Yeah, well things are still
going just like we planned
So far, so good. Heh.
--[explosions]
--[BISCUIT gasps]
[ORGA] All right, let's go
to the next phase.
[BISCUIT]
Got it.
Why hasn't the boss
called us yet?
There's way too
many of these guys!
Stop complaining and just shoot.
[ORGA]
You've all managed to hold on,
and we've lured
them in. Good job.
Now get the hell out of there!
[DIOS, GATT]
Yes, sir.
[CARTA]
I won't accept this.
The Issue family name
can't be tarnished!
But now, at this rate...
[ROYAL GUARD B]
Lady Carta!
[ROYAL GUARD A] There's a
report that the landing troops
have taken control
of the target point.
[CARTA] Perfect! And where
is that girl, Kudelia?
[ROYAL GUARD A]
Uh. They're still searching
the residence, ma'am.
[CARTA] Don't call me
until you've found her!
[explosions]
[gasps]
What?
What happened?
[ROYAL GUARD A]
We uh...
We just lost contact
with the landing troops.
[GATT]
They're coming!
Now hit it, Boss!
[DIOS, GATT]
Yeah! All right!
Join up with Takaki
and the others. you two.
[DIOS, GATT]
On our way!
Now all that's left are
those landing vessels.
Yeah, but... we still
have to stay on guard.
[RIDE]
I hope everyone's okay.
Come on, we're on
guard duty right now.
[RIDE]
I know that.
[MAKANAI] Interesting. They all
appear to be children,
but they're still
quite efficient.
I must admit, I'm impressed.
If we go off shore
aboard those vessels,
the arranged ship will
be waiting for us.
Let's go.
[ORGA] How many more
enemy units are there?
[BISCUIT] The Ahab Wave
reactions indicate there are
five on Mikazuki's runway side,
and three more by Azee and
Lafter on the coastline.
[ORGA]
Those two should be just fine.
They've piloted Mobile
Suits on the battle field
longer than we have.
I just remembered.
Didn't Eco tell us not to get
seawater on these machines?
Well, guess I can't help it now.
What the hell are you doing?
Don't damage Amida's machine!
Cuz I'm the one who's
going to get in trouble!
[ORGA] We're almost there.
if we get rid of them,
we can get everybody
off the island safely.
[BISCUIT]
Right.
[gasps]
Orga! Look! Under Shino!
[ORGA grunts]
That idiot!
[SHINO]
Come on!
Now why won't you
just die already?
[ORGA]
Shino, your feet!
My wha--
[gasps]
Your nothing but a coward!
I got you!
W-What?
L-Lady Carta!
--[ROYAL GUARD E groans]
--[CARTA gasps, grunts]
[sighs]
That was close.
If I fell for our own trap,
I could never live it down.
[ORGA]
Shino, help out Akihiro next.
You got it, Boss.
[CARTA]
You... Damn you!
Another of my
precious subordinates...!
Shut up.
[ORGA] Mika, we secured
the landing vessels.
Take 'em down and
we're out of here.
Who is that?
There!
So he's the head
of these punks!
Just give up.
[MIKAZUKI]
No!
Orga!
Move, Biscuit!
[BISCUIT]
On it!
You are taking the
lives of my men!
How dare you!
[BISCUIT] Theres no way
we're gonna make it.
[grunts]
[BISCUIT]
Orga, you've got to let go!
[ORGA]
What?!
[ORGA grunts]
[gasps]
Biscuit!
[CARTA]
You're still moving?
Its time to say goodbye!
[grunts]
[MIKAZUKI] You bitch.
What have you done to him?
[gasps]
[shouts]
I'll make you pay.
[gasps]
[ORGA]
Hey, uh... Biscuit!
Come on. Answer me!
[ORGA]
Biscuit!
[BISCUIT groans]
[BISCUIT]
I can't hear you... Orga.
I have to keep going.
Not here... Not now...
[BISCUIT grunts]
I can't die.
When this is all over...
...I'll go back to Mars.
To Cookie and Cracker.
And put them through school.
[BISCUIT] Then, we can
all be together again.
[BISCUIT]
So, it can't happen now.
I don't wanna die.
I have to... keep my
promise... to him.
[ORGA gasps]
Biscuit.
[BISCUIT]
Orga...
I know... that we
can make Tekkadan.
[gasps]
[ORGA]
Biscuit?
[ATRA] I think it stopped.
Seems so quiet now.
Everyone, please be safe.
[ORGA sobs]
[ORGA screams]
♪
[GAELIO] Some head towards
death and some escape it.
Ein, I don't want you to die.
To me, your life means
more than so many others.
It has value and a true purpose.
But, now Ive been told that
there's something needed
to keep you alive.
Something requiring...
A sinful and immoral decision.
Next time on Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
Episode 22:
"Not Yet Home."