[MASKED MAN] I had no idea
this could be so much fun.
I'm quite excited. Even more
than I expected to be.
♪
[sighs]
[MAN IN BLACK A]
Excuse me, sir.
[NOBLISS]
What?
[MAN IN BLACK A] It seems the
cargo was safely delivered
to the union members.
But when Gjallarhorn
came to investigate,
it didn't turn into the massive
incident that we'd hoped.
I suppose their forces
within the Earth Sphere
aren't all they're
cracked up to be.
[MAN IN BLACK A] In addition,
we've received multiple reports
of Kudelia Aina
Bernstein at Dort 3.
[NOBLISS]
What?
Did you say Dort 3?
[MAN IN BLACK A] Yes, Sir. Her
watchdog is with her as well.
The hell is that
woman thinking anyway?
[MIKAZUKI]
What's the matter?
I'm not sure I understand.
[MIKAZUKI] Usually, I have no
idea what you're thinkin' about,
but right now, I can tell
something's on your mind.
Oh, it's nothing important.
It's just... I've been
thinking about responsibility
quite a bit, lately.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
[FUMITAN]
Regardless of your actions,
you always bear the
burden in the end.
[MIKAZUKI] Yeah, well, I suppose
that's to be expected, isn't it?
Just like Orga says,
always do things honorably.
You're absolutely right.
You must take responsibility
for yourself.
That goes for me... and you.
[KUDELIA] I'm sorry.
Thank you for waiting.
Uh. What's wrong?
Nothing. We were just talking
about responsibility.
Oh. Is that so?
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
Uh. Well... do you know if
Biscuit managed to meet up
with his older brother yet?
[MIKAZUKI] Not a clue. But I
hope it goes well for him.
Because I never want
him to experience
what Akihiro went through.
Yeah, me too.
A-And, speaking of siblings,
I sometimes think
that you and Orga are
a lot more like brothers
than just a couple of friends.
Yeah?
[MIKAZUKI]
Orga's a lot more...
[MIKAZUKI] Well, I don't know
how to put it exactly.
[UNION MEMBER A] Hurry! We
don't know when they'll be back!
Let's go!
Never thought we'd be hauling
somethin' so dangerous out here.
This is a mess.
[YAMAGI]
What are we supposed to do now?
[EUGENE] I say we go
back to the Isaribi ,
or we're gonna get
dragged into all this.
[SHINO] We should let Mikazuki
know what's happening
before that.
But it isn't time for
the scheduled contact
so we're not gonna have any way
of doing that until then.
[NAVONA] What happened!?
Are you all right?
[UNION MEMBER B]
Mr. Navona.
[UNION MEMBER A] I'm sorry,
but we had to get into a fight
with those guys just to try
to keep the weapons safe.
Whatever happens now,
there's no turning back.
[NAVONA]
We knew this was coming.
It's just sooner than expected.
[UNION MEMBER A]
You're right.
Mr. Navona...
[NAVONA]
So you're Tekkadan?
[ORGA]
And you are?
The name's Navona Mingo.
I'm the leader of the union
out here in Dort 2.
[ORGA] I'm Orga Itsuka,
the boss of all these guys.
Pleasure.
I just found out what happened.
We need to get you
somewhere safe.
You can hide with us
until your pickup arrives.
Well, I suppose we
got no choice here.
Our lives are in your hands.
Then this way.
What's wrong? Aren't you happy
about seeing your brother?
[BISCUIT]
Huh?
[ATRA]
You don't look very excited.
[BISCUIT]
I wanna meet with him.
But I guess I'm kinda worried
he's gonna be disappointed
when he sees me.
Why's that?
When he was the
same age I am now,
Savarin was already working and
trying to make it on his own.
I remember seeing all the things
he was able to accomplish
and wanting
to be just like him.
But I'm not.
Guess I never could be.
[ATRA]
Hey!
Did you forget how hard
you've been working, Biscuit?
Come on, you should
have more confidence.
You think so, huh?
[ATRA]
Mh-hm!
I just wanna thank
him, you know?
'Cause when times got
tough, he was there,
and made sure we
were taken care of.
You don't have to worry, okay?
If I knew a family member
felt that way about me,
I'd treasure them
more than anything.
[BISCUIT]
Thank you, Atra.
Brother.
Biscuit? Is it really you?
[BISCUIT]
U-Uh-huh. It's me.
[SAVARIN] I see. You've grown
so big. I hardly recognize you.
[BISCUIT]
Yeah. I'm 16 years old now.
Hard to believe the little ankle
biter who followed me around
is big enough to lift
me these days.
[BISCUIT]
And you must be... Uh.
It's nice to meet you.
Ah! Sorry! This is my friend.
Huh?
Brother?
It's nothing. Don't mind me.
Excuse me for a moment.
If there's a young lady too,
I'll find a spot where
the three of us can talk.
[ATRA] What'd I tell you?
He's really glad you're here.
[SAVARIN]
Send four or five men and a car.
That's right. We'll be
saved the trouble now.
[ORGA]
Where are we?
[NAVONA] My home,
I'm embarrassed to say.
It's kinda small,
so please bear with me.
Crazy.
I thought the colonies would
be a lot better looking.
[ORGA]
Yamagi.
It's the same kinda
dump Chryse was.
[EUGENE] Nah, Chryse was better.
I mean, at least it had a sky.
Hey, knock it off.
[NAVONA]
I know it's not much,
but this is the area that all
the union workers live in.
The commercial area in Dort 3
is a whole lot nicerthough.
Trust me.
In fact, it's so nice they don't
allow anybody from the slums
to even get near
the neighborhood.
I'm afraid those
born in the slums
are all destined to live
and die here, too.
[UNION MEMBER A]
Unless you're Savarin.
In the past few years, he's the
only one of us that's left.
Yeah, but he was
extremely talented,
and got lucky enough for
a rich family to adopt him.
I take it you guys
know him pretty well?
[NAVONA]
He's a youth from the slums.
But now, he's become
a company executive
who acts as mediator
in our negotiations.
[UNION MEMBER B] But we haven't
gotten a decent reply yet.
[UNION MEMBER A] He changed a
lot since he gained some status.
Now he's a man
on the other side.
I'm sure he has
his reasons for it.
[ATRA] No! Let me go!
Please let me go!
[BISCUIT]
Brother, stop this!
Ow! She bit me!
[BISCUIT]
Atra!
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?!
[SUBORDINATE A]
You fool.
I could ask you
the same thing.
Why are you giving weapons
to the people in the slums?
Hold on, what're
you talking about!?
I am talking about
all the goods
that your friends
hauled into Dort 2!
W-Wait, we were only
delivering the supplies
that Teiwaz gave to us.
Weapons were inside?
[SAVARIN]
I see.
So you guys were
just pawns as well.
Can't blame you for that.
But I can blame
Kudelia Aina Bernstine!
[ATRA]
Huh?
[BISCUIT] Brother, wait.
You have it all wrong.
Gjallarhorn?
This is the leader of the
Mars independence movement?
She's a lot younger than
I thought she'd be...
[SAVARIN] She's been
working with Tekkadan.
[SOLDIER A]
You sure about that?
[BISCUIT]
No... Please...
She isn't--!
It's just as you said.
You've managed to capture
the Kudelia Aina Burnstine.
[BISCUIT]
Huh?!
[LAFTER] The Isaribi 's coming
here? Is everything okay?
Orga and the others managed
to land themselves in trouble
when they made their delivery.
Huh?
It's happening in all
industrial colonies.
The workers' frustrations
are just about
to reach their limits.
I guess centralized
control from Earth
isn't working for them anymore.
Far as I know, most of
the upper management staff
are from there.
Everything runs smoothly
as long as they're happy,
but the scumbags push the
blame onto the workers
whenever profits take a dive.
[AMIDA] Once people started
demanding better treatment
through protests, it was
just a matter of time
till they became more common.
[LAFTER]
I see...
You really should study
more often, Lafter.
Fine.
Y'know, maybe I
should start to protest
for better treatment
around here, too.
You've been more
than a little lax
in your responsibilities,
darling.
I'm sorry about that.
Can you accept the recklessness
of our new brother as my excuse?
[ALL]
No, we can't!
[CHILDREN, SHINO laughing]
[SHINO] You're all full
of energy, aren't ya?
Ha! Whoa! All right!
Hold on tight!
We'll head to Dort 3 in about
an hour. Be ready to move.
We've got a launch
prepared for you.
I hope you guys
are able to use it.
Thanks a lot. Me, too.
Dort 3, huh?
Now I probably shouldn't
be asking this,
but are weapons
really the only way?
The company has to meet us
at the negotiating table.
And we're willing to
do whatever it takes
to make sure that happens.
There are many union
members who believe
what we're doing isn't
extreme enough,
and wanna take
things even further.
I wouldn't be
surprised in the least
if they were planning
something big on their own.
We've held them
back by asking them
to wait for the
negotiation results,
but they could riot
at any moment.
And the problem isn't
just here, either.
Dissatisfaction's
spreading like wildfire
through all the Dort colonies.
I hesitate to ask, but...
if it's possible,
could you lend us a hand?
As you can see, we're nothing
but a bunch of amateurs
when it comes to fighting.
I'm sorry. If we do that,
it'll make trouble for
someone we owe a lot to.
Well, it just was a shot
in the dark anyway.
Please, forget I asked.
It's fine...
Mr. Navona! Look!
[NAVONA]
What happened?
[UNION MEMBER B] It's from one
of ours, undercover in Dort 3.
They captured someone wearing
a Tekkadan uniform.
Our guy thinks that's
Miss Kudelia there with him.
No, what are they doing?
That girl is our cook!
What in the hell
happened over there?
[ringing]
[ORGA]
What is that?
[SHINO]
Uh, it-it's our terminal.
Hey, Orga?
Mika! Are you safe? Talk to me!
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah. What's up?
I'm just makin' the
scheduled contact.
[ORGA]
Are you with Kudelia?
[MIKAZUKI]
Mh-hm.
Did something happen?
[ORGA] It's Biscuit and Atra.
They've been captured.
[FUMITAN]
Please wait, Miss.
But Atra and Biscuit are...
The two of you need
to hide somewhere
until Orga comes down
to pick you up.
[KUDELIA]
What about you?
Can you look after
Kudelia for me?
[FUMITAN]
Understood.
Because protecting the young
miss is also my responsibility.
All right, good.
[FUMITAN] We'll be waiting
here for you. Now be safe.
Mikazuki!
[GAELIO]
Ein.
So have you finished
tuning the machine, yet?
Yes. I can be ready anytime.
[GAELIO]
I understand that you're eager,
but we're gonna need permission
to enter first, all right?
[OFFICER A]
Specialist Major Bauduin.
The captain wants
to speak with you.
[GAELIO]
Yeah, all right.
Now show me you can
handle my Schwalbe Graze.
Sir!
[GAELIO] Have Kimaris ready for
activation before I'm back here.
[MECHANIC A]
Understood!
[GAELIO] Captain, did we finally
get permission to enter?
Actually, I'm afraid you might
have to wait a little longer.
Why's that?
You didn't give
them advance notice.
Permission won't
be easily granted.
Those space rats are
right in front of us!
Well, perhaps that operation
is having an influence
on their current procedures.
"That operation"?
Oh, the Regulatory
Bureau's extensive suppression
of dissatisfied people, huh?
They'll provoke the
dissidents into attacking,
and then round all of
them up in one fell swoop.
They're setting an
example, is that it?
Precisely, and that's
the very reason why
any ships with the Seven Stars
emblem aren't welcome.
The activists will be cautious.
Let the Regulatory Bureau
take the credit for this one.
It'll be better for everyone.
Please be patient.
If you want me to play
politics, then I will.
Thanks, Captain.
That was really great, Captain.
[CAPTAIN A]
There's nothing great about it.
Contact the Mobile Suit Deck.
Don't let the Specialist
Major go out in Kimaris.
For goodness sake. It's my
daughter's birthday today.
So when the hell are we gonna
be able to get in there?
With security this tight,
it's gonna be a problem.
[EUGENE] Wouldn't it
have been faster to go
from the industrial area
with the union guys?
[ORGA]
No use saying that now. Shino!
[SHINO]
Huh?
Dock wherever you can.
[SHINO]
Got it.
[EUGENE]
Seriously?
[footsteps]
[UNION MEMBER D] You're from
Tekkadan, isn't that right?
[SOLDIER A, ASTRA grunting]
[SOLDIER A]
What a stubborn girl.
We know what
you've been planning,
so you might as well
stop trying to hide it.
There isn't anything
for me to talk about.
Not to you two.
Is that so?
I'm not saying another
word to you.
You're just wasting your time.
You'll get it worse back
at the base, sweetheart.
They got drugs and everything.
Heh. You'll tell us
one way or the other.
It takes a special
kind of person
not to crack under
intense interrogation.
[BISCUIT]
Atra... Why did you do that?
[SAVARIN] Biscuit, if she told
you anything about her plans,
you need to tell me.
Do you understand?
I can use it to negotiate
with Gjallarhorn.
So did you know
that Cookie and Cracker
turned nine years old this year?
They're both happy and healthy.
Every day, they help
Grandma on her farm.
And do you know how they were
able to grow up to be so big?
Because you let us go to
Mars and start a new life.
I did that because
you were in the way.
I wanted you gone.
When we were little kids,
I wanted to be just like you.
You meant everything to me.
So why are you doing
something so horrible?!
Don't you see what's
happening here?
What if the union
members start a riot
with the weapons you delivered?
Gjallarhorn was
waiting for this.
An armed uprising gives them
the justification they need
to suppress the workers!
People in the slums we once
lived in will die needlessly.
Do you really want that
kind of bloodshed?!
But it still doesn't
give you the right
to hand Kudelia over to
Gjallarhorn and let her die!
If we hand over the Maiden of
Revolution, this could end!
We might be able to strike up
some kinda deal with them!
If sacrificing her
stops a massacre,
I'm more than willing to do it!
But that girl isn't
Kudelia, you idiot!
What?
She has nothing to do with this.
[SAVARIN] No. She is
Kudelia Aina Bernstein.
Now, wait a minute,
you can't mean that...
[SAVARIN] Being a different
person is of little consequence.
If she can stop
Gjallarhorn, that's enough.
[BISCUIT] Do you hear what
you're saying, brother?
[SAVARIN]
This conversation's over!
Because right now,
we don't have time to go
looking for other options.
[door opens]
Where are you going, Miss?!
I'm so worried about
Atra and Biscuit.
If I go and turn myself in,
at least I know they'll be safe.
I'm afraid I can't
let you do that.
Please, Fumitan,
I have to help them.
No, at this point, it might
even be more dangerous
for Miss Atra if they find out
she's only an imposter.
[gasps]
Listen, Atra told me that I'm
part of the Tekkadan family now.
If I hand her over
to save my own skin,
I'll be no different
than my father.
I realize who's
important in my life.
It's you, Atra, and Tekkadan.
And I have no intention
of betraying any of you!
[FUMITAN] You haven't changed
after all these years, have you?
[KUDELIA]
Huh?
[FUMITAN] Those bright, honest
eyes. I hated them. Always have.
Fumitan...
[FUMITAN]
You could have hope
because you didn't
know any better.
I wished that reality
would slap you in the face
and cloud those eyes
once and for all.
[KUDELIA]
What are you saying?
[FUMITAN]
But before I knew it,
I was the one whose
feelings had changed.
If they hadn't,
I wouldn't understand
things the way I do now.
Because I've
realized every action
comes with a responsibility.
[KUDELIA]
Fumitan.
What are you talking about?
[MASKED MAN] I've been waiting
a long time to meet you.
Miss Kudelia Aina Bernstein.
[KUDELIA]
Wh-Who are you?
[MASKED MAN] Someone like
you shouldn't die here.
This place will soon
be caught in the chaos
of the worker's armed uprising.
I suggest you leave
before it's too late.
[KUDELIA]
What do you want?
[MASKED MAN] Who do you
suppose had Tekkadan
haul the weapons being
used for this revolt?
None other than your
benefactor: Nobliss Gordon.
[KUDELIA gasps]
I'm confident you're old enough
to know exactly what that means.
He's the kind of
man that will do
whatever it takes to use you.
Even sending one of his
own to be at your side.
Wh-What are you trying to say?
You never had a moment's
doubt about your maid here?
[KUDELIA]
Fumitan's like family to me.
We're practically sisters
we've been together so long.
I won't allow you to
accuse her of such things.
[MASKED MAN] Now why don't
you let her deny it herself?
What this man's saying
is true. I'm sorry.
No... You must be lying.
This has to be a joke.
[FUMITAN]
Goodbye, Young Miss.
[KUDELIA]
Wait. Wait, Fumitan!
You are the Maiden
of Revolution.
Please, take care of yourself.
You can become
the hope of the people.
[KUDELIA]
Fumitan!
[BISCUIT] I'm so sorry I got
you into this mess, Atra.
[ATRA] Mm-mm. I'm glad that
I'm the one who got caught.
I hope Miss Kudelia's okay.
Well, Mikazuki's with
her so I'm sure she is.
Yeah.
[ATRA groans]
Atra!
Why did you let them
beat you like that?
What, this? It's nothing.
Used to happen every day
when I was a little girl.
Besides, Miss Kudelia is
a part of our family now.
You're right.
So how'd it go
with your brother?
[ATRA] Did you tell him all the
things you were hoping to?
Well, I...
[explosion]
What happened?
[SUBORDINATE A]
Go look outside.
[SUBORDINATE B]
You got it.
Hey, come here!
There's no driver!
[SUBORDINATE C]
Is it the extremists?
[SUBORDINATE B] They couldn't
have gotten too far.
[SUBORDINATE A yelps]
[thud]
No, wait! Don't shoot! It's me!
Mikazuki?
What happened?
Did those bastards
do this to you?
[ATRA]
Huh? Mm.
Hold on, where's Kudelia?
Is she someplace safe?
Huh?
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah, she's hiding at a hotel.
[sighs]
I'm so glad.
[BISCUIT]
Come on.
Let's get outta this hell hole.
[ATRA]
Huh?
Mikazuki!
[BISCUIT] Okay...
Now what're we gonna do?
I'm not really sure, yet.
Huh? You hadn't
thought about it?
That's...
They're out here!
Don't let them get away!
Wait! Biscuit!
Mika!
[MIKAZUKI]
Orga.
[BISCUIT]
Huh? What are you...?
No time! Get in!
[SAVARIN]
Biscuit!
If you leave now,
so many people in Dort 2
will lose their lives.
I'm begging you. Bring me
that girl so I can save them!
This is our only chance.
[ORGA]
Who's that?
It's Biscuit's older brother.
I'm grateful for all
you've done, Brother.
You worked hard and did what
you could to take care of us
after Mom and Dad died.
I wouldn't be here today
if it wasn't for you.
Then, I--
[BISCUIT]
I'll never forget it!
And I appreciate everything you
did for our sisters and me
more than you'll ever know!
But... that was then!
I'm a member of Tekkadan now!
--Wait...
--[fence rattling]
You won't get away!
[ORGA]
Biscuit!
Punch it!
Let's get outta here!
[SOLDIER A]
Stop right there!
Wait!
I'm so sorry, Mr. Navona.
The only thing I can
do now... is...
All right. Are you ready?
[ORGA]
Kudelia's missing? Dammit...
We're gonna have to find her
before she gets caught
in the crossfire.
Miss Kudelia. Where did you go?
[KUDELIA panting]
[KUDELIA]
Fumitan. Where are you?
Fumitan....
[FUMITAN] I'll have to
thank that Masked Man
for what he's done.
I thought I had understood
my mission and obligations.
But being so
foolishly innocent,
she will surely believe
in me, and look for me.
Goodbye... Young Miss.
Next time on Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
Episode 16:
"Fumitan Admoss."