♪
[LAFTER hums]
[LAFTER]
Hm!
Lookin' good.
[LAFTER] Anyway, I'm looking
forward to gobbling that up.
It looks like a big,
tasty, lobster. Yummy!
[RIDE] Hey! Do you
know what's goin' on?
No, not a clue. I just heard
there was a stop signal.
Gjallarhorn's giving it
their all to keep up with us.
I was hopin' the distance from
Mars would discourage 'em.
The bridge keeps saying
something about Maruba.
No way! What's he
doin' out here?
So, do you think there's
gonna be another fight?
[exhales] For now,
let's just worry about
makin' this thing work. I want
it ready for battle yesterday.
[TECHNICIANS]
Sir!
[YUKINOJO]
Yamagi, how's yours?
I'll get it ready. It doesn't
have as much damage.
Good! Get goin'!
Takaki, Ride, get a move on!
[RIDE,TAKAKI]
Will do!
[MARUBA] How dare you take off
in my ship without permission!
I'll have your heads
for this, you rats!
Hey.
[MARUBA] I want you to hand
over the Will-O-the-Wisp now!
Huh?!
[EUGENE] Those are some big
words comin' from a coward
who ran off and left us to
die like a bunch like dogs.
Tell it to somebody who cares.
[MARUBA]
Who the hell are you?
I wanna talk to
that bastard, Orga!
You hear me?
Ms. Admoss. You think you
can analyze the LCS signal?
Absolutely. It's on
the monitor, now.
Directly behind us.
Distance 6,200.
Their relative speed
almost matches ours.
[BISCUIT] This isn't good.
They're directly on our six.
But how? There was no
Ahab Wave reaction.
It doesn't make sense.
Well, if they're good
enough to pull that off...
[MARUBA] Shut up!
I'm sick of this!
They could end up
being a real problem.
[MARUBA]
Are you listening, brats?
Stop the ship!
Do it now and your
death will--
[computer beeps]
[ORGA]
Huh?
[MARUBA]
What the hell?
Please Get outta
the way, All right?
[MARUBA]
O-Of course.
I'm sorry, but this is
really going nowhere.
I'm bored outta my mind here.
Who the hell are you?
[NAZE]
Straight to business, huh?
The name's Naze Turbine.
I represent the Turbines.
And who might you be?
I'm the leader of
Tekkadan, Orga Itsuka.
[MARUBA] Tekkadan? What?
Give me a break.
I'm sure you know Maruba.
The two of us have something
of a working relationship.
I recently stopped on Mars
where I just happened
to bump into him.
Poor guy was a big mess.
He told me he had a
run-in with Gjallarhorn
and was in a little
bit of trouble.
I told him we could make
all of his problems go away,
for the right price.
After some negotiating,
we decided to lend our support.
Who's 'we'?
[BISCUIT]
The Turbines are actually
a subsidiary crew of Teiwaz.
Oh yeah?
Their group is on the smaller
side, but Naze's a big shot.
He even swore a Sakazuki
blood oath to Teiwaz's boss,
McMurdo Barriston.
[ORGA]
He sounds important.
This situation couldn't
be any worse.
If we cross Teiwaz too,
it'll be the end for us.
[BISCUIT]
Orga?
No. This is our chance, guys.
Gettin' the support of Teiwaz
was a shot in the dark.
And Maruba just brought them
to us on a silver platter.
[gasps]
[NAZE] Don't you know
it's rude to whisper
when someone's trying
to talk to you?
I can't stand guys who
gossip like old ladies.
[grunts]
[SHINO]
Huh?
[ORGA] Sorry about that.
Please continue.
[NAZE]
Thank you.
Watch yourself, All right?
Now, then.
Maruba promised that he would
reward us for backing him up
by having all of CGS's assets
handed over to the Turbines.
But when I looked
into it, on paper,
CGS had gone out of business.
And apparently, all its
property had been transferred
to some group named Tekkadan.
I think I get it now.
You couldn't get
anything from Maruba,
so you came out here
to take it from us.
There's no reason
to get uptight.
By the way, I caught a
glimpse of your fight
with Gjallarhorn the other day.
Not bad for a bunch a kids.
If you agree to return
Maruba's property peacefully,
I promise you won't
be mistreated.
'll let you operate
under the Turbines,
and give you decent work, too.
I assure you,
it'll be far better than
risking your lives every day.
Yeah? What does that mean?
[MARUBA]
Are you kidding!
I'll see these pathetic rats
dead, if I have to do it myself!
[grunts]
Ah, then again, you do
have a pretty large crew.
It simply wouldn't be possible
to keep you together forever.
You can't be serious.
[NAZE]
Did it sound like I was joking?
But I don't want everybody
to go their separate ways.
Orga, wait--
Sorry, Mr. Turbine, but we
can't accept your offer.
No?
[ORGA]
We took on a job as Tekkadan,
and we intend to keep it.
We're not just
gonna stop halfway.
Yes. You see, I've hired
Tekkadan to escort me
all the way to Earth.
I can't have their company
dissolved just yet.
[NAZE exhales] You must be the
famous Kudelia Aina Bernstine.
Since you're considered
Maruba's property,
that'll make this even
more complicated.
Property? What's he mean?
I'm... not really sure.
[NAZE sighs] Looks like I'm
gonna have to double-check with
McMurdo on this one.
[BISCUIT] Excuse me.
May I say one thing?
Huh? What is it, chubby?
My name is Biscuit Griffon, sir.
[OPERATOR 0A]
What a delicious name!
[NAZE]
I'm listening, Biscuit Boy.
Thank you very much.
If it's possible, I would like
to make a contract between
Tekkadan and the Turbines.
[EUGENE]
What? Are you crazy?
As you know,
we've all been hired
to escort Miss Kudelia to Earth.
If we have any chance
of succeeding,
we're gonna need to get
past Gjallarhorn undetected
and find a guide that can
secure our safe passage.
[NAZE]
Hm.
If I'm right, the Turbines
manage the transport branch
of Teiwaz. Would it be possible
for us to use your route?
Of course, we'd be
more than happy to pay
the appropriate tolls.
I'm afraid that's
out of the question.
But, why can't we?
I don't owe an explanation
to a squawking little brat
that stole everything he has!
Besides, I have my own
principles when it
comes to finishing a job.
You think you have principles
when you're working
for that bloated coward?
Don't make me laugh.
Being seen as beneath
that sadistic bastard
makes my skin crawl.
All right, so what
are you gonna do?
If you want to think of
yourselves as grown-ups,
you need to face the
consequences of your actions.
[gasps]
I haven't changed my mind.
We can't accept your offer.
[NAZE]
Hm.
You might have your
way of doin' things,
But we have our own
sense of honor to protect.
[NAZE] So. You're saying
that you're willing
to fight against us?
That's right. And we'll prove
to you that we're more
than just a bunch of kids.
That goes for you too, Maruba.
Huh?
[ORGA] We lost a lot
of friends back there.
We're gonna make sure you
pay for each one of 'em.
Let's see ya try it!
Your loss, kid.
That arrogance of yours
is gonna cost you, dearly.
[NAZE] Sorry Amida.
Looks like you're up.
Well, it is a grown-up's job
to scold naughty children,
isn't it?
Uh-huh. You could
punish me any day, dear.
Tell Lafter she better wear
a normal suit this time.
[OPERATOR A]
Yes, ma'am.
Everybody prepare for battle!
Get to your stations, now.
Azee, I need you
to come with me.
[AZEE]
Yes, ma'am. Of course
[BISCUIT]
I told you to watch yourself!
There was still
room for negotiation!
[ORGA]
I'm well aware of that.
But I have no intention
of backing down.
[BISCUIT exhales]
[ORGA]
Those bastards on our six,
which gives us a chance to show
them Tekkadan's true power.
Are you with me or not?
[EUGENE]
You're damn right!
Hell yeah! Time to
show 'em how it's done.
We might not get another chance
to negotiate with Teiwaz,
so let's grab it!
Yes sir.
[EUGENE]
Right!
Confirming Ahab Wave reaction.
They've increased their speed
and are closing in fast!
[ORGA]
Okay! Stow away the bridge.
Now! Maintain speed
and turn one-eighty.
Prepare to exchange fire.
[CHAD] Yes, sir.
Stowing away the bridge.
[FUMITAN] This ship will
now engage in battle.
Deactivating artificial gravity.
[ATRA]
No! Wait a minute!
[ATRA gasps]
[FUMITAN] Everyone, prepare for
the turn in 120 seconds.
Akihiro, you got this?
[AKIHIRO]
Yeah. All right.
[ORGA]
Mika?
[MIKAZUKI]
I'm on it.
[ORGA]
I'm countin' on ya.
Outta the way.
[KUDELIA grunts]
Oh, sorry.
You go too, Shino.
Yes! I'm ready!
[EUGENE]
I'll go too.
[ORGA]
No, Eugene. You stay put.
[EUGENE]
What?
[ORGA]
Take command of the ship.
'Cause you're the only one
I can trust to pull it off
[gasps]
Kay... If you insist.
[FUMITAN] Miss Kudelia,
please evacuate to the core.
I'll help you get into a normal
suit before you go down.
I guess I'll be in the
way if I stay here?
Huh?
It's fine. I'll go by myself.
You need to focus on
helping everyone, Fumitan.
[FUMITAN] If that's what
you want, I'll obey.
Please. Be careful, Miss.
[grunts]
[ORGA]
Sorry, Biscuit.
[BISCUIT]
No turning back, huh?
[ORGA] You got it.
I'm gonna need your help.
Sure thing.
[CHAD]
Turning 180 degrees!
[AZEE] I'll go first, ma'am.
Preparing to head out.
[AMIDA]
Right.
Azee Gurumin, launching!
[AMIDA]
They're going by the book.
They maintained their speed
while turning their ship to
face us directly. You've passed
the first test, kids.
Amida Arca, Hyakuren,
heading out!
[YUKINOJO]
Sorry about this, Mikazuki.
The reactor hasn't
been fine-tuned yet.
I really wish I didn't have
to send you out like this.
[MIKAZUKI] As long as
it moves, I can get by.
Try not to die out there.
I'd feel guilty.
I plan to live longer
than you, Old Man.
[chuckles]
Now don't get carried away.
Stay sharp, ya hear me?
Hey!
Once Akihiro's Graze is out,
we'll get Barbatos out too.
[MIKAZUKI gasps]
It's not just the reactor.
There's also a weird strain
on all the motors.
Well... we'll just
do what we can, right?
Mikazuki The target has deployed
Mobile Suits. Two so far.
Understood. Let's do this!
[YUKINOJO]
Okay! Bring down Barbatos.
Easy...
[FUMITAN]
Operating Air Lock.
Opening up the catapult hatch.
Catapult on standby.
Ready when you are.
Mikazuki Augus,
I'm in Barbatos heading out.
[grunts]
[MIKAZUKI]
Thanks for waiting.
Heh. Took you long enough.
Is that it?
Azee, don't get in the
ship's line of fire.
[AZEE]
Roger that.
All right! It's time for
your spanking, little boys.
[ALL grunt]
Can't we evade their missiles?
[BISCUIT] If we don't maneuver
properly, they'll close in,
and then we'll be within range
of their Anti-ship Napalm.
[EUGENE grunts]
[FUMITAN]
Missiles approaching.
[ALL grunt]
If we get hit repeatedly,
even the Nanolaminate
armor will disintegrate!
We need to stay far enough
to still intercept them!
[ALL grunt]
Keeping our distance
isn't enough!
[OPERATOR 0A] The enemy
is holding their course.
They're surprisingly
brave for children.
[NAZE]
Is this gonna take long?
Hey, why don't you get
Lofter to come out and play?
Yes sir.
What was that light?
[BISCUIT gasps]
Up there.
[ALL grunt]
Hit on the upper deck.
Air pressure's dropping fast.
Closing off the upper
second block.
My nails didn't have
time to dry, yet.
[EUGENE]
Another Mobile Suit.
Our artillery isn't
gonna cut it.
[BISCUIT] Ms. Admoss,
contact Mikazuki and Akihiro!
We have to call back the Mobile
Suits or we're in big trouble.
When did that one come out?
Don't look away.
[AKIHIRO]
Mikazuki.
[chuckles]
Sorry, Akihiro, but can you
take the two in front of us?
Huh? Sure. My pleasure.
[MIKAZUKI]
I'll be right back.
[AMIDA] Leaving your
friend out in the cold?
Huh?
You guys've been left to me.
[KUDELIA grunts]
[KUDELIA]
For goodness sake!
Fumitan was always around to
help me with stuff like this.
Miss Kudelia?
[KUDELIA]
Huh? Oh, Atra.
What are those?
[ATRA giggles]
Huh?
There! Just like that.
[KUDELIA]
Ah. I see now.
[ATRA] It can be hard
to get it on your own.
[KUDELIA grunts]
Thank you so much, Atra.
[ATRA]
We should get going, now.
[KUDELIA]
Huh?
Oh... That's right.
I probably shouldn't go out
onto the bridge, should I?
[KUDELIA gasps]
Hey, is something wrong?
You're looking at me
like I have two-heads.
[KUDELIA]
Mm-mm.
Huh?
[KUDELIA] You know what?
Feeling down won't help anybody.
I have to watch over
Tekkadan's battle.
That's what I can do now.
[gasps]
Come on. We'll go together.
[ATRA]
Huh?
[ATRA yelps]
[EUGENE grunts] Damn!
We're not gonna last!
This lobster has
one thick shell.
[gasps]
You're never gonna mess
with the Isaribi again!
Wow. He's so rude.
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
Damn, it's fast!
Havin' trouble keepin' up?
[grunts]
Bingo!
My propulsion
power's stronger!
[TECHNICIANS shout]
[TECHNICIAN A]
Come on, just get it done!
[TECHNICIANS chattering]
[SHINO]
Hey, Yamagi.
[YAMAGI]
Huh?
[SHINO]
Is it ready?
Yeah, I just finished up.
[SHINO]
Awesome. Thanks a lot, man.
Huh?
[chuckles]
[SHINO]
There's no need to be shy.
[YAMAGI gasps]
[SHINO] I think I can
take over from here!
[YUKINOJO] Maintenance crew,
go up when you're finished.
The airlock's gonna close soon.
I'm clear.
You guys ready to go?
[DANTE, DEBRIS MEMBERS]
Yeah!
Hey, bridge! We're all
prepared to launch.
Eugene.
[EUGENE]
Yeah. I'm on it.
[BISCUIT]
Uh...
Why isn't Mr. Orga here?
[BISCUIT]
What are you two doing?
I'm gonna see this
through to the end.
--[EUGENE] Hm.
--[BISCUIT] What?
Okay. Just make sure
you hold on tight.
You understand me?!
[EUGENE] That enemy
Mobile Suit's in the way.
Mikazuki, push it
back for us!
[ALL gasp]
[CHAD] Oh man!
It's too fast, even for him!
Careful...
[MIKAZUKI pants]
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
Damn it! It just keeps coming!
[MIKAZUKI gasps]
Been fun,
but playtime's over.
[LAFTER laughs]
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
There!
I've got you.
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
This is nothing.
Do it!
Okay! Let 'em have it!
Enemy firing missiles!
Better not let 'em hit us.
Intercepting them.
What's going on?
Were they just making a
smoke screen, or are they...
--[alarm blares]
--[MARUBA] What's happening?
Ahab Wave reaction increasing.
[OPERATOR A] It's as if
they're heading right for us.
No! They're gonna ram us!
Let's go!
[ATRA yelps]
[NAZE gasps]
The rest is up to
you guys, so kick ass!
[NAZE]
That was pretty ballsy,
but we're not gonna let
you escape that easily.
[FUMITAN] Target is turning
fast. They're closing in on us.
You've got guts;
I'll give you that.
But you're still immature and
playing with someone
twice your si--
[ALL gasp]
[NAZE grunts]
What happened?
[OPERATOR A]
Explosion in the cargo block.
We have intruders on board?!
What?! Did they jump over here
when we almost hit each other?
One wrong move at that speed
and they would've been
paste on our hull.
Believe me, those kids are
nothin' but filthy space rats!
Space Rats? Do you mean that...
...you forced the Alaya-Vijnana
operation onto those kids?
You bet I did!
'Cause brats who refuse the
operation are useless.
Worse than garbage!
I only hired 'em 'cause
they had whiskers.
What a waste of money.
[NAZE gasps]
[AZEE]
Ma'am, they're getting away.
You did a decent job
keeping your distance.
Let's chase, Azee.
[AZEE]
Yes, ma'am.
[AKIHIRO]
You're not getting' away!
[AMIDA]
You'd better move it!
[shouts]
[AKIHIRO]
Damn they're strong...
[AKIHIRO gasps]
[AKIHIRO] Mikazuki left
me to deal with you,
so that's what
I'm gonna do!
I won't pull back!
I can't afford to!
[grunts]
I wasn't expecting you
to play aggressively.
[AMIDA gasps]
[growls]
Amida!
Aw, how adorable.
You think you can stop
me by using brute force.
Well, I can play rough, too.
[LAFTER] I bet your inertial
control isn't helping anymore,
is it? You'd better let go quick
if you don't want to suffer.
But, if I let go right now,
you're just gonna
sink the Isaribi .
'Course I will.
That's what a battle's for.
You won't get in Orga's way.
You're the one who's in
the way, you pipsqueak!
[gasps]
[grunts]
Buh-bye, little boy.
It was really fun.
[LAFTER screams]
[MIKAZUKI] Finally.
Now you're mine!
[grunts]
Time for you to disappear.
[LAFTER]
I'm not done yet!
[MIKAZUKI gasps]
You are such a sore loser.
Look who's talkin'. I hate it
when men come on too strong.
[MIKAZUKI] All right, then.
Why don't we end it?
[ORGA] That's enough, Mika!
It's been settled.
[NAZE] Sorry for all
the trouble, Amida.
[gasps]
[NAZE]
Come on back.
I've decided to listen
to their story.
[AKIHIRO pants]
Is it over?
[LAFTER] It was just
getting exciting, too.
Man! That fight was
such a tease!
[MIKAZUKI gasps]
♪
[LAFTER]
Hey, wait a minute!
It's just gonna end
halfway like this?
But, I was ready
to go all the way!
I'm so unsatisfied.
This is really frustrating.
I'm burning up inside!
Ugh, I'll have to have
my darling help
release all this tension.
Next time on Mobile Suit
Gundam: Iron Blooded Orphans,
Episode 8:
"The Form of Closeness."