[MIKAZUKI]
Shino, are you okay?
[SHINO]
Yeah. For now anyway.
Those're a whole lotta ships.
What do you say we take off?
Yeah, I have a feeling
they're not gonna let us.
[KUDELIA] My name is
Kudelia Aina Bernstein.
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
Kudelia?
[KUDELIA]
Is my voice reaching you?
If so, then I beg you to listen.
'Cause I need to tell you
what's happening
at the Dort colonies.
And I want you all to know
the truth about their people.
Miss Kudelia.
[KUDELIA]
For some time,
I've been doing
everything I could
to save the citizens of Mars,
the people of my homeland.
But now, I realize
how ignorant I've been.
Innocent men, women,
and children from all over
are feeling the grip of
Gallarhorn's oppression.
At the Dort Colony, I met people
who took it upon themselves
to try and stand up for
what they believed in.
With no alternative,
they marched in protest.
But that was just so they could
have the opportunity...
I want you men to stop
this broadcast now!
It's being shown at the
African Union's request, sir.
You can't be serious. They're
really assisting those fools?
Without any violent provocation,
mysterious explosions
went off around them,
as if the entire thing
had been set up.
And I'm more than certain
that none of them were ignited
by the citizens of Dort.
[COMMANDER A] I've heard enough!
Shut down the broadcast!
[KUDELIA]
But using that as a pretext,
Gjallarhorn began viciously
attacking the protestors.
At this moment,
that battle... No...
That massacre continues on.
Hey! Why haven't you
shut them down, yet?
We've just located the source
of their transmission, sir.
The signal's from that armored
assault vessel in front.
[AKIHIRO]
They're coming.
[SHINO] I can't believe this.
There's so many of 'em.
[KUDELIA] Right now, my ship is
being completely surrounded
by Gjallarhorn's fleet.
What?
[KUDELIA] So I'll this
moment to ask them...
Aren't you supposed
to be the ones
we can depend on
to uphold justice?
I wanna know, is this what
you call ethical treatment?
If so... I don't accept
what you stand for.
And if you choose to disagree
with what I've been saying...
...that's fine.
Hey, wait a minute.
What's she talkin' about?
You can shoot down
this ship right now!
Hey, hey.
Did she just threaten
them to attack?
Yeah, well, either way--
[CHAD]
Don't move, Mikazuki!
Huh?
Very well. Only happy
to oblige. All ships, aim--
Orders from the
Regulatory Bureau, sir!
[COMMANDER 17-A]
Hm?
[SHINO] I don't know
what's goin' on here.
They're not movin' in on us.
[MIKAZUKI]
That's amazing. She's good.
[AKIHIRO]
What do you mean?
[MIKAZUKI] All those fighters
who came after us...
All that it took to take each
of them down one by one...
And she stopped 'em
with just her voice.
[PRODUCER A]
And cut!
Thanks so much for doing this.
We got some really
powerful footage.
Now that is what I call
journalism. Extraordinary.
[ORGA]
What you did was pretty risky.
[KUDELIA]
Boss, I, uh...
Not bad. Looks like
you won in the end.
Did I really win?
Because honestly,
I'm beginning to wonder exactly
what I've been fighting for.
[chuckles]
[TODO]
I still don't understand
why they didn't just
blow 'em to bits.
The Regulatory Bureau
must have given them orders
for a cease-fire.
[TODO]
What? Why would they do that?
[MASKED MAN]
Most likely,
it was at the African
Union's request,
Gjallarhorn can't
afford to have
their international reputation
damaged further.
So it sounds like
those rotten kids
got their asses saved again.
Those punks have no
idea how lucky they are.
[MASKED MAN]
Seems rather appropriate
for the Maiden of Revolution.
It was a much better
show than I expected.
If it's her...
If it's Tekkadan...
♪
[NAZE] Sorry we got here
later than expected.
It's fine.
We should apologize for getting
you involved in all this.
No worries, Brother.
But I gotta admit,
Kudelia really stuck it
to those guys, didn't she?
[KUDELIA] My apologies
for making you wait.
I heard about Fumitan.
So unfortunate...
All right. So is everybody
ready to get going?
[NAZE]
Uh...
Yeah, about that...
Originally, we were gonna go
to one of the two Space Ports
that currently orbit Earth,
rent a reentry ship, then
travel down to the surface.
But now you've been identified.
And Gjallerhorn can track
every single move you make.
So we'll have to
scratch that plan.
Then what are we
supposed to do about it?
[EUGENE] Look, let's not
forget who blew our cover
in the first place, all right?
You need to watch your tone.
Eugene!
[EUGENE]
Hey, I'm just sayin'.
[KUDELIA]
I have a huge responsibility.
Wait a minute...
I can't let down the people
who believe in me. Not now.
It's my obligation to do
everything I can for them.
Of course. We know that,
but I think you...
[beeping]
[MERRIBIT]
An Ahab Wave reaction?
We have a ship approaching.
Do you think it could
be Gjallarhorn?
If it was, there'd be a
lot more than just one.
We're receiving contact
from the approaching vessel.
All right, then put it up front.
It's that man again.
[MASKED MAN]
I know this may seem sudden,
but I'm with the
Montag Company.
And I wish to speak with
your representative.
I'm Naze Turbine
of the Turbines.
Now tell me, what would a
trading company want with us?
Well, as a matter of fact,
we have a business proposal.
[GAELIO] You should rest, Ein.
Let those injuries heal.
[EIN]
Please, forgive me, sir.
Somehow I let those bastards
get the best of me again.
Hey, don't apologize.
After all, those are wounds
you got saving me.
I should be the one
saying "I'm sorry."
I had no idea two Gundam
Frames would join the fight.
[GAELIO]
No. That's just an excuse.
The fact is, after what happened
back there, I owe you one.
[EIN] Specialist Major,
do you think that...
...if I were to get the
Alaya-Vijnana implanted...
...I might be able
to defeat them?
[GAELIO grunts]
What did you just say?
Don't ask such a
disgusting thing.
You have those
implanted in your body
and you won't be
a human anymore.
Won't be human, huh?
I know what that's like.
The Earth people in Gjallerhorn
remind me all the time.
[GAELIO]
Huh?
I'm not like them because
I was born half-Martian.
[GAELIO]
What?
[EIN] But they aren't the only
ones who feel that way.
It's Earth people in general.
They only approve of you if
you've got pure bloodlines.
It's the same on Mars, too.
That's where my mother's from.
I was only allowed
in Gjallerhorn
because my father was
already an officer.
There was still
discrimination though.
But Lieutenant Crank...
he was different.
He always treated me
like everybody else.
[CRANK]
Listen, Ein.
Your worth has nothing to do
with where you were born.
[EIN]
Thank you, Sir. I just...
There are no two people
who're exactly alike.
That's why it's pointless to
group them together as one.
The most important thing
is choosing the path
that's right for you.
Don't let 'em get ya down.
Just show those guys
how you want to live.
You're right, Sir.
[EIN]
He inspired me.
And gave me the strength
I needed to move on.
Now I don't care what people
think. I believe in myself.
[GAELIO] Kinda sounds to me
like you think I'm no different
than all the others
who bullied you.
[EIN]
N-No, that's not true, Sir. I--
It's fine. Relax.
I don't think I've ever met a
man who's quite like you, Ein.
And you were right when you
said we have to be the ones
who face Tekkadan head-on
and bring them down.
But at this rate,
I'm not so sure.
We're entering the territory
of the Outer Earth Orbit
Regulatory Joint Fleet.
Though you're a Seven Star, they
won't let us do as we please.
Oh, I'm well aware.
And while bowing down to that
woman is the very last thing
I wanna do,
there's no other choice.
[MCGILLIS] As I told you, I
represent the Montag Company.
It's a pleasure to see you once
again, Miss Bernstine.
You know this guy?
We met briefly, once.
Now tell us your proposal.
[MASKED MAN] We have the means
necessary to provide you
with a reentry ship
down to Earth.
[ORGA]
Huh?
You desire a revolution
and we'd like to
extend our support.
If that's agreeable
to you, Miss.
So you're offering
to be our advocate?
I could've sworn you were
here to talk business.
[MASKED MAN]
Yes, of course I am.
When you've achieved
your goals,
Nobliss Gordon and
McMurdo Barriston
will each gain the rights
to all half-metals
To put it simply,
my company wants in.
N-Nobliss?
Now I understand.
[MASKED MAN]
What do you say?
Negotiations haven't
started yet.
Do you think they'll succeed?
[MASKED MAN] Based on what
I've seen at the Dort Colonies,
I've reason to
believe they will.
How soon do you need an answer?
Afraid we don't have
a lot of time left.
Please, make your
decision quickly.
Man, who would've ever guessed
that Barriston and Gordon
were connected like that?
Yeah.
Seemed like Naze
knew all about it.
I can't figure out why he didn't
wanna fill the rest of us in.
I guess it means
he doesn't think
we're important enough
to hear those things yet.
Huh?
[ORGA] They do business by
tryin' to outsmart each other.
And right now, we're only
scurryin' around their feet.
So if we really want them to
think of us as their equals,
we need to make some changes.
[TAKAKI]
Look at this stuff comin' in.
Apparently, the Montag Company
thought it'd be nice
to bring over some gifts.
We got missiles, loads of
ammo, all kinds of weaponry.
Yeah, and even new
parts for Barbatos.
Seems kinda fishy to me.
It sorta feels like they're
taking advantage of us,
you know?
Like they say:
"There's no such thing as
somethin' for nothin'."
Hey, be careful when you're
countin' those things, Ride!
[RIDE]
Got it!
[ORGA]
Hey, Mika.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
How's the cargo lookin'?
[MIKAZUKI]
I'm not sure, yet.
The old man's still checkin'
to find out what we've got.
Hang on. Why's
chocolate man here?
[BISCUIT]
Huh?
[MASKED MAN chuckles]
I hope your twin sisters are
doing well these days.
Hey, wait. Are you the guy
we met from Gjallarhorn?
No way. What the hell
are you doin' here?!
Did you come to
set a trap for us?
Answer me!
Who's side are you on?!
Honestly, how would it
benefit me to come aboard
and then pull
something like that?
You'd better start talkin'.
[MCGILLIS]
I will.
Because we both know you'd see
through it if I were deceptive.
I want to reform Gjallarhorn,
and finally put an end
to all the corruption.
What?
[MCGILLIS]
Then as a new organization,
we'll be allowed more freedom.
With you on the outside,
you're in the perfect position
to help us return to
our former glory.
I'm not so sure we'd
be able to do that, so--
I disagree.
I've seen what you've
accomplished with Kudelia.
And that's why I'm fully
prepared to lend a hand.
You see, we share
mutual interests. Don't we?
Still think it's a trap?
Right now, it's hard to say.
[MCGILLIS chuckles]
[MCGILLIS]
Well, think about it, won't you?
Oh. And don't say
a word about me.
Because if you do...
...it's all over.
The deal's
off the table.
Phew. I'm starved...
Oh, uh, would you like to eat
something, Miss Kudelia?
Uh, excuse me?
Oh. I'm sorry.
I didn't see you there.
You don't look very well to me.
Maybe you need to
get a little rest.
I really appreciate it,
but I have to prepare
for negotiations, so--
Look, I understand
your situation,
but that won't matter
if you fall ill.
No. It's okay. I'll be fine.
Miss Kudelia...
[MIKAZUKI]
You know...
She's pretty incredible.
[ATRA]
Huh?
[MIKAZUKI]
Like a whole different person...
Maybe she's forcing herself.
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
I mean, before, when
she was standing there
in front of the camera and
talking to everybody...
...her legs were
kinda shaking.
I see.
[CARTA]
Men! Stand proud!
For we are the Outer Earth Orbit
Regulatory Joint Fleet!
[SUBORDINATES] We are
perseverant and fortitudinous!
[sighs]
Just perfect.
Now, the Kudilia-woman is still
headed our way, isn't she?
Her name is Kudelia
Aina berstine, ma'am.
According to Specialist
Major Bauduin's report,
it's confirmed.
Well, I sincerely hope so.
To the old men representing
the Seven Stars,
and to that one man
in particular,
it'll be a chance to show
them what we're made of.
[SUBORDINATE B] The Specialist
Major requested to join us
on the battlefront, ma'am.
[CARTA] I can assure you
there's nothing to worry about.
A sad loser like that Gaelio-boy
could never steal our thunder.
Oh, I'm so pumped up,
I can't even stand it!
They better not change course.
Hurry up and get here.
Then we'll squash
you fools to death!
[REPORTER A]
A few questions, Ms. Fleurs.
[REPORTER B] There's been
a lot of talk lately
about the ex-prime minister,
Makanai, running.
[REPORTER A]
As a member of parliament,
care to comment on
his alleged bribery?
[REPORTER B] At the general
assembly meeting in two months,
can we expect you to be
vying for the nomination
of prime minister as well?
There'll be an official
announcement soon.
Till then, I must ask
for your patience.
That's all for now, gentlemen.
Have a lovely weekend.
Makanai still at the
Oceanian Federation?
[IZNARIO]
Don't worry.
We're keeping an eye on him.
So was he the one who
called for this girl?
People are always in search
of an idol they can believe in.
But of course,
they're just fictitious.
Most don't seem to
care about the truth.
[MAKANAI humming]
[MAKANAI sighs]
[AIDE A] Excuse me, but
haven't you had enough, Sir?
I feel like celebrating.
After all, an important
guest is on the way.
[AIDE A]
Yes, of course.
Though she may have
just been lucky.
Lucky? Well, I suppose so.
Random twists of fate always
decide things in the end.
Don't they?
To me, she won't be
the Maiden of Revolution.
She just might be
my Lady Luck instead.
Sir.
Right now, I feel like
a princess in a castle
who's waiting for her Prince
Charming to arrive.
[NAZE]
Based on what I've read,
the Montag Company's been
around for a hundred years.
And they haven't run
into any real problems.
At least as far as we know.
Can't believe Tekkadan
got caught up
in another annoying thing.
[AMIDA] They may be a
little hard to handle,
but what's wrong with
some excitement?
You know, I think you might
just have a point there.
Those are the same reasons I
can't get enough of you in bed.
[AMIDA chuckles]
[SHINO grunting]
Come on! What the hell?!
Hey, what's wrong, man?!
[SHINO] Shut up, okay?!
I'm not finished yet!
[AZEE] Those two, again?
They do train hard.
The one with muscles?
Yeah, he's playing with
that pierced idiot.
Really seems to care about
the others, doesn't he?
What do you mean?
[LAFTER sighs]
[LAFTER]
I don't know.
It's kinda hard to explain...
[AZEE]
Huh?
[AKIHIRO]
Are you all right?
Sorry to make you keep
trainin' with me like this.
I'm surprised.
[SHINO]
Hm?
To be honest, I guess
I never realized
you had such a sense of duty.
Seriously?
Yeah, well, things are kinda
different for me these days.
'Cause I'm free of that now.
To tell you the truth,
having to give my friends
directions and bark out orders,
that isn't for me,
anymore, ya know?
What if somebody died
following my commands?
If I can go fight in a Mobile
Suit out on the front lines,
I won't have to worry
about things like that.
And I'd still be able to
protect the other guys.
Makes sense.
[YUKINOJO] Hm. Don't think I've
ever seen you lookin' better.
I just hope it improves
your mobility a little
when you need it the most.
Hm?
Hey! You can finish
up now, Yamagi.
Not yet. Needs a
little more work.
The rest of 'em
go out and fight.
Best we can do is
give our support.
For their sake,
I wanna do all I can.
[KUDELIA]
Fumitan.
If we hadn't run
into that man...
[KUDELIA] But I know
I have to make it to Earth.
To achieve our goal,
to carry out your dying wishes.
Maybe I don't have a choice.
Will I have to work with him?
[ATRA]
Miss Kudelia!
Oh, hey, Atra.
[ATRA] There you are!
I'm so glad I found you.
[KUDELIA] You-You've come all
this way, is something wrong?
I didn't think it
was good for you
to go this long without eating.
Here's a snack. Let's see.
Oh, great. I can't believe
I forgot to bring it with me.
[KUDELIA]
Does it hurt at all?
Oh, these are only to--
[KUDELIA]
I'm so sorry.
They're all my fault.
Please forgive me.
[ATRA]
N-No, don't say that.
You know, I've been thinking
We should really talk
to each other more.
Uh, I'm sorry. I guess that
came out kinda weird, huh?
But just remember,
if you ever feel like things
are getting sorta tough,
I want you to tell
me about it, okay?
You can count on me.
Uh.
Then again, maybe I'm not
exactly the most reliable girl.
I think I'm the one
you can't depend on.
[ATRA]
Huh?
[KUDELIA] 'Cause, lately...
I just feel so powerless.
But It has to stop.
I know I can't stay
like this anymore.
To give hope...
...and to try and
lead other people...
...I need to make a change.
[MIKAZUKI]
You're really something.
[ATRA]
Mikazuki. Why're you...?
Hm? Oh, the lunch box!
Thanks a lot.
[MIKAZUKI] You were able
to stop Gjallarhorn
just by using your voice.
As far as I know,
even Orga can't do that.
[KUDELIA]
Huh?
[ATRA] Yeah, he's right.
And you looked so awesome, too.
In fact, I wanna join you,
Miss Kudelia.
It's a r-revolution, right?
I'd like to do "revolution."
[MIKAZUKI]
I'll help, too.
Fumitan was talking
about what it means
to have sense of duty.
And ever since, I've been
thinking about that myself.
While there isn't really
a whole lot I can do,
I promise, if you
have the responsibility
of going to Earth now, I'll
help you any way that I can.
Yeah, me too.
That isn't something
you should ever
have to deal with by yourself.
'Cause we're your friends
and your family.
Together, we can...
[KUDELIA crying]
N-No, please don't cry.
Mikazuki, you've gotta
hurry up and do something!
Uh, wait. Me?
[ATRA] Everybody knows:
When a girl's crying,
a boy is supposed to make
her feel better.
This is when you should hold
her in your arms. Come on!
Mikazuki, hold on, I--
[KUDELIA crying]
[ATRA]
Miss Kudelia...
It's okay. Really.
And you've had to keep
this inside for...
Mikazuki.
D-Don't worry about me.
Yeah, but... you're
crying, too, Atra.
No, I'm just fine.
You don't...
[BOTH crying]
[NAZE] I've researched
that company of theirs.
And they seem pretty
legitimate to me.
But it's still a
dangerous bet, guys.
Yeah, I know it. The thing is--
[door opens]
[KUDELIA]
It's our only option, isn't it?
M-Miss Kudelia.
I'll use anything I can.
And do whatever it takes.
In for a penny, in for
a pound, aren't ya?
Are you in, Brother?
Okay. It looks like
they've got a deal.
[DANTE]
Sometimes when I'm feeling down,
I just look at the diagram
of an electric circuit.
Staring into all
that information,
so efficiently laid out,
makes me think it's pretty
inefficient to feel bad
when people call
my character "dull,"
or that they can't
remember my name.
A-Anyway, I'm Dante Morgro.
Don't you forget it, okay?
Next time on Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
Episode 19:
"The Gravity of Wishes."