[ROYAL GUARD A] Are you
sure we should've gone without
orders to retreat?
[ROYAL GUARD B] Look, we're
just lucky we got Lady Carta
outta there.
But now she's with us and we can
start planning our next strike.
[inaudible]
[ORGA sobs, screams]
♪
[ECO grunts]
--[clattering]
--Huh?
[YAMAGI grunts]
Hey, are you all right?
Uh, yeah. I-I'm sorry.
Dammit...
[TAKAKI] It can't be.
We promised we'd work hard
and put our sisters
through school.
We swore nothing would
stop us. Remember, Biscuit?
How could they do this? W-Why?
[sobs]
[SHINO] How are we supposed
to tell his little sisters
back on Mars?
We should leave here together.
All of us. Let's take you home.
[MIKAZUKI]
We can't do that.
[gasps]
Until our job is finished,
we have to see it through.
Yeah. Guess you're right.
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
Where's Orga?
[MCGILLIS]
I see.
I'm glad to hear that they
arrived at the ship safely.
Thank you. Do make sure that
they're well taken care of.
And report to me
immediately of any changes.
[MCGILLIS] Tekkadan fought hard.
Carta must be pretty resilient
to have lived. I'm impressed.
Although, if she'd died there,
she wouldn't have to bear the
shame of her failure, anymore.
I can only imagine the look
of disgust on my father's face.
[computer beeps]
[SUBORDINATE A] Specialist
Major Bauduin has just arrived
at headquarters, sir.
[MCGILLIS]
Very well...
[HENRI] This is nothing
like we discussed.
The election was to end
without Togonosuke Makanai
ever leaving the island.
I'm appointed as prime
minister of Arbrau, and then
we'll be able to
seize the power.
You said that was the plan.
What she did was
totally unnecessary
I spent years as her guardian,
giving her all my support.
I maintained her family status.
And this is how Carta repays me?
Such an impetuous tomboy.
[HENRI] Makanai's whereabouts
are still unknown,
But if he were to
appear in Parliament...
No need to hurry.
We know where he's headed,
so it's only a matter of
time now. He won't get too far.
In two weeks, you will
be elected into office.
I should go. They'll need me
back at headquarters, soon.
Might as well start preparing
your inauguration speech.
[HENRI grunts]
[IZNARIO] I've spent years
lining this up as carefully
as possible... I married
McGillis into the Bauduins,
became a guardian for the
Issue family's daughter,
and strengthened my position
within the Seven Stars.
Now, if I can assume the power
of Arbrau through Henri Fleurs,
my position will
be even greater.
I can't afford to
make a wrong move.
[CORLIS] I'm so relieved that
you're safe, Colonel Issue.
Please, rest well and--
I was only moments away from
dying on the battlefield!
Me, of all people!
Meanwhile, my precious
subordinates were being
slaughtered out there!
Uh!
[CARTA grunts]
I'll never forgive them.
Now there's only one mission.
Pursue the enemy until every
last one of them is destroyed!
[CORLIS gasps]
But, Ma'am, the Regulatory
Bureau's ordered us
to return at once!
Just ignore it.
[CORLIS]
Uh! Colonel!
This one was issued from
Lord Fareed, himself.
What's that?
Lady Carta, I think it'd be
best if we just head back.
After all, the Fareed's
are your guardian family.
You shouldn't disregard them.
[growls]
Those miserable space rats.
Next time I see them,
I'll tear them apart!
So how's Ein's condition?
It hasn't changed.
He's completely
dependent on life-support.
You've been given
the solution, right?
Look, McGillis. I won't
let that happen to him.
I'm well aware that Ein
can't be saved like this.
And I want him to take revenge
for the deaths of
his senior officers.
But, still. To implant a
machine inside him...
...and having to
give up being human...
Giving up being human, huh?
Well...
It's been said if it weren't
for that single choice,
civilization wouldn't exist.
What are you talking about?
Three hundred years ago,
the Calamity War was
taking its toll.
Affecting everyone.
Humanity, itself,
faced extinction.
For people to try and live on,
they knew the only answer
was to end the fighting.
But it had to be done by
breaking the balance of power.
using strength surpassing
human abilities.
[GAELIO gasps]
[MCGILLIS] People, sharing the
same vision came together,
forming an organization beyond
countries and economic blocs.
They invented a mechanism
that could heighten the
maneuverability of man's
greatest military achievement
to its farthest limits.
After rigorous testing,
they created the
Alaya-Vijnana System
and engineered 72
Mobile Suits that could
display its full potential
on the battlefield.
The Gundam Frames.
Tracing it back, everything
stems from that point.
[MCGILLIS] The selfless ones
who gave up being human
to save their own race,
would later go on to become
the organization we now
know as Gjallarhorn.
[GAELIO] These days, the very
system responsible for our
salvation has been reduced
to a hated relic of the war.
How ironic...
[MCGILLIS] Indeed. And in the
300 years since its inception,
Gjallarhorn has grown corrupt,
becoming a hotbed for those
struggling to gain power.
Incidentally, were you
aware that Carta's fleet
failed in their
pursuit of Tekkadan?
[GAELIO]
They did?
Kudelia escaped with them
and they managed to bring
Arbrau's former leader,
Makanai, too.
We lost contact in the Pacific.
[gasps] We've got
satellite surveillance.
How could they all just
disappear like that?
[MCGILLIS]
Well, more than likely,
there's an informant
hiding among our ranks.
Further proof of
their corruption.
[GAELIO grunts]
Despicable.
They could learn something
from the loyalty Ein's shown.
Maybe more than anybody else,
he embodies the essence of
what it once meant to be
a member of Gjallarhorn.
Where are we?
A research facility.
Until very recently,
development of
the Alaya-Vinjana
was conducted right here.
[GAELIO]
Really?
You must understand, Gaelio.
This isn't just for Ein's sake,
it's for ours, as well.
[GAELIO]
T-This is...
[MCGILLIS] Show them
the spirit of Gjallarhorn.
Sacrificing your needs
for the greater good.
Just as soon as he has
the system implanted,
you can join Ein
and destroy them.
Then, they'll be no
question that we are
the ones with the power to lead.
[GAELIO gasps]
[GAELIO] Show them
our origin. Is that it?
[YAMAGI] I wonder if...
boss is doing okay.
We haven't gotten any
orders in a while.
[TAKAKI]
Yeah...
Can't imagine
how it must've felt
seeing Biscuit die like that.
[grunts]
I'm sure it was terrible.
Damn Gjallarhorn to hell.
Next time around,
I'm gonna kill 'em.
[TAKAKI]
Calm down.
We need to find out what
Boss wants to do first.
Aren't you even mad
about what happened?
Or maybe you're just scared.
[TAKAKI]
Not even close, Ride!
So what is it, then?!
[TAKAKI] All I said was
that we have to wait.
[RIDE]
You are always trying to.--
[YUKINOJO] That's enough!
Now go and argue somewhere else.
Some people want to eat
their food in peace.
[ALL gasp]
[YAMAGI]
We're sorry.
So, is Orga doin' any better?
I brought him food earlier,
but he didn't come out.
[YUKINOJO]
I see...
--[clattering]
--[ATRA] Oops! S-Sorry.
Atra, are you all right?
Uh, yeah.
You sure?
[ATRA] I was just remembering
back when Cookie and Cracker
asked me to look after Biscuit.
[MERRIBIT] Would you like me
to take over in the kitchen
for a while?
[ATRA]
No. I'm fine.
Well...
[YUKINOJO]
Just let her take care of it.
Huh?
[YUKINOJO]
If she keeps herself busy,
it might keep her
mind off things.
[YUKINOJO]
Mmm... This is delicious.
[ATRA giggles]
Glad you like it!
I'm so confused. I wish
I knew a way to help him.
But, my job is to stay out of
the way, if that makes sense.
You just have to let him be.
Besides, nothin' you say'll
cheer him up anyway.
Right.
But, it looks to me like
the guy's really bein'
hard on himself, this time.
Which is too bad, 'cause those
kids need someone to lift
their spirits They need
their leader back.
[gasps]
You're kidding, right?
No, I'm not. He went down in
the skirmish. Now he's gone.
And Orga got banged up
pretty bad out there,
so I'm takin' over for today.
This is too much
to take, Shino.
I mean, he just
found out that his
older brother killed himself.
It doesn't seem fair...
It's time. Further
transmissions aren't safe.
[SHINO] Yeah, okay. Sounds like
I'd better get going.
[EUGENE] Hey. How's Orga
taking all this?
[SHINO] I don't know. We haven't
seen him since it happened.
In fact, we haven't
heard a thing.
Everyone's just
sort of waiting.
[MAKANAI] It appears
the mood inside the ship
is becoming rather unstable.
The death of one who's so
close must be difficult
for such young children.
I suppose it's possible
a thing like this
could even take away
Tekkadan's will to fight.
Well, if they all decide
that they're ready to quit,
there's no way I can
change their mind.
But just let me assure you.
If that happens,
then I'll escort you by myself.
Oh?
'Cause I need to
keep moving forward
and do everything I can.
I haven't traveled this far
just to throw it all away.
This is too important to me.
I must say, you have courage
for such a young girl.
Now, what did you
want to discuss?
Well at the moment sir,
we're staying on course
and heading to
Parliament in Edmonton.
But between here and there,
I'm almost certain that
Gjallarhorn plans to
set up traps to try
and ambush us along the way.
So, I think changing our
destination would be safer.
[MAKANAI]
You do? Where, then?
[KUDELIA] Our best bet
is Anchorage, Alaska.
[MAKANAI]
Are you serious?
But what are we supposed
to do when we get there?
First, we can all disembark at
the port. Then, board a train
owned by Teiwaz and
head to the election.
[AIDE A]
A train?
[MAKANAI]
Interesting.
Wasn't aware such
a thing still existed.
Once every week, it transports
cargo from Anchorage here,
through the city
of Fairbanks
and runs all the
way to Edmonton.
The train isn't marked
or particularly unusual,
so it won't raise any suspicion.
Also, its route is
far from any cities,
which means our
Ahab reactors aren't
going to interfere with their
radio waves whatsoever.
[AIDE A]
Yes, of course.
That way, we can haul the Mobile
Suits without any problem.
I've made the necessary
arrangments with Teiwaz.
The Montag Company
approves too,
so I think we've got
everything taken care of.
You've put together
quite an amazing plan.
Particularly since you've never
even been to Earth before,
as far as I know.
I'm always studying.
I have to. It helps me to live
up to people's expectations.
I see.
Ah, well, I have no objections.
It's in your hands, now.
Thank you very much, sir.
And if I may, There are still
a couple of things that
I'd like to ask of you.
[MAKANAI]
Oh?
Out in Anchorage, I hear that
there's a powerful member
of the Arbrau Parliament.
He's a collegue of yours,
named Lasker Alesi, right?
Yes. That's correct, young lady.
[KUDELIA] Could you please
ask for his assistance?
He can transfer us
to the train faster
and make sure that it's
done more discreetly.
You have a point, there. Very
well, I'll arrange for it then.
[KUDELIA]
One more thing.
[MAKANAI]
Hm?
[KUDELIA] You said you could
win if we make it in time,
but once we get
there and it begins,
we still have no guarantee that
you'll be re-elected, do we?
[chuckles] What's the matter?
You don't trust me?
We only have one chance, sir.
I just want to make certain
we've done all we can.
've been told that Mr. Alesi
has quite a bit of influence
within the Makanai faction.
And I was wondering if it would
be possible to ask him to lobby
for you in Parliament,
until we get there ourselves?
I can see you've
thought of everything.
All right, then.
I'll tell him to do so.
[gasps]
Thank you so much.
[MAKANAI]
First, the leader of Teiwaz,
then that merchant Montag.
And this time, it's me.
Well, you certainly know
how to get your way
with men, don't you?
You want independence from Mars.
And your qualities as an
idealistic young woman have
the ability to move people,
yet you're also a realist who
wants to deregulate half-metal.
No doubt about it. You'll be a
good leader, one of these days.
[KUDELIA] Actually, sir.
I don't want to become a leader.
More than anything,
I want to be hope.
Even if my hands get
stained with blood,
long as people have hope,
I'll know that I've
made a difference.
[MERRIBIT] Honestly.
Isn't there anything I can do?
[LAFTER]
What do you mean?
There must be a way for me
to bring him out of this.
I may be an adult, but I
still don't know how to help.
There's really
nothing you can do.
And besides.
We were only told to help out
those kids in battle, anyway.
Can't believe you're so cold.
I mean, they may seem mature,
but they are still children.
[LAFTER]
Yeah, so what?
[MERRIBIT]
Huh?
[LAFTER] What I'm saying is:
Sure, I guess we might be a
little older than some of 'em,
but it's not as if we have
anything to preach.
'Cause we're just the same.
[MERRIBIT]
Eh?
The girls who're like us and
kids like them, who are out
there doin' this kinda work.
We could all die at any moment.
[LAFTER]
Take the Turbines for example.
we're more or less a shelter
for young girls who don't really
have anywhere else to go.
[gasps]
[LAFTER] And if we hadn't
picked some of 'em up,
they would've been in
bad shape. Believe me.
[MERRIBIT]
I had no idea...
[LAFTER] But, Darling likes
to say that, no matter what,
we're all his "precious women".
Just give 'em some time
and they'll come up with
their own conclusions.
Since Naze can't be here, We'll
do our best to support them.
[MERRIBIT exhales]
Uh...
Mikazuki.
Hey, uh, is he
still in there?
[MERRIBIT]
Y-Yes.
Okay
[MERRIBIT]
Wait a minute.
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
Maybe he should just
be alone for now.
[BISCUIT] But, don't you
feel like you're kinda
rushing things
on this one?
It'll be fine. Whatever happens,
you know that we'll still
follow you, no matter
what comes our way.
[grunts]
[BISCUIT] Maybe we should
discuss this a little later.
We've got more urgent things
to deal with, anyway.
Orga...
I know... that we can
make Tekkadan...
[ORGA grunts]
Biscuit...
Come on. What were you
tryin' to tell me back there?
[gasps]
Mika...
[MIKAZUKI]
Everybody's waiting.
Biscuit told me that he, uh,
he wanted to quit Tekkadan.
That I'm always goin' down the
most dangerous path I can find.
If that's true, it means I'm the
one responsible for his death.
Tell me. What do you
want me to do next, Orga?
[gasps]
Hey, gimme a break, Mika.
I just...
Look, I'm sorry.
But I can't stop yet.
That's enough.
[MIKAZUKI]
Now, I want to know--
I said that's enough!
Is this the place
you told me about?
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
'Cause I won't stop.
Not 'till we're there.
I can't. On that day, Orga,
I decided.
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
So. How many should I kill?
How many more until
we get there?
Because I need to know.
Tell me, Orga Itsuka.
You're gonna take me,
aren't you?
That's what you told me.
What should I do next?
[ORGA]
Get off me!
Yeah, all right, fine.
I'll get you there.
We can't turn
around now, anyway.
That's what you want, right?
No matter what kinda hell
might be waitin' for us.
Okay! Then, I'll do it and
I'm bringing everyone with me.
Yeah. That's right.
Take us there.
So who do you need me
to take out, then?
And what do you
want me to destroy?
'Cause if I finally get to
reach that place some day,
There's nothing that I won't do.
[ORGA]
All right, listen up.
Biscuit's not with us anymore.
Another of our brothers
has left us, forever.
But it doesn't mean
we can stop movin'.
Because our job isn't
close to being finished.
Biscuit was somebody with
a strong sense of duty.
So, the best way to honor
him is to move forward
and complete the mission.
Out here on Earth, there are
those who only want to crush us.
And Biscuit already
paid the price.
But those people
don't understand, do they?
Tekkadan is a hell of a lot more
than just a group of kids.
The fact is, up until now,
we tried to fend them
off best we could.
But all those days are over.
From this day forward,
if they get in our way again,
then we'll destroy
every last one of them.
Yeah. Anyone in our
way is the enemy.
This is for Biscuit, guys.
No-- It isn't only for him.
This is a war to avenge those
who fought and died in battle.
For our friends.
Time for revenge.
[MERRIBIT]
Now, that's enough.
Your mission is bringing
Mr. Makanai to Edmonton,
not taking revenge.
[MIKAZUKI]
It's the same thing.
Huh?
If we don't take
out Gjallarhorn,
they'll be the ones
to take us out.
Right now, it's kill
or be killed.
[ATRA]
Mikazuki...
But, please...
Might as well stop.
[MERRIBIT gasps]
Everything you're
saying is making sense,
but they still aren't gonna
listen. Least not right now.
Yep, I kinda figured
that it'd be like this.
[AZEE] We're gonna
have to help 'em out.
You know, so they
don't die out there.
Hey, Boss. I've been
wanting to speak with you
about our next route.
Our what?
♪
[ORGA] Tekkadan. Iron flowers
that'll never wilt.
Can't remember how many
times Eugene told me
he thought it sounded lame.
But you always liked the name.
Thought it was perfect.
Right, Biscuit?
I know you don't want
us to go into battle
to try and avenge your death,
but we can't stop now.
That's what it means
to be in Tekkadan.
Next time on Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
Episode 23:
"The Final Lie."