Kenji!
Please, stop hurting him!
I'm begging you...
don't hurt him any more!
Guy had a pretty sweet
RideBack, didn't he?
And you not having one,
of course you'd be envious,
after all you're only human...
Hell, I'd have been...
back in the day anyway...
But pushing him to his death
'cause you're jealous
of his ride?
You took it to a whole
'nother level, kid.
What were you thinking?
I didn't kill him,
I swear it!
Come on!
Listen to me--I
didn't kill anybody!
You sure about that?
I can do this all night...
You're the murderers
here, not me.
You keep getting 'em wrong...
Maybe you wanna rethink your
answers before Sis has to
take a shot at the
lightning round...
You know you're guilty...
Sign the confession.
Fine, I'll do it.
Kenji!
Kenji?
I'm okay.
That little brother of yours
spared you a world of pain.
The streets of Kasahara
are that much safer today
after nearly a dozen vandals
on RideBacks were arrested in
the prefecture yesterday evening
and charged with assault.
Many of those arrested
are minors, we've been told,
and as such their names
will not be released.
We're sorry.
The phone you're trying
to reach is turned off
or outside of the service area.
Please try
your call again later.
No luck?
Every time I call...
nothing...
Don't get too worried...
I mean, we don't even
know if she was there.
Maaaan!
I so knew something totally
messed up was gonna go down...!
Why would you say that?!
This sucks!
Haruki...!
Can I take Balon out?
Uh...
take it out?
Whad'ya want Balon for?
I gotta distract
myself, or else...
I'll just keep worrying.
You know I think
it might help.
Dude, how's it gonna help?!
Y'know Douta,
us stressing isn't gonna
make Rin magically appear...
I mean it's not like she
would have broken the law...
Even if she had gotten
herself arrested...
it's just...
a mix-up and they'll
figure it out soon...
She's a good egg.
Suzuri's right...
Hey, why not let her hop onto
Balon and putter around a bit.
We're the RideBack Club,
for crying out loud?!
And besides...
We can't let people go thinking
only terrorists ride 'em.
C'mon, it's the
least we can do.
RideBack Cluuuub...!
Go!
Okay, have it your way.
Keep it nice
and slow, yeah...?
We're down to
our last RideBack...
you smash up Balon
and we're sunk!
"Nice an' slow"
is my middle name!
Welp, time for liftoff!
Whoa...
whoa...
I... I got it...
I got it!
On three, Balon!
--whoa!
What the hell was that?
Ah, mission accomplished.
You're way cuter when
you smile, y'know.
Do I look bad-ass or what!
Hands on the handles--this
ain't a parade!
Huh...?!
Whoa!
Again...
the streets of Kasahara
are that much safer today...
I asked my brother
to look into it.
Rin's been arrested.
But, at least
we know she's okay.
They're trying to pin
some random guy's murder
on her little brother.
If the GGP is half as mixed
up in this as my brother
seems to think, they might
not be getting out.
Okakura...
Enough with the secrecy, I need
you to be straight up with me.
Who the hell are you?
Officers in Sendai have already
arrested several elusive
criminals with the help
of their new RideBacks,
the White Riders.
These are specialized machines,
bearing little resemblance
to those sold to civilians...
White Rider patrols
in Chiba have arrested
a terror suspect
atop a RideBack.
One officer was injured
during the pursuit.
Our viewers have been calling
in from all over Japan,
and they are not happy
about these White Riders
being forced upon them.
Well who would be...?
That said, what can
we do from here...?
I'd be hard pressed to think of
a more effective alternative
in eradicating terrorism.
Local governments,
on the other hand, are going
out of their way to request
White Rider squads,
isn't that so?
That's true--especially
in areas considered --
Teams are slated for deployment
in Yokohama, Sendai, Kobe,
and Miyazaki...
Adding thirteen more squads will
get us to our goal of thirty.
You can't just barge in!
Sorry, but it couldn't wait.
At ease...
For now.
Quite a theatrical entrance...
Superintendent.
What's the meaning of this?
I think it speaks for itself.
"Rin Ogata will be transferred
to a GGP facility and
detained indefinitely"?
You're acting like
we don't exist...!
How dare you
disrespect my department?!
I call the shots here, sir...
If I were you,
I'd get accustomed to it.
Police searched the house,
I suppose they were
looking for evidence...
They inadvertently
straightened up Kenji's room,
it's so tidy now...
But you know...
Messy was better.
Yeah...
I guess...
Honey...
You're strong...
Far stronger than you know.
So don't you
give up, all right?
Time's up, lady.
And Kenji's a good boy,
say what they will.
You have to leave--now.
Don't lose hope, dear.
Save Shouko...
Protect Kenji...
That's all I wanted to do...
But helping them
came at a price.
Would you have done
the same thing, Mom?
Stop dancing
and just answer me.
You have been chosen.
"Chosen?"...
By who?
You've been chosen
for your strength.
Who...?
And what for...?
How am I strong?
You've the
strength to fight...
To emerge victorious...
To rip your enemies
to shreds...!
The GGP's ruling
philosophy seems to be
"might makes right."...
And people are finding this
an increasingly bitter pill
to swallow.
Easy to see why.
People are starting to wonder if
this whole Rideback Girl story
was simply some kind
of publicity stunt...
Rin...
I wonder...
Why haven't
they named Rin yet...?
The GGP is up to something.
I know you're back there.
Wasn't I quiet enough?
Fuego...?
Do what you have to.
And what about you?
I have a date
with a dead man...
What a dump, am I right?
Don't you worry, sweetie.
A little paperwork
and we'll have you
transferred out of here...
Give it a week or so...
You'll be in GGP custody
where it's much comfier.
Until then, is there anything
else we can do for you?
Don't transfer me.
I'm sorry?
You're in lockdown,
babydoll--get a clue...
We're gonna take you
where we damn well please.
Huh?
What's wrong?
He disappeared.
Hand out of the coat.
Nice and slow.
Far enough.
You tell Colonel Romanov...
Goblin is gonna
pay him a visit soon.
You're telling me
he just walked away?
Shall I put out an all-points
bulletin for Okakura?
What, to catch
a washed-up veteran...?
That's overkill.
Goblin would've been
better off staying dead.
Account for your things
and sign out for them.
Outta the way!
No, wait--!
I don't care anymore...
Just leave me in the truck...
The video on your screen
was submitted to us
by an anonymous source.
Though the resolution is
grainy in comparison
to the official footage,
this sheds new light
on the incident.
The presence of the armored
GGP vehicle in the shot
is significant.
Clearly, the GGP's
involvement in this situation...
Sato, tell me you're watching
The WideShow right now...!
This just in: One of
the young suspects
apprehended in the
Kasahara incident...
was taken by BMA agents...
as she was making her way
to GGP headquarters...
just moments ago.
According to a statement
issued by the police,.
all five of the officers on the
scene were wounded or killed.
The prisoner at large is
suspected to have played
a significant role in the
TV tower bombing as well.
Since she is a minor, however,
her name cannot be disclosed.
The BMA have
released the following.
Good afternoon, Japan.
The RideBack Girl was imprisoned
on false terrorism charges
at the GGP's behest.
We of the BMA have taken
the righteous path
and liberated her
from their tyranny.
In the twenty minutes since the
attack occurred, we've come
no closer to discovering the
fate of the kidnapped prisoner.
Again, the BMA claims
to have abducted the youth
known as the RideBack Girl
while she was being moved
to GGP custody.
The GGP have neither
confirmed nor denied this.
They can't move
a single co-ed from A to B?
Some Intelligence Bureau!
Go ahead.
We found Okakura, but BMA
agents are shadowing him.
Please advise, Colonel.
He'll lead you to them...
If you play your cards right.
Hey, you're Goblin, ain'tcha?
Why'd you free the girl...?
We both know she has
nothing to do with this.
Ask 1st Lieutenant Kiefer...
We'll even give ya a ride.
I see...
Rin was just the bait
to draw me out into the open.
Target is moving southwest
at 80 kilometers per hour...
Unit Eight will give pursuit
on the ground via the overpass.
Recon out.
I know you...
So we meet again.
So this is the preview?
Pretty cool!
Super cool!
But Haruki's such a slacker,
he never helps me
like he's supposed to!
Hey, now--don't look at me.
Oh, I see how it is!
You're probably jealous
'cause you've never been
--on a RideBack, huh!
--Yeah, that'll be the day! No.