Good morning,
thanks for watching TKN News.
Today marks the
sixth anniversary
of the Great Earthquake...
Aw... Stupid control rod's
got a crack in it...
Scrap pile!
Hey boss...!
Yeah, no, not yet...
The shop definitely has the
parts Balon needs and all...
I just...
I put her together,
so I wanted to at least
fix anything I could, you know?
Turning now, to the
political front...
Colonel Romanov Kallenbach will
be sworn in today as the new
Commander in Chief of the
GGP's Peacekeeping Forces...
Rin...?
Can you grab that
off the table?
Oh, yeah...
Silly me...
I'm going by the club later,
and I didn't wanna forget it.
Really, on Sunday?
After competing against other
racers, I feel like I'm finally
beginning to understand
some things...
Like handling and how to coax
out a RideBack's full power.
I'm gonna go out on a limb
and guess you forgot...
Huh?
You're unbelievable.
Can't believe you
forgot about the mall.
Sorry, Shouko!
I did forget!
I even promised that
I'd go with you!
So overdramatic...
I'll text you if I spot
anything you have to have.
I know the club's
important to you...
Its nice to see you
excited like this again.
This is great!
Aw, thank you.
Hey, look, RideBacks on TV!
Hesner Enterprises is
holding a conference today,
unveiling their
new police-issued
"White Rider" vehicles.
No, he didn't "do" anything...
It's just we've got this new
girl who's caught his eye...
But he's pretending like he
couldn't care less about her.
Has he told you about his past?
Not a word...
I've asked him flat out, and
all I get is a blank stare.
Go figure, huh?
Just as well...
I'll talk to you again soon.
We came all the way out here
on a Sunday for nothing?!
Thought you knew...
We didn't have
anything planned...
Wish you coulda told me
you were heading here.
Well, we're here!
You couldn't send
a text or an email?!
This was all
kinda last minute...
We're taking Balon
and Fuego to the shop.
Is there...
something wrong with Fuego?
No, figured since we're
bringing in Balon that Feugo
might as well get a tune up...
Unless you want
Fuego to stay behind?
No thanks...
That's okay...
But would you mind giving me
a lift into the city?
I guess I could.
What are you gonna do there?
Oh, Shouko's shopping,
I was gonna meet up with her.
Ooh...!
I wanna go shopping too!
What? You are coming?
You sure it's cool?
Ah...
I gotcha...
Call me when you guys
get close, okay...?
Great!
Seriously?
This is the new thing
in police enforcement...?
Talk about overkill?
Come on, keep it down!
You got a prototype or
somethin' to show us, right...?
'Cause the glossy press kits are
nice and all, but you know...
Yoda, I'm telling you.
Shut... Up!
I apologize for the delay...
To begin,...
There are a few opening comments
from our Vice President Goudou
of Hesner Enterprises.
Is there a checkpoint?
I guess so.
There's some kind of
inauguration ceremony
for some big cheese at the GGP.
reporting live from
GGP Headquarters...
We expect to see Colonel
Kallenbach making his way
to the ceremony
at any time now...
The route to the inauguration
site is under heavy security--
Aw, how long?
I'd guess at least
another half hour or so...
Sorry!
That's fine, I'm over
by the TV Tower.
I'll just wait for you in
the lobby café and who knows...
I might even have a donut!
Hey!
Wait for us...!
Suzuri's coming with me!
Alright...
Tea only until you get
your butts over here.
What the--?
Hello...?
Shouko...?
What was that?
I can't see anything...!
Oh, no...
What?
Shouko...!
Are you there?!
Whoa!
What's that?!
The city...
Isn't that where we're
supposed to meet Shouko?!
Please people!
Stay calm...!
Our security team will lead you
all outside to safety!
You get that?
Hell yeah.
And This isn't...
part of the
presentation, is it?
Uh, yeah, no.
Go ahead.
We've set up a perimeter
and begun surveillance...
They've used several
smoke grenades inside...
So we still don't have
a clear picture of what's
going on in there...
But a group online has already
claimed responsibility.
Understood...
I'll try and calm our no-doubt
enraged commander.
Man, what should we do?
What are we supposed to do?
Traffic's gonna
make any plan impossible.
Shouko...
At two-oh-two this afternoon...
A blast on the Thirty-Seventh
Floor Observation Deck of--
We're still unclear on the
exact number of hostages
being held captive inside...
The armed gunmen...
here on the edge
of the cordoned-off area...
I'm told the yellowish
smoke we're seeing
is in fact from smoke
grenades, being used...
Now for this late
breaking development...
There is a group now claiming
responsibility for the attack...
The BMA have just posted
the following message
on their website...
Let's take a look...
The BMA will not abide
the appointment
of Romanov Kallenbach,
a corrupt, bloodthirsty
blight on our nation...
Exchange for the safe
release of our hostages,
we demand immediate negotiations
with the Colonel...
The BMA will not allow
a government of fools.
A cabinet representative has
made an official plea to the
Police Department and the
GGP Peacekeeping Forces
to engage in countermeasures
against the terrorists...
Access to the surrounding
area is currently limited
to emergency vehicles
at this time.
No use...
Can't connect...
Those being admitted currently
are the injured found
immediately outside
the blast area...
We're still waiting
for confirmation...
But there are reports
of injured trapped inside...
That does it...
Hey, Rin...
Rin, no!
I'm taking Fuego out!
Wait...!
I understand how you feel...
But hopping on
a Rideback isn't...
Don't go...!
They said there's
terrorists there...!
You're gonna wind up
killing yourself!
There's nothing you can do!
Would think about this...
Rin?
I'll be back when I get
Shouko out of that place!
Rin...!
Catch!
And she's gone.
Shouko...
Please be all right!
The BMA are not
the murderers...!
Do what we say quietly
and you won't be harmed!
The BMA are not
the murderers...!
Do what we say quietly
and you won't be harmed!
I have to call the police!
No...
As you can see behind me,
GGP forces are moving in
to begin their
counter-terrorist operation.
Their first order of business
will be to establish a blockade
in a two-kilometer radius
around the tower.
We are strongly advising
anyone within this area
to evacuate immediately...
Specifically,
we're talking about
the following Districts:...
West Twenty-Four,...
West Twenty-Five,...
West Thirty-Seven,...
and West Fifty-One.
Pesky little terrorists,
wouldn't you say?
I'm sorry we've had
to postpone your ceremony.
Why would I let a minor hostage
situation bother me...?
Let this BMA do their worst.
They'll prove my point and
my White Riders will be
on the ground all the sooner.
It's like a war zone
down there!
Yeah, great, you got
the shots, can we go now?
Where's your
journalistic integrity?
It's buried under
my desire to not die!
Oh, come on...
Please pick up!
Shouko...
Hello...?!
Shouko!
Hold on...
Rin...
Please, just hold on.
Rin...?
Are you there?
Shouko...!
You okay?!
Where are you...?
I just got to
the train station...
I'm gonna rescue you!
Second floor lobby...
in a corner.
But Rin, you have
to stay away!
There are men with guns here!.
I'm okay, but it's not safe--
Shouko...!
Can you hear me?!
Stop!
Where do you think
you're off to?
Nice RideBack...
This area's closed
to civilians...!
Turn around and leave now!
Please, my friend
is trapped in there...!
I just talked to her
on the pho--
Don't worry!
We'll get her
out of there, okay!
You just get
yourself to safety!
Shouko!
No!
Get back here!
Echo-One-Five to Base...
A civilian RideBack
has ignored our orders
and is riding into
the building!
Rin!
Shoukoooo!
Shouko!
Rin!
Hey...!
Are you all right?
I can't...
believe you came for me...!
I was so scared, Rin!
Sorry it took me so long...
Now let's get outta here.
Yeah.
Okay...
Climb up here.
Don't move!
A commercial RideBack?
Kill the engine and dismount.
Where you been
hidin' all this time?
Hang on tight, Shouko!
Get with it!
Open Fire!
Echo-Two-Four to Base...!
Possible terrorist vehicle
moving toward the bridge...!
It's a Red RideBack!
Aw, man!
We're missing all
the good stuff, C'mon!
Aren't we like, breaking the
law by not evacuating?
Think of it as
having an exclusive.
We're not goin' all the way
up to the roof, are we?!
Chop-chop!
Why me?
We're receiving word that
GGP Peacekeeping Forces
have entered the building...
Sasaki is live with more.
Good afternoon, I'm
standing here in front
of the southern Great Bridge,
a mere two kilometers
from the TV Tower situation...
All roads in the area have
been closed by GGP forces,
making this the closest we
can get to what's going on...
The city center is blanketed
in smoke...
Please, God...
Keep them safe!
What are we gonna do...?!
Everybody thinks
we're terrorists now!
It's weird...
I feel like I'm
connected to Fuego...
Just like the
first time I rode her...
As if she's an extension
of my own limbs...
Yoda...!
Look over there!
Rin...
Behind us!
As the situation continues
to unfold, a helicopter is
in pursuit of what appears to
be a Rideback which emerged
from the barricaded area.
We believe this may be
one of the terrorists
attempting to flee, but
we're unable to confirm
that at this time.
Rin...
Let's just stop...
I'm sure they'll
understand if we explain...!
Okay, Rin?
You might want to jump.
Shouko, hold on
and do not let go!
There it is again...
That light...
The chopper has
been destroyed...!
Ladies and gentlemen, there's
been some kind of explosion...!
The Rideback barely
escaped the blast...
Holy--...
Rin, no...
What the heck is she doing?
All right...
I think we're safe now...
Shouko?
That's a Type-L Fuego...?
When were you chosen?
Your machine
has unique tuning...
Their programming allows a
Rideback to choose its rider.
Say what?
Good luck.
Today's terrorist attack on
the TV Tower, which began
just past two this afternoon,
was resolved by GGP Peacekeeping
Forces by four-thirty...
All five of the political
radicals were killed
in the ensuing conflict.
The Japanese government has
issued a formal thanks to
the GGP for their swift
response with minimal
loss of civilian life.
Sworn in soon after,
Commander Kallenbach
expressed his condolences to all
victims of terrorist violence,
including those in
Sasebo and Kokura,...
and renewed his vow
to wipe out terrorism.
Rin...
Please don't go...
That light...
We're too young to go to jail!
Hey, relax, dude.
I got an idea,
why don't you relax, dude?!
The GGP think we're terrorists!
Nah, we're fine...
We're minor supporting
characters at best.
Whaaaaat?!