This is Private
First Class Robert.
He served under Kallenbach
during the Battle of Arizona.
He's been unresponsive
to my questions.
Catatonic,
or something like that.
He would have been
a perfect witness.
Don't fall back, we
have to hold the line...
I wondered why they let me
in here with so little fuss...
Shouldn't have
gotten my hopes up...
I'll try again tomorrow,
see if he remembers working
at Hesner Incorporated...
Don't hold your breath.
So much for our witness...
Basically...
But the fact they
let her try at all
betrays something significant...
She got in without a fight...
If any evidence still exists,
they're sure we're not
going to find it...
You know...
Colonel Kallenbach may
have won this battle
before we even knew
to take the field.
Hey, new guy--we're
off at the next stop.
Thanks.
Using a proprietary OS,
are we?
There's no place left
to hide, is there?
Okakura's gonna
figure something out.
White Riders could
roll up here any minute.
Maybe...
I should turn myself in.
No, Rin...
Hell no...
Have you forgotten that they're
bloodthirsty murderers?
'Cause I sure haven't...
My father and brother hate
the GGP, and with good reason.
They're not getting
you--not on my watch.
Listen up, guys--from
here, we're gonna march
to Peace Memorial Park.
If you're taking
your RideBack over,
make sure you sign
the list first, okay?
Yeah, hang a right--you
can park over there.
Man, why're these guys
jumping the gun so bad?
What did you expect, dude?
Why wait until the cops've
jacked all our RideBacks
to protest the fact they've
started impounding 'em...?
Folks need to see RideBacks
are nothing to be afraid of.
Just leave it to me!
I'm gonna prove Rin
is innocent and show
how awesome RideBacks are!
Fair enough, but if
they take Balon away,
you're gonna owe us
a boat load of cash!
Huh?
That's not fair!
Don't go bonkers out there and
you won't have to--just keep it
nice and chill like
we talked about, yeah?
Got it!
Whatcha holding?
Don't laugh...!
It's my new good-luck
charm!--it's a picture
of Rin dancing
that Shouko gave me.
We've got a really good
turnout today, you guys...!
We're going to keep this
nice and organized!
What's in the back?
Just some artwork, sir.
A permit, huh?
I'll be back.
That...
permit's gonna
do the trick...
isn't it?
Hope so.
Hey you...!
Open it up!
Damn.
What're you waiting for?
Get back here!
And we're screwed.
Guys, the permit's good...
They're clear to go through.
Sorry for the delay!
Man...
Your dad is
a political pimp...
He's got some bomb-ass clout.
All clear.
This seems awfully risky...
Are you sure this
is going to work?
What, hiding you
in the city...?
It's like hiding a tree in
the woods--who's gonna notice?
Anyway,.
You wanna see
the others, don't ya?
The others?
The RideBack crowd is holding an
anti-GGP rally in town today.
We're gonna meet up with 'em
after the shouting's done.
Is Shouko there?
She's isn't marching
in the protest,.
but she's gonna
swing by later.
They left ya a message.
Cool, go for it!
Glad you're okay, Rin...!
'Cause if anything happened
to you, I'd totally fall apart!
--Squeeze in, Shouko!
Hey...!
What's up...?!
I'm doing pretty good...!
Since we got your message,
I've been way less worried...!
When are you coming home?
We're gonna e-mail this,
so we gotta keep it
kinda short, ladies...
Sup!
I've been practicing
on Balon all the time!
Maybe when you get back,
we could, like, ride together?!
There--I said it!
What is this,
a video slumber-party--?
Oh.
You, guys...
you're the best.
Our intel suggests the
BMA's next target will be
a government office or major
public transportation hub...
Surveillance teams have been
dispatched to those areas...
We need as many eyes
on the ground as possible,
so we've notified
the police, as well...
And White Riders
are canvassing the city.
On a related note,
it's come to our attention
that Parliament member Nanpuu
Katowka has lent his support
to anti-GGP activities.
Under the Anti-Terrorism Act,
we can arrest him, but...
well...
You see...
Colonel Kallenbach...
You do know the traitor's son
is Ryuunosuke Katowka.
All the more reason to act.
So what are we up against?
The military designed
their information network
to be a totally
cloistered system...
No way of taking it down
from the outside.
Talk about suicide.
We might as well pack up
if we can't disable
their security systems.
I don't think Goblin
was done speaking yet.
Their network design is
unique, but it's based on
the Harvard configuration,
or at least some of it is...
We can't just
kick down the firewall.
What we can do is confuse
the hell out of the system.
We route connection requests
through third-party
zombie terminals,
then we flood their system
with teardrop packets--a classic
denial-of-service attack.
It's going to
take some time, though.
Level with me...
What do you really plan to
accomplish with this attack?
Conscience, Goblin...?
It's a little late for that.
Fine, on account
of our history.
Yes, I have other motives.
Winning isn't
enough for you, Kiefer?
I fully intend to win...
But I'm not simple minded.
All who join the
BMA do so because
it furthers their own agenda.
Doesn't take a psychic
to know your agenda...
I hate him, too...
His actions are unforgivable.
My vendetta was forged in the
flames of that missile site
as he abandoned
us to our fate...
I swore his betrayal
would not be the end of me.
Once I've destroyed
everything he holds dear,
Kallenbach shall die.
Speaking of agendas...
Why did you create Fuego?
It...
reminds me of every life
I took on the battlefield.
I wasn't looking for a Rin.
Yes, but you found one.
And...
thanks to you, that girl's been
made privy to her true nature...
She's happiest twirling
among bullets and flame.
She's a 19 year old girl,
Kiefer...
What've we condemned her to?
You know...
I wonder how it got
to this point.
What if I hadn't broken through
the blockade that day...
Had enough of RideBacks, eh?
No, it's nothing like that...
I just wish I could go riding
around on one without making
the six o'clock news
or getting arrested.
You ever dance over there,
at the Third National Theater?
Personally, I think that
place is way more your style.
I did, but those days
are behind me now.
Suck it up...!
You hurt yourself, big deal...
Maybe you won't
be the best ballerina
in the history of
the universe anymore...
but that doesn't mean
you just throw in the towel.
Gonna give up on Fuego?
There's no way I can
force you to ride her...
But like it or not, this
is your EW Band and you're
part of our club, dammit...
Learn to deal and move on
because quitting the club
just isn't an option, Rin.
I guess it isn't.
We want the GGP out of Japan!
When do we want it, guys?!
Right now!
That's right!
This crowd is freakin'
huge, man--Hopefully,
it'll make the cops
think twice about trying
to bust any heads, you know?
Hey, yo, Suzuri...
You cool up there?
I chilled out--cantcha tell?
I can tell you're not
flopping around...
Uh, what's the matter?
Whoa...
The Third National Theater...
Rin used to dance there,
back in the day.
Dang...
Look at the size
of that place...
Just between us, I'd rather
see Rin doing her thing
on stage than zipping
around on a RideBack...
But!
I couldn't tell her that--oh,
she would hate my guts for sure!
Huh...
Really?
I can't just be, like,
"Hey, that thing you used
to do was way awesomer!"
Maybe...
I didn't know Rin back
when she was a dancer,
but I betcha it's her
ballet skills that make her
so awesome with Fuego.
If ballet helped with riding,
maybe Ridebacks could
help her with dancing.
Makes sense,
when you think about it.
She just needs to get back
in the saddle, right?
Uh-huh...
Seems like she'd rock at
whatever she puts her mind to.
After Rin hurt herself,
she probably didn't think
too much before up
and quitting ballet...
In my experience, when
stuff like that goes down,
it's friend's job to
get them out of their head.
You and Shouko
are her best friends...
Give it a try!
Dude's got a point...
Sometimes ya gotta bust out
the tough love to be a pal...
Like Haruki--I'm older, but
he's always bossing me around.
Its too soon for friendship!
I'm just her biggest fan,
nothing else!
Whad'ya mean, "too soon?" It's
not like there's a rulebook!
Exactly...
Go for it...
From where we're standing,
this looks like the
perfect time to speak up!
Hey, you up there--you're
the RideBack girl, aren'tcha?
Huh?
Yeah--that's her, isn't it?
Calm down, you guys...!
I am so not her!
I'm a big fan!
Are you really her?
I'd love to tell you I am--
See?!
I knew it!
Hey...!
The RideBack girl came to
the demonstration, everybody!
For real?!
Awesome...!
Where is she?!
No, wait!
C'mon!
I...!
Thanks for taking us
as far as you did.
Come on, Rin.
Parliament member Nanpuu
Kataoka has been taken
into custody just moments ago.
The GGP allege that
Kataoka has lent support
to a terrorist organization,
and are detaining him
in his hospital room in lieu
of jail, citing his condition.
Simply put, Colonel,
any combat vet who tries
to go head-to-head with the
Grimoire isn't going to live
long enough to rue his mistake.
We'll have a chance
to test your confidence
in the Grimoire soon enough.
A white RideBack...?!
The protest is still going...?
Let's make some noise, people!
We gotta show
the GGP we mean business!
I can't believe the RideBack
girl is out in public...!
That's the BMA chick
from the blockade?
Wow, she's taking a risk...!
She looks like she's
cutting class to be here...
Oh, crap...
It's Suzuri-mania.
Let's head out soon.
Still gotta meet up
with everybody.
Attention passengers.
This train will stop
for five additional minutes
to allow for a mandatory GGP
counter-terrorism inspection.
Your safety and comfort
are our top priorities.
Sweating yet?
We apologize for the delay.
We're gonna be safe
with the others, aren't we?
Hey...
You should check on
the old man...
I can hold down the fort.
No, we need
to observe the protest.
Mr. Kataoka, the boss
is asking for you.
RideBack girl's here--what
do you pigs think of that?!
We're not afraid
of you damn fascists!
You tell 'em, man!
YEAH!
Suzuri...!
It's time to go now...!
Oh, dangit...
She can't hear me at all!
Haruki... look.
White Riders?!
The GGP's here, too.
That's bad, right?
Headquarters is saying we've
got a fugitive in the crowd
on a RideBack, one Rin Ogata.
Is that her?
Attention all units: there's
a wanted criminal in there,
thumbing her nose at us.
She's on RideBack.
Beat the hell out of a cop
with one a few nights ago.
Look sharp.
Roger.
Did you see that?
Those bastards
better not roll in here!
Get the hell out
of our country, you thugs!
You're not the boss
of us, dammit!
Should we run or what?!
They're coming!
That concludes the
anti-terror inspection.
Thank you for your patience.
First your sister, now your
father--it must be tough.
Why'd you come here?
Have you looked
into Kallenbach's past?
The GGP is evolving...
Warmongers like the Colonel
are fast becoming a liability.
And your point is?
We can get your father
out of this little fix...
Which is why...
you're going to do
something nice for me.
Hesner Incorporated...
You're going to expose them.
Who do you think you are?.
You presume to threaten me?
Not at all...
Keeping the audience interested
requires a change in regime...
All I ask is that
you simply hit your marks
and recite your lines.
I'd love to have you on board.
Wait--they can't do that?!
Oh my God!
We gotta get outta here!
Yeah, no kidding.
Just run!
Suzuri...!
Get outta there!
What, Haruki?
Why's she leaving the park?!
Rin Ogata is fleeing the scene.
Vehicle One, get out there
and bring her in.
Ten-four.
Awesome...!
Rin and Tamayo are here!
Suzuri...?!
Hey, Rin!
I'm on her six--Rider Two,
cut around and box her in!
Roger!
Idiot!
They're after you...! Suzuri!
Balon?
Wait--Suzuri?
Oh my God!
Crap, they're trying
to cut her off!
Suzuri!
Just stop!
Hey, Rin...!
Listen...!
You need to start
dancing again...!
I wanna see you happy...!
you're my bestfriend!
Tamayo...!
What is she saying?!
I've got a surprise
for you, Rin!
While you were gone, I've been
practicing like crazy...!
And I can jump now, too!
No way...
Oh my God...!
Please, No...!
No...
This...
isn't real...
None of this...
is happening...
It's a dream...
a bad dream...
I, I'm gonna wake up...
and Suzuri's,
gonna be fine, she's...!
She's not gonna be...
Nooooooooo!
Yeah...
Understood...
Thanks for everything...
I'll call you later on, kay?
They...
murdered her...
--I know.
--That's... all you can say?!
I wish you never would have
made this horrible thing...!
Then Suzuri would...
Suzuri'd be fine...!
She wouldn't be dead!
Leave him.
We killed her...
With a RideBack...
With our mistakes...
She died...
because of
the things we've done!