My mother danced with a radiance
that captivated audiences...
Their attention granted
her form and focus,.
In return, she let them
bathe in her luminescence.
She was the stuff of legend,
a treasure of the stage...
Watching, not daring to blink,
I followed her path--
chasing that sacred
fire I was lacking...
I wanted so badly
to be like her.
It seemed easier
than being me.
But then, when the curtain
came crashing down...
When I awoke from the dream,
and life forced me
to live as Rin Ogata...
Shouko was there for me...
Never without
that smile of hers...
She shared her spark,
and I cherished it.
It was all I had,
until Fuego.
I danced through the sky,
my heart fit to burst.
My legs had failed me,
but with her wheels,
I could take flight again.
That freedom...
came at a heavy price.
My greed has hurt people
I've never even met...
all but destroyed my family...
and led to a dear friend
dying in my place.
We attack the tyrant
in his lair tomorrow...
Take the field with me.
Their pawns are
no match for my knights,
but having a strong queen
on the board never hurt.
The game doesn't
appeal to you...?
Will you flee...
as Goblin did long ago...?
Always running, waiting for
that night when they finally
kick your door in, and secretly
relieved when they do?
Have you any idea
what you want to do, Rin...?
Run for it?
Mourn your dead?
Make your enemy bleed?
You love RideBacks so much,
but you don't give a damn
about anybody,
you make me sick!
Letting emotions
enslave you is not a virtue.
Suzuri was killed because
they thought she was me...!
Her blood is on my hands!
Fine--do as you will.
Without a rider
to lend it strength,
a RideBack is mere scrap metal.
If you would let your
talent wither on the vine,
then you're unworthy
of the freedom
these machines can grant...
Get out.
We...
can't even get
flowers for her?
I think...
Suzuri would understand.
They're gone...
We're all that's left.
Come on...
Let's get you
out of this rain.
You sure the
phone's not tapped?
I'm taking a big risk here.
Yes, it's clean...
I checked it myself.
Have you looked
through that paperwork?
Oh yeah...
I confirmed Hesner
landed a juicy contract
for a new military vehicle,
but the plug got pulled on it
at the last second.
GGP and Hesner
pulled a fast one...
Somebody used
connections to force
the order of White Riders...
Looks like the big
whigs wanted insure
they didn't leave empty handed.
All well and good...
but a whole lot of money
changed hands in the process.
And...
without proof, we're up
a creek without a paddle...
I'm leaving that to you guys.
We already have
all the proof we'll need.
All that's left for us
to figure out...
is how they're going
to react when everything
is out in the open.
Hey...
Are you positive
we can trust these guys?
They should do
as they're told...
Just trust me on this, okay?
How's she doing?
Hanging in there...
Acts like she is, at least...
Inside, who knows?
"Anything you need, just name
it," I told her, and she said...
"Flowers...
for Suzuri."
Hey, why won't you
come with us?
Once we're outta here,
we'll be set.
I got a few contacts that
could help us out, you know?
I promised that I'd protect her,
but you have to now.
Yeah, I know.
Idiot.
Geez, Rin--you're
soaking wet...!
It's not safe out
there--you can't just--
I see...
Come on in.
It's quiet out there...
I don't like it.
They've closed off all
access points into the city.
But, with roads being so empty,
we'll have our run of the place.
What'll we do if
they attack us first...?
We don't have a Plan B.
Not likely.
Kallenbach would never
kill me in my bed, as it were.
He needs to feel like
he's finally bested me...
He'll cut me down from
a RideBack, or not at all.
The two of us have unfinished
business from Arizona.
He won't fire until he sees
the whites of my eyes...
A fatal mistake...
Romanov's time is at an end.
Be careful out there, man.
Thanks--Gonna need it.
Never really was any good
at big, teary goodbyes.
Good thing I'm heading out on
that chopper with you tomorrow.
I'm sorry for...
Getting you
mixed up in all this.
Hey, don't beat
yourself up about it...
The choice was mine
to make after all.
So...
your mom...
She was a famous dancer, right?
The one and only Yuki Ogata.
I tried so hard to be her.
Performing at her level
was all I ever wanted to do...
Any chance of that disappeared
the second I got hurt...
I simply sat back and watched as
my one goal in life faded away.
It was like,.
a giant weight had been
lifted from my shoulders.
I didn't have to live in
the shadow of my mother anymore.
Being one of her fans
would have been enough for me...
I'd given up.
But then Fuego showed up...
and I was so sure
I could dance again...
God, what was I thinking...?
Stop, Rin.
I joined your club...
and made such
wonderful friends...
Now look at us...
This is all my fault.
Why do all of my dreams
come crashing to the ground
just when I start
believing in them...?
Whenever I find
something precious,
life snatches it away from me.
I don't care if
I have to shuffle through
the rest of
my life in a fog...!
But I can't
lose anything else!
You be careful out there...
And remember to
take care of each other.
We'll do our best.
Rin...
I'm so sorry.
Be safe, dummy.
What was she
saying that day...
Before...
Right before she...
The monorail was so loud
I couldn't hear her...
but she definitely
said something.
What was she trying to say?
Suzuri really wanted to
see you dance again, you know.
Haruki felt
compelled to tell me...
Wasn't gonna say anything...
But she let it slip to
the boys during the protest.
I guess she thought
it would hurt you
or piss you off
or something...
so she never brought it up.
Oh, Suzuri...
Unit H-5 reporting in!
We've got a visual on
an armed band of RideBacks
coming up northwest
of the base!
We've IDed the leader near the
head of the pack--they're BMA!
Orders, sir?
Leave 'em be, soldier...
I'll go lay out
the welcome mat.
Huh?
What the hell...?!
I'm gonna be good and pissed if
that chopper is running late.
Calm down, Princess--it's
already on the roof.
--It's called a RideBack.
--Why the sudden interest,
Don't tell me, you're thinking
about picking up riding?
Girl's got some crazy skills!
You can ride again
if you really want to.
Its fire.
That's what "Fuego" means
in the Spanish language.
I promise I'll protect you.
Do you have any regrets?
I know the club's
important to you...
Its nice to see you
excited like this again.
Listen...!
You need to start
dancing again...!
I wanna see you happy!
Rin, honey...
are you nervous?
Yeah.
Let your heart guide you.
Trust me, it knows
the choreography.
Take the stage
and make it welcome you.
C'mon.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, Tamayo--
I have to stay here.
Don't even think of
leaving without us!
What are you doing...?!
We gotta go!
What the..?!
This is Vehicle Two.
We've neutralized
a helicopter on a rooftop
in the west district...
Commencing
forward assault, over.
What was that sound?!
What's going on in here...?
Rin--come on!
We gotta go!
You okay, Tamayo?!
Never better...!
The RideBacks are two klicks
from our front gate and closing.
Status report!
Computer anomaly, Colonel!
Someone's wreaking havoc
on our network!
System live in three, two...
Blips on the NRS radar...!
They're missiles...!
They're too close, sir--
The AA guns are useless!
Hacking our system
is impossible!
It's Goblin...!
What the hell is going on?!
How long I've waited for this.
Gatobu!
Send them to hell!
Yessir!
The Grimoires have secured
the first floor, sir...
Remaining enemy forces
are dug in.
Entering now to take 'em out.
Two female terrorists
are fleeing the building
on RideBack!
No...
Tearing through wind
and flame alike...
the crimson metal
steed pauses...
to bathe its hero
in the righteous light.
Next time,
the final episode:...
"To the Lighted Stage."