The rush of excitement...
The view as I soared above...
I felt the faint flame
smoldering in my heart
dance to life with
this crimson machine.
Authorities are set to
pursue the militant group BMA...
After another
bombing on the GGP...
Officials will employ
the Damage Prevention Act...
What these terrorists
don't realize is that they're
playing right into
the hands of the GGP.
But the group
is wanted nationwide...
Any act of vandalism
will be considered-
It's only a matter
of time before they have
full government support.
Yeah...
they've got the
cabinet's ear...
With all these attacks...
legislature will give them
the green light...
and then they'll roll out
the White RideBacks.
You don't sound
too thrilled about it...
Your sister on the other
hand is practically glued
to the seat of that RideBack,
regardless how much
we may disapprove...
To call that girl stubborn...
would be an understatement.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Son...
Know that I'm counting on you
to look after your sister.
My heart just about
leapt out of my mouth!
You've gotta be
some kind of prodigy...
You're instantly amazing
at anything you try.
And it's like your sense
of balance isn't even affected
by the laws of gravity.
Your body's gotta operate
on its own molecular level.
I mean you...
wow...
You soared through the heavens
like you were riding on
the back of Pegasus!
It made my heart flutter
like a butterfly.
Did she really jump that high?
You betcha!
She jumped so high
I felt like I was witnessing
some kind of miracle.
It wasn't that high...
And it was mostly luck because
I had no idea what to do
on that thing.
Oh, would you
stop being modest...
I bet you're the only
person who's ever made
a jump like that before.
It makes me want to try it!
Hey, go easy on the mayo!
So...
What's the story on the white
knight who came to your rescue?
Well, it turns out
he's the club's advisor.
You know there's
something about that guy,
he seems like he's
from a different planet...
He looks like he could strangle
a grizzly bear with his hands.
So he's the manly type then.
Rin...?
Why are you doing that?
You were great yesterday.
Yeah...
She's pretty cute...
This is the girl that everyone
on campus has been raving about.
Are you talking to me?
No, it's the girl next to her.
Your name is Rin,
if I'm not mistaken?
Sorry things got
so intense yesterday.
My name's Haruki,
I'm an engineering sophomore.
Pleased to meet you...
And this is Douta,
he's a junior.
Hello there...
Not to be too presumptuous...
But I wanted to give you
our club's application form.
You should come by
the shop again,
even if it's just to
hang out or something.
Anytime you want is cool.
There's always someone there.
How about you stop trying
to gloss over the real
issue at hand here?
Uh, what issue?
You endangered my friend's
life by putting her
on that thing and you want
her to sign up for your club?!
I uh...
I didn't think about it...
It's a good thing
Rin is so talented.
Anyone else could've died.
I'm really sorry, okay?
See ya...
Bye!
Buh-bye...
Later...
She seems kind of
infatuated with you.
What?
In other news...
The GGP has been attacked...
The terrorist group known
as the BMA is responsible...
As evidenced by
the on-site footage,
the terrorists were using
weapons known as RideBacks.
What is it?
You thinking about her?
The rookie daredevil
from yesterday?
Why would I be?
A normal beginner could
never make a jump like that...
Especially on Fuego...
There's no way you're not
the least bit curious.
That's everything
I could find...
Rin Ogata...
She's the daughter
of the late Yuki Ogata,
a world-famous dancer...
Rin started training as
a dancer at the age of three
and she's regarded as a natural
prodigy in the ballet world.
But I doubt you'd have
any interest in Yuki Ogata...
There's no reason she
should mean anything to you.
Where's the other one...?
The Fuego?
R, B, dash Z.
She's a beauty, isn't she...?
Fuego's being repaired.
I had a feeling you'd be back.
Excuse me?
You've got the craving
to ride again, don't you?
No, no, I was just walking by.
You a coward?
A coward?
You can ride again
if you really want to.
But if that is what you want,
then you're gonna
have to race me to do it.
I'll even give you a handicap.
On the off chance that you
win, you'll be able to use
the Rideback whenever
and however you see fit.
But if you lose, well then...
you'll have to
act as my servant.
R B Z...
Lower.
So whadda ya say...?
Do we have a deal,
Miss Ballerina?
I'll do what I can to get
Fuego up and running.
Let's set the place
and time for right here,
next Saturday at
10 in the morning.
And I'll count it as a loss
if you don't show up.
Wait a sec, I didn't
even agree to this.
Her...
Her servant?
What does she think she is?
A British noble?
She said she would
give me a handicap.
I'd be a little concerned...
You are aware that she's the
captain of the RideBack Club,
right...?
Tamayo Kataoka,
junior year French major
with a minor in lit,
currently single.
It's a little odd
that you collect
all this random information...
So...
I wonder why this club leader
chick is challenging a beginner
like you to a race.
Me too.
She must've seen that
amazing jump you made!
If anyone could make her
jealous, it's you...!
I'll show up to cheer you
on but I know for a fact
you're gonna beat her!
Well...
I'm not even sure
I'm gonna do it yet.
Ohhh, is that so?
Uh, yeah.
Sure.
Don't doubt yourself, Rin...!
There's no way
you could possibly lose!
I...
know...
How many times have I
gotta tell you that?
I'll believe that
when you stop skipping class.
I'm in tutoring right now.
Sure you are.
Sounds like tutoring.
Really not the
time for a lecture.
Wait, hold on, Kenji...
You know a lot about
RideBacks, don't you?
About RideBacks, hell yeah!
I practically know
everything there is to know...
Why the sudden interest?
Don't tell me you're thinking
about picking up riding?
What, no.
Actually, one of my friends
was wondering about it,
so I thought I'd ask.
Uh huh...
Wait a minute...
I think you go to the
same school as Tamayo Kataoka.
She was last year's
RideBack champion.
Hey, do me a favor...
Can you try to get her
autograph for me...?
I'll tell you anything
you want if you do.
Okay...
let's see...
Spread Legs Form...
To shift into the high speed
form from the default mode,
apply light pressure
to the left hand lever...
while stepping down
on the right pedal.
Release pressure in order
to lock the form in place.
Hey, girly.
Were you able to get
to the Laundromat in time?
What are you up to?
I'm not up to anything.
About Saturday-
Yeah, I don't think I'm gonna
do that silly little race...
My focus should be on organizing
my schedule and studying,
you know what I mean...?
And we've got better stuff
to do on the weekend anyway.
Nice try, but you can't
hide how fired up you are.
My heart...
never felt like that.
I wonder if she's
actually gonna show up.
Of course she will...!
She'll be here any minute!
Hey, you're Suzuri
if I'm not mistaken...
It looks like you've
come prepared today.
I'm pumped for Rin to win.
I'm cheerleading for her!
Well it's fun
to actually ride them too...
You should try it.
You can ride one
after the race if you want.
Haruki...
What's the status?
We're still waiting on Rin.
She's probably not gonna show.
Analyze.
And, checkpoint number five
is reading clearly.
I'm heading over to set up six
and seven right now, 'kay?
Roger that.
Hey, Rin...!
There you are...!
We've been waiting!
Haruki...
Give her one of
my extra riding suits.
Sure thing, captain.
We ran a thorough diagnostic...
But just in case something
goes wrong on you...
All you've gotta do is press the
stop button on your wristband.
All right.
The rules are simple enough.
Just stick to the main
thoroughfare running
through the university...
Circle the water tower on the
third block and then head back.
You've got a one-lap handicap...
If you finish three laps
before I can complete four,
then I officially lose.
We'll run two preliminary
laps so you're familiar
with the course.
And that's it...
Any objections?
No.
Show me watch you got.
Get to know the track for now.
Remember, you've
got two free laps.
I'm rooting for you, Rin!
You can do it!
Thanks.
Go, Rin, for the win!
It's kind of reckless for
Tamayo to challenge a beginner
like Rin to a race...
But for Rin to
actually accept it...?
Well it's gutsy
to say to the least.
They're really burning rubber.
What's the deal, Captain?
I thought you said
you were gonna take it slow.
That was the plan...
But I'm adjusting
my pace to hers.
Whoa, I can't believe
they're already here.
Am I seeing this?
She's actually keeping
pace with Tamayo!
--Girl's got some crazy skills!
--Go...! Go...! Go, Rin, go...!
Are you sure this is only
her second time riding?
Don't let the pressure
of defeat get you down...
The outcome for this
is already decided...
But you still showed up.
There are some people
in this world...
They simply can't say no
to challenge no matter
how obvious it is
they're gonna lose.
I'm one of them...
You are too.
Wouldn't have shown up
if you weren't,...
I could see it in your eyes
the second you arrived...
The two of us are cut
from the same cloth, Rin.
Wrong...
That's not why I showed up...
I uh...
Honestly, I was curious...
I don't mean for this to sound
rude, but I needed to see
if the national
champion is everything
she's cracked up to be...
And of course...
I need to experience
that feeling.
Is that so...?
It kind of sounds like you
think you're better than me...
Alright then...
I'll give you
a two-lap handicap.
But if I give you
that much leeway...
You and I are gonna
get this race going...
You got it?
Okay!
Captain, hold on a second...
Rin isn't familiar
with the track just yet...
Oh, and I forgot
to mention something...
What's going on here...?
Explain.
That's what I was
about to tell you.
They're transporting stuff
for a construction site...
Looks like its gonna be
another five minutes
or so before
everything's ready.
Maybe you could take
a detour around building eight?
Of course...
Hey, Haruki...
Stop the timer...
We'll restart from the
beginning of the track.
Roger.
So, if I did want to try,
how difficult is it
to pilot a RideBack?
That all depends...
First mode is automatic...
Its easy...
Balancing is a breeze...
In that mode anyway.
But our Rideback ladies
are in manual mode...
Pretty tough for
a beginner to simply stand,
even if they've
got good reflexes.
Wow...
That makes Rin's grand jeté
even more impressive.
What's a grand jeté?
It's a ballet term...
It's a type of
long horizontal jump.
Are you sure this is okay...?
Us riding through here?
That depends on who you ask...
But I say it's fine...
Improvising your own path
is part of the fun
of riding a RideBack.
Hey, Captain!
What are you guys doing...?!
We're gonna get a complaint
from the student council.
Who cares?
Add it to the pile.
Oh, man.
How's it look?
Still no sign of them.
Keep looking...
It should be any second.
They're here!
Here they come!
Annnnnnd...
Begin!
Alright, Rin...!
Go get her...!
Okay, I admit it.
RideBacks are totally cool!
Yeah...
That's what I've been
trying to tell you.
I know, I'm agreeing with you.
Was that Rin who passed by?
Shouko!
So...?
How are things going so far?
Time to get serious about this.
Oh, wow...
She really picked up speed.
That form...
the one on the internet.
Okay.
The speed is amazing.
What...?
How the heck does she know
the Spread Legs Form?
What is that?
The wheels reposition themselves
to the front and back...
The legs spread, which in turn,
lowers the center of gravity.
Higher speeds can be reached,
due to less air resistance,
but controlling turns
becomes a bit of an obstacle.
Haruki...!
Check out their stats!
Uh, why?
I can't believe it...
The newbie's closing in!
Are you intentionally
letting her catch up, Tamayo?
Will you shut up...?
I'm trying to focus.
How is she catching up with me?
Its her second time riding...
Is this talent...?
Alright...
Let's see her handle this!
Why am I not surprised?
That timed out perfectly...
It was bound to
plunge into the lake
while accelerating
on that curve.
She may come off as all
kinds of cute and polite
but that girl's got a
powerful set of fangs on her.
Haruki...
Fuego fell into the lake.
Come and help dredge her out.
You ready for this, Fuego?
Tamayo just passed
the water tower!
Is that all you're
worried about...?
Where's Rin?
Try to keep an eye on the
monitor while I'm gone, okay?
Wait, hold on...
I'm gonna go with you.
Hey...!
She's up and moving!
Oh, wait.
It looks like
she stopped again.
That's right where Tamayo is...
Hey Captain, listen up.
Rin should be
somewhere ahead of you...
Got a visual on her?
Not too shabby, ballerina.
You're a little impressive.
We're resuming the race!
I don't believe it!
So she's okay?
Go, Rin!
She's closing
the gap between them.
I had no idea Fuego
could move that fast!
C'mon...
Just try to pass me.
Neck and neck!
She passed her!
Way to go, Rin!
Idiot...!
You're gonna wipe out
again going that fast!
She's incredible.
Doctor said it's
nothing too major...
She got off with only
a mild concussion.
Well, I guess all we should be
worried about is how she reacts.
Gotta feeling it
isn't gonna be pretty.
Haruki...
Entries are still open, right?
Hey.
How long've you been awake?
Rest easy, I've already
sent in your registration
for the nationals.
We're all set.
Not for me, for her.
You'll need to work on your
skills before we race again...
We're gonna start
the training tomorrow,
so make sure you're prepared.
Okay.
So listen to this...
Suzuri's joining
the club as well.
Apparently she can't stop
thinking about trying it.
You might have something
to do with that.
I wonder...
Do you think
I've made a mistake?
What, of course not.
I gotta admit you looked
pretty cool out there.
They're letting a beginner
like Rin into the Nationals?
What, seriously, for real?!
For really real
they're going to?!
Well, it's not that hard...
You just have to register
on time to get in.
Well that's the
minor sports for you...!
How awesome!
Don't call it minor!