Do we need to take you
to the hospital?
Why did you risk
your life to save me?
It's my fault
you're involved...
Just be quiet and rest.
You made Fuego.
What about the rest
of the Ridebacks...?
Did you make the BMA's too?
Not them!
I dunno what kinda crap he's
been filling your head with...
Kiefer uses any excuse
to justify killing.
I'm starting to think
that some of the things
he's told me might be true.
Rin, listen...
Fuego's one of
my biggest regrets...
The fact I dragged you
into all of this...
I'm sorry.
Romanov Kallenbach...
Just know that
I'm coming for you next.
Call a senior staff meeting!
Shouldn't we worry
about retaliation, Colonel?
Looting or even worse, riots?
Are you criticizing
my decision...?
I'm too busy protecting
them from terrorists
to give a damn what they think.
I want checkpoints on all
main roads before morning...
Counter-Terrorism Squad:
go to Alert Level-Four.
Detain everyone
who resists...!
This terrorist threat
will be wiped out...
Within the month!
We interrupt this program
for a special news report...
The GGP has declared
a State of Emergency,
to be effective immediately...
In addition to a curfew
for all civilians, RideBacks
and other unauthorized
vehicles are to be seized
by local and military police...
Those strongly affected
include RideBack retailers,
who have been
shut down indefinitely,
and ordered to disclose
their clients to the GGP.
SNN's cameras are just now
making it onto the scene,...
but already we're seeing
increased military presence,
with checkpoints bringing
traffic to a halt...
Also... the Japanese Government
was quick to respond,
claiming they received
no advance warning
of the GGP's actions,
which is in violation
of established protocols...
Foreign Affairs Minister
Ogino had this to say...
Emergency...
Tensions continue
to rise as public outcry
spills onto city streets,...
Local police are at their
limits trying to keep
the protests contained...
Several arrests
have already been made,
but the situation is
quickly deteriorating...
Numerous officials are
challenging the legality
of the GGP's
de facto martial law,...
and some fear
it may be the first step
in an outright coup attempt.
The city's going nuts over
this GGP martial law crap...
Where is she?
Upstairs resting.
Now lemme see your arm.
Forget it, I'm fine.
I'm just gonna have to clean
your blood off the floor --
This is bad...
I'm in a forest
engulfed in flames...
The image is so surreal,...
it's like a painted
backdrop on a stage...
Though I feel
the heat on my face...
there's also something
deeper--a spark of life.
And I can't look away
from the flames...
They're so beautiful
to behold...
The light pulsating,
flickering...
dancing.
Fuego...
My deepest regret.
What are you doing?!
Can't stay
in one place too long.
You can stay here...
This is a safe-house
used by politicians...
Even the Chief of Police
doesn't know about it...
No one would
ever look for you--
Make sure the two of you
are ready to bail
at a moment's notice.
You asked for my help...
Where do you think you can go?!
Just keep Rin safe, okay?
I'm gonna make sure
she can get out of here.
You can't...
They've got all those damn
checkpoints everywhere...
You'll be lucky if you
make it to the next district.
Tamayo...
Forgive me.
Don't do anything stupid...
Enough, I refuse to just
sit here and do nothing!
Why's Tamayo calling?
Text from Haruki...
"Rin is somewhere
safe for now"...?
"Her and Tamayo
are trying to lay low"...
That makes me feel
so much better...
"I'll text you again if
I find out anything else."
Rin,...
you're safe...
Oh, thank god!
Got one!
Is this okay...?
Being out in public?
Just securing rations,
then we'll head out.
Took the liberty of contacting
our family attorney.
He's looking into
your brother's case.
Oh wow, thank you...
For everything, really,
you didn't have to do that...
Enough with the sad face.
So last year a bunch of us came
out here on a camping trip...
Everyone was fishin'
n' havin' a blast...!
Douta showed up with hip-waders
and full-on angler gear,
but he never caught a bite!
Hey, look!
Dinner!
I've been
wondering something...
I'm pretty sure you've
never mentioned it to me,
but how did you pickup riding?
Wanted to piss off
my bastard of a father...
Since he was always out with one
of his "lovely lady friends"
I hardly ever saw him...
Needless to say,
growing up I had some
anger management issues...
Birthdays of course,
he was extra generous;
so one year I asked
for an RB-Z, just 'cause
they were impossible to find...
But he did anyway...
Isn't that obnoxious?
Not even a little...
Your father must
have a kind heart.
Yeah!
If he had one.
I didn't even want the damn
thing, but he called my bluff,
so I was stuck with it...
Now I can't imagine
ever living without it...
It's like it's
become a part of me.
When you put it that way,
I can totally understand...
But I've had it all wrong.
In the beginning,
I felt like Fuego was
an extension of myself...
It set me free...
The more I rode it,
the more attached I became...
I practically considered
it a friend...
But then I realized
something...
Fuego was a replacement
for what I'd lost...
A high-tech crutch
for my injured leg...
The feelings I had for
this machine weren't real...
They were part of the fantasy
I created to try and cope.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm through with
Rideback from here on out.
So what are you gonna do...?
Will you try
going back to the ballet?
Not sure yet.
You don't wanna ride
anymore, fine I get it.
But don't think you're getting
out of our arrangement.
You still owe me
a race, Ballerina.
If you can beat me,
I'll allow you to quit...
But... since
that'll never happen,
you'll have to stay
and be our slave!
Guess we'll see.
Please keep Kenji safe.
Guess I can't
give her this now.
Yeah, I owe you big time...
Nah, getting over here
was easy...
Smooth sailing so far...
Hope my luck holds up,
and the GGP don't start
to question these credentials.
Just be careful out there.
The situation could change
at the drop of a hat...
And there's only so much
I can do from over here.
Yeah, yeah...
I know what I'm doin' here.
Where are you...?
You know it's a delicate
time for Dad right now,
and your disappearing act
doesn't help matters!
Sorry, usually when I call you
it's 'cause I need something,
and I didn't want
to stress you out.
So what do you need?
Not a thing, actually...
But Okakura's doing exactly
what you said he would...
Trying to save the day.
He doesn't have much time...
The GGP are going
full-scale tomorrow...
None of you will
be safe anywhere.
I know.
Do one more thing for me...
Give Dad a call...
He's worried about you.
I will, thanks.
You must be Tamayo.
The GGP has finally
crossed a line...!
You're just making things
worse, so go home!
As protests escalate...
The GGP has ordered the
temporary seizure of
all RideBack vehicles, in order
to prevent terrorist use...
Owners of--
This sucks...!
Way things are goin',...
They could bust down
the door any second.
They can't just come
and take them, right?
I wouldn't be surprised
if they locked us out...
They can't...!
It would break Rin's
heart if she sees that
when she comes back!
They're a corrupt
military dictatorship...
I hear ya,...
but what are we
supposed to do?
I don't know, but there
has to be something!
Shouko, you with me?!
Well, to be honest...
I don't think it would be such
a bad idea if we quit now...
Things keep getting worse,
at this rate
someone could get hurt.
If Rin was here...
I know she would
agree with me.
Well, I'll fight back!
I dunno about
the rest of you,...
but these babies
mean the world to me...
None of us
would've ever met...
If it wasn't for Ridebacks.
The GGP can spout off
on how they're being used
by terrorists and
all that mumbo jumbo...
But I can't sit back and
let them take away my ride.
Glad you're optimistic...
That makes one of us.
I didn't expect
to see you again so soon...
Well, "dead man?"...
To what do I owe the
pleasure of your company?
I'm here
to make you an offer.
Who is this?
It's me.
Well if it isn't my horrible
ingrate of a daughter...
I'm assuming your brother
put you up to this.
Tamayo...?
Tamayo, Are you here?!
Tamayo?
Why don't you tell me what
this is really about, sweetie?
I can't...
It'll just make
trouble for you.
Um...
So, yeah.
Is that what
you're worried about...?
If there's one thing I've
learned, it's that children
are supposed to cause trouble
for their parents...
Tell me what you need.
I'll move the Earth
to do what I can for you.
Thanks, Dad...
Love you.
What's the RB-Z doing here?
Fuego?
Why is it here?
Is...
she gone...?
Took her apart,
and threw her away.
So you weren't
disassembled after all...
I'm so glad.
Goodbye, Fuego...
I'm sorry.
Okay, open 'er up!
Look at that...
Instant army.
In other news...
Mounting tension,...
a series of nationwide protests
are set to take place,
opposing the GGP's
counter-terrorism methods.
Thousands of local
police officers will be...
This is just what Kallenbach
needs, more fuel for the fire.
Previous rallies have
remained non-violent,
but the sheer number --
Looks like the demonstration
starts with a march...
from Hiigata all the way down
to the Earthquake Memorial.
As of right now,
there are gonna be
at least ten Ridebackers
participating.
Whoa!
That's a lot more
people than I thought!
Haruki!
We got company.
Uh, your friend Tamayo
asked me to swing by...
Special delivery for ya.
Oil?
Suh-weet...
This stuff's not easy
to find these days.
Hang on--there's a letter...
Let's see...
"Hey guys, last time I
checked, the club's stock
of mixed-base
was running low...
So here's a small present...
to show you all I miss you.
"But I'm not the only one.
There's also a little
something to show you
our other AWOL member is okay.
Yeah, 'bout that part...
She also sent this for ya.
C'mon, hurry,
load it already!
Rin!
Thank god, it looks
like she's okay!
Yeah...
Shouko, don't...
Cryyyy!
Yo, long time no see...!
I guess I never did explain
the whole machine gun thing
from before...
Old news.
Well, it's still relevant...!
It was a metaphor about
our upside-down world...
And how we, as a club, survive.
Got another metaphor explaining
hybrids and full electrics.