It's really tall...!
I thought it'd be scarier!
Took me all night to put
her back together, so try...
--This is so cool!
--Stop being a spaz up there...!
Kay?
Hey, Haruki.
What does it mean
to be "in regulation?"
Oh!
It means a ride's
been cleared for use
in a sanctioned race
or tournament.
Keeps it about skill,
instead of who's got the
money for the sickest mods.
That's why I can't use Fuego.
Right...
Fuego may look like your
typical off-the-lot RideBack,
but Okakura tricked the hell out
of its insides, top to bottom.
The frame's legit,
but the guts are way too leet.
Sorry.
What a shame...
Don't sweat it...
Balon's a new model from the
same design team responsible
for Fuego and all the
controls are the same,
so you shouldn't
run into any problems.
Help!
I'm still getting
the hang of it.
Geez, Suzuri!
Don't treat it like
a mechanical bull...!
I'm sorry!
Whenever you two
are done flirting,
maybe somebody
could give me a hand?!
--Okay...
Wishing it were race-legal?
What's in here?
Think of it as
a little graduation present.
I pushed you pretty hard
these last two weeks,
but you made it
through boot camp...
I think you're gonna
hold your own out there.
Thanks a lot for training me.
Don't get all mushy on me...
I've a score
to settle with you.
Our top story:...
Colonel Romanov Kallenbach,
the soon to be
commander of the GGP,...
has arrived at the
Yokota Military Base.
Following his inauguration next
week, he will assume the title
of Supreme Commander,
in keeping with the...
Look...!
it's the RB-Z!
Dude, no wonder it's Junkoku's
flagship model--that's
a sweet-ass ride...!
How'd she get
her hands on one?
Kataoka's the one to beat,
just like last year...
Move it!
Dumbass!
Try accelerating, ya amateur!
The pre-race briefing
is about to start, sir.
Fine.
This is All-Out Hurricane,
the special FM broadcast
coming at ya from the big
RideBack tournament in Kanto!
Greetings to all
you riders out there!
Now, before we get into
the afternoon's events,
I just wanna
put out a disclaimer.
A disclaimer?
Hey, Shouko...!
We're over here!
Hey...
I hope you're hungry!
Heavenly!
Thanks for hooking us
up like this.
No biggie, it was nothing.
This is like some kind
of festival or something.
Everybody's pretty
stoked about it...
This kind of thing
only happens once a year...
Most of the teams out here
are just looking to have
a good time, but as
the defending champs,
we gotta make sure
our rep stays in tact.
Where's Rin?
Tamayo and her
are doing a practice run.
Hey, speak of the devil.
...And we're excited as all hell
to be here with you today!
This might come as actual news
to those of you listening in
at home, but let me state the
obvious to anybody who's...
What was all that about...?
You weren't even
trying out there.
I couldn't get it to
turn like I wanted...
Its weird, but it kinda
felt like I was being
pulled by the handlebars.
I don't know how
to explain it...
Haruki...
Balon's LSD settings
need a boost about now.
While you're at it...
Check her absorbers, see if
you can do her any favors
on those sharp left turns.
Wait a sec...!
Prelims are two hours
from now...!
How am I gonna finish that?!
She might as well
go home if you don't.
She felt like the
handlebars pulled her.
Whaddya think...?
Will you win
two years in a row?
I came here to win
this thing, end of story.
What's Dad say?
This is about me, not him.
Hey, you guys, is Tamayo's dad,
like, famous or something?
Come on, he's only
the Minister of Finance
and of Foreign Affairs...
Nanpuu Kataoka's
a real big shot...
He's like an uber-politician.
You never saw him on TV?
Oh!
You mean the guy
who's all corrupted!
Quiet!
That's not all--her brother is
some hot-shot with the police.
Kataoka, I assume you
met the new commander
at the GGP training summit?
The job has its perks,
I suppose.
Rumor has it he led
the RideBack battalion
during the war.
From what I've heard,
he took part in
the Battle of
Arizona--after that fight,
the GGP were unstoppable.
No records to
substantiate it, though...
The Colonel's a mysterious one.
"Suspicious" is more like it.
Gentlemen...
If you'll follow me...
Shall we pay our respects
to the new Commander?
All right!
The preliminary race to
determine the starting grid
is underway!
The most difficult leg will
be the stretch through
the mountains.
If you look at the roster...
Nothing's wrong
with its settings...
Is Fuego the only
reason she's good?
There she is!
Knock 'em dead, girl!
Go Rin!
Why's she still
going so slow?
Maybe she's, you know,
saving it for later on.
Oh, you're the expert?
This is only
her first race ever.
Just her being out there
is pretty amazing.
I mean, no disrespect,
but this isn't exactly
an event for noobs.
I figured Rin would be fast no
matter what model she was on,
but I guess RideBacks are more
different than I thought...
Nope!
If the settings match up, might
as well be the same machine.
Yeah, but...
If I'm not mistaken,
Fuego does have a few quirks...
Maybe Rin's just having trouble
adjusting to Balon's settings.
I doubt it, she's just
a noob--end of story.
Nah, I think I might
be onto something here...
Tamayo's never been a
big fan of Fuego--says
the handling is crappy...
But somehow,
Rin doesn't have a problem...
Don't you think that's odd?
Yeah, I guess so.
I'm doing horribly.
What's holding me back...?
I don't get it...
I wish I had Fuego...
Damn, Bro--these amateurs
need to quit screwing around!
Hey bitch!
You're gonna pay for that!
You mess with my protégé,
you mess with me.
Winner of the prelims, the
RideBack Princess herself,
Tamayo Kataoka!
No surprise...
First in the
prelims--pretty good!
That's awesome!
Yay us!
What the heck's going on
with Fuego's ACS settings?
This is one funky matrix...
Looks like it's been disabled.
Why would Okakura jury-rig
it all weird like that?
Haruki, whatever you're messing
around with, it can wait...
Listen up, I need you to set
the fork back the way it was...
And I'm losing speed
when I shift into third,
so fix that crap, pronto!
You just took first in the
prelims--what exactly
are you worried about?
Earn those pastries, gearhead.
Oh, and Rin's issues
with Balon...
I have an idea...
it's kinda risky...
All or nothing, huh?
Well then,
what are you waiting for?
Gotcha!
Good job, you.
Only 16 people beat you.
Thanks, you guys.
Ten minutes 'til
showtime, Haruki...!
Just one more
change I gotta make...
Is Rin gonna be okay...?
She's been sitting over
there, all by herself...
She's just getting herself
into the zone is all.
That's her focused face...
I know Rin Ogata better than
anyone and she's no quitter...
Trust me, she's fine.
Well, it's almost time for
the All-Japan RideBack
Championship Race to begin!
CS Motor Channel will provide
coverage of the event,
with editor-in-chief
of RideBack Magazine,
Mr. Suzuki, as commentator.
Good afternoon!
Thanks for having me
up in the booth with you.
Hey, it's our pleasure...
To make a long story, less...
long...
I pulled out Balon's
ride-assist module,
better known by gearheads
as an ACS System.
"Ride-assist?"
Fuego's got one, too.
They're pretty standard.
Ready for the crazy part...?
Fuego's never
actually kicked in...
You should get a smoother ride
without Balon's ride-assist...
Sounds simply enough...
Don't you think?
Take it easy those
first couple minutes, okay?
Good luck out there!
Thanks.
We're getting closer
to the start of
the All-Japan RideBack
Championship Race.
It's anybody's game,
but still you gotta wonder:
Will Kataoka take home the
trophy like she did last year,
or will her bitter rivals,
Team Cobra, stand in her way?
Catch me if I faint...!
Rin!
Kick some tail!
Seriously...
tweaking her
RideBack is dangerous.
I know, man...
This is pretty risky.
But, hey...
Rin's got the goods
to pull this off.
If anyone can do it,
my money's on her.
We're all just moment away from
the All-Japan Championship Race!
Damn, that chick
was on to us, Bro!
That chick is
smarter than you!
Nice, Tamayo's
past curve number one.
Where's Rin?
Oh no...
she's way back.
Benjamin Franklin...
Inventor and Founding Father...
And, first US ambassador...
He went to France to try
and drum up support
for the American Revolution.
That's a nice start...!
Care to continue, Mr. Ogata?
Huh?! Sure thing!
Ohh...
What page are we on, again?
It's been a long time...
Welcome to Japan, sir.
The tournament's defending champ
Kataoka is taking the lead,
followed by Team Cobra--Takeshi
and his younger brother
Hiroshi, who had to settle for
second and third last year.
We're looking at
a field of 22 riders.
Nobody DQed in the
prelims, so the battle
for first place will
undoubtedly be a tough one.
Sweet, the RB-Z
is still in first place.
How 'bout Balon?
Back in...
second-to-last place.
You think she's
going to be all right?
Show 'em whatcha got--c'mon!
Wait! She moved up!
The mountain trail and field
tracks are clear and ready...
Number 710 is leading
the pack onto the mountain.
Rin just moved up
another spot!
She's looking good
out there...!
Real good!
It's still messy
on the curves...
But at least I'm
calling the shots now...
The white RideBacks are just
beyond the horizon--does
that worry you?
My own opinion is irrelevant.
All I want...
is enough information...
to make a decision
regarding their practicality.
You're very circumspect.
My predecessor made the
mistake of letting you
run him around in
polite little circles.
So here I am.
My country has accepted
this new world of ours.
We don't need
enforcement RideBacks.
But that isn't the
situation here--here,
terrorists use RideBacks and
attack their targets unopposed.
Seems they're very effective
weapons in little,
crowded nations.
We have very effective weaponry
at our disposal, too, sir.
You prefer a tank
on every corner,
right next to the police box?
How picturesque.
No, that's not what I meant...
I just simply don't see how some
glorified motorcycle with arms
is going to single-handedly
bring terrorism
to a grinding halt.
I'm starting to see why the
Japanese are thought of
as a stubborn people...
I had a Japanese guy
in my old unit.
He was nothing on two legs.
But on a RideBack,
he was a hero...
Tamayo Kataoka is speeding onto
the field track just ahead
of the Cobra Brothers--they're
hissing at her heels!
Say your prayers, Kataoka...!
I'm gonna beat you
no matter what!
Persistent, aren't we?
It looks like one of the
riders is working their way
through the pack, from last
place--it's Number 711,
a newcomer to the
All-Japan tournament!
Why are they
driving so reckless?!
Not cool!
Wait, something
isn't right here.
Awesome!
She's almost
into the top ten!
Attagirl!
That's weird, he should
be officiating the race...
Hey, boss man...
You removed Balon's ACS system.
So you noticed that,
did ya...?
It's not against the rule
or anything, what's the harm?
Her driving is spooking
the other riders...
Pull her out
of the race right now.
Say what?
Come on, she's up to
eleventh place--I can't just--!
Are you trying
to fight me on this?
Uh, no sir!
I'll get the ball rolling
soon as we hang up--...
Oh, crap!
What happened?
I may have forgotten to tell her
how to read the sign boards.
Bring her in, you idiot!
Hey, is something wrong?
Straight from Okakura...
He thinks Balon might be
too much of a liability.
What do you mean?
He figured out that
I disabled the ACS system.
ACS system?
What's that do?
Basically, it keeps the
rider from falling over
when they make a mistake.
A foolproof of sorts
if you will.
Deactivating the ACS
is bit of gamble...
One wrong move,
and down ya go.
"Down ya go?!" She's gonna
hurt herself out there!
A week ago,
you'd probably be right.
But she's gotten
pretty good on a Rideback...
This could just be me,
but I think Rin's reflexes
are actually better
than the ACS system's...
To put it simply,
she's like a human upgrade.
I know all this sounds crazy,
but look at what
she's doing out there.
The real action seems
to be further back a ways...
It's that rookie
you were mentioning earlier...!
I'm in control...!
She's catching up at speeds
that're out of this world...!
Her speed is picking up
with each lap...
About time she made it back
into the competition.
Number 711 is back
from the dead,
zipping past
everybody in one shot!
Go, girl!
Be careful...!
"The breaking into this money
of Vernon's was one of
the first great
errata of my life..."
Wow!
My jaw's on the floor, here!
This rookie is flying past the
opposition at breakneck speeds!
The announcer's going
crazy about something...
Wish I could watch...!
Finally got your
engine revved, Rin?
I'm out, Bro!
It's all you, nooow!
Peace out.
I'll win this for both of--
That's it!
Your ass is mine!
Those snake brothers
are a buncha meanies!
I say let's
push for a red-card.
Naaah,...
I'll bet the marshals
were watching as it went down.
We just gotta make sure
Tamayo doesn't murder
those fools after
the race, y'know?
One of the Cobra Brothers
takes the lead here
in the home stretch, but
Kataoka's in hot pursuit!
I caught you.
Waiting for an
invitation, ballerina?
Hey, um...
I know you told me
what to read...
Long as I got a sec...
...is not Kataoka,
but some rookie!
Meet Number 711,
a new darling for a new day!
The RideBack Princess
is dead--long live
the RideBack Princess!
Consider yourself doomed,...
Mr. Ogata.
Oh... I do, sir...!
Rin's all the way up to fourth!
The suspense is killing me!
Almost there...
Balon's good enough...
but she's still no Fuego.
Sooo, are we gonna
show her this sign or what?
Oh, come on,
it's the final lap.
Huh?
Wonder who that could be.
She seems to be
running fine, so I--
You hear that sound
Balon's exhaust is making?
Huh?
She burned out the engine.
You're paying for the new one.
No!
After Ogata comes from behind
to practically win it all,
--Fortune steps out on her!
--Adios, engine.
Always a damn shame to see
a good engine give out.
She was mounting a comeback
for the record books,
but Ogata won't be seeing
the checkered flag today!
Better luck next time!
Looks like Rin demands more
out of a Rideback
than Balon can provide.
This race is gonna come down
to its final turn, people!
Sorry, Rin...
Guess we'll have
to settle this next year.
I'm sorry...
According to our records,
no Japanese citizen
ever enlisted in
the GGP's RideBack
force... Not a one.
Right...
Not even a rumor.
But, there's a man
who fits the bill.
The Public Safety Force
has been keeping an eye
on him at the GGP's request.
He was gone during the war.
And wouldn't you know it,
he's a RideBack enthusiast.
Cheers!
Tamayo, it was soooooo
cool the way you spanked
those Cobra Brothers...!
It's like you were
a big ol' mongoose!
When I grow up,
I wanna be like you!
All right...
which of you got her drunk?
Nobody did.
She isn't old enough.
All we gave her was a
little bit of orange juice.
Oh man!
How come Balon had to
go an' break down
like that right
at the end, huh?!
What'd she do get
plastered off the smell...?
Hold on,...
Where did Rin go?
She's out with Fuego.
Wanted to take her for a ride.
So, what's up?
Sorry...
About breaking Balon.
That was the
engineer's fault...
not yours.
Can I ask you something?
When Fuego malfunctioned
that day,...
Why did you go for the jump
when you could have just
slammed on the brakes?
I got scared when I saw
the edge coming up...
But still...
Somehow I knew I could
trust Fuego with my life.
I'll come back after
I've ridden a little more.
Hey Okakura, I just got the
repair bill for Balon.
The new engine's gonna be
really little pricey.
And I don't I have the cash.
Huh?
Wait, you were asleep? Your face
never changes!