...are endorsing ratification
of a new domestic
counter-terrorism unit...
The so-called "White Riders" are
to be operated by local police,
but under strict
guidance from the GGP...
When this might go into effect
is still under some debate...
Your thoughts, Mr. Suzuki?
Terrorists have an incredible
advantage because of
their work with Ridebacks...
Some say this move is not only
logical, but overdue...
The question I'm
forced to ask, however,
is how much of a deterrent
will this really be?
You're crazy to be working
in this kind of heat.
I told you, club's
suspended indefinitely.
Yeah, well, I guess I just
don't listen too good...
But of course,
you already knew that.
Can you expand on that a bit?
Unlike typical police
vehicles, the White Riders
are armored and equipped
with high-caliber firearms...
My concern...
is that police forces are slowly
becoming small military units.
Interesting.
When I rode that thing
I had no control over it...
But the "Swan Princess" did...
How is it I can't drive it
but a newbie like Rin can...?
What is Fuego--really?
You don't need to know
the answer to that question...
It doesn't concern you.
The hell it doesn't...!
By bringing it here, you made
it the whole club's concern!
At this point,
I have a right to know.
What...?
Whaddaya mean you're
"not coming in"?!
Did you forget
our deadline today?
The Yakuza piece?
Sorry...
I gotta check somethin'
in Toranomon...
Close up the office;
the editor can bitch
to the answering service.
Your funeral...
Oh!
I found some info
you're gonna love!
On what?
Our mystery
"RideBack Girl"...
Goes to the same school
as Tamayo Kataoka.
And she's got a name...
Rin Ogata.
Long, straight dark hair...
Oh yeah, it's her...
Dark hair...?
I mean, I been staring at that
footage of her for days ...
So now what...?
Maybe you're when done there,
we should try callin'
the university and
see if-- Uh- hello?
Guess I better pay
the young lady a visit.
Looks like Kenji
won't be joining us.
Hey, Kenji...!
You here?
Oh, man...
What is all of this?
Hey, RideBack...
When did Kenji get all these?
That jerk.
What could he possibly be
doing that's so important?
Well, he was only ten years old
when your mother passed away...
To lose her
at such a young age-
I suppose it affected
him differently.
Even so...
He should come
visit her grave with us.
He's going to do
what he's going to do...
Hard to believe it's been
six whole years, isn't it?
So...
Are you getting involved
with any campus activities?
I guess I've found
a couple of things I like...
Nothing too serious...
I even found this one club
that I'm really enjoying.
I'm so glad...
It's good that you're
finding new things
to focus your talents on.
It's wonderful, actually.
So, Rin...
how's dorm life treating you?
Are you and Shouko still
getting along all right?
Yeah, we are...
In fact, we're supposed
to meet up later.
Whoa!
Badass!
Hell yeah!
Hey, where did you get 'em?
I don't see how that's
any of your business.
Let's just say
they fell off...
a boat somewhere.
Best you don't know more.
We can take all of them?
I tell you what...
Make a nice big mess tonight.
Tell me something champ...
You ain't afraid
of the police, are ya?
Good, 'cause here's
a little bonus...
What are they?
Military-grade smoke flares.
BMA use 'em, too...
You can figure out
how they work.
Now go an' raise some hell.
Wh--...
Whoa!
Holy crap, this is Gremlin's
like, brand-newest model...
Not bad for a Luxury--
There's no manufacturer badge...
Was this thing smuggled out of
the freakin' factory?
I don't wanna sound
like a lamoid,
but doesn't this seem
kinda dangerous to you?
You trust me, don't you?
Yeah, but...
Shut up 'n show me
how to ride this thing.
That's a Dumont
Co E-W Band!
Suh-weet!
Hey...
Yeah, four of 'em,
just like ya wanted...
We'll set 'em loose
later tonight.
Of the three
escaped RideBackers,...
we've identified two...
First is Abraham Ronstadt...
Former Special Ops
with the U.S. Army...
No name yet on the second...
But he is South African
and served in the
French Foreign Legion.
Unfortunately, the third was not
found in any of our databases,
so we don't have much...
We have obtained
footage of him,
taken just after
he launched the rocket...
And a closer look...
Facial analysis tells us he's
Caucasian of European descent...
Due to his ability to fire
a shoulder-mounted rocket
from such an
unstable vehicle,...
we believe him to be a highly
trained soldier or mercenary.
Given the large number
of combat professionals
we've identified
within their ranks...
Gentlemen, I strongly
believe at this point...
It's safe to say the BMA
radicals have evolved...
From a terrorist cell...
To a full-fledged militia.
We should not be surprised
to see them attempt
more and more
larger-scale attacks.
Therefore, my intelligence
staff hereby recommends
the immediate implementation
of the White Rider program
in police departments
nationwide,.
For the protection
of our cities,
and the preservation
of public safety.
Hey, sorry I'm late...!
I missed the bus,
can you believe it?
Sorry I made you come
all the way out here...
Every so often, I just have the
urge to get away from it all.
Yeah...
I get those feelings
too sometimes.
Hey, Shouko...
Do you remember...?
Last year after
the school festival,...
the fireworks?
Mm hm...
We were making
so much noise,...
the police came out...
Gave us all warnings...
Then we all ran--just
scattered!
In all the craziness,
you and I got separated...
I was so scared!
I walked up and down
that pitch black beach
calling out for you, "Shouko!
Shouko!"...
But all I heard back
was the waves...
God, I was so relieved
when I finally found you...
I'm glad you looked for me too,
instead of running home!
I hugged you so tight and
we couldn't stop crying...
Even with all
the chaos and tears...
It's still worth
remembering, isn't it?
Rin...
You're the most talented
dancer I've ever seen,
but when it comes to
acting you really suck.
I know what you're doing...
Okay, I was pretty freaked
out for while there,
who wouldn't be...?
But I'm fine now...
Really.
Its just...
I know how you feel
about big crowds
and everything right now...
Honestly,I can't say I blame you
after all that's happened...
Maybe if I had taken
the time to think it over,
you might not have
gotten so traumatized.
You rescued me...
'Kay?
Shouko...
Aw, man...
The bus is gonna
be here any second now...
You comin'?
Yeah, no...
I think I'll
catch the next one.
Alright then, girlie...
Guess I'll catch up
with ya later.
Gimme a call
or something tomorrow!
There you are...
Dude!
I am freakin' lovin' this!
Listen to that baby purr!
All right...!
Rev 'em up, boys!
Let's roll!
Yeah!
You're Rin Ogata, right?
I dropped by your club the
other day, you remember me?
I don't suppose I could
trouble you for a moment
of your time...?
Not right now.
Sorry, I have
somewhere I need to be.
Please don't go...
Is that a motorcycle gang...?
On Ridebacks?
Kenji?!
Need a lift?
Damn kids,
someone could get hurt!
You stupid punk!
Yeah, tear it up!
Take this!
Kizaki...
Aren't we taking it
a bit far?
Relax, kid!
This is what we're here for,
try not to be a little pansy!
Attention RideBacker!
Pull the vehicle over and stop
the engine, immediately!
Yeah...
That'll happen.
Whoopsie.
That was a cop car!
We're sorry, the number
you are trying to reach--
Kenji...
What have you
gotten yourself into?
I guess delinquency
is an Ogata family trait.
Just kidding.
Seriously?
They're messing
with the police?
Well, Good Evening,
Officers...!
Is there something
going on up ahead?
Sorry, ma'am.
Road's closed
from this point.
You'll have to go around.
Interesting, I'm a journalist
and I just happened to notice
the smoke as I drove by...
I'll need to see your driver's
license please, ma'am.
I'm sorry, your
passenger can't be here
without the proper
press credentials.
GGP?
You hear me?
Yes, that's fine...
Thank you, gentlemen!
I think I've stumbled
onto a big scoop...
Hang on...
This might get rough.
They're currently
on Forty-Seventh Street...
Moving from the Inamura District
to the reclaimed land area.
You both know that vandalism
and traffic violations
aren't justification
for deadly force.
Ah, come on...
They'll trump up
some worse charges later,...
right?
Uh, something like that...
Damn...
These GGP bastards, thinkin'
they own anything and everyone!
They've been diverted
to the closed-off area.
Two units standing by.
Colonel...
The combat operations test
will be starting shortly...
Would you like to join us
in the briefing room?
Thank you, no...
You seem to have a handle on it;
I'll watch the feed in here.
Shall I report in
to the home office?
That won't be necessary...
He's a "terrorist" now...
When we find him, we just
get to kill him again.
Man, those cops were nothin'!
What the holy hell
is happening?!
No way...
Those are White Riders!
No...!
Suck on this!
Damn...!
It was all a set up!
This is bad!
Yeah, ya think?!
Gun it!
Kizaki!
Kenji!
White Riders...?
But they're not supposed
to be on the streets yet...!
What the--?
Damn it!
uh...
I give up!
What the hell did a
biker gang ever do
to deserve this brutality?!
Damn iiit!
Why is this happening?!
Gimme a break!
Oh, crap! Oh, crap! Oh, Crap!
Hey wait!
Kenji!
Oh, god...
What're you, nuts...?!
Get back here!
Come on...!
It started!
Rin Ogata...?
What is she doing there?
This female rider...
She's the terrorist
from the BMA incident...
Do not hold back.
This is turning into
quite the field test.
Run, Rin.
Kenji!
She dodged them again!
That's insane...!
No one can do that!
Go...
Leave me...
Kenji...
She's the RideBack Girl...
I knew it.
Stay where you are...!
Turn off the engine,...
then put your hands
where we can see 'em,
and slowly
dismount the RideBack!
Now...!
I repeat:...
Disengage the engine...
and step away from
the vehicle at once!
She's busted!
Nabbed!
Sent Up the river...!
What do we do now?!
Haruki!
Have you ever wondered
if its truly possible...?
Will the meek inherit
the planet they inhabit...?
Can we fight those
who govern us?
We broke Haruki...!
And, scene!