I know you...
So we meet again.
You might want to jump.
That's a Type-L Fuego...?
When were you chosen?
Good luck.
You don't look happy...
Do you prefer
the company of the GGP?
How should I look?
You're a stranger to me.
Sorry--my name is Kiefer...
I suppose I'm a terrorist.
And who is Rin Ogata?
You're the girl who
danced through the blockade...
The same girl who toppled
the fearsome White Riders
like so many dominos...
You make it sound so bad...
Both times I was just trying
to save someone close to me.
No, you weren't.
Sitting atop Fuego, your
intentions dissolve like smoke.
As you bask in
the light of the elect,
you shed the
obligations that bind you.
How would you know
what's going on in my head?
Because I, too, have known
the bliss of that light.
You're not a prisoner here.
He'll be coming
for you soon enough...
'Til then,
make yourself at home.
Huh...?
A trivial conflict
in one of those places
you can barely
find on the map...
That's all we thought it was.
Ten years later, we know
it was the end of one world
and the beginning of another.
The GGP started off
as a tiny band of rebels,
striking out at a common foe:
the world's policeman,
who wanted to trade
in its badge for a crown.
They had awakened a sleeping
giant--one that could
crush it with ease.
But if the Battle of
Arizona proved anything,
it's that
fortune favors the brave.
The ICBM base was the symbol
of the western empire's
global dominance.
It housed the most destructive
of their weaponry,.
so it was built
to be invincible.
But a squad of RideBacks,
designed by the brilliant
Killy McCannon,
threw themselves at it
in a daring surprise attack.
Romanov Kallenbach
led the assault.
The GGP left
the base in ruins...
and proceeded to fill the
very void in global politics
they themselves had created.
But victory came at a price...
Half of the GGP
were killed in action,
as was Professor McCannon--
who'd been imprisoned
within the base.
Later on, several GGP officers
were court-martialed
for human-rights violations
against prisoners of war.
The most important
battle of our time,
and nobody knows
quite what happened...
Victors write
the history books,.
or leave them blank.
Rin Ogata's Rideback Club was
started by Tenshirou Okakura...
And back in day he was
tight with Kallenbach,
our new supreme commander.
RideBacks have helped
to shape each man's destiny...
And Hesner Incorporated
makes the RideBacks...
the White Rider models,
at least...
Dig my little party-favors?.
I think our guests
are gonna have a blast.
The GGP comes stormin' in
and you blow 'em up...?
And if they call in
an airstrike, what then?
They won't.
Kallenbach wants you
too much to let that happen.
He wants is my dead body...
Kiefer's, too--never mind how.
Yeah, that's what
I keep hearing...
You can uncuff him.
The little lady's at a mansion
five kliks northwest of here...
I'd get up there
pretty quick if I were you.
We gotta make sure to give
the GGP a warm welcome.
It's like riding a bike.
You get rusty,
but ya don't forget how.
The target vehicle
remains stationary, sir.
What do you advise?
Establish a five-k perimeter.
No one gets in or out.
Bravo Team,
move to the target's six.
We're at an
abandoned weather station.
An airstrike'll flatten it
easily, Colonel.
Permission to fire?
I want them to feel the heat
before we snuff 'em out.
Permission denied.
Understood.
Sir, we lost the Strike team!
Incoming transmission, sir!
Bravo Team had a visual
on our suspected targets...
but they lost them.
Initiate a
door-to-door search--
they didn't
just vanish, dammit...!
All others, regroup
and prepare to mobilize!
Gatobu!
Your RideBack battalion
will lead the charge!
Yes sir!
We gotta stop
meeting like this.
Who'dve thought a war hero would
end up stuck in acadeemia,
poor Goblin...
I was hoping we could have
a nicer chat this time...
Perhaps about Rin Ogata
and Mr. Okakura.
She was just trying
to protect her brother,
but they got her
for assaulting an officer...
Man, if only I hadn't
given her a ride that night...
she wouldn't have gotten mixed
up in all this crazy crap...
I can't help, but feel
like it's all my fault.
'Kay, but...
you still haven't said how
this ties in with Okakura.
Well, it turns out your club
advisor fought alongside
the supreme commander
of the GGP during the war.
You kidding me?
I don't know what transpired
between the two of them,
but the honeymoon
is definitely over...
I think Okakura's in danger.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I think we can
clear your friend's name...
I dug up some juicy info, but
without proof it's worthless.
The kind of proof you
can never track down
unless you're really
well-connected...
Like you are.
All right.
But in exchange,
there's a little something
you're gonna do for me.
Behold the Black Knights.
They're standard issue
within the BMA...
Care to try one?
My interest is riding,
not preparing for war.
The day of the blockade,
you told me Fuego was special.
How is she special?!
I need to know
what you're talking about!
You know what I mean,
more than anybody else...
Enough of this charade.
"Charade?" No!
Look, I'm telling you the truth
when I say I don't understand-
It is a moment of rare
and sublime beauty
when rider and machine
achieve perfect harmony.
Your heart takes flight.
The chosen few can live and die
a life complete in that moment.
Rin...
There's something I want you
to remember, sweetie.
For people like us, honey,
the stage is our one true home.
It's our entire world...
There we live
our life complete.
"Life complete?"
"Life... complete... "
You were chosen by Fuego...
Accepted, Rin...
Blessed.
Her creator
chose you, as well.
He chose the both of us...
The man you call Okakura,
I call Goblin.
He's on his way here as we
speak, but until his arrival...
I've many things to show you.
Why is the army mobilizing?!
Well, the GGP's
up to something--
that's for damn sure...!
We just received
word the highways
have been closed off...!
--What do I tell these guys?
--No! No comment, dammit!
Mr. Kataoka?
I think you have a visitor.
My sister told me you'd come.
Pardon me, but...
I should be getting
back out into the chaos.
This just in: The GGP
has ordered the closure
of National Highway 20.
Listen to what I've got to say,
I promise it'll be worth it.
"Dual Arrows?"
It's a special
RideBack operating system...
Once you execute
a particular move,
the machine learns
to anticipate it.
Goblin invented this
OS, and in doing so,
he breathed new life into
Fuego and the Black Knights.
Such a RideBack chooses its own
master, and with good reason.
Only a skilled rider will
possess instincts strong enough
for the machine to predict.
Those who lack faith in
themselves are not worthy.
Their chaos is
a danger to them both.
I guess that makes sense.
I've synced up your EW-Band
with this Black-Knight.
Breathe life and grace
into this cold metal...
Lend it your sublimity...
Experience perfection.
Take the reins,
Rin Ogata...!
All that strength
hidden within you...
Set it ablaze!
Ride with me!
Kiefer, we're mobilizing.
I understand...
On my way.
You stay here.
He'll be along
for you shortly.
This is all the ammo we've
got--shoot 'til you're empty!
There are 15--repeat,
one five--enemy RideBacks,
and those are just the ones
we've seen so far...!
No worse than what we expected.
You invite me over, then
take off before I get there?
Typical Kiefer.
You took your
sweet time, Goblin...
Your damsel in distress
is getting bored.
Where is she, dammit?
Care for a fight, Goblin?.
I can make the time.
Goblin is a dead man.
Quite right...
So am I.
Kallenbach would be, too,
if the world were fair.
She's waiting
in the rear courtyard.
You can take the RideBack.
See ya.
Get in there--let's
finish them off!
Booby-traps!
They've set
landmines everywhere!
A black RideBack
put down all of Unit Two!
Gatobu?
I'm on it!
You gonna fight me or what?
Rin...
No response, sir--the
signal's dead!
That's enough.
Send in the Apaches
and level the place.
Is that wise, Colonel?
Huh?
Beg pardon?
May I remind you,
we're cleaning up the
Intelligence Bureau's mess...
Now be a good girl
and shut your mouth.
Sir, it's Lieutenant Gatobu.
Patch him through.
What the...?
Romanov Kallenbach...
Kiefer...
Congratulations
on your promotion.
Oh, and thanks--tearing that
pathetic RideBack squad
of yours to shreds
was a pleasant diversion...
Though I imagine their
widows and children
might have a different opinion.
You want me dead, Romanov.
I can appreciate that.
For what it's worth,
the feeling is mutual.
Do you really think
you can best me...?
You cowering Kallenbach?
Just know that
I'm coming for you next.
The BMA's fierce--let's
call 'em "buma"!
Yeah...
I think the word
you're looking for is "puma"...
We'll "bear" with the GGP
while they "skunk" 'em out.
Who doesn't love a pun...?
Been lookin' for a chance
to use those haven'tcha?
Yeah.