[WHIRRING]
So are you ready to
die, Lupin III?
No, but do you care to hear
what I am ready for tonight?
Ready to beg for mercy?
The sweet young thing
I’m taking to bed.
Hm?
Oh, shut it.
[GUN SHOOTING]
Is that all you got?
Huh?
Emmy.
It’s time to go, Emmy.
It’s Ami.
It looks like he’s
by the fountain.
Bring us around.
Hey, somebody’s got
a live feed on him.
This will be the
easiest kill ever.
They’re just writing the first
thing that comes to their mind.
Hey, Emmy!
I see what you’re going for.
Trap him.
That’s the Rat Clan for you.
They always bring
a bunch of guys.
They’re wrong.
Speed beats numbers.
And since all the best
kills happen at night--
Yes, hello Underworld.
Open German CPS.
Enter default admin
username and password.
[BEEPING]
Just where could you
be hiding, Lupin?
It already wreaks of death.
We see you there, hiding.
Discharge.
Ah!
Lupin!
[GROANING]
Run fire alarm system test.
Fire detected.
This is just a system test.
Stop all that yapping.
They’re just playing mind games.
[ALARM BLARING]
[SCREAMING]
They’re playing dirty.
Huh?
[GRUNTING]
It seems like we made the
right call by not rushing in.
Here he comes!
Ah!
Always wanted to drive
a car fresh off the lot.
Grr!
Move it!
Ah!
Emmy!
[GRUNTING]
Grr!
He got away!
There’s no need to fret.
After all, it’s not like Lupin
can leave the country, eh.
Inspector, going somewhere?
Bwanda of course.
Sir, but Bwanda’s
not in our jurisdiction.
I know that.
A vacation request?
I’m free to go wherever I’d
like during my vacation, right?
It’s just a matter of time.
In a country that small with
that many hitmen on his trail
there’s simply no way
he’s going to get away.
[LAUGHING]
Serves you right,
Lupin III!
[RAIN FALLING]
It’s going to hurt.
Ah!
The pain is proof
you are still alive.
Let’s talk.
It’ll keep your
mind off the pain.
Sounds unscientific.
[GROANING IN PAIN]
Pain like this reminds me of
back when they kidnapped me.
They?
When I was six.
I was abducted by
child pornographers.
Ah!
After they’d taken the
pictures they wanted,
we lived like animals waiting
for someone to buy us.
I’m here.
I’m listening.
But my tech skills
saved me from that fate.
Hey, yeah!
[LAUGHING]
What are you brats laughing at?
Oh!
Ah!
Did you make this on your own?
Huh, you might make us even
more dough than the porn.
I spent every day after that
writing source code non-stop.
Missing deadlines
meant beatings.
So I learned to work fast.
And one of the
things you cooked up
was Marco Polo’s payment system?
When I was 14
I managed to escape
and hid myself down
in the Twin Towers.
Not that my quality
of life improved much.
Ah!
[RAIN FALLING]
She’s out cold.
I feel bad about
this whole thing.
If only I had been
a bit more careful.
Are you in any position
to worry about others?
What the hell brought out
the assassin all stars
in the first place?
A website for hitmen.
Or at least that’s what
my followers are saying.
But these guys know
absolutely everything when
it comes to Lupin III.
That’s rich coming
from the man himself.
Lupin, I will leave
our plan up to you.
But I have one question.
Do we fight or do we flee?
That’s simple.
We take them all down.
[PEOPLE TALKING]
So then, how did your entire
Rat Clan let Lupin slip
through their fingers?
How did your people
fail to take out Goemon?
Huh!
Ichiro, settle down.
Hmph.
Lupin’s online!
What’s up to you hit morons?
This is taking way too long.
So I would rather deal
with you guys all at once.
I’m at the ruins of the
Nudabale tribe’s
old town.
So come and get me a
bunch of one of wannabes.
Watson says there’s no
tech in the Nudabale
ruins that Lupin’s hacker
can use against us this time.
So he can’t try and
pull the same crap
he did at the factory, huh?
All right.
Look alive, boys.
Yeah!
There’s no way in hell
he can pull that off.
This is the real world.
Hm? Isn’t it obvious.
He’s out of options.
Have you made a
decision, Fujiko?
Well, I can’t say
no and I’m simply
the best at this type of game.
Does it hurt?
Not enough to affect my work.
Are you worried about me?
Huh?
Hey!
They’re here.
Well, well, well.
All those vehicles have
hired killers in them, huh?
Lupin’s up there.
Kill him.
Scan their faces.
Cross-reference with available
databases on the dark web.
That’s Mama from the Union.
Next to her are
Ichiro and Lucky.
They use fishing rods and bombs.
And there’s Akaki
He wields a transparent gun
and a knife.
It’s time to go.
It’d be an outright shame if
no one welcomed our guests
to the party.
And remember to stick
to the plan, you guys.
OK guys, here’s the plan.
This gambling website lets
people bet on what day I’ll die.
Or in other words, what
day they’ll kill me.
But what if multiple
people bet on the same day?
They split the pot?
No, no one wants that.
So they all been
on different days.
Exactly what do the people
who attack us really want?
I figured that they would
want to capture and kill me
only on the day they
placed a bet on.
Makes sense.
They do their best to make
sure no one else kills you
on a different day.
In other words,
you have two types
of players in this death game.
Those who want to
kill me and those
who need to catch me later.
The Rat Clan could have shot me.
But they aimed for Emmy so
they could slow me down.
Anything?
Nothing so far.
Hm, he’s back!
Here’s our first tip of the day.
Kinkaku and Ginkaku,
entry number four.
They bet on me dying today.
What’s this?
What’s going on here, bro?
Ginkaku shoot her!
What all this means is,
I’m no longer the biggest
threat in this game.
Everyone else is.
[GROANING]
What the hell?
Weren’t all of the bets
supposed to be anonymous?
Watson says it’s highly likely
that he’s got that hacker girl
from the factory assisting him.
You did good today, Emmy.
This assassination website
has so much security
that I’d say they’re paranoid.
It’ll take a while even for me.
Then how--
Actually, I’m bluffing.
But it seems like
it only took one
set to make everyone
turn on each other.
You really got
what it takes, kid.
Having what it takes to
become a thief isn’t my thing.
Huh?
Not that.
You’ve got what it takes
for the real world.
They’re dropping like flies.
There’s not many left now.
This is bad.
Don’t let him get to you.
This is one of Lupin’s schemes.
I’ll have to avoid
all those idiots
and head straight for Lupin.
If you’re heading straight
up I got a shortcut for you.
Daisuke Jigen!
Gah!
The thing is, I
was never planning
on letting you take it.
Now there’s only one
person left to put money
on my death happening today.
Who out of these
three could it be?
Ah!
Can I ask you something?
Anything you like by
internet princess.
Who did you mean by
sweet young thing?
Do you really want to know?
I’ve been thinking for a while.
But I just can’t come
up with an answer.
I have a hard time
understanding how
your mind could have
been on women at a time
like that in the first place.
It was already too late.
Were you talking
about a call girl?
Maybe Jigan or Goemon
is secretly a woman.
Now that’s just gross.
Then do you intend
on sleeping with me?
Do you want me to?
I am interested.
After all, I have
never had sex before.
Well, sorry.
But I only sleep with adults.
Adults like Fujiko Mine?
Now where did you
get that name from?
It came out by using
a search algorithm.
Along with Jigen
and Goemon, she’s
one of the known associates
of Lupin III.
And that’s not getting
into the rumors
that she’s actually
your girlfriend.
That info seems a
little out of date.
It’s not like that between
Fujiko and me any longer.
I’m going to take
Goemon down first, Mama.
Hm!
What the hell!
This guy got off
my weight thingies!
Damn you!
Got him, Mama!
One tug and his
head goes flying.
And I win!
And how is it that you
plan on doing that?
Huh?
Agghhh!
Even if you managed to
kill every assassin here
this death game won’t end.
The bounty’s still
on the website.
They’ll never stop
hunting you, Lupin.
Seems so, huh?
You could quit.
With your talent for disguises
you could live a quiet life
somewhere.
Is that another one of
your logical conclusions?
Sorry, but that’s not my--
hm?
Seems like a guest
has finally arrived!
[WIND BLOWING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
Is it just you?
Lupin, I couldn’t care less
about the bounty anymore.
In the name of my fallen clan
members, I’m going to kill you.
Sounds good to me.
After what you just
did to my publicist
I really can’t wait to
settle up the score.
[WIND BLOWING]
[GUN SHOOTING]
Sorry pal, but I’ve never
been the type to play fair
when it’s about love and war.
You see that?
We beat them all!
Oh, man.
That’s good.
Today wasn’t a
bad day after all.
Makes a man truly feel
alive when he’s got a foe.
That makes no sense.
Foes to surpass.
Foes to oppose.
Rivals, friends, parents, women.
Women are your foes?
The most puzzling and
precious ones ever.
Oh?
Huh?
[AIRPLANE SOARING]
Is it another assassin?
Hey, Fujiko.
Did you come because you
were worried about me?
Of course not.
You know I’ll never be the
one chasing after you, silly.
Yeah that’s true.
You were the one who stole me on
my wedding day, remember Lupin?
Well, after all a thief’s
job is to steal things.
I don’t remember asking you to.
I’ve got a present
for you, Lupin.
The first in four years.
If anybody’s going to kill
you, it should be me right?