hirping]
- So what you're saying is,
you won't accept our conditions
under any circumstance.
Is that a correct assessment?
- No. We did not mean to give
you that impression.
- That's right.
- Huh?
- Not Lupin's, nor anyone
else's postings on PeopleLog
will be taken down.
- If Lupin keeps
posting like he is,
it's only going to make
the situation worse.
His posts have already
been responsible
for a presidential race
where every single candidate
withdrew.
And a string of posts about
global fraudulent accounting
has left every stock market
in the world in chaos.
And claims he made about
international trade
have torpedoed existing deals.
- The world's been
brought to its knees,
and it's all because
of Lupin's lies.
- Except they're not
lies, are they?
PeopleLog gives them all
A ratings.
- And that's just the problem.
That makes it look like
PeopleLog itself is endorsing
everything Lupin says.
- Sounds like you
need to stop having
secrets that get you
into trouble
when Lupin makes them public.
If you all stopped
being shady,
the world would be
a better place.
That's part of the future
our app is trying to create.
- [scoffs]
- Is something funny?
- Yes. Because PeopleLog
couldn't predict
what Lupin was going to do.
- [growls]
- You're going to need much
more than just data
to even come close
to understanding that guy.
ｶ [jazz music plays]
- So where have you been
for the past month?
- Just traveling around, and
catching up with old friends.
- Any female friends?
- Oh, good heavens, no.
- For all the enemies
this guy has,
he has just as many allies.
- A gallery of rogues
the likes of which
no machine could ever predict.
- I gotta ask you
something though,
what's with the trawler?
- Oh, it's camouflage.
Cause, you know,
I'm super famous and all that.
There are times I want
to get away from prying eyes.
You know what I'm saying.
- I feel you.
[exhales]
Nothing any good ever
comes from being famous.
- [laughs]
[reel whirs]
Got a bite.
[quiet boom]
- [screaming]
- Now, then.
We've got a calling
card to send.
- So why did you
break up with Lupin?
- Because we were dating.
- Is that a joke?
- No, it's true.
Are you stupid or something?
- Well, letting you die alone
seemed a little lonely.
- That's true.
If this really is
the end,
I should settle down
with a nice guy.
Wonder who I should pick?
Aw, don't be like that.
Do you see any
other guys up here?
Well then, I'll settle for you.
I'm not sure why I said yes.
I mean it was fun
living together,
getting up together,
going to bed together,
sharing meals and drinks.
We even went couch
shopping together.
- But did you have a fight?
Over another woman, maybe?
- Nothing broke us up.
- Huh?
Then why did you
break up in the end?
- It was nothing.
- I've always hated riddles.
- There was no need for
romantic cat and mouse games.
No excitement or thrills,
no death defying heists.
Nothing.
I suppose settling down
didn't suit us in the end.
- Well then, what
does suit you?
- I'd love to know that myself.
- What do you want?
- Lupin's vanished.
- [gasps]
- PeopleLog is
functioning properly,
so that means we must be missing
some crucial data on him.
Lupin has to have
some kind of secret.
It has to be something huge,
something no one knows.
- Enzo!
China's following
the European Union's lead,
and talking about sanctions.
We need to start
softening our stance.
- We can't.
Database objective
analysis is the very thing
that makes PeopleLog,
an app that can correct
humanity's prejudices
and ignorance.
- But that's an ideal.
- I thought we were trying
to make those ideals a reality.
- But that's--
- [growls]
[explosion booms]
- What?
[rocket roars]
[explosions]
- My fellow Americans, following
closed door discussions
with our closest allies,
I have ordered
military strikes
on the Shake Handz
corporation headquarters.
Not only does their
PeopleLog program
infringe on our cherished
American right to privacy,
it also represents
a grave threat
to the national security
of this great nation.
Their intention to unravel
our democracy is quite clear.
And even though Shake Handz
may call themselves a business,
they will now be classified
as a terrorist organization.
- What is he saying?
- Does that mean
we're terrorists now?
- We haven't even done
anything illegal.
- We're going to jail.
- What's the boss doing?
- [gasping]
Why is this--
This isn't
what we agreed on!
You promised to keep
military action off the table
as long as PeopleLog--
- You're right.
I did make that promise.
But now, I broke it.
[explosions in the distance]
- He totally played you, Ling,
which is no doubt one
of the reasons
why PeopleLog couldn't predict
this attack.
- Let's go now, Enzo!
If we go through the network
cable tunnels, we can get out.
- By all means. Go.
- Enzo.
- It would seem you never
had faith
in the app we created
after all.
- Looks like I can't
wait for Lupin.
- Fujiko, Lupin's calling card.
- Yata, let's move!
- Yes, sir.
Right behind you!
- Just ignore that nonsense.
No thief is going
to make any difference.
- Something's on sonar!
- What?
- It's a sub!
- Diana, I really owe you one.
- After that business
with grandfather,
I owed you one too.
- Thieves are in the shadows.
All is right with the world.
To all the folks who are
looking for me, nice try, guys!
- Lupin.
- And now to save you
all the trouble,
you're about to see
a livestreaming
of a Lupin III
heist.
[rapid gunfire]
- Goemon?
- I'm on it.
- Bull's eye.
- All right!
Huh?
- You guys are rooting
for Lupin?
- Lupin is the best
there ever was.
- That's right.
- [growling]
[groaning]
- Yeah, get him!
- I'm with Lupin, too!
- You're cheer-leading
for the crook?
- The hell did you say?
- [groaning]
- What the--
[sword zings]
[screaming]
- Everyone, fall back.
[gunshots]
[groaning]
- Lupin, we shall
handle this.
- You're going to go have some
face time with Fujiko, right?
- Good idea.
Think I will.
- Hmm?
[laughs]
- Think we can take
these guys on
with just the two of us?
- There is nothing
duller than a battle
where the outcome is certain.
- Heh.
Hell yeah, man.
- They're not working.
Just you watch what
human legs can do.
- We're having a hard
time getting in.
The enemy's putting up
heavy resistance.
- They have a PNC?
What kind of enemy force
are we looking at?
- Just two targets.
Two enemies --
a gunslinger and a samurai.
- Quit screwing around.
- [groaning]
[gunshots]
[sword zings]
- [screams]
- Goemon.
[screaming]
- Look, mother.
It's Jigen.
- Hmm.
- Yay, Goemon!
- All right!
- [pants]
I'm on my way, my princess.
[explosions boom]
- [crying]
Enzo. Enzo!
Oh!
- Did you really think
we seriously didn't know
about these tunnels?
[phone rings]
- Yes. It seems
the negotiations have failed,
and Enzo is in the wind.
And I've confirmed
that Ling was taken out
by one of the airstrikes.
I'm personally
bringing you in,
and putting your talents
to use.
PeopleLog's tech
will come in handy
when I want
to control a country.
- You're going
to betray your nation?
They'll be far better off
with me running the show,
than leaders who change every
time there's an election.
- All right, then.
- Hmm.
Lupin, I've stolen
what I want.
What about you?
- Not good.
The fire suppression
systems are failing.
The building's going to come
crashing down within the hour.
- Lupin, are you okay?
[gasps]
- Is the camera acting up?
- Come on, you can't
stop at the best part.
- Maybe there's too
many people
trying to access the livestream.
- No! Can't be!
It's Lupin!
- He's taken
administrative access.
What the hell is the
countermeasure team doing?
- You think you can bring
PeopleLog down
with a pathetic little
prank like this?
[metal creaks]
It can't--
[metal creaking]
- [grunts]
- Lupin!
- You climbed
the elevator cable by hand
just to get up here?
Well then, looks like
PeopleLog isn't as omniscient
as you thought.
- Did you come
all this way to say that?
- That's right.
And also, Fujiko,
I wanted to prove
that I'm not going to die.
- [giggles]
- That's enough out of you.
- [groans]
- Lupin!
- Spill it, Lupin.
You must have some
kind of hidden secret.
Otherwise, you couldn't
possibly have evaded PeopleLog.
- Put the gun down now.
- What the--
Stop it.
I know you can't shoot me.
- And why is that?
Did PeopleLog
tell you I couldn't?
You don't even know
your own daughter.
So how would PeopleLog know?
I already have some
blood on my hands.
- It's OK, Emmy.
I wouldn't worry.
There's no way
he's going to shoot now.
- But he--
- Enzo here just has to know.
What I'll say next.
What I'll do next.
Because unless
it can figure me out,
PeopleLog will never be
perfect.
- Huh?
- Fujiko, I love you.
- I know that.
- Hmm.
You're the most ravishing
woman in the world.
- I know that, too.
- [sighs]
You want me to answer
the question from way back when?
- Yes I do, Lupin.
What am I to you, anyway?
Your lover?
Your rival?
An obstacle?
Harbor?
Support?
Or am I supposed to be
the end of you?
If we were men, I'd be
fine with being friends.
But personally, I don't
really believe men and women
can be just friends.
- I, too, have
been thinking about it.
About a lot of stuff
since you asked me that.
The thing is,
I still really don't know
myself, honestly.
Who really is Lupin III?
- Running away again?
- But after spending time
to think it through,
this is the best answer
I could come up with.
- [gasps]
Lupin?
- That's it, Lupin.
That's your secret.
[explosion]
- [gasping]
- It's collapsing.
- Emmy, analyze the construction
of the building.
Make a simulation
of how it's going to fall.
Find out which bit's going
to be the last bit standing.
- Huh?
Hello Underworld, come in!
- You're the--
[building rumbling]
- Lupin!
This way, Jigen.
Huh?
[rumbling continues]
ｶｶ
- Angle looks good.
Come on!
- Analysis complete.
We've got 32 seconds
until it collapses.
So we've got to hit
the ground first.
- Lupin.
- Whoa.
- I finally
know your secret now.
My next iteration of PeopleLog
will catch you for sure.
- You think that's the only
secret I've got up my sleeve?
Lupin III has plenty more.
- Lupin!
[screaming]
- You've got to be kidding me.
Emmy, over here.
Emmy.
- [screams]
- It's not Emmy, it's Ami.
- Everyone gets my name wrong.
Why did you give me
such a hard name?
It's a word from your
mother's country.
It means "net."
- [gasps]
- We came up with it together.
See, your name
connects to the future!
[helicopter whirs]
- Damn it.
It's become
a war zone down there.
- But sir, Lupin might be--
- He's not dead.
Lupin is not going to die
'til I catch him.
At least, not on my watch.
Huh.
Lupin, you're under arrest!
[wind howls]
- Hey, it's Pops.
- Trouble just keeps
finding us.
- Lupin, we'll go on ahead.
- Fujiko.
- Ami, you want to join
the crew?
- [gasps]
Thank you, Lupin.
I'll see you around.
- I see.
See you soon, Emmy.
- You sure?
- Yes, I want to be
by his side.
But if I'm too close,
I get restless.
I want him to be mine
more than anything.
But if I had him all to myself,
I'd only be disappointed.
I want to know
everything about him.
But I still want him
to surprise me.
It's strange, isn't it?
- Ami, there's a perfect
word for people like that.
Did you know?
- Huh?
There is?
- They're called heroes.
- [gasps]
[rockets explode]
- [panting]
- Lupin, did you shut down
PeopleLog before it collapsed?
- He says he's going
to make another one.
- What?
- Even if we stop Enzo,
there's going to be
plenty of people with
the same idea down the line.
- The world has truly become
a troublesome place.
- That mean
you're going to retire?
- Perhaps I shall.
I did defeat you, after all.
- Best two out of three.
We're fighting again, Goemon.
The first serious duel
between men settles the issue.
- Get back here!
Lupin!
You're under arrest!
- He never changes.
- And neither do we.
- But that's not bad.
- Hey, it works for me.
ｶ [jazzy theme music plays]
ｶｶ
ｶ [song ends]
[earpiece buzzes]