- MAN:
This is quite a match.
- LUPIN: Oh, really?
Which one?
- Why both, of course.
This is such fun.
- Heh.
- You know, I feel
so alive right now.
[gusts blowing]
¶¶
¶ [upbeat jazzy theme music]
[church bell ringing]
[overlapping conversations]
- Here you are, sir.
Is there anything
else I can get you?
- Hm.
Hi!
- [gasping] [giggling]
You're always here
around this time of day.
- That's 'cause I know
I'll run into a cutie like you.
- Oh, you.
[gunshot]
- Huh?
[grunting]
- WOMAN ON TV: Her injuries
are relatively minor,
and she should make
a quick recovery.
So far, no one has claimed
responsibility for the attack.
The scene of the shooting--
- It looks like Lupin
wasn't the only one
gunning after that waitress.
And no pun intended.
- ..before it was too late.
- What a freaking nightmare.
No way I can ask her out now.
- But a video uploaded
to the internet
appears to show
the type of ammunition
the gunman used in
carrying out the attack.
- LUPIN:
D4 is a chess move, you see.
- ...is the only evidence
retrieved from the scene.
- Old man Zylberstein
is calling me out.
- You mean
the psychotic rich guy?
What are you going to do,
Lupin?
- I'm totally wiped out
after our last job.
I don't have the energy to
humor the elderly and senile.
- I figured as much.
Well, I'm getting
some shut eye, then.
[chatter]
[gunshot,
crowd screaming]
- And it would appear
an officer on patrol
has been shot in the arm.
We still don't
have any statement
from those responsible.
What is their motive for
this spree of attacks?
- ZYLBERSTEIN: Lupin the Third
has accepted my invitation.
I am expecting great
things from you.
[cocks gun]
- Hmm.
- Well, now, it's been a while,
my little Lupin.
- About three years, I think.
You're still
in good health, I see.
So I gather we're
playing chess this time?
Hm.
Well, what are the stakes?
- Heh.
All right.
Let's settle for
a million euros a match.
- Hm.
I'm counting on you, partner.
- The police on site
have searched the scene
of the shooting
thoroughly,
but have yet to turn up
any meaning.
- Hey, Jigen.
- Hm?
- Ever hear of a sniper who
goes by the name of Mirage?
- [gasps]
Huh?
- It looks like the old man's
been hunting for mercenaries
all over the internet.
- Mirage, huh?
It's been a very long time
since I heard that name.
Used to be a sniper for hire.
We fought side by side
a few times.
- I see.
Then Mirage must have
been the one he hired.
- Lupin, Mirage
is a real crack shot.
If you don't take
this seriously,
you're going to end up
with a hole in your head.
- It'll be fine.
I've got an even better sniper
who's always watching my back.
N'est pas?
- If that's the case, maybe
I'll help you track down
this sniper friend.
- Come on, Jigen.
That's ice cold, man.
Besides, you'll find him
in the bathroom.
Just look in the mirror.
He's an old, uh, dashing
young fellow with a beard.
- I heard what you said.
- You in?
- [grunts]
Just so you know,
I didn't bring my rifle
since I'm supposed to be
on vacation.
[gulping]
Where are you?
Bingo.
No.
Mirage wouldn't be
that stupid.
- Hm.
- Damn.
[gunshot]
[grunts]
That's right, Mirage.
Looks like you and me will
have our first dance together.
[gunshots]
[gunshots in distance]
- You really want
to see me die that badly?
You realize we're not going
to make it easy for you.
- [chuckles]
I'm positively giddy
at the prospect
of seeing
your whole head explode
like a watermelon.
- You never learn.
- By the way, my boy...
...did you know
Mirage was a woman?
- Huh?
- Heh.
Oh, dear.
Friends keeping secrets
from each other.
- Maybe he was scared I'd steal
her out from under his nose.
- You know, that girl...
...she became a civil war
refugee
after her parents were
executed right in front of her.
- So then, how did
she end up as a sniper?
- [chuckles]
Perhaps you could
call it a twist of fate.
Her refugee camp was attacked
by some particularly vicious
guerrilla fighters, you see.
- And?
- She fought all of them off
with the rifle
of a dead French soldier
who was protecting the camp.
- Hm.
- She took after her dad,
who was a hell of a hunter.
It seems to run in the family.
- I see.
- That girl grew up to be
a truly peerless sniper.
She is feared by enemies
and allies alike.
It was around that time people
started calling her "Mirage."
- People were getting shot
by an illusion.
That right?
- When the war finally ended,
she became a professional
gun for hire.
Actually, I hired her
a few times
when she was first
starting out.
- Hey, Gramps.
- Hm?
- You left out
the most important
bit of information here.
- Oh, did I?
- Yeah.
Is she hot or not?
- Hm?
[chuckles]
Yes.
Even your beloved Fujiko Mine
pales in comparison to her.
- Yeah, right.
- Hmph.
Huh?
[gunshot]
[gasps]
HEIAP rounds?
[gunshots]
[grunting]
Gotcha.
She predicted my movements.
How did she know?
Huh?
[gunshot]
Dammit.
Moving with the times, huh?
- This is quite a match.
- Oh, really?
Which one?
- Why, both, of course.
This is such fun.
- [chuckles]
- You know, I feel
so alive right now.
- [grunting]
(VOICEOVER) Never thought
you'd quit before me.
- Well, I have
a new battle to fight now.
I'm looking forward to it.
- Do you think you'll be
able to manage all right?
- Thanks for the concern,
Jigen.
But, you know, I'm OK.
I think that I can be
stronger than ever,
if I'll be fighting for
somebody else's sake.
- Well, I've never been serious
about protecting someone else,
so I really wouldn't know.
- [giggling]
- That looks heavy.
- Huh?
- You want me to take that
off your hands?
- Mnh-mnh.
I'll carry this
weight on my own.
- As you wish.
- Part of me thinks
I only made it this far
because I've never gone up
against you, Jigen.
And now, I'm relieved
I'll never have to fight you.
- Believe me,
the feeling is mutual.
- [sighing]
Well, we'll probably
never meet again.
- Yeah, it's probably
for the best.
What exactly are you protecting
by coming back, "Mirage"?
[boom]
[gunshots]
[gunfire]
[gunfire echoing]
- Checkmate, I think.
- No, not yet.
- I mean for them.
- [panting]
[slurps]
Damn it.
This is making me wish
I quit smoking.
- [panting]
Huh?
[gunfire]
[rocks rumbling]
[sighing]
[gunshot]
- [grunting]
Ah!
Ugh!
[groaning]
- A ricochet, huh?
Looks like your luck ran out.
- Why?
Damn it.
- My leg!
Aaaahhh!
King to F5.
[groaning]
- King to F7.
- Pawn to F3.
- Hm.
I resign, Gramps.
- Ha, ha!
Gotcha.
[grunting]
- [yelling]
- Mirage!
Huh?
- [grunting]
- What the hell is this?
- But how?
All of those rocks
should have crushed you.
- I shot my way out.
- Huh?
[gunshots]
- Who the hell are you?
- Mirage's daughter, right?
- [grunts]
- So what has happened
to the real Mirage, then?
- My mother is still fighting.
She's very sick.
- Huh?!
- She won't get better
unless we get her
to a hospital in Europe,
but it's too expensive.
- So when you heard about
someone looking to hire Mirage,
you signed up instead.
- Just cut the crap.
Mirage left.
She left the battlefield so
she could raise you right.
And now what?
You waltz right back into it
just because you're hard up for
something as stupid as cash?
Shut up! Even though we were
living in peace time,
my mother taught me
how to fight.
She told me if I ever had
a reason to fight
she wouldn't
stand in my way.
Well, now is that time!
If I don't fight for her now,
when will I take up arms?
If you think you can take
her pain away and make
her whole again, then do so!
- All right.
Settle down, you two.
The fight's over.
- No, it's not.
I still need that money!
- I'll provide you with
what you need soon enough.
- Eh?
- [gasps]
And I'm not talking
about charity.
I lost to this old timer
at chess.
And he's out, so you
get the money instead.
How does that sound?
- Your mom was one
hell of a shot.
And I'm going to butt in
one last time before I go.
You're not cut
out for this work.
You could even dedicate
your whole life to it,
but you'll never be even
half the sniper your mom was.
It's not too late.
Turn your hand
to something else.
- [gasping]
- It's time to stop
chasing a mirage.
Since I didn't kill you,
I'm taking this rifle.
If you've learned
anything today,
I don't think you'll be
needing it again.
Tell your mom
you chucked it or something.
I know she'll understand.
- [sobbing]
- You sure you want to let
the old coot off the hook?
- Once he's feeling better,
I'll go against him again.
- Well, count me out.
Today shaved five years
off my life.
- You really saved my butt,
Jigen,
and I do appreciate it.
- You're welcome.
You know that girl?
If she kept at it--
- If she kept at it?
- I think she might have
become an even better sniper
than her mom.
- Looks heavy.
Want me to take it
off your hands?
- I'll carry
this weight on my own.
- Hm.
¶¶
¶ [Japanese singing]