[music playing]
I’ve got a present for you,
Lupin, the first in four years.
Mm.
If anybody’s going to
kill you, it should be me.
Right?
[THEME - YUJI OHNO,
"LUPIN TROIS 2018"]
[typewriter keys clicking]
[music playing]
[comments chiming]
Are you ready to
receive my last gift?
Nah.
I think I’ll pass on that one.
Go and return it.
And I wouldn’t bother
reaching for whatever
you’ve got in your hairpiece.
[sighs]
I’m counting down now, Lupin.
[chiming]
Lupin!
[car engine roaring]
Zenigata?
Pops?
Get in.
You too, young lady.
Let’s go, Ami.
Stop!
[shoots]
[explosion]
Pops, not that I don’t
appreciate the sweet rescue,
but you’re out of
your jurisdiction.
You know you can’t
arrest me here.
Right?
I realize that, so I’m
crossing the border where
I can officially arrest you.
I was afraid you were
going to say that.
[music playing]
You had to get in the way.
Didn’t you, Inspector Zenigata?
[gun cocks]
Hm?
Nice to see you again, Jigen.
Didn’t figure you
would show up and try
to cash in on Lupin too?
What’s wrong with that?
Women can be damn scary.
Really?
I can think of
something even scarier.
And what’s that?
Men who value
genuine friendship.
[music playing]
Even Fujiko’s after you now.
You two have a falling out?
No, nothing like that.
There’s nothing between
Fujiko and me anymore.
What?
You used to drool
all over that woman,
calling her Fujicakes
and whatnot.
That’s ancient history.
All she is to me now is
competition in this biz.
[helicopter whirring]
Huh?
The Bawandan military?
I’m Zenigata with the ICPO!
I want to speak
with your commander!
[gunfire]
What in the world?
Don’t bother, pops.
The guys who are
running this country
are practically
mobsters themselves.
[groans]
Figures.
No wonder they don’t want
to be a part of the ICPO.
[gunfire continues]
Huh?
Chasing us like we’re
common criminals.
As a public servant,
this is an insult.
[explosion]
Come on.
Time to go, kid.
[car crashing]
Hm.
Mm-hm.
[camera shutter]
[music playing]
Hey.
Nice try, Lupin, but the bounty
on the assassination site
doesn’t expire until
you’re six feet under.
Don’t worry.
We’ll never run out of hitmen.
I guess we finally lost them.
Can’t be easy to spot
us here in the bush.
There are no paths
in here though.
Well, young miss, not to worry.
Look there.
In the southern
hemisphere, the sun
travels in a northern
arc, which means
walking in the opposite
direction will take us south.
Yes.
Hello, Underworld.
Connect now through
the ponyan proxy.
What’s the shortest
route to the border?
That’s the AR map by
shake hands for you.
Got to love these
modern conveniences.
[music playing]
If you’re looking for drinkable
water, I can help out.
What is the meaning
of this, for the ICPO
to be seen as aiding and
abetting a wanted criminal?
Not to mention the fact that
it was broadcast globally.
This is very bad.
All Inspector Zenigata has
done is apprehend a criminal.
The public won’t
see it that way.
We will have to open
disciplinary proceedings
when he gets back.
Our appearance matters.
[growls]
Run an object search.
Cross reference
with edible flora.
Hm.
Hey, look at you,
professor botany.
Just about anyone with
an internet connection
can be a scientist, as long as
you know what to search for.
[fire crackling]
[slurping]
And so you lived as a
shut-in for 15 years?
I wasn’t a shut-in.
I just had no reason
to go outside.
So now that you’re outside,
how’s the rest of the world
treating you?
Poorly.
Communication takes too long.
Is that so?
There are countless
threats to your life.
It’s hot and it’s
dusty, and the food.
That’s because
you’re with this guy.
[scoffs]
Young miss, a girl your
age should be at school.
Don’t worry.
The ICPO’s witness
protection program
can take you in once we’re
done with Marco Polo.
We’ll happily keep
you safe and sound.
I see no reason to go to school.
Mm?
I can find any information
I want on the internet,
and I’m above average in
terms of basic logic and math.
I’m sure I’m above average.
I bet.
But at school, you
can make friends.
I have plenty of
friends on the internet
from all over the world, where
gender, age, and race don’t
matter.
A space as confined
as a school building
can’t offer even a
fraction of that diversity.
Well, now.
You’re mistaken
about that, miss.
Love and friendship can’t
be defined by logic.
Do you consider Lupin a friend?
Eh?
Your irrational actions
to help us like this,
is this your idea of friendship?
With him?
How could I with this lying,
lawbreaking, womanizing thief?
I see.
That’s really cold, pops.
Oh, I get it.
You do?
Not to worry.
I believe love comes in
all shapes and sizes,
and all are equally valid.
[groans]
No.
I only came because of Lupin.
No, wait, I--
A pair of lovers on
opposite sides of the law.
It’s so romantic.
No!
[laughing]
[blowing kisses]
I love you, honey.
Shut it, you monkey-faced idiot.
Sorry.
I never realized you had
feelings for me, my darling.
I’ll shoot you, you bastard!
Oh, scary.
But if you want to shoot, use
that other gun in your pants
instead.
Seems fun.
Oh, such thick sideburns.
You’ve got sideburns too!
Oh, don’t be shy.
[yelling continues]
It’s going to be all
desert for a while.
If we go straight
for the border,
it’s a 50-kilometer trek.
The temperature at this time
of year is around 40 degrees
Celsius.
Should be walkable.
Isn’t this your very
first time in a desert?
I’ve got a good idea
of the broader picture.
I’ve read the equivalent of 83
books on desert environments.
[chuckles]
Well, aren’t you a book worm?
They were abridged versions.
An AI summarized all 83 through
a machine learning algorithm.
Hm?
[music playing]
After wandering through
the desert for a day,
it was like I was on
a different planet.
In time, I felt I had
stopped being an Earthling
altogether and was now a
denizen of a desert world.
The intense sun began to
feel pleasant on my skin.
Stop.
What, are you done already?
What about your 84th book?
It’s fiction and I
wanted nonfiction,
and there’s nothing
pleasant about this.
Well, there’s all sorts
of people out there.
[laughing]
Maybe the guy who wrote it
was a bit of a masochist.
What would you write about
the desert, if you could?
It sucks, this crummy,
blinding, bone-dry hellhole!
[laughing]
Perhaps we should have
waited for nightfall.
This is still better than the
military catching up with us.
[whimpers]
[thud]
[gasps]
Huh?
Ami!
[music playing]
Hey.
If something bad ever
happened to me, pops,
can you help her out?
Nothing bad is
happening on my watch.
That I promise.
Appreciate it.
Thanks, pops.
[music playing]
[groans]
You’ve got to be
kidding me, Lupin.
You think you can just
wander off and die
where no one can see?
There’s got to be a lot
more to it than just that.
[music playing]
[labored breathing]
Huh?
I see a camel.
Hm?
Are you joking, pops?
All I see is a bunch
of beautiful babes.
[giggling]
[moans]
You awake, Ami?
The sun’s almost down.
It’ll cool off.
Windmill?
That means--
Huh?
Water!
Hey!
Quit squirming!
[struggling]
[panting]
Water.
[inhales deeply]
[gulping]
[music playing]
Don’t drink that too fast.
It will upset your stomach.
[music playing]
Once we’re through this
bit, we’ll be at the border.
And when we cross the border,
you can finally arrest me, huh?
Lupin, come peacefully.
It looks like you’re finally
going to get your wish, pops.
Once you’re in custody, it’ll
be tough for these assassins
to get to you.
Hm.
I really appreciate it, pops.
But, you know, I would no
longer be Lupin if I did that.
[music playing]
[drone whirring]
Take care of it before
they cross the border.
If you help us win the
bet, you’ll get a share.
You can leave it to us, sir.
There’s nowhere to hide
in the desert, sir.
That money is as good as ours.
[helicopter approaching]
Hm?
And here they come.
Positions.
It’s the same
model as last time.
But now, it’s armed
with missiles.
[fires]
[yelling]
What is that?
[explosions]
Lupin!
Zenigata?
Did we get them?
There’s still one more.
Lupin!
Zenigata!
[gunfire]
Hunting people is more fun
than I thought it would be.
Aren’t missiles
kind of overkills?
[gasps]
Ami!
[gunfire continues]
All right.
Let’s go for the kill now.
Aw, come on.
You’re no fun.
[music playing]
[screams]
What the hell?
Damn it.
The rotors!
[yelling out]
[crashing]
She did it!
Ami, are you OK?
[fire burning]
[whimpering]
I’m still alive.
[laughing]
Huh?
[music playing]
Look.
That fence marks the border.
Once we’re past
that, I guess we’re
back to playing hide and seek.
Inspector Zenigata!
Well, maybe I will take you
up on that offer for a ride.
I have the girl
with me after all.
Not to worry.
I can take you past the
border and straight to jail.
[laughing]
Oh, no, pops.
You’re really far too kind.
[laughing]
[gunshot]
Get down.
A sniper?
How the heck did they
find us out here?
Hey, pops, keep her safe.
[gunshot]
Lupin.
You two get going.
I’ll catch up.
Let’s go.
He won’t try to escape
until you’re safe.
Is he an idiot?
How’d you know?
Where I come from, Lupin
is synonymous with idiot.
[music playing]
Get in the car!
Inspector, you all right?
Start a fire.
Huh?
We need enough smoke to block
the sniper’s line of sight.
Move it!
Yes, sir.
[drone whirring]
Is that all you got,
you persistent jerk?
You’ll need more
than that to kill--
[whimpers]
[laughing]
Talk about a sore loser.
Huh?
[music playing]
Get over here, Lupin!
Yata, take this over, now.
Inspector!
I’m not going to
let you kill him.
[gunfire]
I’m going to take him in alive.
Pops, stay back!
I’ll take you in
once and for all.
[gunshot]
[gasps]
[music playing]
Lupin.
[music - yuji ohno, "adieu"]
[non-english singing]