- The kidnapped girl
who inspired Enzo was you.
- In a weird way, PeopleLog
was made because of me.
- Lupin's weakness
is his family,
just as PeopleLog
had predicted.
- Wait, father--
- Hm?
- It's me.
I might have changed a bit,
but I'm the daughter
you had with Yuko Enan.
- That's wonderful, Enzo.
- Yeah, PeopleLog finally
managed to take Lupin III down.
- [gasp]
- That's not what I meant.
Your daughter was
alive the entire time.
- Oh.
Yeah, that happened, too.
- Huh?
What's with you?
- Stop trying to act tough.
Didn't you create
PeopleLog for the sake
of finding your daughter?
- I suppose that could've
been the reason why,
but that doesn't
matter any longer.
- Mother's passed away.
- Did she?
- You didn't know that?
- Why would I keep tabs
on my ex?
- What the hell were you doing?
You didn't even
come to her funeral.
You never even looked for me!
- What do you think is more
worthy of being saved--
the world itself,
or one kidnapped child?
- Lupin!
You're under arrest!
What happened here?
- Lupin has been arrested
and the age of heroes is over.
¶¶
¶ [jazzy theme music]
- To the Rat Clan!
To the capture of
Lupin III and drink up!
- So I've heard Lupin's
finally been captured.
- I heard one of his gang
betrayed him.
What a joke.
- Looks like Lupin's
been arrested.
- But he's just going
to break out again, isn't he?
- There's no point
in running anymore.
- You can run all you
want,
but PeopleLog will know
exactly where you are.
- There's nowhere left
in the world
where Lupin can
hide from PeopleLog now.
- Hey, I was thinking
we should go on down there
and watch them lock him up.
Good idea.
PeopleLog knows where they're
planning on sticking him, too.
[crash]
- Hold it right there.
PeopleLog also knew
where to find you two.
- It's been two weeks since
Lupin III was arrested,
and the ICPO is preparing
to transfer him.
- They sure took
their sweet time, huh?
- His injuries were so bad
they had to wait
for his condition to stabilize.
- You there!
Do you mind removing
the head of your costume?
A known criminal
has been spotted
wearing a costume
like yours,
so we just need to check
your identity.
- Hey!
- Freeze!
- Man, Lupin, just
what the hell is happening
to this crazy world?
[wind blows]
- Goemon,
what should
I do with this?
- I have finally defeated
Lupin
and I am now the strongest man
in the world.
[grunts]
All right.
I'll hold on to it
for you, then.
You can have it back when
you've done your time.
- Goemon!
- Fujiko Mine!
- Really look at him.
That's the only way you'll
find what you're looking for.
- Fujiko Mine, you're also
coming with us.
- Fujiko, if you'd like,
we can get the government
to reject the ICPO's
request to hand you over.
- Sounds good.
I'll let you boys keep me
in your cage a while longer.
I have no doubt Lupin will
come back, and when he does,
he'll need a glittering
prize to steal, right?
- It won't happen,
just like how you can't
put the genie back
in the bottle,
Lupin III and all
master thieves like him
are nostalgic
footnotes in history now.
- Ling, I've thought up some
new prediction vectors
that we can cook up using
Bayesian probabilities.
Hm?
- I don't really remember
you all that well,
and Mama never
talked about you,
so I thought it was better
not to ask.
And the thing is,
we were happy on our own,
so I never tried to find you.
But then--
- [laughter]
Oh, my dear Emmy,
I'm your father.
He pretended to be my father,
but he didn't even know
how to pronounce
my name properly.
So I took pot shots at him
because I was angry as hell.
But I realized somewhere deep
down inside of me,
some part of me always
hoped my real father
would come searching for me
someday. And so--
- Is this little monologue going
to go on for much longer?
It's rather rude of you
to show up
without a bullet point
breakdown.
I'm a little busy right now.
- If you keep staring
at me like that, pal,
you'll make me blush.
- Lupin.
- No need to look so blue.
I'm still alive and kicking.
- Yes, I suppose you are.
- [laughter]
Remember the last
time this happened?
When that one girl
tricked you real bad?
You fell hard for her,
but it turned out
she was a guy.
You really are a magnet for
trouble when it comes to women.
Laugh, Goemon.
Once something's over,
you may as well laugh about it.
[laughs, groans]
- Lupin.
- What else can you do
at a time like this?
- [laughter]
- Damn it!
- COP: He went that way.
Don't let him escape!
- Don't even have time
for a smoke break.
Crap.
Only one bullet left.
Huh?
[crowd chatter]
- This is quite the arrest.
- REPORTER:
What was the decisive factor
in catching the elusive
Lupin III after all this time?
- Actually, it's all thanks
to the years of collaboration
between our organization
and the various police forces
of our member states.
- Hold on a second!
What are you saying?
Inspector Zenigata is the one
who arrested Lupin.
- No one's denying Zenigata's
contributions were immense.
- A lot of people think
that Lupin was only arrested
thanks to PeopleLog.
- It's thanks to Zenigata
that PeopleLog had data
to predict Lupin's actions.
His career has been
stuck in a rut
since the day he was put
on the Lupin case.
You're the ones who made him
a dedicated Lupin investigator.
How could you do this to him?
That's like telling a salesman
to hawk something
no one would ever want,
and yet, we finally got him
and you take all the credit.
- That's enough, Yata.
Dealing with press conferences
isn't our department.
- But, sir--
- Let's head back.
The job's not done
until Lupin is behind bars.
- Right.
[sirens]
- MAN ON TV:
Take a good look--
the greatest criminal
mastermind of our age,
Lupin III,
is being taken away.
A large crowd of onlookers has
turned out to see the convoy.
- You know something, Yata?
I've been chasing after Lupin
for a long time now.
I even managed to catch him
a couple of times, too.
And I wasn't
the only one who did.
However, he'd always find
some way to get away.
- But him escaping
wasn't your fault, sir.
- Now what I'm looking
forward to
is seeing him finally serve
his debt to society--
and buy him a drink
when he's done.
And that's why all
these years
I've tried to take him
down by the book.
It's the only way
to make him realize
he needs to change his ways.
I need to appeal
to Lupin's heart.
- There appears to be
a broken down car
blocking the road ahead.
Stop the convoy.
It's safe.
There isn't any place to hide
an ambush out here.
- They're stopping the convoy.
- Those fools.
- Has something happened?
- It's him.
He's here.
- Excuse me, sir.
We need you
to move your vehicle.
- Daisuke Jigen!
Hold your hands
above your head now!
- Oh, good grief.
Let a man finish his cigarette.
I'm almost done with it.
- What are you waiting for?
He's all by himself.
If he resists at all,
shoot him.
- But sir, I--
- Daisuke Jigen, you will
give yourself up to us
or we'll shoot.
- [spits]
- [grunts]
- Get down!
[gunshots]
- Get him!
- Aaah!
- Time for an upgrade.
[boom]
[gunshots]
- Lupin--
- Yeah, it's Jigen.
Goemon, could you help me
to sit up?
[gunshots]
- Yata, we're sitting
ducks here.
- Understood, sir.
[helicopter crashing]
- Whoa!
[gunshots]
- Hey there, Jigen.
I appreciate the help.
- Lupin, don't you think
it's about time
you hung up your hat?
- But I don't wear a hat.
- Retirement, Lupin.
I hate to admit
that Enzo guy is right,
but it seems times
really have changed.
- Well, yeah, you might
have a point there.
- If I'm brutally honest,
there's a lot
of crap going on now
that I have trouble
keeping up with.
I preferred it
when things were simple.
- [grunting]
- Lupin, I've been
running around with you
longer than anybody else.
- Yeah.
- I figure I'm the only one who
can get you to call it quits.
Sure as hell ain't
going to be Fujiko.
- And just like that,
an old buddy
said something to him--
said it was time to retire.
The enemy's fierce,
quite possibly
the strongest adversary
he'd ever faced.
His friends were
bruised and battered
and things seemed hopeless.
What will happen to Lupin III?
What sort of plan does he have
for getting out of this one?
- Just give it a rest.
- So Jigen, with that kind
of setup,
can't you just hear it?
That sweet music?
- Music?
- You know, that super cool
incidental music
that plays right when the hero
is about to turn the tables?
- Lupin, life doesn't work out
like it does on TV.
- So why don't we make it
more like a TV show?
- What did you say?
- You're the only person
in the audience of your life,
so what's the point
in going on
if you're not thrilled
to see what happens next
in the story
that you get to live?
- Story?
Man, this is
one hell of a tight spot.
How is he ever going
to get out of it?
Maybe the bad guys
are too tough!
How is he going to find
a way to ever beat them?
See?
I want to look forward
to what I do next.
- And what are you supposed
to do if the ending doesn't
turn out the way you want it to?
- Aw, damn it!
Got all my hopes up for
nothing.
Guess I'll have to leave and
come back some other time.
- And what if the friggin
comeback never happens, huh?
- Then the audience
loses interest
and finds a way to move on.
That's why, Jigen.
Until the story's over,
I really want to keep
on being Lupin III.
- Huh?
[birds tweet]
- Lupin, I think I'm
starting to hear it too--
my own personalized
soundtrack.
- [laughter]
And it seems
you agree, too.
[crash]
- Just where the hell
has Lupin gone?
- It's been a month
and they still have no leads.
- No hits on PeopleLog either.
- That's impossible.
Did Lupin III turn into the
invisible man or something?
There's been no sign of Lupin
III anywhere on the internet.
- Lupin, what the hell
kind of trick
did you pull this time,
you bastard?
Could it be?
- It's possible he's dead.
- That's not true!
- [laughter]
- You believe in him.
Well, aren't you
the romantic one,
waiting for your prince to come
and rescue you from the tower?
- Well, for adults,
sometimes we need
a grand romantic gesture.
As for money and fame,
I have as much
as I want, but--
[ding]
- Someone posted
on Lupin's PeopleLog.
The poster was...
Lupin III!
- There he is!
It's Lupin!
- Finally!
- The little bastard's alive.
- President Jack King
and the oil companies
have been colluding illegally.
Lupin posted this?
[crowd chatter]
- Lies!
- What a liar!
- It's not only America--
China, France, India,
England, and even the Saudis.
They're all
in an uproar
about Lupin airing
their dirty laundry.
- PeopleLog is giving
an A rating
to every fact Lupin's posting.
- Basically it would
seem that PeopleLog
has given Lupin its approval.
- We have reports that
the FCC is now looking
into regulating PeopleLog.
- The Russians are threatening
to deport Shake Hands personnel
if PeopleLog
isn't shut down at once.
- We're being hit by
an onslaught of cyber attacks
that's too big to just be
a group of hackers.
- The EU parliament
could exclude PeopleLog
from their net
neutrality regulations.
- We'll go nowhere if we're
bogged down in details.
Just tell them all
that we're dealing with it.
- Well, Lupin III,
it would seem
you steal more
than just fine art.
- This is bad, Enzo.
Lupin's using PeopleLog
to rile up the whole world.
We need to start taking
his posts down right now.
- Not happening.
- But he's going
to kill this company.
- The censorship will kill us.
Collecting and analyzing
data objectively
is the reason
why PeopleLog exists.
You got us in a pinch,
Lupin III.
But where the hell
are you hiding?
- Hey, what's up guys?
- Got this here
from the old man.
It's Rebecca's response.
- I have also prepared
the fishing rod.
- Cool. Then let's get this
show on the road.
We're on our way, Enzo.
Your story is about
to arrive at its climax.
[laughter]
[singing in Japanese]