[thunder crashes]
- Lupin III,
you finally arrived.
- I could hardly
call myself a gentleman
if I dawdled after being
summoned.
So how about you put that
hardware away, Countess?
- There's something I need
you to do for me, Lupin.
Your reward will be this ring.
- Huh?
- You've shown up here
time and time again,
trying to get your hands
on it, and every time.
- Well, shoot.
You even had pictures
to rub my nose in it.
But isn't this ring
a Monboisont family heirloom?
Not to mention
a keepsake of your spouse?
- Three years ago
my husband, Philippe,
was killed in Paris
by an unknown assailant.
- I heard the law
got nowhere with the case,
and it wound up going cold.
- Which is why I'm still
investigating the matter.
And now I'm on the verge
of discovering his killer.
- Oh?
- I've whittled it down
to three suspects,
but it's unclear
which one did it.
[knocking]
- Your guests this evening will
be arriving shortly, madam.
- I see.
I've invited the three of them
here for the evening.
- Huh?
- And I want you
to figure out
which one of them
killed my husband.
- Oh, great.
You gotta be kidding.
- LUPIN:
Count Philippe Du Monboisont,
the man who created France's
security systems industry
from the ground up.
Nobody could deny
his brilliance.
And there were rumors
that his business
was set to break
into the political sector.
But three years ago, while out
jogging in a park in Paris,
someone took out a gun
and shot him.
Huh?
The world famous sommelier,
Frederic Ottaway,
renowned for his
collection of gemstones.
He'd apparently been trying
to pressure the count
into selling him his emerald.
Hmm.
- The Count's nephew,
Allen DuBois--
his father had a business
that went under.
And after the count refused
to help, he committed suicide,
and his family fell apart.
Allen supposedly held
a grudge
against the Count
over what happened,
though these days,
he's a successful investor.
Pierre Schmidt --
used to run a company
that developed
security systems tech.
But it was bought out by
the Count, and he was let go.
His subsequent
business ventures
didn't
get off the ground,
so he currently ekes
out a meager living
as a computer repair man.
- So you think the killer
is one of these three men?
- I'm sure of it.
- Cops aren't that useless.
They must have checked
him out, right?
- Yes, indeed.
All three of them
had perfect alibis.
- Well, that must have tied
their hands, I suppose.
- That's why I've set a trap.
- The killer had tried to pry
my husband's ring
off of his finger.
But a crowd was gathering, so
he fled before he could get it.
I've used a newly
developed chemical
to isolate the DNA
on the emerald
to find our killer.
- Really?
- I wish.
- It's a lie?
- But the bluff will
make the killer panic
and try to cover his tracks.
And then that's when I'd
like you to apprehend him.
- Oh, good grief.
What have I gotten
myself mixed up in now?
- After showing
everyone to the rooms,
tell them to assemble in
the dining hall in an hour.
- Yes, very well, madam.
- Uh...
hmm?
- The balcony is
on the brink of collapsing,
and all the doors
leading to it are locked.
I'm not the only one
who's grown fragile.
- This is quite the bold scheme
you're cooking up here,
Countess.
The killer might get
a little proactive
and try to come after
you too, you know.
Hm?
- I wouldn't worry.
This is called NZ Face--
the first commercial
facial recognition system.
If an unauthorized person
tries to enter the castle,
an alarm will sound.
- Does that include me, too?
- You're in the system.
- Whoa.
- There's also a metal detector
set up by the front door.
Weapons, of course, are
not allowed in here.
- One question, though.
Why pick a guy like me?
- My husband kept a scrapbook
to record every time
your escapades made the news.
His dream was to create a
system you couldn't circumvent.
At some point, he just
became a fan of yours.
That's why I thought
you'd be the right one
to help me avenge his death.
Well, is that
a satisfying answer?
- Mm-hmm.
- Now let us begin, hmm?
I'm terribly sorry
about the wait.
- Can you tell us what
this is all about?
- Not only that--
you haven't provided us
with a meal or a glass
of wine of any sort.
- I beg your pardon.
I'm shorthanded.
Marie is the only
staff here today.
- Oh, is that so?
- Wait, does that mean
there's no food?
- I wanted to show you
something
a little more important,
gentlemen.
- [gasps]
- Do you remember what happened
three years ago, gentlemen?
- I figured as much.
The three of us were
all suspects
in the count's murder
investigation.
I'm getting out of this place.
- You're running away?
- That's not what I meant.
- FREDERIC: Your business
got bought out,
and now you're just some
two-bit repairman.
I can only imagine how much
that must piss you off.
- PIERRE: I was drinking
at my usual bar at the time.
One of the regulars
confirmed it.
Anyway, weren't you the one who
was after the count's emerald?
- I was partying at a hotel,
and I have an alibi.
- A hotel that
was five-minute's walk
from the scene of the crime.
You were found in
the wine cellar
all by yourself, weren't you?
- FREDERIC: You've got no
right to accuse me
after he practically signed
your father's death warrant.
- ALLEN: And besides, people
testified that they saw you
at the scene of the crime.
- PIERRE: I was in Sicily
at the time.
- ALLEN: The police have
verified that it was
a case of mistaken identity.
Why would someone
with my fortune
take such a stupid risk, huh?
Not that a washed-up drunk like
you would ever comprehend that.
- What did you just say?
- There's no need
for these accusations.
I have evidence that will
now reveal the man
who murdered my husband.
The emerald will
tell us everything.
Traces of the killer's identity
were left behind on it.
Using a chemical,
I will isolate the DNA.
- What the hell?
- What happened to the lights?
[loud bang]
- What was that?
- It sounded like a gunshot!
- [scream]
- Damn it all to hell.
- It's fine, don't worry.
Lupin, you must find
the killer.
- Isabelle, this was
your plan all along?
[alarm ringing]
- Every exit out of the castle
is now sealed off
until sunrise.
Use that time
to apprehend the killer.
Your reward's on the table.
The case will open automatically
at the crack of dawn--
the case even you
couldn't crack open.
- Isabelle!
- Madame!
- ALLEN: This is absurd.
- PIERRE: The drawbridge is up.
- FREDERIC: So we're trapped
in this place?
- Please calm down, gentlemen.
The castle's on lockdown and
will remain that way 'til dawn,
as the Countess
herself requested.
- What the-- and who
are you, might I ask?
I'm Lu-- sorry,
I'm Jim Barnett,
a private eye
hired by the Countess
to catch the killer.
First off, I need to ask you
all to let me body search you.
- What?
- What did you say?
You're just some
two-bit gumshoe.
- It goes without saying.
However, including myself, there
were six of us in the castle.
And of the six, the
Countess has been murdered,
which means someone
in this room is the killer.
So the question is,
who killed the Countess?
t.
The tapes were
somehow removed,
which means there's no security
footage to look at.
- But the facial recognition
system is active.
- Yes, so if anyone
other than you, me,
and our blood thirsty trio
was in here, it'd tell us.
So where are they?
- Back in their rooms.
I've locked the door
to the dining room
so no one can go back
in there.
- I can't believe I didn't
anticipate her doing something
like this.
- Madam Isabelle
looks so peaceful.
Mr. Barnett, she must
have really trusted you.
- Just you wait, Isabelle.
So the three of them
were sitting over
by that end of the table.
A blackout,
a flash of light,
and a gunshot,
and the Countess.
First comes the weapon.
I searched all three of them,
but no one had a gun on them.
So where's the murder weapon?
- But Mr. Barnett,
how was the killer
able to know exactly where
to shoot the Countess
in complete darkness?
- Well, her wheelchair
is powered by electricity.
These lights would have
let them line up the shot.
- Hmm, oh.
That's--
I tidied up the place
before everyone entered
the dining room.
I would have
noticed if there was
this much pollen on the floor.
- Uh-huh.
Were you the one who closed
the curtains in the hall?
- No, I didn't.
The only curtains I closed
were in the dining room.
[thunder crashes]
- Hmm?
Hmm.
You greeted them
as they came in.
Is that right?
- Yes.
- And then they stayed
in their rooms?
- Yes, Mr. Frederic was
the only one who left his room.
- Was he, now?
- I ran into him in the hallway
near the stairs
to the basement.
Can I help you?
- I was hoping to take a look
at the castle's wine cellar.
- I'm sorry, but I would need
the Countess' approval.
- Fair enough.
Well, some other time, perhaps.
- So that's what happened.
Then you didn't see Allen or
Pierre outside the dining room?
- Actually, I did happen
to see Mr. Allen
while he was resting
in his room.
When I was walking
down the hallway,
his door was left ajar.
- So you can confirm that
he was in his room?
- Yes, he was staring
out of the window.
Something like this.
- What about Pierre?
- Mr. Pierre never left
his room.
- Is that right?
- I'm sorry I can't be
of more help to you.
- It's OK.
- [frightened gasp]
- Of course!
That's how he did it.
Marie, bring everyone
to the dining room.
- Why isn't Pierre here?
- Who knows.
- [laughs]
Yo.
Sorry, I dozed off for a bit.
- OK, now that we are
all gathered together--
- You've figured out
who the killer is?
- Yes, precisely.
- Oh, this should be
fun to hear.
I mean, they took any
possible weapon off us
when we entered
the castle, right?
So how'd one of us
shoot the Countess?
- The slug that
killed the Countess
had been discharged
from her own gun.
- That sounds like
complete nonsense.
- When's the last time
you saw her gun
before the shooting went down?
- I checked it while
I was in her room.
- Well, when the
two of you finally decided
to come and join us
in the dining room,
we were already here.
We couldn't have grabbed
her gun from her room
without passing by you first.
- And one more thing--
you thoroughly
patted each one of us down,
but could not
discover the murder weapon.
How do you explain that?
- The culprit started by
removing the tapes recording
the security camera footage.
After that, he just had
to wait for the right time
to cut the castle's power.
In the darkness, he used
the lights on her wheelchair
as a reference to line up
his shot and fire,
ultimately killing
the Countess.
- This is stupid.
No one could have
managed all that.
How could any of us pull that
off without anybody seeing us?
- You make a very good
point there.
None of the people
in this room
could have carried out
the murder alone.
- However, we know there's
no one else in the castle.
I think this place
has a system
that only lets in
authorized people.
- If any face is detected
that is not authorized,
an alarm will go off.
- Well, in that case--
- Turn your attention
to the flowers.
You'll note that
the rug underneath
is covered in pollen.
Apparently, this wasn't the case
before you gentlemen showed up.
- ALLEN:
What does that matter?
It doesn't take much to make
flowers spread their pollen.
- Precisely.
Accidentally brushing
past could have caused it.
But who could have
brushed past the flowers?
Considering the amount of
pollen, the person who did this
is bound to have
some on his clothes.
But none of you had any
pollen stuck to your clothing.
There's something else, too...
..the curtains on
this hallway window.
According to what
Marie said,
she only closed the curtains
in the dining room,
and the rest should
all still be open.
So who closed the curtains
out here,
and for what possible reason?
- Would you get to the point?
No one gives a damn
about this nonsense
with curtains and pollen.
You seem dead set on
blindly accusing one of us
three as the killer.
But you're not the only one
who's come up with a theory.
- Well, let's hear yours,
then.
- I may not know what kind
of big-shot detective
you're supposed to be.
But how could you possibly
leave the most suspicious person
in the room out of
the investigation?
That's right, you.
You could have slipped away
without the detective noticing,
grabbed the gun, and
stealthily put it back
where you got it from.
The pollen and the curtain
were both disturbed by you.
Yes, you did it all
so the investigation
would be disrupted
and one of us would
look like the killer.
- I wouldn't!
I would never, ever
kill Madame Isabelle.
- Probably wanted to get
your hands on her fortune.
- You're wrong.
She took me in when I had
no family of my own.
- That didn't stop you from
slipping in behind us
and, in the darkness, shooting
Madame Isabelle in cold blood
from across the table.
- No, I didn't.
I would never!
- It's all right, Marie.
Please, take your gloves
off and show them.
- Huh?
- Do you think you can
do it on your own,
or you need me to help you?
- Oh, yes.
I would appreciate
it if you would, Mr. Barnett.
- This is why the Countess
chose you out of all her staff
to work tonight.
- I accidentally burnt
my hands three days ago.
- Marie, catch.
- I'm so sorry.
- She's not pulling any
triggers with hands like that.
Now it's time
to present my theory.
What point is there in drawing
the hallway curtains shut?
The lightning flashes
posed a potential problem
for the killer, so he
decided to shut the curtain.
But why just
the hallway curtains?
Besides, the door
was closed the whole time.
- Well, the killer was worried
about a flash possibly
lighting up the room
at an inopportune time.
- When the power died?
- Yes, at that exact moment,
we were in total darkness.
- The door was open then?
- No way.
- Who could have
opened the door?
We were all sitting down then.
- It was the fourth
guest that opened it.
- But the castle's
facial recognition unit
should have stopped
any unauthorized person
from getting in.
- And yet there was
one more person
who was able to sneak in--
right, Allan?
In your room, you stood in front
of a window that opened out
onto a balcony, right?
What were you doing
so close to the window?
There was a cabinet stopping
that window from opening.
It wasn't blocking your
view, so why was it moved?
- Well, let's see--
- There's one more thing,
too.
Your car's tires seem
to struggle a bit
when they hit that patch of
mud on the way in, right?
Just like it would if you had
something big and heavy
hidden in your trunk.
- What?
What are you talking about?
- It's the same way you killed
the Count three years ago.
The last piece of
this puzzle will be revealed
when you
finally answer my question.
Why did you move the cabinet
away from the window?
- What difference
does it make?
I have an airtight alibi!
- The Countess
sacrificed her life
to find the killer's identity.
So unfortunately for you,
it would seem
that airtight alibi
has sprung a bit of a leak.
And though the cost
was too high,
her plan worked perfectly.
[gunshot]
- [frightened gasp]
- How did you--
- [grunting]
- Brother, brother!
- They're twins?
- Brother!
[sob]
- The face tech isn't
advanced enough
to pick out the subtle facial
differences between twins.
- Then what I saw was--
- That's right, it wasn't his
reflection in the glass.
It was the twins,
facing each other.
Allen must have let his
brother sneak into the house
through the window after he got
out of the trunk of the car.
- Our father was
a superstitious man
who thought twins
were bad luck,
so he put my brother up
for adoption.
After my father killed himself,
and I was left penniless,
I bumped into him again
through sheer luck.
- And you plotted revenge.
- [sobbing]
- Mr. Barnett, I thought--
- I can't imagine she'd
want to meet her husband
in the afterlife without this.
- How sweet, Mr. Barnett.
- I kind of like that name.
Maybe, when I've
got more free time,
I'll open a detective agency.
And I just might need
a trusted assistant
when the time arrives.
- Yes, be glad to.
[singing in Japanese]