- JIGEN: Dammit.
Where the hell did Lupin go?
- Do you think he could
have left the city?
- I don't know about you,
but I just can't
picture him
giving up on a score.
- Yes, I agree.
- You ready?
- This is not the time
for hesitation.
- OK, let's go.
- Who's in charge here,
Private?
- Er-- Lieutenant Pluton,
Colonel.
- [panting]
18th
Infantry Regiment,
First Lieutenant Pluton.
Um, who might that be?
- None other than the future
queen of Padar herself.
- My apologies, sir.
- [gasping]
- It's Princess Dolma.
- She must be feeling better.
- I've decided that your
regiment will accompany us
as our security detail.
We'll need protection on our
way to crown the new queen.
- Looks like we picked up some
new friends along the way.
- LUPIN: Yep, and it's all
thanks to you.
- Because of the airship?
As soon as I saw
the Shake Hands dirigible,
I set up a drone with a
smartphone attached to it.
That was what allowed me
to hack into the ship's
internal network.
They were using
a Wi-Fi download
with a range of only 10 meters
to run their network.
So they didn't bother
making it secure.
[crashing]
It was no big deal.
- That's where you're wrong.
You're much more remarkable
than you realize, you know?
- I'm remarkable?
- You sure are.
I'm starting to think I could
really use you on my crew.
- [gasps]
Thanks, I guess.
- Now then, let's go and
steal ourselves a princess.
- How haven't you still
located the king?
- What happened to the squad
that went after Lupin?
The time of Princess Dolma's
coronation is nearly upon us.
[gunfire]
- I don't care how,
but make sure the internet
stays out of action.
By order of the high priest--
[gunfire]
[grunting]
- [stammering]
- Don't shoot!
- They threatened all of us
to take down the internet.
- We're from a private
military company
hired by the Shake Hands
Corporation to rescue you.
- The Shake Hands?
- Huh?
- They want you to get
the country back online,
and make it so that
every citizen has access
to this URL.
- Huh?
Hm.
- It's the king.
- Hey, what's going on here?
- My dear citizens of Padar.
- Huh?
- This is your 45th king,
Rajahara Sinha, speaking.
Those of you out there
brandishing weapons,
who are you pointing them at?
I ask you to please
consider that.
[explosion]
- [grunts]
- Are you not pointing
your guns
at your own
fellow Padarians?
- MAN: Good gravy!
What in the world
is going on here?
- I told you there
was a civil war.
- Believe me, I noticed.
[explosion]
Fujiko?
- Hm?
Zenigata!
You came all the way here
to nab Lupin?
- Yes, of course.
I'd even wade into a war zone
to track him down.
- That's what you're
literally about to do, sir.
- Fujiko, where is Lupin?
- [stammers]
Hmph, I couldn't
care less where he is.
- [grunts]
Is that so?
What happened with you two?
- Internet access has been
re-established.
- The enemy has breached
our perimeter.
- What happened
to the 18th regiment?
They were supposed to be
our first line of defense.
- Well, sir, apparently,
the bulk of them are
on the move.
- Why's that?
- They're escorting
Princess Dolma.
- Huh? That's not--
Dolma is
in the west tower.
- MAN: You clowns are
living in the past.
You think you still need
a country to have an army.
Nations are too slow
at keeping with the times.
That's why half of them
are about to be taken
off the board.
- Enzo, is it true that half
the nations of the world
are going to vanish?
- Mm-hmm.
- I mean, what about mine?
- There's no need to worry.
It's not just the number of
countries that will reduce.
Crime, misinformation,
inequality--
all of it will be cut in half.
- That would indeed
be wonderful, but--
- It will happen.
Our People Log app is
pushing the clock forward.
And nations, economies,
kings, and master thieves
will be left behind.
- It appears as though a
significant number of subjects
are siding with the king.
- And what are the odds
that we lose?
- 50/50.
- Either way works.
- Huh?
- In our country, it is said
a sacrificial yak is needed
for any great reconciliation.
- Princess Dolma,
do you think--
- Father's reforms should pass
with little resistance now.
- Hm?
- Princess Dolma,
please come.
[beeping]
- Hm... How long has
this been hidden here?
- When in a position
of authority,
it is wise to anticipate
and plan
for every eventuality.
- Good work.
I want you all to
stand guard out here.
- Yes, sir.
- [gasps]
- This is an emergency.
I need to get past.
- Yes, I understand, sir.
Go ahead.
- Huh?
Biometric authentication?
- Is anything wrong, sir?
I'm sure you're aware
that we can't open it for you.
[beeping]
[gunfire]
- So much for tradition.
The security system they've got
here is really cutting edge.
These biometric scanners
are a real pain to defeat.
This might take a while.
- Run analysis on
the estimated response
for corneal reflex
and pupil dilation.
[beeping]
Let's go then.
- Thanks for the help, Emmy.
- It's Ami.
Hey, Lupin.
- Hm?
- Why did you steal me
back when we first met?
- Because I thought
you were valuable enough
to be worth the trouble.
- Heh...
How am I valuable?
- You're going to grow up
to be one hell of a woman.
And look at you now.
How much cooler can you get?
You're sauntering into a civil
war to bail out a friend.
- Well, she is the only
friend that I have.
- Hey, I've only got
two friends myself, I think.
- Your escape route is ready
and waiting, oh, high priest.
- Escape route?
- We still have many devout
followers in the south.
We shall carry out
Princess Dolma's coronation
at our base up there.
- Custom dictates
that we must hold the ceremony
in the palace.
And we cannot perform
the ceremony
without the bloody
teardrop necklace.
- I wouldn't worry about that.
- Are you joking?
That's clearly a fake.
- As expected, our future
queen has a sharp eye.
And yet the people will
never notice the difference.
- You would allow a forgery
to be worn at a coronation?
Are you trying to trample all
over our country's customs?
You claim to support tradition.
You're no high priest!
All you care about is
seizing power for yourself.
Isn't that right?
- Hm.
If I could, I would
have preferred
doing this as genuinely
as possible, my dear.
But Princess Dolma,
I've prepared a replacement
for you as well.
- Traitor.
- LUPIN:
You might want to put
that coronation
on hold for a sec.
- It's you!
- DOLMA:
Lupin the Third!
- Hey there, high priest.
- It's you!
It's about time for
our thieving contest.
- What is that?
- Well, you're a thief,
aren't you?
After all, you're trying
to steal this country, right?
- Huh?
[growls]
- Dolma, please come
with us right away.
- [gasps]
Ami.
- You don't deserve to be
lumped in with a creep,
like that guy.
- My, my.
Such harsh words.
You seem convinced that you
have some kind of advantage now.
I don't think so.
You've leaped headfirst into the
middle of your enemy's forces,
only to end up
as a sacrificial yak.
- Stop this!
- Oh, no.
It is my duty as a high priest
to protect our future queen.
- [quivering]
Lupin.
[slicing]
[grunting]
- Traitor!
[gunfire]
[grunting]
- JIGEN: Took you
long enough, Lupin.
- GOEMON: We were fairly certain
you would turn up here
eventually.
- Hey, it's you guys!
- We got tired of looking
for you all over town.
So we decided to wait
at the finish line.
- Wait a minute, Lupin.
Let's make a deal.
Once this country is under
our faction's control,
I can give you
any treasure you desire.
Well?
- Not a chance.
- [groans]
- You're a two-bit hustler.
You'd need to be
a proper villain.
Otherwise, even
if you took power,
you'd never really
be in control.
- Are you suggesting that also
applies to the current king?
- Well, just look
at what's happened.
Now then, I wonder
whether there's
anyone in this country who has
the chops to be a real villain.
- What's he saying?
- Lupin, aren't you
on the run
in every country in the world?
In that case,
why don't you consider
operating out of Padar?
We'll just tear up
our membership to the ICPO
and offer you protection
from them here.
You've only had a taste of the
treasures Padar has to offer--
seven types of gemstones,
solid gold necklaces.
And the women here-- hacha!
They are to die for.
Graceful, voluptuous,
and SO affectionate.
- Is that really
the high priest talking?
Ling, someone hacked and crashed
one of our airships, right?
- Underworld.
They put their name
out there on purpose.
They wanted us to find it.
- [laughs]
Look at that.
They've got a lot
of nerve, don't they?
- Director of the DCPJ.
What's your take
on this, Albert?
- Well, the coup
d'etat has failed.
As a result, the CIA
is likely to pull out.
Supporting the king's plans for
reconciliation works nicely.
- Very good.
We'll draw up a document for
the foreign minister to sign.
- You're trying to compete
with a thief like Lupin
at your level?
What an idiot.
- Lupin, just tell me
what you want.
There are things that
individuals cannot accomplish
that this state
can make happen for you,
whether that's a harem
or a safe haven.
Whatever you want!
Huh?
Ah!
Excellent timing.
These intruders broke in here
for Princess Dolma.
You must eliminate them
at once.
- Sir High Priest!
- Huh?
- Tell me, was everything
you just said true?
Were you really just
deceiving us all along?
- Huh?
Oh, no.
- LUPIN: Oh, yes.
You just spilled your
guts to the whole country
courtesy of live streaming.
- Lupin, why, you--
- Sir, answer us!
- I want you to swear
before the gods
that you weren't lying to us!
- High priest.
- Answer us, you phony!
- [laughs]
- High priest, you lied!
- And that is the end.
- Princess Dolma, have you
also betrayed your people?
- Please answer us,
Princess Dolma.
- No, Dolma wouldn't do that.
- You're right.
I was--
- High priest, as long as we
still have the royal princess,
the fight isn't over yet.
Let's escape.
- Stop this, Mac!
- The CIA still has your back.
You there!
If you want your royal
princess to live,
don't you dare move a muscle!
- Wait!
Ah-
- Go to hell!
[gunshot]
- [gasps]
Ugo!!
- Princess, are you
all right?
- Your Highness, you must
stay away from him.
- We will never let America
infest our country.
- Wait, all of you.
This man was--
- [grunts]
- Either God or the devil
will do just fine.
Someone, anybody,
please save us!
Please save this country!
- Dolma.
- The American dog
has been put down.
People of Padar,
drop your weapons at once.
The reformers
and traditionalists
are not our enemies.
The Western superpowers
who seek to devour our nation
are our foes.
- Dolma...
- Why, you little liar!
How dare you rob me of my--
[grunts]
- Oh!
- DOLMA: Padar is united.
There are no enemies here.
Stand down and come together.
- [grunts]
- It looks like somebody had the
guts to become the villain.
And I'm glad that it's her.
- LUPIN: That was pretty smooth,
Your Highness.
Though I guess
you'll be queen soon.
- Lupin the Third,
I will follow your advice
and become a ruthless
she devil.
- Sounds great to me.
I just love bad girls.
- I wonder what happened
to the other bad girl anyway.
- Don't rain on my parade, man.
- I've never agreed with
your taste in that regard.
- No fun.
- Having friends is truly
a wonderful thing.
- You'll get the opportunity
to make plenty yourself.
- Yes.
I'm sure I will.
- Dolma!
Dolma,
are you OK?
- As I said, I finally
found resolve.
- Not about that.
Well...
about Mr. Mac.
- I should probably share
a secret with you.
He was actually
my first love.
- [gasps]
Thank you for sharing
that with me.
- Honestly, I also--
- Hm.
- [giggling]
-LUPIN:
You two seemed happy.
What were you talking about?
- Romance.
- Oh.
- Ah, to be young.
- [clears throat]
- Hey, Lupin, speaking
about love--
- Hm?
- Lupin, I think that
I'm in love with you.
- Huh?
- [laughs]
- Look, Emmy, the thing is--
- After all, whenever
I'm scared or anxious,
your face is always the first
thing that comes to my mind.
If I draw a conclusion
based on that,
the most logical conclusion
is that I'm in love with you.
- But I don't think love
is one of those things
that you can analyze logically.
- When the day comes that I am
a better woman than Fujiko Mine,
I shall require an answer.
All right?
- All right.
I'll be waiting.
- Are you sure you want to pass
on this chance to arrest me?
- What exactly happened
between you and Lupin?
- What, are you thinking about
joining the gossip biz?
- It's part
of the investigation.
- I guess.
Just tell me, Lupin,
what am I to you anyway?
- Fujiko, you've always
been my--
[crashing]
- [grunting]
- I'm sorry, but I'm taking
the bloody teardrop.
- He ran away, again.
- Well, he is a thief,
after all.
- [giggles]
- What?
It's rude to laugh when you're
having a serious conversation,
you know.
- Sorry.
Zenigata, you're
really a good guy.
- I'm just doing
my job.
- [laughs]
See you!
Thanks for yesterday.
- Fujiko, how do you
really feel about him?
- I hate him!