Let’s find Lupin, the
greatest thief of our time.
There’s is only one rule.
Look at that.
You’re caught in quite
an interesting game.
Look at that.
You’re caught in quite
an interesting game.
I see.
So this makes everyone
in the world a cop now.
[LAUGH]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[TYPEWRITER]
I guess this means that
we’re celebrities now, huh?
There they are.
It’s the cops.
Lupin’s right over here.
Whoa!
Run for it!
Get those cruisers
over here right now!
I’ll take responsibility!
Hold on tight!
Right.
Left.
Whoa!
On it!
Left.
Right.
Left
Left.
Right.
Emmy, I need info on all
the off-limits areas.
It’s Ami.
Well, hello, underworld.
Airplane forum, the
threat on airports.
Well, since we’re
already at the airport,
we might as well steal
a plane that we can use.
Out of the way, people!
The runway’s through that door!
Ah!
Zenigata must have somehow
figured out our plan.
What now?
Then let’s go for plan B.
Emmy, what’s the quickest
way to a parking garage?
Lupin’s in the Western
parking garage.
Is he planning on
stealing a car to escape?
Yata, we’re heading
back to the car.
Inspector, wait!
Lupin, what about this one?
Nah.
Let’s take that one!
Not your usual style.
Since when do you care
about the environment?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Look at that!
Oh!
We will now continue
with general boarding
at gate eight--
Lupin, you’re not getting away.
Stop right there.
We’ve got the
airport on lockdown.
If you move now and
clear the runway,
you’ll be playing right
into Lupin’s hands.
It’s Zenigata.
Hm?
Why does a cop get
off breaking the speed
limit like that, I wonder?
[GRUNT]
Told you we should have gone
with that tougher-looking one
instead of the electric!
Hold it!
Huh?
Ah!
Hm.
Ah?
Don’t mess with me!
Goemon?
Heading straight for the
sea, he’s trapped like a rat.
Yeah, we’ll see.
There’s a special kind of
aircraft in that hanger.
What an odd looking vehicle.
It’s an AW-609.
And those tilt rotors mean
it doesn’t need a runway.
Impressive work, finding this.
All I did was ask an internet
forum for airplane nerds.
Took less than five minutes
before I got a reply.
No crowds or paparazzi
in here, either.
Looks like they
cut the damn power.
[BEEP]
Here’s the display scan
of the flight manual.
It seems like the main engine
needs electricity to start.
Makes sense.
And we’ve been cut off
from the mainlines.
But isn’t fuel enough
to get it up in the air?
Most of these kinds of aircrafts
require a significant amount
of externally-sourced
electricity
to start up their
engines before takeoff.
Whoa!
Look at that!
A samurai?
Is he bringing a
sword to a gunfight?
Impossible!
How’d he do it?
He’s using the battery
from the electric car?
Yeah.
He must have planned it.
Hop on, Goemon!
Lupin game players,
I bid farewell!
Don’t think you’ve
gotten away with it.
This is just the
first round, Lupin.
[LAUGH]
There it is, everyone!
Look!
We found the plane
Lupin used to escape!
There’s over 100 million
people playing the Lupin game.
That’s more than the entire
population of France.
That’s right.
They were even talking about
it on the radio earlier.
You’re a superstar!
You do know they’re
after you too, right?
What?
Find Daisuke Jigen. As Lupin’s
lover, wherever he goes,
Lupin will be close by.
What the hell?
Who’s lover?
Hey, don’t you back
away from me like that!
Here.
What?
Since we’re having hotpot,
why don’t you join us, Emmy?
Its Ami.
The only two necessities
in life are speed and data.
From procuring all the
necessary ingredients, including
washing all of the dishes, most
meals take up to three hours.
This, however, takes 10 seconds.
As you can see here, it’s
more nutritionally balanced,
as well.
If you break it down in
terms of the amount of time
it takes to get sustenance,
this is 3000% more efficient.
Life, itself, isn’t
very efficient, my dear.
You frigging vultures!
Aren’t you both Japanese?
Eat some of the tofu, would you?
Sheesh!
So what’s the plan?
Are we going to
lay low for a bit?
Not at chance!
I’m not going to take this
kind of treatment lying down!
Not at chance!
I’m not going to take this
kind of treatment lying down!
Does that mean you have a plan?
You bet!
An eye for an eye, as they say.
Hey, Lupin’s finally
appeared online.
You verified this?
Be careful you don’t get
tricked by some prank.
Well, the thing is, Lupin
confirmed his account.
The name’s Lupin III.
And I’m the world’s
greatest master thief.
I heard you guys
are looking for me.
So I’ve decided to grace
you with my presence.
Hello, are you who
I think you are?
Hello, actually, we’re on
our honeymoon together.
And well, if you don’t
mind, can I shake your hand?
It’s your honeymoon?
Oh, you bet!
And why don’t we all take
a picture together too?
I even do autographs.
What’s your name?
Robert?
Where are you from, Robert?
Is that Robert with an R?
Excuse me, Mr.
Samurai, would you
mind taking a picture of us?
I need to press
this button, right?
The thing is, Goemon,
dearest, that’s
the dial for changing
the shooting mode.
And you’ve got the
camera backwards.
There you go.
Got it now.
Let’s get going, inspector.
There’s no point, Yata.
But we can finally get him!
If we let him get away
with showboating like this,
it’ll destroy our reputation!
[GRUNT]
Yata, look closer
at the picture.
The ship’s heading for Bwanda.
And the Republic of Bwanda
isn’t a member of the ICPO.
As long as he stays
there, Lupin’s
out of our jurisdiction.
What a cutey!
This paradise is
full of beauties!
I’m in heaven!
You know, lately, it seems
like my wife’s obsessed
with another man, these days.
She’s head over
heels for him, 24/7.
So here’s Lupin, who’s
being tracked by the nation,
spamming people with
info on where he is.
That should take all the fun
out of trying to track me down.
And in time, boredom
will get to them.
Once everyone’s found a new toy,
they’ll forget all about little
old me.
Is it really that simple?
In the end, people just
don’t care that much
about other people.
Well, in the meantime,
we’ll enjoy ourselves here.
[LAUGH]
That smug bastard,
acting like he’s got
the whole world in his hands!
What do you mean?
Huh?
Heh, I get it.
It’s time to sink everything
that we’ve got left into this.
Oh, the Lupin game seems
to have come to an end.
Well, it’s not much fun
tracking someone down
if they tell you where they are.
People only enjoy the chase when
they see someone running away.
Aren’t you the
same, Fujiko Mine?
No lingering regrets
regarding Lupin III?
I’m not sure what rumors
you might have heard.
Lupin and I are nothing but
professional colleagues.
[PHONE BUZZING]
Oh.
Is that the Lupin game?
It’s not that fun anymore.
I know what you mean, dude.
That guy’s always at
the top of the rankings.
It would be nice if
something different happened.
Even if it did, it’d
probably be a hoax.
Who cares as long as it’s fun?
The problem is when it’s boring.
[LAUGHTER]
Tonight’s dinner
is wild venison.
It’s a shame I’m dining with
this bearded old geezer instead
of a beautiful lady, though.
Hey, don’t drag me into this.
How awfully cold of you!
And here I thought we
had something special.
Quit screwing around,
you little jerk!
We’re just co-workers!
Would it have killed you
to have said we’re friends?
We’re just co-workers!
Would it have killed you
to have said we’re friends?
[BEEP]
Oh, here we go.
What is it?
Emmy’s finished doing the
thing I asked her to do.
Hm?
Hey, now!
I’ve got a runaway
to track down!
Right, good luck.
Do you know where
you’re going, babe?
We can show you
around, if you’d like.
No, I’ve got directions.
Well, we know this killer
club that’s not online.
Yeah, you want to come with us?
Why wouldn’t they
be on the internet?
Did they just open up?
Are they members
only, or even legal?
Well, if you’d just
shut up and let me--
He made it up.
Who said that?
Just get lost, old man.
They don’t allow anyone over 30.
Hey, you guys, that’s Lupin III!
Lupin, the guy from
that internet game?
Quit acting like a hotshot
just ’cause you went viral!
[GRUNT]
You Bastard!
[GRUNTING]
Is that all you--
You shouldn’t mess
with grown ups, boys.
I’m Lupin III.
And I’m not just some
stupid celebrity.
I’m a thief.
And I’m not just some
stupid celebrity.
I’m a thief.
And that means,
sometimes, I steal lives.
[CLICK]
[SIGH]
If you’re not prepared to
finish what you’ve started,
then why even bother
trying, chump?
Huh?
Why did you come after me?
I should be asking the
questions, here, saying goodbye
out of the blue like that.
As promised, you stole me away.
And I gave you backdoor
access to Marco Polo.
Our contract has now ended.
There’s no reason for
us to stay together.
I happen to be
the type of person
who takes good care
of the things I steal.
That’s not true.
I saw the condition of
your loot at the villa.
It didn’t look like you were
taking care of it at all.
Well, yeah, you got me there.
Why didn’t you just leave
me at the airport in France?
Well, it just kind
of ended up that way.
Why do you let me
stay in your room?
I asked you to do a job for me.
There are other
hackers out there.
[BUZZING]
Given what’s happened
since we’ve met,
I can only assume that you
just want me to accompany you.
Well, you know, deductive
reasoning like that
can only lead to theories.
So I dug a little deeper.
Hm?
I’ve been implanted
with a tracking device.
Really?
Well, who did that to you?
Someone who knew
my exact location
and pursued me to
no end, you see.
And that’s why you
wanted to leave?
It was the most efficient
and logical thing to do.
Conclusion, Lupin
III is protecting me.
Answer.
[SIGH]
Some things, like
flowers, that are beautiful,
are better left untouched.
Some things, like
flowers, that are beautiful,
are better left untouched.
Flowers?
It’s a Japanese saying.
Yes, hello, underworld.
You don’t have to look it up.
What I’m trying to say is--
it’d be lame if I said it.
Do you want to have
sex with me, Lupin?
No!
Hm?
You got the wrong idea.
If I left you on
your own, can’t you
see that Marco Polo would
continue to chase you
to the ends of the earth?
I just want to keep you
safe until things calm down.
Ah, just forget about it.
I still don’t understand
what you mean.
To be honest, I don’t
either, anymore.
Hm?
Speak of the devil himself.
Marco Polo have finally
made their move.
Bringing in hit men,
talk about low tech, huh?
His hotels and
restaurants, he even
posts when he’s taking
a bath and going to bed.
You’d be hard pressed to find
a target that makes it easier
to track them down.
Let’s take that truck.
You’re... Shinpei Mayama?
Whoa!
I recognize you.
Not your face, but your MO
is pretty infamous...
The Flea.
[LAUGH]
This might be tough on my own.
Very impressive, Goemon.
You people or with the union?
Captain Bone and Guardsman,
it’s just like the assassin
all-stars are out tonight.
In other words, it’s a
betting pool where gamblers
bet on when people will die.
It would be one thing if
they were terminally ill.
But there’s no sense in
guessing when somebody will die.
For a game like this, there
are some ways to beat the odds.
Wait, you mean--
If you were to kill
them on the day
you placed your bet, that
would count as a correct guess,
right?
I think it’s rather convenient
that this website accepts
untraceable digital
currency, huh?
It’s a game totally
free of danger or risk
on my end, Lupin III.
Emmy, get back.
And don’t even think
about thanking me.
See, I’m protecting you
because...
I love being the kind
of guy who does that.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]