[theme music]
[interposing voices]
[humming]
Hey, you’re meant to sing that
song before New Year’s Day,
not on it.
Hm.
Don’t be such a
stickler for detail.
Weren’t you the one who
wanted to celebrate New Year’s
properly for once?
Or am I going crazy?
It is ready.
Huh?
Red beans for mochi, huh?
Looks good.
You’ve got it all wrong, Goemon.
The paste is supposed
to be smooth.
No.
True bean paste
is always coarse.
I like mine chunky,
to be honest.
[metal ringing]
Huh?
Coin?
No, a medal.
Did you guys forget already?
Hm?
This is from the
Pablo collection.
I’m talking about
the Pablo collection.
Huh?
You mean that drug kingpin?
Thing is, Lupin, Pablo
was getting on in years.
And no one’s seen him
since his disappearance.
Even the existence of such a
collection is just a rumor.
That sounds more like
whining from saps
who weren’t good enough to
find it in the first place.
Huh?
Satellite pics?
Get a load of this.
P-A-B-L-O-- Pablo.
And there you have it.
Now things tend to
get kind of hairy
in that part of South America.
It sure would be handy to have
a big strong fellow like Goemon
helping me out.
Understood.
Hm.
No need to ask any questions
that has obvious answers,
you know?
That settles it, which leaves--
Lupin.
[giggling]
[sigh]
Hello.
Here I am.
Fujiko?
Hey, why in the hell
is she coming with us?
Well, it slipped my tongue and
she insisted on tagging along.
Eh?
Hm.
[groan]
This is the last stop
before we hit the jungle.
Make sure you buy whatever
you’re going to need.
Where’s Fujiko?
Just getting some
intel from the locals.
Say, is there any
map of the area
you could maybe let me have?
There is no maps.
Cartels get mad.
The jungle is their home turf.
But I’m just a little tourist.
I’ve got nothing
to do the cartels.
Well, what they don’t
know won’t hurt anything.
Thank you!
[giggling]
Looks like the feminine power
of a woman and her cleavage
knows no boundaries.
Your drinks are
on the house also.
Really?
You bet.
You’re such a sweetheart.
Woah!
Jeez, couldn’t we have
just chartered a boat?
Unfortunately, that
wasn’t an option.
We had international
affairs to consider.
The Pablo collection is at
the very edge of the jungle.
Hm?
But recently
Borozil and Baraguay
have staked claims
on a nearby lake--
Lake El Alkele, which
means any river travel
invites a lot of
scrutiny from both sides.
So traveling over land is safer.
Hm, heh heh heh.
Everything safe here too?
Behave, Lupin.
Aw.
Hey-- whoa!
[gasp]
Fuji-cakes!
I’m trying to
thrive here, honey.
You--
Oh, I think I see more
potholes up ahead.
[gasp]
Oh, how dangerous.
Hey!
Stop that!
[giggling]
[grunt]
Potholes, Fuji-cakes-- potholes.
Come on, now.
Try to keep it in
your pants, man.
You’re heavy, Jigen.
[humming]
Hey, no peeking, Lupin.
I’ll be sitting here waiting.
Woof woof!
That explains why she brought
so much water with her.
What are you doing?
I shall train.
I get where you’re coming from.
[shivering]
Lupin!
What’s up?
We’re going to go stretch
our legs for a bit--
[whimpering]
--so hold the fort, OK?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Heh.
Say, Lupin.
Who were those people
in the village?
Ah!
[groan]
You noticed them, huh?
Sure did.
Probably some of
Pablo’s old cronies.
Last I heard, the
Pablo cartel disbanded.
All the more reason for them
to get the gang back together
and chase after his fortune
or something like that.
Hm.
Ah!
What the-- Fujiko!
You think you got him?
Yeah, I’m sure of it.
Hey stay.
Sharp there were more of
them just a minute ago.
[gunshot]
Woah!
[groan]
There they are.
It’s Lupin’s gang!
Over here!
Come on, guys!
Light him up!
[interposing voices]
Whoa!
Retreat!
Pull back for now.
Are you OK, Fujiko?
Oh, really.
I saw that ambush
coming a mile away.
Let’s move.
Jigen and Goemon are out there.
So no need to worry.
Oh?
[groaning]
[slam]
Damn!
To hell with that guy.
We should just give up.
There’s no way we can
even beat them now.
Not by ourselves, at least.
Hm?
This village has a
phone, doesn’t it?
Get Commander Gomez of the
Borozilian Navy on the line.
Uh!
I’m tired!
That’s what you get for
wearing heels in the jungle.
Oh!
I don’t want to hear that from a
man who wears the same suit all
the time.
This suit’s a tropical weight
made of breathable whole cloth.
Oh, Fuji-cakes?
Should I give you a
piggyback ride now?
No.
Hm.
Not with that look in your eye.
Over here.
Hm?
Oh!
A submarine, huh?
Seems awfully small to me.
A Kittredge K-350.
You couldn’t ask
for a better ride
if you’re trying
to get somewhere
without people noticing.
Hm?
I wonder what goodies
are in Pablo’s stash.
No clue, but they
say Pablo was making
seven billion bucks a day in the
drug trade back in his heyday.
How did he spend all that dough?
Maybe he saved some.
[gasping]
Hm.
[grunting]
Well, ain’t that’s
something else?
Did you find the collection?
Yeah.
Pablo old pal?
You’ve got one hell
of a collection.
These are--
Yep.
This is the one and
only Pablo Collection.
Get a load of this--
a Bugatti type 57 tank.
A Delahay 175 S-Roadster.
Damn, he’s even got
a Rolls-Royce 15HP.
This is amazing.
It’s quite the car show.
Hm.
And they’re in such
good condition.
I get the feeling
me and their owner
would get along just fine.
This is stupid.
They all look like a
bunch of giant toy cars.
No, not at all, Fuji-cakes.
Sell these to the
right enthusiast
and they’ll net you a tidy sum.
How much?
That one?
About 2.5 mil.
And that one, I couldn’t
even guesstimate.
[gasp]
You should’ve said so sooner.
So how do we get
them out of here?
Now hold your horses.
We should--
[engine revving]
Who’s there?
[grunt]
[engine revving]
[grunting]
Look out!
You!
What the hell?
Pretty sure I aimed
for the tires.
Then it would appear
it is my turn now.
[grunting]
But that’s--
Ha ha!
Looks like your luck
is as bad as mine.
In that case, how about
a race instead? hm?
Fujiko, get the checkered flag.
Huh?
[revving]
Lupin?
What flag?
Hm.
[revving]
Not bad.
[engine roaring]
Huh?
Ah!
Gr.
[sighing] That was brutal.
What was he thinking?
Hm?
Do you see anything?
It’s the name.
Huh?
The Pablo carved
out of the jungle
was actually a race track.
Hm.
Hm?
You having fun?
So am I.
Hm?
Hmph.
[gasp]
Huh?
Who crossed the
finish line first?
Lupin, obviously.
What a nice ride.
You took good care of your
cars, drug kingpin Pablo.
Hm.
Hm?
Wait, I don’t get it.
What’s-- what’s happening?
Hm?
You can see for yourself.
The spell finally wore off.
What about the collection?
If you take it to
a scrap yard, you
might get 500 bucks out of it.
[gasp] No!
But-- but not every single
one of them is scrap, right?
Gah!
[laughter]
That being said, I’ll be
taking this, Senor Pablo.
Huh?
Hm?
What the?
What now?
[squeal]
Those are battleship’s guns.
Has to be.
Why would the Navy be after us?
[explosion]
Uh!
There is no shame in
fleeing when all else fails.
Hey, don’t worry.
We’re just trying to scare them.
More importantly, you’ve
confirmed its existence--
the Pablo collection, right?
Lupin and his gang are here.
You can rest assured
that it’s real.
You didn’t mention that
I was shooting at Lupin.
I think we’re looking
at a 70/30 split here.
If 50-50’s not good enough--
Huh?
--I can always report
you to your superiors.
I’ll just tell your brass that
you went after the collection
yourself.
Gr!
We may be crooks, but we tend
to take these types of deals
very seriously, Commander.
[explosion]
Can’t we just tell them
the collection’s a bunch
of scrap or something?
No, it’s not just mere scrap.
It’s got sentimental value.
And besides, it’s not like they
would believe us even if we
could get a message to them.
So what are we
going to do, then?
Whoa!
Because there’s no way.
I’m not taking on an army.
It’ll be fine.
Huh?
See?
Yes, we could
travel under water.
Well, can you make it go?
It’s been kept in
really good shape.
The only thing missing
is a beautiful stewardess
to round out this little voyage.
Do you really need one
if I’m going in there?
Unfortunately, there is
one problem with that.
Oh!
Fuji-cakes, how heavy are you?
That’s not the sort of
question you ask a lady.
Hey, you want to save the
flirting for after we’ve
made our escape?
The thing is, guys,
this thing was
built for two
people, maybe three
if you don’t mind it
being a bit cramped.
Which means--
Well, then they do say
ladies first, after all.
Uh?
In my country, there
is no such saying.
Lupin!
If you hadn’t brought
Fujiko along with us,
we could have all gotten
into that submarine.
Oh, quit whining.
Let’s just keep it impersonal
and draw lots, shall we?
I will not.
Hm?
I have no doubt that you have
somehow tampered with the lots.
Where’s the trust?
Then how about rock,
paper, scissors?
Hm?
The winner takes all.
Very well.
I’m throwing scissors.
So you guys all throw paper, K?
K!
Ready?
Rock, paper--
Hey, time out.
But we were just about to start.
Sorry.
I need to go tinkle.
Huh?
You know that submarines and
leaks don’t go together, right?
I can’t hold it any longer.
Just go, will ya?
[explosion]
--pee, gotta pee, gotta
pee, gotta pee, gotta pee,
gotta pee.
Let’s see now.
Hm?
Huh, cut off by land,
sea, and air, are we?
So be it, then.
I figure I’m just about the only
guy in the world who could make
it out of this kind of mess.
Oh, if I can disguise
myself as one of them,
this might actually work.
Over there!I It’s Lupin’s gang!
What?
[gasp]
[slashing]
That makes eight.
Gah!
Goemon, it’s me!
Lupin!
What are you doing here?
Shouldn’t I be the
one asking you that?
You can search the
world over and find
no man capable of breaking
through a siege of this scale
other than myself.
You stupid samurai!
[gunfire]
[panicking]
Shoot!
Keep them back!
Gah!
Yeah, I figured I’m just
about the only guy who
can beat odds like this.
Look, it’s Jigen.
SOLDIER: Over there!
A marksman making chitchat.
How foolish.
You’re going to say that to me
after I just saved your asses?
Just go away!
I was going to be heroic
and self-sacrificial.
The two of you should leave now.
I shall be the one
to handle this.
Why don’t you just go
and run off with Fujiko!
Are you two hard of hearing?
Say that again!
I will, then!
Why don’t--
[interposing voices]
Hey!
We’re talking here.
Keep it down, you jerks.
Why don’t we force them
to shut up instead?
Agreed.
Hmph.
[battle cry]
And after all that
fuss, he still
chose his friends over me.
Uh?
Oh!
[gasp]
Oh no!
Oh!
Oh, Lupin!
You dummy!
[sneeze]
It’s already been a week.
I’m pretty sure this
is the rendezvous spot.
I’m the only one who showed up.
Oh man.
That bit with the
bridge was really tough.
Huh?
Who’d have thought they’d
have a tank waiting for us?
Yeah, I was really freaking
out when it showed up.
There is no telling what would
have become of us if you hadn’t
made the right call, Lupin.
It only happened thanks
to you, master Goemon.
I know I told you
to do it, but I
didn’t think he’d be able
to slice through a tank.
Then after all that, I
thought we were really screwed
when that chopper showed up.
Yeah, I thought we were goners.
Yes, as did I.
Wait, we all thought that?
[laughter]
Men can be so
immature sometimes.
Gah!
Hot!
I have the best
pals in the world.
You’re not so bad yourself.
Time really flies.
How long has it been
since that escapade?
I don’t even want
to think about it.
There is one thing I
feel needs addressing.
What’s that?
If my memory serves
me right, when
the battle grew truly fierce,
Jigen was the first to flee.
[growl]
It was not me!
It was Lupin!
Don’t worry, grandpa.
Your memories must be
all jumbled up again.
Hey, you’re not that much
younger than me, you know.
Would you quit acting like--
There is absolutely
no doubt in my mind.
Let’s just chalk it up
to your twilight years
dimming your memory.
You shut the hell up!
I am positive.
You two--
Ji--
--need to shut up!
[japanese singing]