[Music playing]
[snoring]
[pounding]
[sigh]
[snoring]
Fuji cakes.
[gasp]
[thud]
What-- what the-- what?
Hey, there, Lupin.
What?
The can's not working at all.
(SINGING)You broke the toilet.
You broke the toilet.
The toilet was busted
already when I went in there.
Uh huh.
What is it you're saying?
Hey, Goemon.
Were you already awake?
I just woke up.
It seems like something
got really stuck
in the toilet's sewage pipe.
I tried poking around with
some chopsticks, but no luck.
We're out of options.
My chopsticks?
You bet.
One of your disposable pairs.
But that was my favorite pair.
Then why not learn
to use a fork?
The plumber should
be here soon, right?
I wouldn't count on it.
They say the handymen here
like to take their sweet time.
So what do we do?
Well--
[scuffling]
I'm going to use yours instead.
Hey, it's my room.
I get to go first.
You just went, didn't you?
I still need to go.
Hold it.
No leaving the room
without a disguise.
That's the rule.
When we leave the
hideout, we make
sure we're disguised as a pair
of charming middle aged guys.
I'm just going to my
room downstairs, man.
It's precisely in those moments
that you walk face first
into trouble, you know.
I'm really going
to miss this place.
And, of course, you're
covering the moving costs.
Damn it all.
I'm going first.
Son of a--
How is it?
I don't know how you can
see where you're going.
Perfect.
Hey, it's me.
Open the door, will you?
Hello?
You there?
[knocking on door]
Huh?
What's wrong?
This jerk locked
the door behind us.
I tried to get in, and he
just said, identify yourself.
Caution is a virtue.
You're just mad
about the chopsticks.
You child.
What now?
Just buy him some
more later, Lupin.
Anyway, what are we
going to do for food?
Want to eat out somewhere?
Uh, well, I'd like
to, but we don't know
when the plumber's showing up.
What can we cook?
Japanese food.
Going to eat with your hands?
Hey, please don't start
fighting again, children.
What about takeout sushi?
I don't think there's a place
near here that delivers.
Why would you choose such
an unsuitable hideout?
Because sushi isn't a priority.
Well, if I remember correctly,
the first floor cafe
has Japanese
cuisine on the menu.
You mean the one run by
that young married couple?
I heard the owner say he needed
buckwheat flour, the kind you
use for soba noodles.
Oh, going to the restaurant?
Yes, I shall go on my own.
Hey, now.
Where's your disguise?
I came in without one.
It should be all right.
Hey, if you get
spotted on the way out,
it means you can't come
back until you shake it.
At least throw this on.
It's perfect.
Now, you could pass
for our granddaughter.
[laughter]
Your minds are feeble.
Uh, are you sure they
have Japanese food?
I'm positive.
There wasn't any.
Come on.
They must have had something.
Did you bother asking?
Yes.
I asked for the dish that was
made with buckwheat flour.
And they gave it to you.
So what did they give you?
You're actually quite
the show off, huh?
[crinkling]
It looked like this.
Oh, yeah.
The galettes.
Those things are pretty tasty.
They are.
So you liked it?
But it was not Japanese food.
But it was tasty, right?
It was good, but you lied.
I'm going to go back to my room.
Now what?
Let me use your bathroom first.
What the hell is wrong with you
always needing to go when I do?
Take turns.
What do you expect?
We always eat at the same time.
Do you need to go, too?
It is my turn now.
Rock, paper, scissors.
[groaning]
Morning.
[yawning]
What?
Fujiko.
[knocking on door]
What is it?
Buzz off.
The toilet's busted.
Do we-- have a bucket anywhere?
Is it really too much to ask
to put up an out of order sign?
When did you get here, Fujiko?
You let me in last night, Lupin.
Did I, now?
But you were
extremely intoxicated.
This new hideout's
actually quite charming.
Yeah.
Would you like to make
it your hideout, too?
If she moves in,
then I'm moving out.
With floorboards this thick,
you probably won't hear a thing.
That's the very least
of my worries right now.
[groaning]
Why the hell did she come here?
Don't know.
To celebrate us moving in?
And she sneaks in
unnoticed to do this?
She says I let
her in last night.
Well, did you, Lupin?
I honestly don't
remember a thing.
Guys, I can't breathe.
It's suspicious.
What's suspicious?
Put some clothes on.
I'm wearing some.
Wow.
What a nice view.
Hey.
What are you scheming now?
[phone ringing]
Hey, give me a sec, you guys.
Hello there.
Are you the plumber?
What?
You can't make it for a while?
Well, that's no good.
Yeah, something in
the drainage pipe.
Right.
It connects the
tank to the commode.
What are you doing, Fujiko?
What are you doing
letting a total stranger
into your hideout?
You're getting careless, Lupin.
Says an infiltrator
to our hideout.
Well, now.
It's inconvenient not
being able to use the can.
Then I'll just use the one
in Jigen's room instead.
That's not happening.
Well, I need a shower.
The toilet's broken, but
there's still hot water.
With a reaction like that,
Fujiko's hiding something.
Yeah.
When I peeked in on her, I
heard her talking on the phone.
[immitating a child's voice]
Mr. Handyman,
the toilet's working
now, so don't come over.
But grampy said
to say thank you.
What age is she going for?
So she's the granddaughter now?
For some reason, she doesn't
want anyone in that bathroom.
The stuff about taking
a shower was a cover.
What do you think she
could be hiding in there?
Who knows?
But it's gotta be some
kind of small object.
Huh?
In the toilet's water tank.
She snuck in yesterday
without us noticing
and tried to hide
something away in there.
And now, it's stuck in the pipe.
Something dangerous?
Could be loot.
I agree with
something dangerous.
Yeah.
Well, either way, I
don't like the fact
that she's trying
to hide it from us.
Hey, maybe she wanted it
to be a surprise, huh?
Maybe one that goes boom.
You think explosives?
With Fujiko, you can't
rule out anything.
Go ask her what's up, Jigen.
Why do I have to do it?
Because I got a hangover.
Fujiko's your problem, not mine.
All right.
I'll do it, OK?
I need to use the can.
You're going to talk
to Fujiko first.
Gotta go.
Very well then.
Just be sure to be subtle.
[knocking on door]
Fujiko, what have you
hidden in our toilet?
I said subtle.
Goemon!!
[gasp]
I've got nothing
to hide from you.
[giggling] Wow.
Would it kill you to
have a little modesty?
Well now.
Maybe I should go
shower myself, huh?
Please wait, Lupin.
[giggling]
You can't wait any
longer, either?
Right.
Want to play strip Old Maid?
You bet.
Wrapped around
her little finger.
Hm.
This one.
Guest I win again, Lupin.
Rats.
Come on, now.
Take 'em off.
Huh?
Where are you going, Jigen?
I need to dry my hair,
so no peeking, boys.
She's holed up in
the bathroom again.
I guess that means
she still hasn't
been able to recover her stash.
Something smells great.
What are you doing here?
I asked the cafe owner to
give me some buckwheat flour.
Soba?
I shall empty my mind.
You must have really
struck a nerve back there.
Yeah.
Must have.
What's the miso for?
They did not have soba broth.
What?
You're eating them
with miso soup?
So how long must this stand?
Do you have to let
soba noodles stand?
No!
Fujiko staying.
We still have no idea what
she is doing in that bathroom.
Why do you not
force her out, as is
your right as the tenant
of this apartment?
You think she's actually
going to listen to that?
Well, you are Goemon, after all.
Chase her out.
I have that right?
Mhm.
You don't want to do it?
Hey, Lupin.
Do you have anything
long and thin?
Something long and thin?
Nope.
Even some chopsticks would do.
We have none.
What's his problem?
Fujiko, what exactly do you need
something long and thin for?
That's none of your business.
Aw, but Fujiko.
He seriously doesn't remember.
[doorbell buzzing]
[clearing throat]
Yeah.
Wonder who that could be.
Lupin, the bathroom.
ZENIGATA: Bonjour.
Sorry to bother you, sir.
The name's Zenigata.
LUPIN: How can I help you?
Well, I was in the
area and smelled
a wonderful bowl of
miso soup, and I found
myself attracted to the scent.
A truly wondrous smell.
And I haven't had Japanese
food in such a long time.
LUPIN: They don't even sell
sushi around these parts.
Mhm.
Precisely what I mean.
[stomach growling]
[laughter]
Please pardon me, sir.
That was just my
stomach growling.
Well, just hang on a second.
I'll let you in, sonny.
Oh, thank you.
You're far too kind.
You'll have to
forgive the mess, sir.
Not at all.
[slurping]
You've been very kind.
Hot!
Could he have somehow
tracked us down?
Even if it was just luck, he's
got a sharp nose in more ways
than one.
Lupin.
[gasp]
Ever hear that name before, sir?
No.
Can't say that I have.
Well, when I say Lupin,
I mean Lupin III.
It's possible you might not
have heard of him around here.
Oh, you mean Lupin III.
Yeah, even out here in the
sticks, we know that name.
I heard he's some
horrid master crook who
can swipe just about anything.
[laughter]
Not exactly, sir.
It's true that he's a criminal
and should be behind bars,
but he's more than that.
I believe he's a better man than
just your average lawbreaking
scumbag.
Huh...
Oh, pops.
Huh?
I-- I mean since
you popped in, would
you like some soba noodles?
Soba noodles?
I'd love some.
[sigh]
I can't believe you
invited him in here to eat.
If I just told him
to leave instead,
it would've made him
even more suspicious.
Make sure he doesn't hang
around here once he's done.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Is it OK if I use your bathroom?
The bathroom?
The toilet's unfortunately
broken right now.
Oh, I see.
Then I'll have to
check downstairs.
Hey, uh, somebody else in there?
Well--
I'd love to say hello.
No.
Best not.
But sir--
He's incredibly shy.
A bit of a shut in,
if I'm being honest.
If he saw you, inspector, it'd
be too much for his poor heart
to handle.
I see what you mean.
I don't think I mentioned
that I was a police inspector.
[gulp]
Well, everyone
who's heard of Lupin
knows Inspector Zenigata
is hot on his tail.
Oh, sure.
That makes sense.
Boy, that's embarrassing.
He'll be back soon, you know.
Just don't let him back in.
I can't do that,
and you know it.
What if he realizes who you are?
We run.
Yeah, that sounds good to me.
Huh?
Fujiko.
Worried about the thing you've
got stashed in the toilet?
Whatever are you talking about?
Come on, Fujiko.
Huh?
I'm not trying to say I
want in on the action.
I'll hide it if it's important.
If it's dangerous, I'll
help you deal with it.
You really can't tell me?
Well, the thing is--
I'll be right back.
And where are you going?
The bathroom.
Hm?
The bathroom, OK?
I need to use the bathroom.
We can't trust you
to go in there alone.
And why not?
I need to go.
Let me use the
bathroom in your room.
Want me to pee on the floor?
Well, that's always an option.
Idiot.
All right.
I get it already.
Hurry it up.
Is that really how
someone asks for a favor?
Just please.
Will you?
It's rare to hear
her say please.
He'll pay for that later.
[sigh]
OK.
Now's our chance.
Sensei, take care of it.
Cut it open.
[splashing]
I will not.
How come?
It's unworthy.
Are you saying you see no worth
in having a working toilet?
[doorbell ringing]
Hello.
I've finally returned.
[sigh]
That was fast.
Should I--
No cutting.
What should I do, then?
Get the soba noodles ready.
I understand.
Let's do it.
Yes.
Just give me a second.
[gasp]
I'm done for the day.
You can come out now.
Did Zenigata notice
anything unusual?
However, I do think I did
a fine job with the soba.
Yeah.
(IMITATING INSPECTOR
ZENIGATA) I've
had udon noodles and miso
before, but never soba.
It's truly delicious.
That's what he said.
What's this?
Huh?
Huh.
[sniffing]
So did Zenigata finally leave?
Hey.
Nice job earlier.
Where is Fujiko?
She didn't come back?
What?
[running]
Damn it.
She made off with it.
LUPIN: Fujicakes.
Honestly, Lupin.
How drunk are you?
You couldn't wait for me to turn
up before starting to drink?
Today is our little--
JIGEN: Hey, Lupin.
I need some ice.
Shut up.
I'm not your damn waiter.
Geez.
Hold it, Lupin.
You mean you really did
forget what day it is today?
Uh, what was it?
FUJIKO: Unbelievable.
Idiot.
[japanese singing]