- So how does it look to you?
- It's flawless.
I appreciate it.
Would you mind
if I stayed for a bit?
- Huh?
[Snickers]
I heard about
that people log thing.
Must be rough being so famous.
- The world has become
a strange place.
It's disgraceful.
- Hm. You're a little
too old-fashioned.
So, tell me--
when do you plan on
fighting Lupin?
Do you remember
what you told me--
that he may well be the
strongest fighter in the world?
That's why you hang
around him, isn't it?
¶¶
¶ [jazzy theme music plays]
- Jigen: Goemon is
taking his sweet time.
- What did you expect?
It's not like we can
walk around town normally
thanks to people log.
- I think you look cute.
- Yeah, thanks a lot.
- [Laughing]
- [Gasping]
- I see.
You're more likely to go
undetected by anyone's cameras
if you can stay underwater.
- Nice of you to join us, pal.
- Cool. Now we've got
all of the cards.
- Cards?
You referring to me?
- Ever hear of an ace
in the hole?
That's you, pal.
- Hm.
- Enzo: Get Carter to handle
the management
of the cloud servers.
Have we had an answer from
France's digital minister yet?
If he doesn't want
to fast-track us, let him know
we're ready to install
the undersea cables ourselves.
Turn down any requests
for interviews.
All announcements will
be made from my account.
The eu wants to strengthen
Internet regulations?
Ignore them.
We are building
the future itself here.
- Are you boys looking to take
over the world or something?
- Huh.
You caught us.
But that's not Enzo's goal.
I really think he just wants to
make the world a better place.
- Huh.
Is he a Saint or something?
- He's more human
than most, I'd say.
Enzo has a daughter
somewhere out there.
His ex-wife got full
custody of her, however.
- Oh, no.
His backstory is
sadder than I thought.
- But then she was kidnapped
and possibly killed,
maybe a victim of child
pornographers.
- And the mother?
- She killed herself.
Society blamed her for
what happened,
even though she was
a victim herself.
I don't understand
society's mindset sometimes.
- And you boys think people
log can avert such tragedies?
- Enzo's intentions
are pure,
purer than anyone's.
- [Overlapping chatter]
- People log is
becoming a threat
to our national sovereignty.
- It's an online service
trying to muscle in
on the fundamental
roles of government.
- But the problem is
that a lot of people
are advocating
the use of people log.
- Nonsense!
We should declare shake hanz a
terrorist organization at once!
- You would dare to brand
a global it business
as terrorists?
- Rather ironic to hear
that from a country
whose president had his crimes
exposed thanks to people log.
- Settle down.
This isn't the place to bring up
any nation's internal politics.
I will have order.
- Unless the enemy's
a simple one,
it's hard to get them to
organize against anything.
[Groans]
- They are probably
already expecting us
courtesy of people log.
But we've still got
to see this through.
- Emmy?
- It's ami.
Hello, underworld.
Come in.
[Earring beeping]
Run a full ddos attack
on people log
using botnets 1 through 42.
- Okay, let's get
this party started.
When thieves
are in the shadows,
then all is right
with the world.
- Enzo, we're being hit
by a massive ddos attack
on a scale that dwarves
anything we've seen before.
- It's Lupin.
We expected him to launch
an attack on people log
before waltzing in here.
Ling, I want
everything on video.
We'll stream it online.
- Well, it'll make for good PR.
But that's only if we
actually catch Lupin III.
- Have some faith in
what people log can do.
- Now add botnet 63 through 78
to the ddos attack.
[Music playing]
[Overlapping chatter]
- We anticipated this kind
of spike in traffic.
You listening?
Make sure those servers
stay up.
- I can't bring
their servers down?
Hello, underworld.
Come in.
Find Russia's funny bear and
then dragon baby in China.
Get them to launch an attack
on people log with zombie bots.
- The attacks are coming in
from all over the world now.
He must have one very
serious hacker with him.
I don't care
if we have to devote
all of our resources
to doing it --
keep people log online!
[Rapid keyboard tapping]
- Lupin, I haven't been able
to bring down people log,
but the ddos attack has
their offices in a frenzy.
- Gotcha. Then we'll use
the distraction...
To break into their
security system.
- What is he saying?
- Beats the hell out of me.
Thievery nowadays
lacks a certain charm.
- He's turned people log
into a honeypot.
They expected us to do this.
Who is this guy?
Could it be?
- Hackers capable
of an attack on this scale?
Funny bear?
Dragon baby?
No.
It's you.
It's underworld.
- It seems fujiko's
on the top floor.
- Good grief.
What is it with princesses
being locked away
at the very top
of the tallest tower?
- Princess fujiko, really?
- It's just an expression,
man.
- Zenigata will be here
in 15 minutes
to take fujiko into custody.
He should have docked
at the port by now.
- Goemon, mind staying behind?
If they lock this place
down, we'll have no way out.
If you guard the exit, you
can stop them from sealing it.
- Is that an order?
- Huh?
- Lupin,
clarify our relationship.
- What is this?
First fujiko, and now it's you?
- I don't recall
ever being your henchman.
- Henchman?
- Goemon, what's this all about?
- Oh.
I'm guessing you saw this.
For crying out loud,
this is the problem
with people who've never
been on the Internet.
You'll believe
anything, won't you?
- So the information
is unreliable?
- Look here, man.
- Evidence level e?
- It analyzes the info that
gets posted and gives it
a ranking based on how
true it thinks it is.
You could say that's
people log's best feature.
- That means--
- it's a steaming pile
of crap,
at least
according to people log.
- Let me see that.
- Are you sure you know
how to use it?
Miss Emmy, could you post
"when eating grilled salmon,
goemon ishikawa
likes the skin best?"
- When eating grilled
salmon, goemon ishikawa
likes the skin best.
- That is--
- so is that true, goemon?
-The ai found people on the
Internet similar to you
and found the answer by
looking at their profiles
and likes to extrapolate
what you might like too.
- Goemon: This people log thing
is truly remarkable.
- Jigen: That's exactly
why we're in such deep doo doo.
- [Laughing]
- It's not funny.
- [Snickers]
- Let us know if there's
any trouble, ok?
- Hmm.
Well, our relationship is
rather hard to describe.
[Music playing]
Hm
- Seems you've gotten
a lot softer these days,
goemon ishikawa.
- You're responsible
for people log.
- The name's Enzo.
And if you'd looked me up
on people log,
you'd know my name and age.
You could even find out
my favorite food.
- Yet your service
can be wrong.
I know I am not
Lupin's henchmen.
- Is that so?
- We are neither allies
nor friends.
A machine, no
matter how advanced,
could never sum up our
relationship into mere words.
- That's true.
Nothing written on people log
right now is 100% accurate.
But I've come up
with the best way
to describe your relationship.
If Lupin is the kind of man
that people log's analysis
suggests,
then I know exactly
what you are to him...
Part of his collection.
- [Gasps]
That's a lie.
- In Lupin's eyes, everything
is an item in his collection--
his loot, his friends,
his thrills, his love,
everything he experiences.
You're just one more
piece in his collection.
That's what goemon ishikawa is.
- Not true.
- And because of that,
he tries to keep you safe.
He wouldn't want something
in his collection
to get damaged, would he?
- Lupin and I have tried to
kill each other in the past.
- But he was holding back
so he wouldn't kill you.
What's that?
According to people log,
there's no way
you will ever beat Lupin
in a fight.
- Wrong!
I have never once lost to Lupin!
- Then why don't you
go prove it to yourself?
- Don't you worry about it.
After all,
I'm a genius, remember?
Cool.
Now we've got all the cards.
- Lupin.
- The man known
as goemon ishikawa the 13th
has always sought his answers
in the heat of battle.
And that got an a rating.
- Amayata karasu
with the icpo.
We called ahead.
We're here to take
fujiko mine into custody.
- Biometric ID beta verified.
Approved individuals,
please follow the illuminated
red pathway before you.
- Inspector,
why did you tell Lupin
that fujiko mine had
been caught?
- It's the best way to capture
his gang in one fell swoop.
- But sir, we're also
giving Lupin a chance
to break her free.
You should have
just hauled him in,
just like you would with
any other common criminal.
- Then what's left of his
gang would regroup
and find a way
to break him out.
- Even so, his escape
would not change the fact
that you had finally caught him.
Your career has stalled
ever since you started
working on the Lupin case.
- That's enough, yata.
- No!
Someone with your
level of talent
deserves better than this!
[Blast and rumbling]
- Huh?
- What the?
- Lupin!
- Is that what you wanted?
- That will do nicely.
Keep all of the elevators
except for number 7
exactly where they are for now.
- What a coincidence, Lupin,
running into you here.
- Well, I just figured the
biggest business in the world
might have some
crazy loot to steal,
but not seeing much
around here.
- I heard from a good
source you're screwed.
- You trying to be a jinx?
Who told you such a thing?
- People log.
- [Laughs] Are machines
telling the future?
- That's what came up
after analyzing
a huge amount of data.
According to people log,
Lupin III might have
a death wish.
- What the?
- He steals jewelry
and artworks
that he doesn't really
care about.
And the tighter the security,
the more he wants it.
Why is that?
- I've never been good
at riddles.
- It's because
he is self-destructive.
- So what?
What if I really am?
- Lupin, would you steal me?
- Huh?
- I'd be a fitting last job
for the great Lupin III.
- Last job?
Why would--
- ami:
She doesn't want you to die!
- Huh?
- Cute way of putting it.
I like how it sounds.
- Goemon?
- Well, he's looking
rather friendly today.
- I challenge you to a duel.
- Come on, man.
You want to right now?
Isn't there any way this can
wait 'til we're back home?
- The nature of our relationship
has been troubling me
for some time now.
- Huh?
- Words, time, and data
can never properly explain it.
What was once clear has
become clouded to me.
And nothing can cut through
the clouds of doubt
the way my zantetsuken can
in battle.
- Hm.
- Answer me, Lupin.
- Goemon, this isn't
the time to--
- you're on, goemon.
- Lupin!
This is a personal
issue between us.
- Doesn't matter
where or even when.
I've got to.
It's a matter of honor.
[Music playing]
- [Both grunting]
- Yata, take the stairs.
Lupin is
in the penthouse office.
- Yes, inspector.
- You know,
daisuke jigen,
partners can be such
a funny thing.
- Shut your trap.
- You're not friends.
You're like allies,
but also rivals.
And yet there are things
you can only do
with your partner's help.
And sometimes there
are some things
you're forced into doing
because of your partner.
[Phone vibrating]
Can I answer that?
- Of course you can't.
- I want to introduce you.
It's my partner.
Yes?
It's ling.
- Hey! What the hell are you
doing with my partner?
- Are you the boss around here?
Sorry.
We're a little bit occupied.
What the hell?
- My name is Ling Bo,
and you shouldn't
take me lightly.
- Tell me something, jigen.
Are you really happy with
spending the rest of your life
as a footnote in the legend
of Lupin III?
- Lupin, goemon, stop this!
- Settle down.
If you love Lupin,
keep quiet, watch, and learn.
No matter what happens,
you need to be
ready to accept the outcome.
If not, set your
heart on someone else.
- Lupin, are you
taking me seriously?
Did you actually intend
to hit me with that shot?
Am I just an item
in your collection?
Is that why you hold back
when you face me,
treating me like one
of the artworks
or gemstones you steal,
like something you choose
to sit and admire
whenever the mood takes you?
Or are you responding
to my conviction
in a sincere fashion?
Which is it?
Have you forgotten?
[Grunts]
Nicely done, goemon.
- [Sighs]
- [Gasping]
Lupin!
Lupin! Lupin!
Say something, Lupin!
- Fujiko!
- This is the choice he made.
- That can't --
Get out here, Enzo!
You're the one who made
people log, aren't you?
My name is ami enan,
and I'm your daughter!
Father, please save Lupin!
¶¶
[Singing in Japanese]