- Just wondering,
does anybody here know
a Shinjiro Dezai?
Nobody?
Well, shoot.
Apparently he's a
relative of my ex-wife's,
even though I've never met him.
But he just reached out
to me and asked to meet up
so I figured, why not?
[laughter]
- And this guy, who is he?
- He's in charge
of a global IT company--
the president
of Shake Hanz himself.
You came without
knowing any of that?
- [grunts]
- So if we do a search
on Shinjiro Dezai--
[beep]
Huh.
It looks like
he's a car dealer.
Does he want to sell me a car?
Or maybe he's just
looking for a job.
Hope it's not about religion.
Hey, hold on, maybe it's that
samurai sword I left in Kyoto.
Probably just
wants to return it.
[laughter]
Imagine if you knew exactly
who you're dealing with.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Is this person trustworthy?
Do they have a criminal record?
And are they even
worth your time?
We haven't ever met,
have we, sir?
- No.
- But see, I can know
exactly who you are.
Inspector Zenigata.
Hm, with the ICPO, huh?
Oh, and with quite
an impressive record.
Assigned to the Lupin
investigation, huh?
And this will be our
company's new service--
PeopleLog.
- Hey, Lupin.
Pops is on the TV
for some reason.
- He's what now?
- With just this app, I can
more or less figure you out--
all your favorite dishes,
your pet peeves,
your work ethic,
everything from your politics
to your choice in women.
- It can tell you all that?
- Subjects
you've searched online,
any posts you've made
on social media.
Our AI creates profiles
based on the massive amounts
of information
available
on the internet.
- Inspector, is all
of that accurate?
- His expression says yes.
- I don't believe it!
- Wow!
- Incredible!
Users of PeopleLog can update
profiles with new info.
Say if someone's been
nice to you in the past,
or if they stabbed you
in the back at work.
[shudders]
Or maybe they're a womanizer.
- These sound like online
shopping reviews.
- And what if someone
posts a lie?
- Well, let's see--
Inspector Zenigata was
seeing a movie
in New York last Tuesday.
As you can see,
it got an F.
So then you can probably assume
it's a lie.
- How can it make
such an assumption?
- The AI will analyze
and cross-reference
any claim you post
in very fine detail.
And this past Tuesday,
I believe
you were in Tokyo, right?
- Whoa!
- With PeopleLog, you can
predict what a person wants.
Do you invite someone out
to golf or to dinner?
You'll never have to worry
about guessing wrong,
and getting scammed will be
a thing of the past,
since you can see
people's criminal records.
- That's an invasion
of privacy.
- PeopleLog only
collects information
that's already available
on the internet.
- Nonsense.
This is invasive!
It's truly unacceptable!
- Are you sure?
It's not up to us
to make that decision.
It's up to you.
- Hm.
ｶ [jazzy theme music]
ｶｶ
- We're here to check out
your AC.
- Let me just verify
your identities.
[beep]
- LUPIN: The statue we're
looking for should be close by.
- JIGEN: There she is.
And quite a looker
too, ain't she?
- You're up once
the lights are out, Goemon.
- Understood.
- Thieves are in the shadows.
All's right with the world.
[beeping]
- CECILIA: Nicholas,
who is that woman?
- LUPIN: Huh?
What's this?
- NICHOLAS: Cecilia,
what are you doing here?
If you're not going to tell me,
then I'll figure it out myself.
Carla Redson, 31 years old.
A nurse.
- Ah!
- And you're having
an affair with her.
- Another cheater?
- Which one's the wife?
- I feel so bad for her.
- Well, damn, this turned
into a circus fast.
- What now?
- Ah, forget it.
It's the latest thing--
PeopleLog divorces.
- What the hell does
that mean?
- You look your husband up
on PeopleLog
and find the name
of another woman
listed under the section
marked "partners."
- Bad news for the husband.
- It finds out
who's cheating on who
through photos uploaded
by third parties.
[camera snap]
Oh, huh?
- Lupin III!
[chatter]
- He's that thief!
- That is so cool.
- Why does this feel
so damn familiar?
- Yeah, that's me--
the greatest thief
of our time, Lupin III.
- MAN: Over there, officers.
- Hm?
- There he is!
- Looks like it's time
to split.
- Hold it, Lupin III!
- There you go!
[gunshots]
[explosion]
- What the hell?
- Damn PeopleLog,
social media.
I'm having trouble keeping up
with the internet nowadays.
- Mmm.
- You're starting to sound
like an old geezer.
Is Daisuke Jigen thinking
about hanging up his hat?
- Don't joke about that, OK?
- [grunts]
Hm?
- Hey, he actually showed up.
- Well, it did say there
was an 82% chance
he'd escape by the sewers.
- Man, PeopleLog is amazing.
- What's the holdup?
- Eyewitness reports
and data from our old exploits.
It must have used those
to predict our route.
- So does that mean the AI can
figure out all of our plans?
- What a load of crap.
[beep]
[engine starts]
[cameras snapping]
[horn honking]
- Watch where you're going!
- Lupin and his gang are
heading south on route 13.
They're driving a white
Gordini.
License plate is--
[gunshots]
- They just keep coming.
- Lupin, is it not
possible
they have also predicted
this route as well?
- That doesn't matter if
they can't keep up, right?
- After them!
Damn it!
Lupin!
- LUPIN: All right, let's take
a break from escaping
and grab some grub.
- JIGEN: Yeah, after all,
we never got to finish
those rillettes.
- GOEMON: Hold on,
both of you.
- Yeah, it's not my birthday
but there's
a surprise waiting.
- JIGEN: Are the internet
rubber-neckers
all the way out here, too?
[gunshots]
- GOEMON: The Rat Clan.
- I thought that we finished
those bastards off
back in Bawanda.
- I guess these are the
stragglers out for revenge.
- And how the hell did they
sniff out our hideout?
- If you take the places
we've been spotted
and cross reference it with
the local lodging information...
Well, if you get
enough data,
I guess it's not impossible,
but...
That means this thing's
even more trouble
than I gave it credit for.
The world's greatest
outlaw Lupin III itself.
If I can pin you down,
it'll prove beyond
a shadow of a doubt
ｶｶ
- I've decided.
I shall train in the mountains.
- You sure love
training, don't you?
- GOEMON: The two of you
should join me.
I'm the only one
who knows the location.
There is no fear of
PeopleLog tracking you there.
- Don't you worry about it.
After all,
I'm a genius, remember?
Take care of yourself, Goemon.
- What did Goemon say
this time?
- He says he loves us.
[beep]
- I suppose they don't require
my help at this time.
- Here you go.
- LUPIN: Looks
like the coast is clear.
- Well, we've been staying
here in disguise after all.
- Hello, welcome back.
Where did you two go
this time?
- We went to Tokyo to catch up
with my granddaughter.
- She's starting
elementary school, right?
That's wonderful.
- Fujiko Mine is
Lupin III's one true love.
- Man, the galettes here
are really delicious, huh?
- Nothing like eating good food
in familiar surroundings.
- Though I'd rather have
a girlfriend than a gallete.
- You never learn your lesson,
do you, Lupin?
- TV: Up next, it's the app
that's sweeping the globe--
PeopleLog.
While there has been some
criticism of the service,
its popularity and usage
has skyrocketed lately.
- Sure, we use
PeopleLog every time
we conduct a job interview.
It's a lot more trustworthy
and significantly quicker
than checking to see if
someone's padded out
their resume.
- I'm always totally
checking up on my friends--
- And if they post on
PeopleLog, it's gotta be true.
- I know.
- PeopleLog helps me turn
fishing enthusiasts
into future customers.
Gotta bring my business to
the folks who need it, right?
- Well, this sucks.
- You bet.
[buzzing]
- Hm?
Phone calls aren't usually
your style, right, Emmy?
- It's Ami,
and I've secured the line.
Lupin, PeopleLog is
on a whole different level
from what happened last time
with the Lupin Game.
- I've already seen
what it can do.
Seems like it'll be
a tough one this time.
- I want to talk it over
face to face.
- I was just thinking that
I should come to you for help,
to be honest.
- Oh, you were?
- Lupin, look.
- What-- what's up?
We're leaving right now.
[chatter]
- Excuse me, who said you
could take videos of my cafe?
What is this?
- Well, well, well.
Looks to me like there's
trouble brewing out here.
Just go on inside.
I'll listen to what
they have to say.
- It's dangerous.
These people have gone crazy.
- Our PeopleLog does
more than just
standard facial recognition.
It uses what it's learned
from past disguises
to analyze and see
through new ones too.
[chatter]
- Well, I guess the cat's
out of the bag.
- Whoa!
- It is Lupin!
- It's Lupin!
- Oh man, you're right.
- Hey, Lupin!
- Get in!
- I'm sorry for dragging
you into this.
- I have to say, your
galletes were seriously
the best I've ever had.
- It's a real shame we'll never
get to enjoy any more of them.
- You acted like a dirt-bag
so they wouldn't think
I was part of your gang.
- Nah, I really am
a dirt-bag.
Pat me on the back and watch
the dirt fly right off me.
[laughter]
- Plenty of companies
across the nation
have begun treating
PeopleLog profiles
as though they're official
identification.
- We could also start using
PeopleLog instead of passports.
- It's proven to be a much
more cost effective way
of preventing crime
than the police, as well.
[door opening]
- I have just recently returned
from the Kingdom of Padar.
- But why Padar?
- They've been testing it
to see how it could help them
run the kingdom.
- In regards to taxation,
law enforcement,
and public management
in Padar,
PeopleLog is being adapted to
deal with the majority
of administrative tasks.
A distributed network,
public or private,
with such a wealth
of information
lessens the need for centralized
control by the government.
With the voluntary submission of
personal data via social media,
all public services have
seen a significant increase
in efficiency--
including the police.
- That's insane.
- We must consider
its implications
on national security.
- This isn't going to work.
Overseeing their citizens
is why governments exist.
Are you saying that PeopleLog is
going to muscle in on all that?
- I believe so.
In the next 10 years,
it will likely replace
over half of the existing
government services.
[gasp]
It's an innovation-led
revolution,
one that could topple
this very government.
- What a strange surprise.
I never thought I'd run
into a samurai out here.
- Hm.
Did you get lost?
- Bingo.
I thought I was
taking a short cut,
but ended up going
off track.
But I still got a signal,
so it shouldn't be
too bad of a problem.
Oh hey, can I upload
that photo online?
- Young lady, I never
agreed to such a thing.
- [gasp]
Murderer!
- Hm?
Henchman?
- Jigen, look.
Hey, did you use PeopleLog
to find me too, Pops?
- I don't need
that digital nonsense
to track
the likes of you down.
[gunshot]
- They're a little busy
right now.
Sit tight and shut up, kid.
- It's that look.
What's happening, Pops?
- Fujiko's been caught.
PeopleLog tracked her down.
In the end,
she gave herself up.
- Times have changed.
You're nothing more
than relics now.
The very concept of thieves,
especially Lupin III,
is finished.
ｶｶ
[Japanese singing]