[gunshot]
[gasp]
[groaning]
What’s wrong?
\hSurprised that the
gun you swapped out
is now firing live bullets?
[groaning]
\hI’m sure you had a
simple plan in mind.
\h\hLike, I’ve got a
good payback on him
\h\hfor roping me into
this big mess, right?
But it’s that attitude that
\h\halways screws things up
for you.
I have a valid reason
\h\h\hfor shooting you
in the gut and not the heart.
Would you like to know why?
Because I wanted to see
you in despair as I won.
[grunting]
[explosion]
[gasp]
\h\h\hI’m sure you’ve
noticed by now, but I
had to toss the little
\h\hpresent you rigged
my car with into the river.
[groaning]
[splat]
Huh?
[grunting]
Hm.
[sigh]
Huh?
[panting]
[grunting]
[giggle]
Huh?
[hissing]
[groaning]
[grunting]
I’ll kill him!
Don’t bother, Cloe!
Hm?
No need to worry.
We got the notebook.
[sirens]
[laughing]
Huh?
[growling]
\hHe really pulled one
over on you this time.
Huh, kid?
Albert’s a punk.
\h\hI can’t believe he’d steal
the cash first just because he
knew I was coming for it.
Not to mention it couldn’t
\hhave been easy replacing
the whole stash with
\hcounterfeit bills.
Damn it!
\h\hHe even had the nerve to
leave real bills at the end
of each pile just sell it.
Sure about that?
Huh?
Hm.
huh?
[growl]
\h\hIt looks like Albert’s
upped his game yet again.
[growling]
Damn it!
[panting]
[groaning]
I’m glad you’re awake, Lupin,
\h\hbut if you keep screaming,
\h\hyou’ll tear your
stitches wide open.
Hm.
How long was I out?
Two, maybe three days.
I’m sorry, man.
Heh heh.
Quit it.
Just the very thought of you
\hgetting all grateful on me
is giving me the hives.
[footsteps]
Hm?
Hm.
I see that you have awakened.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Seems I caused you
guys some trouble.
\hNo, an apology from you is
enough to give me the hives.
Huh?
[chuckles]
I assume this means
\hwe’ll be splitting
tonight’s dinner three ways.
Oh, is that an eel?
Looks like we’re in for
\hquite a treat tonight.
Actually, this is a treat
\heven finer than an eel.
[hissing]
G-- gah!
And now we return
\hto our coverage
of the presidential election.
\hFormer prime minister
Mr. Arbo and Mr. Beckel,
who was picked up support
\hfrom the moderate left,
have emerged as front runners.
In third place is the right wing
candidate, the eye of the storm
himself, Mr. Calvess,
who has been receiving
increasing criticism over
his staunch anti-immigrant
rhetoric.
\h\hAnd as such, the support
for his campaign has been...
\hThat being said, he’s
made it this far on his
anti-immigrant--
Huh?
Revenant?
You’re still alive?
\h\hWe all thought
that you were dead
and gone seing that you never
checked in or gave us a call.
I’d love to welcome you
\h\hback with open arms,
but I told you to
\hsteal this thing
and kill Lupin and
\hCamille as well.
You screwed up.
Now I’m a merciful leader,
but failure will cost you.
If you keep chowing your
\h\hmeal down like that,
\h\h\hyour wounds will
have rice poking out.
It looks as if you might be able
to sleep easier tonight, Lupin.
I sure hope so.
Apparently, this Albert
\h\h\hperson must really
be getting under your skin.
Uh--
Hey, come on, Goemon.
You were calling his
\hname in your sleep
as you tossed and turned.
He’s the one who
abandoned Lupin.
Albert!
Are you leaving?
Yeah.
Then I’ll be taking the
title of III for myself.
Whatever, dude.
You’re really accepting
defeat that gracefully?
Heh, never.
Really, you of all people should
know that better than anybody.
Ugh.
Then what is your deal?
These small time jobs
\hare a waste of time.
\hI’ve got my sights set
on something much bigger
than just robbing banks.
Much bigger?
Are you going to steal
the moon or something?
Try France.
\h\hSo has Guillon
made his move yet?
\h\h\h\hNo, none that arouses
suspicion for the time being,
\hthough it’s hard to tell,
since his normal activities
are already suspicious.
Hm.
[gulp]
And what about Jose?
We’ve got our people on
\hlookout all over town,
but we have been unable to
locate him or his people.
[grunt]
What are you saying, Jose?
Have you gone deaf?
\h\hI’ve decided I’m not
giving you the notebook.
But don’t you worry.
I found a much better use for it
than whatever you had planned.
Hm.
\h\h\h\h\hWe’ve been unable to
confirm, but we’re estimating
around 20 casualties.
The Cry For Truth
\hterrorist group
claimed responsibility shortly
before the explosion happened.
The Cry For Truth?
Wasn’t the DGSE monitoring
\h\hthem around the clock?
Yes.
Given their surveillance
\h\h\h\h\hcapabilities,
they should have
known everything
the terrorists were planning.
Then why did he-- uh--
He’d let it happen.
But why?
\h\hWe let notorious terrorists
into the country, and now what?
\h\hAre we supposed to turn a
blind eye to all our actions?
\hBut interior minister, if
we don’t follow his demands,
then we’ll all--
I know that!
He’s got the black notebook, a
Pandora’s box of our misdeeds.
\hBut unlike the legend,
there won’t be any hope
left if this one is open.
[interposing voices]
Things are really getting
\h\h\hkind of hairy, huh?
Hm.
It seems as though the hairiness
has found its way here.
[gunfire]
\h\h\hYou know, they
could have knocked.
\h\hThere’s no need to blow
the door to bits like that.
Those fellows must
take after Goemon.
[gasping]
\hAh man, I really
like that room and
its wonderful natural lighting.
\h\h\hIt wasn’t exactly
well-ventilated, though.
I know just how to fix that.
[kiss]
OK.
[grunt]
Catch!
Huh?
[panicking]
Ready, Goemon?
Lupin, I’ll catch up with you.
Huh?
I guess that means that
the bastard did survive.
[grunt]
[slash]
Hold on.
Yeah!
Huh?
I don’t think so!
[screaming]
[whimper]
Duh?
Lupin, over here!
[grunting]
Hm.
[yell]
[metal clashing]
[whimper]
[gunshot]
[grunting]
Ah-- huh?
Uh, [whimpering]
The men who have targeted
\hus are highly dangerous.
You can say that again.
\h\hAnd we don’t even have
the damn notebook anymore.
Actually, the fewer
\h\hpeople who know
about its secrets, the better.
[grunting]
Especially if they’re going
\h\hto use the said secrets
for fraudulent purposes.
Then I imagine that
\hthey will continue
\h\h\h\h\hto pursue us
tenaciously, since we
\h\hhave knowledge of the
contents of the notebook.
You got that right, Goemon.
Then we have only one option.
Yep.
\hThe best defense
is a good offense.
Yeah, I’m pretty sure
that Buddha said that.
I think it was Confucius
\h\h\h\hthat said that.
It was Sun Tzu.
Hm?
Huh?
Uh, uh.
Well, I’m not quite
\h\hsure, actually.
\hFrance is in the
midst of a crisis,
and these animals
we call terrorists
must be dealt with right now.
\h\hI can protect you, and I
will protect you if you all
cast your vote for me.
Calvess!
Support for candidate canvas has
skyrocketed almost overnight.
\h\hIn the past, his far
right leaning tendencies
\h\hhave been viewed as a
handicap when reaching out
to mainstream voters.
But the recent series
\hof terrorist attacks
\hhas the general
public frightened,
and frightened people
\htend to vote right.
\hThen given this
fear, do you think
it’s likely that Calvess will
win the presidential election?
If the terrorist attacks
\hcontinue at this rate,
\hhe stands a good
chance of winning.
I see.
So that’s his plan.
\hSo far, so good,
wouldn’t you say?
Just one last push
\his all we need,
one final fireworks display.
\h\h\hMaybe the day before the
election would seal the deal.
\hYeah, after that, France
will finally belong to us.
What are we going to do?
The public is quickly losing all
faith in the police department.
If we don’t do something soon,
it’s going to get to the point
where it’s--
Then what do you suggest we do?
[gasp]
\hNo one wants to make a
move while the location
of the black notebook
\h\his still unknown.
Hm.
Who would have guessed
\h\hthis country would
descend into civil war right
before our heist kicked off?
Talk about crappy luck.
What now?
At this rate, the entire
\h\hcity and the palace
\h\h\hare going to be
swarming with troops.
Let’s give it a shot.
If we don’t, the army will get
\htheir paws on Gaia’s Naval.
And then we can kiss Africa’s
\h\h\hbiggest diamond goodbye.
Ah!
Seriously?
It’s practically suicide.
Why not?
Should be fun, right?
Besides, I hear someone else
\hhas also set their sights
on our diamond.
\h\hIf you’re ready to sit
back and let them take it,
then I’m not sure you’re
\hcut out to be a thief.
[gasp]
[grunting]
Hm.
France is mine.
I’m not letting anyone take it.
Hm.
Huh?
[mumbling]
Well, well.
Look what the cat dragged in.
[gasp]
Lupin!
\h\hThe idea of someone
else stealing your score
\hmust have gotten you so riled
up that you had to do something.
\h\hYou’ll always be a
thief no matter where
you end up in life, won’t you?
I already told you.
\h\hThe only reason I became a
cop is because it would let me
go after a much bigger target.
And just what brings you here.
Who, me?
\hJust thought I’d ask
our mutual friend here
about the pests that have been
\h\hswarming around me lately.
Then our interests align nicely.
Hm.
Well, then.
I’ll leave the interrogation
\h\h\hin your capable hands.
[muffled grunting]
[laughter]
\hYou’ve got a knack
for getting bad guys
to spill their guts, right?
Ah?
Albert!
\hWhat the hell you
think you’re doing?
\h\h\hDo you honestly think
you’ll get away with-- ah--
Aaah!
\hI’m the one asking
the questions here.
[japanese singing]