[theme music]
THEME SONG: [japanese singing]
[gunshot]
HIRAMEKI JR: Dear Lupin
III, you were the grandson
of Arsene Lupin, famous for
your daring and mysterious
adventure.
And people even call you the
smartest man in the world.
You’re so much more
amazing than me and my bro.
PARROT: Morning.
Squack-
[humming]
Who’s there?
It’s me, your Big Bro.
Uh, no, you’re not.
Here’s a question.
What is 1 plus 1?
It’s, uh, 5, right?
Yeah, it’s you.
What the heck?
Did you put these stickers up?
No, I didn’t.
A guy in a suit stopped
by and stuck them
on just about everything.
It’s too bad they weren’t
here to place an order.
Oh, my stomach just growled.
[gasps] Even the
cabbage has one.
They’re going to take our stuff
if we don’t pay our taxes.
You mean everything?
Mm-hmm.
[gasps] All this!
All that!
Ahh!
Oh, no.
The whole place is
covered in them!
[grunting] They said if
we don’t pay them back,
they’re gonna take the entire
workshop that Dad left us!
No, I just can’t believe
it’s going to be all gone.
Huh?
[distant sirens]
Upsy-daisy.
Pardon us, folks,
coming through.
Whoa.
Uh, oh, boy.
Lupin!
Forgive the intrusion,
fellow citizens.
Get back here!
Huh?
Hey, Lupin’s the answer.
Hey, Lupin sounds delicious.
With Lupin’s help, we
can save Dad’s workshop
from foreclosure.
[typewriter keys clacking]
[theme music]
Mr. president, although
Lupin informed us
about his next move,
isn’t this a bit much?
Yes, you over there.
Is this really OK?
Lupin III said he’s
going to rob you blind,
and isn’t that a problem?
It’s no problem.
It is a huge problem!
Not even Lupin himself can get
past our security measures.
And now, without
any further ado,
let me introduce
you to our new safe.
Huh, what?
Hey, little bro.
It seems like that fake
warning we sent out
has paid off pretty well, huh?
[laughs]
Boys, if you would
do the honors.
[dramatic music]
(TOGETHER) Ooh.
Size isn’t everything, you know.
We’ve invented a safe that
Lupin can’t crack, no matter
how hard he tries.
[gasping]
It uses a scanner to measure a
person’s brain power before it
can actually be opened.
Lupin III has a brain
power rating of 300.
And there’s my big brother
with zero brain power.
But doesn’t that mean Lupin
and his superior brain power
will have an advantage?
Not to mention a save created by
a couple of numbskulls like you
two, Lupin will open
that safe in a flash.
Go ahead.
Say something, you two.
The thing is, having
zero brain power
is actually the key
to us beating Lupin.
How is that even possible?
The guy’s a phony!
All right, people,
settle down now.
[crowd grumbling]
We have a plan-- ow-- a plan.
Don’t we, boys?
The strategy we came up with
to finally get Lupin III
is- to flip the chart.
Now my brother with
zero brain power
has an advantage over Lupin.
Yeah, I could even beat Lupin.
Isn’t this amazing?
This safe only opens when the
brain power scanner hits zero.
So if it take someone like
my big brother to open it,
then someone with 300
brain power like Lupin III
can never open the safe!
[panting]
Isn’t that incredible?
For the first time
ever, we finally
have a way to beat Lupin
III once and for all!
And now, gentlemen, if
you would be so kind.
[rumbling, clattering]
[chime]
[gasps]
Look at that.
It really works.
This thing just
might beat Lupin.
You got that right!
With this safe and
its safeguards,
even the dreaded Lupin
is nothing to fear.
Lupin III, take your best shot!
[laughs]
Hmm.
That sounds like fun, Lupin.
You should try cracking it.
Huh?
Aren’t you going to do anything
about this, the grandson
of Arsene Lupin?
Hmm.
Why are you being so moody?
How boring.
You’re a household name.
That must be nice.
Criminals just
don’t do requests.
[scoffs] Having the
world’s biggest brain
and famous lineage will make
dodging the fallout easy.
That great big brain
is the main problem.
The safe won’t open.
But it should be a cinch
with a brain like yours.
If you’d give it a
shot, I’m sure it’ll
pop open as soon as it sees ya.
Why should I?
I never even sent those
guys that warning.
Maybe that cavity’s
rotting your brain too.
[bang]
Just go and crack
that safe already.
Well, now, I never
thought the famous Fujiko
Mine would be so supportive.
I’m guessing you’re bored
because no new sugar
daddies have turned up lately.
[groans] That’s not it.
I’m just curious about who
sent the phony warning that
created this fuss.
And to think I got worried
on behalf of a man like you,
and you acting like
it’s no big deal at all.
Hey, you still owe me
for that pack of smokes.
Cough it up.
Here you go.
Hmm?
Hey, that reminds me.
You still owe me for that
coffee the other day.
Huh?
Here.
Oh.
And there was a time that I
covered for gas, remember?
[glass breaking]
Lupin, I’ve come to collect
for the rice I bought for you.
I’ve had enough of this!
Exactly how much do I owe you?
The master thief is on his way.
Jeez.
You happy now?
Go on, Professor.
Well, why didn’t you say so?
So I figured less is
definitely more in this case.
Watch closely now, fellas.
[sighs]
Hey, Lupin.
Lupin.
(TOGETHER) Hmm?
Uuuh...
Ugh.
He might actually
do it, you know?
Hmm.
How’s that?
Did I look the part?
Wow, that’s impressive, Lupin.
You really looked like a moron.
I genuinely thought
that you’d finally
lost your marbles, Lupin.
Is that so?
Well, I guess I’d better
get ready to go pay off
my debts now, hmm.
[whirring]
This will be easy.
I gobble up safes like
this for breakfast.
Uuuh.
[clattering]
What are we going to do?
His brain power’s
dropping like crazy.
Gotcha!
He needs my help.
Wait a sec!
Big Bro!
Don’t!
Hey, you can do it.
You’re almost there!
[groans]
[chime]
Oh, wow, thank goodness.
It’s a shame.
He almost made it!
Even if all he
did was space out,
this is still attempted larceny.
Lupin, give yourself up!
Lupin, you’re mine now!
(SLURRING) What’d you say?
[gasps]
L-Lupin!
Ahh!
I’d have to really be brainless
to get caught that easily.
Ohh!
[fizzling]
[pop]
Huh?
Better luck next time, pops.
Gotta go.
Catch you later!
Don’t you mock me!
After him!
This sounds exciting.
I wanna join!
No, don’t!
Lupin
Big Bro!
[thud]
Huh?
Lupin, you got so close!
Uh, whoa, got to
love his enthusiasm!
Get him!
As you just saw, Lupin was
unable to crack the bank
safe thanks to these
brilliant individuals.
[cheering]
They beat Lupin with
his 300 ratings.
Way to go!
Hooray for the
Greater Tokyo bank!
Ha ha!
Come see us again, Lupin!
Big Bro, our shop is
going to be famous now.
That means we’ll
get lots of work,
and we can finally pay
back the money we owe!
[crunching vigorously]
They beat us!
It’s all your fault!
You know, this happened
because you’re too smart!
Huh?
You always have to
be the hot shot.
Do you see what you’re
doing to yourself?
Hmph.
What do you want from me?
Zero brain power isn’t human.
Right, Jigen?
Hmph.
I got it!
All we have to do is whittle
your brain power down bit
by bit.
Ugh.
Huh?
Fujiko’s got a point, you know.
Let’s get started.
Fujiko.
Strip now.
Huh?!
Just what are you trying to do?
We’ve got to rid the
brilliant professor
Lupin of his intelligence.
Am I right?
Well, you know, when a man
sees a woman showing some skin,
their mental faculties
take a nosedive.
Huh?
Oh, yeah, okay!
If you put it that way, I
definitely want to be dumb!
Why would I agree to that?!
So I can get--
[groans]
See, that’s what I’m saying.
Uh-huh.
Here you go.
[groaning] [panting]
Come on, Lupin.
Stop dodging.
All right, now, come to papa.
(FRANTIC) Goemon, save me
from these lunatics, please!
My grandmother once told me that
adding pine cones to your soba
is good for your health.
Oh, no, thank you.
[gagging]
[grunting]
[explosion]
I went ahead and phoned in
a warning for you, Lupin.
[whistle blows]
Now, you can really
focus on your training!
All right, then,
let’s push him harder.
You guys don’t need to
push so hard, you know.
Don’t be shy.
Right?
He’s got a point.
You got to give it your all.
But, Goemon!
My grandmother recommends broth
made solely from earthworms
as an herbal remedy.
[sputtering]
[explosion]
[music playing]
[bgm "go go lupin!"]
Nice.
Looks good.
I’ve really wanted to do this
sort of thing for a long time
now.
But look here.
His brain power
isn’t low enough.
We only have a few more days
until the heist, you know!
[sobbing]
OK, no more rest.
Lupin, are you ready
to push even harder?
All right.
Let’s finish really strong.
Yeah, we got this.
[maniacal laughter]
[groans]
So you’re telling me we’ve
received another warning
from Lupin.
We have had so many new
customers opening bank accounts
with us, we’ve made more money
than I know what to do with!
[laughs] Ka-ching!
Yum.
I’d totally root for Lupin if it
means we get treats like this.
We’re not supposed
to root for him.
There’s plenty more ice cream
where that came from, fellas.
After all, we’re bound
to make even more money
thanks to Lupin!
[laughter]
Ice cream!
[ominous bell ringing]
Lupin, time to show off the
fruits of your training.
[clattering]
Going to be tough to lower
his brainpower from here.
Maybe he’s built up
some kind of resistance.
We’ve barely got any time left.
We have to find a way
to get it even lower.
I know.
Maybe we can try
the direct approach.
Hang on.
You do that, and he’ll
die before he’s dumb.
[sniffling] I just know
Lupin can pull it off.
We’ve made so much
progress together.
It will work!
What should we do, Bro?
Big Bro?
You can do it, Lupin!
Keep going!
You can do it!
Even I can do it!
[clattering]
This is absurd!
No no!!
Don’t interrupt the show!
Sir, this is an
obstruction of justice!
[gasps]
[chime]
Thank goodness, we did it.
We won!
If you keep this up, I may
have to arrest you too!
Big Bro, we did it!
We won over Lupin, didn’t we?
[grumbles]
Huh?
B-Big Bro?
Lupin!
Hey, Big Bro!
[gasping]
Lupin!
Lupin, you worked so very
hard for this, didn’t you?
There’s really not a huge
difference between zero and 1.
Can’t we all just agree
that he opened the safe?
I know.
I’m going to open
the safe for you!
No, Big Bro!
Lupin, it’s OK now.
Huh?
Hold on just a second there.
[gasps]
Lupin?
Getting a wonderfully passionate
pep talk like that from you
is more than enough to
mend a fella who’s had
the brains beaten out of him.
Lupin!
Appreciate it, big fella.
Not a huge difference, right?
I like the way that you think.
But-- but, Big Bro?
All righty, then, friends.
Is everybody ready to see the
world’s greatest intellect--
for Lupin III to show exactly
how he goes about cracking
a safe like this?
[chime]
That’s amazing.
But now, he’s too
smart to open it.
Lupin.
Behold, here’s the solution
the brilliant brain of Lupin
has rustled up.
Fishy, fishy, fishy.
[gasping]
He’s eating the bones!
Brain power’s rising!
What’s happening?
Oh, I get it.
Blueback fish has a
high nutrient density.
And it’s rich in DHA and EPA.
By consuming a ton of that
mega brainy fatty acid
into his body, he’s
making himself smarter.
But wasn’t he supposed
to get a lot dumber?
[clattering]
Go!
You can do it!
[festive music]
It opened.
I guess the difference
between an idiot
and a genius really
is paper thin.
I get it now.
When the brainpower
reaches more than 300,
it causes an overflow.
Any further points would
force it to reset to zero.
Whoa, there.
Hold it right there!
Lupin, gotcha!
Uuuh, ahhh.
Lupin?
Are you--
[thwack]
It’s time to run, Lupin.
Don’t dawdle now.
You OK there, Lupin?
(CALMLY) I’m just fine.
Get back here, Lupin!
Well, he didn’t take the money.
So I guess it all
worked out in the end.
Right, fellas?
This contest ends in a draw, OK?
That being the case,
good night, everyone.
Our dumb safe didn’t win.
And now, dad’s workshop--
You know what?
It just doesn’t matter.
Us and Lupin, we’re the same
kind of people, ain’t we?
Because, I mean, all
we really need to do
is eat fish every day.
Ooh, right, as long as
we eat fish we’ll be OK.
That’s the secret.
[laughs]
Big Brother, we might
lose the workshop.
But you know, I think if we
work together hand in hand,
things will work
out somehow, right?
Thanks a lot, Big Brother.
REPORTER: Your safe
was really incredible.
What does it feel like to
have such low brain power?
Uh.
Hmm.
A new power for a new age!
You know what it is.
Canned fish!
Eat canned fish every day!
(TOGETHER) Increase
your brainpower!
ANNOUNCER: Collect the stickers
that come with the cans
and take on Lupin.
HIRAMEKI JR (VOICEOVER): And
so we became overnight celebs
and started selling
canned blueback fish.
It got popular because it tastes
good and makes you smarter.
And my brother became
famous for being
funny around the neighborhood.
From now on, the
two of us are going
to do lots and lots of work
so we can pay off our debts.
Lupin III, a lot has happened.
But we’re doing well.
Lupin, about that
rice money you owe me?
You guys went all out
for this, didn’t you?
Thinking you could
get away with murder
just because you were trying
to lower my brain power, huh?
I forgot I had an appointment
with the beautician.
I’m going to head out now.
Yeah, my cavity suddenly
started acting up.
You’re all a bunch of
ungrateful, good-for-nothings,
you know that?
Is it too much to expect even
a tiny bit of remorse from you?
I guess our esteemed
professor wants
to be an even bigger pain
than the one in my tooth.
All right then, Fujiko, strip!
Huh?
Have you gone soft
in the head too?
Heh, heh, make my brain
power low again, will ya?
No way!
You can forget that!
[groaning] Ow...
[theme music]
[japanese singing]