Lupin III.
Real name-- unknown.
Family and background-- unknown.
There are claims that
his grandfather was
the infamous the
thief, Arsene Lupin,
but there’s no proof to
back up these claims.
Just looking at the data, it’s
hard to tell whether he even
exists.
Doesn’t that make
him perfect, though?
A celebrity targeted by police
forces from all over the world,
and yet, he remains
a complete enigma.
You know what they
call people like that?
I don’t know, ghosts?
No, they’re heroes.
[THEME MUSIC]
[KEYBOARD CLINKING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[CHURCH BELLS RINGING]
Reme has the ball as it
goes from Metra to Prisige.
Prisige is charging
up the left wing.
Wow, DD manages to get between
him and the ball for the steal.
If it goes--
Huh?
Uh. Woah.
But the goalie saves it!
Oh, what a miss!
Argh, almost!
Oh, jeez, Louise.
You’ve got to be kidding me.
That’s as bad as striking
out after your girl whispers,
you ready?
[GRUNTS] What kind of
a man are you anyway?
[LAUGHS] Looks like I
win this time, Lupin.
Oh, shut it.
Just wait for the second half.
[BUZZER]
Yes, just one moment, please.
Sorry about the climb,
son, four flights and all.
So what’s in the package?
Drugs.
What now?
Oh, they put a bunch of them in.
They’re sending drugs
in the mail now?
It’s not just drugs, you know.
Guns, women, and cash too.
The internet is
quite a place, huh?
[BEEPING]
Seems like it’s
the real deal too.
Hm?
[SNIFFS]
[GROANING]
If you dig deep enough
on the dark web,
you’ll find an online
store called Marco Polo.
And their merch
is the real deal?
Well, see, if they
were scamming people,
that seems like a whole lot
of customer reviews to fake.
Hm?
It’s much safer and more
reliable than the mafia,
and all payments
are untraceable.
Fast, cheap, and convenient.
1/3 of the world’s drugs
are now dealt on the web.
Here you go.
Oh, that’s the stuff.
We practically
rented this room just
for your sweet smile
and these galettes.
Then be sure to eat them up,
and I’ll be sure to smile.
It’s good.
We really should have just come
down here in the first place.
Well, you were the
one who was just about
glued to the TV, you old coot.
[GIGGLES] Bon appetit.
So then I’m assuming
this Marco Polo
website is the target, right?
All of their deals
are done digitally
through their
online marketplace.
So we’re going to swoop in
and snatch all that dough.
Something doesn’t
sit right with me
about stealing something
you can’t touch.
Digital currency or cold
hard cash, it’s all the same.
Even the fact that you always
need a key to open the safe.
Hm?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
The cloud’s data center,
a massive server bank
that was put together by a
bunch of defense contractors,
also known as the Twin Towers.
Twin?
I only see one tower.
The other tower is
right down there.
Under the ocean, huh?
That’s right.
Go down 128 meters and
you’ll find the manager’s
residential block.
The sole resident of
that block has our key.
What kind of person
lives down that deep?
A mole man or a mermaid?
Well, the only ocean
this mermaid swims in
is a cyber one.
A hacker?
Seems this individual
put together
Marco Polo’s payment system.
Thieves are in the shadows.
All’s right with the world.
[BEEPING]
Run infiltration tools.
[DIGITAL STATIC]
Grant administrator access.
[BEEPING]
[CHUCKLES]
Isn’t the key going
to be underwater?
Yeah.
The people guarding
it probably are too.
So first, we go up.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
They cool the servers
here with seawater.
So that’s going
to be our way in.
[WHIRRING]
[GRUNTS] Hey, you know
I’m the type of guy
who only deals with blades
when I’m shaving, right?
Oh, you big baby.
[WHIRRING]
How long can you
shut it off for?
15 seconds.
Sounds good.
[SPLASH]
Let’s do it.
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
[MUFFLED YELLING]
And here we are 128 meters
below sea level, the manager’s
residential block.
So what’s with that
costume, Lupin?
Maybe "family" can get our
hacker friend to open up.
Jeez, does someone
seriously live down here?
According to the lease,
they’ve been down here
for about five years now.
[CREAKING]
A girl?
You are?
[CHOKING UP] Oh, my dear Emmy.
I’m your father, but I
suppose you don’t remember me.
Back then, you were--
you were just so little.
Uh, wrong.
Hm?
It’s not Emmy, it’s Ami.
Whoa!
Oh, hey.
Cut that out.
[GRUNTING]
Hey, are you all right, Lupin?
That was close.
She didn’t even hesitate.
Hello, underworld.
[BEEPING]
Run IDS sniffer.
Analyze logs for
unauthorized access.
Transmit intruder
data to security.
What’s with this girl?
Is she a robot?
It’s the same tech
as my monocle,
although she probably had the
gear surgically implanted.
[ALARMS BEEPING]
Who the hell are they?
When did those guys sneak in?
What?
I thought you hacked the
security system so they
wouldn’t notice us here.
Seems like someone’s
flushed us out,
which means... she’s
the real deal.
(ON INTERCOM) Intruders in the
underwater manager’s residence.
Response team,
mobilize immediately.
Eliminate intruders on sight.
An aim like that tells me she’s
an amateur with that piece.
She won’t hit you unless
you’re at point blank range.
Seems right.
Were you just playing around?
She’s a smart kid.
Because it looked like
she was shooting wildly,
but she left herself some ammo.
[GUN SHOT]
A baby Browning
holds six rounds.
She’s got one bullet left.
In that case, it’s showtime.
Wait, Lupin.
Hey, there.
Sorry about all that "I’m
your father" stuff before.
You don’t think I’ll shoot?
You couldn’t if you tried.
Why?
Because I’m actually a prophet.
[GUNFIRE]
Jeez.
All right, here comes
the professionals.
[GUNFIRE]
Hey, Lupin, I can’t
hold out much longer.
If my prophecy comes
true, then tell me
about Marco Polo’s backdoor.
25 ACP, search velocity
and stopping power.
[BEEPING]
You’re the one who
built the system.
So I’m sure you
built a backdoor.
I warned you.
[CLICK]
Sorry I had to lie to you again.
The thing is... I’m
actually a thief.
Access footage from
camera 24 six minutes ago.
But I suppose you
don’t remember me.
Back then, you were
just so little.
Reduce speed.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I’m Lupin III.
I’m a thief.
And quite the skilled one too.
And you can steal anything?
Other than a woman’s tears.
Run 0-D.exe on this facility.
[GUNFIRE]
What’s going on?
Huh?
You’ve got yourself a
deal, Lupin III.
You help me steal
through the backdoor,
and what can I steal
for you, my dear?
Steal me.
Huh?
Invisible chains
are keeping me here.
We have a deal.
I’m an expert at snatching
away sad little princesses.
[THUD]
Jigen, the path is clear.
Would it have killed
you to take him down
a tad bit sooner, Goemon?
Hmmm.
You sure that’s the only
thing you want to stare at?
Does the dark web
ring any bells?
Is that music?
Sort of.
The sort of music
that puts a smile--
what the hell?
[KEYBOARD CLICKING]
[GROWLING] What the hell?
Who is behind this?!
[LAUGHS] How much money
do these guys make?
Would you look at all
that dough rolling in.
That’s as much as
the national budget.
That’s some fine work, Emmy.
Crypto currency transactions--
So where to, kiddo?
Don’t care.
All I really wanted
was to get out of there
so anywhere is fine.
Were you being held
against your will?
No, I was renting that room.
Wasn’t that bad either.
But after all these
years down there,
I found it hard to
go out of my own.
So what do you think, any
thoughts on the outside world?
It stinks.
[LAUGHS] That’s
gasoline for you.
Shut up.
Gas-powered cars
are way more manly.
How old fashioned of you.
At least I’m not a samurai.
[LAUGHS]
You can find just about
anything on the internet,
even the perfect fixers
for a time like this.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Hm?
[ZINGS]
BeautifulSoup,
analyze html class.
Hey Emmy.
Yes?
Let me guess, you haven’t had
a bite to eat all day, right?
Was I supposed to?
You want to die?
I’d rather not.
Let’s eat.
But-- whoa.
I’m sleepy.
You’re a real
genius, aren’t you?
Figures.
I call not it on diaper duty.
Does she still
require a babysitter?
There’s no way this girl’s
going to make it on her own.
We wait until
Lupin’s ready to go.
Inspector Zenigata, the
perimeter has them surrounded.
Move in right away.
We don’t want to give
Lupin any time to react.
The cops, huh?
Look, Zenigata’s with them.
Time to split, Emmy.
[GASPS]
Smoke bomb.
We let the water run
open for a reason.
Did we get him?
It’s a decoy.
Don’t think he
got away just yet.
How did they ever
discover the villa?
Because you stand
out way too much.
I doubt they find
Japanese people strange.
You know that’s not
my point, right?
[POLICE SIRENS]
Zenigata?
No, this is someone else.
And I wasn’t even speeding.
Not yet, at least, you weren’t.
That’s right.
[POLICE SIRENS]
[SCREAMING]
[CHUCKLES]
Goemon.
I’ll take care of it.
[YELLING]
[CRASH]
You have a nice day.
Hm?
Those are too high up.
Someone’s awfully lazy.
[SPLASH]
Oh, my poor little Fiat.
Something tells me we’d
best save the goodbyes
for later, Lupin.
[WHIMPERS]
I can’t help but wonder how
many people keep finding us.
The fault is not mine.
I have confirmed that no one’s
planted a bug on us either.
[BEEP]
I got our tickets to Dusseldorf.
That’s fine and dandy,
but something’s up.
Hey, would you check
this out, Jessica?
What are you up to, little one?
It’s the Lupin Game.
A game?
Look here.
"Let’s find Lupin, the
greatest thief of our time.
There’s only one rule."
There’s over 100 million users.
Even if only 10% play,
that means 10 million
are tracking him.
[SNICKERS]
Look at that.
Lupin, you’re caught in
quite an interesting game.
I see.
So this makes everyone
in the world a cop now.
[CHUCKLES]
[THEME MUSIC]
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]