[theme music]
Run- Em-my...
[groans]
[gasps] Lupin!
Lupin!
Ugo, you all right?
Yes.
He just knocked me
over, that’s all.
Thank goodness.
Dolma, we both came here to
Padar just to rescue you!
So why?
Yes, thank you.
However, it’s too late.
Princess!
You OK?
Say, are you people foreigners?
You’re coming with us.
(STRAINED) Emmy, run away.
No, I’m not leaving you here.
Hello, Underworld, come in.
The internet must be down.
[gunshot]
What the hell?
Don’t shoot!
You might hit the princess!
[gasp] Fujiko!
We have to leave.
It’s way too dangerous here.
You need to return to your room.
My necklace vanished.
[explosion]
Fujiko?
So what do we do now?
Let’s land there.
Find the king and both
Shake Hands bosses!
Capture them!
You say you can’t find them?
No, sir.
The king and the
Shake Hands executives
are nowhere to be found.
The coronation won’t be
considered legitimate
if the king doesn’t
abdicate the throne.
This is bad.
If they make it
out of the country,
it could turn into
a real problem.
If you let anxiety
overwhelm you,
you’ll lose battles
you should have won.
We shall declare martial law.
After all, we control the
kingdom’s armed forces.
All we need to do is
ensure they don’t escape.
[sirens]
What are those sirens?
It’s martial law.
Anyone wandering around outside
is an enemy, which is why--
You on the bike!
Stop right there!
Hold on real tight.
[gunfire]
Amazing.
[warning sirens]
What the hell’s
going on around here?
I wonder where Lupin could be.
You two!
What are you doing out here?
Can you not hear the sirens?
Return to your own homes.
What’s the plan?
Perhaps we should leave.
Hold it there!
Stand aside and I will
not take your life.
Hold it there!
Goemon!
Don’t move!
Dammit!
In that case-- how did he?
I avoid needless bloodshed.
So I see.
The bloody teardrop’s vanished.
In all likelihood,
Lupin III’s gang
stole it as they were fleeing.
Yes, sir.
I already have a lot of
men out searching now.
In that case, might I ask
why you haven’t joined them?
I shall join the
search immediately!
Wait!
Huh?
A dear friend of mine from
school is with Lupin’s group.
She must be spared
from any harm.
Of course.
Be certain to treat
her with care.
Right.
And also, you will
uphold your promise
to spare the king’s
life from this coup,
won’t you, high priest?
The gods of Padar
are my witnesses.
[grimaces]
[door opens, closes]
Ugo, this fight will
be a difficult one.
I am prepared to do whatever
it takes, Your Highness.
Just tell me this, would you?
Why did you even spare my life?
What are you talking about?
Your orders were to
kill me and then frame
the terrorists for
it, and yet you’ve
chosen to slip away with me.
Why is that?
My homeland was a small one.
It’s only remarkable feature
with its beautiful sea view.
We were in a state of
constant civil war,
waged for the convenience
of other nations.
People who should have been
neighbors hated each other,
killed each other.
When I see Padar, I can’t
help but remember my own home.
So that is why you would
ask me to take the throne?
Even if you’re just a
puppet, your kingdom
will avoid civil war.
Anything would be much
better than the alternative.
What is your real name?
Ugo.
Well, Ugo, I’ll
accept your proposal.
But I will not sell my soul.
I know, one day, I will
take Padar back from them.
And why are you telling me that?
The battle will
no doubt be long.
But I do not have a single
subject to serve me.
Therefore, you shall be the
first to stand at my side.
[laughs] You do know
that I’m a CIA agent?
My struggle against American
influence will be a long one.
But if I cannot persuade
you to stand by my side,
I won’t get far at all.
[gasps]
With all my strength, I
shall serve you, my princess.
Very well.
I’m depending on
you, my first ally.
[grunts] Boil some water!
See if you can find
any clean utensils.
Thank goodness, it’s running.
R-Run.
Believe me, we’re
already on the run.
Go on without me.
I’ll figure something out.
Is that so?
[screams]
Shut up and save your strength!
Here’s some water.
Bring it here.
Can you do it?
I don’t have much of a choice.
- Hold him.
- Huh?
Hold Lupin down, quickly!
Make sure he doesn’t move!
Here we go.
[strained grunting]
Would you hold still, Lupin?
It’ll be over soon!
At least it didn’t
hit any of his organs.
Talk about lucky.
Cold.
S-So cold.
[shivering]
[sighs]
I got it!
Look!
That a girl, Fuji Cakes!
You know, you can go ahead
and just keep that ring
if you like.
That’s a terrible proposal.
Aw, you’re no fun!
[giggles]
[gunshot]
[gasps] [squeals]
Fujiko!
[pants]
Are you stupid or something?
Well, letting you die alone
seems a little lonely.
I guess so.
If this really is the
end, I should settle down
with a nice guy.
I wonder who I’ll pick.
Aw, don’t be like that.
Do you see any
other guys up here?
Well then, I’ll settle for you.
Hurry up and close the door.
Why did you two break up?
You’re a little too young
to pry into adult affairs.
It’s just that Lupin
is a very intense man.
He’s either smiling or fuming.
But he never looks
sad, except when
he starts talking about you.
He can’t hide it.
Hello?
I found the fugitives.
Across the street.
The address--
Dammit, Lupin, why the hell
haven’t you called us already?
He’ll make it somehow.
It’s Lupin after all.
Yeah, I guess, but even so.
We have been in situations
like this before.
Hm?
Lupin has managed to
overcome all obstacles,
with or without our assistance.
Come on, Goemon.
At certain times, I
wonder whether he has ever
truly needed our aid.
Hmm.
I know Lupin’s around
here somewhere.
He’s the only one who’s have
the gall to impersonate me.
By analyzing the chatter
on social networks,
we can deduce what’s going
on in the capital
right before it even happens.
And because of that, we
were able to make our move
before the coup d’etat began.
Actually, we won the information
war before it even began,
Your Highness.
Just what is this
program you’ve made?
It’s called People Log.
Is that correct?
I thought it was just a
more sophisticated form
of social media.
It’s a torch.
Hm?
And with it, we will illuminate
every dark corner of the world.
Wonderful.
They say fire is what allowed
men to evolve from apes.
Enzo, what’s going to happen
to us when there’s no darkness
left?
Half the world’s
countries will disappear.
Mm-hmm.
Huh?
[laughs]
He’s still sleeping.
That’s because he
knows that sleeping is
the fastest way
to heal any wound.
Huh?
[gunfire]
[squealing]
After them, now!
Attack their password list.
Log in.
There’s another squad
coming from the south.
I thought the internet
was down all across town.
I was able to hack into
the enemy’s network.
Their security is outdated.
Nicely done, partner.
[gasps]
[gunfire]
Open the bag!
There’s grenades inside!
This one?
Yes, throw it at them!
I don’t know how.
Well, now’s a perfect
time to learn how.
[grunts] Pull the pin!
Throw it!
[grunts]
[explosion]
Thank you, Emmy.
Just back there, our
lives were in your hands,
and you saved the three of us.
I’m going to try to lose them.
[engine revs]
Infantry units, I
want a perimeter
of vehicles around the forest!
Looks like this is
as far as we can go.
What do we do now?
We can do this.
[gunfire]
[whimpers]
You aren’t--
You’re going to abandon us?
Let me give you a
piece of advice, kid.
If you want to live, try
to find a bush to hide in
and don’t move a
muscle, all right?
That seems about as much as
you can manage right now.
Fujiko Mine, I was almost
starting to respect you.
But you really are
as bad as I thought.
How can you dump Lupin
and abandon us like this?
(YELLING) How can
you be so selfish?
It’s like I told you.
I’m a woman who’s always
loyal to her desires.
[engine revs]
You suck!
Die, you stupid witch!
Lupin, we won’t
get fooled again.
Command, I’ve located the
bloody teardrop necklace!
She’s on a motorcycle
heading northwest with it!
[panting]
I’m not going to let
it end like this.
I have to--
I have to save Lupin.
[grunts]
[gunfire]
[whimpers]
I’ve got them!
Lupin’s here!
[grunting]
I’ve got you now,
you damn shrew.
Hey, Mr. Captain, how
about we do a trade?
Do you really think you’re
in any position to negotiate?
I’m sure you’d prefer to
get the bloody teardrop back
in one piece, right?
Plus I have a juicy bit of
intel you’re just going to love.
[grumbles]
What do you say the
two of us talk it over?
Hm?
Go.
Are you sure, sir?
That’s an order.
[grumbles] Yes, sir.
Shoot as soon as the door opens.
Are you sure about that, sir?
The only order I received
was to retrieve the bloody
teardrop necklace.
How we get it doesn’t
really matter.
Armed forces loyal to the king
have begun their counterattack.
What did you say?
They’ve already taken back
control of the TV station.
His Majesty has started
broadcasting
an address to the nation.
Is that true?
Wait a minute.
The king’s still alive?
Hey, that’s not
what we were told!
Last update that I
heard was that we still
had control of every
road in the capital.
Was there a traitor in our camp?
Look!
It’s the airship, sir!
We really should
get out of here!
Is it crashing?
Retreat!
Everyone retreat!
But what about
the necklace, sir?
Now’s not the time!
Come on!
We gotta go!
- Get out of here!
- It’s coming right for us!
[grumbles] Huh?
Hey, you!
We’re moving out!
Wait a sec is that--
Lupin III!
Fujiko!
Hm?
Lupin?
Fujiko!
[grunts]
That idiot.
You can’t run like that!
Well, it certainly
looks like you love her.
Lupin, you’re not
getting away this time!
Stay away!
Just tell me, Lupin,
what am I to you anyway?
Hm?
[grunts] Eat lead!
Fujiko, you’ve always been my--
[crashing]
[japanese singing]