- MAN: We’ve confirmed that
the students are safe--
seven wounded, none seriously.
One student and one teacher
are still unaccounted for.
According to one
of the other students,
they were flown
out by helicopter.
Civil aviation detected
an unidentified helicopter
but lost it near the border.
- What is the meaning
of all this?
You want me to save Padar?
- As you know,
Padar is split
between the reform movement
spearheaded by the King
and the traditionalists
led by Padar’s high priest.
- I side with the reformers.
My father is
correct when he says
Padar must move with the times.
- My firm would rather
avoid any reforms
that could lead
to internal strife.
- I see your game.
You are hoping to take me
out in the chaos caused
by those terrorists, right?
- Hm.
- Just tell me this, would you?
Why did you even spare my life?
- GOEMON:
Look, Emmy is among them.
- Hm?
- Hm.
- JIGEN:
Isn’t that Fujiko behind her?
- Let’s move.
- Giving up?
- Don’t be daft.
-Then where are we going?
- Do I have to spell
it out for you?
I’m a thief...
and I haven’t
bagged my score just yet.
[chuckle]
♪ [jazzy theme music]
♪
- Two weeks after the incident
at the school in Annecy,
Princess Dolma has been
successfully rescued
from her terrorist captors
by the CIA agents and
the American Special Forces.
- That’s the cover story.
The CIA had a hand in the
attack in the first place.
- But it was
the Wails of Liberation
that carried out the attack.
- But it was
the Wails of Liberation
that carried out the attack.
However, there’s
a very good chance
the CIA were looking to
capitalize on it as well.
- Huh?
So the helicopter that got
Princess Dolma
actually belonged to the CIA?
- Well, Padar is the location of
America’s strategic bridgehead
in South Asia.
Something’s going on there,
down in that little kingdom.
- LUPIN: These clowns think
they can just swoop in
and swipe my loot?
I’ll show them.
- Hm?
- Outside traffic isn’t
allowed in the new district.
On one side of the river
is the new district,
which was built with the help
of the ShakeHanz Corporation,
the famous IT company.
And on the other side, you
have the historic old town.
- What is your destination?
- Who’s that?
- Hey, did the car
just say something?
- Mr. Daisuke Jigen-- welcome
to the kingdom of Padar.
- What the hell?
- Would you like me to take
you to the New Padar Hotel?
- It knows our reservation,
too?
What’s going on here?
- When we crossed the border,
remember we had to say where
we were staying?
The idea is to
use our biometrics
to recognize us
and service our every need
during our stay
in the city.
Oh wow!
It’s really 100% driverless.
- Seems pretty
science fiction-y.
[sirens]
- This is a no smoking area.
- Huh?
- Please refrain
from smoking
or relocate to an authorized
smoking area.
- Sorry, did I say
science fiction-y?
I meant more like Big Brother.
[interposing voices]
- Here.
- WOMAN: This is a lovely city,
Ling.
Seems you boys are another step
closer to realizing your dream.
- Thank you, Fujiko.
But where do we stand
on fulfilling
that other lovely dream of mine?
- What other dream?
- Going to see the
northern lights with you.
- Hm.
I must admit, I didn’t take
you for the romantic type,
what with the whole global
IT thing you’ve got going.
- I’m just a mere
business partner.
Enzo is the real hero here.
- Can you get to the point?
Adults waste too much
time on small talk.
- Can you get to the point?
Adults waste too much
time on small talk.
- And children are
too direct and rather rude.
- [sigh]
- You want to know
about Princess Dolma?
She’s currently being
taken care of at a hospital.
- [gasp]
Was she injured?
- Psychologically.
- [gasp]
- She has acute stress
disorder brought on
by getting caught up
in that terrorist attack.
- She didn’t seem like a fragile
little princess to me.
- No one really knows the truth.
She’s not allowed visitors.
Even the King has been
barred from seeing her.
- [sigh]
- The King and his people
haven’t caught on yet.
With this, we’ll finally
be able to take back Padar.
[interposing voices]
- MAN: Thanks a lot.
- The princess’ hospital
is right here in the old town
so she can relax, supposedly.
- WOMAN: Piping hot!
Fresh fried samosas.
Get them here.
- Oh man, tasty!
Can I get three, please?
- Sure thing.
They’re really
hot, so be careful.
So, Mister, are
you a photographer?
Are you here for Princess Dolma?
- Oh, is it that obvious?
- Well, you don’t
look like a tourist,
and foreigners on
business usually stick
to the new district.
- Gah!
- You big baby.
- Hot! Hot!
- Oh.
Man, it’s hot!
Ho, oh, oh!
- [giggling]
Man, it’s hot!
Ho, oh, oh!
- [giggling]
Well, Mister, the
simosas are on the house.
But please don’t track
down Princess Dolma.
- People around here really
care about the princess, huh?
- Before she was
shipped off to school,
she used to come by a lot.
Princess Dolma looked
so happy eating her samosas.
- [panting]
- Catch!
- Oh.
Hot! Hot!
[interposing voices]
- I actually heard
this from a very--
- No security cameras
in this day and age.
What an analog hospital.
- Heh, see you around.
- Apparently, she’s not
actually in the hospital.
- Used your feminine wiles
again?
- People with smarts
become scholars.
And people with fast legs
become athletes, right?
What’s wrong with playing
to your strong points?
- What can I get you ladies?
- I’ll have a cup of chai.
- I want a bowl of
buttered Padar yak stew.
- Huh?
- What is that?
- Dolma-- uh!
A friend of mine
made it for me once.
She said it was
a Padar specialty.
- I’m impressed
you’ve heard of it,
but we don’t serve it here.
Most restaurants
don’t serve it either.
- Why not?
- Because yaks are
servants of the gods.
It’s a special dish
you should eat
only with your family
or those who
you hold close to your heart.
only with your family
or those who
you hold close to your heart.
- (VOICEOVER) Dolma...
- [muffled grunt]
- Huh?
- LUPIN: A princess
miraculously rescued
from the clutches
of the terrorists
who had kidnapped her.
And a very cute
princess at that.
Any picture of her would
be front page fodder.
- Sounds like the sort
of thing
paparazzi would just
drool over.
- And yet for some reason,
no pictures have surfaced.
- GOEMON: They cannot photograph
someone they cannot find.
- So where would
even the paparazzi
have trouble getting into?
- Probably places run
by the military.
- Reporting for duty, sir.
[grunting]
- Congratulations!
- Uh...
- It’s your birthday
today, isn’t it?
Here you go.
- Uh, yeah, thanks.
- [sighs]
It’s his birthday, huh?
- Boy, now I feel really
guilty for what we did.
- Stop right there!
- [gasp]
- Tomorrow at 1700 hours,
there’s going to be
a special exercise.
Just be prepared.
- What was that?
- Soldiers whispering
among themselves.
And there’s a big rift
between the reformers
and the traditionalists.
Add it all together and--
- A coup d’etat, right?
- Oh great high priest,
the commanding officer
of the eighth artillery
regiment has joined our cause.
- We’re using an emergency
urban training exercise
as a pretext for mobilizing
our allied forces.
- What about
the Shake Hanz Corporation?
- Don’t worry, sir.
We have avoided
using the internet
to communicate or coordinate
any plans for the coup d’etat.
- We won’t let
those capitalist misers
have free reign over Padar.
- We have just received word
from our superiors in Langley.
America is going to maintain
its neutral stance in public.
But behind the scenes,
we will be secretly
supporting the coup.
- CIA agents are truly
naturals at this.
- I want to apologize to you all
for the changes in the plan
regarding Princess Dolma.
- I won’t deny requests
from our sponsors.
As long as I am
the true authority,
I have no issues.
- Yes, but of course,
mister high priest.
- A freaking coup d’etat.
This has turned
into a real drag.
- What now, Lupin?
- What’s the deal?
This just means we’re
dealing with fellow thieves.
The only difference is
they want the country
and I want the girl.
I’m not going to let them
make a fool of us.
- Heh.
And all along,
I thought you had
your heart set on a necklace.
- Heh.
And all along,
I thought you had
your heart set on a necklace.
- This is the fifth
airborne regiment.
We’re ready to descend on
the designated control point.
- This is the second combat
engineering regiment.
We’re ready and waiting to
blow the fiber optic cables.
- Try to hurry, all right?
- Mm-hm.
- Something sounds off to me.
- I hear sight and hearing
are the first things to go
when you get old.
- All right, you really
don’t like me, do you?
- That’s right.
- How come?
- Huh?
[sigh]
- The coup d’etat is under way.
In six hours time,
you will be queen.
- And a puppet.
[dramatic Padar music]
- [gasp]
[interposing voices]
- We now control the Ministry
of Home Affairs
and the Central Police
Headquarters.
- The ministers for finance
and trade are in custody.
- We know occupy the Royal
Communications Center.
- The royal guards
are staying neutral.
No sign of any
movement from them.
- A request for an audience
with his excellency
the high priest himself.
- At a time like this?
- Get rid of him.
I’m here because I heard Lupin
sent one of his calling cards
to this location.
- Who are you?
You can’t just barge in here!
- I’m Inspector Zenigata
with the ICPO.
Lupin’s after the Bloody
Teardrop Necklace.
- Oh, I thought that was
some kind of prank.
But the bloody teardrop
isn’t even here.
Princess Dolma
has taken it with her.
- Are you saying Lupin
sent a calling card
to the wrong location?
- It certainly would
seem that way.
- [laughter]
- It certainly would
seem that way.
- [laughter]
- Hm?
- I know Lupin.
And while he may be a fool,
he’s not stupid.
If he sent the card here--
- Freeze!
- Don’t move!
--it simply must be here!
- Are you calling his
excellency a liar?
- Hm.
Well, if you insist,
you can join
the palace’s security detail.
After all, you seem to
know this Lupin quite well.
- It’s my pleasure.
- Amore.
- Yes, sir.
Give the inspector
here an overview
of the palace’s security.
- Yes, your excellency.
- No security cameras at all?
- Our palace has used
traditional methods
for 600 years.
Besides, using machines
makes you dependent on them.
- Smart thinking there.
Not much for a hacker
to sink their teeth into.
And 600 years--
that’s certainly quite a lot
of tradition to uphold.
Uh!
This palace is wonderful!
- [grunt]
- Whoa, whoa!
- [gasp]
You idiot!
[gasp]
- Hey, thanks for the tour!
- Why you--
- You want to tell me where
Princess Dolma is being held?
- No.
- Okay.
- You want to tell me where
Princess Dolma is being held?
- No.
- Okay.
Are there any parts of
the palace that have been
declared off limits lately?
- [grumbles]
- Do you really want
to die here?
Wouldn’t your family be sad?
- [gasp]
- You all look really happy
in that picture
you had tucked away in
your wallet.
Right, Papa?
- [groan]
The west tower.
- Thanks, pal.
Now, then.
Time to wrap this up
before
they catch on to anything.
- It’s Zenigata with the ICPO.
That’s right, give me
everything you can.
- Oh!
- What is it?
- I think it got
caught on something.
- Oh!
- What is it?
- I think it got
caught on something.
See, it looks like
the right wheel’s stuck.
Oh.
- Dolma, I’m almost there.
- Huh?
- How’s the backup?
- It’s all good.
Just checked it the other day.
- Wha?
- Huh?
- Shut down all access to
the internet immediately.
If you truly love this kingdom,
you will cooperate with us.
- I’m heading to the west tower.
I’m thinking it’s about time
that our little princess
entered the picture.
- [gasp]
[wind blowing]
[whimpering]
[gasp]
Don’t look down.
[whimpering]
[wind blowing]
Pull it together.
Fujiko would laugh at you.
[grunting]
- Isn’t it a little late for
you to be out and about?
- [gasp]
- All school girls should
have gone home by now.
- You don’t get to pretend
you’re a teacher anymore.
Where’s Dolma?
- You think you have
a fighting chance here?
- I’m filming this.
You OK with footage
of a CIA agent
shooting a civilian
showing up online?
[gasp]
- I’m afraid that bluff
doesn’t make the grade.
It earns you no points.
- [grunting]
- Hm.
- There’s no way you made
it here on your own.
Give me the names of
everyone you’re working with.
- Save me, someone,
any one...
Lupin...
- LUPIN: How immature.
Give it a rest.
-Hm?
- [groaning]
- Oh, good, it’s--
- Lupin III,
here to engage
his excellency the high priest
in a thieving competition.
- Ugh-
[coughing]
- You OK, Emmy?
Good grief, it was crazy
to try to do this solo.
- Lupin.
- Lupin!
Stop right there.
- You American meddler.
What are you even doing here?
I’m guessing you CIA goons
are the ones who are really
pulling the strings behind
this entire coup, aren’t you?
Probably in the name of world
peace or some other crap.
But all you really
want is to make things
more convenient for yourselves.
Compared to guys like me
who freely
admit to being crooks,
you’re several degrees nastier.
- Just shut up, you.
- Oh, but I won’t.
You think
you’re untouchable
just because
you’re a sizable country
with the best army
and mountains of cash.
Is that it?
Why don’t you get
over yourselves?
- Whatever you’re stalling
for, it won’t work.
- Oh, shut up.
- [gasp]
If you’re going to be a lapdog,
then stick to howling like one.
[grunt]
[gunshot]
-[gasp]
See, that’s the thing
about working for royalty.
You really got to
take it seriously.
- Lupin!
- Hey, Emmy.
Are you OK?
- What are you doing here?
- I came to get you.
- Uh?
- Uh--
- Just stop with the
dumb jokes, OK?
Getting Dolma out
of here is why I’m--
Ah-
Dolma!
I came to save you.
Let’s get out of here.
- Why are you here?
- It’s because we are friends.
- [gasp]
[gunshot]
- Hey, we’re in the middle of
a heart warming reunion here!
- [grunt]
- Could you possibly not
ruin it for their sake?
[arrow launching]
Uh!
Uh, what the--
- Uh, why?
But--
- [panting]
- Run, Emmy-- uh.
- [gasp]
Lupin!
♪ [jazzy music plays]
♪ [Japanese singing]