[suspenseful music]
[gun shot]
Lupin!
Huh?
The Border Patrol--
Inspector, you can’t!
Let go, Yata I’m still off-duty!
[grunting]
Zenigata, we have to go.
Lupin’s dead.
And right now, it’s up to us
to do what only we can do.
- Hey, Pops, if anything bad
should ever happen to me,
can you please help her?
[growls]
That damn stubborn fool.
I’m going to do
something only I can do.
[theme music]
[clicking noises]
Once again, it seems my wife’s
obsessed with another man--
Ricky, the search dog.
[laughter]
The world will join
hands, like this.
And more news now on
the recent dismantling
of an art forgery ring.
The chief of
the French Central Directorate
of the Judicial Police,
Albert d’Andresy has said his--
Hey--
--organization’s collaboration
with the General Directorate--
You remember that game that
went viral a while back?
No, which one?
You know-- that game
about catching that thief?
Ah!
I think it ended when
he was killed, right?
Isn’t that it.
Yes, that’s right.
Do you remember his name?
Hm-- wasn’t it something
foreign sounding?
[gasps]
I thought so.
Inspector Zenigata, you’re
going to be working narcotics
from now on.
But sir, that’s simply not fair!
The inspector was just
trying to arrest Lupin, and--
It was broadcast to
the entire world.
And it looked like he was seen
assisting a known criminal.
You’ve been after
Lupin all this time.
But he’s dead now.
Hm-- enough is enough.
I understand, sir.
Huh?
Inspector Zenigata--
Transferring?
Yeah-- narcotics now.
[slurping]
Mm-- Lupin’s not dead.
I won’t believe it till I
see it with my own eyes.
Zenigata--
Hm?
This pasta soba is pretty good--
yeah.
That so?
Glad you like it.
Mm-hm.
I’m heading out.
Have a safe trip.
Huh?
What’s up?
Is this necessary?
Routines are important.
When you stay at my place,
you have to play by my rules.
[smirks]
Hello, Underworld.
[beeping]
Verify session information
from web crawl.
Check stacks.
Once the indexing
is completed,
search for any
unique passwords.
[digital beeping]
[doorbell buzzing]
IP camera network-- front door.
Hello, I’m here to
deliver a message.
[beeping]
Huh?
Hm.
[clears throat]
So who is Underworld?
[beeping]
[smirks]
Hello, and welcome to
Marco Polo’s Castle.
Castle?-- more like
an amusement park.
Crazy girl, job hunting with
the people you stole from?
I can turn the Marco Polo
website and its payment system
security into something
a little less shoddy.
You’ve seen how scary getting
hacked can be after all.
How dare you say that to me?
Who better to say something
like that than me?
[growls]
Take a seat.
I can’t offer you
any drinks though.
Why is there only one seat here?
Our deal was for us
to meet face-to-face.
[giggles]
You really think you’re in
any position to negotiate?
Do you really think I
only made one back door?
Threats, huh?
Well, in that case--
[rumbling noise]
And here, I thought stuff
like this only happened
in the movies.
Same here-- but what can I say?
I wanted to give it a shot.
I guess you’re the bad guy then.
We’ve both been the bad guys
from the beginning--
a hacker and a drug dealer.
Let’s get started.
Tell me about
Lupin’s collection.
Is that not the only reason
you agreed to meet with me?
You hung around with
Lupin for a bit.
Hide outs, passwords--
tell me everything you saw.
We’re going to take
back everything
he took from us and then some.
Don’t expect the water
to stop, unless you talk.
I’m the bad guy, after all.
When I first touched a
computer, I was so excited.
I could go anywhere
and meet anybody.
It felt just like
the sky was my limit.
I know.
That’s how I felt when I got
my very first motorcycle.
I got praise for
the code I wrote
from people all over the world.
And that same world stopped
treating me like a child.
Information, money, security--
I could easily access them all.
I couldn’t care less
about your life story.
Tell me about
Lupin’s collection!
However, one day, it
stopped being exciting.
But I didn’t have the
courage to change.
Huh?
That was when he showed
up from the hell-hole
I call the real world.
And I accepted his
invitation to go outside.
Start talking about Lupin.
Why do women always talk
about this emotional crap?
But the real world was
just as much of a hellhole
as I thought it would be--
inconvenient, unpleasant,
hot, and-- most of all--
dangerous.
Quit screwing around.
Talk now, or you’ll die.
However, it was exciting!
It gave me the best
high I’ve ever had.
Ugh!
Idiot!-- how
stubborn can you be?
[phone ringing]
Huh?
What the hell do you want?
Is your real name Chuck Clay?
Our pics were just
posted on Happy Death Day
with our real names!
What in the hell?!
[beeping]
Ugh!
But Lupin’s already dead!
His friends must have done it.
Damn! Then put them up too.
Put Jigen and Goemon’s
names up there on the list.
What’s the point?
Even if we do that, our names
will still be on the site!
Huh!
[frightened gasping]
[screaming]
Hey there, Chuck,
what’s going on?
Was it a hit man?
Ugh-- damn it.
Don’t you dare!
- Sounds like the hit men
have already found you.
- Huh?
What in the hell’s going on?
How are you still talking?
If you’re curious, why
don’t you come down here.
We can make a deal.
I can remove your name
and photo off that website
if you agree to that.
You think I believe you?
You think you have
much of a choice?
[growls]
First, we meet face-to-face.
Then we can talk.
[heavy breathing]
You’re serious about getting
my name off the website, right?
I hacked it back
when I was trying
to get Lupin’s name removed.
But I broke in too
late to save him.
All right-- you get my
name off that website,
and I will save your life.
Save my life?
I’m pretty sure I’m the
one saving your life.
We’re equals now.
Sorry-- my bad.
I’ll pick my words
more carefully.
Huh?
It’s open?
OK, I’m here now, Underworld.
Now then, get us
off that website!
No way!
Lupin III?
There’s no way!
But I saw you die
with my own eyes!
Besides--
It’s AR.
You see, I knew all
about your little trap,
you Bond villain wannabe.
So I got Emmy to program an AR
filter with underwater effects.
Huh!
[scoffs]
Huh?
Now that’s it.
You’re alive, because--
You’re a little slow
on the uptake, bub.
That drone was ours all along.
[gun shot]
Emmy used AR to
make it look like I
died that day to everyone
watching the stream.
It wasn’t easy, standing in the
right spot to match the filter.
I’ve been playing you like a
violin from the very start.
Fujiko was meant to be
the one to make the kill.
But old-man Zenigata
got in the way.
So we had to improvise.
That bastard, the whole
time he was in Buwanda,
he had us figured out.
[heavy breathing]
Ah!
Agh!
You’re not going
anywhere, buddy.
Stay there.
So long.
It was fun while it
lasted, children.
Move-- and I strike.
We have your partners’
locations as well.
Jigen and Goemon are
rounding them up as we speak.
[cowering gasps]
That gun is not a toy, right?
Huh?
[stammering]
Are you ready to put
your life on the line?
[frightened stammering]
Because if you don’t
have what it takes,
then you shouldn’t be a villain.
You should just
play by the rules,
like everybody else does.
[frightened stammering]
See ya--
That’s far enough, Lupin!
Wait-- Pops!
How did you know?
I left him a note
with our location.
What?
Why would you do that?
Lupin, if you shoot him,
I’ll have to take you down
for being a murderer as well.
You’re not even surprised
that I’m still alive?
I saw what happened.
Did you really think
your scheme could
trick this inspector’s eyes?
[laughs]
And here, I was
thinking the smoke
would have helped a little.
[frightened stammering]
Hold it you.
We’re not done yet.
That old timer is
Zenigata from the ICPO.
He’s every villain’s
worst nightmare.
Hm.
What’s the call?
You could always call it quits
if the stakes are too high.
Cough up enough info,
and they might even
keep you safe for
a decade or two--
behind bars of course.
Time to choose-- your
life or your freedom.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
I can’t!
[frightened stammering]
Please-- please, arrest me.
Would you, Inspector?
I sell drugs.
And I’m a real bad
man-- so please!
Will you testify?
Anything you want--
I beg you!
All right.
It looks like, in the end,
you were never a match for me.
Ah!
See ya, Pops!
Eh-- huh?
Hold it! Lupin!
Emmy!
It’s Ami.
Zenigata, thank you.
No need to thank me.
I’m just doing my job.
Don’t leave me alone!
I’m begging you!
We’re going to have
a nice long chat.
After all, I just got
transferred to narcotics.
[phone ringing]
OK, it’s done.
Were you calling to say thanks?
Just wanted to let you know.
It’s nothing personal.
Even though you turned to
me in your time of need?
Well, out of all
the women I know,
there’s no one in the world
that can lie quite like you.
You know, a bit of gratitude
would be appreciated.
You mean, winning the
bounty from Happy Death Day
isn’t gratitude enough,
Miss Drone Fighter ?
I guess so.
The payment arrived, just
like you promised me.
So with that, the job is done.
And we’re left with no more
reasons to keep talking.
That’s true.
Everything’s been said.
Well, not between us anyway.
[phone clicks]
Hm.
It’s no problem at all.
You’re both regulars.
And I know you guys.
Here.
Thank you so much.
This old coot’s gone senile.
You’re the one who
forgot the pepper.
No, it was definitely you.
They live upstairs?
Huh?
Oh, yeah-- they hadn’t come
down here to eat in a while,
so I was getting a little
bit worried about them.
[grinding noise]
I hear Zenigata’s
has been allowed
to return to his previous post.
That’s right.
When you bring down Marco
Polo, you get rewarded.
I guess I’m back playing
hide-and-seek with pops.
Talk about a pain in the neck.
I must say, this European
shabu shabu is delicious.
It’s cheese fondue, man.
By the way, whatever
happened with Emmy?
She’s going to school now--
a boarding school, that is.
[birds chirping]
Mm--
Think you can make
it on your own?
I’m not sure.
Come now.
But I feel really excited.
Huh?
I see.
Very good.
Mm-hm.
Hey, Lupin, do you remember
back when I asked you
why you don’t just retire?
Yeah.
You’ve stolen
enough money to live
in luxury for the rest
of your life, right?
And it’s not like you’re
obsessed with art.
No shortage of ladies either.
I have always wondered--
why risk the danger
of being a thief?
Why keep at it
after all this time?
And what’s your
diagnosis, doctor?
Because it’s exciting.
Here’s to you, kiddo.
[smirks]
Hm.
Anyway, I found
something interesting.
That’s of Spain, right?
That map seems reversed, though.
So let’s hear your plan.
Yeah-- you’re going to find
this one pretty exciting, guys.
[theme music]
[singing in japanese]