[somber music playing]
I am really looking forward
to seeing his reaction.
It’s been a while, Gaston.
Yeah, just how long has it been?
What is it, 10 years, or 20?
At the very least, it was
back when you were still
just wet behind the ears.
That so.
I’d wager it was before
your hands started to shake.
[laugh]
So what was it that made you
call me out here like this?
I can’t imagine you got me
here just to reminisce, right?
The truth is, Lupin, I’ve got
a job only you can pull off.
A job?
Are you trying to land a
big score, or something?
Not exactly.
Besides, I’ve been
retired for a while now.
Ah, now, quit making me
feel so blue, Gaston.
It’s sad to hear that from the
criminal world’s god of forgery
himself.
I need you to retrieve something
for me, against the wishes
of its owner, naturally.
That’s as easy as pie.
I’d dive headfirst
into any fire or vault
you asked, since you helped me
back when I was starting out.
This isn’t going
to be a cakewalk.
I’m asking you to
steal from Mr. B.
That just makes me even
more excited to do it.
Yeah, I kind of thought
that would be the case.
How much time do you think
you’ll need to prepare?
Three days seems
just about right.
I’ll be looking forward to it.
In that case, we can both meet
back here at the same time
next week.
Ah, come on.
You don’t believe me?
Of course I believe you.
That’s why I’ll be paying
you upfront this time.
Huh?
Oh.
Is this--
Napoleon’s Bible, a one of a
kind item from the library he
called a personal collection.
Hm.
Hmph!
It’s a replica, right?
It’s just a bit of fun, is all.
But when my time
has come, would you
please read a prayer
from it in my name?
Hm?
[typewriter]
Oh, slow down a little, Mr. B.
Ah, you don’t understand.
I’ve waited so long for a
moment alone like this with you.
Then, waiting another few
minutes won’t kill you, right?
Huh?
Wait here, ’K?
I’ll go freshen up.
[groan]
Good grief, what
a horny old man.
The retinal capture
looks good, huh?
The fingerprints, too.
Fujiko, how long are you going
to be in that shower, anyway?
I can’t wait much
longer, you know.
Huh?
Ah, crap!
[music playing]
Hm!
Man, talk about a cliche.
Let’s go.
Retina and fingerprints.
If you only knew
the sort of things
I had to do to get these ready.
Huh?
Well, will you look at that.
Check it out.
This little stash must easily
be worth millions of dollars.
But I’ve seen tidier junkyards,
if I’m being honest about it.
The guy buys every
piece of art he sees
just so he can say he owns it.
But once he has it,
he loses interest.
So he ends up hoarding all
this incredible treasure
in a hole like this.
It could be a masterpiece.
But once it’s down here, it’ll
never see the light of day
again.
That’s why...
I’ve heard that people say
that the B and Mr. B actually
stands for black hole.
Found it!
Eh!
What is that?
Oh, just a previously
unknown Picasso that’s never
seen the light of day.
Eh?
But this just looks like
something a kid doodled to me.
You have got a sharp eye.
Huh?
Gaston’s grandkid was actually
the one who drew that.
Then Gaston forged Picasso’d
signature on it as a joke.
And everybody thinks that
this is the real deal?
All kinds of experts
examined it and agreed.
That’s Gaston, for you.
When you’re a master
of your craft,
even a little prank
can cause trouble.
[laugh]
And that goes for you, too.
Hm?
We’re DGSE.
And we’re joining you
on this investigation.
Hmph!
I see, the directorate
general for external security.
I believe Director Guillaume
probably sent them.
Now that they made their
move, we know who wanted it.
Director, what should we do?
In any interpretation
of the law,
this case is clearly
a police matter.
An intelligence agency
getting involved
is overstepping their authority.
We’ll let them have their fun.
The more in play, the
more exciting it gets.
Albert, talking shop so
early in the morning?
No, just having some fun.
There’s something
weird about this.
What’s weird?
What do you mean?
It almost looks
like a real Picasso.
The composition is similar
to his Las Meninas series.
Well, isn’t it supposed
to look genuine?
It’s a forgery by a
master, after all.
Did you forget?
The painting was done
by Gaston’s grandkid.
And he just slapped
Picasso’s signature on it.
The fact that it looks so much
like a real Picasso is weird.
Well, is there any chance that
it could be just a coincidence?
Something just doesn’t
smell right about this.
Are we talking about
the stench of being
saddled with a bad-luck magnet?
More like the
aroma of a lie that
was sold a little too hard.
So what’s the plan?
Hold your nose, pretend
we didn’t notice anything,
and just hand it over?
Guess I’ve got to start digging.
Hm?
Hey, business doing well?
What do you want, Lupin?
Are you hard-up for
cash and finally
looking to sell me some
of your collection?
You wish.
I am curious about
this piece, though.
Hm.
After all, you come
across all sorts of things
that can’t be sold legally.
I figured that you’d be the
guy to talk to about it.
It’s trash.
It doesn’t have a shred
of artistic value.
The frame on it’s
probably worth more.
Even with Picasso’s
signature on it?
Hm?
I’m guessing by that
reaction that you
know what’s really going on.
All right, then.
Let’s talk about
this down below.
Whoa, what’s going on, here?
Degas, Monet, Delacroix, you’ve
got a collection to rival Mr.
B’s.
How the hell could you
possibly compare me
to that artistically-illiterate
barbarian?
Doesn’t stop you from selling
to him, though, doesn’t it?
Ah, that’s just business.
Incidentally, I was the one
who sold this piece to Mr. B
in the first place.
You were?
Gaston himself asked me to.
Say what?
It’s been more than
just a couple of years
since Gaston asked me to
sell this painting to Mr. B,
you know.
At first, I thought it
was some stupid prank.
But I soon realized why.
Any piece of art Mr. B
buys gets locked away
and never sees the
light of day again.
So wouldn’t that
make his collection
the perfect place
to hide something?
That makes sense.
But there is a problem
with that plan.
What do you do if you
need to get it back?
Mr. B never lets anything
escape his grasp once it’s his,
isn’t that right?
True.
But if that’s the
case, then it’s
a darn good thing Gaston has
an old friend that can even
steal from a black hole.
Isn’t that right?
Hey, we’re being followed.
You’re right.
Hm.
Heh.
[music playing]
[panting]
You don’t give up
so easy, do you?
[laugh]
That didn’t work.
Guess I’ll have to try
harder to ditch this guy.
Hey, up here!
Huh?
[groan]
Don’t move!
Place the package on the
ground by your feet, slowly.
Good.
Now, put your hands above your--
[groan]
Got to say, sneaking up
on a man from behind just
doesn’t feel right in my book.
Hey, nice assist,
there, partner!
Heh!
Hm, these guys are
from the DGSE, huh?
No wonder they
were so persistent.
Listen, Lupin, if these guys
were watching Aghion’s shop
before, that means--
They figured out where Mr.
B got his paintings from.
So then, they’re after
this thing, too, huh?
Seems that way.
What are you doing?
I figured I’d just ask
the man in charge himself
and confirm as to why
they’re coming after me.
Hm!
[phone buzzing]
Yeah, hello?
(ON PHONE) I assume you’re
the head of the DGSE?
Who the hell is this?
I’m the guy who has that little
thing you guys are looking for.
You’re Lupin?
And to be frank, I have
enough on my plate already
playing hide and seek
with Inspector Zenigata.
So how about a trade?
[groan] Hm?
Don’t turn around.
This is what you’re
after, right?
You mentioned a
trade over the phone.
Just what do you want, exactly?
Money?
Hm?
Hm.
How about you enlighten
me about something, first.
Why are the DGSE so desperate
to get their hands on this?
What’s the point of asking that?
Curiosity.
Curiosity killed
the rat, you know.
Oh, wait, was it the cat?
Maybe it was the dog.
[groan]
Mm.
Hey!
Don’t move!
[music playing]
Oh, man, I didn’t
realize you guys
had this place so locked down.
I said don’t make a move!
Keep your hands off
that damned earpiece!
Wow, you guys know
me really well.
Well, if it’s going
to be the end,
do you mind if I at
least say a prayer first?
Oh, my lord.
Let there be light.
[beeping]
Huh?
Ah!
He’s getting oh away!
Go!
Kill him if you have to!
So that book is what
you were really after.
Lupin!
How did you--
I don’t mind it when
he asks for help.
But I hope he knows I’m no
better at dodging bullets
than him.
The questions come later.
First things first, hand
that book over here.
Hurry up, now.
Whoa, there.
Putting the pedal to the
metal isn’t going to throw off
my aim any, you know.
It’ll just redecorate
the car with your brains.
What’s written in there, anyway?
Places where you can
find stashed loot?
Nothing as nice as that.
Carne Noir, the Black Notebook.
This thing holds the details
of every misdeed and crime
committed and covered up by
the French police’s top brass.
Sounds like internal
affairs would love it.
If the stuff in
here went public,
you can forget the DGSE.
Even the interior
minister would be--
[groan] [laugh]
Must be one hell of
a ticking time bomb,
from the perspective
of the cops.
Which is probably
why their bosses
have been trying to keep
it firmly in the shadows.
And yet, here it is
in your very hands.
Yeah.
But how did Gaston get
himself mixed up in something
that’s this messed up?
I’m a little early
for our meeting.
But I guess I should
go and talk to him.
You’re going to talk
to Gaston, you mean?
I’ve been getting chased high
and low because of this thing.
I say we should see what the
old coot has to say for himself.
Director, Lupin has left Paris.
Uh...
Director?
There’s no need
to fret about it.
He and the notebook will
return right back to me
in their own time.
Hey, now, are you suddenly going
all religious on me, Lupin?
What’s on your mind, huh?
Hm?
I guess I’m wondering
why Gaston gave me
this thing in the first place.
Well, from that
look on your face,
I’m guessing only God
knows, at this point.
Hasn’t changed at all, or
I wish I could say that.
It’s actually
pretty rundown now.
Is Gaston’s place
anywhere nearby?
Nah, if he’s in the same
place, it’s pretty far.
A taxi?
What gives you the idea
any taxis come here?
There’s no one to pick up.
Ugh!
So much for that.
The only option left now
is doing this on foot.
Mister, so where
are you going to?
I’m looking to meet
up with Gaston.
Ah...
You won’t be able to,
even if you go there.
Huh?
He’s six feet under.
What?
See, Gaston passed away
about a month ago now.
No way!
That’s ridiculous!
I met up with him
just the other day!
And-- uh.
In this world, there is only
one who is without falsehood.
And that one is the Lord.
Huh.
If that’s the case, then
who is the Gaston you met?
A ghost?
But when my time
has come, would you
please read a prayer
from it in my name?
Albert.
Who’s Albert?
Know who he is?
Yeah, he’s the last guy I ever
wanted to deal with again.
[music playing]
[singing in japanese]