My name... is
Yukinari Sasaki.
I'm just your average
high school student.
Except for being
allergic to women
and breaking out in a rash
whenever one touched me,
my day-to-day life
was pretty quiet.
But ever since that day
I was transported to Seiren,
a planet of almost all women,
my life has changed completely.
That's where I met Miharu,
the one girl
I'm not allergic to.
She came back to earth
with me somehow,
and now we live together.
There's also my
best friend, Kirie;
Fukuyama, our resident pervert;
his kooky sister, Lisa;
and some other
visitors from Seiren:
Koyomi, who's afraid of men;
Tomoka who's a legend
in her own mind;
and Ebi, our
extra-terrestrial pet.
Life is anything but boring.
I wonder what else
is in store for me.
Hey, you, lookin' good!
You did remember to send that
letter to Koyomi, didn't you?
[LILICA] Indeed, just
as you ordered, Master.
Today... today I finally get
both Miharu and Koyomi at once!
All of my scheming...
it's about to bear fruit!
Two in one blow.
Wow! It's really big!
I've been looking forward to
today's swim class
for a long time!
Yeah, it's just
the thing on a hot day!
Right! Come on,
Kirie, let's go.
What's the hurry, Miharu?
Hey, look.
The pool's not going anywhere.
Damn. Miharu is totally hot.
Even in one of those
school swimsuits!
Yeah, Kirie, too.
Not too shabby, huh guys?
How come there's a hole
in my swimsuit, Kirie?
Oh yeah, that's just there to--
There's a hole
in yours too, Kirie!
It's like a pocket!
Miharu get your
arms out of my suit!
Oh, they both went in!
This swimsuit's
really stretchy.
That's not what
it's there for!
The hole just lets the water
that comes in through the top
go out through
the bottom, okay?
That's amazing, Kirie!
Let's go, Miharu.
Before their trunks
get any tighter.
Sorry I'm late!
My locker's too tall!
Sorry! Sorry!
It was an accident!
What's this thing
doing here, anyway?
Huh?
Hey, they're all
over the place...
Oh no, Yukinari,
are you all right?
Geez, Yukinari
can be such a clutz.
Surf's up!
Fukuyama, that's amazing!
You can't ride
that thing in a pool!
Come on!
Thanks to an unexpected
illness,
our teacher can't make it
today.
My goodness, what
happened?
Just tell me where it hurts,
honey.
My stomach. It came so
fast.
Hang in there,
okay?
I'll take you over to the
nurse's office right away.
Ah! The
baby!
What?
It's coming! It's coming!
Wait a minute, do you
even go to this school?
There's only one thing to
do in a time like this...
Ready when you are, Kirie!
Woo-hoo!
All right, ladies.
It's pool party time.
What are you talking about?
You can't just throw a party
because the teacher's gone.
And you floozies on the raft,
what are you doing
wearing those bikinis?
Enjoy, Miharu.
And for Kirie, the white.
Feel free to lose these
as you experience
the wonders of my pool.
Wow, I didn't know the school
had swimsuits like that.
They don't!
Those are his!
What are you babbling about?
This isn't your pool!
Do you know
how stupid you are?
Oh, it's mine.
I had this sudden
inexplicable interest
in the high school swim team,
so the Fukuyama family
paid to remodel the pool.
Wait, your family did what?!
Good grades depend on
a good learning environment,
and I'd rather do my learning
poolside at a resort.
What's going on?!
You... you didn't.
And the coup de grace.
Goodbye hapless rivals.
Hello exclusive harem oasis.
Whatever you're planning,
Fukuyama, just forget it.
I've already had
enough stupidity
out of you for one day.
Kirie, there's plenty of time
for talking you out
of that one-piece later.
'Til then, it's Miharu time!
Hya!
Miharu watch out!
Um, Fukuyama,
where are you taking me?
Don't you worry
about that, Miharu.
After we find
some place secluded,
I'm going to take
you to paradise!
Miharu looks so hot
in this swimsuit,
it's almost a shame
it has to go!
Wait a minute,
what am I saying?!
Not so fast, Fukuyama!
Where did that
jet ski come from?
You're the one who
brought it to school today.
Dumb ass!
Oh, thank you for
catching me Yukinari.
I didn't hurt you, did I?
No, I'm okay.
I should've flushed you
out of the swimming pool
with the rest of the boys.
If Miharu's going to have
poolside naughtiness
with anyone,
it's going to be me!
No she's not!
Yukinari!
Yukinari... Yukinari!
Are you all right?
Oh, you finally woke up.
I'm so glad.
Mi-Miharu...
If something bad
ever happened to you,
I don't know what
I'd do, Yukinari.
But... but I'm not Puny-nari.
Um, Yukinari?
[FUKUYAMA as YUKINARI]
Don't worry Miharu, I feel fine.
I could stand to be taller
and less scrawny you know.
But hey.
Uh. Yukinari...
[FUKUYAMA as YUKINARI]
I know, let's rub sunscreen
all over each other's
willing, pliant flesh.
Sure.
[FUKUYAMA as YUKINARI]
Lisa's magic did the trick.
Poor Fukuyama, I think
he needs mouth-to-mouth.
I should be the one to do it.
Aww, no fair.
[YUKINARI as FUKUYAMA]
What?
Come on, Yoko, you gotta share.
All I know is I'm next.
[YUKINARI as FUKUYAMA]
What are they talking about?
I'm not Fukuyama, I'm Yukinari!
Oh, Fukuyama!
How awful!
He had it coming.
You can't get
anywhere with Miharu,
so you go running back
to your floozies?
Just give it a rest, Fukuyama.
[YUKINARI/FUKUYAMA]
Huh? It's me!
[YUKINARI as FUKUYAMA]
But then I'm... I'm... Fukuyama!
This is bad.
[YUKINARI as FUKUYAMA]
Huh? Kirie, listen to me.
I need you to
believe what I'm saying.
I know I look
exactly like Fukuyama,
[YUKINARI as FUKUYAMA] but I'm
not Fukuyama, I'm Yukinari.
I'm Yukinari! That's the
dumbest thing I've ever heard!
[FUKUYAMA as YUKINARI]
Hmm.
[YUKINARI AS FUKUYAMA] That
doesn't mean it's not the truth.
Take that!
Don't look, stupid!
[FUKUYAMA AS YUKINARI]
Hubba hubba.
Oh, sorry about that, Yukinari.
[FUKUYAMA AS YUKINARI]
Not a problem!
[YUKINARI AS FUKUYAMA]
Um, Miharu?
Fukuyama?
[YUKINARI AS FUKUYAMA]
I was wondering if maybe
you'd like to play
with us for a while?
[YUKINARI AS FUKUYAMA] Since
nobody believes I'm Yukinari,
I guess I'll just
start acting like Fukuyama.
[YUKINAR AS FUKUYAMA]
Gosh, I wish I were
even half as popular
as Fukuyama here.
[FUKUYAMA AS YUKINARI]
You cheater.
You're so lucky Fukuyama,
but I'm allergic to women,
so I can't play with
the other girls like you do.
[FUKUYAMA AS YUKINARI]
It's so unfair.
Miharu's the only one
who doesn't set it off...
Hmm.
[FUKUYAMA AS YUKINARI]
Without her I'd have nothing.
Nothing I tell you!
Poor Yukinari.
[YUKINARI AS FUKUYAMA] Miharu,
don't you fall for it, too.
I'm sorry, Fukuyama.
Yukinari gets itchy,
and I'd feel bad if
he were all by himself.
But I'll try to make
sure Yukinari has fun today,
even if it's
just the two of us!
[YUKINARI AS FUKUYAMA]
You-you don't recognize me.
[FUKUYAMA AS YUKINARI] Well
then, better luck next time!
[YUKINARI AS FUKUYAMA]
But I... I don't
need to be around
all these other girls.
I'm not like Fukuyama.
[YUKINARI AS FUKUYAMA]
I was perfectly happy
just being with Miharu.
She's the only one I need.
[YUKINARI AS FUKUYAMA]
And now she's with him.
Oh, my poor dear Yukinari.
Don't you worry,
starting tonight,
we'll live together
as brother and sister.
I'll love you as
a sister should.
Well as a sister
shouldn't, I mean.
[YUKINARI AS FUKUYAMA] Miharu...
I'm happy just being with you.
[YUKINARI AS FUKUYAMA]
What's that doing here?
[FUKUYAMA AS YUKINARI] Now then,
what's next on my itinerary.
[FUKUYAMA AS YUKINARI]
An all-girls swimming contest!
Or perhaps a water-fight
with these luscious beauties.
Yukinari...
What's up? You haven't
been yourself this afternoon.
[FUKUYAMA AS YUKINARI]
Uh, whatever do you mean, Kirie?
I'm the same old Puny-nari
you know and love, really.
Like hell you are.
Miharu's a different story,
but how come your rashes aren't
popping up when you touch me?!
[FUKUYAMA as YUKINARI]
Uh...
Um, maybe I've finally gotten
over that pesky allergy.
Yeah, that's the ticket.
[FUKUYAMA AS YUKINARI]
Touching your body must have
put me on the path of healing.
If that's the case, you should
let me grope you more...
[FUKUYAMA AS YUKINARI] just
to make sure I'm totally well.
Are you out of your mind?!
Wait! You don't want
to hit me with that thing!
[KIRIE AS YUKINARI]
But-But that's me.
[FUKUYAMA/ AS KIRIE]
Then, I'm inside...
[FUKUYAMA AS KIRIE] This is
the greatest moment of my life!
[FUKUYAMA AS KIRIE]
Jackpot, baby.
[KIRIE AS YUKINARI] Hey! Stop
rubbing on those this instant!
[KIRIE AS YUKINARI]
They're not yours to play with!
[FUKUYAMA/KIRIE]
Oh, yeah, I definitely love
swim class day
the very best of all.
[KIRIE AS YUKINARI]
Only one person I know
would do this sort of thing!
[KIRIE/YUKINARI] This is
all your fault, Fukuyama!
[YUKINARI AS FUKUYAMA]
I'm not Fukuyama!
[KIRIE AS FUKUYAMA]
Huh? I'm Fukuyama!
All right! It's my body!
Oh, it's so good to be home
again!
[GIRL 1 AS YUKINARI]
No way!
[YUKINARI AS GIRL 1] Just
when I'd gotten my body back!
Wow! This game looks like fun!
Oh yeah, this is a total blast.
Take that!
[MIHARU AS YUKINARI]
I'm inside Yukinari.
[YUKINARI AS KIRIE]
Whoa, Miharu is inside my body?
[KIRIE AS FUKUYAMA]
Yukinari, you're dead meat
if you do anything
weird to my body!
[FUKUYAMA AS MIHARU]
All right! I'm in Miharu!
I'll never have to
leave the house again!
[YUKINARI AS KIRIE]
Fukuyama, I'm not gonna let you
fool around
with Miharu's body!
[FUKUYAMA AS MIHARU] Sorry,
Puny-nari, finders keepers.
This body is mine.
Why don't you go play
with Kirie for a while.
[YUKINARI AS KIRIE]
You pervert!
You had Lisa do all this
with her magic, didn't you?
[YUKINARI AS KIRIE] Have her
change us back right now!
[KIRIE as FUKUYAMA]
Huh? Huh?
That's not supposed to happen!
[KIRIE AS FUKUYAMA]
An o-o-octopus!
Get out of here!
Everyone, run for it!
[KIRIE AS FUKUYAMA]
Miharu! I mean... Fukuyama.
[YUKINARI AS KIRIE]
What's he doing?
[FUKUYAMA AS MIHARU] This
entire mess is Lisa's fault.
Only one thing to do.
[MIHARU AS YUKINARI]
Fukuyama!
[FUKUYAMA AS MIHARU]
Hey, come on, baby.
Yeah, right there.
[KIRIE AS FUKUYAMA]
He didn't.
[YUKINARI AS KIRIE]
B-b-but Miharu's body...
[FUKUYAMA AS MIHARU]
Oh, almost there!
[KIRIE AS FUKUYAMA]
Wait! Yukinari!
[YUKINARI AS KIRIE]
Let go you monster!
Give up already!
Between Kirie's body and
my resolve, I'm invincible!
[YUKINARI AS KIRIE]
Or maybe not!
[MIHARU AS YUKINARI]
Yu-Yukinari!
Kirie, please don't faint on me.
[KIRIE AS FUKUYAMA]
Hold on, Miharu...
[MIHARU AS YUKINARI]
But Kirie...
[KIRIE AS FUKUYAMA]
Listen, if you blow up
that octopus right now,
your real body is just gonna
get blown up along with it.
[FUKUYAMA AS MIHARU] Ooh, don't
ever stop the tentacle love.
[MIHARU AS YUKINARI]
I'll miss my body,
but if I can save Yukinari,
it's worth it.
[KIRIE AS FUKUYAMA]
You would... do that for him?
Don't! It'll take
my body with it!
[MIHARU AS YUKINARI]
Oh no, not Kirie's body, too!
I'm here!
[MIHARU AS YUKINARI]
Lisa?
[KIRIE AS FUKUYAMA]
Yeah, I should've known
that this was
all your fault.
I'm sorry. My fun
got a bit out of hand.
Playtime's over!
Miharu! Miharu!
Or are you Fukuyama?
Uh... hello Yukinari.
Uh, is it really you?
I'm definitely me,
Yukinari. We're okay!
All right!
You're finally
back to normal, Miharu!
I'm glad you're you again, too!
It's so good to be back.
Kirie! Are you all right?
Yeah, never been better.
I know I've said
it before, mother,
but Earth is
a really dreadful place.
[TOMO] It's a lucky thing
we came down here!
There's gotta be one good man
in a pile that big, right?
[TOMO] Wow, cool!
Big Brother?
Where did you go?
Big Brother!
Aww, I could've
had Yukinari all to myself
if you hadn't
ruined everything.
Yeah, thanks for all
the help, Big Brother, dear.
Big Brother! Where are
you, anyway? Big Brother!
[FUKUYAMA AS BOARD]
Wait! I'm over here!
Change me back already!
Lisa, change me back!
Oh, am I condemned to spend
the rest of my life like this?
As a section of
poolside walking planks?
To have strangers step on me
until I get moldy and rot away!
Somebody! Help me!
Kazuharu Fukuyama
is stuck in here.
It's terrible, huh?
No kidding. Seriously.
Let's get showered.
Sounds good.
Then again...
this could work.
Love, it's a prize
worth fighting for.
[KOSAME] Any battle waged for
love is a battle worth waging.
Fight for the love
you feel, Kirie!
Put your pride and your life
on the line, Kirie!
Do it for love!
What are you
talking about?
Girls Bravo Season Two,
next episode, "Fight Bravo!"
Hmm, I can't wait.
No, seriously,
what are you talking about?