[shower water running]
[MIHARU humming]
Yukinari?
M-Miharu!
[YUKINARI whimpers]
[MIHARU giggles]
Yukinari! Are you ready?
[KIRIE sighs]
He is such a slowpoke.
[door opens]
[YUKINARI]
Miharu, let me go!
Please, let go!
[MIHARU]
Come on, Yukinari.
Let's take a nice
hot bath together.
Stop! I told you,
if I don't hurry up,
I'm not going to make
it to class on time!
Taking a bath is more
important than going to school.
Wah!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
--[MIHARU] Hurry up already.
--[KIRIE growling]
[YUKINARI]
N-no no no! You can't!
Not my underwear!
You can't wear them
into the bathtub, silly.
Uh, Kirie?
Good morning, there.
Oh, do you wanna
take a bath, too?
No, Kirie, w-w-w-w-wait.
This isn't what you think!
It's not like that!
--[YUKINARI] It's not--
--[MIHARU beating up YUKINARI]
[KIRIE]
Sorry.
[YUKINARI] I think it
stinks how you always
punch first and
ask questions later.
Well, it looked
really bad!
Sorry.
As far as she's
concerned...
She really
puts it away.
No kidding!
[YUKINARI] Miharu accidentally
came to Earth not too long ago,
from her home planet, Seiren,
a world filled almost
totally with women.
Since then, we've tried
sending her back
a bunch of different ways,
but no luck so far.
For now, at least,
she's staying at my house.
[MIHARU]
Yukinari!
Huh?
This is really tasty!
I was wondering what it is.
[KIRIE]
The thin pieces?
They're called bread.
Do you like it?
Yeah!
Kirie understands the...
unique situation with Miharu.
So they don't have any bread
on the planet that you're from?
Now she actually
helps me out with her.
Nuh-uh, but we do have
a similar kind of food
that we call "pana."
For her part, Miharu doesn't
seem too homesick for Seiren...
"Pana"?
...which is good, because we
don't know how to get her there.
I guess that's
a good thing.
Yukinari!
Thank you!
That food is wonderful!
It's so soft and tasty.
You like bread
that much?
Yeah. I like that
curry rice from yesterday, too.
But I think the bread I ate
right now is even better.
Okay then.
Hey, I know!
I'll bring back
some bread for you
when I come home
from school today.
From school?
So you can buy
bread where you learn?
Uh-huh! The school bread almost
makes it worth having to go.
The school bread...
There are a lot
of different types,
but the best is the bread
with the curry inside.
[MIHARU gasps]
It's curry bread!
Oh yeah. It's so
popular it sells out
as soon as the
lunch bell rings.
I would just
love to try some.
Okay, then I guess
I'll get you some.
Thank you, I am
kind of hungry again.
Oh.
Uh, you mean-- you mean now.
I can't get it for you now.
Huh? He can't get it?
Well, it's not
that I can't.
But the school curry bread
is the most popular one!
And it sells out when
the lunch bell rings!
Kirie said so!
Yeah, but I--
Yukinari, come on.
We're gonna miss first period
if we don't get going.
Oh, right.
Sorry, Miharu,
we have to go,
but don't you worry!
I'll get that
curry bread for you.
Oh yeah, there are
snacks in the cupboard.
Help yourself
if you get hungry.
I'll see you later.
I'm so hungry.
Bread. School bread.
It must be like silk.
Spicy curry wrapped inside
all that doughy goodness.
With one bite,
it fills the mouth
with warmth and
leaves you ecstatic!
I want it.
That's it!
If I buy the school
bread for myself,
I don't have to
wait for Yukinari,
and that means
I get to go outside.
I'm outside on
a beautiful day!
Hmm, I wonder how
I get to Yukinari's school.
Ah! Hello, hello!
Bananas are on sale, today!
Want some, lady?
No? How 'bout you?
[VENDOR sighs]
Huh?
Oh, Miss, can I help
you with something?
Are these okay to eat?
They smell really good.
Uh, you've never
seen a banana before?
It's a banana?
It's a banana.
So, it's a banana.
Yeah, it's
a banana.
Is it different
than curry bread?
It is very different
than curry bread.
That's what I thought.
Yeah, they're
the sale item for today.
Are they going
to sell out?
Well, the demand for
bananas has been down lately.
People just don't eat 'em
as much as they used to.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, in the old days,
bananas were
a pretty ritzy fruit...
really hard to come by.
Imported fruit!
Fit for a king!
Wow, fit for a king!
That's really incredible.
[VENDOR laughs]
Wanna try one?
Is it okay?
Sure.
Dig in.
You like it?
Yes! Thank you,
it's good!
It's really
soft and very sweet!
It is, isn't it?
I can remember the very first
banana that I ever tasted.
Heh, changed my life forever.
I was a boy of fifteen.
I was in bed with
a bad case of the measles,
and my mother,
poor woman that she was,
went without to buy me bananas.
She fed me those bananas
with her own chapped hands
with such devotion it
made me want to weep
tears of gratitude flowed down
my young face like a river,
as I kept saying,
"It's good. It's good."
There and then, I vowed
that I would someday
open my own
produce store.
Taiwan, China,
the Philippines, Ecuador!
I sailed the world over
chasing a dream.
I can remember how many
times I almost perished at sea,
but it was all worth it when
I finally found the very best
bananas and brought them back!
I negotiated the planters
into an exclusive contract!
The first shipment
sold in minutes.
I spent every
penny on this building,
and now, by God,
I sell bananas!
I see, the day-to-day
grind made me forget
why I wanted into the produce
business in the first place.
That brush with destiny...
Thanks for the banana.
It was good for me, too.
Ah, it was nothing
at all, young lady.
If anything,
I should thank you.
Oh, um... do you know
anything about school bread?
I've been looking
for some all morning now.
Bread?
Yukinari told me
they sell it as his school.
At his school?
You mean Mizuno High School?
If that's where you mean,
go straight, turn right,
and it'll be right there.
Thank you very much.
See you later!
Sure! Come again,
anytime.
See you around,
banana girl!
Huh?
This smells good,
what's it called?
It's called a croquette.
They must have broke
the mold after that one.
[bell rings]
[GIRL 1] Oh, Fukuyama,
you shouldn't touch me there.
You're such a naughty boy.
[GIRL 2] Oh, Fukuyama, save some
for me.
I hope Miharu likes it.
You can do anything
you want with me.
[FUKUYAMA]
Is that a promise?
Kirie, let's go
home soon, okay?
It's so hard
being popular.
[KIRIE growling]
[FUKUYAMA and GIRLS laughing]
Will you stop that already?!
Fukuyama!
Yes?
All you do is sit
in the back of the class
and act like King Pervert!
News flash, pal,
you're seventeen!
And why are you the only
one wearing a white uniform?
You are so damn pretentious!
Why, Kirie,
I'm surprised at you.
If you wanted to
be part of the group,
all you had to do was ask.
[GYM INSTRUCTOR]
Mizuno High School! Fight!
[INSTURCTOR]
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
[STUDENTS] Uh! Uh! Uh! Uh!
Kirie again?
Yeah, Fukuyama I bet.
What is that,
the 27th window this month?
They don't let up, do they?
[FUKUYAMA giggles]
Kirie, you really
should do something
about that
horrible temper.
You'll never catch
a husband that way.
Like I need
your advice on love!
Yukinari, go ahead!
Huh?
Come on! Put this white
uniform pervert in his place!
No, I'll pass.
[FUKUYAMA laughs maniacally]
Now that's just cruel, Kirie!
My family is super rich!
I'm practically 6 feet tall!
Of all the guys at
Mizuno High School,
I am easily the best looking.
[FUKUYAMA giggles maniacally]
How could poor little
Puny-nari Sasaki,
the class runt,
possibly put me in my place?!
[FUKUYAMA laughs maniacally]
Dumbass.
Just who the hell
do you think you are?
I know Yukinari, and there are
lots of great things about him.
--[YUKINARI] Kirie?
--[KIRIE] He's nice.
--What's up with Kirie?
--And he's funny.
And he's way more mature
than someone like you
who goes around all day
with his brain in his pants!
And one more thing,
I know about you...
The chink in your armor...
The secret behind
these white gloves.
Ha! Guess I'll
enjoy the view!
[KIRIE gasps]
I'll make you mine,
one way or another, Kirie!
I think my secret's
safe with you.
The right one, the left?
Which one's enjoying it more?
[FUKUYAMA making kissing sound]
[ATHLETES]
Mizuno High School! Fight!
Fight! Fight!
Uh! Uh! Uh! Uh!
[COACH 1]
There goes number 28.
[COACH 2]
Yeah, that was quick.
[MIHARU] Um, excuse me.
[COACH]
Huh?
Could you tell me if
this is Mizuno High School?
[KIRIE]
Die! Die! Die! Die!
[FUKUYAMA groaning]
You white uniform
perverted bastard!
Kirie, I'm so pretty.
Shut up, you oversexed demon!
No one likes pretty boys,
I'm doing you a favor!
[BOY 1] Hey, hey,
what's your name?
Are you a transfer
student or something?
[KIRIE]
Does it hurt?
Well it's not gonna for long,
'cause you'll be dead!
That's a cool hair color.
What's that on your forehead?
Is that some new fad?
--[YUKINARI whimpers]
--[KIRIE yelling at FUKUYAMA]
Mi-Miharu?
[FUKUYAMA groaning]
Yukinari!
Mi-Miharu.
Yep, here I am.
So, this is your school!
This is so exciting!
It looks like such
a wonderful place.
I like your house,
but the bathtub's a bit small.
[FUKUYAMA]
Mi-haru.
I bet this place has
a really big bathtub.
I'm liking Earth more
and more every day I'm here.
But... Miharu...
you shouldn't have
come here
all by yourself.
[FUKUYAMA] Miharu...
Who is that?
Huh?
Seiren's a lot
different from here.
Who's Puny-nari talking to?
You don't know
anything about Earth yet.
Could there possibly be a girl
at Mizuno High School
that I... Kazuharu Fukuyama
am not aware of?
Miharu? Miharu.
You whom I have not yet seen,
such a lovely girl,
you are like
the blooming Rafflesia
deep within a secret forest.
As your sweet
fragrance overwhelms me,
I surrender myself to you.
I'm in love.
Um, I ate all the snacks
I could find in the house,
but I was still hungry.
I thought I could go out and
buy school bread all by myself.
I just...
I'm sorry.
Hey...
Miharu,
I'm sorry also.
You must have been so
lonely there all by yourself.
Yukinari!
[BOY] Back to class...
Hey, I know,
as long as you're here,
how about I show you around?
You'd enjoy that, right?
Uh-huh.
Where'd she--
[FUKUYAMA laughing]
Good thinking, Puny-nari!
I, Kazuharu Fukuyama,
will be your guide.
Let us find
the perfect setting
in which to
consummate our love!
[BOTH] Miharu!
The fourth floor
girl's bathroom.
Good to know.
[GIRLS scream]
And the third
floor girl's bathroom.
Oh, I see.
[GIRLS scream]
[FUKUYAMA panting] The second
floor girl's bathroom.
Is that so?
[GIRLS scream]
[FUKUYAMA panting]
And last, but not least,
the faculty women's bathroom.
[LADY] Hey!
No men allowed, sonny! Hmph!
Thank you very much
for showing me all
of these bathrooms.
But if you don't mind,
could you maybe carry me
back to where
Yukinari is waiting for me?
Be patient, my sweet, we have
one more stop on our itinerary.
The grand climax of the Mizuno
High School tour, you might say.
You'll love it.
Oh.
Who is this
person anyway?
Let us go, now, to
Mizuno High School's
Secret Garden of
Earthly Delights!
Miharu!
Miharu?
Hey, Yukinari,
any luck over there?
Uh-unh. She's just gone.
Damn that Fukuyama!
Where's that
pervert hiding?!
This very moment,
Miharu might be...
with Fukuyama...
[MIHARI] Oh, no,
but I... I don't...
There's nothing to
be afraid of, Miharu.
Let us become Mizuno
High School's Adam and Eve.
Behold!
Oh, no!
Ah, what good does it do
getting yourself all
depressed like that?!
But, Kirie.
Oh, just give it a rest.
You've always been that way.
You give up
without even trying,
and then you act
like a hermit.
You mope, and you're clumsy.
God you're clumsy.
But you're good to people,
and you do try.
Huh?
All of that stuff I said
back in the classroom...
all the good things
that I said about you...
I meant them.
Kirie?
That's why...
you should have...
you know...
more faith in yourself!
[YUKINARI] That was--
[FUKUYAMA laughing maniacally]
Yukinari!
Mi-Miharu!
Yukinari, wait!
Ah, man, and right when we
were at the good part, too.
Stop, Fukuyama!
Oh, don't waste
your breath, Puny-nari.
You know you can't
possibly catch me!
Dammit, I'm not giving up!
I'm going to get Miharu back!
[FUKUYAMA laughing]
If you can, that is!
Um, excuse me, but
I should get back to Yukinari.
Don't be silly, Miharu,
we've reached our destination.
Okay.
[YUKINARI panting]
She... must be... in there.
No! Yukinari!
Don't open that door!
Oh! My! God!
[ALL GIRLS]
Peeping tom!
[KIRIE sighs]
Um, excuse me.
Will you stop beating him up?
I said "Stop it!"
Puny-nari had it coming.
Fukuyama!
Anybody who'd peep
at these sweet young things
is an enemy
to womanhood.
You're one to talk.
Yukinari!
Yukinari! Yukinari!
Sorry, but Miharu's
coming with me!
Fukuyama!
Kirie!
What a baby.
Yukinari! Yukinar--!
Just forget about him.
Leave that runt behind,
and spend every day with me
in my perverted wonderland.
What do you say?
[FUKUYAMA laughing]
What just... happened?
Fukuyama!
Kirie, wait a minute!
Sorry. I got carried away.
I'm sorry. Sorry. Okay? Okay?
Go apologize...
in Hell!
What was that?!
First an explosion, and now...
He looks hurt, fellas.
Hey, he's waking up.
Are you okay?
Peeping tom!
There it is... his secret.
Exactly the opposite
of Yukinari...
an allergy... to men.
I'm really sorry.
Because of me, you got beat up.
Don't worry about it.
Really, that wasn't your fault.
If I never came to school...
I should have just stayed
at home like you told me
to do in the first place.
Miharu...
Still, I'm sorry.
I'm telling you I'm fine.
Sure I'm not very big,
but I'm tougher than I look.
Yukinari!
Oh yeah, I got you
some school bread.
Oh... I'm sorry
it got all burnt up.
I'll buy you another
one tomorrow, 'kay?
This is very tasty...
Yukinari's curry bread!