[YUKINARI] Miharu, hurry up,
we're going to be late!
[KIRIE] Our teacher'll kill us
if we're tardy to writing
class again. Come on.
[MIHARU] But I'm still in
the middle of eating breakfast.
[YUKINARI] It's okay. Let's go.
[MIHARU] Oh, sorry, breakfast.
Nothing personal.
[front door opens and closes]
[KOYOMI gasps]
[KOYOMI panting]
[KOYOMI] Uh, this is...
[KIRIE] We're here!
I can't believe it.
It just started pouring!
Now we're all wet.
But I thought
the weatherman said
it wasn't
supposed to rain today.
Like you can go
off what they say.
Hey Yukinari,
I got dibs on the tub.
Sure.
Miharu, why don't you...
M-M-M-M-Miharu, what are you
doing taking your clothes off?
It's really chilly
in these wet clothes,
so I'd like to
take a bath, too.
Okay, but could you
please do it in there?
I'm sorry, Yukinari, but...
...could you help me out
of my clothes, please?
[KIRIE] Yukinari...
Cool off, you little perv!
[MIHARU] Yukinari!
I'm sure the little
pervert will be fine.
Come on,
let's take our bath.
[front door closes]
[KIRIE and MIHARU scream]
[YUKINARI gasps]
Hey, what's wrong?
[KIRIE] Get out of here,
you sleazeball!
Dumbass.
[MIHARU] Uh, Kirie...
I didn't hit him that hard.
Besides, that's
the only way he'll learn.
Okay, but what about...
Oh yeah, huh.
We've got a problem,
Yukinari.
Yeah, no kidding.
A girl?
[KIRIE] Yeah.
We looked in the tub
and there she was, out cold.
She was...
in my bathtub?
[MIHARU] Yeah.
I'll take her
to the living room.
Wait, Yukinari,
what about your allergy?
Hey, I'll be okay.
You two should hurry up
and take your bath now.
After all, you'll catch a cold
if you stay wet too long.
[CHILD KOYOMI] Hey Daddy?
The planet that you came from,
tell me what it's like.
[KOYOMI'S DAD] If it weren't
raining today, you could see it.
[KOYOMI sighs]
Okay.
I wanna go visit
Earth someday.
Someday it is, then.
You can go.
Really? Really?
We'll go there together,
Daddy? It's a promise?
Sure.
It's a promise.
[KOYOMI] No!
[KOYOMI panting]
Excuse me, but...
...are you okay?
Huh?
No!
[YUKINARI]
Hey, wait, what did I do?
What?
M-m-m-ma-- it's a man!
Hey, hold on! Calm down!
Ow.
[KIRIE] Oh, man.
Where'd she go?
[alarm goes off]
[YUKINARI]
Pretty neat, huh?
You can record
stuff onto it.
Geez, don't freak
her out anymore!
But, I was just
trying to be nice.
It's okay, just wait over there.
Now then, are
you feeling better?
Mm-hmm.
I wanna ask you a few things...
if that's all right.
Oh yeah. Your clothes.
I washed 'em for you.
What's the matter?
Are you okay?
Oh, uh, yes.
Good. I'll leave
these right here then.
All right.
--[KYOMI] Koyomi.
--[KIRIE] Huh?
I haven't told you...
My name...
my name's Koyomi.
[MIHARU]
Koyomi?
You're lucky, Koyomi.
It's a really lovely name.
Thank you.
Hey, uh, why don't you
give me your phone number?
We had better give
your family a call.
My phone... number?
How about
your address?
Where do you live?
Address?
O...kay then.
Do you know
how old you are?
Un-unh.
Parents... or
siblings... or a pet?
Uh...
Ooh, I've got one.
What's your
favorite food?
I don't know.
What's your
favorite TV show?
TV show?
My favorite TV show is called
"Have Stomach Will Travel."
It's a reality show!
They go traveling
all over Japan
tracking down different
kinds of rare or weird
or yummy well-known dishes.
When I watch it,
I get really excited
about all the tasty food
on Earth I haven't
had a chance to try.
There's so much out there.
And the host
is very energetic.
By the end of the show,
I'm all fired up
for my next meal.
What are you talking about?
Well it's still your
favorite show, right?
But seriously, all you
remember about yourself
is your own name?
Mhmm.
You must have--
It's amnesia,
there's no question.
[ALL GIRLS gasp]
Fukuyama!
Good afternoon,
everyone!
Where the hell'd
you come from?
The weather cleared up,
so I thought maybe I could
convince you and Miharu
to spend the afternoon
having some naughty fun.
I even went to
the trouble of being
chauffeured out
to this peasant hovel.
Little did I know that
Puny-nari could be hiding
such a delicious
young beauty within it.
Her loss of
memory is your gain.
Bury your face in her breasts
and grope her sweet buttocks
'til the cows come home.
[YUKINARI] What are you talking
about? I'm not like that!
Surrender to it, Puny-nari.
Behold! Behold!
Your hidden
curves are no match
for the likes of
Kazuharu Fukuyama!
You're mine for the taking!
Shut up!
You're scaring Koyomi!
Koyomi is it?
My name is
Kazuharu Fukuyama.
The pleasure is all mine.
Huh?
[FUKUYAMA thinking]
Nothing happened.
Did the shock of
losing her memory
render her immune to
my animal magnetism?
Push her on the couch,
and go for broke.
Take advantage of her amnesia.
Grandfather always said
the first impression's
the most important.
No, Kirie would beat me
like a red-headed step-child.
It's time to show them
exactly what I'm made of!
It's my duty,
my righteous quest!
Greetings!
Kazuharu Fukuyama's the name.
I'm handsome, athletic,
and an all-around nice guy.
I hate all men,
but I love all women.
You most of all.
We should get married!
Well, baby, whattya think?
Do you know how
annoying you are?
This isn't just another garden
variety seduction, you know?
My manhood hangs
in the balance!
Why don't you try
making sense for once?
Huh! I wouldn't
expect you to understand
a genius' concerns, Kirie.
Bite me!
Well, in that case...
Plan B!
Oh, my dear Koyomi.
Hey!
Have you really
forgotten?
[YUKINARI] Fukuyama!
[KOYOMI crying]
Don't frighten her,
Puny-nari!
There, there, my darling.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Just take your time
and try to remember
the days that
we loved each other...
Take that,
you deluded pervert!
[YUKINARI]
He kinda had it coming.
Hey...
Koyomi!
Uh, hold on!
Koyomi, wait!
Hey, come back!
It'll be okay!
Come back!
[FUKUYAMA smirks]
You will be mine, Koyomi...
[LITTLE GIRL crying]
[MOM] Oh, don't cry Honey,
it's all right.
I'll buy you a new bird.
But I don't want a new bird.
I want Pippy back!
Pippy flew away, Honey.
She's gone.
But I really
miss her.
Bring her back,
Mommy, please!
Bring her back?
Koyomi! Koyomi!
She's gone.
Where'd she run off to?
I'm here to...
[KOYOMI gasps]
[BOSS MAN yelps]
Oh my God, Boss!
Are you all right?
I didn't mean to... I'm...
Hey you, girl, why the hell'd
you attack my boss like that?
I'm... I'm really sorry.
Oh you're sorry, huh?
Tell it to the cops!
But I...
I think you should show us
just how sorry you are.
Ain't that right, Boss?
[BOSS MAN laughs pervertedly]
[KIRIE]
Koyomi!
Boss! Wake up!
[KOYOMI]
I'm sorry. Sorry.
It's okay.
Just calm down.
--Hey!
--Wait, Koyomi!
[BOSS MAN laughs pervertedly]
[KOYOMI whimpers]
Koyomi!
Huh, Fukuyama?
[ALL]
All in a day's work.
Now, Koyomi, it's time
we had a heart to heart
discussion about our future.
[FUKUYAMA giggles pervertedly]
[KOYOMI whimpers and yells]
No!
I'm the moth
and you're the flame, Koyomi!
Didn't we just save her
from a couple of perverts?
Yeah, we did, and led
a bigger pervert right to her.
Just look at
the two of them go!
Come on, you guys.
Let's chase 'em!
Right!
Yeah! I think our team
is going to win!
And here's your change.
Thank you very much.
Business has sure
been booming lately.
Even the bananas are selling.
I love produce again.
Hmm. Everything changed
after I met that banana girl.
Oh!
Hey, what was that?
Oh, it's the banana man.
Good afternoon.
Oh, nice
to see you.
What was
that all about?
Oh, you can
play too if you want.
Can play what?
We're all playing Earth tag.
Huh?
[KOYOMI panting]
You can't outrun
your feelings, Koyomi!
Not when two people
are in love like we are!
But we're not in love
with each other!
Don't be embarrassed, darling.
I know that every fiber
of your being longs for me!
My fibers don't even know you!
Just leave me alone!
Koyomi!
When should we have
the marriage ceremony?
Whenever I'm somewhere else!
Which would you rather wear,
a wedding dress or a kimono?
I don't want
either of them!
How many kids do you
think we should have?
Let's have daughters!
A dozen of them! Yeah!
It's just 9 years
of pregnancy!
I don't wanna have
any of your kids, okay?
I love how you keep
playing hard to get.
I didn't know Earth
tag was so exciting.
Damn that Fukuyama.
But Kirie, if he
catches her again,
it's all over.
What are we gonna do?
Let's see how he likes it!
Yukinari, go straight.
Miharu, you're with me,
we'll take a side street.
Right!
Good luck, Yukinari.
I'll see you later.
Yeah! Let's go!
How on earth could I have
lost such a dainty morsel?
If I hadn't been hiding in here,
he would've caught me.
I hope they're having
better luck than I am.
Koyomi?
I'm here.
I'm here to...
I wanna go visit
Earth someday.
Earth... a planet where...
where my father was born.
You'll catch a cold
if you just stand in it.
What?
[KOYOMI crying]
No!
[YUKINARI yelps]
[KOYOMI and YUKINARI
fall into water]
[KOYOMI] Um, excuse me...
I'm sorry. I just...
It's all right.
Don't worry about it.
Still, I'm sorry.
Your clothes are
still damp, Koyomi.
Come on,
we should go back home
before you end up
getting sick.
Still have...
amnesia?
Yes.
I see.
I do remember one thing.
Something about my father...
from when I was
a little girl.
Yeah?
When I was little
my father told me
about the place
he came from.
I loved those stories.
He'd carry me on
his shoulders
and I'd ask to hear one of
them for the thousandth time.
And he'd always tell it to me.
They were all so exciting.
I dreamed about
going there someday.
The Earth... it's
so close and yet so far...
my father's planet.
Are you saying...
you're from--
Your little speech
gave me goosebumps, Koyomi.
[YUKINARI Fukuyama!]
[KOYOMI gasps]
Fancy meeting you here.
I've been looking
all over for you.
Oh. Walking around
in such a skimpy outfit
could give men the wrong idea.
Isn't it about
time we head home?
Stop it already, Fukuyama!
What's your problem, Puny-nari?
Can't you see
she doesn't like you?
Just stop bugging her already!
You've got moxie,
but seriously now...
what could you
possibly do to me?
Oh...
Koyomi, run for it!
Okay!
Puny-nari, you dare
exploit my weakness
to steal my woman?!
Take this you
ballsy little freak!
[YUKINARI and KOYOMI yelp]
[KOYOMI thinks]
The star mark.
That's it! I remember!
[NANAE] The subject
is Miharu Sena Kanaka.
She disappeared from her
bathroom about a month ago now.
We have reason to
think she's on Earth.
I want you to bring her
back to Seiren...
before the Special Forces
ladies start butting in.
Can I count on you, Koyomi?
Yes.
The crystalized Aqua Lamp
will only give you a 36-hour
window of opportunity in
which to complete your mission.
If you exceed
that 36-hour limit,
you won't be able
to return to Seiren.
Do you understand?
Perfectly, Captain.
K-Koyomi!
Koyomi?
[FUKUYAMA smirks]
Your landing could use
some work, Puny-nari.
Dammit!
You managed to outwit me,
if only for a moment.
I underestimated you,
but it's time to separate
the men from the boys.
Come on, Koyomi.
I'll make your first night
on Earth a memorable one.
And by memorable,
I mean nasty!
[FUKUYAMA laughs]
[KIRIE] Go be nasty...
in Hell!
Hey Kirie.
[MIHARU]
Yukinari!
Miharu!
Hi, Koyomi.
But where's Fukuyama?
[KIRIE] I'm sure he's having
a memorable time right now.
And by memorable,
I mean unconscious.
Oh, that sounds like fun.
I guess that means Yukinari won
our game of Earth tag, right?
Uh...
[KIRIE laughs]
Yeah, Yukinari won all right.
[MIHARU, KIRIE,
and YUKINARI laugh]
[KOYOMI]
I remember...
What I'm supposed to do.
[MIHARU] All of that running
around made me hungry.
[KIRIE] Yeah, me too.
How 'bout you, Yukinari?
[YUKINARI] I think I could
eat a horse right now!
[KOYOMI] I'm supposed to...