Here we are!
It's bath time!
I don't know, are you sure
we came to the right place?
Let me double check.
Three days, two nights,
at Mountain Hot Spring Inn
for up to five people.
Yeah, this is it.
A real popular
place this hot spring.
Isn't this how
horror movies start?
I stand corrected.
There's a light shining
through the trees!
Nobody who likes delicious
food could possibly be evil.
No, wait, Miharu!
Yukinari, is that you?
Kirie, and Miharu,
Koyomi, and Tomoka.
Don't poor people know
how to knock anymore?
It's so pretty here.
Yeah. It kind of makes up
for yesterday being so crazy.
I love a good
bath in the morning.
Whoa! Miharu!
It's a brand new year and
I know it's gonna be great!
It's not New Year's yet, Miharu!
Come on girl, put 'em away.
Happy New Year!
More like Happy Nude Year!
[MIHARU, TOMO,
and KIRIE laughing]
[KOYOMI sighs]
All right!
I'm here and I'm ready to fish.
Kirie, it's really chilly!
Well, duh,
that's why I did it!
Tomo didn't start
the water fight,
but Tomo's gonna end it!
[MIHARU, KIRIE,
and TOMO laughing]
Take that! And that!
I give up! No more Tomoka!
I was too freaked out
yesterday to notice...
but this place is pretty nice.
I'm glad we came.
Koyomi?
Any second now...
How do you know
what it's going to do?
Well, I can feel
the bait moving around
on the end of the line,
trying to get
away from the fish.
Fish are pretty predictable.
I still don't get it.
Nya.
Just watch.
There! The first thing
you do is hold the rod steady.
Keep the fish from moving.
You use the rod's flexibility
to lure the fish
toward the rocks.
If you keep
pulling up on it,
you'll see the bait, and then...
...got him!
Wow!
Wow! That's amazing!
Cool! You caught it!
Nya nya!
What's wrong, Koyomi?
You've been
acting weird all day.
If something's bugging you,
you can tell me.
Hey! Koyomi!
Miharu...
Koyomi, Yukinari
is really amazing.
Look at all these fish!
He just keeps catching more
of them. I was so surprised.
Does he really?
It's almost like magic.
I don't think that it's magic.
He told me how it works.
You put some tasty bait
on the end of the line
and wait for the fish
to start chasing after it.
I see...
So they chase them.
Is... is something
the matter, Koyomi?
Koyomi, come on.
Something's
really bothering you.
I'm so sorry.
Everyone's
having a good time,
and here I am
ruining it for you two.
Hey now, we're
worried about you,
because you're our friend,
and that's what friends are for.
Kirie...
Now then, what's going on?
Nya nya nya nya nya nya!
Stop whining Ebi, it'll be fun!
Uh, Tomoka, I think your
bait's a little too fresh.
Tomo knows what she's doing!
I'm gonna catch me the biggest
fish you've ever seen!
Oh yeah!
Nyaaah!
Not too bad for
my first time, huh?
But up ahead there's a...
Nyaaaah!
He's... nearby.
Who's nearby?
That person.
What person?
Hmph. That person!
Don't sweat it.
If that pervert
shows up again,
I'll kick his ass for you.
That'll teach
him a lesson, right?
I guess so.
Thanks a lot, Kirie.
Hey, Kirie.
Are these good to eat?
Miharu, you're so strange.
Am I? I don't feel it.
Yes. Quite strange.
You're totally strange.
Maybe I am. Oh.
Big Brother!
Nature makes me itchy.
Why are we out here anyway?
Don't you fret, Lisa.
I think we're in for
a very amusing evening.
We sure had a lot
of fun today, didn't we?
Mhmm. The sun was shining.
The water felt great.
And best of all,
there were no nasty
cockroaches to bother us.
Cockroaches?
There aren't really
cockroaches around
the hot springs, are there?
Right, Koyomi?
Tomo didn't
catch one single fish.
Ebi is useless!
Nya...
You know, I was pretty
surprised, Yukinari...
I never knew you were
so good at fishing!
Yeah, you're amazing, Yukinari!
When I was younger,
my dad and I used to
go fishing all the time.
Yukinari and I have been
friends ever since we were kids,
but there are still lots of
things I don't know about him.
You looked really cool doing it.
Maybe you're not so useless.
Thanks... I think.
Yukinari, you're such
a little sleezeball!
Go drown in Hell!
You really shouldn't be
so rough with him, Kirie.
It's okay,
I'll just have to nurse
my poor broken soul mate
back to health.
Huh?
Lisa?
What the hell?
Huh? Fukuyama!
Who else?
I hope my co-ed bath
is to your liking.
What did you say?
You bought the damn hotel?!
Yes. Why not? We're rich.
We bought every hot springs
hotel in the area.
From now on,
this place will be called
the Fukuyamaville
Hot Springs Resort.
Right, old woman?
That's a wonderful idea,
Master Kazuharu.
It's very rare to find such
sound business sense
in one still so young.
Don't fall for it, landlady.
He's acting nice right now,
but you don't
know him like we do.
How could you
let him have his way?
It was simple, dearie.
Ah! She's gonna eat me!
Yukinari, are you
feeling any better?
Come on! Just leave us
alone for a few days, Fukuyama!
We're on vacation!
It's my hotel. I can make
the bath co-ed if I want to.
How can you be
so damn selfish!
What is wrong with you?
Maybe if you'd
invited us along,
we wouldn't be at
this dreadful impasse.
Why would we?
All you and your
screwy sister ever do
is try to get into our pants!
Well, which came first,
the chicken or the egg?
The egg.
Or was Mr. Chicken first?
Whatever. How about we
settle this fair and square.
How's that?
[KIRIE screams]
Big Brother wins
eleven to zero. It's over!
Well, I guess that's settled.
That was cool.
I mean, I never
would have guessed
that that big dumb pervert
was so handy with a paddle.
Fukuyama, what
kind of man are you?
You only beat me
because Lisa used her magic.
You cheated!
Obviously.
If I'd lost, I'd have to
return my beloved hot spring
to how it was,
and stay two miles away
from Miharu and Koyomi
for a whole week.
With stakes that high,
of course I'm going to cheat!
What happened to
"fair and square"?
Those were your words, not mine.
Wha--?
Anyway, it's time
to make good on your bet.
Huh? Human body-brush?
You're a dirty boy!
Fukuyama, let's play again!
Best two out of three.
I would just beat you again.
Go ahead and prove it
if you're so damn cocky.
I wonder what part of me
I should have you wash first?
I'll be dead in
the cold, cold ground
before I do a human
body-brush on you!
When a person
really wants something,
they use the magic word.
Don't they, Kirie?
Please. Give me a rematch.
Huh?
Oh, generous Fukuyama,
I beg of you, play me again.
And after you lose?
If I lose again,
I'll do whatever you want.
I promise!
All right. It's a deal.
Really?
However, I think it's time
that we upped the ante.
If you lose, you have
to be my bath time mate
for the rest of my life!
What?!
Ooh. Rub a dub dub.
Um, isn't there anything
else you'd rather have?
There's always Plan 'A'.
All right,
all right, I get it.
I agree to your condition.
Very well. Let's get
this rematch underway.
Puny-nari.
Yukinari?
Wait a minute!
What does he have
to do with this?
Correct me if I'm
wrong, and I'm not,
but I never said who
my opponent would be.
No fair. Yukinari's hurt
right now, and you know it.
And just whose
fault would that be?
I-I can do it, Kirie.
Yukinari...
But you can hardly walk.
I-I'll be okay,
don't worry.
What?
I felt pretty confident when
I was fishing earlier today.
Maybe there's a bit of it left.
Yukinari...
Okay, then.
And because
I'm feeling generous,
I'll even let
him have a partner.
Really?
Ooh, me! That game
looks like lots of fun!
Anybody but you.
Oh.
When you get over-excited,
you have a tendency
to make things explode.
Puny-nari's partner will be...
Pick Tomo! I know
you're not too smart,
but this should be
a no-brainer, even for you.
Hmm.
Koyomi's the obvious choice!
What?! But I don't wanna play!
Hey, that's not fair, Fukuyama.
You can't pick Koyomi,
you know how
scared she is of you.
Don't burst a blood
vessel, Puny-nari,
I just agreed to let the two
of you team up against me.
You should be thankful.
I'll do it.
I'm going to play. I want to.
It's okay, Koyomi,
don't force yourself.
But... I-I want to
help out for a change.
And I'll do my best.
Koyomi...
Please let me!
All right.
Let's give it our all.
Yeah!
New rule: if Koyomi's
on the losing team,
there's an
additional consequence.
What?
A fun dinner party dish,
aptly named Fruit Salad
à la Koyomi.
Look at those melons.
[KOYOMI whimpers]
Koyomi! Koyomi,
you have to snap out of it!
Maybe this isn't
such a good idea.
No, if that's
the rule, I accept!
Koyomi!
Sassy, I like.
We're not gonna lose!
Just you wait!
Just don't come
crying when I beat you.
Okay, let's get started.
I'm sorry, Yukinari.
Blood is thicker than ping-pong.
I have to root for
Big Brother this time.
But my heart will always
be on your side of the net.
If I remember how it felt
to go fishing, I'll be okay.
Concentrate. Concentrate!
Take that!
Fine! Bring it on!
Uh. Yukinari?
I almost feel bad.
Are you okay?
Yukinari...
Anyone have a maid
outfit I can borrow?
All of a sudden we're
looking at a singles match.
Shall we continue,
sweet Koyomi?
I can have that
fruit ready in a snap.
Now, Koyomi, let's
get down to business!
Hah!
What?
All right.
Amazing.
No way!
Well, I must not have been
paying any attention just then.
It won't happen again, Koyomi.
That was just a fluke,
yeah, that's it.
Koyomi, you're awesome!
Koyomi, you looked really cool!
I think the basic
idea's the same.
I knew this game would
be right up Koyo's alley.
But how could you
have known? Tell me!
It's a little different
from Earth ping-pong,
but we have a game on
Seiren called Pan Pon Pin.
Koyo's won the tournament
five years in a row!
Really?
That means there's no way
Fukuyama can beat her, right?
Lisa... magic time.
Hmph.
Curses.
Who would've ever guessed
that Koyomi was a veritable
ping-pong Valkyrie?
I wanted to win
by skill alone,
but desperate times
call for desperate measures.
Project S.
I love you.
Who's your daddy?
Fukuyama!
You're just a cheating coward!
I-I'm sorry. I can't...
Look at her shaking like
a winsome full-breasted leaf.
The sexual
harassment is working.
All I have to do is keep
talking, and victory is mine!
Let's get married!
Work that kimono, baby!
Oh, what a wonderful bra!
I can totally see it!
No, don't say any more!
I just can't take it!
And what color panties?
Let's see now, if I remember,
Koyomi's bra and panties
are both blue-ish green.
No!
Miharu, why are
you telling him that?
I'm sorry. I forgot
about the polka dots, huh?
Please, make it stop.
Get a hold of yourself, Koyomi!
You can't give up now!
If you lose this match,
that cheating pervert's gonna
serve you up like a fruit salad!
You'll never stop
being afraid of him!
And I really don't want
to be his damn loofah.
It's terrible,
I know, but I... I...
It's not over until
the fat lady sings.
Just pretend that ping-pong
ball is Fukuyama and hit it!
Fukuyama's the ball?
Koyomi... kiss me!
[FUKUYAMA] Woo woo woo woo...
No! I hate pushy men!
I hit it! And the ball looked
exactly like Fukuyama's face!
Yes! It actually worked!
Keep it up, Koyomi!
It's nine all!
Your serve, Koyomi.
I won't lose!
Not to you, pervert!
I'm not losing today!
Behold my last weapon,
my plentiful balls!
No... means no!
That's it!
Koyomi wins!
Nineteen to nine!
Yeah! You did it!
You won the match, Koyomi!
Koyomi, you were amazing!
I couldn't have
done it without you.
Woah. I don't think his
balls will ever be the same.
Nya. Nya. Nya. Nya...
Hey! One more match!
Double or nothing!
Or the winner could
scrub the loser's back.
Come on, Kirie,
what do ya think?
Good idea?
Ah! I'm boiling in here,
let me out already.
Why'd I even
bother coming here?
This feels really good.
Yeah, it's very
relaxing in here.
I think this hot spring
is the best of 'em all.
You said it!
The perfect end to a long day.
Hey, Koyomi, come and join us!
Yes!
Nya nya!
Hey!