[ANNOUNCER]
Now, tomorrow's horoscope:
Aries, bad luck
awaits you outside,
so stay at home and relax.
Taurus, you're in
for a rocky day, too.
Just go with the flow.
Gemini, wearing
a silver bracelet
can really increase
your productivity at work.
No handcuffs though!
Next, Cancer,
a vase of Dandelions
on the window sill
brings financial gain,
and Leo, you are
one lucky girl!
Keep your eyes peeled for
a checkered handkerchief,
a bandaged face,
and a Killty keychain.
If you find somebody
with all three,
they're your soul mate!
My... soul mate?
All done.
What's wrong, Puny-nari?
You got something to say, Puny?
Uh, no,
not really. I just-
You're too much of
a coward to talk back.
If you're a man,
then act like one!
[YUKINARI panting]
[YUKINARI yelps in surprise]
Time to start
the day, Yukinari.
Miharu...
It's morning, and that
means it's breakfast time.
Breakfast?
Yeah. We're having white rice,
homemade miso soup,
and an omelet filled with lots
of vitamins from Mr. Chicken.
Mister?
All that food will push the bad
dreams right out of your head.
Miharu...
I still need to get ready,
so please, go ahead
and start breakfast without me.
Get ready?
Oh yeah... this'll be your
first day of school, won't it?
Uh-huh!
Well, you better hurry up!
Your food is getting cold.
Um, Miharu?
Huh?
Thank you. You know,
for being so patient with me.
I'm sure I'll get over
this phobia sooner or later.
[MIHARU giggles]
[YURIKUMA] Miharu accidentally
wandered to Earth,
from her home planet of Seiren-
a world of almost all women.
After what happened before,
it didn't seem smart to leave
her home alone all day.
Instead, she'll go
to school with us.
Fukuyama convinced the principal
to let her in right away...
without having to deal
with the usual red tape.
Though I'm still a little
worried, I mean it is Fukuyama.
I have to protect Miharu against
people like that.
But first, the breakfast Miharu
prepared especially for me!
I knew it. Well, she did
make me breakfast, sort of.
Thank you for the food!
Hey, this is pretty good.
Hmm, delicious.
Um, Yukinari,
does it taste all right?
Oh, yeah, it's terrific!
Do you really mean it?
You sure know your way
around the kitchen, Miharu!
Thank you very much!
You know, all that food
you made for me on
Seiren was terrific, too.
I'm so happy to
hear that you liked it.
If only there were just
a little bit more of it...
Oh, sorry about that.
I nibbled at it to check
the flavor, and when I stopped--
Oh no, don't worry about it.
Too much food would have
been bad for me, anyway.
Food is bad for
you if you eat too much?
Is that true?
Oh, ow ow ow!
I'm having a little trouble
getting into
these Earth clothes.
Wah!
Yukinari, what's the matter?!
Miharu, what do you
think you're doing?!
I think I'm changing.
Ch-ch-ch-changing?
If you're changing,
why are you naked?
Is naked bad?
It's not that it's bad...
but if Kirie
sees us like this...
Oh, Kirie, good morning.
Yukinari?
Yeah?
Why is it morning after morning,
after morning, after morning,
after morning she's naked?!
Does it hurt much, Yukinari?
Yeah, well, just a little bit.
Oh, your lip,
there's blood on it.
It's not that bad.
I'm fine.
Here. Use this.
You wouldn't be bleeding
if I hadn't hit you so hard.
I have two, so... you can
keep this one if you want to.
Thanks a lot, Kirie.
Uh, what, I didn't
mean anything by it!
Oh, me next!
I have a present to
give Yukinari also.
A present?
Oh, wow, it's a...
It's your very own Killty doll.
Killty, huh?
Yeah.
[KILLTY] I love you.
I hold you. I kill you.
Neat, huh?
I found him in a shop just
yesterday, isn't he the cutest?
Yeah, uh...
Here, I'll put him on.
[LISA] A checkered handkerchief,
a bandage on his face,
a Killty keychain...
Yukinari?
Ow. Ow.
I'm sorry about
that, Miss. I didn't--
Huh?
N-n-now I'm really sorry.
Are you hurt?
A bandage on your face,
checkered handkerchief...
Killty keychain...
I found you! My soul mate!
[MIHARU and KIRIE] Yukinari!
Oh, this is definitely more
than some mere coincidence!
This is no chance encounter!
No, it's the hand of fate!
I am the absolute luckiest
girl in the universe
to have Mabanya shower
such blessings down on me.
I'm so thankful.
Yukinari, snap out of it!
Let's take him
to the nurse's office.
--[KIRIE] Come on.
--[MIHARU] Okay.
Oh, Miharu,
grab his bag.
Right.
...And I owe it
all to black magic.
This is a thank you
from the netherworld
for my faithful service.
Oh, Mabanya, please watch
us from your unholy domain
as my soul mate and
I walk hand-in-hand
through our life together.
I just know that
I'll be blissfully happy
with my soul mate, my...
Oh, in the excitement
of the moment,
I didn't even ask for his name.
I can be so stupid,
stupid, stupid!
Please, my love,
may I have your name?
Hayate. Kosame.
[HAYATE] Did you summon us?
[KOSAME] Mistress?
The uniform that
man was wearing,
it seems we both attend
Mizuno High School, does it not?
Yes.
Then you know
what must be done.
Do you understand?
Quite, my mistress.
I love you. I hold you.
I kill you.
My soul mate.
You're not going anywhere.
I'm so wiped out.
Will you be all right,
Yukinari?
Well, you did have yourself
kind of a tough morning.
Ah, it could've been worse.
Least Fukuyama's
not here today.
I wonder what
happened to Fukuyama.
I really wanted to
thank him for convincing
the principal to let me go
to school with the two of you.
I don't know, he's not the type
that skips out on class...
The silence is
kind of weird, huh?
And speaking of weird,
the blond girl
from this morning...
Who let her out
of the nuthouse?
Kirie!
Fu... kuyama?
Kirie, I need you to tell me
more about that girl you met.
Where did you see her?
Tell me, Kirie!
What's the matter, Kirie?
Answer me!
Answer me, Kirie!
Ask your questions in Hell!!
[bell dings]
[KIRIE panting]
So...
Tell me a little bit more
about that girl, Kirie.
Gross.
What exactly was she like?
Extremely cute?
Yeah, she kept
going on about Mabanya
and how Yukinari is her
destined mate or something.
What?!
Gross.
A little longer,
just a little longer,
and I'll be joined
with my soul mate.
Oh, Mabanya,
lend me your strength,
so that I may have
success in this endeavor.
Ah! My future husband!
I'm crazy with waiting!
Puny-nari, you little bastard,
what did you do to her?
Well, I don't remember anything,
because I was unconscious.
Don't try and
hide it from me!
Hide what?
I don't know anything!
Fukuyama...
Chill out Fukuyama.
Target is acquired.
Kosame, are you ready?
Always.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Zero.
What's happening?
An ambush!
Could it be?
My eyes!
My eyes, oh, and my ears!
Target neutralized.
Time to head out.
Hey, you.
Where do you think
you're taking Yukinari, huh?
And who might you be?
I'll ask the questions!
The audacity of
attacking us at a school!
There's absolutely no way
you're gonna get away with this!
Lovely.
Why you!
Too bad. We'll have to
start from here next time.
What the hell was that about?
Kirie, where is Yukinari?
It was them...
no doubt about it.
Huh? Fukuyama, wait!
Where are you going?!
Hey!
Oh please, let me outta here!
What are you going
to do with me?!
Yukinari Sasaki,
Mizuno High School second year.
His extreme fear of
women manifests itself
in an allergic reaction
whenever he's touched by one.
He's allergic?
Yes.
With the sole exception
of a girl named Miharu,
who currently resides with him,
all women who
touch him trigger it.
My poor dear that's terrible.
But don't worry...
your days of suffering are over.
I'm going to cure your disease
with some demonic
assistance, that is.
Lisa!
Hmm? Oh, hey.
Lisa! So this is where
you've been hiding!
You! You're from this morning!
Yukinari!
You know each other?
I couldn't find you, Lisa!
You don't know how
much a brother worries!
Brother?
Oh, Lisa,
I've never known such pain!
Your brother?
Uh-huh.
Allow me to introduce myself,
I'm Lisa Fukuyama,
and this is my first
year at high school!
And to my left are my trusty
servants, Hayate and Kosame.
They've been
my private body guards
ever since I was a baby,
and they do my bidding.
Bidding... huh.
Well, it's been
fun chatting with you.
Lisa! You've been locking
yourself in your room
for months going
on and on about Mabanya.
Then you just
disappear this morning,
and I find you
cozying up to Puny-nari?!
It's more than a brother
should have to bear!
Lisa!
Um, excuse me.
Why did you have
your bidders kidnap
Yukinari in the first place?
Oh, why you ask?
Well, it's simple.
We're going to
have a ceremony
to join my soul mate and me
in unholy matrimony!
Lisa!
Marriage?!
Mat-ri-mo-ny?
What is this?
You don't get to decide for him.
Ceremony?
Yeah, ya see it's when, uh...
If you'd like to participate,
please keep your arms and
legs outside of the pentagram.
Wh-What's happening?
Spirits of the darkness,
creatures of
the eldritch beyond,
in the name
of Lisa Fukuyama,
show yourselves to me!
Sanctify my marriage
with your presence!
Don't do it, Lisa!
[FUKUYUAMA] I don't
think I can live in a world
where Puny-nari
is my brother-in-law.
Now, dear Yukinari...
Our infernal union.
Sealed with a kiss.
Huh?
This can't be possible!
My poor broken Yukinari.
It's mostly your
fault that he's broken!
Hey! She's the one
you should be blaming!
She ruined everything with some
sort of funky pink-haired magic!
Now, Lisa! Don't talk
to Miharu like that!
And anyway, why Puny-nari?
Haven't I told you
before I'd be happy
to find the
perfect guy for you?
If you continue interfering
with my destined love match,
I'll never forgive you.
But... but I didn't--
Hey, wait, hold on!
Look, I don't know how
you got it into your head
that Yukinari
was the guy for you,
but trust me on this,
it wouldn't work out.
Because... Yukinari
is afraid of women.
So! How come she
gets to chase him?
Miss Lisa, this is
the girl I told you about.
The one named Miharu.
Miharu?
Yes, the one female
who doesn't trigger
Yukinari's allergic reaction.
Oh. I see.
So, now that you get it,
you can go home, right?
But I'm not finished yet!
Yukinari's hurt.
Just leave the poor
guy alone already.
Oh yeah, and don't
forget to pick up
your unconscious pervert
brother on your way out.
What? Where am I? I don't...
What? What? What?!
Uh, hey, what?
I'm so glad
you could make it.
Are you feeling
any better, Yukinari?
I sure hope so.
Fukuyama's sister?
Hey, now.
No need to call me
Fukuyama's sister,
like we're strangers.
Please, call me Lisa.
Okay, but what is all this?
Oh, you mean
the full-course meal?
I pulled a few strings and
borrowed the cooking classroom.
I thought that a special dinner
might help with your recovery.
Uh, special how?
Yeah, ya know...
I'm really
not that hungry.
I mean, I am...
I'm really, really hungry!
Well then.
I should get you a plate!
Now Yukinari, there's plenty
of everything, so dig in.
Okay.
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
Well then... here I go!
Delicious.
Of course, silly.
When it comes to home cooking,
Lisa's the best!
I also made duck blood,
deep fried scorpions,
and royal jelly with bee larva.
Not only does
it taste wonderful,
but it's really good for you.
By the way, Yukinari, dear.
Hmm?
Is it true what they say?
That you have this
condition that flares up
if you get too
close to a woman?
Afraid so.
That is absolutely tragic.
To have you right here
and be denied your embrace.
I guess... sure.
But don't you worry.
I came up with
a great new idea
on how to banish your
woman phobia forever!
Um, your idea... tell me
it won't involve demons.
Goodness no!
Just forget about all that
black magic this afternoon.
Phew.
You see, my dear Yukinari,
the whole reason
I prepared this meal
was to help you try
and kick your allergy.
But... how will it help?
Most conditions
can be reversed...
if you know
what you're doing.
Huh?
Chinese medicine believes
that like cures like.
It's pretty simple.
If you have stomach troubles,
you eat a stomach.
If your liver's bad,
you eat a liver.
Huh.
The point is...
since touching a woman
makes you
break out in a rash,
what better cure
than a woman's touch?
Now, Yukinari.
Enjoy me.
It's time for dessert.
Yukinari, get back
here and fondle me!
This is your destiny!
Mabanya told me so!
I have no clue
what you're talking about!
Yukinari dearest, I adore you.
I'm yours for the taking!
No thank you!
Oh, Brother. Sorry I had
to put you in there,
but I couldn't let
you interfere with us.
Yukinari and I are in love,
and nothing's going
to get in the way of that.
Wah!
Yukinari! Yukinari, wait!
I know that you love me!
I'm not giving up!
I did mention you're
my soul mate, right?!
I'm home.
Today was just too much.
Miharu?
Oh, Yukinari, welcome home.
You waited up for me?
Yeah, I thought that
maybe you'd be hungry,
so I prepared
dinner for you.
Hmm. I see.
Sorry about that.
I was making it, and then
I got really, really hungry.
I tried.
So, let's eat.
Okay. Oh, I'll serve
you some soup...
Well, whatever's
left of it that is.
Um, Yukinari?
Yeah?
Sorry I dropped
a demon on you.
Don't worry about it,
everything worked out.
You really mean it?
Sure do.
Good!
Dig in!
Yeah.