Why do I have this feeling
you're gonna be hungry again
10 minutes from now?
Crab bread is
really tasty, Kirie.
You want some, Yukinari?
Uh, no thanks. I'm okay.
Oh well.
Come on, time for gym class!
Gotta burn off that bread!
One more, Kirie.
I'll run extra laps!
Get goin', Tubby.
Girls are weird.
I want crab bread.
You're gonna explode
if you eat any more.
[MACHIDA] Hold on!
Just where do you
think you're going?
This school is a sacred place.
How dare you sully it
with your garbage?!
Okay. Who is that person?
He's just some nutcase.
You want to know my name?
So be it!
Okay then.
See ya 'round, Klingon.
Hey! Gimme a second.
Just a little equipment trouble.
As long as there's
trash in the world,
and as long as I draw breath,
I'll be there to make sure
it gets thrown away!
Sworn protector
of Mizuno High School,
Lightning Cleaning
Squadron, Mamo-ranger!
We should go.
Good idea.
Don't you need
more than one person
to make a squadron?
Hold on!
What are you going to
do about this wrapper?
Oh.
We'll be more careful
from now on, so...
Look at this wrapper!
It's not gonna grow hands
and throw itself away!
You found the damn thing!
If it bugs you so much,
throw it away yourself...
Mamo-dork!
How dare you!
Still refuse to admit
your wrong-doing?
Fine! Face the
awesome sucking power
of the Lightning Mamo-vacuum!
Litter vanquished!
All in a day's work
for the sworn protector
of Mizuno High School,
Mamo-ranger!
Hey, wait!
What is it already?
Repent villains!
How can you not care about
the future of our planet?
The wrapper's gone!
Litter vanquished, okay?
Ah, I thought I could
open your eyes to the truth,
but oh well.
You're all too far gone.
Suffer the pine-scented
wrath of Mamo-ranger!
What are you doing, you pervert?
I'm just taking out the garbage.
What's wrong Mamo-vacuum?
I dare you to do that again--
Mamoru Machida!
Who're you?
Being president of
the cleaning committee
doesn't give you the
right to terrorize people!
Take off that mask this instant!
What are you doing? Stop it!
Once the hero is unmasked,
his only solace is death.
Miharu, are you all right?
Oh, uh, yeah.
I'm glad.
I'll be in my hidden
fortress if you need me.
Not so fast!
We're taking a trip
to the guidance office.
It just isn't fair!
I did all this for
Mizuno High School,
and this is the thanks I get?
Spare me the theatrics.
Oh man. Ms. Hijiri runs
a pretty tight ship.
Ms. Hijiri?
Uh-huh! That was Ms. Hijiri.
She arrived at the beginning
of the second term.
Rumor has it,
she'll drag students
down to the guidance office
and scold them
for almost anything.
Poor Mr. Moo Moo-ranger.
If I had thrown away that
wrapper like I was supposed to,
he wouldn't be in
any trouble right now.
It's not your fault, Miharu.
He's right.
Don't sweat it, okay?
She thinks she's so smart
putting me on clean-up duty.
That's not a punishment.
More like a reward...
Why don't people
clean up after themselves?
You think I'm gonna
give up just like that?
I'll never abandon my quest
to turn Mizuno High School
into an antiseptic
paradise. Mamo-ranger!
It's that boy from before.
Problem solved.
How dare you crap on me!
Excuse me.
Huh?
So we meet again,
Little Miss Crab-breath.
Attacking me
before I've had a chance
to transform into
Mamo-ranger is totally uncool!
I'm sorry about earlier.
You just want me to let my guard
down so you can finish me off.
Mr. Moo Moo-ranger you wanna
keep the school clean, right?
Right! Now leave me alone!
I'd like to
introduce you to someone,
to make up for this morning.
Introduce me to someone?
Uh-huh!
Miss Lilica!
Hello there.
Sorry to interrupt
your cleaning.
Is this young man
a friend of yours?
Yes. I'd like you
to meet Moo Moo-ranger.
Mamo-ranger.
Moo Moo-ranger meet Miss Lilica.
She cleans Fukuyama's whole
mansion every single day!
Isn't that amazing?
So, what is it that you need?
Well, you see...
we wanna know how to
make the school cleaner!
I thought maybe you could
share your cleaning secrets.
Hey, what's the big idea?
I don't mean to be impolite,
but Moo Moo here has
been fighting every day
to try to keep our school clean.
He calls himself a squadron,
but it's just him.
Thanks Crab-breath.
It's so brave how Moo Moo
tries to keep the school
clean by himself.
Can you teach him?
Let me get this straight,
day after day you've been
fighting grime all by yourself?
That's right! And I'll
never rest until it's gone!
A dirty school is worse
than no school at all!
I'll scrub those floors
'til my last breath!
'Til your last breath...
Tell me, is this
the path you've chosen?
Are you truly prepared to defend
those ideals, no matter what?
Uh, yeah!
So be it.
You'll help?
Meet me downtown at midnight.
You've much to learn,
my disciple.
Wow. You're
really lucky Moo Moo.
Uh, Moo Moo?
Well, well...
a careless smoker.
How would you deal
with such a man?
I'd give him a warning?
Pointless!
[Smoker] Stop! I can't breathe!
Why did you do that?
[Smoker] Huh? What do you mean?
You shouldn't toss your
cigarettes on the ground.
It's not healthy.
[Smoker] No, I'm sorry.
It's just one cigarette.
[Smoker] I'll never do
it again! I promise!
The ideals you hold most dear
mean nothing to your enemies.
If you cannot win them over
to your way of thinking,
you must annihilate them.
Of course, Master!
Tell me, what's wrong
with this picture?
Here in Mizuno,
non-combustible garbage
is supposed to be placed
in transparent trash bags.
There's all sorts of
non-combustible garbage in here.
Right the wrong
that stands before you.
Yeah! Just leave it to me.
Um, newspapers
and magazines, okay.
And these milk packs
are recyclable also.
Cardboard boxes are okay
if they're not waxed.
This one's a no-brainer.
Envelopes with plastic windows
are waste paper, not recyclable.
They're only fit for burning.
Master, this trash is
within the legal size limit.
I don't get it.
Ah!
Things aren't always as
they seem. Uncover the truth.
How did my master know?
Her instincts are
just out of this world!
You've had enough
training for one night.
But what should I do
with this giant tanuki?
Reflect on the
mysteries of recycling,
and the question
will answer itself.
All right, Master.
What's up, Miharu?
Yeah, you're all
smiles this morning.
It's a brand new day,
and I already know
it's gonna be wonderful.
Say, Miharu...
you're not just happy
because you can eat more
crab bread are you?
Un-unh. I'm too
excited to be hungry.
I can't wait
to get to school.
You'll see.
Everybody will be so happy.
So tell us. Come on.
I don't wanna
spoil the surprise.
Huh. Hey, buncha slobs.
What was that?
So long as the
world has garbage,
and trash does
its maximum harm-age,
and people keep littering
because they're stupid
and don't think about
the consequences-age,
why stop here when I can
clean the whole universe?
Lightning Cleaning
Squadron Mamo-ranger!
Commander Mamo-Red reporting for
duty.
Wow.
Still can't be a
squadron by yourself.
Lightning Squadron Mamo-ranger.
Who's alone now?
Your puppets are cool!
Oh, Master, I stayed
up all night long
making this new costume.
You taught me well,
and I'm ready to put
your wisdom into practice.
Stupid crow!
Watch out, Miharu!
If you can't win them over...
you must annihilate them!
I kind of miss
the Lightning Mamo-vacuum.
Good morning, everyone.
Why are you all crouching?
What the hell is going on?!
Look! On the roof!
Mamoru Machida's
lost his marbles.
Machida? That nerd?
Maybe something happened while
he was training with Lilica.
Lilica?
What did you just say?
It all makes sense.
Lilica asked if she
could go out last night.
If I'd only known...
Uh, Fukuyama?
If Lilica actually trained
Machida to be her protégé,
we should start
wetting ourselves now.
What?
W-What do you mean?
Outta ammo? Hmm?
Hmm, I wonder
where everyone went.
Well, at least I can do
my witchcraft in peace.
Here goes nothin'.
Oh mighty Mabanya, so long
as I have his Killty doll,
let me have
Yukinari's heart as well!
Don't move.
Excuse me,
I'm kind of in the middle
of something
important right now.
Quiet!
All you're doing
is making a mess!
Yeah, yeah, I'll clean
it up when I'm finished.
Smoke damage is
no laughing matter!
Do you have
any idea how long
it'll take to get
this place clean?!
No? 'Cause I do!
Blah blah blah, leave me alone!
Shut up!
Right, no ammo.
I'm so scared. Now go away.
Don't make fun of me!
The battle has just begun!
Lightning! Mamo-slugger!
Aww, bummer.
Look what you did to my crystal
ball, you jerk!
It's because you moved, stupid!
[KILLTY] Kill you.
Kill you.
Isn't that...
Machida must have tangled with
Lisa's magic.
Fine then, Lisa and Lilica are
both your problems, Fukuyama.
Do something about it!
Like hell!
We're talking about a magic
wielding ditz
and a trained killer!
If you think I'm interfering,
you're dumber than I thought!
If you didn't let them do
whatever they damn well please,
none of this would've happened!
There's just...
no pleasing you, is there?
What do we do?!
It'll destroy the school
if we don't stop it!
What are you
talking about? We?
This is all your fault!
Uh-unh! Well maybe a bit!
Killty smash!
Kill you!
I think that Killty doll's
gotten way too big
for his britches!
Lemme check how to stop him.
Uh.
You have to check the book?!
All right! I don't
know if this'll work,
but it's a chance
I'm gonna have to take!
Mamo-ranger final weapon...
Go!
Now what?
I've had about all
the weirdness I can take!
Hey! Up there!
When Mamo-Red's in a pinch,
he summons his final weapon
from its underground hangar!
The Lightning Mamo-machinedar!
Mamo-machinedar, get it?
'Cause it sounds
like my name, kinda...
Master Lilica, I've finally
thought of a way to recycle it.
Killty wins!
My depth perception sucks!
Wow! You showed
that tanuki who's boss.
I was only trying
to protect the school.
I wouldn't expect someone
like you to understand.
Really?
Then how come it looks like
a garbage dump right now?
Look around, dummy.
The school is completely
trashed thanks to you.
And your costume is completely
unoriginal, so there.
Huh?
Why can't I do anything right?
Mamoru!
[LITTLE MAMORU] Yeah?
I'm here, Mama!
Turning off the water's
too hard for you?
I'm sorry.
You can just go to bed hungry!
But first...
Please, Mama, forgive me.
Who am I kidding? I'm useless!
So, you're running away.
Master Lilica, why'd you come?
Then all that was just a lie?
Huh?
You told me you were prepared
to defend your
ideals no matter what.
What happened to that
indomitable spirit?
I'm useless. It's true.
My mom told me so.
I thought wearing this mask
would help.
Maybe wearing it would help me
change for the better,
maybe I could be like one of
those cool heroes
I admired so much when I was a
kid.
It was a good idea, but I-I'm
not...
Look at me.
Huh?
Hey! What was that for?
M-M-M-Master!
Those scars...
They're from my time
in Bosnia and Chechnya,
Afghanistan, Somalia...
I've been sent out on
assignments all over the world.
No matter how dire the
situation,
no matter how slim the odds,
I always found a way to prevail.
I'm so sorry, my Master.
If you really believe in keeping
the school clean, fight for it.
'Til your last breath.
Okay.
It doesn't matter that
you're a squadron of one.
Uh-huh.
As long as you fight
for what you know is right,
you're already a hero.
Kill you!
Nice knowing you two.
Hold on!
[Everyone] Machida!
It's Moo Moo!
No! I am Mamo-ranger,
Lightning Cleaning Squadron!
Mamo-ranger!
Kiss my ass!
Machida!
Go Moo Moo!
Lightning! Mamo-broom!
Huh?
Where's Moo Moo?
Is he all right?
Ah!
He's okay! Oh Moo Moo-ranger!
That stupid witch!
How could we have tied?
Actually, I won,
but who's keeping track, right?
What? Let's have a
rematch next episode.
I'll show you who's best!
Sorry, no time.
Next episode is all about
Tomoka and Big Brother.
Um, don't freak out,
but you're not even in it.
What?!
Girls Bravo Season Two,
next episode,
"As Long As We're
Together Then Bravo!"
Wait! Don't I come back again?
I made this
costume for nothing?!