[glass shattering]
[alarm ringing]
Dammit!
Sir!
[MACHIDA] My daughter
and I are all right,
but they made off
w-w-with our family's
most treasured heirloom,
the Mamo-ranger mask!
Rabbit monsters!
The rabbit monsters took it!
Damn! The Phantom Rabbits!
I should have known.
They're not
getting away this time!
[police whistles blowing]
Stop!
He's really persistent.
Here, catch Kirie!
Hey, nice pass, Miharu.
Go ahead and call me a tortoise,
I'm coming out
of my shell today.
Look out evil-doers!
Maybe not.
What a shame.
Some guys don't
know when to quit.
You shouldn't even try to
catch the Phantom Rabbits.
Here.
Don't underestimate me,
you thieving hussies!
Gotcha!
I finally captured
the Phantom Rabbits.
Piece o' cake!
Huh? What the--?
Blow-up dolls?
Get back here!
Hey...
Not their intended use,
but oh well.
Funny. I feel like
I know them from somewhere.
Nya nya nya. Nya nya. Arf!
You know we cut it
really close last night.
I'm really sorry.
I know I never should
have been so careless.
That's true.
They almost
captured us, Kirie.
Still, I'm glad you
weren't injured worse.
I guess it's a good thing
he's not a better shot, huh?
Well! I think he
meant to only wing me.
I happen to know that
Kazuharu's a very skilled shot.
You'd think
Kazuharu was perfect
the way you always
stick up for him.
No I don't!
Big Sister Kirie goes for
the strong, violent type.
No I don't!
I like him too.
After all, he has
been one of our café's
most loyal customers.
Customer...
Oh.
Hey! Don't get sloppy now.
You know he
must never find out
that we are
the Phantom Rabbits
who give him
so much trouble.
Don't you worry, Koyomi.
I promise not to
tell him our secret.
And I'm going to
get our loot back
if it's the
last thing I do.
Ugh. Great,
I got the joker.
Listen up you guys!
Oh my gosh, Tomoka.
Are you
trying to scare us
all half to
death or something?
Don't sneak up
on us like that!
I wanna come
along next time!
Tomoka, you're
still not old enough yet.
She's right.
That's why
we always say no.
What kind of
reason is that?
Why can't I go?
I could help out
with all kinds of stuff.
It's not fun
and games, Tomoka.
Huh?
Failure is not an option.
The stakes are too high.
We leave with the loot
no matter what risk.
And that's the cardinal
rule of the Phantom Rabbits.
Tomoka?
Nya! Nya!
Somebody get
him off of me!
These tailor-made pants
cost me a small fortune.
But Fukuyama, Ebi loves
you more than anyone.
Sure Miharu, just go ahead
and kick me while I'm down.
Hey, I've got an idea,
you should ask
your superiors
to hire Ebi
as a police dog.
Oh, don't you start in.
Here, your favorite.
Oh, why thank you.
Huh?
So, uh, how
about them Rabbits?
Huh?
Oh yeah, I almost
captured them again,
for whatever
that's worth.
I read about it
in the newspaper.
You know, at least
they didn't get away
with that mask
they were after.
Yeah.
But only
because one of them
dropped it into the river
as they were
making their escape.
And there was
another incident
at the same
time last night.
Huh? Another incident?
Can you ladies
keep a secret?
Yeah. Yeah.
They left behind
a ransom note!
You were chasing the Rabbits.
I was in the bathroom,
and when I came out,
my daughter was gone.
The only clues I found
were her panties
and that note!
Oh no!
"I have your daughter.
If you want her back,
I'll trade her for the
gold Mamo-ranger mask.
--The Phantom Thief BS."
Ah, The Phantom Thief,
a dastardly new villain
here in Water Field Town.
Otherwise known
as Black Snow.
But... that's
the worst kind!
Rumor has it he's collecting
rare and valuable masks
from all over the world.
First the Rabbits,
and now this Black Snow?
Oh, Lisa!
So then, how are you going
to track him down, Fukuyama?
Easy. Scotland Yard
is nothing if not thorough.
Our investigation has yielded
a very likely suspect.
Really? Who do
you think it is?
Loose lips sink ships,
as they say.
This CD contains
all of the information
on our suspect.
Just be careful.
You'd be in
a bit of a pickle
if anything
should happen to it.
Thank you, Kirie.
But he's already
as good as caught.
We'll storm
into his hideout
just as soon as
everything's in place.
Tell me, Kirie...
Uh?
What's wrong
with your hand?
Oh no, it's nothing.
So, uh, Fukuyama.
Um, I bought
some new lipstick.
Well, what do you think?
Uh, it's rather sexy.
D-D-Don't work too
hard on this case.
All work and no play...
Okay.
You pulled it off!
Koyomi, that
was really amazing!
What is this place?
Please, somebody help me!
Is anybody there?
That must be her...
the poor little thing.
Come on, let's get her
out of here right away.
If Mr. Machida buys
his daughter back
with the gold mask,
and Black Snow
gets his hands on it...
Then the Phantom Rabbits
would be disgraced!
Yeah we would!
Let's stop 'em!
I'll make sure we
get that mask back
if it's the
last thing I do.
Daddy, help!
Who are all of you?
A trap?
Please, just
let us out of here!
Come on, I'll make
it worth your while,
if you know
what I mean.
It'll be okay,
we're gonna
get you out of here.
I expected those bumbling
fools from Scotland Yard,
but you three
were a surprise.
Amazing what good
bait will attract.
Hey, you don't play fair.
Trading the loot
for a hostage
isn't a very
sporting way
to go about
stealing things.
When it comes to me
getting the masks I desire,
the ends
justify the means.
So what are you
going to do with us?
I've come to the conclusion
that Water Field Town
isn't big enough
for the four of us.
I do appreciate my rivals
delivering themselves
into my clutches like this.
They're not
technically masks,
but your rabbit ears
are pretty cute.
Perhaps I should add
them to my collection, eh?
Why don't you add this
to your collection?!
Ow! Damn you
Phantom Rabbits!
Mark my words,
I'm gonna make you
pay for that later!
I'd like to see you try it.
Don't worry,
we'll get you out, Lisa.
Just trust us.
Why should I
trust you thieves?
You're thieves aren't you?
Then there isn't
any difference, huh?
You're no better
than Black Snow is.
We're way better.
The only thing
we have in common
with that hooded freak
is that we all really want
your father's gold mask.
That's right!
We did risk our lives
to sneak in here
and rescue you, you know.
Where do you get off
saying that we're
no better than Black Snow?
Quiet!
Now let's get outta here.
All right!
Hey, you really
can trust us.
Oh, you'd think
a place this big
would have exit signs!
Keep your eyes
peeled for traps.
Well, they're a risk
we're gonna have to face.
There's something I don't get.
Huh?
How did you
know where I was?
Well, it's because...
It's because somebody
has a really big mouth.
Somebody has
a really big mouth?
Yeah, and it's
Scotland Yard's
most famous and
successful detective!
He's really just
a big blabbermouth.
Kazuharu's not a blabbermouth.
Koyomi managed
to steal that disc
with the information
about Black Snow right out
from underneath
Kazuharu's nose.
Thank you
for telling me.
All right, enough
with the chit chat, girls.
Black Snow
might have noticed
we broke out
of our cell.
Let's hurry.
Okay, you can
come out now!
Could you be any louder?
Why is there
sticky stuff on the floor?
It's too sticky!
I can't... pull
myself out of it.
Now we're in trouble.
Thank you for
bringing her back.
We weren't trying
to bring her back,
we were trying to leave.
Hey, Lisa,
are you all right?
Uh-huh,
I'm fine, Kirie!
But what about where that
bullet grazed your hand?
Huh? But how'd you...?
Phantom Rabbits,
you're under arrest!
Ka-Kazuharu?
You're a girl?
It can't be.
I don't believe it.
I always knew
I'd get a leg up
on you three eventually.
So how'd you
figure out who we were?
Between your demeanor
when I'd come into
the Nap Rabbit Café
and those
playing cards you use,
I had my suspicions.
I gambled on a hunch
and set up this trap.
Voila. You fell for it
hook, line, and sinker.
Then... Black Snow's
working for you?
This man does work for me,
but there's no such
person as Black Snow!
I'm Yukinari Sasaki!
And Mr. Machida
generously allowed us
to borrow one
of his castles.
I-I wanna talk to a lawyer.
You don't
have any evidence,
no jury on Earth
is gonna find--
Koyomi managed
to steal that disc
with the information
about Black Snow
right out from
underneath Kazuharu's nose.
Hey, that was my voice!
Do I sound that
cute in real life?
Indeed, it's
clear as a bell.
It'll be Exhibit 'A'
at your trial.
So that's what you're
going to do with it.
What?! You're gonna use
that to put us in jail?
No fair!
They shouldn't let people
like you be detectives!
Careful Miharu,
you're about to have
a wardrobe malfunction.
Huh?
Gah! The goo pulled
my clothes down.
Moving just
makes it worse.
Huh? No!
My word, look at those
stretchy tights, Koyomi.
No!
Kirie, I am so
sorry I shot you.
But... Kazuharu...
If only I'd known it was you.
I never would
have fired my gun.
I should have
told you my secret.
I'm sorry, too.
It's all right.
I suppose this
makes us even now.
Turn yourself
in to the police.
It's the right thing to do.
I can help you.
Kazuharu...
I need you to trust me, Kirie.
No! No!
Don't fall for it!
No, Kirie, don't!
Huh?
What is this... oil?
Is this another one
of your sneaky traps?
I don't think
this is another trap.
Huh?
Ta-da! It's the
Phantom Rabbit Petite!
You three can
thank me later.
What? Now there's
a Phantom Rabbit Petite?
Wow, she must have
followed us over here.
I told you I could be
useful for stuff, remember?
But nobody listened!
Okay, who wants
to go back home?
Me!
Maybe next time, right?
Come back!
Go and arrest me... in Hell!
It's nothing personal. Bye!
Congrats, Tomoka.
You're an excellent Rabbit.
Yeah! I told you so!
I didn't even know
you could do this with Ebi.
Hold on!
Huh?
You're all under arrest!
Damn Rabbits!
Gotcha!
Phantom Rabbits, why don't
you surrender already?
He's very persistent,
isn't he, Kirie?
Hey, Koyomi...
Wow. It's amazing
how stubborn he is.
Just hang on
Scotland Yard Big Brother.
He can't hold onto
that rope forever.
What do I do?
Kirie!
Huh?
Convince the
others to give up.
Kirie, I'm begging you.
Huh? But how can I...?
Remember Kirie,
it doesn't matter
how much you like Kazuharu
and he likes you back,
you really shouldn't try
to break up
the Phantom Rabbits.
Dammit. Well, in
that case, take this!
And this! And this!
Stop the Ebi,
I wanna get off!
We'll be okay,
just hold on.
It's not gonna work.
Poor Ebi's
running out of air.
Do doo.
Nya nya nya
nya nya nyaaa!
Oh no! There's too
much weight on here!
If we don't think
of something right away,
we're gonna crash!
We have to dump
something, and quick!
[GIRLS screaming]
Kirie!
Yeah?
I want you to promise me...
Promise...
Turn yourself in.
It's the only way.
Okay then.
Kazuharu!
He did that to
save us, didn't he?
What a courageous man.
Kazuharu.
I'm so glad
that you're all right!
I thought you were a goner.
Look, that lamp caught him.
How is he gonna
get down from there?
I wanna thank you for
honoring your promise, Kirie.
I did it... I did it...
because I...
Not so fast.
I can't just let
you have Kazuharu
all to yourself, Kirie.
You're both too
young for Kazuharu.
Um, I'm just the right
age to be his girlfriend.
Your sex appeal
hasn't had a chance
to mature like mine.
Keep dreaming!
Everyone knows guys
prefer younger women.
What are you talking about?
Kazuharu has loved me
for a long time now!
No, me! He loves me!
He actually loves me.
He loves Tomo best!
You know that's not true.
He winked at me.
Bravo Detective Fukuyama.
I think their days
of crime are over.
Why thank you,
but this time around,
I'm the one who pilfered
something outrageous.
What?
Oh, just their heart.
It's a masterpiece!
[EVERYONE] Huh?
What the hell was that?!
We shot a scene
after that one
where the Phantom Rabbits
team up and kick your ass.
Really?
And what the hell was up
with that superglue scene?
Superglue?
We never shot it half naked,
you damn pervert!
Why'd I change it around?
Right, I'm me.
Lying bastard!
This movie needs
a whole lot more Tomo.
Nya nya!
That bathtub scene
was so embarrassing.
Big Brother, I wanted to play
the part of
Yukinari's soul mate.
Why did you kick
me so hard, Kirie?
This is the best movie ever!
I'm gonna get that mask
and become the
Gold Mamo-ranger!
I'll get the attention
of all the girls
when I screen my
big-budget masterpiece
at the school festival.
They're not gonna
let you show this crap!
Originally, the festival was
held for ceremonial purposes.
Oh.
Back in the old days,
it was a chance
to offer sacrifices
to the various gods.
I don't think you
should sacrifice things
at a school festival.
Hey, come on out!
That's how you
summon them, see?
Girls Bravo Season
Two, next episode,
"School Festival is Bravo!"
Bring a friend!
Come out devil!
From the blue forest
metropolis, I summon thee.