[DEVIL laughing]
Welcome to my nightmare.
[KIRIE screaming]
[ALL] Huh?
[TOMO growls]
This is so boring!
What's boring?
You didn't like the movie?
Uh, yeah, Tomoka's right.
The movie is
pretty stupid, huh?
We should take it back.
That's not what I mean!
Sitting around the house
watching movies is boring.
Tomo wants to
do something fun!
Come on Short Stuff.
Why don't you take us
someplace fun for once.
I'd like to, but...
...we're a little
short on money.
Yes, it's because he's been
letting us live here
for free all this time.
Yes, that's right.
Yukinari is
poor because of us.
No! I don't wanna hear excuses!
I just wanna go out!
Hey, Tomoka, do you feel like
playing an Earthling game?
Huh? An Earthling game?
Do you really mean it?
Nya...
It's still your turn Tomoka.
Maybe you can't play
any more of your cards.
Tomoka, if you
have to skip your turn
3 times in a row, then...
You're out.
I'm sorry, Tomoka.
All right. Which one?
Huh?
Which one of you is it?
Locking the 8 of hearts!
Trying to force me out, huh?
I'm not having fun!
No fair! No fair!
Tomo wanted to win!
Um, maybe...
you'll win next time.
I didn't wanna play this
stupid game in the first place.
How am I supposed to
show you how clever I am
if I'm stuck playing a game
meant for little kids, huh?
Who's there?
Care to try your luck
at something more adult then?
[EVERYONE] Fu-Fukuyama!
I overheard the conversation
as I was sneaking in.
It sounds like Tomoka
wants to play something
a little more exciting, right?
Exactly! Yeah! I wanna
play a game that's super fun!
You're very lucky
I stopped by, Tomoka!
If there's one thing
I've got, it's game!
[doorbell rings]
[LILICA] Please
forgive my tardiness.
[EVERYONE] Huh?
[LILICA] Allow me
to set this up for you.
Wh--Hey!
Huh?
[LILICA] I'll be
leaving now, Master.
Unless there's anything else?
No, Lilica, that will do.
[LILICA] Good luck, everybody.
Ooh.
I bet this game
will be a lot more fun!
Nya!
Hey, wait, those are tiles
for Mah-Jong, aren't they?
Ma-Mah-Jong? What's that?
Mah-Jong sounds like
a really tasty game.
Get real!
You know Mah-Jong's
gonna bore Tomoka
right out of her
blonde little head.
If this were ordinary
Mah-Jong, yes, but it's not.
It's a very, very
special version.
A Fukuyama family favorite.
He's right.
The tiles are... different.
Huh? Different?
Different how?
Um, this one says "undress."
Hey, look at this tile.
What are you supposed to rub?
What the hell are those?!
I told you it was
Fukuyama-style Mah-Jong.
The rules are the same:
Collect 4 three-tile sets
and you win.
Child's play.
And what happens
when the game's over?
Keep talking, perv.
Based on their tiles,
the winner can make
the loser undress,
rub them for a while,
or make them wear one
of our delightful costumes.
What... kind of costumes?
I'm so glad
you asked, Koyomi!
Hey, costumes!
Hey Big Brother, I brought
over the Mah-Jong outfits.
I don't want to get rubbed
any more than I already have.
Why don't you go
play strip Mah-Jong
with your ancestors
in Hell, you pervert!
Help me, Lisa! Li-sa!
[KOSAME] Well, well.
Miss Kirie, long time no see.
Wah!
Dammit. Just tie me into
a knot already, why don't you?
You really should be
more careful, Kirie.
What would the
world do without me?
Don't bring over
sleazy games,
and I won't hurt you, okay?
It's not a sleazy game! This
game looks really interesting!
Yeah, it sounds
like a lot of fun.
And these costumes
are adorable.
Seashells!
Oh look, there's
even rabbit ears.
Miharu says the cutest things,
but sometimes
I think she's sort of...
Yeah, a little slow. Ditto.
Well, at least these two
are willing to take a chance.
Yeah!
Bring on the Mah-Jong!
Nya nya!
Okay, it's your call, Kirie.
Of course, if you're
really that afraid of losing,
I'll stop
pestering you about it.
Getting you naked would be
like shooting fish in a barrel,
only a whole lot less sporting.
No wonder you're
too afraid to play.
[FUKUYAMA laughing]
Kirie, no!
Don't do it!
Can't you see he's trying to--
Bring it on!
I'll show you who's scared.
First, I'm gonna beat
your ass at Mah-Jong,
and then we're
gonna play dress up!
Hmm. That's the spirit.
I'm glad you changed your mind.
As for you, I'd usually
say no, but I'm feeling
uncharacteristically
generous today.
You can play also.
Just try to stay clothed.
What?!
Your generosity is legendary.
Thank you for this privilege.
All right then. Here we go!
The first game will
be between the four of us.
I'm gonna win!
I'll try my best
not to beat you, sir.
Nobody made me play games
like this on Seiren.
Enough talking!
Let's get started!
Nya! Nya! Nya! Nya!
Huh? Do you wanna
play too, Ebi?
Okay! You can
be on Tomo's team!
Nya. Nya nya-nya-nya!
[EBI] So, here's what
we're gonna do.
I wanna finish the game
with an easy hand at first.
You know, get a
"feel" for the table.
If we get some rubs, we
should throw away rabbit ears.
Then we play the waiting game
and grab good tiles
from Fukuyama and Hayate.
Damn I'm good.
So which tile
should Tomo choose?
Mmm. This one!
Nya! Nya!
That's a stupid tile!
Nyo nyo nyo nyo!
What's gotten into you, Ebi?
Stop freaking out!
I don't want that!
Nyo.
I don't want that.
No!
I don't want that, either!
No no!
And I definitely
don't want that.
Nyo nyo nyo nyo!
Why is it...
that I'm sitting here
wearing nothing but a snake?
Hey! I can hardly
move in this thing!
Neither can I.
This is a problem.
Fukuyama! How come you're
not wearing something dumb?
I guess I'm just that good.
If you don't feel
like getting naked,
you should just quit
while you're ahead, Kirie.
I'm not quitting!
There's no way you're
getting off that easy!
Then let's begin
the second game.
I'll do my best! Yay!
Is it too late to
watch that horror movie?
And so it begins!
Nyo nyo nyo!
I see. Someone has trained you.
But not well enough!
"Dear Mother, How are you?
I'm sitting in a
backyard on Earth,
naked except for the huge
snake wrapped around my body.
I've never been so
humiliated in my entire life.
I wish the snake would
just swallow me whole,
so I wouldn't have to
deal with this horrible,
horrible planet any longer.
Love, Koyomi"
Now what? Oh it's you.
Ha! Read 'em and weep!
So, Kirie, how 'bout you slip
into a gym class outfit for me?
And let me have it...
when you're done.
Fukuyama! How come
you're only targeting me?!
I'm not exactly fully
clothed over here, you know.
There's plenty of humiliation
to go around, okay?
What did you say?
I'm gonna wedge those tights
where the sun don't shine!
They're already there,
but I appreciate the offer.
Now lose the top!
Don't get so riled up, you two.
It's only a game of Mah-Jong.
Just look on the bright side.
Now you have a brand
new gym uniform,
and it didn't
cost you a thing.
Isn't that lucky?
Yeah, that's
gonna calm her down.
Hmph. You can
drop out if you want to,
but you'll have to pay
the balance, either way.
For the last time,
I'm not quitting!
Hmm. Good to know.
Fine. Now come on,
let's hurry up
and start
the next game already.
Kirie's competitive nature
clouds her judgment.
She can't beat me.
The real threat is... Miharu.
Oh! That one!
Huh? Already?
Done!
All right, I get to rub
Yukinari 3 times, right?
Uh, Miharu?
Wah! Hold on Miharu! No, wait!
This is fun!
Rub rub rub rub rub!
Who would have guessed
Miharu has such good luck?
So much for my naughty
fun. Pity that.
Hey, why don't
you take a break?
You can re-think
your strategery.
Huh?
Splendid idea.
All right, let's take
a break. How's that sound?
Oh! Okay!
I'll go make
some tea for everyone.
Damn it all, I was so
close to finishing, too.
One of these,
and one more rub tile,
and I'd have
the perfect hand.
Well, I need to go
take care of something.
Quiet, cat boy.
Looking good, Puny-nari.
Fukuyama...
what are you doing
in here... with Kosame?
Oh, nothing.
I just thought maybe
you'd like to team up with me.
Team up? With you?
That's right. I think we
should try working together.
It's the only
way to beat Miharu.
Wait, you wanna cheat?!
Do you really wanna
die looking like that?
Come, Puny-nari, you
know you're dying to see
Miharu wear all
sorts of sexy costumes!
You know you want to.
Well...
I mean I...
... a little bit.
So you shall.
Don't bungle
this up, Puny-nari.
Hey, Big Brother,
how did it go?
He said he'd help.
There's some testosterone
in there somewhere!
Bravo!
Wait 'til I tell
Miharu how Yukinari
teamed up with Big Brother
to cheat her out of her clothes.
You cheated and made me
wear skimpy outfits.
Yukinari, how could you?
Miharu, wait!
Don't worry, Yukinari.
I'll never abandon
you like Miharu did.
Lisa, how foolish I've been.
We are soul mates. Ha ha.
[FUKUYAMA and LISA laughing]
Oh, I wondered where
the two of you went.
I made some tea for you.
Okay!
Thanks a lot.
Uh, can I... go now?
I'm only going to
say this one time.
Listen up. I wanna see
Kirie wearing something kinky.
Huh? Kirie?
That's right, I want Kirie's
lovely body on display
for everyone to enjoy.
Oh, just the thought
of it drives me wild.
Uh, gotcha.
You know what to do then.
Oh, one more thing.
If you double-cross me,
I'll kill you.
I don't wanna play anymore!
Your fighting skills are
improving, young Tomoka.
When I left,
Tomo was just the learner.
Now Tomo is the master!
Stay back.
Come here, you!
No, no, ow!
Oh, I haven't
been very thoughtful.
Care for some bean paste?
You'll be
hibernating before long,
so you can't skip any meals.
What the hell
is going on here?
Why can't I finish
a single hand?
Rub rub rub the boy
sitting across from me.
You're all mine, Miharu.
You're all mine, Yukinari.
You're all mine, Kirie.
Here's the plan: I'll pretend
like I'm on Fukuyama's side,
but what I'll really
do is protect Miharu.
Hmm. I think I'll
get rid of this one.
Check it out, baby!
Oh wow, you finished
that really fast.
I have to take off three
things and put on a blouse?
Okay then.
So far, so good.
You just keep 'em coming.
Um, yeah.
Um, excuse me.
Does this look all right?
[YUKINARI and FUKUYAMA panting]
Come on. Let's start
the next game already.
Right! I think I'm going
to win this time.
Better not get too attached
to that blouse, Miharu.
Okay then.
I have one of those,
so I guess I could
throw this away.
Ready, Puny-nari?
Roger.
Oh no! Look over there!
How did a chupacabra
get into the house?
Quick hide all the goats!
My mistake!
It was really just a coat rack.
You're an odd little girl.
Done.
Well, I'm gonna finish
my set now, too. Here we go.
Perfect.
There's no damn way
I'm gonna lose this time.
Done!
You've gotta be kidding me!
This is degrading.
Why do I have to
wear this thing.
Cheer up, Kirie.
I think that costume
looks really cute on you.
It could be worse.
You could look like
that guy at the convention.
Fukuyama! It's time
we upped the ante.
I think the loser
of the final game
should walk around
the neighborhood.
I'm having plenty of fun
just the way things are.
Why the hell would I want--
If I lose the last game,
I'll go around in a loin cloth
or anything else you
can possibly think of.
Do you want to do it or not?
What are you saying, Kirie?
Are you crazy?
Huh. A loin cloth, eh?
Fantastic!
Then I accept your offer.
And if I win the last game,
then I wanna give Yukinari
a super extra special rub.
Knock yourself out.
You can rub him all you want.
Great! Hold on to
your ears, Yukinari.
But I don't want a rub!
Do or die time, Puny-nari.
We'll play it safe
and knock Kirie out
right away with a Tenho.
What's a Tenho?
Wait, don't tell me.
I've had enough.
I'm done playing.
You sure about that?
The idea behind
Tenho is simple.
You give me enough good
tiles to win right away.
Don't fail me, Puny-nari.
I can't betray Kirie.
Don't try anything funny.
Huh? Yukinari dear,
are you all right?
You look sick.
I'm sure they're just
"last game jitters."
Am I right?
Uh, yeah.
Okay, let's finish this!
Yeah! I'll play my very best,
so I can give Yukinari
my super special rub!
Good luck, Yukinari.
And so begins...
our final game!
This is perfect.
Once I roll two on the dice,
everything will be set.
Prepare yourself, Kirie.
Here goes!
Nya nya nya nya!
Wha? What the hell
just happened?
I got a little
wild with my swing.
A thousand pardons.
You're not injured,
are you, Master?
Um, I'm guessing that we did
something we shouldn't have.
Dammit. You know I thought
something seemed fishy.
You were cheating
the whole damn time, huh?
Even you, Yukinari!
Yukinari, how could you?
I thought you were different,
but you're just
like all the others.
But... I didn't... I mean...
Kosame was gonna shoot me!
Save your lame excuses.
Enjoy your little
field trip you cheaters.
You ready?
Hmm. A promise is a promise.
How come I have to do this?
I wasn't even playing.
I'm sorry, Miss Lisa.
I'll explain guilt
by association later.
For now though,
we should get walking.
Hey Fukuyama, cheaters
never do prosper, do they?
Well, not this time.
My strategy was perfect.
If she'd kept that rub
and thrown away rabbit ears,
she could have finished a set.
I can't figure out why
she didn't hang on to that rub.
You gotta form sets
fast in that first game.
Why doesn't she get
something so simple?
We're together every day,
but she doesn't understand me.
Huh, that's women for ya.
How come the others never
seem to understand me...
The sound of
a siren at midnight...
People scream and it cuts
through the peaceful night.
Observe the fatal battle
between 3 rabbits
who steal everything
in the darkness of night,
and the detective intent
on tracking them down.
Girls Bravo
Season Two, next episode,
"Rabbit Ears Bravo!"
Don't miss it.
Am I just a sound effect?