Everyone, be careful over there.
[KIRIE panting]
So... so this is...
Seiren?
It's just like I remember.
This is no time for
stupidity, Puny-nari.
Stay focused on
why we came here!
That's right! We have to save
Miharu and get new gifts!
Nya nya nya nya nya.
Huh?
HUH?
What? What??
[YUKINA] They're here.
[HIJIRI] Understood.
Yukinari...
[GREEN GIRL] It's a man?
[ORANGE GIRL] Not just one!
Two of them!
Our fiancé's back!
Well, this sucks.
Of all the places
we could end up,
we had to appear
in the middle
of Seiren's biggest
outdoor bath?
Nya nya nyaa!
So, now that we're
here, what do we do?
Um, no clue.
[FUKUYAMA laughs pervertedly]
Fukuyama?
Well I know I've got
a couple of ideas!
This is paradise!
I've died and gone to Heaven.
Don't worry, I'll stay behind
and hold them off. Now go!
Thanks Big Brother,
you're so brave.
Ladies, please, I only
have four appendages.
[YUKINARI] My hero.
[TOMO] I'm glad I'm underage.
Nya nya.
Hey, Tomoka, are
you sure you know
where the Space
Management Bureau is?
It's straight ahead.
Stop worrying so
much Short Stuff,
Tomo knows Seiren
like the back of her hand.
Follow me!
Or maybe not...
Whatever happened to knowing
it like the back of your hand?
Calm down. Everybody makes
mistakes, Lisa, even you.
You're fine, Kirie.
It was just a couple of bats.
We're not even on the map.
You have no idea
where we are, do you?
This isn't my fault!
This whole thing is a trap.
A trap?
You think so? But what?
Dunno. It could
be almost anything.
I don't care what it is, let's
just get out of here already!
I remember!
This passage should lead us
back up to the surface, Lisa.
Nya. Nya. Nya. Nya. Nyo!
Is this... the way out?
Well it might be, but...
...we're not out
of the woods yet.
But... we're not in the woods.
They're all exits right,
let's just pick one and get out!
Hold on! You don't know
what might be in there!
[EVERYONE] Huh?
What is this place?
BEAR.
[KIRIE giggles]
HUH?
BEAR!
What was that thing?
Geez, Kirie, be less
careful why don't you?
Those little blue bears
are only the most dangerous
creatures on Seiren, that's all.
We call them the
"cuddly killers."
Bear... Bear? Bear.
BEAR.
BEAR!
Bear. Bear. Bear.
This... is bad.
Yeah. Ideas?
Anyone?
Yeah! Run for it!
BEAR!
Quick! Grab on!
Whah!
[TOMO yelling]
Tomoka!
[TOMO] NO WAY!
NYA!
Huh? Ebi? Ebi!
Ebi!
Lisa, no!
Bye Yukinari!
I'll see you later!
Lisa!
Nya nyanyanya nya.
Bear. Bear. Bear.
Bear.
You're okay.
NYA?
I was right about watching you.
It really is a full-time job.
NYA.
NYOOO.
Now. How dare you attack one of
Lisa Fukuyama's best friends?!
Your cute little asses are mine.
[explosion]
Lisa...
So this... this is the place.
Get ready.
Time to raise a ruckus!
Wha?
Hey! Hold on!
Go!
Tomoka!
No, don't!
There's gotta be another way!
Blond witchy girl... and Ebi...
I promise you both...
Tomo is gonna
avenge your deaths!
I think you guys will have
to do the avenging for me.
Miharu's gotta be
in here somewhere.
How come we got inside
so easily? No one's here.
Hey, are you all right?
[GUARD] Get out of here.
They've already taken
over the entire building.
[hands clapping]
Welcome to the Space
Management Bureau, you two.
You should be more
respectful, Kirie.
I was your teacher
only yesterday.
Ms. Hijiri! Give Miharu
back to us right now!
Hmm. Let's think about that...
There's nothing for you
to think about!
Give her back,
or you'll regret it!
Well this isn't good.
What do you think you're doing?
They don't.
Think, that is. Every last one
of them is under my control.
Control?
Yes, I'm controlling
their weak little minds.
And I'm rather skilled at it,
if I do say so myself.
Now submit to me.
[HIJIRI laughs]
Very good. I guess you two
are stronger than I thought.
Ladies, kill them.
Maharu!
Hey, Yukki, Kirie.
Didja miss me?
Am I glad to see you!
The feeling's mutual.
Now let's go, Miharu is still
being held prisoner in there.
Right. Come on.
I'm not leaving, not just yet.
Maharu is awesome,
but she shouldn't have to
fight them all by herself.
Kirie...
Go save her.
Mmm.
[HIJIRI laughs]
Maharu, you never
give up, do you?
You still haven't changed.
Neither have you.
You're still totally
obsessed with my little sister.
I already know who's
gonna win this battle.
Do you still wanna fight?
Yes, of course.
The real question is whether
or not you still want to.
Hey, Hijiri.
Kirie...
You tried to take Miharu
away from Yukinari,
and that's the kind of
thing I can't forgive.
What are you going to do?
I'm gonna kick your ass.
[KOYOMI panting]
Are you all right, Koyomi?
Uh-huh. Tired, but I'm okay.
[something falling]
Look who's here.
My, my, you've grown
so big... Koyomi.
You're... my father?
Miharu!
Yukinari!
Hold on! I'll get
you out of there!
You...
I saw you on Earth.
You're behind all this?
Why did you take her?
Nevermind. Just give Miharu back
to me. Give her back, damn you!
Yukinari!
Kosame, don't worry about me.
Protect Koyomi.
He's too strong, but how?
It's hypnosis.
Lilica!
Yukinari! Yukinari!
I'm okay.
Remember what I told you.
Sure I'm small, but I'm actually
a lot stronger than I look.
I'm sorry, but I really don't
like it when people yell at me.
Why are you doing this to her?
You must have a reason.
Yukinari?
My name is Yukina.
My telekinetic powers
are stronger than those
of any other woman on Seiren.
T-Telekinetic powers?
Look at me.
It's not only on my chest.
It's all over my body...
on my arms and legs...
and my back, too.
The star mark.
The star mark, that's right.
It's both my blessing
and my curse.
But... what's that have
to do with Miharu?
You're... allergic.
It's funny, isn't it?
This rash, I get it every
time I touch a man.
That's why I decided...
if I could never enjoy
a man's embrace,
then no one else on Seiren
should get to enjoy one either.
I'm very sorry.
Yukinari!
Huh? Wah!
You're a very talented girl.
Your fighting skills
are top notch.
Why the hell are you doing this?
Never you mind.
I'll tell you what she's doing!
She's been
following Miharu around
ever since she
was a little girl.
Huh?
Once Hijiri joined the
Space Management Bureau,
she stopped stalking her,
but I guess old habits die hard.
So... so you're saying she's a--
My, my, you seem
a little nervous.
Great, I'm like
catnip for lesbians.
[KOSAME sneezes]
[KOYOMI] Kosame!
Just keep concentrating.
Yukinari, are you
all right? Yukinari!
Once we disband the
Space Management Bureau,
the Aqua Lamps won't
be made anymore.
Koyomi can open a gate,
but she's going to die
on Earth any minute now.
And then there's you.
If I can nullify your power, I
wouldn't have to suffer anymore.
No more star marks.
No more men appearing on Seiren.
I wouldn't have to be afraid.
I wouldn't have to be ashamed.
Give me your power,
so I can finally live in peace.
I'll give you anything you want.
I don't care what happens to me,
just please don't hurt
Yukinari. I beg you!
Kirie!
The only thing I've ever wanted
was to live with
my darling Miharu.
Yukina and I are working
towards the very same goal.
She's the chief of the
Special Forces unit, you see.
We're going to turn Seiren
into a women only paradise.
This concludes today's
lesson, Kirie.
When you wake up, I think
that you'll be seeing things
in a much different light!
Fu-Fukuyama?
What?
[TOMO] Everybody, charge!
What is this?
Now, learned this from Kazuharu.
Clothesline from hell!
[BLUE GIRL] Kazuharu taught
me this, burning hammer!
[LITTLE GIRLS]
Reverse leg twist!
'Bout damn time.
Fukuyama!
Well, I taught them a few moves.
I had to put all your
beatings to good use.
You're hurt.
Don't worry, it's not
as bad as it seems.
Fukuyama!
Tomo didn't start
this fight, lady,
but Tomo's definitely
gonna end it.
You little brat.
Ms. Hijiri,
do you remember before
when I told you that
I was going to kick your ass?
I was wrong.
So, you finally give up.
I should have said...
...I'm sending your ass to Hell!
Yeah, Kirie! You did it!
[MIHARU crying]
Please don't cry, Miharu.
Huh?
You see, I'm all right.
Yukinari!
I'm sorry that I
yelled at you...
You and I...we're
kind of the same.
We have the same problem.
A few girls were mean to me,
and I got really insecure.
What are you talking about?
I know how much it hurts, but
it's time to stop doing this.
Stay away from me.
Why, because you're different?
You're fine.
Liar! I showed you my body!
I'm covered in
these repulsive marks.
I'm so ugly, no man
would even look at me!
But that isn't true, Yukina.
Don't tell me
that it's not true.
Besides, I'm short.
Nobody likes
someone who's short.
I'm pretty short myself.
I'm not very attractive, and my
breasts... well, they're small.
My body's not so great either.
I'm not exactly what
you'd call muscular.
It doesn't matter! Whenever
I touch a man, I get a rash!
I know. But you can
still touch them.
You touched me
a moment ago, right?
Yeah! And it hurt!
Sometimes people hurt you,
but loneliness hurts worse.
I know, because I used
to be just like you.
But if you're brave
and reach out to somebody
with your hands,
you just might end up
touching their heart.
Miharu taught me that.
Yukinari...
I'm coming over.
No, stay away!
It's all right. Don't be afraid.
Please, I'm begging you.
I said, "Stay away!"
But... no one...
no one looks at me... ever.
No one tries to know
who I really am.
I was lonely too,
but then I met someone...
the most important
girl in my life.
I met Miharu.
If you can just
open your heart,
you'll meet
someone special, too.
It can happen. Right, Miharu?
Right.
Yukki... you did it.
He's okay.
Yes. Everything is okay now.
They're all coming
back home to us.
You know... you're a damn idiot,
but you're my kind of idiot.
Oh, Yukinari! Rise and shine!
It's time for breakfast.
Today I made fresh
cooked rice and clam miso soup,
a Japanese style omelette,
and baked horse mackerel.
I hope you're hungry,
sleepyhead.
Huh? Yukinari?
Miharu?
Yukinari!
Ah, Miharu... good morning.
You know better
than that, Yukina.
You're both going
to end up all itchy.
Not me!
And that's because
Yukinari is the man
that I'm destined to be with.
After that first time I met him,
I haven't gotten one rash.
So you get cured and my
allergy comes right back.
Yeah, that seems
all kind of fair.
Please, just get
off him already.
Sorry, Yukinari.
Can I hide in here?
Uh, Kirie?
So here you are, Kirie.
When you slammed me
into the floor like that,
I suddenly realized you
were the perfect girl for me.
Hold on. I'm not sharing
Miss Kirie with anyone.
What are you talking about?
I've been harassing Kirie
for years now, she's mine!
Ms. Hijiri, it looks like she's
turned over a whole new leaf.
Ah, don't worry Yukinari,
my feelings for you
will never change.
They shouldn't be so noisy
this early... right, Daddy?
They're all just a bunch of
horny teenagers if you ask me.
NYA.
It would seem so.
You're wise beyond
your years, Tomoka.
Well, that's all right.
At least the gate
is staying open now.
I can comb this
wonderful masculine planet
for the man of my dreams!
You know, you're pretty cute.
Wanna get married
later this afternoon?
Huh?
Aw geez. And I thought there
were too many girls here before.
[GIRLS] Yukinari!
Yeah, I'll be right down!
Huh?
Yukinari!
Coming!
My name is Yukinari Sasaki.
Girls have been picking on
me and bossing me around
ever since I was a little kid.
It got so bad I started breaking
out whenever they touched me.
You know what?
I still do, but it doesn't
really bother me anymore.
There was a time
I thought I hated 'em.
But I've had a change of heart.
I love girls! I really do!