[KIRIE] Look, I don't know
how you got it into your head
that Yukinari was
the guy for you,
but trust me on this,
it wouldn't work out.
Because Yukinari's
afraid of women.
She's so hard-headed.
Like I should talk.
Okay, Mom! I'll be over at
Yukinari's house if you need me!
Hey, don't wanna forget that.
I put tons of work into this,
and it'll all be for
nothing if I leave it here.
I'll see ya later!
Hold on... wasn't that Miharu?
I wonder where she's off to.
But if she's out right now...
That means Yukinari's
home all by himself.
Oh, why am I getting
so nervous all of a sudden?
I mean, this is
my lucky break, right?
Come on,
just press the button
like usual
and open the door.
[doorbell rings]
Huh?
Yukinari!
Answer the damn door!
Yukinari?
So the other day
I'm walking down the street,
and this really disheveled
guy comes stumbling up to me.
I don't get it.
In this note, Miharu said
she was going out for a while,
and that
she'll be back later.
But that's no reason
to be so down about it.
Besides, it's not
like the two of you
are joined at
the hip or something.
She can't spend
every minute with you.
Maybe something
unexpected came up, right?
I'm sure she'll be back
home in time for dinner.
Okay?
Yukinari...
If you're like this now,
what are you going
to do if Miharu ends up
returning to Seiren some day?
Seiren?
Sorry, that was
a stupid thing to say.
And that's exactly
what's going to happen.
Huh?
Miharu... I mean
just look at me.
She's definitely gonna go back
to Seiren one of these days.
Because I'm slow and puny.
She's gonna throw me away.
Stop.
Why would Miharu do
something dumb like that?
You are so... it's okay.
I'm sure that's not
what happened this time.
This time?
What do you mean it's
not what happened this time?
What? Well, uh...
I didn't mean anything.
But do you
know what happened?
Well, I saw her riding
in a car on my way over.
I don't think Seiren
had anything to do with it.
She was in a car? What kind?!
Um... it was
an expensive white import...?
I didn't know I was gonna
get grilled about it later!
So it was an expensive
white import...
She wouldn't
ride with a stranger.
Now, who does Miharu know
with that kind of a car?
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH] Fukuyama!
That's terrible!
I have to go save
Miharu right now!
Oh geez!
Yukinari, wait for me!
I've never been here before.
The word "mansion"
doesn't quite cover it.
[LILICA] Might I help
you two with something?
Um, uh, hi... is Fuku- I mean,
is Kazuharu here right now?
Ya see, we're friends
of his from school.
And we were in the neighborhood
just now, and well...
Wait, Yukinari, why'd you say
that we're friends with him?
If we tell her the truth,
she won't let us in.
Just leave the talking to me.
What? What did you just say?
What?
What did you say
just a moment ago?
Uh, I said that we're
both friends of Kazuharu's.
Friends?!
Master Kazuharu has friends?!
Excuse my outburst.
The shock has rendered me
slightly light-headed.
Uh, what do you
mean "the shock"?
Well then, if there
are no more questions,
would the young
lady care to step inside?
Huh? But why only me?
Hey, wait a minute,
can't I go in too?
A thousand pardons,
but Master Kazuharu's
hatred of men is unrivaled.
That is all.
Think I'm throwing
in the towel, do you?
I'm a new man today,
so look out!
If Miharu needs rescuing,
I'll show this wall who's boss!
Just wait!
Miharu!
Where am I?
I think I've been
going in circles...
I don't even see
the mansion anymore.
Maybe I should catch
my breath for a second.
And then I'll go on.
This is the heliport;
the pool's down that way.
Oh.
Fukuyama's stupid,
but he sure is rich.
[rapid gunfire]
Ah!
Is something the matter?
Is something the...
wasn't that gunfire just now?!
Yes. It would seem that
a mouse has sneaked in.
An amateur.
Has anyone ever suggested
that you might be taking
pest control a little too far?
Let us go inside now.
Huh?
Unfortunately, Master Kazuharu
is taking a nap right now,
but I will take full
responsibility for your welfare
and show you around
the mansion in the meantime.
Uh, don't go to any trouble.
I'm simply implying
that right now it is
much safer to
be indoors than out.
But, hey... what's
that supposed to mean?
Any closer, and I'd look
like swiss cheese.
Ah, but I'm not
going to give up!
No! I have to rescue Miharu
from Fukuyama's lewd clutches!
Crap!
Damn, I missed.
This is Alpha One, I've cited
the intruder. I am in pursuit.
What the heck's going on?!
What's with this place?!
Hey! Where'd all this wind
suddenly come from?!
All central air conditioning
is automatically routed
through the vents
near the floor.
Something wrong?
Will you just
turn the thing off?!
Stop it!
This way please.
Damn it.
What's with this place?
It would seem that
your bra is too small.
Is that an oversight or
a matter of preference?
Say what?
Your measurements are
89 on top and 64 underneath.
Might I be so bold as to suggest
that you stop wearing an F cup.
It would be a waste
of such lovely bountiful
breasts as yours.
When did my chest
become such a hot topic?
This elevator is designed
to perform a full body MRI
of all of its female passengers.
It then strips away the clothes
from that computer image
and measures one's bust,
waist, and hips.
Truth be known,
it's a very innovative system.
Not to mention,
a very expensive one.
Master Kazuharu can enjoy
all female visitors' bodies
in 3-d rendered,
real-time virtual imagery.
This technology was pioneered
by the Fukuyama Science Fou--
That took five years to develop.
Are you stupid?
This machine is pointless!
If you're going
to make something,
why not make something
useful for society!
I'm sensing you
didn't much like it.
Why would I?!
Let's move on then.
I wanna go home.
Damn it all,
we lost the target.
Don't worry about it.
Come on, let's check out
the next sector.
Okay Romeo 6-4,
we're moving on to
the north quadrant.
[HEADQUARTERS]
Understood Alpha Two.
I'm still alive.
Okay, now what?
How am I going to find
my way out of this maze?
No way! I can't let
myself get discouraged.
Right now, the only thing
I should worry about
is how to save Miharu!
What?
Today's mouse
is very energetic.
Wouldn't you
agree with me?
Oh, I'm talking to myself.
But where on
earth did she go?
I needed that.
Master Kazuharu.
Lilica.
Are you awake Master?
Why are you talking to me?
My sincere apologies.
You had a visitor--
a buxom young woman
who mentioned to me that
she was a friend of yours.
Friend of mine?
I was showing her
around the mansion,
but I seem to have lost her.
Huh. I don't know.
It's nothing to brag about,
but I don't really have friends.
I, Lilica,
regret her disappearance.
Oh, nevermind. Speaking of
girls, where's you-know-who?
Right. Miharu's
in a room in the back.
I see.
Come on!
How the hell
am I supposed to get out
of this place anyway?
Oh. All I wanted was to have
some quality time with Yukinari,
and I even got up
extra early to make this.
Why does it always
have to turn out this way?
Huh?
Hey! Miharu?
Oh. Hmm? Kirie?
What happened?
There's only one pervert
who would do such a thing!
Fukuyama! Is this
your idea of a joke?!
I want my clothes
back this instant!
Fukuyama!
Are you listenin--
[KIRIE yells]
Fukuyama?
What's wrong, Fukuyama?
Are you okay, Fukuyama?
What happened to you, Fukuyama?
Hey, Fukuyama!
Are you stupid?!
Ever since
I made the mistake
of trying that nasty ass
bento you brought me,
I've been barfing non-stop!
Huh? Oh, you've
been eating my bento!
Geez, how on earth
could you possibly
make it taste like that?
I probably have stuff
in my garbage cans
tastier than that slop.
You've got some nerve!
I got up early and tried
my very best on this, too.
Of course,
I know it's not as good
compared to Miharu's cooking,
but I put a lot of thought into
the foods nutritional value.
You know, I even
counted the calories.
I made sure to include
a lot of different
kinds of ingredients
and packed it full
of vitamins and minerals!
It's not exciting,
but it's healthy!
It's not so bad.
Are you paying
attention, Fukuyama?
I think my groping
days are over.
What are you saying?
You can't die from my cooking.
Everything's
getting dark, Kirie.
Will you hear my last wish?
Uh, what is it?
Nurse me.
Huh?
If you'd be my nurse,
I could leave this
world without regrets.
Oh, and in a pink nurse
outfit if possible.
You son-of-a--
[FUKUYAMA coughing]
I guess that'd be okay.
I just have to be
your nurse, right?
Your temperature is good.
Looking good, Kirie.
The fit is perfect.
How is it perfect?
The skirt is tiny.
Don't worry about that.
That's how I like them.
Hey, do you think you
could hand me that book?
Thank you Nurse Girl.
Oh no! I can't
control my hands!
The patient shouldn't
be pulling up skirts!
Sorry, it seems that you
have kicked me so much
that I've developed a terrible
case of Phantom Hands Syndrome.
Huh? What are you saying?
Please, forgive
these hands of mine,
they know not what they do.
It's just that you beat me up
over and over and over again.
Oh, stop it. I get it already.
Oh, my hands, I can't stop them.
Why, you...
Perverted faker!
Hmm? You didn't...
what's wrong, Kirie?
Just now, I swear some
little blue kid's face
was poking out of your chest.
What are you talking about?
Brother, dear?
Oh, Lisa.
I'm sorry to barge in like this.
I made a mistake in
my ghost-rain technique
and the ghosts all escaped.
I'll exorcise them right away,
it'll only take a minute.
All right,
just be quick, okay?
Hayate, the sage's seal.
Sorry it got so noisy.
Be gone, spirits!
You'll have to forgive my little
sister for her unorthodox hobby.
I don't care why they're here,
just do something
about it already!
Ah, do something about it, huh?
I think you should
do something about it!
You... must be kidding.
You're even hot as
a shrine maiden, Kirie.
Go now, tool of divine justice!
Return these lost souls to
the abyss from which they came!
Yes, I'll do it!
I'll defeat them!
What are you, nuts?!
Um, should I help
you clean that up?
No, thank you.
I'll be just fine on
my own, so please go
to Master Kazuharu's
bedroom now.
Yes, ma'am!
I'll go there right now!
Just like that, my room becomes
a portal to the great beyond.
Don't worry, Big Brother,
these ghosts will be
out of here any minute now.
I don't think
I'll be holding my breath.
I give up!
I just wanted to spend some
time with Yukinari, that's all!
I'm going home now.
Or maybe not.
Lisa...
How much longer
is this going to take?
I won't let a single
one of you escape!
Hold on,
what's this all about?
Who are you anyway?
W-w-w-w-what are you doing?!
Kosame. I want you
to call me Kosame.
I remember you. We fought
when you kidnapped my friend.
You looked very...
lovely that day.
I'd like to get to know
you a little bit better.
So how about we pick up
where we left off?
No!
Hey, wait a minute!
So this is where
you've been, Kirie?
Fukuya--
Would you please
take care of me, Kirie?
I'm really not feeling
all that good right now.
Miss Kirie...
Where were we?
[KIRIE yells]
Hey, wait a minute!
Take care of me!
Miss Kirie...
No!
Don't come near me!
All I wanted was to eat
my bento with Yukinari, okay!
Nurse Girl.
Huh?
Miharu!
Oh my, hi, Kirie.
Miharu, you're all right.
Yes, and you're
looking very healthy also.
Are you okay?
Did Fukuyama do
anything weird to you?
No. Fukuyama... I mean Master
and the maid named Lilica
have both been
extremely kind to me.
Master?
I'm working
part-time for Fuku--
I mean part-time
for Master now.
This is my first day.
You're working here?!
Uh-huh!
Yukinari has to buy so much
extra food to keep me fed,
so I thought if
I could work here,
I could help with
the grocery bills.
So naïve.
Fuku-- I mean, Master, told me
that I needed to call him Master
when I'm wearing
this uniform,
because it's all
part of the job.
I don't really
understand it yet.
Where are you going, Kirie?
I want you to wear that
outfit next, all right?
You and Miharu can both be
my cute little
tag-team pair of maids.
Go be sick... in Hell!
I guess that Kirie
can be a bigger handful
than these spirits when
she gets into one of her moods.
I find her to be quite barbaric.
But that's why she's lovely.
This was a long day...
I'm sorry. I really
wanted it to be a surprise.
Oh, don't worry about it.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Miharu?
Ever since I came to Earth,
it seems like I just
cause trouble for everyone.
Today, I got Yukinari
really worried for nothing.
Hey, Miharu, are you hungry?
Huh?
Here. Let's go
home and eat okay?
Yukinari can have some, too.
Yeah.
Kirie, I am pretty hungry,
now that you mention it.
Oh, Miharu, big surprise.
I'm looking
forward to your bento.
Don't look forward
to the taste though.
They're coming.
The ones in red
are coming after me.
They're coming to catch me.