[ANNOUNCER]
And there's the whistle.
The game is over.
Japan did it.
What a miraculous win!
[ANNOUNCER 2]
That was amazing.
Truly, a historic match.
How right you are.
They've met their opponents
on the field of battle
and bested them.
But when the match is over,
they all share
the same love of soccer.
And look! The players
are exchanging uniforms.
It's quite touching.
What a wonderful
act of friendship.
Friendship, huh?
What a bunch of bologna.
Wow! They did it!
They sure did!
The blue uniformed
people won the game!
I'm so glad for them!
They really gave it their all!
Those players
are just amazing!
And the coach!
I haven't been
this excited since--
Phew! I almost missed Poyon.
Good thing I switched over!
That was unbelievable!
You could color me shocked!
Hey! What's the big idea?!
Tomo's watching TV!
Are you kidding me?!
We weren't done
watching soccer yet!
But Tomo watches
Poyon's show every single day!
So watch it tomorrow!
Ours happens
once every four years!
It must not be very popular!
Come on, it's a
damned re-run!
Shut up already!
Stop it, you
little brat!
Just give me
the clicker!
[YUKINARI] Maybe we
could find a way
to make everybody happy.
[KIRIE and TOMO]
Huh?
Nobody asked you to butt in!
[YUKINARI]
Just trying to help!
Yukinari, are you all right?
Uh-oh. I think it's broken.
Yeah, it's cause Tomoka
was acting like a little brat.
Hey! Tomo is
not a little brat!
Really?
That cartoon you were
watching is a little kid's show.
I just assumed that only
a little kid would like it.
[KIRIE laughs]
Tomo is not a little kid!
On Seiren, Tomo is super
mature and super elite.
Just to prove it, I'm gonna
show you my magic powers!
Magic?
That's right, Kirie.
Tomoka is a very distinguished
person back on Seiren.
That's why she's
allowed to practice magic.
Not like me.
I'm just a failure
who can't do anything right.
But it's probably something
totally random
and useless, right?
Like how Miharu can
cause an explosion?
Oh yeah! I'll show you
what my magic can do!
Tomo knows how to
magically transform stuff.
And to prove it,
I'm gonna turn Ebi
into something different.
Poyonyo poyo poyo poyo poyo!
Switcheroo!
[BOTH] Wow!
I told you so!
Tomo's magical
powers are top-notch!
But don't be afraid, Earthlings.
The mighty Tomo
means you no harm.
She is so cute!
Aww, she's like a little doll.
I just wanna squeeze her!
Yes, you really
are cute, aren't you?
I wonder if she can talk.
Say what?
Nya nya nya nyo.
Oh, she's just adorable!
Making those cute
little noises of hers.
You're gonna have all
the guys wrapped around
your little finger,
aren't you, cutie?
We'll have to keep her inside.
Hello. Hey, you guys...
Tomo's powers are
really great, aren't they?
Okay, everyone pay
attention to Tomo now.
[TOMO laughing]
Listen up!
What a waste of time.
Who needs friends when
they already have a soul mate?
I just know he's realized
our connection by now.
Don't worry, darling Yukinari.
Lisa Fukuyama,
the love of your life,
is only moments away.
My dearest Yukinari!
It's time to bask in
our pre-destined bliss.
Geez, Tomoka, chill out!
Ow! My head!
Lisa!
What was all
that yelling about?
Who are you supposed to be?
Hand over that thing,
or you and me are
gonna have problems.
Uh, hi there Lisa.
Miss me, Yukinari?
Lisa?
Yeah. This is
Fukuyama's younger sister.
Fukuyama's younger sister?
So you're the younger sister
of that perverted
Earthling guy I kidnapped.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I don't wanna have to hurt you,
so you should give
Ebi to me right now.
What on earth is that
little girl talking about?
Tomo is not a little girl!
Just hand over Ebi already,
okay Blondie?!
Ebi?
Yeah, that little
affection sponge behind you.
Get back here, you!
Tomoka!
Go ahead and wimper.
I'm still gonna change you
back to your ugly old self.
There's only room for one cute
little girl in this house,
and that's Tomo!
Hey! Hold on.
Problem?
You're not being
very nice to her!
You're just a stranger,
so what do you know?
It's a tricky alien beast
that acts like a pretty
little girl to sucker people in.
Leave her alone!
Ow!
Here we go...
Uh... Tomoka...
You've got some nerve, Blondie.
Prepare yourself for
the awesome wrath of Tomo!
Huh?
Come on.
I can't believe she made
this appear in your living room.
It's unbelievable all right.
That's great, but how
do we get it out of here?
She's pretty darn good...
for just an Earthling I mean.
Four. Five. Six. Seven. Eight.
Nine. Ten.
Eleven. Twelve. Thirt--
Nya! Nya!
Nya nya nya?
Hey! This isn't
a playground in here, you know?
Nya?
Maybe bringing her
here wasn't such a good idea.
Nya, nya, nya...
Put a sock in it!
Lisa...
Oh, hey Big Brother.
Do you remember that voodoo
doll I asked you to make me?
Nya?
You are so damned cute!
Look at those
thin alabaster legs,
sticking out of your shirt.
Your slender body
that would snap
under anything but
the lightest embrace.
You, who meow up at me
with tear-filled eyes,
just like a frightened
little animal.
You are perfection!
An angel made flesh!
I, Kazuharu Fukuyama,
thank the heavens above
for sending down
such a sublime creature.
Nya! Nya! Nya! Nya!
It's okay. Here let me see you.
Nya, nya...
Aww, look at you.
Such a cute
little trouble-maker.
Watching you's going
to be a full-time job.
Lisa...
You're my younger sister,
and I respect that,
but if you try to keep me away
from that stunning cherub,
I'll never forgive you.
My, my.
For somebody who spends most of
her time shut away in her room,
Miss Lisa has
a lot of guests today.
Master Kazuharu
will be so pleased.
Coming. The ones in red
are coming to get me.
She's here.
That crazy naked woman.
That pervert will find me.
You bunch of 'fraidy cats.
Nothing's gonna happen
with Tomo here to protect you!
[TOMO laughs]
This time, Blondie's going down!
Do watch your step.
Nya... Nya...
Faster! Faster!
Wait for me!
Hurry up!
Hold on, wait for me.
Nya, nya!
Hey! Stop it!
That really tickles.
Come on, cut it out Ellie.
Nya, nyo?
Sorry about that.
Right then you reminded me
of somebody I used to know.
Nyo?
Nyo...
A photo?
Yes.
It was taken when Mistress Lisa
was still very young.
And that's Ellie,
her favorite doll.
Ellie?
It's been ten years,
but it feels like yesterday.
Where could you be hiding?
Ellie?
Ellie, come out!
[EILLIE] Boo!
Ellie! Don't scare me like that.
Hurry up, and let's play!
It was all thanks
to the book I found
the first time I went
down into that laboratory.
By performing the rites
written inside of it,
I brought my doll
Ellie to life.
We did everything together:
play time, baths, bedtime.
We were inseparable.
Ellie was the one person
I felt comfortable with.
But our good times
ended too soon.
Ellie! What should
we play with today?
Ellie? Ellie?
Is something wrong?
Why aren't you moving?
Stop playing around!
It isn't funny anymore.
You're so mean!
You didn't even
say goodbye, Ellie.
So that's what happened.
Correct.
Hey, I wonder if Lisa's
reliving her memories with Ebi.
Maybe Ebi reminds her of
that doll she used to have.
It is possible.
I think maybe we should
all go try to cheer up Lisa.
Mm. You're right.
Let's go see if we can
find the two of them.
Well, I guess even
she has her good qualities.
Hey, Koyomi, we're going
to be heading out pretty soon.
Oh, I think I'll stay behind
and help clean up a bit more,
if that's all right.
Tomoka!
What got into her?
It's gonna take a lot more
than that to stop me, Lisa!
Nya, nya, nya...
Keep on dreaming, cutie.
Ellie, the only reason
I got so good at black magic
was to bring you back to life.
The spell worked
the first time I cast it,
but that's the only
time it ever worked.
I tried so many times,
that I knew the
pentagrams by heart.
But you never
woke up again, Ellie.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to wake you up.
Hey! My face is super ticklish!
Remember me, Blondie?
Tomoka, you did hear
that story back there, right?
It's true.
Lisa had her reasons
for acting like she did.
So there's nothing
to fight about, right?
It's way too late for excuses.
Tomo's here
to settle the score
with that blond
black magic bimbo.
You're acting like a chicken,
so I'll go first.
Poyonyo poyo poyo switcheroo!
Turtle!
What the--?!
What is that?
But wait! There's more!
Snake!
Switcheroo!
Crayfish!
Listen up, you monsters.
The great and mighty
Tomo commands you
to mop up the floor
with that blond witchy girl.
Snake.
Crayfish!
Turtle!
This is nuts.
You're amazing Tomoka!
And so subtle...
Cease fire, monster troops.
After all that,
there's probably
nothing left of her.
No way!
Take her down!
Hit her with
everything you got!
Turtle!
Crayfish!
Snake!
She's blocking it all.
Yeah, it's like a cartoon.
What kind of cartoon
would have fighting monsters?
I think it's about
time you learn what happens
to those who
dare to oppose me.
Crumble before
the power of the netherworld!
Nya nyo? Nya!
[FUKUYAMA giggles pervertedly]
So this is where
you've been hiding,
you sweet young thing.
Now bask in the
warmth of my love!
Watch the hair!
Ebi! Stop playing hard to get!
She's inside the pentagram!
Get out of there right now!
Hurry! If you stand there,
it'll steal your soul!
Please, not again!
I can't bear to lose
you like I lost Ellie!
Huh?
No! It's all my fault!
[LISA crying]
Nya Nya...
Nya?
Oh, Ebi.
Thank goodness you're okay.
But how? How'd you survive?
[LISA gasps]
It-It can't be.
I don't really
understand what's going on,
but are you okay my darling?
The danger has passed,
and there's
nothing to be afraid of,
so relax and let's
have ourselves some fun.
There's no time
like the present!
Go do it in Hell!
That a girl, Tomoka.
Ellie.
[ELLIE barks]
Um, Tomo knows how much you
wanted to see your doll again.
Tomo heard about before.
It was sad.
So then, you used magic
to make this Ellie for me?
Tomo admits that she
lost this time, so I guess...
I think that...
Maybe you and me could
kinda sorta be friends.
Huh?
When the match is over,
everyone becomes friends.
That's how it works here.
I saw it on TV.
You won, fair and square,
and the match is over.
So Blondie and Tomo
are friends now.
You know, the TV
isn't always right...
But...
If you really wanna
be friends with me,
I guess it would be kinda
neat to have you as one.
[ELLIE barks]
You're glad it
worked out. Me too.
Nya nyaa! Nya nya nyuu!
Nya nyu nya nyu...!
Hey, come on, that tickles!
[TOMO] I know!
You should come over to
our house and watch Poyon!
[LISA] When is it on?
Don't worry, I recorded it!