Ah?
[YUKINARI] Yeah.
Don't worry, Dad.
I'm doing just fine.
You know, Mom says you've
been working too hard lately.
Try to relax a bit, okay?
I mean, you don't
wanna burn yourself out.
Yeah. I miss you too, Dad.
Daddy, where are you?
"Eye on Mizuno."
If you love delicious
fruits and vegetables,
and who doesn't?
You don't want
to touch that dial.
This week we
focus on Mr. Yaoshichi,
a local grocer whose ripe,
luscious produce
leaves his competitors,
and their veggies,
green with envy.
You'll find him
in the shopping arcade
near the train station.
And here he is!
Thank you for
speaking to us today.
Thanks!
Do you wanna buy bananas?
Then come to
the banana man!
I got 'em all!
You know what?
This is the best cake
I've had all day.
It's the only
cake you've had.
That's what you think.
[MIHARU and YUKINARI laughing]
Hey, Miharu?
What's up with those
dots on your forehead?
I mean, is that
a birthmark or tattoo or what?
All I know is when they glow,
better run for it!
You know, I'm not sure.
What do you mean?
It's on your head,
isn't it?
Yeah, but those dots
have been up there
ever since
I was a little girl.
You know,
I guess I never really
gave it any thought, Kirie.
I don't remember Maharu
having one of those
when she visited.
Observe!
Tomo's forehead
is zit-free.
Nya!
Maybe there's something
special about those dots.
I wonder...
Special how?
I've got it!
If Miharu's
special zits disappear,
she'll start acting
like a whole other person.
No way.
Interesting.
Without dots, maybe
she'd act... like this...
Wah!
Ah!
No! Spying on me
in the bathroom!
You're such a pervert!
No! It's not like that!
I swear it!
Save your excuses, dumbass.
Stare at naked girls in Hell!
Hey, if we get rid of
that mark on her forehead,
maybe Miharu
won't flounce around
like a chuckleheaded nudist!
Huh? But why is her
beating me up a good thing?
There's no knowing
what she might do.
Think of it.
Nya.
Here! Bon appetit!
Have as much
as you want.
Hey, thanks Miharu.
It's great!
What did you...
put in my food?
Voila!
But... why,
Miharu, why?
I don't know.
It just seemed
like a good idea.
What kind of
reason is that?
Farewell, Yukinari.
Guess you won't
be having seconds.
Once we get rid of
those zits on her forehead,
no more Little Miss
Goody-Goody Two Shoes.
No! I would never
poison Yukinari!
Are you two mad
at me or something?
Maybe nothing will happen.
But there's only one
way to know for sure.
Huh? Um...
What are you doing?
No! Stop touching me there!
What's going on?
So, how do
you feel, Miharu?
Like kicking ass
and taking names?
Are you evil yet, or what?
I don't have all day.
The two of you
aren't very nice.
It's okay, Miharu.
Let's get you
cleaned up, all right?
There's just
no pleasing some people.
That was dumb.
And people wonder
why girls give me a rash.
The mark on
her forehead?
That's right, Koyo!
But you don't
have one either!
No, I don't have it,
but my mother
back on Seiren
has one on her head, too.
Wow, your mom's
pretty cool.
Hey, in that case,
do you know
anything about them?
Uh, not really.
I mean...
Now let's see what
his customers have to say!
Ma'am, do you come to
Yaoshichi's shop very often?
[SHOPPER] Oh, yes.
His produce has always
been very fresh. Ahh!
Especially the bananas!
Our bananas are the best!
Ah! That's him!
Huh?
Koyomi?
What's up with Koyo?
That man.
He looked like...
...my father.
Hey Mommy?
Hmm?
Where did Daddy go?
To a faraway place.
A faraway place?
Father went
back to his home.
Uh?
He went up there.
Back to his
home on Earth.
Do you understand?
But... he'll
come back, right?
When do I get
to see my daddy?
Koyomi?
Huh?
Tell me what you see.
There's something
on your head.
That's right,
without this mark,
I never would have met
your father and married him.
But what
does it do, Mommy?
Well, whoever bears
this mark on her forehead
has somebody waiting for
her in a place far, far away.
This mark is
the key, Koyomi.
It opens a door
to that faraway place,
so they can be together.
It's called the star mark.
Star mark?
But... my star mark
won't shine anymore.
The door will
never open again.
I'll never see him again.
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry, Koyomi.
Mommy!
Well, how's she
doing in there?
Dunno. She still
looks pretty depressed.
Hey, come on guys.
You shouldn't
spy on people.
It's not nice.
Shh, she's gonna hear you.
Poor Koyomi.
What's the matter?
How come she got
so upset, anyway?
Yeah. Something must
have happened to her.
But what?
All right.
Dammit, she's coming out!
Quick, everybody
let's hide in my room.
Right!
What? Hmm? Huh?
We made it.
Hold on, where's Tomoka?
Oh, why are you just
standing out here, Tomoka?
I-I'm field testing
my latest invention.
Yeah, that's it.
I call it
the Ebi-Clean 2,000.
Nyuh.
It's a mop, it's a pet,
it's a skateboard.
We can mass produce them
and get filthy rich, Koyo.
Nyo.
So, feel like getting
in on the ground floor?
Uh, no thanks.
Actually,
I have to go down
to the shopping
arcade for a while.
Husband hunting for Maharu?
Good idea, Koyo.
I'll come too.
Um, I think
I'll just go alone.
See ya later, Tomoka.
Oh.
I'm sorry about earlier.
Please forgive me.
Hmm.
Well, all right then.
But I'm only gonna
let it slide this one time.
Nya!
Here, Ebi, help me
eat all this ice cream.
Nya!
Why would Koyomi leave
her behind like that?
Yeah.
I don't know.
Something must
really be bothering her.
Excuse me,
I'm looking for this man.
Sorry, you haven't seen
the man in this photo, have you?
No, I don't know him.
Um, thank you very much.
Uh, hello?
Huh? Yeah?
Uh, d-d-do you know
the man in this photo?
Doesn't ring a bell.
So you're lookin'
for a man, huh?
Uh!
How 'bout we have
some fun, hot stuff?
Sorry I-I have to go!
I don't believe it.
Koyomi was talking
to some random guy.
Yeah. I guess that means
she's not scared
of men anymore.
Um, she did run
away screaming.
Well, shy little Koyomi
is talking to strange men
instead of worrying
that they're going to do
kinky things to her.
Well, she must be stuck
between a rock
and my hard place.
Fu-Fukuyama?
Nya!
It's Big Brother Kazuharu.
Here, Tomoka.
Nobody likes a dirty girl.
Thank you very much.
What are you doing here?
I don't even
want to know, do I?
Calm down, Kirie.
We can help you figure out
what's wrong with Koyomi.
We're smart!
Oh yes, I'm really
worried about her, Lisa.
Me too.
If there's anything
we can do for her,
we have to give it a try.
Oh, my dear Yukinari!
You're so sweet.
I would love to help
you out with this.
Hey Lisa, you've got
something brown on your nose.
Our poor little Koyomi!
I had no idea!
It's the saddest
thing ever!
Oh, so that's it.
Koyomi was out
looking for her father.
[HAYATE] Yes.
However, none of
my sources were able
to provide me
with a name.
[KOSAME] Ooh, Miss Kirie!
Kirie... Oh Miss Kirie.
Ooh, Miss Kirie.
Don't worry, Miss.
I'll certainly do
my best to keep Kosame
from ravishing you today.
Gee thanks.
Oh yeah, Koyomi's
father was an Earthling.
I'd forgotten.
Huh? Are you
sure about that?
Uh-huh! She told me the same
evening she arrived here.
And you never
thought to share
that tidbit of
information until right now?
Well, I didn't
know until right now
that her father was
living here on Earth.
I just kind of assumed
he was back on Seiren.
That's neat.
Koyomi's parents
are just like
Yukinari and me,
aren't they?
Because I was
born on Seiren
and Yukinari
was born on Earth.
Oh, and Koyomi's mom
has something on
her forehead, too.
Just like me.
You both have the birthmark,
but what does it mean?
Let's get to work already!
Uh, Fukuyama?
Dry your tears, Tomoka.
This is no time
for maudlin sentiment.
We have to find
Koyomi's father.
With my brains and your...
something, we're unstoppable!
Nya!
Go!
Yeah, we'll check in
with the hospitals later.
But what now?
Since Koyomi was looking
for her father around here,
she must have
had some reason
to think this was
a good spot to do it.
Right! So we should
look around here for him.
I want Koyomi and her
father to be together.
Yeah, but she never
did tell any of us
about this
whole dad thing.
Maybe she kept it to
herself for a good reason.
Oh.
Maybe, but now that I know,
I can't just ignore it.
Me neither.
We gotta help
her out somehow.
Uh. Right!
Okay, if you won't
take no for an answer.
Has anybody seen
the man in this picture?
Excuse me, have
you seen this man?
Thank you very
much for your time.
Uh, sir, have
you ever seen this--
Sorry.
I'm fine. I can't give up.
Hello?
Have you... have
you seen this man?
He's my... he's my father.
I can't. I can't
do anything right.
I'm useless.
I can't even
find my own father.
I thought I could
find a husband for Maharu,
but I can't find anybody.
You don't have to
do it alone, Koyomi.
Huh? What are
you all doing here?
Come on, it's okay.
If there's any way
we can help out,
Koyomi, just let us know.
Yeah, you should have
said something before.
We could have
been helping you
look for him all
this time, silly.
Helping me look?
Here. You see?
You have great
parents, Koyomi.
You all seem so happy.
Um, sorry.
I don't mean to be nosey
about something personal
like your father
being missing, Koyomi,
but when I see
you working so hard,
I feel like
the least I can do
is try to
help you find him.
Miharu...
Oh please,
won't you let us all
help you find your father?
We wanna help.
Okay!
Sorry to bother you guys,
but... has anyone seen
the man in this photo?
We really have to find him.
My friend's
father is missing.
Does anybody recognize
the man in this photograph?
Asking around like that
is just a big waste of time.
I'll channel Mabanya's powers
and find him right away.
Lisa, what are you doing?!
Uh, excuse me.
Do you know
anything about this man?
Have any of you seen
the man in this photograph?
Anybody?
Excuse me,
do you know this man?
Have any of you
seen him before?
Everybody, we're
looking for Koyomi's dad.
Excuse me, ma'am,
have you seen
the man in this picture?
If you could
just take a look,
it'd be greatly appreciated.
He's about yea tall.
They're right.
I shouldn't just give up.
Excuse me, have
you seen this man?
What gives?
We didn't come up
with a single lead.
Yeah, and we were
out here all afternoon.
But we tried.
Hey, but don't
let it get you down,
we'll find him
next time for sure.
Yeah!
At least we know
he's somewhere
in this town, right?
Right! We'll look
around some more tomorrow.
So don't be sad,
okay Koyomi?
I'm all right.
Huh?
Really. I'm not
so upset anymore.
I really wish I could have
found my father on Earth,
but I did find a bunch
of wonderful friends
who care about me.
That's more
than enough for me.
Miharu's star mark helped
bring all of us together.
This isn't over!
That's right!
Big Brother!
And Tomoka's with him!
So, you're finally
done fooling around, huh?
Fooling around?
You wound me!
Yeah, Kirie.
Big Brother Kazuharu
and me spent all day
trying to help
Koyomi find her dad.
What? You were
looking, too?
Yes! Incompetent
though I may be,
I'll toil to my
last breath to reunite
the fair Koyomi
with her father.
Fukyuyama...
Big Brother Kazuharu,
it's showtime!
Oh, I see.
Then witness if you will...
...the power of my genius!
Huh? That's me.
Good evening,
we're interrupting
our regular programming
to bring you a special
exposé entitled
"Where is Koyomi's Father?"
We'll begin by interviewing
Kazuharu Fukuyama
and Tomoka Lana Jude,
No way.
Way.
who are kind enough to bring
this tale of woe
to our attention.
Hello.
Greetings, TV Land.
Now, what can
you share with us
about this
sad situation?
I-I'm sorry,
I promised myself
I wouldn't cry,
but... imagine
a father and daughter
living worlds apart!
She came to Earth
forsaking all she knew
to try and find him!
Hey Koyo's dad,
if you're watching this,
come down to the station.
Nya!
What do you think?
We took our idea to
the Mizuno Cable TV station
and spent the rest of
the afternoon taping it.
Finding Koyo's dad after
this is gonna be a cinch!
Nya nya!
That wasn't so bad.
And one more thing.
This is Koyomi!
Her measurements
are 80, 50, and 78.
Her breasts are a
little on the small side,
but she really makes
the most of what she's got.
She's got a huge heart
under those little boobs.
But her hips are
a different story.
Yes, curvy and splendid.
And so smooth and supple.
They're the hips
of a seductress.
Yeah, Koyo's hips make up
for her little boobs.
Look! Koyomi's father!
Feast your eyes on her.
The gorgeous
fruit of your loins.
She's hot.
Please come forward.
Uh-huh.
Your smokin' hot
daughter misses you.
Who's your daddy?
There's a big cash
reward if you come forward!
Tomoka's right,
I'm filthy rich.
Money hand over fist.
I'll even reward you to find
Koyomi's father for us!
If you have any information,
call our 24-hour hotline
at the Mizuno Cable station.
Just look at her!
Operators are
standing by. Call now!
Fukuyama!
What the hell is this?
Genius, isn't it?
Wouldn't any
absent father wonder
how his daughter
has grown up?
What man wouldn't
step forward to claim
parentage of
such a beauty?
Sometimes I wonder
if mom did drugs.
Look guys, it's them!
You're right.
I wanna hear more
about that reward.
Huh
Hey, I know her father.
Hell, I am her father.
Check it out. Hey!
Wow! Koyo has a
whole bunch of dads!
Well, this isn't
what I had intended,
but it sure is hilarious.
It always ends up
like this, doesn't it?
I know what you mean.
Look at Koyomi,
she seems so happy.
Happy? She's beside herself.
[TEACHER] It's time to
put our plan into motion.
[YUKINA] Agreed.
[YUKINA] Not even the star
mark can save you now.
Kosame, why are you
hugging that empty soda can?
Miss Kirie gave this to me.
It's a present.
A gift from my love!
Um, it's trash, Kosame.
Girls Bravo
Season Two, next episode,
"Present is Bravo!"
She shouldn't have...
Well, you're
right about that.