[MIHARU]
You're lucky, Koyomi,
your skin is
really smooth.
[KOYOMI]
Um, I guess so.
I envy you Miharu.
You eat what you
want and stay skinny.
And you're a lot curvier,
you know... on top.
But why? I think that
you're beautiful, Koyomi!
--Look at you!
--Hey! Stop it, Miharu!
That tickles.
[MIHARU and KOYOMI laughing]
[MIHARU sneezes]
[bathtub explodes]
[KOYOMI]
Ah! The bathtub!
[MIHARU] Oh, no.
What are we going to do?
[TOMO] Wake up already!
It's Sunday, Tomoka.
Good night.
Come on! It's practically
six in the morning!
Get up!
Okay, okay, I'll get up.
What do you want?
Miharu and Koyo
went out somewhere
and didn't even
invite me along.
Huh?
Well good morning, Kirie.
Morning you two.
So, did anyone
see you sneak out?
I guess not.
[TOMO] I don't believe it!
Kirie gets to go
with them, and I don't?
How come nobody
invited Tomo? Huh?
[YUKINARI yawns]
Maybe some store's
having an early bird sale.
Maybe Tomo wanted
to go shopping, too!
It's not nice to leave me
behind like some little kid!
They're on the move!
Come on, hurry up
and get dressed
so we can follow them.
[YUKINARI sighs]
You're kidding, right?
[YUKINARI] We've been
riding for a long time.
I wonder where they're heading.
[TOMO] Hey! Get a load of that!
An amusement park.
But why wouldn't
they take you along?
[TOMO growls]
It's not fair! It's not fair!
I can't believe
they'd go to a theme park
and leave me at home!
Hold on, they're not
getting off of the train.
[TOMO] Hmm. So where are
they sneaking off to, huh?
Huh?
Who are all these guys?
I mean, I feel like we just took
the train to Nerdville.
Maybe there's
some kind of big event
happening around here today.
Big event, huh?
Something boring
or something fun?
Hey! Over there!
Tokyo Game Carnival?
What's that?
It's where they announce
the new video games every year.
Well, Tomo is not amused.
I'm way better at video
games than the three of them!
We're going in there!
Nya nya!
Hey, wait up, Tomoka!
That line to get inside was
a lot longer than I thought.
Nya!
No way! That looks like Poyon!
Hey, Tomoka! That's not...
I'm your biggest
fan in the world!
[COSPLAYER] Hi! I'm Poyon.
Wh-Wh-Wh-What?
Why didn't
anyone tell me Poyon
was some fat guy in drag
who smelled like wet feet?
Don't freak out now, Tomoka.
He's just cosplaying.
[TOMO growling]
Nya?
I don't care
what you call it!
This loser has no right
to be dressing up like Poyon!
But my costume's so accurate.
This isn't over, freak.
If you don't want to
see me beating this weirdo
within an inch of his life,
you better look away now!
Hey, calm down, Tomoka!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you all right, miss?
That was weird.
That girl...
[GUARD] Hey you!
This is bad. Tomoka!
I'm not scared of you!
I'll take you all on at once!
[YUKINARI and TOMO panting]
Are you happy now?
I'll show 'em!
I'll vaporize
them with the E-Beam,
and that fake Poyon too!
No way. Please, just
try to behave, okay?
Yukinari, this way!
Huh? Miharu?
I've been looking
all over for you.
[YUKINA] That's him?
Yes.
Explain yourselves!
You better have a good excuse,
or you'll be hearing
from my lawyer!
Tomoka, you don't
have a lawyer.
So guys, why are you here?
You see,
what happened was...
I sort of broke
the bathtub last night,
so I wanted to make
some money to repair it.
I told Kirie what happened,
and so she set us up
with this part-time job.
Yeah, our official
title is "Eye-candy."
So that's...
...why you're
dressed like that?
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
You look good.
But...
it doesn't matter now.
But why not?
We're in trouble, Yukinari.
One more girl was supposed
to show up this morning,
but she flaked out
at the last minute.
And it's too late now to try
and find a replacement for her.
Oh what do I do?
I don't know.
Me neither.
I know it's totally unfair
to spring this on you
at the last minute, but...
Um, you wanna
fill in for her?
Say what?
Yeah, she was gonna be
our emcee, and you can do that.
It'll be easy.
So, whattya say?
Kirie, I get dizzy
just standing up
to give a book report!
You can do it, Yukinari!
Everything is written down.
All you need to do is
read straight from the script.
It's the easiest
money you'll ever make!
Talking in front of people
makes me wanna throw up.
Wait, what did you say?
Huh?
Please, just say it
for me one more time.
Talking in front of people
makes me wanna barf?
Perfect.
What?
Your voice is just perfect!
Perfect? Really?
Forgive me, Yukinari...
Oh how stupid I've been
not to realize it...
I can't believe
I've never noticed until now
what a beautiful
voice you have.
Right, Miharu?
Yes! Yukinari's voice
is really pretty!
It's so soothing yet clear,
the sort of voice
that rejuvenates
anyone lucky
enough to hear it.
Your vocal chords are a blessing
from the heavens above!
That's right!
Yeah? You think so?
But Kirie...
don't we need a girl?
The best voice in the world!
It's marvelous!
Excellent! Fantastic!
Wow, it's really that good?
This is your destiny!
Only your voice
can soothe the masses.
Now, let's go out there
and make this world
of ours a better place!
Right, Miharu?
Yeah! Can Yukinari
and I do it together?
Sure! Hey, I wanna do
it with Yukinari, too!
I'll do my best.
I can only do it for
a little while though.
Great! We get to
do it with Yukinari!
That's awesome!
Not awesome.
[KIRIE giggles]
Oh Yukinari, you're so cute!
Yukinari you're amazing!
You'll be the
prettiest girl out there!
You never
mentioned this part!
Find yourself a new emcee!
Uh, hold on.
Think of the people
who need your voice.
Please, do it
for all of humanity.
Can't I help humanity
and wear pants?
♪ sad music playing ♪
I told my boss
everything was taken care of.
If we go out there
without an emcee...
Kirie...
The costume's good.
Just use a girly voice,
and nobody'll be the wiser.
Please Yukinari, save me.
Save all of us.
But Kirie...
The audience
and voice actors
are going to be
so disappointed.
They were really
looking forward to it.
Right Miharu... Tomoka?
Uh-huh, they're
all waiting for you.
That's right.
Uh, well I guess so.
[sad music ends]
Right on! Let's go
out there and do it!
O...kay.
By the way, from now on,
you only answer
to the name of Yukina.
What?
That's a pretty name.
I like it!
'Cause if they figure out
that you're really a boy,
they'd fire us
all on the spot.
Do your best, Miss Yu-ki-na!
[KOYOMI giggles]
Just shoot me.
[YUKINARI] Uh, hello there.
Um, thank you all for coming.
I'm going to be
the emcee today.
My name is Yukina.
Shit! All right then.
It's great to see so
many enthusiastic guys
in the audience this morning.
Okay. I guess it's
time to bring out
our special
voice actor guests,
so make some noise, guys!
[otaku clapping and cheering]
Hello everybody.
Hello!
We love you!
All right, hey everyone!
Hello Michelle!
So, are you all
having a good time?
Oh yeah!
Don't you all have
somewhere better to be?
Seriously guys,
what's up with that?
Come on Lulu,
cut the otaku a break.
Yeah, so... we're very
glad to have you here today.
Our pleasure!
Yukina's not doing
half bad. You go girl!
Hmm. Look at
all this eye candy.
Decisions, decisions.
So, who do I fondle first?
Will it be Miharu or Koyomi?
Or I could just give
yours a good squeeze!
Hey!
So, ladies, uh,
time for questions!
What did you
have for breakfast?
What did I have
for breakfast? Um...
Fukuyama, what the
hell are you doing here?
What a silly question.
I go wherever
the beautiful women are.
And also,
it just so happens
my family owns
this game company.
What? Is that the reason
I got this job so easily?
I may have
pulled a few strings.
But tell me, Kirie,
who's the girl acting as emcee?
Heh?
I don't think I know her.
She doesn't go to
Mizuno High School, does she?
Uh, yeah, she does.
See that girl is really--
She's a fox.
Huh?
Measurements:
83-62-82, no 83.
She's... uh...
not your type.
Observe Kirie,
the hills and valleys of
her burgeoning womanhood.
Her limbs are
tapered and graceful,
and she speaks with
the voice of a nightingale.
Graceful yeah.
And that look in her eyes
equal parts naïveté and fear,
how it sets my loins ablaze!
Hey, Fukuyama,
do you wanna meet her?
She's a friend of mine.
Huh? Are you serious?
Sure I am! I think you two
would make a cute couple.
We would, wouldn't we?
One hand washes the other.
You know,
I think that you girls
might just deserve a raise.
Pretty tasty.
That's all the time we have,
but thanks so much
for joining us!
All right, since you guys
are such an awesome crowd,
we're gonna hold a game
competition between Yukina here
and one lucky audience member.
What?
If you can beat
Yukina in our tournament,
you get to take
her home with you!
Huh?
I'm not saying she's easy,
but this girl sure knows
her way around a joystick!
You know what
I'm saying guys?
Gah!
Are you crazy?
You're pimping me
out to otaku?
So, is anybody
here brave enough
to challenge our
video game vixen?
Over here!
I'll give it a shot!
Let the games begin!
Fukuyama!
Okay, the retarded-looking
blonde guy down in the front.
Kirie, what are you doing?
Wait until she gets a load
of my first person shooter!
What the hell's
going on, Kirie?
Sorry Yukinari.
I didn't know
until a minute ago,
but the video
game company...
...well, Fukuyama's
family owns it.
What?
He said he'd fire us
if I didn't pick him.
[sad music playing]
He thinks you're really cute.
And if he...
if he finds out
that you're really
not a girl after all...
But-But I'm not!
Please, Yukinari!
Don't go! I need you.
Miharu and Koyomi... we all do.
Yeah? You're our only hope.
Mm.
Will you?
I know you can
beat him, Yukinari!
I just know it!
Mm. Okay I'll do it.
But only one game.
Thank you, Yukinari!
[sad music ends]
All right!
I think it's time we get this
3 game tournament started!
I said just one!
I-I wonder what all those men
by the stage
are yelling about...
I think they're
about to play a game!
Do your best!
Good luck Yukinari--
I mean Yukina!
Hey Big Brother Kazuharu!
Don't lose, okay?
I know you're all
anxious to find out
whether or not Yukina will
be sleeping alone tonight!
It's time to
reveal our first game!
Exciting bike!
It's a racing simulator.
Whoever can do
3 laps around the course
in the shortest
time wins the round!
[FUKUYAMA laughs]
[YUKINARI gasps]
Do your best Yukinari!
Yeah, thanks.
[motorcycle turns on]
motorcycle revs]
[YUKINARI gasps]
Hold on, what do you think
you're doing back there?
This is a 2-person
bike, my dear.
All of our games
are specially designed
to put couples in
the mood for love.
[YUKINARI yelps]
Ready! Begin!
[otaku cheering]
Wow, it looks so real!
Oh, no! I'm falling off.
I'd better hold on tighter.
[YUKINARI gasps]
What's going on?
[YUKINARI yelps]
[FUKUYAMA] Hot damn!
Feast your eyes on
that exquisite panty-line!
[otaku babbling]
No! Let go!
I'm not that kind of girl!
Got your boobs!
Whoopsie-daisy!
Yukina!
Don't tell me you're...
Game over, man, game over.
You're busted!
Everyone!
Yukina's
definiely an 'A' cup!
She said I just had
to read the script.
Oh, you are
just so scrumptious.
[KIRIE] Yukina's time was
3 minutes and 10 seconds.
Fukuyama's time was
2 minutes and 55 seconds.
All right!
Fukuyama is the winner!
Oh poor Yukina,
can she win the next 2 rounds?
Or will Fukuyama
win the tournament
and finish the day on top?
On top of her that is!
Wah. This sucks.
Our second game?
The all new Prance
Prance Convolution.
There's nothing to it,
all you have to do
is keep touching
whatever color paddles
come up on the screen.
If it's so easy, why do I
have a bad feeling about this?
And what is that hole for?
[FUKUYAMA giggles]
What's that? You have
a hole that needs filling?
All set!
[KIRIE]
Ready! Begin!
[YUKINARI gasps]
[FUKUYAMA giggles]
Best damn seat in the house.
Okay.
[FUKUYAMA giggles]
Oh, you're really
aggressive Yukina!
Wait until
we're home, okay?
Ahh!
Oh no, I guess I lost.
But don't
think you'll beat me
that easily
in the last game.
[FUKUYAMA laughs]
[YUKINARI] You lost on purpose!
And now, last but not least,
Sleep Fighters Omega!
Sure, it may look like just
another generic fighting title,
but it uses cutting edge
technology to scan the players
and import them as
their game characters.
Good luck Yukina!
I know you can beat him again!
This game is gonna rock!
Yukina's fate depends on
the outcome of this final round!
Ready! Begin!
[KIRIE] Oops, looks like
Yukina mistimed her kick!
--[FUKUYAMA] Oogie oogie boogie!
--[YUKINARI] Dammit!
Take your gloves off in Hell!
[KIRIE] Yukina's talking
a lot of trash,
but can she finish him off?
Hey, how come you're
not fighting back, huh?
I just can't
bear to hurt you.
Even if it is only your
character in some video game.
Huh? What do you mean?
So I'm going to finish you
off... quick and painless.
Huh?
Witness the power of
my Hundred-handed Strip Attack!
[YUKINARI screams]
Oh man! Fukuyama's
technique is dynamite!
Game over!
Fukuyama wins the tournament!
[otaku cheering]
Hmm. I owe you.
My pleasure.
Right on,
Big Brother Kazuharu!
Amazing! But I think
Yukina did a very good job also.
That was some
great playing, Fukuyama!
Come on up and claim your prize.
Wait, I'm a--
I know, but it only
hurts the first time.
Get off!
Hmm? There's something...
...in my hand
that shouldn't be.
That's a...
That's right, it's
exactly what you thought.
And now you can
get the tub fixed up!
Lucky me.
I hope you're happy.
Fukuyama got to third base.
It was really fun!
There were so many
different games!
Nya! Nya!
Uh-huh! And Yukina
was really cute.
Yeah, a little too cute.
I love a good
game of Mah-Jong.
I've never seen
tiles like these.
Well I have made
a few changes to it.
A few changes, huh?
I don't know...
I think you'll
like it, Puny-nari.
If the girls lose, they have
to take their clothes off.
Well, what do you say?
Girls Bravo Season Two,
next episode,
"Bravo at Mah-Jong!"
Let's play!
Wow! Fukuyama,
you have really good tiles!