Correct. The target
is still here on Earth,
therefore the gate's
condition remains unstable.
Left unattended,
there's a strong likelihood
that the gate will
spontaneously open again.
Yes. Very well.
I'll continue to
watch the target.
[MAHARU] Aww. Koyomi and Tomoka
have been gone so
long and still nothing.
When are they gonna show up
with my hot
new husband to be?
The big 3-0 is
right around the corner.
Is this my fate?
Alone and unloved
for the rest of my life?
My sister is
having all sorts of fun
with that boy on Earth,
and I just sit here at home,
inching towards
my expiration date.
I'll die a lonely old maid.
It's Koyomi and Tomoka's fault!
I bet they're
too busy having fun
on Earth to even
think about men!
I am royally pissed!
I'll be in the damned tub!
Miharu! Time to go!
Coming!
Hey, I didn't mean
to rush you, Miharu.
We've got plenty of time.
Yeah, but... this is
my first school festival.
Wait a minute,
they don't have any
school festivals on Seiren?
Un-unh. We only
have town festivals.
I used to go
with my big sister.
She'd go too?
Uh-huh!
Big Sister Maharu loves
going out and having fun.
She never missed
a single festival.
Okay, let's go.
I wonder how
Maharu's doing.
Miharu!
I'm coming, Yukinari!
The coast is clear.
Tomoka, do we
really have to go?
We're going, okay?
You're such a 'fraidy cat!
But that school
is such a scary place.
There are
so many boys there...
and male teachers...
and Fukuyama.
I know he's
kind of perverted,
but Big Brother
Kazuharu is pretty nice.
You shouldn't say
bad things about him.
But we still have to find
a husband for Maharu.
If we don't
bring her one soon,
she's gonna be
really mad at us!
Why do today what you
can put off 'til tomorrow?
Um, but...
The two of us are going
to that school festival,
and that's final!
If you really
don't wanna go,
what's up with
the school uniform, huh Koyo?
Uh... n-nothing
else was clean...?
A likely story!
Nya! Nya nya nya nya!
Nya nya nya nya...
What's the matter, Ebi?
I have no idea
what you're saying.
Okay Koyo, let's
head down to school.
Nyo.
I know they're doing it
as a personal favor,
but maybe I shouldn't
have asked them
to do it in
the first place.
Miharu... I wonder if
she's doing well over there.
Hm. I'm sure she is.
Oh, you know, if I could
get to Earth somehow,
I could wrap up
the husband-hunt in a snap.
Huh?
Nya Nya?
[explosion]
Yahhh!
[MAHARU coughing]
W-What the hell
just happened?
Huh?
Nya nya?
No way.
[MAHARU panting]
Good morning.
Aren't these just
the smoothest threads
you've ever seen?
[MAHARU] It can't be.
Did I really
end up... on Earth?
[MAHARU laughing]
Okay! Let's go get me a man!
Welcome back, Master.
We're so glad you're home.
Okay then.
Yes, Master.
Table for one, coming up.
Hey you in the apron,
act more dignified.
Okay!
Keep working!
And don't forget to smile.
Listen up ladies,
even though it's only
for a few minutes,
every person here is
your actual master right now.
Make sure that
you treat them
with the respect
they deserve.
Right!
[MACHIDA] She's so good.
Check her out, guys.
Thanks to Lilica
cracking the whip,
our class' maid café
is doing big business.
I guess.
Although I still
think they should've
voted to screen
my movie instead.
But things could be worse.
[FUKUYAMA laughing]
Guys being lazy,
that's a shock.
Uh, hi Kirie.
We're here to
make sure you girls
are working hard enough.
Go scrub a bathroom,
clean-freak.
So, anyway,
wanna be a pal
and go shopping for me?
Go shopping?
Somebody ate all
the dessert bananas.
Let me guess...
All right, we'll go
buy some more then.
Hey, where'd...
where'd they...
Geez, the minute there's
a little work to be done,
those two just
vanish into thin air.
Well, the shopping
arcade isn't very far.
I'll go by myself.
Tomoka...
I really don't
wanna go in there.
Fine, go home then,
but I'm staying here!
Don't leave me!
Please don't leave me
here all by myself, Tomoka.
Get a grip!
Are you coming or not?
Make up your mind already!
Big 'fraidy cat.
Here.
But why?
Everything's so fuzzy.
Guys won't freak you out
if you can't even see 'em
in the first place, right?
Wow! They've got
all sorts of booths.
Yes, it looks
like a lot of fun.
I mean, I think it does.
Ooh, this one!
Here we are!
Hey guys.
Enjoying the festival?
Koyo! Look, it's
the blond witchy girl.
Wanna look in
your crystal ball
and read our
fortunes for us?
Hmm. Both of your
fortunes are looking...
...kind of crappy.
Kind of crappy?!
Worst fortune teller ever!
Whatever, come
on Koyo, let's go.
Tomoka! Wait up,
I can't see, remember?
They really
shouldn't have run off
in the middle
of it like that.
I was gonna give 'em
the best two out of three.
But it's true.
[WOMAN laughing]
[MAN gasping]
Boobies!
[MOM] Huh!
[MAHARU] Huh?
[MOM] Where did you
learn that word, young lady?
Get over here!
Something's up.
And every time I talk
to a guy, they run off.
Maybe I'm just more woman
than Earth men can handle.
Excuse me!
Eh?
M-M-M-M-Maharu!
Ah! It's you again!
Miss me much?
But-But-But why are
you on Earth, Maharu?
[YUKINARI yells]
Oh! I'm so glad
I get to see you again!
[YUKINARI]
Must purchase bananas.
[MAHARU] I'm sure
you can do that later.
Hey, are you all
by yourself today?
Want some company?
How's Miharu been?
Is she doing all right?
I mean, I don't have
any reason to worry,
but that's just what
sisters do, you know?
Hey! Come on, you
can't just faint on me!
I am talking to you!
Hey, thanks again for
buying me this great outfit.
But... they gave me
that money to buy bananas.
So, this is
Miharu's high school.
It seems pretty cheerful.
It doesn't
always look like this.
There's a festival today.
Huh? Nice timing!
Man, do I love me
a good festival!
Huh? Isn't that...
Cotton candy and
octopus balls are delicious!
I could eat this
stuff every day!
Yes, but...
we haven't found
a husband for Maharu yet.
If she could
see us right now...
Koyo, don't be
a stick in the mud.
Stick in the mud?
Yeah, just chill out
about that promise
we made to
Maharu already.
You think I
should... chill out?
Think about it!
Maharu can't come to
Earth without permission
from the Space Management
Bureau back on Seiren, right?
And they're not gonna
let her come over here!
They know
better than to let
that man-crazy
goofball run amuck!
There's nothing wrong
with having a little fun.
Who's gonna know?
I guess you're right.
See, aren't
you glad you came?
Uh-huh! I'm gonna forget
all about Maharu today
and have some
fun for a change!
That crotchety old maid.
Really? So this Maharu person's
a crotchety
old maid, is she?
Oh yeah, we wouldn't
be here except for Maharu.
She asked us for
a really big favor,
and so we had
to come to Earth.
It's all her fault
we're on this planet.
Maybe if she
weren't so mean,
she'd actually find a man
who could put up with her!
Wow, so...
tell me something...
Uh-huh?
What's this
bitch look like?
Ahh!
I'm glad we had this moment.
Now I know what
you think of me.
Run for it, Koyo!
Hmph. Well, well,
the plot thickens.
Okay, I'll see
you later then.
Come on!
Let's catch those brats!
That's what we get for having
fun all the time, Tomoka.
Maharu's spirit
came here to punish us.
That wasn't
Maharu's spirit, you dummy,
that was
the real life Maharu!
But what is she
doing on Earth?
How would Tomo know?
I'm just a little kid!
I got 'em!
Ah!
Koyo!
Did you really
think you could get away?
You just trashed
our booth, lady.
That was totally not cool!
How'm I supposed
to sell any of my--
Has anyone told you
you're cute when you're mad?
Huh? W-What
are you doing?
Mm. I just wanna see
what's underneath that apron!
Help me!
Somebody! Anybody!
Mommy!
Let's get outta here!
I swear by
the sword of my father,
I'll face any
foe to protect you,
no matter how vicious,
how monstrous,
how dangerous he may be.
Ahh!
Hey, hero, go fight
that red-head for me, okay?
All right! This one
looks pretty cute, too.
You know, I love
a man with a big sword.
Not to burst your bubble,
but that chick sitting
behind him is his girlfriend.
What? What did you say?
How could you string
a 30-year-old old
woman along like that?
So cruel. It's so cruel.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Well, I did tell them their
futures looked pretty crappy.
Thanks for taking
one for the team, hero!
What team?
Hell hath no fury
like a woman scorned.
How dare Kirie kick me
out of the classroom?
How impudent!
She kicked me out,
and I'm a superhero!
Huh? What's with
all the yelling?
Oh no, maybe that monster
is attacking the school again!
Big Brother Kazuharu,
the woman
coming down the hall
wants to spend some naughty
quality-time with you...
...or something.
Yeah! Oh, can it be?
Maharu you
really came all the way
from Seiren to see me again?
Cuddle me to
your endless breasts
and call me your cupcake!
Go to Hell,
you damn pervert.
No space Amazon is gonna
threaten my classmates!
Wait, almost ready.
Out of my way!
[HALL MONITOR]
Take it outside!
No roughhousing
in the halls!
I don't understand,
how did Maharu come to Earth?
Don't look at me?
Maybe she did it
without asking the bureau.
Or she found
some other way.
Some other way?
Uh! Miharu.
I wonder if she...
That was...
an Aqua Lamp.
Huh? Koyo, no!
She'll see you!
There you are.
I expected
something like this,
but not nearly so soon.
Oh well, once
we've sealed the gate,
it won't happen again.
Cha-ching!
Our maid café
was a big hit.
Maybe we should do
one of these every year.
Um, Miharu?
I'm worried about Yukinari.
He went banana shopping
and never came back.
What if something
happened to him?
Don't worry, Miharu,
he's not as
helpless as he looks.
If you're concerned
about his well-being,
feel free to go
and look for him.
Really, it's okay?
Of course.
Any maid worth her salt
should be worried
about her master's safety.
Yes. Thank you.
Maharu?
Ah! Yukinari!
What's going on?
Hey! Where are you...
Aww, jeez.
The roof!
No duh, Koyo!
Tomoka?
Come on! We can
hide under this thing.
Okay.
Tomoka?
Yeah?
What's gonna happen...
when Maharu catches us?
First she'll
beat us to a pulp,
and then she'll
toss us off the roof.
Tomo sure didn't
plan on dying young.
What do we do?
I'm not ready to die!
Tomo is really sorry.
Let me live and
I promise I'll find you
the best damn
guy on the planet.
Me too!
If you forgive us,
I promise
I won't eat or sleep
or anything until
we find him for you,
so please don't kill us.
Maharu, no!
We're not dead?
I finally caught you guys.
Well, today
was a lot of fun.
And if one day on
Earth was this great,
I can't blame you two
for wanting to
have fun all the time.
But don't spend all
your time playing, okay?
Do an old maid a favor
and find her a man.
I am almost 30, you know!
--Right.
--On it!
Here Miharu.
Sorry, but I kind of
borrowed your boyfriend today.
Go easy on him for a while.
I love Earth.
Big Sister Maharu,
can't you stay
a little while longer?
The gate's so unstable.
I really should
be leaving now.
Don't worry about it.
If the gate closes,
I can use my Aqua Lamp
to send you back to Seiren.
Thank you, but no thanks.
There's something I have to
take care of when I get home.
Something you
have to take care of?
That's right.
What's Hijiri doing on Earth?
Something's up.
Maharu?
Oh don't mind me,
I'm just thinking out loud.
When you get to
be as old as I am,
you always end up
talking to yourself.
The two of them look
totally different, don't they?
Yeah, they really do.
Oh, that reminds me.
Your name's
Kirie, isn't it?
Uh, that's right.
Thank you for
being Miharu's friend.
Keep an eye on
her for me, would you?
It'd mean a lot to me.
Sure.
As for you, boy,
sorry about all
the trouble that I caused.
But I'm glad that
I came here today.
There's no way to know
what the future holds,
but I think my sister's
in good hands at your place.
So please keep looking
after my little sister
just like you have been.
Okay, Yukki?
Um, it's Yukinari.
Hmm? Something
bothering you, Yukki?
No ma'am!
I'll protect her!
Good! That's the spirit!
Well, it's time for me to go.
Take care, Miharu.
Big Sister.
Okay then, goodbye.
Big Sister, take care
of yourself, too.
Mmm, there's nothing
like soaking up the sun.
Maharu, all the redhead like
you would soak up are freckles.
Shut up, slacker.
I'm just trying to get
a spot in the next episode.
Don't worry, you'll
get lots of screen time
in the last volume.
I would certainly hope so!
Girls Bravo Season Two,
next episode,
"Sunny Afternoon is Bravo!"
Keep cool.
I wonder which
will happen first:
Maharu gets a husband or she'll
get a big part in the show!