Love wisdom number 997.
People say you
can't force love,
but a well-timed
push never hurt anything.
Love wisdom number 998.
Embody love.
When people ask,
"Where's the love?"
tell them "Right here."
Love wisdom number 999.
Love is an endless path.
Walk at a brisk pace,
but be careful not to trip.
Hmm.
All right. I'll do
my very best! Yeah!
At last, we've
reached our destination.
This is the place where
ambitious young people
arrive with nothing
but a dream
and work to make it come true.
Come one, come all to
the fabled Ikebukuro!
Miharu?
Am I mistaken?
No, Ikebukuro is pretty neat.
Today is my first time
going out with Yukinari.
I'm really excited!
Huh? Yeah, I guess we
haven't ever gone out
just the two of us before.
And today we get to!
That's right!
Well, are you ready?
Yeah! Let's go!
You kids have
a good time now.
Fukuyama, you remember
our agreement, right?
Of course.
Today I sit
impotently by and watch
Puny-nari fumble
through their date.
No interference, right?
That's the rule.
And don't you forget it.
That's why we
went to the trouble
of following them all the
way down here this afternoon.
I'm gonna make sure you
don't try anything shady.
You flatter me.
Who the hell do you think I am?
Harry Houdini?!
If I let you run wild,
who knows what kind
of trouble you'd get into.
This is for your own good.
Yes. It. Is.
Trotting me around
like some disobedient dog?
Have you no shame, woman?
Thinking back to our moment
of Sapphic bliss
with Kosame, are we?
Quiet!
It's not too late to
add a muzzle you know.
Now, let's go!
Hey, Miharu, you done?
This is kinda weird for me.
Oh. Okay!
M-M-M-M-M-M-iharu!
Why on earth did you wanna
go lingerie shopping anyway?
Nothing says
"a tiger in the sack"
like seductive lingerie!
What are you talking about?!
Anyway, Yukinari, which of
these gets you hot and bothered,
the panties that I'm wearing
now, or the revealing pair?
Isn't she too young
to be buying lingerie?
Really! I bet that guy she's
with is a tiger in the sack.
[CASHIER] Have fun you kids!
Wow! You're so fast, Yukinari!
Am I fast? I guess I am.
Good. Glad to hear it.
Okay. Great.
Well then,
on to our next stop.
Huh?
It's over there!
Some geckos, some turtles,
some seahorse, and some viper.
Don't worry.
This'll give him a giant boner!
A giant boner?
Yeah! By nightfall,
it'll be super hard.
Super hard?
Yukinari! This nice man
made something for you!
He said it'll give you
a giant super-hard boner!
You have no idea what
you're talking about, do you?
Ah, the poor little guy.
Best of luck to you, Limpy.
Have fun you kids!
Wow! You're so
strong, Yukinari!
That's right, Miharu,
I'm all muscle.
Come on. Can't we
go to the movies now?
Um, there is one more
shop I'd like to visit.
Huh? There's one more?
Wow! It's like
Poyon's magic wand.
We should buy it for Tomoka!
Hey, would you
like to have one?
Uh, I think Tomoka would
have to turn me into a girl
before that thing
would do me any good.
You could use it all right.
Think outside the box.
Um, Yukinari?
I'm fine.
Let's just go to the movies.
Yeah! There's a movie
I've been wanting to see.
What's it about?
Here we are!
But what could you
possibly wanna see here?!
If a couple watches
one of these movies,
they have a good time
when they get home.
Come on, Yukinari.
You and I are about to climb
the stairs of
adulthood together.
I'm just gonna
pretend that made sense.
Huh?
Miharu's acting weird.
She's done her homework.
I can tell.
Why do I have a hunch that
you're about to piss me off?
What is this tripe?
Ever wonder why Kazuharu
Fukuyama is such a lady killer?
I share my methods
with the world in my book,
"The 999 Walls
between the Idiots and Me."
I gave Miharu a copy of it.
She's put it to good use.
Huh?
First, you memorize
the 999 love truths in the book,
and then you apply them
to the appropriate situations.
All the places Miharu is
taking Puny-nari on their date
are Fukuyama-approved locations,
specifically intended
to put couples in the mood.
Idiot! Are you ready
to feel like a total bastard
if your bad advice
ruins their date?
Well of course I'm ready!
I've always made it quite plain
that I don't want Miharu and
Puny-nari to end up together.
Come on, you're not exactly
rooting for them, are you?
Hey!
Why you look down
your nose at my motives,
if you're so unwilling to
be honest with yourself?
It's the official "Walls between
the Idiots and Me" website.
You should give it a look.
Whatever you're doing
certainly hasn't worked.
Not my brand new
satellite cell phone!
Worry about yourself, dumbass.
Kirie really should learn
how to curb that temper.
Tying me up and beating me
is all well and good,
but I damn near died!
However, at least now I'm free
of my irksome chaperone!
So far Miharu's done exactly
what I outlined in the book,
but what if things go too far
and I'm not there to stop her
from throwing
herself at Puny-nari?
I'd be hoisted
by my own petard.
I'll have to
keep an eye on them.
I'm sorry Yukinari.
You don't seem to be
having much fun on our date.
I did everything just
like the book said I should.
A book?
That does explain a lot,
but you know, it's our date.
We should do it our way!
Wow! I can see
really far through these.
Yukinari, which direction
is our house from here?
I think it's
somewhere over there.
Wow! If I can
see that far away,
maybe I can even see Seiren.
Right, Yukinari?
Maybe. I guess
anything's possible.
Aww, man. What am I doing?
I can't just sit back
and watch this anymore.
Are you tired?
We've had a pretty full day.
No way! I'm too busy
having fun to be tired.
It kind of feels
like I get to eat
the Lantern Festival and
New Year's Day for dinner!
You can't eat either
of those things, silly!
No, I guess that I can't.
That's too bad.
But I think today
was the most fun
I've had since
I came to Earth.
I saw really far
with a telescope,
and that movie
was interesting!
And also...
there was... um...
Oh, I almost
forgot the best part!
Hmm? What do you mean, Miharu?
Whoa! You made all this?
Yeah, I woke up early
this morning to do it!
Please! Dig in!
Good idea!
Thanks for the food!
All right.
Ahh! M-M-M-M-Miharu!
Why are you taking
your clothes off in public?
Huh? You see in my dating book,
it says you should
take off your clothes
and get freaky in the
bushes if you go to the park.
Oh, by the way,
what does "get freaky" mean?
The book doesn't say.
You don't wanna know, okay?
Just please,
put your clothes back on.
But... I thought...
You should
look up "get freaky"
in the book's
glossary, Miharu!
Or if you're not too busy,
I'd be happy to demonstrate.
Yeah! Show me how to get freaky.
Fukuyama! Why are you here?
I merely wanted to observe
my pupil in action,
so I followed
you all afternoon.
Observe your pupil?
What does that mean?!
Miharu,
you pre-pubescent fool.
Well hello there, Miharu!
Are you putting all the things
you learned in
that book to good use?
Yeah! Now I know how
to be a tiger in the sack!
Wait! You wrote that dating
book she was trying to follow?
Guilty as charged.
Our Miharu's a very
quick learner,
but I'm going to be the one
to give her the final exam.
So I'm here to put
the kibosh on your date.
Tada!
Huh?
Huh? That's the bento
Miharu made for our date!
Dating tips aren't free.
Fukuyama away!
Dammit! Fukuyama!
But... Yukinari!
As soon as I rescue our bento,
I'll come right back.
Wait for me at the benches,
okay Miharu? Just sit tight.
But...
Okay.
That dumbass.
Mommy, where did you go?
What's wrong, little girl?
Are you looking
for your mother?
I-I was looking at toys,
and then I turned
around and she was gone.
I-I looked around a lot,
but she's not anywhere.
I can't...
Here.
First have something to drink,
and then we can go
find your mother, okay?
Fukuyama, hand over
that bento, right now!
Oh, he's using his big
boy voice. I'm so scared.
I guess I have to
take it back by force!
Hey!
Poor Puny-nari.
You must have no idea
how weak you really are.
How else could you even dream
of trying to overpower me?
Well, I'd love to
watch you tear up,
but I've got
a date with bento.
You're far too scrawny to
date Miharu, and you know it!
Shut up!
Hey. Puny-nari, get off!
I don't swing that way,
so whatever you're
thinking, forget it.
I-I know I'm not
strong enough to defeat you,
but I can't just give up.
Miharu got up early to make
that bento for the two of us,
and I'm not gonna
let you run off with it!
Stop molesting my leg
you little freak!
Unhand me!
Give it back!
Yukinari, you putz.
Get off, dammit.
Seems your best
wasn't good enough.
Hey, you!
Huh?
We're the frog and cow
comedy duo at your service.
We saw you steal the bento
and run away with it.
Yeah, and that
is no laughing matter.
Don't worry, little boy,
Frog and Cow are
here to help you.
Have you lost your mind, Kirie?
Shut up, dumbass!
We're the frog and cow
comedy duo, remember?
Are you ready Mr. Frog?
Ready and willing!
Good!
Yeah!
Steal lunch...
...in Hell!
Hey you, little boy.
Here ya go.
Thanks Kiri-- nevermind.
Thank you both.
Thanks, Kirie.
Dummy.
Bye lady! Thank you!
It's so late!
I didn't know.
I have to get back!
Pardon me, could I trouble
you for some directions?
Oh. Oh dear.
Hello. What can I
help you with, ma'am?
You see, I have to return
to the train station now,
but I've forgotten
how to get there.
Oh, I know where the train
station is. I'll show you.
Well thank you, Miss.
That's very thoughtful of you.
Huh?
Miharu!
Where could she be?
I have to find her,
right away!
Ah. Thank you so
much for your kindness.
I'm glad I could help.
Take care!
What should I do?
It's almost 7 at night!
She's still not here.
Yukinari!
It's been 3 hours
since I left.
But Yukinari
told me to sit tight
until he rescued our lunch.
I bet he'll be back any minute.
All right, I just have to be
patient for a little bit longer.
I can't stand it! I'll
save you, Miharu!
Dammit! Stop
tying me to things!
No way, it's not your job.
Let Yukinari be her
knight in shining armor.
He's earned it.
You saw it yourself.
Weak little
Yukinari tried so hard
to get Miharu's bento
away from you.
He didn't have a chance
in the world, but he tried.
Kirie, do you have a cell phone?
Thanks to a certain
over-zealous someone,
mine doesn't work anymore.
Yeah I have one. What for?
Her knight in shining
armor needs some help.
Miharu! Miharu!
Where could she have gone?
I don't know where else
to look for you, Miharu.
Huh?
A restricted number?
Hello?
Have you tried looking for
her in the park, you retard?
What? Hello? Hello?
Miharu!
Huh?
Yukinari!
Miharu!
Other people's happiness
is no fun. I'm leaving.
Wait! Hey, Fukuyama.
Now what?
Why'd you do that,
after you spent all day
trying to ruin their date?
I don't really know.
What? Is something amusing?
Oh, nothing.
You're laughing at nothing?
What? Tell me already!
You take the caps off
and recycle plastic bottles
with the non-burning trash.
Miharu, you learned how
to separate the trash?
Yes, if we all do our part,
the town stays nice and clean.
You're right.
I should pitch in too.
The insides of
bananas are really tasty.
But what about
the peels, Kirie?
Girls Bravo Season Two,
next episode, "Clean Up Bravo!"
Should be neat.
Is a banana peel inedible trash
if I just ate it?