Ah! This is...
A girl?
Yeah. We looked in the tub,
and there she was... out cold.
She was...
in my bathtub?
[YUKINARI and KOYOMI]
Ahh!
Hey, wait, what did I do?
What?
It's a man!
It's amnesia,
there's no question.
The Earth... it's so close
and yet so far...
my father's planet.
Are you saying...
you're from--
The star mark.
I remember...
What I'm
supposed to do.
I'm supposed to...
[MIHARU] Koyomi! Go on,
I brought you a towel.
Oh, uh, well thank you
for doing that.
[MIHARU giggles]
Seiren...
[MAHARU] Listen up! How many
times do I have to explain?!
My younger sister
disappeared from our bathroom.
[CUSTOMER SERVICE AGENT]
So you keep telling us.
Could you please try
to calm down a little?
[MAHARU] My sister
vanished into thin air!
I'm not feeling very serene!
Anyhow, she--she's been
assigned a case number.
There's no point
waiting around.
Whatever! Just hurry up
and find her already!
We'll do our best!
But it still might
take a little time.
Miharu... here I am
worried sick about her,
and she's probably having
all sorts of fun with that guy!
They're probably getting it
on morning, noon, and night!
So unfair! I'm not gonna
let her have all the fun!
A missing person case?
The subject is
Miharu Sena Kanaka.
She disappeared from her
bathroom about a month ago now.
We have reason to
think she's on Earth.
I want you to bring
her back to Seiren...
before the Special Forces
ladies start butting in.
Can I count on you, Koyomi?
Yes.
The crystalized Aqua Lamp
will only give you
a 36-hour window
of opportunity
in which to
complete your mission.
If you exceed
that 36-hour limit,
you won't be able
to return to Seiren.
Do you understand?
Perfectly, Captain.
I do hope that your first
assignment goes smoothly.
[KOYOMI] Right!
[FROG] Rise and shine!
It's time to eat breakfast.
Rise and shine!
Only 12 hours...
Hello?
[KIRIE] Yukinari!
How come you act
like such a damn pervert
every single morning!
[MIHARU] Excuse me, but did
I do something I shouldn't have?
Listen to me, please!
You've got it all wrong!
[KOYOMI] Excuse me...
[KIRIE] I've got it all wrong?
Fine!
Why the hell is
Miharu wearing that?
[YUKINARI] Well...
[KIRIE] Why?
I--
[KIRIE] You what?
[YUKINARI] ...don't know.
Hello?
What do you mean
you don't know?
Excuse me?
If you made Miharu wear that,
you are dead meat!
Hold on a minute!
[MIHARU] But he didn't, Kirie.
I wanted to learn more about
doing things the Earth way. See?
Ah!
I found this magazine in a box
underneath Yukinari's bed.
There are a bunch of pictures
of women who are cooking,
but they're not wearing
anything but an apron and socks.
I just assumed that's how
you're supposed
to cook on Earth.
[YUKINARI] Not quite, Miharu.
Uh, gimme that magazine.
[KIRIE speaking angrily]
Yukinari!
[YUKINARI laughs uncomfortably]
I'm not allergic to
photographs of girls, you know.
You porn-reading pervert!
Nasty! Nasty! Nasty! Nasty!
I thought you were afraid
of girls, you sleazy bastard!
What should I do?
First the shock of traveling
here gives me amnesia...
then I discover
that one of the people
who took care of me
was the very girl I was
sent here to locate
and bring back to Seiren.
I really wanted to do a good
job on my first assignment.
What should I do?
There's only half a day left!
Koyomi?
Uh, yes?
Miharu made a couple
of rice balls for you,
if you're hungry, uh...
Let's see... where...
Uh, thank you.
I'll leave them
over here.
Do you...
remember yet?
Oh... sorry.
I see.
Koyomi?
Uh, yeah?
I got a hunch that...
you came here from Seiren, huh?
What?
You were saying yesterday
that your father is from Earth.
Oh... right.
I guess that your
memory came back.
Mhmm.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to lie.
Hey, don't
worry about it.
Well, then, I...
You're here because
of Miharu, aren't you?
Yes. My name is
Koyomi Hare Nanaka.
Miharu's older sister
put in a request
with the Space Management
Bureau, and... they sent me.
You came to take Miharu back.
Yeah.
This is all of it, right?
This is definitely
most of it!
I know Koyomi's eating with us,
but isn't this still
gonna be too much food?
But... I wanna make
sure that Yukinari
can eat as much
as he wants today.
As much as he wants?
[KOYOMI] The wormhole that
connects Seiren and Earth
will close in
another half a day.
We have to go back
before that happens.
[YUKINARI] Miharu doesn't
know any of this yet, does she?
No.
I see.
Uh, Yukinari?
Yeah?
I thought that you were...
they told me that you
were allergic to women,
but you seem
fine around Miharu.
I'm better than fine.
I can't really explain it.
I randomly popped into
Miharu's bathroom on Seiren.
When she accidentally
came to Earth,
I let her stay here,
'cause she had nowhere to go.
Pure coincidence...
But now... I think
that it was meant to be!
[CHILD KOYOMI]
Hey Mommy?
[MOM] Hmm?
Where did Daddy go?
To a faraway place.
A faraway place?
Father went back to his home.
Uh?
He went up there.
Back to his home on Earth.
Do you understand?
But... he'll
come back, right?
[KOYOMI] To reunite people
with their loved ones...
that's the whole
reason I took this job.
I know it's my
assignment, but...
I don't think
I have the right
to separate two people who
care so much for each other.
I'll go alone.
[YUKINARI knocking]
Koyomi?
Uh? Yukinari!
I, uh... I'm going back
to Seiren by myself.
I'll just tell my superiors
that I couldn't
find Miharu in time.
Miharu! I-I just...
Koyomi, I know
you came here
all the way from
Seiren to find me.
You knew it all along?
Mmm.
It's okay,
I can tell Maharu
that you're safe
and sound here on Earth.
That way you can stay--
No.
Yukinari and I had
a long talk about it.
I think I should
go back to Seiren.
But if... if
you do that,
Yukinari and you won't
be together anymore.
I really like Earth,
but Seiren is my home.
Miharu...
Don't worry.
I know Yukinari and I
will both be all right.
So come on. It's time
we were going home.
Yeah... Yeah.
[indistincit chatter]
Goodbye...
Miharu.
[MAHARU crying] Miharu!
Hi Maharu.
Miharu, I was so
worried about you!
Excellent work, Koyomi.
But Chief, I...
I didn't really do much.
Mission accomplished.
Congratulations.
[MAHARU] I'm so glad.
I'm so glad you're home.
I'm going!
Yukinari?
Good morning.
Good morning!
You're early for a change.
It wasn't so tough.
Uh, so, uh where's Miharu?
She went home.
Huh?
To Seiren.
What? Hold on!
Wait, Yukinari,
what are you saying?
They're both gone?!
Koyomi came to take
Miharu back to Seiren,
and you just stood there
and let the two of them leave?
Hey, leave him
alone, Fukuyama!
They'd still be here
if you weren't such
an asexual waste of space.
Now they're gone forever,
and it's your fault!
Stop it, Fukuyama!
It's all your fault!
Cut it out!
Cut it out already!
My back...
my back is breaking.
But the warmth
of Kirie's firm, taut buttocks
against mine leaves
the rest of me
throbbing with pleasure.
Do your throbbing
in Hell!
[YUKINARI]
Kirie...
Yukinari...
Fukuyama is right,
you know.
It's my fault
that she left.
It's the truth.
Just let him go.
Yukinari...
Huh?
Oh.
Miharu...
I'm sorry.
Hey, don't worry about it.
I'll clean it up.
You've been
through a lot lately,
so I really want you to take
it easy for a while, okay?
Mhmm.
[doorbell rings]
[MAHARU] Yes, who is it?
Oh, it's you.
You know I forgot to say it
in the excitement
of the moment, but...
thank you for
finding my sister.
Oh, don't mention it.
I mean, I was
only doing my job,
and Miharu helped me
out so much on Earth,
I should probably
be thanking her.
Yeah?
She did, huh?
Um, is Miharu
home right now?
Yeah, she's helping me
out with the dishes.
[glass dish breaks]
I, uh... actually I wanted
your advice on something,
and it's about Miharu.
I thought so.
It's that guy back
on Earth, isn't it?
[MAHARU]
Miharu?
Oh, hello again,
Koyomi.
Sorry about the mess,
Big Sister Maharu.
As soon as I've cleaned up,
I'll get everything
ready for dinner.
Say, can Koyomi stay
and eat dinner with us?
Miharu...
It's okay.
Just leave it be.
Big Sister?
You're such a sweet girl.
From the moment that
our father passed away,
you've never asked me
for a single thing.
Except for seconds, right?
I'm really happy
to have you back,
and Koyomi, I'll never
forget what you did.
But it's not up to me.
For once in your life,
you should think of
your own happiness.
Be selfish.
Do whatever you want to do.
Big Sister!
So, what do you want
more than anything?
To be with Yukinari.
Then that's
what you should do.
I wonder if all of
the men on that planet
are as great as
the one that she found.
Maybe I should wish on
a star for my future husband.
And for my little sister.
I know she'll be happy.
We've received a communique
from the Information Division.
It seems that girl has used
the gate to return to Earth.
[KOYOMI]
What's its status?
It's stabilized for
the moment. The Aqua Lamp
should function
without any problems.
It's a Special Forces
matter now.
I didn't know...
I'm very sorry.
Don't worry.
So far nobody has
filed a search request.
And truth be known,
I'm not too fond
of those
Special Forces ladies.
But Chief Nanae!
And Koyomi...
I have another job for you.
Hey, Yukinari,
do you wanna swing by
the shopping
arcade for a bit?
Huh?
There's a new cake shop
opening up down there,
and they say it's
supposed to be pretty good.
No thank you.
I think I just
wanna be alone today.
I know.
Well...
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
Uh, Kirie...
Huh?
Thanks for trying.
[MIHARU]
Yukinari...
Ah?
But... Miharu...
I thought you...
Big Sister Maharu
said that I could go.
So I thought
about you really hard
until that special blue light
started shining around me.
And suddenly, there I was...
sitting in your bathtub.
I guess... I came back.
Oh, Kirie!
Koyomi, you came
back to Earth, too!
Looks like things around
here are gonna be lively again.
Oh, there is something...
that I should mention.
[TOMO] Hello!
Missing people?
Stolen items? General worries?
Have no fear,
now that Tomoka's here!