[MAHARU laughs]
I'll have an Earth man
of my very own in no time!
With a body as hot as mine,
there's no way he'll
be able to resist me.
I'm counting on you two,
happy hunting!
[POYON] Magical Girl
Papipupe-poyon!
Give transcendence advent
in this world of anxiety!
What?
Maharu wants you to track down
a husband for her on Earth?
Uh-huh.
Wait... Maharu?
Yeah, she's my big sister.
She's having a bit of trouble
in the romance department.
It's because men are pretty
rare back home on Seiren.
Oh, I see.
Maharu asked me if
I'd look as a favor.
She told me to take
as long as I need,
but I just don't
know if I can do it.
You get kind of... anxious
when there're
guys around, huh?
Yeah.
That mission is child's play.
Just leave it to Tomo!
I'll get the job done.
Uh...
Okay.
Who's she?
Right. I didn't
introduce her yet.
I'd like you all to meet
Tomoka Lana Jude.
She came along to assist me.
I'm a special agent with the
Seiren Space Management Bureau.
You're a special agent?
But aren't you just a kid?
Tomo's not just a kid!
Tomo is a very important
person back on Seiren,
and I brought
a bunch of stuff
that'll make this
assignment a piece of cake.
Observe.
[EBI] Nya?
Get out of there!
What the hell is that?
Is that gonna
help us find a man?
I don't know.
What does it do, Tomoka?
I've never seen
that thing before.
What was it doing in my bag?
Let's eat it.
Nyo!
Nya nya!
Don't look at me, freeloader.
Nya!
Hey, quit it, come on.
You can't just go
sticking your nose wherev--
You damn kinky seal!
Stop it already!
Nya!
Nya nyo.
It's okay, little guy.
I'm not gonna eat you... yet.
Nya nya!
Wait! Stop bouncing away!
I gotta ask,
do you really think
Miharu's gonna
eat that thing?
Pretty much
looks that way.
That's just gross.
At this rate,
how will I ever be able
to carry out
my promise to Maharu?
Whoa! What is that?
That's totally cool!
Wow! That's amazing!
What's that one? Neat!
Ahh. Special agent or not,
she's still just a little kid.
So anyway, Miharu,
when did the two of you
start getting along so well?
Little Ebi and I have
gotten along from the beginning.
Ebi?
Right, huh, Ebi?
Nya nya nya.
Is that really what
you've decided to call it?
Uh-huh!
Doesn't it sound tasty?
Nya nya nya nya-nya!
I'm ashamed
to admit it, Mother,
but I'm beginning
to lose heart.
I took this job,
because I wanted to be able
to bring people together.
And I really wanted
to do right by Maharu
and honor her request
for a husband,
because I felt bad
about how she hasn't
been able to get married,
but there are
so many men on Earth.
More than I ever
could have imagined.
I can't even walk down
the street out of fear of them.
I have to hide in
the shadows and in the alleys,
and even there
I don't feel safe.
I always expect the worst.
What if I can't
fulfill Maharu's request?
And what do
I do if I run into
that monstrous man
from before...
the one with the demented
laugh and the white gloves.
If he should
ever catch me...
I can't even imagine
the horrors that await me!
The things he'll do!
Oh no no! No no no no! Wah!
Hey, uh, Koyomi?
Now what?!
Oh man. I could be wrong,
but I don't think
you're up for this.
Hey Koyo,
stop hiding in there.
You're never gonna
complete Maharu's request
if you're always acting
like such a 'fraidy cat!
Well it's the truth, right?
Aw, come on now, Tomoka.
There's no reason
to get so upset.
Tomo is not upset!
I'm only saying
all this stuff
'cause Koyo needed some
positive reinforcement.
Well, that's
just how kids are.
They think that yelling
fixes every problem.
Koyomi, there's no deadline,
so just take your time.
I agree.
Just do your best,
and you'll be
sure to find a man.
Yeah, totally.
Don't worry about what
some little kid has to say.
Tomo is not a little kid!
And to prove
that Tomo's no kid,
I'm gonna go out there
and find a husband
for Maharu
before Koyo can!
But... what about Koyomi?
Well I can't
possibly take care
of shy little
Koyo all the time.
If you wanna make it fair,
I guess you guys
could team up with her.
You want us to
help out Koyomi, then?
Sure I do.
Somebody as important,
and mature, and beautiful
as Tomo doesn't mind a handicap.
Well then, Koyo.
No time to waste.
Hey, cheer up.
The three of us are
gonna help you find a guy.
It'll be easy, okay?
Okay.
So then, what do we do?
Just relax.
There's always more than
one way to skin a cat.
Will we have to...
skin a cat?
Careless. Very careless.
I let Yukinari out of my
sight for just a little while,
and now some other girl's
in love with my soul mate again.
Look at her, throwing
herself at my dear Yukinari.
[muffled scream]
Hayate! Kosame!
You summoned us?
Mistress Lisa?
You will investigate
that girl for me.
Know thy enemy.
Right.
Is this... one of the ways
that you skin a cat?
Stop freaking out!
This way you'll be able
to find a man in no time flat.
Even so, I think
this is... a bit much.
Hey, cutie!
Gimme some love!
Okay!
Yeah! Over here, too! Bend
forward a little, yeah!
Do you mean like this?
Woah! Cleavage-a-rama!
Whoa! Booty-licious!
Shoot men!
Just keep shooting!
Shoot from
the front and from the back!
Shoot at her every move
until you camera's run dry!
It is our sublime calling
to chronicle this exact moment
in which these nubile goddesses,
descending upon us,
so that we can leave a record
for future generations.
Oh yeah!
Koyomi, look!
Here's what you do.
But I can't.
I can't do that.
Come on, it's not gonna kill
you to show off a little T&amp;A.
Now lean your chest forward,
just like that. Yeah.
Please stop it.
Please, Kirie, stop!
[KOYOMI whimpers]
Stop!
That Kirie, I think
she enjoys a challenge
a little too much.
Nya.
Miss Kirie,
so lovely.
What is that girl who's after
my soul mate doing over there?
I have discovered
her weakness.
It would seem that
she's quite terrified of men.
She's terrified
of men?
Then how exactly do
you explain all that.
Well, the details are unclear,
but I'm relatively sure
she's looking for a husband.
What? Did you
just say husband?!
What I wouldn't do
to bury my face in those.
She's wearing that
trampy little outfit
to try to sink her
hooks into Yukinari.
So that's her idea?
[laughing]
Oh that
exquisite waist.
Miss, do you have a plan?
That girl...
You said she's terrified
of men, did you not?
Oh I can't resist
much longer,
my beautiful
Miss Kirie.
Then there's only
one thing to do.
Oh I want
you so bad.
Take ruthless
advantage of her weakness.
Show her no mercy.
Understood.
[laughs pervertedly]
Huh?
Hey!
Anybody who tries
to keep me from him...
is another obstacle
that must be removed!
Yukinari is mine!
Hey! What do you retards
think you're lookin' at?!
It totally sucks, huh boss?
These bastards
should really learn
not to be so
damn superficial!
Boss, what's up?
[BOSS mumbling]
Hey! Hold on, Boss!
What's wrong, little girl?
Say there, are you hungry?
Or maybe you somehow got lost.
[BOSS mumbling]
Actually Tomo is
looking for a man
who would be willing
to go to Seiren with me.
What? Seiren, huh?
What's that? The name
of a shop or something?
[TOMO cries]
No, no, listen!
I really need one of you
to go to Seiren
with me, okay?
I'll take you!
To Seiren or anywhere!
Hey, not so fast!
I'm going with her
to Seiren, dig?
Back off, youngsters.
This is obviously a task
intended for someone
of my age and experience.
Get over here!
I'm gonna take you
straight to my fist, buddy!
You're not gonna go
anywhere with this girl.
She's mine!
I saw her first!
Heh. Suckers.
[cell phones ring]
[ALL MEN] Huh?
Hey, she's hot.
Yeah, this
chick's hot like fire.
[BOSS mumbling]
You like her?
If you want her,
she's there for the taking.
Wait! Where you going?
Huh?
Come back, Boss.
So, uh, something just
happened but I don't know what.
Hey Panda! Make us laugh!
Come on, Panda.
Here's some bamboo. Eat it!
Eat it! Eat it!
Huh?
Hey, haven't you heard?
Pandas can be
pretty dangerous.
They put up
a pretty good front,
but pandas are actually
nature's killing machines.
And, if you bully a panda
because it seems gentle...
[KIRIE slurps]
it'll take
your head off...
with a single
swipe of its claw.
[KIRIE giggles]
[KIDS scream]
[KOYOMI crying]
What did I do
to deserve this?
Uh, Koyomi?
If I have to deal with
any more embarrassment today,
I think I'll die
on the spot!
Koyomi, it hasn't been so bad.
Nya nya.
Koyomi! If you give up
just like that,
then Tomoka
is going to win!
But we look
stupid in these!
I only put
this dumb thing on,
because you said it
would help us to attract men!
[KOYOMI whines]
Do we really?
Well I think our animal
outfits are pretty nifty.
Nya nya nya.
She's got a point.
I didn't think you
were going to attract
any men dressed like this.
What do you mean?
Are you saying
that I have bad taste?
No, that... that isn't
what I was getting at.
So what were
you trying to say?
Uh, Kirie, look!
See, it worked! I love it
when a plan comes together.
If it worked, why do I have
a bad feeling about this?
No... kidding.
Hey, wanna sashay
around in a maid uniform?
Put on a bunny outfit for me!
A kimono,
so I can pull the sash.
[BOSS mumbling]
Wow! That's amazing, Koyomi!
They love you!
Is that what you think?
Behold the power of
cleavage and panda suits.
You think so, huh?
Have fun with
your new fan club.
Such is the fate
of all who try to steal
dear Yukinari from
the likes of Lisa Fukuyama.
Uh, regarding that...
I did some
additional research.
She is looking
for a husband,
but the husband in question
isn't meant for her.
What?
She's searches on behalf
of a woman named Maharu.
This could be bad...
Indeed it could.
Quick! Run for it!
We're leaving?
Right after we
found all these men?
Forget it, Miharu!
Just keep running!
You know, maybe
we've done enough
to them for one afternoon.
Perhaps we
should call it a day.
[TOMO crying]
What happened?
I tried my hardest to get
a group of Earth men,
and then they
all just ran away.
Why are you
sitting here crying?
Are you lost?
So, did you find her?
No, how 'bout you?
No luck.
Where could she have gone?
I think we've
lost them for now.
[KOYOMI crying]
Hey, I'm sorry.
I didn't know it
was gonna get that bad.
Just leave me alone already!
I've got it!
This is a great
time for a bath!
What?
Whenever you're sad,
a good bath makes you feel
like a whole new person!
Come on, Koyomi.
But I... I don't want to!
Hey Mister, do you wanna
go somewhere with Tomo?
Sure, we can go
anywhere you want.
Tomo is so happy!
I'm super glad
that I met you.
Hey now,
don't get carried away.
[TOMO giggles]
Okay! Here we are.
Huh? But this is...
I'm terrible...
taking it out on them
after all
they've done to help me.
I need to apologize.
And I have to tell
Maharu the truth, too.
I'm not going to be able
to honor her request.
Well this is it!
Hmm? Koyomi?
All right!
Nooo!
[KIRIE] What?
[MIHARU] Huh?
[YUKINARI] Koyomi!
Fukuyama?
Oh, Miharu too.
You both found it impossible
to forget about me,
and so you came
back to Earth, right?
That's so sweet.
Wrong wrong wrong!
I didn't come back for you!
Let go, you!
Tomo found this
man fair and square!
I hope the irony of this
isn't lost on the two of you.
Please just let go of me.
Wait, Koyomi, don't
wriggle around so much!
It's that light again!
They... they all vanished.
Hey Maharu.
So I guess Miharu
used to live here too, huh?
What is it with you?
I'm in the middle
of taking a bath!
Now, now. You'll be
very glad Tomo stopped in.
Yeah! I brought you
a husband from Earth,
just like you
asked us to do.
Let's see...
Ah, a husband.
And that would be him?
That's right!
He seems kinda stupid,
but I think
he's pretty cute.
Please, I'm begging you!
You don't have to
play so hard to get.
I know that in your most
secret heart of hearts,
you think that
I'm number one.
If anything, I think that
you're public enemy number one!
He's good looking all right...
for a guy who acts like
he needs to be hosed down.
Yeah, I hadn't noticed.
Seriously, I had no idea
that guy was
such a pervert.
I guess that
was my fault.
Quiet!
Uh... Ma-Maharu.
Maharu! I've ended up
in some nudist paradise
where all the women
are as beautiful as Koyomi!
Did you seriously
think that I would
accept this sleazeball?
No! I had nothing to do
with it! He wouldn't let go!
A sleazeball?
No, you've got it all wrong.
And if loving beautiful
women like you is wrong,
I don't wanna be right.
Stop feeding me
lame excuses,
and go find me
a quality man!
I'm really sorry!
Koyomi and the others...
they haven't come back yet.
I wonder how
things turned out.
I mean look at
the guy they took.
Yeah. I'll bet Seiren
still doesn't know what hit it.
Huh?
I'm so sorry!
Koyomi!
Almost forgot
what it looked like...
Koyomi my darling.
Where did you go?
Koyomi?
Go look for her... in Hell!
Uh, what just happened?
Looks kinda iffy.
Tomoka's back also.
You weren't gone very long.
Did it not go too well.
Um, about that...
Maharu kinda
sorta chewed us out.
She told us not
to bring back perverts.
Well, at least
the girl's got good taste.
I'll have to start
looking all over again.
It's tough being the best.
I have to tell you, Mother,
Earth is a scary place.
Random men pick on me,
and there's this
one pervert
who won't stop
chasing me around.
I want... I want...
I just wanna go
home to Seiren!