Long live the Black Knights! Hip, hip, hooray!
What happened to that Knightmare?
The one that saved Zero?
It escaped using a route Xing-ke gave us.
Xing-ke?
The Chinese Federation guy I mentioned.
I see.
Then I'll be sure to make use of that route, as well.
So, was that pilot the same one from Babel Tower?
Because of what happened to Urabe,
I won't tell you his name.
Simply think of him as a person who supports our cause.
You didn't use your Geass on him, did you?
As it turned out, I didn't need to.
Anyway, C.C., about the Emperor and...
Now wait a minute!
You'll keep the pilot a secret from me?!
So what?
There are times when I like to keep secrets, too.
Are you speaking as Zero, or Lelouch right now?
It's not as if everyone knows
about our relationship, do they?
Stop saying weird stuff like that, all right?!
And your true identity?
Kallen and I are the only ones
among the group who know who you really are.
That's secret, too.
Lelouch, do you still want me to be the
captain of Zero's personal force, as I have been?
I do.
Understood. I'll consider that roger and out!
I'm counting on you, now.
We'll talk about Geass later.
There are more pressing matters.
Very well. I catch your drift.
Here it is! Man, I've missed my old uniform!
Rock n' roll...!
I can't believe they had all this ready for us!
They say Captain Kouzuki and Urabe arranged it.
Oh man...
Oh, I see. And you say Urabe died well?
Yes.
You should just confess already.
W-What do you mean by "confess?"
It's Zero!
Hold it! Hold it!
While we appreciate your rescuing us, Zero,
we wouldn't have been captured in the first place
if you hadn't betrayed us the way you did!
Don't you owe us an explanation?
What happened? We deserve to know!
Everything is for victory over Britannia.
Okay... Go on.
That's all.
Huh?!
Nothing more to say?
No apologies? No excuses?
Stop it!
Zero.
Were your actions intended to give us a chance of winning?
I'm always focused on getting results.
I understand.
At times, our operations must be kept secret.
Right now, we need to rely on his power!
I can think of no one more
capable than Zero to be our leader!
I agree! We should all trust Zero!
But Zero treated you as if
you were nothing more than a pawn.
Who other than Zero could have pulled this off?!
Even the Chinese Federation isn't
strong enough to wage war on Britannia!
And the E.U. continues to lose
to Prince Schneizel, doesn't it?
We're the last hope out of all
the Areas that Britannia has colonized.
Zero is the only one who can lead us
to victory in our war of independence!
Ohgi's right!
Zero! Zero! Zero! Zero!
Zerp! Zero! Zero! Zero...
Hello, everyone.
My name is Suzaku Kururugi,
and I'll be returning to classes here
at Ashford Academy starting today.
I look forward to studying here.
Suzaku Kururugi?!
The guy who caught Zero?!
The White Death is coming to school here?!
He's the Knight of Seven.
But, he's an Eleven.
Doesn't matter.
He's the emperor's immediate subord...
Okay, quiet down!
Sir Kururugi has been reassigned to Area 11,
and that's why he's coming back to school here.
Why don't you take the desk next to Lelouch for now.
Yes, ma'am.
Suzaku... You...
You were my first real friend.
But... the war tore us apart.
The Second Pacific War.
The conflict in which Britannia took control of Japan.
After it's defeat,
Japan became an Area colony of Britannian.
I, who was abandoned by my homeland...
I, who was forced to abandon my homeland...
When reunited, we were at once enemies and allies.
Although I was Japanese,
I was also a Britannian soldier.
I was Zero.
We both hid our true identities.
We fought each other.
However, those are memories of what really happened.
The emperor rewrote three things in Lelouch's memory.
Nunnally...
Anything about Zero...
And that I...
...was a prince of the royal family of Britannia.
And so, the two of us now...
Hey, welcome back. It's been some time.
I missed everyone a lot.
Suzaku, it feels like forever!
You've really come up in the world, haven't you!
Suzaku's back?! Where is he?!
Madame President!
Class is in progress. You mind?
Oh, what's with you, Lelouch?
You screwed up, Suzaku.
When you heard the name Lelouch,
you just walked right to my side.
In other words, you acted as if you knew me.
Now, to make sure Rolo doesn't do anything stupid.
Hm?
And so everybody up and left, except us.
They all went back home. Even the teachers!
Back to the homeland?
Yeah.
And that's the reason why we're the only
ones here at the school who know you. Right, Rolo?
R-Right.
That explains why I don't recognize any one here.
Hey, you saw Zero's face, didn't you?
So what did he look like?
Is he really a girl?
It's really Prince Clovis, right?
Or a prince from another country?
Uhh...well, um...
Can't you share that with us?
No, it's a military secret.
I'm sorry... Ah!
Arthur!
Ah! You brought him with you?
Well, Suzaku,
you really have a thing for cats, don't you?
Did anything leap out at you during your contact with him?
No, not especially.
Then we can conclude that the
subject's memories haven't returned?
Wait just a minute.
Please, I feel we have to investigate this further.
Do you mean you don't trust our surveillance?
There's also the matter of C.C.
Continue playing his little brother
just the way you have been.
All right, my lord.
It seems the student council is
planning to throw you a welcoming party.
Please reconfirm his state then.
Yes, understood.
What should I do?
Do I dare trust Lelouch?
Teacher, could you please overlook all the
campus infractions that Rolo and I are involved in?
Very well. I can do that.
Just don't wander off school grounds so often, you two.
Yes, sir.
The only member left now is Ms. Villetta, right?
Correct. But Suzaku Kururugi is here now.
Shall I kill him?
You shouldn't behave like that.
Oh, and something else...
Yes?
Can you quit speaking to me in such a formal manner?
After all, we are supposed to be brothers.
Uh!
Don't worry.
I'll hurry up with my plan for your sake, as well.
I am going to do it. Independence for Japan,
will begin with this school.
Iwate.
Wakayama.
Tokushima.
There are reports from Yamaguchi, too.
Zero makes an appearance again, and now we get this!
It may be an effect of Lord Guilford's absence, too.
If this keeps up, our Sakuradite supply will also be...
Emergency! Unknown M.R.F. within the perimeter!
What is it?!
No way! This government bureau controls all of Area 11!
Getting in here couldn't have been easier!
These guys are almost annoyingly sloppy!
Is this the best line of defense
that Area 11's got to offer?
Uh-huh. Perhaps I was being a bit hasty.
Oh?
I don't know who you are, but this ends right here!
Pitiful. That armament shows you
care more about protecting the building.
Oh well, too bad.
What?!
That Knightmare! Could it be the one?!
I see, that's what we're dealing with.
The variable Knightmare Frame, Tristan.
Which makes you Lord Gino Weinberg,
the Knight of Three. Am I correct?
You are. I'm putting you guys to the test.
Alright! Try and stop me!
Very well. We accept your challenge!!
We can't allow this insult to us go unanswered!
Don't hold back. Gimme your best shot.
As you wish!
Thank you!
Why, you...!
Stop it!
That's enough! The battle's been decided!
Then, Sir Kururugi, is that the
final decision of the Knight of Seven?
It is.
Hey, Suzaku!
Gino, I thought I asked you to bring Lancelot here for me.
Yeah, but Earl Asplund is coming with it next week.
And not to change the subject,
but what's with that outfit?
I came straight here from school. It's required.
Very fashionable!
Gino, I know you're from a great, noble family,
but can't you act more normal?
By the way, you're amazingly heavy.
Is it over?
The Mordred? Anya came along, too?
Yup. Suzaku made me end it.
Ohh...
How dull.
We should have more than
enough firepower assembled by now.
Lelouch, three days from now, at the welcome party,
everything will be made clear.
Apologies for the delay!
We are now officially kicking off
the welcome party for the Knight of Seven!
Give the word, guest of honor.
Yeah, um... I don't suppose I can refuse?
Sorry, nope! It's a presidential order!
Just accept it. She sets the rules in this school.
Hmph. All right, guys.
I'll get ready, then.
Meow!
This way to the horseback riding course!
Lelouch, are these things appropriate for the occasion?
That's Milly for ya. The Prez loves events like this.
She's also overcompensating for last year.
Oh?
What should I do now? I ought to just...
Rolo.
Huh?
I've told you, that's dangerous.
Here, hold your knife like this. Got it?
L-Like this?
Careful of your fingers.
Mm.
Lelouch...
Hm?
The truth is... my Geass does have an Achilles heel.
Wow, would you look at that! Hey Anya, check it out!
Recorded.
You sure love that stuff, huh? All right, so now what?
There's nothing in particular to do here.
Shall we take a tour of where the commoners go to school?
I'm here now.
In the storehouse under the school.
Okay, so where are those spare energy fillers?
Hm? Hey, didn't these belong to Nina?
All right. Understood.
Go through cell F in Kyushu
and make contact with Diethard.
Yes, that's right. Have Rakshata come here and...
She wouldn't!
Come and watch us make the world's biggest pizza pie!
Do you have information about it?
Of course! Here's a flyer for you!
Come see the world's biggest pizza!
Hey! What do you think... you're doing?
I'm looking for something I left behind.
Why are you so obsessed with this stuff anyway?
Come on!
Acting a little devilish aren't you?
Shut up, witch!
Don't you understand your situation?
The emperor is trying to capture me.
And he's using you as bait.
That's right. Suzaku's here.
As well as another. A woman I can't use my Geass on.
From pretty girls...
To sexy grownup women!
Welcome to the Swim Club Café,
where you get exactly what you want!
Oh, I'm so glad the coach agreed to do this for us!
So help me, Shirley,
you'll die a thousand deaths for this!
If I didn't have to play teacher for my mission, I'd...!
I used to be a schoolteacher,
so I was feeling a little nostalgic.
They've confirmed that the Guren Mark-2 is there.
I assume Kallen is in the consulate building.
I see. It's hard to judge her.
They call themselves "resistance fighters," but still...
Nina's doing quite well.
She just presented a thesis at the Science Academy.
I wonder if she's planning to perfect the Ganymede.
Don't know.
Unlike Lloyd and Cecile, Nina's specialty is...
Uh?
Um, has Earl Asplund happened to mention me?
Afraid not.
Maybe he was overwhelmed?
The wedding was put off because I had to repeat school.
The thing with him is...
So many things are wrong with him as a human being,
so...Uh! What the...?
Arthur! That was Euphie's!
Suzaku!
You're the guest of honor! You have to wait here!
You can't run off like that!
What have we here?
They're using a Knightmare to create a giant pizza?!
So, the person who gave the emperor his Geass
is the same person who told Suzaku?
That's right.
But you shouldn't delve into it any further.
I'm already involved in this.
V.V.
V.V.?
Did he give Suzaku a Geass power?
No, it doesn't appear that he did.
Aanyway, about Villetta...
Lulu!
Uh?
What's up, Shirley?
Hm? Oh, there you are.
Do you need something?
Well, I have a little problem
that I hope you can help me with.
Ms. Villetta seems to be avoiding me,
so I was thinking you should... Huh? You're alone?
Yeah.
I could've sworn you were talking to someone just now.
Nope. We're the only ones here, just the two of us.
Hm?
Just the two of us? What awful timing,
but this might be my best chance to tell him how I feel.
Listen, um, Lulu. Would you go out...
Sorry, but I couldn't quite catch that.
Hey! What's the big idea?!
What are you doing?!
If someone spots you, as well...
Don't worry! I'm came here to take Pizza Girl back!
Fine. She's in with the tomatoes.
Take the whole container,
then have Tohdoh or Ohgi command the...
Who's in there being so rude!
How undignified!
Will you quit standing there and say something!
If I say something, she'll find out who I am!
Ugh! Hey, wait!
Shirley! Be careful with that!
Hey, Lelouch!
Say, have you seen Arthur?!
He grabbed a valuable quill pen from me, and...
Uh!
Oh no, is he inside this thing?!
No! Cats and tomatoes don't mix!
You're supposed to start with this, right?
It can't be... Gino?!
Yeah! This commoner school is really a blast!
Hey! Wait!
Hey!
Hm?
Was that Arthur?
Now we'll have to change the schedule.
It looks like it's coming out onto the parade route now!
They'll be marched around the school
building first, then make their way down here!
Even though it's a vintage Knightmare, it's handling well.
Okay, the route's all set, so...
Shake time!
What a mess!
He's taking her straight to the stage!
Let me at least see who you are!
Huh?
I'm not cut out for this sort of thing.
Release the hounds!
Over there!
The Knight of Seven, Suzaku Kururugi!
He's arrived, along with our
Andes-grown Ultimate Tomatoes!
Suzaku, come on over!
You're the one we've been waiting for!
Uh. Except that...
There's a different person piloting!
Ah! Whoa!
Team Leader 1! Turn around, and look up at me!
Yes, what is it, Vice President?
Employ system pattern rouge!
Now going to system pattern rouge.
Release fire-extinguishing gas.
Initiating.
What's the matter?
Is it really that much of a surprise?
What the hell's going on here?! Ugh!
Sorry. Are you okay?
Uh, oh no, it was my fault.
Ah!
That was...
Huh?
Recorded. Thank you, Miss.
No problem. You're welcome.
Oh, Arthur.
Well, sometimes you just get
these little filler incidents in life.
And that's fine!
So then?
The person who saw you was from the Swim Club?
I think it may have been the teacher.
Villetta?!
I didn't get her name.
But the weird thing is that I think I remember seeing her
at the festival last year with Ohgi.
Ohgi and Villetta?
Minami said that Ohgi might have had a collaborator
who reported directly to him.
Ohgi kept... a secret from me?
When it comes to these sorts of things,
you're really very thick.
The truth is...
That's it, Rolo? You've turned traitor?
Villetta Nu.
The woman who was awarded the
rank of baron for ascertaining Zero's real identity.
But unknown to most,
you're connected to the Black Knights.
Not true! I never betrayed...
Kaname Ohgi.
If word of your relationship with him ever got out,
you'd have to relinquish that
title you worked so hard to earn.
Why not be reborn as someone new?
Oh, yes. Shirley gave me this to give to you,
so the timing works out nicely.
Happy birthday, Coach Villetta.
It seems I owe you another debt.
I simply used my diplomatic immunity.
Besides, I'd like to repay
my debt to you as quick as I can.
Then, may I ask another favor of you?
I don't like to be in collusion with you.
I'd like to get in contact with the High Eunuchs.
The only one left to defeat is Suzaku.
Lelouch?
Mm?
Shouldn't the guest of honor be at the main stage?
Hm? No.
Everyone seems to be having a fine time without me.
Besides, I want to discuss something with you.
What is it?
Well you see...
I'm aspiring to become the Knight of One.
Whoa! That's the greatest knight in the entire empire...
The Knight of One is bestowed the privilege
of choosing one of the Britannian Areas for his own.
I intend to have Japan. I'll take this area for myself.
Lelouch, I've lost too much;
Precious friends and a woman who no one can ever replace.
By acquiring power,
I will never again lose anyone else I care about.
And then, the Japanese people won't need Zero any more.
Hm? Indirect rule, huh?
You wanna make it a protectorate?
You can ask this person. They'll know.
Huh?
The new viceroy who's coming
to take charge of Area 11 next week.
You think a student should speak to the viceroy?
It's Kururugi.
Yes. He's standing right here in front of me.
Yes.
What do I say? How awkward.
This is such an important person.
Hello? Big Brother?
Lelouch, is that you?!
It's me! Nunnally! Can you hear me?
I'm coming there to be the viceroy!
Um, is there something wrong?
Lelouch, it's Nunnally. Your sister.
At this very moment, Nunnally is
on the other end of the phone.
Does she know that I'm Zero? No, I doubt it.
Then this must be a trick
Suzaku is perpetrating against me.
Because if I respond to my little sister,
he'll know that my memories have returned.
He's using Nunnally to trap me!
Nunnally! Suzaku!
No matter how he wears the face of a friend,
his true face is that of the fiend
who sold me to the emperor!
There mere thought that he's been at my sister's side!