The world continues moving on,
thanks to miracles which Zero has performed.
The world is being reborn,
thanks to actions which Zero has taken.
Yes. The world is moving to the next stage, as it should.
Against conflicting emotions, Zero must carry on.
For the hands which mark time cannot be stopped.
The Emperor's gone?
He's disappeared?
He has.
I've just received word from
Prime Minister Schneizel about it.
It's important that we restrict
this information to only those present here.
He also said that this situation is only
known to a handful of people in the homeland.
What on earth happened to him?
There is no news on the investigation.
Hold on a minute.
Won't this affect our plans to
attack the Chinese Federation?
If His Majesty isn't present to issue
a declaration of war, then we can't do anything!
And there's domestic security.
If the Numbers were to learn of this situation,
you had better have new policies in place.
Well I'd...
People expect action from authority figures!
Uh, Miss Lohmeyer?
Do you think you'd like to handle it alone?
Sorry. I meant no disrespect.
Is this for the best?
With the Emperor gone,
Nunnally should be safe for now, but...
I've done it!
The actions which Britannia
has taken prove the Emperor is absent.
It's seems he is truly trapped in the other realm.
Though I am concerned about what he said before,
I am content simply knowing that Nunnally is safe.
Um, what should I be doing now?
Let's see now...
Sing me a song while hopping on one foot
and wearing your clothes inside out.
Yes. Right away, master.
Wha...?
No, wait! I was kidding!
I'm sorry!
Please don't beat me hard again!
Her mind has completely reverted.
She's now only the slave girl
before the power of Geass came.
Don't you worry.
I would never do anything to harm you at all.
It's the truth. I promise you.
Master Lelouch.
Yes, Jeremiah. What is it?
I see. You got her out of there,
inside of the Sutherland's cockpit.
Please forgive me.
You ordered me to destroy them all,
but killing a member of the
Britannian royal family was just...
Forget it.
Or rather, I should say, well done.
Tell me, Lelouch, what is it you are
seeking within that accursed power?
What am I seeking?
I'm seeking to save a sister that I adore.
How dare you!
Kinoshita.
Captain Asahina!
I see. Bloodstains.
I'd sure like to know... What was Zero doing?
Well I...
...won't say a thing.
Those are Zero's orders.
The details are top secret.
Even General Tohdoh isn't allowed to know.
You toss real confident weight around for a newbie.
Value in this team is gained by confidence.
And confidence is earned by
a Black Knight from Zero himself.
That's some trusting value system.
I'm so sorry!
What the hell's that mean?!
There's no need to apologize!
It's either right or wrong!
You think you can flip on the
good guy routine whenever you like?!
Not when I'm this pissed off!
Kallen Kouzuki's a soldier, not a sideshow!
Hmph! I'm mostly pissed off because you're not resisting.
There. Put me to death.
An inmate assaulting a Knight of the Round
should be a good reason enough for anyone.
No, I won't.
Because I'm the one who did wrong.
"No, I won't."
I hate you!
And so,
by ratifying this charter, it will give birth to an
alliance that will rival the Holy Britannian Empire.
And its name shall be...
...The United Federation Of Nations!
It's wonderful, Master Zero!
There are exiled regimes
throughout the Britannian colonies.
Some have agreed to participate.
With this move, we've finally earned
a just cause to launch a war of liberation!
A just cause to launch war...
If the forthcoming operation to
recapture Japan is indeed successful,
then other undecided nations
will join us in a chain reaction.
Mm-hmm.
And it will succeed,
but we must form the U.F.N. before Britannia can act!
Time decides our victory or defeat.
I ask only that you cooperate on the focus of our plan.
I know representatives here must
discuss the needs of their individual countries.
But remember...
What you decide will change the course of world history!
Hi, everyone! How are you?
I'm so sorry!
It's an up-and-coming one-woman
festival with Milly Ashford here!
Well you're not exactly alone, you know.
Guess what, audience?
We're going to the jungle, right here in the city!
We are?
Animal time!
And that means hot topics with Trend Watch!
I brought you some food to eat.
It's only me.
Huh?
It's called pizza.
I'd think you be hungry by now.
I really wanted you to have some,
so I asked Sugiyama to help me out.
You don't remember, do you?
Go ahead. Try it.
It's all right. You can eat.
Okay!
It's good, isn't it?
Oh, yes, yes! It's really, really good!
Thought so.
I'm glad you like it.
Prez, I'm not sure that's the
way to start out a new career.
I see. That's right.
You don't even know what this is, do you?
Troubled mind?
Nothing but trouble.
Even though I chose it myself.
Decisions I made eight years back.
Do you still place trust in him?
The you from eight years ago?
Are you asking if the choices I made were foolish?
Memories that people have are always vague.
No point in believing in them.
I'd have to disagree with that.
But I know it.
In my case...
I kept a diary from nine years ago.
I don't remember anything from it at all.
Huh?
And there's more I don't trust.
The data I stored doesn't match any memories I have.
Could that be it?
The Emperor's Geass?
But why use it on Anya?
Even recent things.
My memories don't match the recordings at all.
Like when fighting with the Chinese Federation,
they don't...
What do people value most, Sir Kururugi the traitor?
Their own life, of course.
So I see that you've returned
from the Belarusian Front, Sir Bradley.
It's the Knight of Ten.
I see your skill at courting with
the new ladies is still intact.
Princess Massacre wasn't enough for you?
Speak another untrue word of her name
and you will have to face me in a duel, sir.
Oh. It's seems you've forgotten.
I'm very well known as the "Genius of Homicide."
Perhaps being only a Number without
any true bloodline has dulled your...
They sent the Galahad?!
Both of you! Cease your squabbling!
The Knight of One.
But why would they send Bismarck Waldstein here?
Anya, a foolish question.
Obviously The Black Knights will invade Area 11 first.
Luciano.
I've brought the Valkyrie Squadron for that here as well.
I have also readied Gareths for this event.
Now is the time for us to join our forces
under the command of Prince Schneizel.
So save your solo flaunting for the battlefield!
Hah! I understand it well.
Whatever you say, my lord.
So Lelouch always acted like that, huh?
My big brother can be so stubborn at times,
but actually, he's really very kind.
My brother Naoto was like that as well.
Oh! I'd heard we had captured the Black Knight Ace,
but I didn't expect to find such a lovely young girl.
I don't believe I gave you
permission to enter this area, Sir Bradley.
My apologies, Your Highness.
Well... So you're the Vampire of Britannia?
Yes.
It's a shame we're not on a battlefield
or I could savor your blood as well.
Pity.
So, are you here to finish off the hostage?
Not so.
Hostages have only one value I care for.
It seems to hold dear its own life.
And while alive,
one can do anything he has a whim for to its body.
Have you no sense of pride, Dear Sir Bradley?
Threatening an unarmed, imprisoned woman.
The naïve child. Still getting by on family laurels?
Hmm...
Tell me.
Are you implying that it's easy to become
a Knight Of The Round on family recognition alone?
Huh?!
Mount the F.L.E.I.J.A onto the Lancelot?
Well the intention was for
Suzaku to pilot the Guren, but...
The Guren?
Sorry, he's right.
I got so carried away I forgot.
It's just Lloyd and I got so
wrapped up in our little hobby, we...
Hobby?
Rakshata's mechanisms are quite easy to tinker with.
Now it's so souped-up it can't be flown!
End result, you're our little devicer again!
Excuse me, Professor Lloyd,
now that you mention the Lancelot...
You wouldn't mix up a strategic
weapon with a tactical one, would you?
I have thought it through.
Any matter caught within the primary area of effect field
will be annihilated by the
F.L.E.I.J.A.'s rapid sphere collapse.
Hold on!
You want Suzaku to fire a weapon like that?!
He'd kill his own people. A massacre.
Suzaku, you don't consider
yourself an Eleven anymore, right?
That's why I want to entrust the F.L.E.I.J.A. to you.
You'd give me that burden?
You were Princess Euphemia's knight,
so naturally...
Mm-mmm, Nina, darling.
A fine quandary might just kill Suzaku,
and take you along as well!
Yes. We've finished preparations
for our worldwide broadcast.
Lin Xing-ke and General Tohdoh are in the waiting area.
Right.
Very good.
After I meet with the Indian and Guinean members,
expect me at the assembly.
Do not leave this room.
Uh, okay.
And so, later...
Later?
I mean, see you later.
Huh?
I'll be off, then.
R-Regarding the union of the nations charter,
I will leave explanation of it to Representative
of the Supreme Council, Kaguya Sumeragi.
Are you all right?
We could always...
No! I already got the...
You're the Empress. We know you can.
Good thing we followed old Zero, isn't it, buddy?!
Sure is.
By the way, where's C.C.?
I heard that she was still feeling ill.
Morning sickness, huh?
Congrats to Papa Zero!
Tamaki-san, maybe you've had a little too much.
Bring on the good stuff!
A soldier wearing makeup is disgraceful.
I have to make you look good.
Um, sir...
After this current situation is over...
I'd like to propose a request to Kyoshiro Tohdoh that...
Great! You're finally here!
Is this any time to be running late again?
I know. Sorry, guys.
Ohgi. Did you oversleep again?
Too slow.
Sorry I'm late, but the truth is, uh...
We're all here, let's go.
It's our day to change all of the history books, right?
We are coming live to you right over Horai Island.
Where the ratification ceremony
for the United States Charter is about to begin!
To help viewers understand this development,
the ceremony and ratification of this new charter
will create a federation of nations
that will rival our own empire.
As parts of the now dissipating E.U.
are joining as well, it will have a great unified power.
Included from the E.U. are: Poland, Italy...
Can't reach soldiers like Suzaku...
No brainer, but why can't I contact Rolo or Lelouch?
The Black Knights have convinced
all of these these representative nations to participate.
Therefore the leader behind this must be Zero.
In short, the U.F.N. will most
likely be an enemy to Britannia.
Military forces are deployed
in Kyushu, Chugoku, and Hokuriku.
As everyone watching this broadcast has witnessed,
all 47 nations have just
ratified the United States Charter.
Please stay tuned...
Lord Guilford, we've finished
preparations for your troops review.
Very good. On my way.
Yes?
Don't worry, if it's about the troop review I...
Lord Guilford.
Orange boy?
They're forming a union of nations, just as you said.
But the militaries of each country
will never be able to work together.
They'll just be an unruly mob.
No. There is an option.
...and those of international accords,
this article takes precedence.
Finally, article 17 of the United States Charter.
All ratifying nations do now declare
to abandon native military power forever.
Abandon military power?
Are they mad?
To guarantee security,
member nations have agreed to employ a fighting force
not affiliated with any one country.
They have contracted the Black Knights.
We hereby accept.
Our acceptance also allows for
U.F.N. funding and personnel involvement.
In return, we will become the shield
to defend every member nation,
and its sword to oppose any external foe!
The option, right?
Disturbances in this world are caused
by military powers of disparate nations.
The U.F.N. shall only use military force
in accordance with a full
resolution by the supreme council.
And with that, I shall put forth the first motion.
Japan is being held by an unjust foreign power,
and the U.S.J. have asked for our help
to free them from this occupation.
I request that the Black Knights be dispatched at once.
All those in favor please stand up.
And so with overwhelming majority,
under U.F.N. resolution number 1,
the Black Knights shall now go forth to liberate Japan.
So be it!
Under U.F.N. resolution number 1,
our first operational objective shall be...
...Japan!
Our Japan.
And now we shall take it back!
Might rescue Kallen, also.
Huh? Yeah, we'll do that.
Hear me, Zero!
What?!
The system's hacked?!
It's coming in from 14 external paths!
The emperor!
Well. Look who's back.
Was this fake disappearance your doing, father? A charade?
Switch to the auxiliary lines!
Cut the link, dammit!
We can't! They've got those as well!
Zero. You thought this foolishness would surprise me?
Impossible! He's still alive?!
However, it matters not.
This charter you've made is a child's note.
The E.U., once a third of the world, is now dead.
You've only helped distinguish Britannia on a map
from the rest of the pitiful dirt.
The situation is very simple and clear.
For in the end whoever succeeds in this battle
shall gain control of the entire world.
Very well. Have at me, Zero.
I'm ready.
So will you win it all now, Zero,
or will you lose everything?
Time to learn the gambles of war.
All hail Britannia!
All hail Britannia! All hail Britannia!
Long live Japan!
All hail Britannia!
The emperor is still alive?
Um, excuse me.
Welcome back.
This isn't good.
Not good at all.
I have to rescue Nunnally at once!
Maybe I could use Cornelia some way.
No! The hostage ploy would have no effect on him.
Perhaps use Jeremiah or Rolo?
No, I can't!
And Geass won't work on him!
Should I reveal to the world that Zero's Lelouch?
No!
If the Black Knights found out their leader
were an enemy prince, I'd lose that too!
And rescuing Nunnally is useless
if there's no country that will accept us!
Dammit! What should I do?!
Um, master, I kept this last piece so you could have it.
You left without having breakfast and must be hungry.
So please, if you...
Be quiet!
Hey...
Forgive me, master, I'll clean it up at once!
No. Leave it there!
Careful now, you're bleeding.
Uh... No. It's fine.
I'm okay. I get cut up all the time.
All the time?
Bleeding feels even better when it's cold.
It feels warm on your outside.
It stings a bit, but only on the outside,
and that's always better than hurt on your inside.
It's just...
Any kind of warmth helps make you try to keep going.
Oh, lookit, master, you're shaking.
Are you cold now?
Yeah, maybe. Maybe I am.
And the hurt on the inside...
How's it healed?
You just think of...
...some friends.
I've never actually had one.
Not like families, that always comes and goes.
I mean someone special who stands beside you.
At least I guess that's what I've heard that friends do...
Yes, they do.
I'm right?
A friend will stand by your side?
Exactly right.
A friend is always there.
I'm here.
It's Lelouch.
I know.
Um, so... Have you seen the news?
About Area 11 becoming a battlefield again?
Yes.
The Tokyo Settlement. It'll be in danger?
Depends... on your decisions.
Huh?
Lelouch. Are you Zero?
Yes, I am.
I am Zero.
Now tell me why an enemy of Britannia is calling.
Help me. Please save Nunnally.
The emperor has been using her
as hostage to try and lure me into his trap!
Don't you see?
That's why I've had to operate in secret!
Please, Suzaku!
You're the only person I can turn to now!
How dare you!
You think that request means anything to me?!
No, I don't.
But I need your help. I need it now!
Always so selfish.
Yes! You're all I have.
The only friend I can turn to!
Suzaku!
Protect her. It's Nunnally.
My heart's begging!
Very well, then.
However... One condition.
I will protect Nunnally.
But you must come to Area 11 by yourself,
where she is.
The place will be the Kururugi shrine.
The two of us meet there.
Alone.
With things as there are,
should I have forced my way through
to save Nunnally much earlier?
But if I had,
I'd be forced to treat her as an enemy hostage.
And she will never come to me of her own free will.
With all this hatred united against Britannia,
I can't stop the malice that
will now be directed at Nunnally.
It's all too dangerous.
Right. Only one chance left.
All I have left is trust.
I need to trust Suzaku!