Is that you, Lelouch?
It's me, Nunnally.
If your memory hasn't returned,
you won't know who she is.
Go on, Lelouch, let's hear your answer!
Suzaku, you've got me trapped.
Um. This is my brother, isn't it?
I can't do this! I can't lie to Nunnally!
I... I... Uh?
Rolo?
Good work. Keep him like that.
You'll have to hurry. Don't forget the time limit.
I know. Nunally, listen to me.
Lelouch! It is you!
For right now, we have to act like we're strangers.
It's necessary! Just follow my lead!
I'm going to come for you. I swear it!
And so, until then...
Until then, I love you, Nunnally!
Uh, you're confusing me with someone else.
That's right, I'm just a student at the school here.
Lelouch, your memory really hasn't come back?
Yes. I beg your pardon.
Forgive me.
When I heard you was a good friend of Suzaku's,
I guess I just jumped to conclusions.
It's just I...
No, please, it's an honor for me
to speak with a royal princess.
Um, could you please put Suzaku back on?
Yes, Your Highness.
Forgive me, Nunnally.
I didn't mean to cause a misunderstanding.
No, it's all right.
He just seemed so similar that it surprised me.
Well, um, I'll see you when I get to Area 11.
Don't underestimate the threat.
He may be at a disadvantage,
but, we're still dealing with Zero!
You can be sure he has some plan underway.
Such a cowardly response.
And they call you the "Spearhead of the Empire". Hmph.
Fortunately, Viceroy Nunnally has me to protect her.
Your services won't be needed.
But, general, Zero is...
Dead, Lord Guilford!
Zero was killed last year!
The Zero we face now is just using his name!
Princess Cornelia would regret seeing
your contemptible fear for this cheap imposter?
Speaking of regret.
Earl Asplund.
Sorry we're late.
Adjusting Lancelot took longer than we thought it would!
It's been quite a while, Earl Asplund.
That's because I'm working
directly under little Charlie now!
Are you referring to His Majesty!
Please forgive him, sir!
Lloyd, please!
Hm? Did I say something wrong?
I see that you haven't changed.
As for the item we discussed...
Yes, It comes to us via Prince Schneizel.
It's rather nice, having a second prince to call on.
You have my thanks.
Unbelievable!
This prodigal aristocrat is
serving as Lord Kururugi's guardian!
He'd better not interfere with
efforts to educate the new viceroy.
Did Suzaku lie to me?
But, my own brother... I don't understand.
Has something happened between them?
The new viceroy is set to arrive at
Area 11 tomorrow to take up her post.
The name and background of the new viceroy
still has not been released to the public.
The big question's the
Chinese Federation consulate, right?
You mean regarding Zero?
As there has been no formal announcement,
some think Chief Consul Gao-Hai may be acting on his own.
The consul general's standing will
depend upon the balance of power...
W-What about the stand-off in Area 11?
Oh, I'm afraid I don't know the details.
Can you tell me anything about the outside world?
I've never gone beyond the walls of this palace.
That's because this Forbidden City in the
Luoyang Capital is the very center of the world, Empress.
But...
I'm going to go outside and see what's happening.
Huh?
The truth is, I came today to say goodbye to you.
Oh, no!
Not now, when I've finally made a real friend.
I'm very sorry,
but you know my husband is waiting for me.
The supplies were successfully received in Niigata.
I see.
However, there's no way to
get them into the consulate now.
As expected.
Nunnally is going to be the new viceroy.
Will you be able to fight her? Your sister?
Fight? Nunnally?
Is that some kind of joke?
Then you're just going to leave her alone?
Out of the question.
If nothing's done, Nunnally will be used
as a political tool, just like she was before!
A girl who can't walk and can't see...
Do they plan to use her as a pawn, then throw her away?
I'm doing all this to keep that from happening!
That's why I formed the Black Knights!
I became Zero for Nunnally's sake!
I'm well aware that your
sister's your entire reason for living.
However...
I am going to create a world
where Nunnally can live happily!
To do that, I will obliterate Britannia!
You mentioned, V.V.
Is he in the Britannian homeland?
I don't know that much about him.
However, I know that he's your father's first ally:
Emperor Charles of Britannia's chief confederate.
Confederate?
Long ago, they made a pact.
I shall slay the god!
Yes, that is our binding contract.
Tell me, Charles, why didn't you tell Nunnally
about Zero's true identity. And about Geass.
It wasn't necessary for her to know.
You know, Charles, you really are still a child.
Perhaps I am, big brother.
Where's Viceroy Nunnally?
She's in the garden.
Even if she came to the bridge...
I guess there'd be no point
The Black Knights?!
They're not here?!
Right. We only just confirmed it ourselves.
I'll give you all the information I have.
That way, it should be crystal clear that
my country has no hostile intentions toward Britannia.
Did Zero go with them?!
It appears so.
They took their knightmares with them and they vanished.
We're guessing they left through an underground level.
To where?
No idea. That's all I have.
They wouldn't attack Nunnally?
We've been had.
Should we... strike back.
The Black Knights!
The objective of this operation
is the capture of the new viceroy!
No matter what happens,
she absolutely must not be harmed!
Keep her safe, is that clear!
Roger!
Tamaki, what are you doing?!
Amateurs!
Bringing land-based units for an aerial mission... Ah!
Surface flares will have no effect on our defense.
Surround and attack now!
All right, General Tohdoh, the rest is up to you.
Right. Good luck, Deputy-Commander.
Impossible!
They're landing on top of us?!
Two more enemy Knightmares have landed on our main wing!
They're on our escorts as well!
Send our aerial forces to...
You took the bait, commander.
I figured you'd concentrate your air power on the smoke.
The obvious response.
Now we can focus on the flagship.
All right! We're withdrawing!
Deploy the remaining air ships.
Have the escort ships fire as well!
But sir, the enemy is targeting our float units.
We can't shoot back because our shields are up!
Then how can we defend this ship?!
If I'd known this was possible,
I'd have brought Lord Guilford along!
It'll take an hour for reinforcements
to reach us from the Tokyo settlement!
What if a Knightmare makes it inside?
Then we crash.
Our job now is to help the survivors...
What... is that?
Die!
Ya.
Understood.
Nunnally, I'm coming to save you.
Now, Samurai Leap over Floating Boats attack!
You can put your shields up,
but once we get inside, your finished.
Looks like they're running out of air strength too.
You'll end up a skinned rabbit.
Don't get cocky.
Right, right. I'll stick to basics, but, huh?
Reinforcements from Tokyo? So soon?
No, it looks like their rear guard.
And, they have float units.
Knightmares!
It can't be! That machine is...
Now, Let's bring down the curtain.
Output on all units is normal.
Isn't mass production nice?
Well, I'm not so sure about this.
Did Prince Scneizel really approved the budget?
If he didn't, he'll notice it pretty soon.
What?!
You didn't tell him what you were doing?
I don't need to fly for this.
You have the right instincts, but the wrong Knightmare.
Sorry! I'm out.
Damn Guilford, acting without orders!
But he saved us, my lord.
Yes, and he'll take all of the credit for it!
All tasks at hand have been cleared.
And now, the tide of battle shall turn!
Nunnally...
Look! Zero's inside!
What are those guards doing?
Viceroy Nunnally, it's Zero!
I'm informing General Upson now.
Their reunion is starting. It must not be disturbed.
Nunnally...
We're together again. At last.
You're, Zero, aren't you? The terrorist.
Have you come to kill me as well?
Like you killed my brother Clovis and my sister Euphie?
Even so, will you wait just a moment, please?
I think that what you're doing is wrong!
It's a Harken!
Hit him now, Kouzuki!
Right!
Okay, it's discipline time!
What a weird-looking fighter plane.
Even so...!
A Knightmare?!
I'm finished. Sorry.
That just leaves four enemy units.
The Knights of the Round as well!
I'll never bear this disgrace.
Now what?!
Starboard escort ship has lost control!
What?!
It's on a collision course!
Turn the ship!
We'll never make it!
We're going to crash!
The Mordred always handles things in its own unique way.
Anya, don't do that again, okay?
We don't want to kill the viceroy now, do we?
But I saved her.
Lloyd, how's the Lancelot?
Ready and waiting for you! Come and get it!
General! What are you doing in that gun turret?
At this rate, I'm going to be demoted!
I have to do something to prove myself!
I'll kill the Black Knights!
You fool! You shot your own engines!
Right now, Zero is standing in front of me.
Lelouch, give me the courage I need.
It's Britannia that is wrong.
The emperor believes that might is always right.
Do you approve of that?
Well...
Viceroy Nunnally, you're just being used.
You're saying they sent a blind,
crippled girl to win everyone's sympathy?
Then, you're wrong.
Hm?
I asked them to send me. That's why I'm here.
Where's Zero?
We can't contact him because of the ECCM effects.
I want to rendezvous with Chiba
and Kouzuki and scout inside the ship.
But the ship's going to crash.
Do you think you have time for that?
It's very...
Senba!
I don't like picking on those
who are weaker than me, but...
Never thought a place like this...
Senba!
Using land units for an aerial attack?
That's not your kind of tactic, Toudo.
You requested it?
I think with a peaceful approach,
I can make the world a gentler place.
That's why I want to carry out Euphie's plan
to create the Specially Administrated Zone of Japan.
You'd have that return?!
Zero, won't you please try to help me to rebuild it?
People can start over! Please!
Zero's coming to steal Nunnally away,
but there's been no word
from the Office of Secret Intelligence.
So, am I fighting Zero or Lelouch?
Sir Kururugi, I'm confirming the data now.
The number 2 float unit on
Viceroy Nunnally's Flagship has shut down.
The number 3 and 4 float units are interlinked,
so a case theta has occured.
To sum that up, we'll all be swimming in the ocean soon.
Uh. Except for general Upson,
who's regrettably didn't make it.
Right now, rescuing the viceroy has top priority!
Initiating search for her wheelchair beacon.
Starting E.C.M. signal noise cleanup.
Phase, preset. Sending the layout of the ship's interior.
Confirming Data link.
Complete.
Transmit the viceroy's location as soon as it's known.
Channel M.B., roger!
Lancelot Conquista...
Now launch!
Launching!
Kallen, I have to save Nunnally. Nothing else matters now.
I won't ask for your forgiveness... any more.
Kouzuki, hide! Get inside of the ship!
I can't. Not until everyone's gotten away!
What the hell!
Kouzuki!
Pull the eject lever, Kouzuki!
No use! It isn't working!
Defective equipment at a time like this!
Tag, you're dead.
I'm falling!
Forgive me, Guren...
Mother, Naoto...
What a perfect position!
Wha...? Rakshata?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I have the new Black Knight glide wing pack for you.
You did review the manual I sent?
Uh, sure. I'm good to go!
All right, let's try it out then.
We'll give you the basic guidance from here.
Please rescue Master Zero.
Uh, right!
Opening number 3 launch chamber.
Connection signal with Guren Mk-II, confirmed.
Take to the skies, my soaring glide wings!
Rotate!
Guidance signal, confirmed.
Contact angle, aligned.
Link up.
Linking up!
Fly!
Armor piercing artillery, right arm unit!
Right arm unit decelerating for linkup.
Transmission neuron 0.5 to 0.8 M.M.P.
No obstacles detected.
Elastic muscles 1 through 5 are operating normally.
Activation of shock control, confirmed. Linking up.
Kallen, please.
No matter how many enemies are coming...!
Our unit will go after Tohdoh!
Right, and we'll protect the viceroy.
Huh? In the sky?
The Black Knights have a float system, too?
Kouzuki! Save Zero!
I'm on it, sir!
Oh? You've gained wings and a shield, huh? So what!
If this Guren doesn't work perfectly, then I'm finished.
Well, we don't have much choice, try shooting it.
You've got a point, there!
From long range?!
I can do it! With this Guren Flight-Enabled Version!
Nice one.
Suzaku, get to the viceroy!
Don't let your guard down!
That's the pilot who defeated Lord Jeremiah!
The one who beat Orange boy?
Come on!
Well, look at that.
As good as the Knights of the Round?
We'll see, right now.
Don't underestimate the Guren!
Dirty shoes.
I'll take care of you guys later.
Gad!
It can fire wide-range, too?!
What's its total energy?!
The same amount, but scattered.
With the internal damage it caused,
those units won't be able to function for a while.
So, what's with that knightmare?
Uh-uhh. It's all the pilot.
I shouldn't have held back on my attack.
Kallen, Why would you come back under these conditions?
Is it that Zero's on the ship already?!
MOVE IT!
Have a taste of the Gefjun Net!
We have a countermeasure for this!
You're still stuck where you are!
No way!
It can't be more powerful
than and advanced Yggdrasil Drive!
Suzaku!
We've located the viceroy!
She's in the garden space to the rear of the main bridge!
But hurry! Now there's only
47 seconds till the ship crashes!
I promise, I'll save her!
Damn!
Kallen! Forget about Suzaku!
Save Master Zero!
I understand, but where?!
Tsk! There's no time left.
I'll have to use the Core Luminous Cone.
Go!
What do I do?
I can't reveal Zero's identity to her,
but I can't take her by force either.
I can see now that would traumatize her!
Suzaku!
Escape with me!
Nunnally!
Suzaku!
No! Not after he sold me out to the emperor!
Suzaku! Down here!
Were you frightened?
Forgive me! It's all right now!
Nunnally with Suzaku!
Zero! Not this time!
Nunnally!
Eight years ago, because our mother was murdered,
because we were abandoned by Britannia,
protecting Nunnally became everything to me.
Cleaning the house, making our dinner everything.
But now! I'm a fool!
Nunnally has dreams of her own.
She has chosen a path for herself.
It's so obvious. So simple.
What should I do?