This is the first time in eight years I've seen your face.
The face of a brother and a murderer.
And I wear the same face, as well, don't I, Lelouch?
Then...
It's been you firing the F.L.E.I.J.A.s up until now.
Yes. I wanted to stop it all. To stop you.
I would have done whatever I had to,
even if it meant killing my big brother.
That's why I can't allow you
to have control of the F.L.E.I.J.A.s...
Why I can't hand this key to you.
And I wouldn't even if you...
Even if you used your Geass on me!
Use Geass on Nunnally?
It's true.
Time after time, I've wanted to use it on her.
At the very least, I wanted
to use it to cure her blindness.
The power of the king...
But Nunnally was the reason for everything I've done,
so I could never use Geass' power
of absolute submission on her.
But now... No, I can't!
If I resort to twisting my own sister's will...
...then I'm...!
Kallen... Are you determined to defy me?
It's clear to me now that I misjudged you, Suzaku.
Hm?
Even though we're on opposite sides
and our methods differ from one another,
I always thought you cared about Japan in your way.
But now...!
There's something that I...
...that Lelouch and I have to do.
I see...
You really crave power that much?
In that case...
In that case, what?
You mustn't be allowed to live, Suzaku.
I'm going to defeat you and stop Lelouch!
No, that won't happen!
You having any second thoughts about not running away?
Just where exactly would I be running to?
You have a point, Rivalz.
What I wish for...
...is to enjoy fun-filled days with the old gang again,
the way we used to.
Mm. I do miss them.
You, power without a master!
You, who has to have something to depend on.
A weak man!
Stop, please! You're too badly wounded!
No, I have to take responsibility for starting this!
Because that's what allows me the right to lead others!
Lelouch, you have no right to seize control of the world.
You, of all people, who took the name Zero
then bent the will of so many in order to serve your own!
Are you saying we would have
been better off to remain in hiding?
Did you want a future of living
in constant fear of assassination?
This was for your future, too, Nunnally.
My future?! When did I ever say that I wanted this?!
Lelouch...
I would have been perfectly satisfied
by just living with you!
Don't you see?
Our reality is restricted by all sorts of things!
Our whole history is struggle!
That's the reason I've been
fighting on the side of the resistance!
You could have used the system to achieve your ideals!
But what about the others?!
Those people who aren't allowed into the system?
How will they ever be able to
voice their objections to anything?!
You...!
Don't you dare look down on others, you elitist!
What about those who've no choice
but to join the system?!
What's fair?!
When you follow the methods of an aggressor,
then you're only serving to legitimize them.
But, if you go into battle now, you'll die!
Why you...! And you call yourself a...!
I apologize.
Huh?
This is the only way I know how to live.
Kyoshiro!
Why do people always have to fight?!
I fight because there is something that I must protect!
It may be that we can no longer find
morality or a sense of dignity in our warfare.
Regardless, I still needed to belong somewhere.
For that reason alone, we fought.
Naoto... This is really the best thing for us?
You know what they say,
war is the mother of invention.
Nonsense, Earl of Pudding.
You don't care one bit whether or not
your invention benefits mankind.
Nina, was it? What about you, huh?
I was just... doing whatever I could.
You see, we simply didn't want it to happen again.
Oh?
However, people are subject to weakness.
That's right! Even I have dreams, don't I?!
But now they're telling me I don't have any right to them!
They don't think I'm able to fight, but I can!
Why does everyone treat me like a fool?!
Poor guy.
I've seen it before.
I've seen it over and over.
Human history is one of struggle. Even so...
The world and the people in it...
They'll never be what we want them to be!
So now you'll force them?!
That's your solution?!
That's plain...
Despicable!
Using Geass, a power that manipulates the minds
of people and violates their human dignity.
Then what about the Damocles?
So would you agree that's a despicable method
that forces people to obey?!
The Damocles...
...will become the symbol of their hatred.
All their hatred will be focused here.
That way, people can move toward the future.
I see. You have the same idea, Nunnally.
In that case...
Lelouch vi Britannia commands you!
Hand over the Damocles key to me now!
No!
No, I mustn't give it to you! I mustn't do it!
All the sins...
...you've... committed!
Take this. It's yours now.
Why you impudent...!
Memorized recording complete.
Not quite!
Fire!
Memorize this! Memorize Jeremiah Gottwald!
Commit it to memory, because that's the
memorable name of the man who has defeated you!
Memory? What memory?
I remember nothing, I have no memories.
No memories? Could it be...?
C'mon, Tristan, move it! Just let me fly, will ya?
The radiant wave surger's out of ammo.
Now my shield energy is exhausted, too?
Big deal!
I can't beat her!
Even using the Geass I'm cursed with!
Your strength is unimaginable, Kallen!
My machine has better specs than yours, yet...
Why...? While you're this strong...
Do the right thing!
Let's end this once and for all!
If only you had justice on your side!
What happened?
You mean I didn't get him, then?
You're wrong. You got me, all right... Kallen.
You won. You beat him, Kallen.
Nunnally...
...you've grown up following your
own thoughts, without help from others.
Which means, I am now free to follow the path
I must take to my destiny.
I thank you.
I love you, little sister.
Huh?
You used your Geass on me, didn't you?!
Come back!
Stop, Lelouch! Wait...
You've become a demon, Lelouch!
Despicable!
Cowardly!
How can you? How can you be so cruel?
The traitorous knight, Suzaku Kururugi,
has reportedly been killed.
Aren't you going to beg for your life to be spared?
Even for his sake, at least?
Kaguya...
You never knew Lelouch's
true face until recently, isn't that right?
What of it?
Well, in spite of that, you still
understood a bit of his true nature.
So you're obviously a very kind young woman.
Huh?
Attention, entire world!
Hear my proclamation! I am Lelouch vi Britannia,
emperor of the Holy Britannian Empire and your only ruler!
It's not possible!
If Lelouch used a F.L.E.I.J.A., then that means...!
It can't be!
There's no way!
Schneizel has surrendered to me!
As a result of this, I am now in control of both
the Damocles and the F.L.E.I.J.A. weapons!
And even the Black Knights no longer
possess the strength to oppose me now!
If anyone dares to resist my supreme authority,
they shall know the devastating power of the F.L.E.I.A.s!
Those who could challenge
my military rule no longer exist!
Yes! From this day, from this moment forward,
the world belongs to me!
Lelouch vi Britannia commands you!
Obey me, subjects! Obey me, world!
All hail Lelouch!
All hail Lelouch! All hail Lelouch!
And now, just coming into view,
is the 99th and sole emperor
of the Holy Britannian Empire,
His Majesty Lelouch vi Britannia.
Our emperor also carries the
distinction of being CEO of the Black Knights,
as well as the current chairman
of the U.F.N. Supreme Council.
And look at this, too.
Those who foolishly opposed Emperor Lelouch
are being transported to the execution grounds.
During the latest great war, the capital, Pendragon,
was destroyed and countless
soldiers sacrificed their lives,
among them, Sir Suzaku Kururugi, the Knight of Zero.
Now that the E.U. has ratified the
United Federation of Nations charter,
the emperor has allowed us to
complete the grand task of unifying the world!
Glory to His Majesty Lelouch!
All hail Britannia! All Hail Lelouch!
Glory, my ass.
This is just a dictatorship.
Anyone who disobeys him gets killed!
Shh! If the wrong people hear you,
they'll kill your entire family!
I can't believe we have to
broadcast this and call it justice!
Lelouch... is this what you wanted?
What you set out to do?
To control the world? To control every person in it?!
None of you were very bright.
If you hadn't disobeyed Lelouch at that time...
We had to move into the future.
Hm? It's through repeated successes
and failures that we advance.
That not only goes for science, but people, as well.
But that's evolution.
You mean progress, don't you, Earl of Pudding?
About that name you call me...
Hm?
Are you still bitter?
I could be. I could be not.
What's up with them, Professor Lloyd and Miss Rakshata?
Hm?
Did something once happen between them?
It's hardly worth mentioning.
And when I think back on
it now, it wasn't anything at all.
It was just a starting point.
Ohgi!
Do that, and you'll play right into their hands!
But he's...!
What is that?
Zero?!
Huh? Zero?
That's him?! But Lelouch is over there!
Was that it?!
Was that what Lelouch and Suzaku had to do?!
Cease fire!
I'll take care of this interloper!
Hm?!
Onward, masked knight.
Impudent fool!
Heh.
Suzaku... You have to kill me.
You must promise.
You're going through with this?
No matter what?
As planned...
The hatred of the whole world
is now focused directly upon me.
And now, the only thing that remains
is to get rid of me and finally break the cycle of hatred.
The legend of Zero isn't dead.
It lives within the hearts of the Black Knights.
Schneizel will serve Zero, also.
With this, the world will gather,
not for an exchange of force,
but for an exchange of open dialog around one table.
Mankind will be able to move forward into the future.
And that...
Yes.
...is the Zero... Requiem.
We both realized it back in Cs' world.
We knew how humanity was longing for the future.
Hey, Suzaku, Geass power is
similar to a wish, don't you think?
Huh?
It's a request to someone to give you
the power to achieve what you can't on your own.
A wish? No.
Yes. And I'm going to grant a wish
called Geass to all the people everywhere.
For the future of the entire world.
Lelouch...
The price you're going to pay for
using your Geass on them is a dear one.
The only ones who should kill
are those prepared to be killed.
Suzaku... You're going to be a hero, now.
The messiah who saved the world
from Emperor Lelouch vi Britannia,
the enemy of the world.
As Zero.
L... Lelouch...!
The punishment for what you've done shall be this, then...
You will live on... always wearing that mask,
serving as a knight for justice and truth.
ou will no longer live your life as Suzaku Kururugi.
You shall sacrifice the ordinary pleasures
of your life for the benefit of the world...
For eternity...
This Geass... I do solemnly accept.
Lelouch? Are you...?
You mean...
...everything you've done until now...
Oh, big brother, I love you!
Yes... I...
I destroy... the world...
...and create it...
...anew...
You can't leave me!
You can't!
Please open your eyes, big brother! Please...!
Big brother...!
Lelouch the demon is dead!
Free his prisoners!
This isn't good! Everyone, retreat!
Is that... who I think it is?
It's Zero!
Uh?!
It's him!
It's Zero!
It's unfair!
All I wanted and needed to be happy was to be with you!
How can I ever look forward the future without you?
Zero! Zero! Zero!
Well, Lelouch...
The world's gotten a lot better since that eventful day.
All the energy that was once expended on war
has now been directed toward solving hunger and poverty.
As expected, all sorts of hateful and
evil deeds have been blamed on you. Hm...
Maybe that's because people find it
a lot easier to accuse a person with a name,
rather than a piece of technology called Damocles.
Perhaps that's putting it too simply.
But... whatever the reason...
...the world is free of the past
and it's finally able to move forward into the future now.
I wonder if you're laughing right now about how everything
went according to your elaborate strategy.
Nevertheless, there are still plenty of problems
we have to work out for ourselves.
But even so...
I said that Geass was the power of the king
which would condemn you to a life of solitude.
I think maybe that's not quite correct.
Right... Lelouch?