Imperial Calendar, 2018.
As the Holy Britannian Empire continues its drive
to dominate the world, a lone rebel is resurrected.
His name is Zero.
A mysterious girl named C.C.
has given him the power of Geass,
the absolute power to compel anyone to obey him.
Now, Zero is again challenging
the Britannian conquerors of Japan,
the once proud nation now referred to only as Area 11.
As his actions spread like a ripple through the world,
how will they affect the people of this age?
For the moment, no one knows.
What about the O.S.I. forces that broke in first?
No contact with them yet.
The chaff density should be dropping now.
Recon section four!
The terrorists remain embattled inside of Babel Tower.
They're believed to be members of the Black Knights
We've confirmed the presence of enemy Knightmare Frames.
All right, Special Weapons
Batallion Seven will break in from below.
Yes, my lord!
This is hopeless! Let's run for it!
Just hold out a little bit longer.
Wait until Zero can get the layout of the building!
We'll back you up, but you've gotta stand firm!
Lelouch...
It's true, I am Zero.
Zero!
It's Lelouch!
It's the man who's used the Japanese people!
Who's used you!
You wanna defend a man like that?! You?!
Hm.
Zero, this is the end of you.
I was defeated by the old me. By Suzaku.
And by my biggest enemy.
He dragged me before the Britannian Emperor!
The former 17th heir to the
imperial throne, Lelouch vi Britannia.
It's been a long time, hasn't it, my errant son?
How dare you!
You won't use your Geass!
Your Majesty, I have a request.
Please, sire, allow me to join the Knights of the Round,
the 12 strongest knights of the Britannian empire!
As a reward for capturing Zero, is that it?
You!
I told you before, Lelouch,
that I was going to change this world from the inside.
Even if it means selling out your friends?!
That's right.
Tch!
Very well.
I like the answer you just gave him.
Now then, as a Knight of the Round, I order you:
Cover up Zero's left eye.
Yes, Your Majesty.
My unworthy son, who raised the banner
of rebellion although he was a prince.
Still, there's another way we can make use of him.
What?!
I will rewrite your memory:
about being Zero, about the death of your mother,
about the very existence of Nunnally...
No! Geass?!
You'll remember none of it.
You'll just be insignificant.
No, stop!
You're stealing what's most precious to me again!
First my mother, and now you're taking Nunnally?!
Charles zi Britannia engraves into you...
Stop it!
False memories of a false life.
C.C...
Don't even think it.
I'm not the one who gave him his Geass.
Hm.
Where is Nunnally now?
We tried to find your sister,
but with the Black Knights all but destroyed,
that's why...
What about Sayoko?
She and Diethard escaped to the Chinese Federation.
She still doesn't know Zero's true identity.
And she didn't know Nunnally's
real importance, so she can't be blamed.
Hmph.
I'll find the one who gave the
emperor his Geass and then get Nunnally.
I had a younger sister,
but not a younger brother!
So, who is he?
Thank goodness! You're Britannian soldiers, right?
I'm looking for my big brother.
This has the layout of the building
in detail, but the I.D. code I need isn't here.
So we can't commandeer this Knightmare, can we?
What are you doing there?
That's a student uniform, isn't it?
Oh, you're a soldier! Thank goodness!
We need to help this man at once!
Office of Secret Intelligence?
What are the emperor's personal agents doing here?
Good. These reports are accurate.
Calares's forces don't know about me.
So I can use the data in this journal.
There's only one survivor?
Yes. Just you.
What?
That's right.
Now give me your Knightmare.
I understand.
The I.D. code is QR5-YK1D6.
Thank you.
Even though you need direct eye contact,
are those theatrics necessary?
I don't need comments from an immortal witch.
The terrorists are staging a counterattack?
Yes. It seems that they've managed
to capture some of our Knightmares.
That's disgraceful!
Still, their numbers are small.
If I could possibly join the battle...
No. You're still a guest here, and under our protection.
As viceroy, it's my place to go out there.
But...
Hm...
I don't like the spices in Chinese food.
However, I might enjoy it.
Huh?
A manhunt.
Let me see you burst, Britannian!
Well done, Q1! Now, head up to level 21.
P4, block the stairway.
R5, left 30 degrees.
N1, fire a barrage 50 meters ahead,
angled toward the ceiling.
Contact lost with Lord Emilio!
Change I.F.F. codes!
We have! Five times already!
Ortiz unit, wiped out!
Outrageous! Who's directing these terrorists?!
What are you doing?
Viceroy!
So, Zero really is just a student, huh?
Well, he's something special!
Zero supplied more stolen Sutherlands for us to use.
Get on them, fast!
With Zero here, we can win!
He'll make a miracle for us! He will!
Damned terrorists!
Shouldn't Viceroy Calares be making his appearance, soon?
It's going well.
Hm?
Kallen I sent you to level 21.
I wanted to be here by your side.
We're finally alone, just you and me.
It would seem that somebody is
nibbling at the bait we left in Area 11.
Is it C.C., Majesty?
We do not know that.
Kururugi, even among Knights of the Round,
you're the first one ever allowed to enter this place.
Even Schneizel and the others aren't aware of it.
I'm honored, Your Majesty. But, why me?
Because you are the only one of
the Knights of the Round who knows...
About Zero's identity. And Geass.
This place... Is it a shrine?
No, it's not.
This is...
This is a weapon for destroying God.
A weapon?!
It is called the Sword of Akasha.
You, who abandoned Zero at Kamine Island,
what do you wanna tell me?
Lelouch, you were deceiving me
right from the very beginning.
About Zero being your classmate?
Or about my Geass power? Which one has offended you?
Both of them.
Tell me this!
Did you use your Geass on me like you did the others?
Did you twist my mind and my heart
and make me follow you?
Lelouch!
Your mind and your heart are yours alone.
As was your loyalty and admiration for Zero.
Don't move!
Kallen, you should be proud of what you did.
You decided. You made the choice.
You chose...
...Zero.
You don't believe me?
I wanted to believe so much that I'd become a slave...
I see.
But the one that I believe in is Zero!
Just him! It's not you, Lelouch!
Well, fine with me. By the way...
Are you ever going to change out of those clothes?
Don't look at me, you pervert!
Oh? Is that the way you talk to Zero now?
I'm saying it to you, Lelouch!
Very well then.
Go ahead.
Britannian reinforcements are here.
There's zillions of 'em! What do we do?
We can't beat this many! There's no chance.
What's happening over there?
Special Weapons Batallion Four has begun to drop.
Show the Chinese Federation!
Show them our emperor's might!
The overwhelming power of our Holy Britannian Empire!
Yes, my lord!
They're coming in from above, too!
That's right.
Viceroy Calares must have arrived.
Escape would be difficult. That's why...
...I'm going to win.
Assault team two now has control up to floor J!
That leaves only one escape route
the Black Knights can use.
And our main fighting force
is right there waiting for them.
Yes, sir. We just need to drive them out.
Set up a broadcast link quickly.
We'll make the extermination
of these terrorists a media event.
The Britannians must feel certain of their victory.
That clears all the tasks at hand.
All that's left is your level, right?
We'll be finished in ten minutes.
Understood.
We'll make a stand here to buy you time.
What about Diethard's setup?
The system's still running.
Everything is going according to plan.
This is B2!
A single enemy Knightmare is... Agh!
What's wrong?
But, that's... It was just there!
B2? What's going on?
An enemy deactivating his I.F.F.? Operating on his own?
Zero, this is P6! The enemy is...! It's... Agh!
P6!
This is R5! They destroyed R1!
This isn't good.
And he's headed right for me!
Zero! At the very least, you have to get outta here!
We can move in and act as decoys,
sacrificial pawns for the plan. So, please...
That's wrong.
Hm?
You're mistaken, Urabe.
If you consider yourselves disposable,
you'll never beat the Britannians.
Captain Urabe!
Can you get over there?
Yeah. The cargo loading dock, right?
Yes.
It's a shortcut to this level.
Confirmed.
Yes, I see it.
This looks like a mass-production
prototype based on the Lancelot.
I see.
Still, this is not the time to try capturing it.
Destroy it.
Understood.
Huh?
It vanished?!
How'd it get over here?!
Hold on! Are you saying the Knightmare "disappeared?!"
C.C.!
Aren't you finished preparing that level yet?
Why are you panicking?
You have Kallen and Urabe with you.
That's it! The aberration!
You're out of your league.
You aren't Suzaku, and your
maneuvers are no match for real strategy.
We've got the advantage in close-range combat!
Too slow!
It vanished! Just like that!
Fast as a god!
That can't be...
It's not physically possible! It must be something else!
It's closing in!
Urabe!
Oh, no!
Zero, I don't care if you're really
a student, or what your background is.
And I know you meant it
when you said we're not expendable.
I know that every fighter we've got counts.
Kozuki!
Ye-Yes?
Protect Zero.
He's our last hope, and hope is what our people need.
Forgive me, Rakshata.
Zero! Save Japan!
Help our people to lift their heads again and fight!
"The Four Holy Swords"...
...have proven our worth.
Urabe...
Damn. He used that teleportation again.
No, wait!
I have to make my move now.
This one's for Zero.
I have more bad news for you. We're all finished here.
Then it's done.
Urabe, your sacrifice wasn't in vain.
Hope begins now!
Damned terrorists! A suicide attack!
Uncivilized monkeys!
All units, lost! Contact lost with all units!
Wh-What the...?! ...
Ascending from intercept to 1,500 and circling!
That's it!
The tower will smash the enemies
above us and crush them as it falls!
Not just that.
No! It can't be!
Your mistake was sealing off your escape route.
And signaling your location
like that made you so easy to target.
Goodbye, Viceroy Calares.
The viceroy has been killed?!
Where's Lord Cornwell? He was with the viceroy.
Then, who's next in the chain of command?
The Minister of Internal Affairs.
A civil servant in charge now?!
This is no time to panic!
Hm?
I am taking command!
This is not a grab for political power!
It's a temporary measure!
I swear it in the name of my princess!
I ask for your cooperation!
The Princess?
Does he mean Princess Cornelia?
In that case...
Right.
Yes, my lord!
Thank you. I am grateful to you.
Now then, I'll go to the scene to
direct emergency rescue operations.
Alfred, you contact the police. Bart, you remain here.
Hm?
But that's...!
What's wrong?
I am Zero!
What the hell?!
Whoa, whoa! What the...?!
Isn't that Zero?
No...
I thought he was dead!
How could this happen?
It can't be the real Zero, can it?
People of Japan, I have returned!
Kill the video!
I can't! It won't take my access code!
That's it! The Omega Line that I set up!
And the only one who knows about it...
...is Zero!
Yes! I knew you were still alive!
Hear me, Britannia!
All you who have power, heed my words carefully.
I am burdened by sorrow.
War and discrimination.
Malicious deeds carried out by the strong.
The same abhorrent interplay of tragedy and comedy.
The world has not changed! The people still suffer.
That is why the resurrection of Zero was necessary!
So long as the strong oppress the weak,
my rebellion will continue to grow!
It begins today with the divine punishment
I have wrought upon the inept and foolish Viceroy Calares!
Man, oh man.
The Elevens' rebel leader sure popped
back up with a vengeance. Right, Suzaku?
Got it! The signal's coming from
the Chinese Federation consulate!
Chinese Federation?
Has he defected?
They broke through our encirclement.
Of course!
They've stayed inside the fallen building!
They've made Babel Tower itself their pathway!
But, what about the Chinese Federation?
Did they plan this out with them beforehand?
Is that possible?!
C'mon, Zero's dead, isn't he?
Yes.
So, this guy's a fake.
And whoever he is, if we just
go over there and storm the consulate...
Then we'd be breaking our treaty
with them, risking an international incident.
He's saying that he's Zero, and Zero killed our royals.
That gives this equal status with the E.U. war.
It's a slippery slope, either way.
Killing the viceroy and securing our escape route.
He was able to do both at the same time!
Such cunning and audacity is impressive.
It's Zero! The real one!
I shall fight against all those who abuse their power!
Therefore, once again, here and now,
I declare the establishment of the United States of Japan!
Are you certain about this?
We still haven't received direct orders from the Empress.
Are you dissatisfied with my decision?
No. Never mind.
Zero, you've actually founded the United States of...
...Japan.
Terrorists forming a nation?
Starting from this moment,
this room shall be the first dominion of the U.S.J.!
A nation consisting of just one room!
That man's as amusing as ever.
Race, ideology, and religion will not matter!
Being a citizen will have but one requirement!
To do that which is just!
I trust you understand the
consequences if you force your way in.
All right.
We'll settle this in diplomatic chambers later.
Zero... How useful will he prove to us in the end?
If you're Britannian, you have
already been asked to leave.
Or, are you one of Zero's followers?
I'm not sure. Which am I?
I'm not terribly fond of riddles.
Yes, I'm exactly the same way, myself.
What I wanna know is the truth.
That's why I came here to kill Zero.
I cannot move a world by waiting.
To find Nunnally and get her back,
I'm going to need real power.
Power stronger than the emperor and Suzaku.
I must seize that power, and I'll use my Geass to do it!
With the United States of Japan as my starting point,
I'll build a new world that's even greater than Britannia.
But before I can do it, I'll need to take care of him
My phony little brother, Rolo.