The world continues moving on,
thanks to miracles which Zero has performed.
The world is being reborn,
thanks to actions which Zero has taken.
Yes... the world is moving to
the next stage, as it should.
Against conflicting emotions, Zero must carry on,
for the hands which mark time cannot be stopped.
I came alone, as I promised.
Now, what's the meaning of this, Jeremiah?
If you have information on
Princess Cornelia's whereabouts,
then why do you need to tell it only to me in secret?
The Black Knights are approaching the Kagoshima coast.
But rest assured, there's no need to worry.
Under the command of Lord Waldstein,
the Knight of One, we Britannians shall...
This is already Britannian territory!
Don't let a single soldier land here!
The enemy has fallen for our plan!
They'll be shorthanded in the south,
so dispatch our landing forces ashore!
Enemy headed for Yamaguchi!
Garcia team wiped out!
Damn the Black Knights!
How did they amass this strength?!
We thought we could hold our territorial defense line,
but after what Xing-ke did to us
in the Battle of the East China Sea...
All right, don't panic!
As long as we're able to defend Area 11,
all the imperial armies led by Prince Odysseus
and the other royal family members
can rush into the U.F.N. territories.
The remaining Knights of the Round
are deployed on the front line, as well.
Or, to put it another way,
if Japan is liberated, the other colony areas of Britannia
will spring into action one after another,
which would redefine the map of the world!
In summation...
...it's the decisive battle.
Has it really been eight years?
Eight years since Nunnally and I
were left on our own at the Kururugi shrine.
And there...
How do you like that, you stupid Brit?!
That was where we first met Suzaku.
I don't need a reason to save who
I want to save or do what I want to do!
You always were stubborn.
But of course... that was the reason.
The reason you became the first
and only real friend I ever had.
And that's why...
Why I think I'll take a chance on you, Suzaku.
If you can accept me, then perhaps...
This will hardly do for me! Why such meager offerings?
The Vampire of Britannia!
Let's hit him at the same time!
Right!
Six-Way Charge attack!
Hah!
Wha...What the...?!
Question: "What do people value most?"
Stop it! Please!
That's right! Your own life!
Please, no...!
Our left wing is crumbling, Master Xing-ke!
It's one Knightmare with unique breakthrough power.
Dispatch Indira's team for support.
Have left-wing teams fall back at once.
Decoy and isolate enemy unit!
Roger!
As far as I'm aware, Prince Schneizel
ought to be staying in Tokyo.
There's nothing to fear.
The Knight of One,
the strongest in the empire, is in Kyushu.
If we can just ride this out and remain anchored in Tokyo,
this will only look like
minor trouble to foreign countries.
Yes, Your Highness!
It'll be all right, Nunna.
I expect this war will be over soon.
I have a knack for reading these situations.
The Savage Valkyrie Squadron repelled
the ambush troops from Nagasaki.
Now dispatching reinforcements to Shimane。
Send Sir Morrey to the front as back-up.
Sir Karim, fall back,
rendezvous with Sir Lasceaux...
It looks as if the enemy offensive is losing steam,
and if you join the battle, you'll surely
finish this with one blow, Lord Waldstein!
You think so?
Huh?
This attack is far too weak for
one of Zero's trademark strategies.
Prepare to launch.
Special equipment unit one, provide support.
Galahad, launch!
You came alone?
I promised I would.
You have a lot of nerve coming here.
According to this particular situation,
there are 31 routes I can take.
Especially with Britannia being so loose
with the routes relating to the royal family...
That's not what I meant, Lelouch.
Showing your face in front of me, that's what took nerves.
Not your own daring.
But you promised?
I have no reason to believe
any of your promises at this point.
Then explain to me.
Why did you come here alone as well?
After what you did?
You want to know?
I'm fed up with lying.
I've had to lie to Nunnally. Just the way you have.
That's the worst thing.
Some friend you were.
You've been betraying me all along!
Not just me, either, but everyone
on the student council, too.
And even Nunnally.
And don't forget Euphy!
Are you sure about this, Tohdoh?
We just wait here?
We still haven't received word from Zero.
But now that the Knights of
the Round have joined the battle,
even General Commander Xing-ke is no match.
Have faith in Zero.
How can we, after he brought Orange
and that Rolo person into our ranks
without conferring with us first?
Don't you feel that he's keeping too many secrets from us?
Like when he took Kinoshita on that secret mission!
We need Zero's abilities now more than ever.
Haven't we already discussed this
many times with Ohgi as well as the others?
So... what if Japan is liberated?
Right. What happens then?
Rakshata, where are Ohgi and Diethard?
Don't know.
All right, just what are you trying
to achieve by threatening me, Diethard?
Threaten you? Oh, no.
I'm simply asking you to continue working
as a member of the Black Knights as you have been.
What do you mean by that?
Look, I'm only saying that I don't want
you to be any trouble to Zero, that's all.
Why? There are plenty of people who can replace me.
You're valuable for the simple reason
that you're a man of ordinary character.
Hm?
Organizations need more than brilliant leadership
and star players in order to succeed.
I need to know.
Did you use your Geass power on Euphy? Be honest.
Yes.
You caused her to massacre the Japanese?
I ordered her to do it.
Why would you use your Geass like that?!
Answer me!
To motivate the Japanese people.
If the Specially Administrated Zone
of Japan had been established,
the Black Knights would have collapsed.
And Shirley's death?
Also my fault.
You aren't even human, you know that?
Shirley and Euphy...
Were both of them nothing
more than pawns for your ambitions?
Yes, that's right.
So all the sin is mine alone to shoulder.
My little sister had nothing to do with it!
Why, you coward!
How could you use Nunnally like that?!
Suzaku... I'm sorry.
And he always played Santa Claus for me.
Big brother would dress up like him
and even stuff pillows under his shirt.
The face of the kind older brother and the mask of Zero...
Which is the real Lelouch?
Huh? He isn't here, either?
By any chance, have you seen Suzaku?
No. I doubt he'd come here.
Send Hong's unit into the right wing,
and get ready for the second charge!
You are the commander, are you not, sir?
Came to crush the head of the snake, have you?!
It's a basic tactic.
Hmph.
Behold, Excalibur!
The holy sword bestowed upon me by His Majesty himself!
For the first time in my life,
I'm bowing down to another person.
Shame and honor mean nothing to me.
All I want is this, and my Geass be damned!
Just please! You have to save Nunnally!
I beg of you...
After everything you've done,
you really think this is sufficient?!
You believe that some bowing and begging
is enough to get me to forgive you?!
No, of course I don't, but it's all I've got!
I have nothing else left to offer!
And you're the only person in
the world who can save my sister now!
So you believe...
...that I'll just ignore the past and forgive you?
That everyone is going to forgive you?!
The people you've tricked?
The people who died thanks to you?
And what about Euphy?!
You want to apologize?!
Then bring Euphy back to life! Right now!
I want to see you save the world with all your malice!
Right now!
You're Zero, the miracle worker, aren't you?!
I've performed no miracles.
It's all been calculation and stage production.
The mask they call Zero is a symbol!
Just a device that lets me tell lies!
A device?
You don't really expect me to buy that excuse, do you?!
If you're going to tell a lie,
then keep it up till the very end!
I can't go back to the past!
It's not a choice!
You know I can't undo what's already been done!
Lelouch, you will answer me!
Why did you use your Geass
on me to make me want to live?
Why?!
The Geass you used on me that drives me to live
has corrupted my convictions.
Why would you put such a curse me?!
I only did it because I wanted to survive.
And why did you save me when
I was accused of Prince Clovis' murder?
I wanted to make the Japanese trust me, that's all.
Why did you save the student council
members from the hotel jacking?!
Because I thought it presented an ideal
opportunity for the Black Knights' debut.
The look in his eyes...
I know that look.
The look of torment that comes from bottling up a lie.
That's why I joined the Britannian army.
For redemption.
So that the tragedy wouldn't repeat itself.
You're lying, aren't you?
Lelouch...
There's only one way to redeem yourself for those lies.
Turn your falsehoods into the truth.
Huh?
You told the world a lie when you
proclaimed that you were a knight for justice.
Why don't you live up to that lie by
trying to become a true knight for justice?
Then you'll have to keep the lie going.
To the very end.
But how... how could I do that?
By putting an end to this war.
You are Zero.
This job... only Zero can do it.
It's within your power.
Bring peace and happiness to the world.
If you do that, I'll save Nunnally.
You will? You'll save her?
But we'll work together.
One more time, for her sake.
I'm grateful.
The two of us together...
We can accomplish anything.
Wh-What the...?!
Hold it right there, Zero!
We've already uncovered your true identity!
Are you all right, Sir Kururugi?!
Please step back!
Suzaku...!
You set me up from the start!
No, wait!
You've done a great deed here, Sir Kururugi.
Excellent work.
You've managed to bring this war to an end.
I see...
You planned to sell me out again!
You betrayed me, Suzaku...
You betrayed me!
It's because Suzaku's been acting so weird lately.
I thought this might help to
take his mind off things for a while.
This was in the student council room?
Yeah.
I found it hidden deep in a locker,
like it was something valuable.
There are a few photos missing here and there, though.
Ones of you, too.
But I suppose he couldn't leave evidence
that shows him palling around with a terrorist!
Yet everyone appears... well...
That's right. He...
He can look like that too, huh?
Huh?
I've never seen Suzaku smile like that.
He's so happy.
Good for him.
Hey, look.
What?
I understand that you're a
Britannian-Eleven half-breed, right?
If you chose the name Stadtfelt instead of Kouzuki,
you could very well have a good life, couldn't you?
Even become one of the Knights
of the Round if you have such ambitions.
Is this going somewhere?
What I mean, is wouldn't you like to
come back over to our side, Kallen?
Sir Bradley, please stop!
Oh, buck up!
You've taken so many hits,
you're only going to crash anyway.
So, in light of that, I, Luciano,
will use your plight to our advantage!
And settle it in one blow!
He's using one of his own ships as a weapon?!
Fall back at full speed while firing!
It's no use! We'll never make it!
Where do you think you're going?
Ah... You show skill!
Good! From this position...!
Nicely done. Good form.
You parried my sword thrust then
swiftly attacked in the follow-through.
You, the one named Xing-ke.
The rumors of your prowess are evidently true.
General Commander Xing-ke appears to be wounded!
Da Long Dan, withdrawing!
Chief of staff Zhou Xiang-Lin
now assuming operational command.
Zero, what's taking so long?!
I can't believe Zero's identity is that of a student!
Guilford!
How sad.
Zero, killer of royalty.
It's tragic that it would turn out to be you.
My own younger brother.
Your brother...!
However, Lelouch, I'm willing to
intercede with His Majesty on your behalf.
You realize, of course, that you can't simply
be excused for the crimes you've committed,
but your life may yet be spared.
So you think you can take pity on me?!
Y-You mean...
Yes.
This was all done under orders from Prince Schneizel.
He figured that following you
would ultimately lead us to Zero.
You see, His Highness was well aware of the fact
that you and Zero shared an unusual relationship.
Lelouch, even now, I do still
consider myself your brother.
I carry no grudge.
Can you believe me when I say this?
And why should I?
You should trust your brother.
I would love to be able to, brother.
Unfortunately, I'm done with trusting anyone or anything.
Because friendship only leads to betrayal.
Lord Guilford.
Identify yourself! You're not Orange!
Wait. I just have a request to ask of you.
Yes, all right, then.
What is it you want me to do for you?
Oh, it's quite simple, really.
Whenever you see me assume this pose...
You will recognize and
acknowledge me as Princess Cornelia.
And then...
P-Princess Cornelia! Is that you?!
Guilford, my knight, it is I!
You must rescue me!
Yes... Your Highness!
Very good, Guilford. I'm pleased that you noticed it!
Stop it, Lord Guilford! What are you doing?!
Have you gone mad?!
How dare you hold her captive like that?!
Even Lord Guilford has been affected.
Now I suppose I have no choice
but to believe in this power.
Princess, we need to withdraw for now!
Lelouch, no!
I bid you farewell, my first and last friend.
Lelouch! Come back!
Lloyd! I can't believe it!
Lord Guilford has turned into a traitor!
Is it true?!
We're just standing by?
Mm-hmm.
Prince Schneizel ordered us to, so we're complying.
I had heard that Zero made an appearance, but...
We haven't been told anything yet.
But something critical was disclosed is my suspicion.
I need to know.
Did you use your Geass power on Euphy? Be honest.
Sir Kururugi, would you happen to know
the reason why Lord Guilford
would suddenly betray us like this?
As well as why you behaved the way
you did on Kamine Island that time?
Shouldn't we be pursuing Zero right now, sir?
There's some important information
we need before we can pursue him.
Information that only you know, Sir Kururugi.
Wired C response, confirmed.
Synchronization, achieved.
Ragnarok backup, reinitializing.
Guilford, we'll proceed on course to the Tokyo settlement.
Yes, Your Highness.
Suzaku Kururugi!
Who are you? A Japanese?
An honorary Britannian? A Knight of Seven?
Or are you the son of a Prime Minister?
The son of Genbu Kururugi?
Lelouch's friend?
Euphemia's knight?
Unless you tell us right now what we need to know,
there are going to be more unnecessary
casualties and destruction before it's over.
Just how long?
How long will you allow this
sad chain of events to continue?
Don't worry.
The modifications to the
settlement's structure are complete.
Zero won't be able to collapse it the way he did before.
We have word. It's Zero.
So, the fool has come.
Prepare to attack!
You're cleared to shoot down the Vincent as well!
Don't assume that I was portraying the role of
a student in the settlement without reason!
Tokyo settlement, I'll bring you to a halt right now!
Fire!
What?!
My... My energy filler!
A Gefijun Disturber?!
And so, that situation will lead us to...Hm?
Sorry, viewers,
but it seems that the power's gone out here in the studio.
Um, are we still broadcasting?
All tasks at hand have been cleared.
Tohdoh!
Acknowledged! Now commencing Seventh Operation!
Raise the Ikaruga!
Ikaruga surfacing!
All fleet units, surface at will!
Ohgi, right now, you realize...
Yes, I'm aware!
The main fleet will stay on course through Tokyo Bay,
break through into the Tokyo settlement,
and rendezvous with Zero!
All hands, battle stations!
All right, let's do this!
This battle...
...will be ours!
Now I shall prove my loyalty!
For Prince Lelouch and Princess Nunnally!
What? The Black Knights are in Tokyo Bay?!
Lord Waldstein, I request that you
dispatch me and my Savage Valkyrie Squadron!
You mean to the Tokyo settlement?
Do you really want to burnish your record that badly?
No. I merely take uncommon pleasure in destroying them.
Rolo, how are things on your end?
Fine. We're beginning the operation right now.
We'll make our way to Nunnally first thing.
Good. I'm counting on you, Rolo.
That's right.
I was grossly mistaken.
I was wrong to think that I could depend on sympathy.
Cold and callous, that's the prescription.
Unless I keep myself perfectly in this frame of mind,
I won't be able to take Nunnally back!
Lelouch...
I thought something strange had been
going on ever since our brother Clovis was killed.
But now I understand.
I understand everything.
But now...
I'm the one controlling the game.
That's right, Suzaku.
If you had only informed Prince
Schneizel from the very start,
we could have avoided this battle.
Being that you're one of the Knights of the Round,
you won't be subjected to disciplinary action.
However, you'll have to answer
to the sins of your own heart.
What should I do?
Be realistic.
The world won't become a kinder place only for you.
Do I have to pilot it?
The Lancelot armed with the F.L.E.I.J.A. device?
Will I have to use it... on Lelouch?
How dare you have done this to me!
You who sneered at me, trampled me, looked down on me!
I swear to you, I'll win!
I have to win against Schneizel and Suzaku!
I realize now that I'm the one you're after.
I'm the target.
Very well! Have at me, then!
Take your best shot!
I'll destroy you! I'll show you despair!
And to top it off, I'll steal Nunnally back!
I'll rescue Kallen!
In the end, I'll have the last laugh!