Imperial calendar year 2017.
The colony of Japan, now re-named Area 11,
declared a war of independence against the
suzerain state of the Holy Britannian Empire.
This uprising, which came to be known as the
Black Rebellion, was marked by heavy bloodshed
and ended with the second historic defeat for Japan.
Since then, one year has passed.
The terrorist known as Zero, presumed dead,
has again appeared in Area 11.
Zero leads an armed group of
Japanese known as the Black Knights.
His true identity: Lelouch Lamperouge,
the exiled prince of the Britannian Empire.
Therefore, once again, here and now,
I declare the establishment of the United States of Japan!
Starting from this moment,
this room shall be the first dominion of the USJ!
Race, ideology, and religion will not matter!
Being a citizen will have but one requirement:
To do that which is just!
I came here to kill...
...Zero.
It's my cell phone. Nothing else.
Rolo! Are you okay?!
Lelouch?!
Thank heaven!
I was getting really worried
because I couldn't get a hold of you.
You aren't hurt, are you? You're somewhere safe, right?
What's going on here?
Is the Zero making the speech
right now a different person?
Uh, Big Brother, where are you right now?
Me? What are you talkin' about? Especially since... Huh?
Hello, Rolo, it's me.
M-Miss Villetta?!
Lelouch came back to school,
and he's making up all the classes that he missed.
You should get back here soon, too.
Yes, ma'am, I understand.
Well, then? Are you finished with your phone call?
It seems all my business... is finished here.
The ragtag remnants of the Black Knights
and the man claiming to be Zero are currently hiding in
a section of the Chinese Federation consulate.
However, there is no cause for alarm.
Acting Viceroy Guilford has taken command of the army
in the absence of wounded Viceroy Calares...
the consulate has been completely
surrounded and the public is...
You have the town jumping, Lelouch.
Naturally.
Uh?!
A new nation has just been created in their own territory.
And not to mention, of course,
that it also just declared war on Britannia.
What's the matter?
When did you two switch places?
Before the speech.
But I...
His voice was re-recorded.
The moment "he" appeared, it was already me.
Just like in a magic show.
You planned it on your own.
We don't like it when you keep secrets from us.
"We" don't like it?
You mean, you don't like it. Do you?
Lelouch, open the oven!
Yeah, yeah.
Some salt.
Frying pan.
A fresh egg.
Bechamel sauce.
Put the gelato on another plate.
Oh, and add the rosemary to the sorbet.
Then, add the dill to the sauerkraut.
The Black Forest Cake...
I can't do this by myself!
Why do you only keep asking me to help with it all?
We didn't have a choice.
Rivalz has no sense of taste.
And of course, she is..
Well, after all, she isn't the
most focused person in the world.
Oh, just behave and do what you're told, now.
Usually, a character like you, would act
as the type who couldn't earn a living.
And he keeps a book of his household spending.
How'd you know that?!
Oh, jeez, you really do?!
Want a towel?
I will get it myself, thank you.
President, can I ask something?
Certainly, although I may choose not to answer you.
So today... we are celebrating
Rolo and me coming back alive.
Mm-hm!
You two escaped that terror attack, all right!
Shirley was practically out of her mind, the poor girl!
"Oh! If my Lulu's been killed, I'll..."
Hey, where is Rolo?
I spoke with him, but, you know...
The boy's a lot more sensitive than his older brother.
That's partly why he doesn't have any friends, isn't it?
You should simply say he's quiet!
Uh...
Not that I mind your dirty hands on my mouth, but...
Oh, right. I'm sorry.
Look at this mess!
Nobody remembers anything about Nunnally.
My little sister's been replaced
by a pretend little brother.
I wasn't the only one whose memory was rewritten.
The entire student council
has been manipulated with, as well!
How dare they!
Even after the Babel Tower incident,
Lelouch Lamperouge has shown no special changes.
There are 180 cameras on campus,
as well as 47 undercover observers.
That's 48 observers.
We've found no clues or information that could
connect Lelouch with the destruction of Carthage's unit.
Surveillance is perfect.
He has no opportunity to use his Geass.
If he is Zero, it would be odd
if he returned here to the school.
And what's the status of C.C.?
Where is she?
If she's not in close proximity to Lelouch, then...
...the odds are very slim that
she would be in the consulate.
You mean things are the same
as they were before the incident?
You've still no clue where C.C. is?
Those of us in the Office of Secret Intelligence
will carry on our mission to capture her!
People, continue observing the bait as you have been.
Yes, My Lord.
The enemy's center is where
their surveillance data is transmitted.
I can just keep acting the way I have been,
but the problem is Nunnally.
The fact that all memory of her
has been erased from everyone's minds
tells me she would never show up here at school.
In short, the probability is high that
the Britannian emperor has my sister now.
I'm dealing with a man who would
use his own children as pawns.
If they learn that I've regained my memories...
that I've reverted to being Zero...
Nunnally will be in danger!
I have to plan my movements carefully.
First, I'll trick the people they have spying on me.
And then...
Lelouch?
Make sure you come to class tomorrow, you hear?
Yes, I hear you.
Coach Villetta, you really should have more faith in me.
Villetta Nu...
A woman I once used my Geass on.
I can use my Geass power on a person only once.
Which means... it won't work on her any more.
That leaves my brother Rolo, who shouldn't even exist.
Why don't I begin by gradually subduing him?
Italian state forces are holding
strong on the right flank, too!
The victory Bordeaux we drink
tonight will be a fine vintage!
Unknown craft approaching from above!
What?!
The Lancelot!
Britannia's White Death!
Knights of the Round here at the front line?!
Please surrender.
Huh? What?
You have no chance of winning.
Anyone who throws his weapon down will not be shot.
Of all the impertinent...!
Destroy him, dammit! He's only one knight!
Then so be it.
Do you want more?!
Allowing him to conduct a solo operation?
Are you sure?
Kururugi used to be your subordinate, Your Highness.
He's now the Knight of Seven
and reports directly to His Majesty.
Yes, My Lord...
He has been elevated in rank.
He's to be admired.
The world today is overflowing with despair.
That's why he uses his humility and sense of duty
as a compass to guide him through these dark times.
Nina's gone, too.
I wonder if Suzaku took Arthur with him.
Huh?
What's up?
How come you're looking through the album?
Hey, that's the student council
marathon dance file, isn't it?
You know the Prez. She runs us ragged
with all these events she likes to put on.
Oh, that's the Broken Heart Contest.
Talk about sad irony.
The Prez stomps on Rivalz's heart
then presents him with the award for winning.
Weird how you happened to escape.
Hm?
You heard the news, didn't you?
Our military had Babel Tower completely surrounded.
So how did you do it? How did you manage to get past them?
What're you talking about, Rolo?
Do you wanna know how I got away from the military,
or did you mean to say terrorists?
I took an emergency corridor.
I tried to call you, but my cell
wouldn't work in that particular area.
I see.
A locket...
That's right.
I remember giving it to Rolo for his birthday.
No, that's wrong.
October 25th... is not his birthday.
It's Nunnally's birthday!
Rolo, give me that locket.
Huh?
I don't know what I was thinking.
That's not a good gift for a guy.
I'll get you something else...
Don't take it! You gave it to me! It's mine!
Please don't! Don't take it back!
Uh... Sure, fine.
You keep it then, Rolo.
Uh...
Right. We haven't observed
any changes in Lelouch's behavior.
There are no indications that he's used his Geass, either.
The order won't divulge the secrets
of Geass due to its religious nature...
Uh, sorry, I can see you're busy. It can wait.
Rolo, no! He's one of us!
He's on the same mission we are...
Wait for orders!
There's a chance he overheard us.
Knowledge of Geass is restricted
to just us two in the Tokyo section!
We can't take the risk!
But still...
How many of our agents have you killed so far?
It was the quickest and most
certain method to keeping the secret.
Or am I wrong?
It's been three days since the
United States of Japan was established.
I doubt Britannia is going to
keep glaring at us indefinitely.
There's even talk about ousting the consul-general
back in the Chinese Federation's homeland.
And yet, we still haven't received
any instructions from Lelouch.
What on earth is he doing?
You really are Zero, aren't you?
Of course!
I can drag out the extradition
negotiations with the Britannians.
I think I might be able to buy us up to a week.
I'll report that to Zero.
As for the Chinese Federation government's...
C.C.! I was just thinking!
Wouldn't it have made more sense
for you to have played the bunny girl?!
Huh?! Uh!
Zero is... a girl?!
Correct.
I'm not Zero!
Oh, you let on too soon.
You have no sense of humor, do you?
Don't play around with Zero!
We can see you.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Ms. Kallen Kouzuki.
You're the pilot of the Guren MK-II, right?
How did you...
I'm someone who takes an avid interest in you people.
There's trouble!
It's Ohgi and the other prisoners!
Can you hear me, Zero?
Listen closely. I am Lord Gilbert G.P. Guilford,
knight of her royal highness, Cornelia li Britannia!
Beginning tomorrow at 15:00 hours,
these 256 special class A
felons who are guilty of treason...
They wouldn't...
...against the empire,
will all be executed for their crimes!
Zero!
If you value the lives of
your people, then you will face me,
one-on-one, in an honorable duel!
Guilford... You've really gone and done it now.
Lulu! Are you in here all by yourself?
Yeah. Shirley, don't you have swim club now?
Yes, I do, but...
You see, I have to go shopping
because I have to buy a birthday gift.
Whose birthday?
Ms. Villetta, our counselor.
They all agree I should buy it,
since I'm always the one who always gets her mad.
Problem is, I'm incredibly
impaired at picking out presents.
She seems to enjoy liquor, I could buy her that.
But I don't know what brand she likes.
Should I go with you?
Huh?!
I could help you select a present for her.
Y-You would?! Seriously?!
Sure. You ready to go?
Yeah! Mm-hm!
All right! Now I've got my scoop! Thank you, guys!
Since you're unable to control your Geass,
this is for your protection.
It only has to block optical data,
so a normal color contact lens would work fine,
Don't try to probe for information.
As you've already guessed, you're holding a special lens.
Although...
Should your Geass grow stronger than what you have now...
Well, we'll just have to end this game...
...before that happens.
Are you're going out?
Yeah, I have to help pick out a gift.
It's a present for Ms. Villetta's birthday.
Her birthday?
I see.
I guess birthdays are important, aren't they?
Well, I'd better be going.
See you later.
Rolo!
Huh? Ah!
Miss President!
Rolo, you come along, too!
Huh?
It'll be fun to chat.
Hm...
I've learned about wines but never tried any.
Outta luck there.
How about this stuff?
Maybe those are too sweet.
How 'bout a Sopron?
Could this be...
...a date?
If it's not...
...I'll make it one, then!
Just as I planned.
Although, I didn't think they'd bring Rolo, too.
Typical of Milly...
What a great topic for our next meeting of
the Society of Research on Male-Female Dating!
Um... Right.
Yeah, but it fair for him to follow his own brother?
You're as interested as we are, aren't you?
She may end up being your family member.
She's right!
Family...
Target is taking assumed route "Zebra."
Roger. Switch off with Group 7.
Group 2, watch for contact with C.C.
Yes, My Lord. Cleaning the perimeter.
Can it be that he really isn't Zero?
They specifically set a trap at Babel Tower.
Which means my enemy isn't
the settlement's vice-regal government.
While I can't tell for certain who's watching me,
the system itself that they're using has flaws in it.
If he is Zero, he won't ignore the
execution of his people tomorrow.
Maybe his memory truly hasn't returned.
Excuse me.
How do I fill this part out?
Pardon?
Sorry, but could you do me a favor, please?
Sure. What can I do for you?
Well, it's like this...
Mmm...
Huh?
I'm back.
What were you looking at?
Oh! Um... That!
I... was just wishing I could
take a ride on a cable car sometime.
It's my fault.
My fault that Shirley's memories were wiped.
Milly and Rivalz, too!
Their memories re-written without their consent!
I just can't let things go the way they are.
When this is all over...
I swear I'll...
What's the matter?
The Prez and the others are following us.
What? Where?
Shirley.
Huh?
I thought of a terrific idea.
Target entering store.
Alpha-14. It's a small shop.
There's a risk I'll blow my cover if I follow.
Cover the front of the place.
I'll send three people to cover the rear.
Okay.
All I want you do to is
pretend that I'm in here for a while.
What are you gonna do?
I'm going to sneak out of the store
and surprise the Prez and the others.
Sure! I gotcha!
I don't normally shop here.
I hope they don't have any
surveillance cameras or microphones.
Shirley thinks this is only a harmless prank.
Even on the off-chance that something goes wrong,
I won't cause any trouble for her.
I used my Geass to make the preparations.
Now all I have to do...
Hello, Omotesando Mall security; may I help you?
Huh?! The Black Knights?!
We have planted a bomb
in the mall, and we will detonate it
if all our following demands are not met immediately.
No... He can't be Zero!
Paging Mr. Maximillian from the Hakodate settlement.
That means a...!
You have a phone call.
A terrorist warning!
It must be the Black Knights!
Zero's been resurrected!
Keep your voices down! The customers will hear!
But...!
Uh?
A bomb threat has just been
made to Omotesando Mall, My Lord!
Okay, hold your positions! Prepare for contact from C.C.!
All tasks at hand have been cleared,
except for the detonator.
10... 9... 8... 7...
...6... 5... 4... 3...
...2... 1...!
It's the Black Knights!
Terrorists?!
What's happening?!
What the hell?!
Whoa, what's going on?!
Rolo!
Rolo! Don't run off!
Rolo?
He's gone!
We've lost the target, M'Lord!
What should we do about the
info that we've got from Scorpion?
Where's Rolo?!
All cell phone calls are being
jammed to maintain civic order!
My Lord, should we act on Scorpion's info or not?!
Very well, I'll go myself!
And that's just one easy way...
...to cause a panic.
What's his location?! Uh?!
No one's here. Where are they?
It seems they've gone looking for C.C...
I see.
You really have awakened.
I put the man who was following me
under my absolute control and turned him into my slave.
Just as I thought, your top
priority was the capture of C.C.
No matter how wrong the information is that you get.
As of this moment, this gilded prison of a school
will become my castle, my fortress of freedom.
And as for you, dear brother,
I'll make you my pawn to find Nunnally.
What?!
Geass?!
You stopped time?!
Lelouch...
Now you and your demonic eye...
...will die.
Zero! Emergency!
The Chinese Federation just...
Huh?!
Here and now, you cursed Black Knights will be vanquished!
Guilford is about to exectue
the core members of the Black Knights.
The very people I need in order to carry out my plan!
Somehow, I have to save them.
But at the moment,
my phony brother Rolo is my main obstacle.
It's only logical that they would
assign a Geass-user to observe me.
But that power of his...
No...
There's a breach I can exploit.
For the sake of everyone whose
memories were rewritten, I must!