So? Tell us!
How are things with you and Lelouch?
Huh?
You two are the official school couple now, aren't you?
Have you kissed yet?
Um, th-that was just for the event.
We're not fooling around.
Don't be embarrassed.
It's no secret that you've always
had a big crush on Lelouch.
Oh! Not you too, Coach Villetta!
But you love him, don't you?
Enough to shoot me?
Huh?
It's been very difficult, you know?
Having to come here and spend each day
cheerfully smiling at the young woman who shot me.
My true feelings have to be
hidden behind the mask of a teacher.
Shirley Fenette... How dare you!
How dare you shoot me!
Lulu!
Uh?
That's right. While Lelouch was Zero,
he killed my father.
So, Jianmen pass has fallen?
We've also taken over the air force facility in Macau.
We should send Asahina and Hong Gu to defend Jianmenguan.
And why don't we assign Minase and Sugiyama
to take charge of municipal affairs there?
Well, looks like things are going smoothly.
Our so-called foes are just local
military factions that won't join us,
but they'll deploy forces without talking to each other.
Not to mention that you've
already got a hold of the empress.
The one leader who could unify all those factions.
Exactly.
You're off?
I'm going to Ikebukuro.
But I'll help you with the rest of
your homework when I return.
I'll catch you later, then.
Lulu was Zero. And coach Villetta was a soldier.
And Kallen was one of the Black Knights.
Then what about Nina? And the Prez? And Rivalz?
Is our school the weirdest place on Earth?
Oh, why is Nunnally now the viceroy?
What are the lies, and what is the truth?
Attention: The local express is running 10 minutes
behind schedule and will be arriving at platform three.
For those passengers who do not wish to wait...
Very well.
For the first stage, this will be fine.
All right then,
we'll continue with the same procedure.
And now, here's an announcement to all our
patrons about a special deal. For a limited time only,
we're running a campaign...
Shirley!
Wait! It's just me.
Huh?
So what's wrong? Why'd you want to me to come here?
Um...
Uh...
Shirley!
Lelouch.
Where's Lelouch? On a date?
At the moment, he's out testing the G cars.
Hmph. How convenient.
Huh?
Rolo, why have you turned your back on your country?
Unlike me, you were dispatched
here by the Order, so why would you...
Just why are you asking me that?
What's between my brother and me is...
Uh!
B7 to control.
Suspicious male sighted near the chapel.
B5 and B9 have moved in to apprehend him.
Hmph.
Look what happened simply by asking where Lelouch was.
Lord Jeremiah! But how?!
Target is moving toward the clubhouse.
B2 and B8 have been eliminated, as well.
Sound a school-wide alarm!
Get students out of the vicinity of the target!
Attention all students and personnel.
This is an emergency announcement.
Do not go near the clubhouse area.
A suspicious person has been sighted there.
Out of my way.
I have no desire to kill a woman if I don't need to.
We at least share that.
I, too, would like to avoid any unnecessary killing.
Oh?
En garde!
Cyborg?!
And I have Zero to thank.
They say they're going to kill God.
God?
I thought they were speaking metaphorically, but now...
At the very least these people
believe what they're saying!
Ridiculous. To believe in God. There's no such being!
That's right.
No winged goddesses or long-bearded old men
in white gowns with kingdoms in the clouds.
No. Not that sort of God. Uh!
Uh!
Hmph.
Princess Cornelia!
Who knows what type of Geass he controls!
You must never let your guard down, even for a child.
Yes, that's correct.
Cornelia, you do live up to your reputation, don't you?
As your uncle, I'm very proud of you.
My what?!
We made a solemn vow.
If there was ever a god that made men fight each other...
...we'd kill him and his divine rule.
Even if you are a cyborg,
your exposed Hmphan parts make you vulnerable!
You have good aim!
I'll stop you! For Master Lelouch's sake!
Uh?!
Your skill in martial arts is impressive.
But, it won't impede Jeremiah Gottwald.
Sayoko!
Uh!
Dammit.
Steal time!
Okay! Now get him while I'm holding him still! Go on!
With great pleasure!
But that's not possible! My Geass...
It should stop time with absolutely anyone!
Rolo Lamperouge!
Just as I thought! You've been fooled!
But how could you break my Geass?
How? Because I was chosen, that's how!
Picked by the Order to be an assassin!
Then you've come to kill Lelouch, is that it?!
Lord Jeremiah!
Huh?
Villetta! You mean Lelouch has snared you, too?!
Lelouch is at the Ikebukuro station right now!
Lord Jeremiah, I'm begging you!
What ever you do, please let me go!
All right, then.
What do I do? I called Suzaku out here,
but what should I say to him? Especially with Lulu here.
Shirley, what kind of game are you playing?
Or was it Suzaku who called her out here?
Rivalz told me that Lelouch has
been here in Japan the entire time.
Intelligence from the O.S.I. backs that up, also.
But... Why don't I believe it?
Villetta. What are you doing?
Are you betraying Lelouch, or... are you...
We should contact Lelouch right away.
I will stay here and protect the place.
The rest of you go on to Ikebukuro.
If Lelouch is ready for him,
we may be able to pin Jeremiah from two sides.
I have to tell Suzaku.
He needs to know that Lelouch
is Zero and the he killed my father!
This is the boundary line, right here.
The demarcation between the settlement and the ghettos.
We have to erase it.
Hold it. What if these two are accomplices?
To turn Area 11 back into Japan?
That's it! They've been friends since way back!
Uh?
What's the matter? Is something wrong?
No!
Shirley!
Stay away from me!
You're both liars! You two
are nothing but a pair of fakes!
I won't... Aaggh...!
No! Let me go! Let me go!
Stop it! I can't lose you!
I don't want to lose you or anyone else in my life!
Not one more person!
Please...
Shirley!
Uh-huh.
Uh! Suzaku!
Hey... You've done this once before, haven't you?
Huh?
You know, that time back at school
when you tried to catch Arthur.
Yeah, you're right.
Uh?
I guess you're right Shirley. We have done this before.
And Suzaku is always the one who pulls you back up.
If Lelouch had been the one on top,
both of us would have fallen.
You exercise nut!
If you're gonna brag,
you should've saved us before we fell.
That's ridiculous.
Why am I laughing?
After what Lelouch did to Euphy!
I'm wrong. He's acting on his own. Lulu is...
Oh.
'Scuse me. Uh?!
Lelouch, be careful!
Jeremiah's heading toward you right now!
He's an assassin sent by the Order.
My Geass didn't work on him!
Wait, Jeremiah is alive?!
And what do you mean an assassin, Rolo?
I'm not sure.
Anyway, don't do anything rash until we get there.
What's up? Is something wrong?
This is bad. With Suzaku here...
By your expression, I'm guessing
that wasn't a friendly phone call.
Ah, ow!
Suzaku, stop that!
My problem comes first, doesn't it?
Right.
Oh, yeah, that's right, you two were
waiting for each other here, weren't you?
What's the matter, are you jealous?
Hmph.
Thanks so much, Lulu.
Can't we wait for just a while? We should...
Come on. Let's go, Suzaku.
Wait! Hold on!
This area is about to become a battlefield.
And I can think of no safer place for Shirley,
than to be with Suzaku.
Jeremiah Gottwald?
Yes, I am.
What? The guy's bulletproof!
I understand. Lelouch has used his Geass on you.
Huh?
Huh?!
Not only does Geass have no effect on him,
he has the power to cancel it, as well.
Fire?!
Terrorists?!
Hmph.
Right! Come up and get me, Orange!
So, what's this important thing
you need to talk to me about?
Uh, well I'm...
Well, I'm in love with Lulu.
But you hate him, don't you?
I liked him...
...at one time.
And now?
I thought something was wrong.
The two of you used to be so close together.
What happened, did you have a fight?
I can't forgive him.
Nothing is unforgivable, you know.
In other words, it only means that
you're not willing to forgive him.
You don't want to forgive him.
I forgave him. I chose to a long time ago.
Shirley... What are you...
Did you call the fire department?
In situations like this, doesn't the Army respond first?
Sir Suzaku Kururugi! I'm the Knight of Seven.
Uh! M-My lord!
This might be an act of terrorism, so from here on,
I'm taking command of all the
perimeter police and fire fighting units.
Right, understood, my lord!
And I want you to protect that
young woman right over there.
What is it? We're in the middle of a meeting.
Like I care? Ain't no meeting I was invited to!
Emergency call from Zero.
Somethin' weird's going on there.
Uh?
Zero! It's Ohgi.
What's happened? What's the emergency?
If it's about the guys from Taiwan, right now we're...
Ohgi!
Mm! That voice! It's...
Lelouch, just hang in there!
All units in position. Support teams en route.
Lulu...
Please get into the vehicle, Miss.
It's the Knight of Seven's orders.
Wha...?! Miss, come back here!
Hold on, Lulu!
Don't worry, I won't leave you alone!
You won't escape me!
Lulu, where can you be? Uh!
He must be fighting.
Lulu's fighting...
...on his own.
A mechanical body...
And you've got a Geass canceller.
Your vengefulness is truly top-notch, Orange boy!
There's no vengefulness. It's sheer loyalty.
How I hate to hear that.
What could the emperor have
possibly done to deserve such loyalty?
Wha...?!
From your performance,
I figured that you must be using sakuradite.
A Gefijun Disturber...!
Well, well, I see you've done your homework.
You're aware, that when this
sakuradite disruption system is complete,
we can paralyze all urban functions
with the railway's circular route.
In other words, bring Tokyo to a standstill.
I'm grateful. You've been an exemplary test subject.
Rolo!
Shirley, you're here?!
Answer me, Rolo.
Um.
Do you truly... love Lulu?
Now then, are you going to tell me what I want to know?
Where is the Order located? And where is V.V.?
You're the one... who will talk here!
What?!
Because I have... my reasons...
I'm resolved to see my loyalty through!
I must know the truth for certain... once and for all!
But how...?! He shouldn't be able to move!
Why, Lelouch? Why did you adopt the role of Zero?
Why did you turn against your homeland?
Becoming an enemy of the emperor as a result?!
I did it because I am Lelouch vi Britannia!
My father, the Britannian emperor,
allowed my mother to be killed!
In so doing, he stole Nunnally's sight...
her legs... and our futures from us!
I know. I remember, because I was there, too.
Uh?! You were?!
My first assignment. To guard her. Lady Marianne,
whom I loved and respected.
But I failed to carry through with that loyalty.
I just wasn't able to protect her!
So you founded the Purebloods, then?
Master Lelouch.
Everything is becoming clear now.
You became Zero for the sake
of Lady Marianne, didn't you?
But if you didn't come here to
kill me, then what are you trying to do?
I don't serve V.V...
I follow only one.
It's Lady Marianne...
Now... I'll die without regret.
Lord Jeremiah!
Ugh! My prince...!
Jeremiah Gottwald, listen.
Your steadfast loyalty is still
desperately needed here. Isn't that right?
Indeed. Yes, Your Majesty.
Rolo, I love Lulu. But what about you?
What a question.
He's my only brother, so of course I love him.
Then you're on Lulu's side, right? Right?!
Uh?
Please. Let me join you!
I want Lulu to be safe, too! I can help you protect him!
I want to bring all the happiness back into Lulu's life!
Then maybe he can be together with his sister Nunna!
Right. I've sent Jeremiah on ahead.
He'll take care of any obstacles in the way.
Don't try to fight him! He just came over to our side!
Uh?
Shirley!
Shirley, who did this to you?!
Lulu...?
I'm glad... we can talk at the very end...
Don't say that! It's not the end!
I'll call a doctor, so just...
Ever since my memories have come back,
I've been feeling so very afraid...
A teacher who wasn't a teacher.
Friends who don't... have memories to share.
Everyone... was just... lying...
It felt as though... the whole world was spying on me.
That's the world... you've been
fighting all by yourself, isn't it?
All alone...
So that's why I...
why I wanted to be someone
who would at least be truthful to you.
Shirley...
Lulu... I love you.
Even knowing how you caught my father in all this...
I simply couldn't hate you.
Even though you made me forget everything...
I still fell in love with you...
Even though my memories were tampered with...
I kept falling in love...
with you all over again...
No, Shirley! You can't die...!
No matter how many times I'm reborn...
I'll keep falling in love... with you, Lulu...
I suppose... that it's simply fate...
No, don't die! I order you not to die...!
So, is that okay then... Lulu...?
And as I'm reborn...
I'll fall in love with you over and over...
I'll keep...
...falling...
...in love... with...
Shirley! Shirley...!
C.C. once told me something.
She said that Geass was the power of the king.
And a life of solitude.
Then this must be what she meant.
Shirley... I wanted...
I had to apologize for involving you with Geass.
For making you the sacrifice.
How can I make up for that?
Tell me, please. Tell me...