This is 2-D-4.
We are now entering Tokyo Settlement-controlled airspace.
Roger.
Your flight objective here is
commercial advertising, correct?
No change in that.
As filed, the duration of our flight will be 14 hours.
That is confirmed. You are cleared for fly-over.
Acknowledged. I appreciate it.
We're the only ones left now.
This is all that remains of the Black Knights
who, along with Zero, once struck
terror in the heart of Britannia.
Still, it's too soon to give in to despair!
If Operation Flying Swallow Four is successful, then...!
Yes.
Forgive me. Here's to you.
To victory! Long live Japan!
Long live Japan!
Lelouch.
Uh? Oh, not again. You are persistent.
You're not going to get away this time!
Hey, Lelouch, about what you said
Sorry! Catch ya later!
Lelouch, you come back here!
Vice Prez!
Hope you get lucky.
Yeah, whatever!
You lost the moment you turned this
into a contest of strength and speed.
Aren't you overreacting?
I mean, this is just about making up a P.E. class.
No! Quit cutting class, Lelouch!
I have more than enough school credits to pass, don't I?
Don't worry, it's only colored smoke!
Wait!
Hey, Vice Prez, hang in there!
Uh! Thanks a lot!
What kind of student president are you?!
Oh, I'm so sorry. Lost my head.
Lelouch...!
Heh!
Ow, are you trying to kill me, coach?
Rivalz?! But how did you...?
I need to borrow your bike, Rivalz! See ya!
What're you up to now, Lulu?
For crying out loud!
Can't they give me a break
and leave me alone after school?
But... they only do that because
you're always skipping class, big brother.
Because I find them insufferably boring.
Here, have some. It's from Milly.
Uh...
Whoa!
I can't eat and steer!
You're right. I'm sorry.
It's been a year since Britannian forces
crushed the Black Rebellion the revolt instigated by Zero.
Things have finally quieted down,
even here in Area 11.
When the insurrection began,
all sorts of rumors were flying.
At one point, I considered returning
to the homeland with my brother.
Did you hand in your career guidance report yet?
Huh?
That's the reason Ms. Villetta was so upset.
Oh...
So, what about college?
Well, I haven't decided yet.
I am sick and tired of being a student.
But I'm not ready to get a job
and join the system, either.
A typical answer.
Besides, what could I ever hope to
attain by entering the workforce?
Big corporations and the nobility
would still be above me.
A structured, mature world.
I would simply be absorbed into the hierarchy of adults.
We all need to understand that this is not discrimination!
But rather, it's differentiation!
The Elevens revealed themselves to be a dangerous,
belligerent race!
They followed the scoundrel, Zero,
and took up the name "Japanese"!
It's our duty as Britannians to control and educate them!
The Elevens lost. They didn't have the strength.
If they'd only kept quiet and behaved,
this place wouldn't have been
downgraded to a re-education zone.
Zero... He was a fool.
No matter what you try, the world is just a...
Viceroy Calares, please hurry,
the delegation from the Chinese Federation is waiting.
I understand.
Are those O.S.I. people going to carry it out?
Yes, at Babel Tower, my lord.
On today, of all days...
What could His Majesty be thinking?
I seriously doubt that the scattered remnants
of the Black Knights can do anything to us at this point.
Besides... Zero is long dead.
Quit slackin' off, lazy Eleven monkey!
Y-Yes, sir!
Target arriving, as predicted.
Ground foot patrol to main.
Sending I.D. numbers of peripheral vehicles.
Main to ground...
Target now entering fifth gate from B-3.
Do you think she'll show this time?
I just know we can't afford to fail.
We're taking a huge risk by letting Lelouch
go to the settlement's outer edge.
Oh, all right then.
You can come with me, but I warn you,
you'll have to watch out.
Because today, I'm going to be breaking the law.
Don't get caught!
Heh. Cops don't scare me.
Why do this?
'Cause I mean, you're not even
doing this for the money, are you?
Need you ask?
It's because I wanna battle more challenging opponents!
That's a lie. I do this out of sheer boredom.
In short... I'm...
Today's main event is a brutal match between brothers!
Which sibling will win? The older one or the younger?!
We don't belong here. Let's go.
It's simple to figure out. Just relax.
Uh?
Look there.
The Britannians, like ourselves,
are laughing and having fun.
The ones who are being laughed at are the Elevens.
You pretend not to notice, but in the end...
But then, why...?
I know, but it's the truth. The Elevens lost twice.
First, with Prime Minister Kururugi, and again, with Zero.
How could they rebel when they don't have the strength?
I'm terribly sorry!
No, it's fine, don't worry.
But I'm an Eleven, and you're a Britannian student!
This is inexcusable!
All the more reason to excuse you.
I hate having our social class held over you like a sword.
It doesn't matter.
The powerless have no choice,
but to bear their lot in life.
Huh?
Regardless if their oppressor is wrong.
I'd appreciate it if you didn't push
your values on me. I'm not interested.
I beg your pardon.
C'mere, lemme take a look at ya. Hm?
Hm, nice goods you've got here.
Yes, Mr. King, we have a large,
quality catch of bunnies today.
You're wrong, sir, I'm not for sale!
But you are for sale.
You should know by now, losers don't have any rights!
Alert. Unforeseen trouble occurring.
Tsk!
Curse your own wretched birth
for not having been born with power.
That's what His Majesty always says, isn't it?
His Majesty...
The strong feed upon and devour the weak.
That's the rule, kid!
The guy's Mafia, Lelouch!
What an arrogant display.
Hm?
Feeding upon the weak, are you?
This is the grownup world in here, schoolboy, so get lost.
Then will the adult world devour the student,
or is it the other way around?
Why don't we find out the answer with this?
With chess?
Big brother, don't!
Too late, fellas. Right, boys?
Students really don't know much of anything, do they?
That's not true, Mr. Black King.
Hm?!
You're a famous chess player
in the gambling arena, aren't you?
So, you know who I am, huh?
If Zero was here, you wouldn't be acting so tough!
Do me a favor.
Don't say that traitor's name again.
Hey, Zero didn't betray us!
Shut up, you stinkin' Eleven!
There has to be a reason for what he did.
What reason? Why'd the commander vanish
during the final decisive battle like that?!
Huh?
Stop it!
It serves no purpose. Zero's dead, after all.
He's dead?
And that's checkmate.
Impossible!
The student beat him!
Black King lost!
How could he lose so easily?
Looks like you're the one who's been devoured here.
Damn. That's inconvenient.
How will I ever be able to show my face in public
if word of this gets around?
I would never spread rumors.
No, schoolboy, not that.
What I'm saying is that others will
hear how you cunningly cheated me.
I what?!
Such a naughty little man...
Uh! Now wait a minute!
Cheat? But in chess, how could you?
There's no way to do it!
Get him and hold him.
Now to whip up a little evidence against the kid.
You filthy, lying adult!
Fair play doesn't win the game. Learn that, schoolboy!
Let him go!
Terrorists?!
Move out!
Come on! This way!
What?! Hey!
Lelouch!
An airship, huh? Their final gasp.
Office of Secret Intelligence,
initiate Operation Valhalla Seven.
Yes, my lord!
What is this?! What's happening?!
What?!
We welcome you here to Area 11.
We didn't expect an armed reception.
Especially after hearing that Zero was dead.
Zero? You have the wrong idea.
I hoped it would offer you and the other
representatives of the Chinese Federation
a better understanding of us Britannians.
My... An uncommonly straightforward approach. Hm...?
May we have what you're carrying, sir?
Our security is perfect.
You don't need to carry that antique weapon here.
Xing-ke! That was rude of you!
Please forgive me.
But I hoped it would offer you and the other Britannians
a better understanding of the Chinese Federation.
Why you...
Huh?
Huh? What?
Big brother, this way!
Hey!
No! Wait a minute!
We what?! Lost sight of the target?!
Yes, that is correct. We will be going in now.
Understood.
The terrorists attacking Babel Tower appear well equipped.
They're armed with several Knightmares.
At commencement of the operation,
perimeter cleaning complete.
Good. Now enter the seventh sequence.
Commander, Viceroy Calares is...
Pay no attention to that low-level bureaucrat.
Our orders come directly from the emperor himself!
Yes, my lord.
Elevens can take the stairs!
Get out, we're overloaded!
Stop pushing!
Terrorists?
What are leftover fragments
of the Black Knights doing here?
Huh?!
Britannian military!
Filthy Britannians!
Sorry, I wasn't able to bring him here like we planned!
Don't sweat it.
Urabe and the others are looking for him right now.
Understood!
Rolo, this way!
What the hell's going on?
That Knightmare earlier... Was it trying to...
Lelouch, what'll we do now?
Don't worry. We'll be all right, I promise you.
I'll get us out of here.
Yeah, I'm-I'm sure. We'll be fine.
Rolo!
Lelouch!
And now, Lulu's giving all of his same bad habits to Rolo!
Admit it, Shirley.
You're worried about your darling Lulu.
No, I am not!
There she goes again!
Uh!
Whatever...
R-Rolo...
Rolo!
I'm out of range. What do I do now?
At this rate, we'll both be...!
No! I have to try and save him!
The least I should be able to do is save my only brother!
Even I ought to have enough strength in me to do that.
I have to!
Terrorists are responsible for this?
But... Elevens were killed, too!
Are these people still counting
on Zero to rescue them?! Uh?!
The Black Knights!
What do I do? Will they kill me?
Even if I run...
Lelouch.
I came to get you out of here, Lelouch.
I'm on your side, an ally.
And your sworn enemy is Britannia.
Huh?
We have a contract.
You and I are both accomplices.
Contract? Accomplices?
I'm the only one who knows you. The real you.
What does she mean, the real me?
Le-Lelouch...
Hey, are you all right?!
Why are soldiers...
No, hold on! What are you...
Stop it, that woman's still alive!
You've served your function well.
Good Lelouch Lamperouge.
Function?! What're you talking about?!
We've had our eye on you
for a very long time now, young man.
Wakes up at 6:59 AM.
From 7:12 AM, watches the news with
his little brother while eating breakfast.
No ideological deviations with the program he watches.
8:45 AM, goes to class.
Doesn't attend his morning homeroom or first period class.
Instead, he reads on the roof.
During his second period...
Those are things... I've done today...
I prefer to think of it as
a pet diary, or... bait journal.
Bait journal?
Or call it a trap, if you wish.
For that witch. All to lure C.C. out of hiding!
No, wait, please! What's going on?!
Boy, I'll have you know that I am a Baron.
I'm through wasting words on bait like you!
Now, time to dispose of you.
And there won't be any witnesses left.
Dispose...?
Is this... the end for me?
Without even knowing why? So matter-of-factly?
To hell with that! Power! If I only had power!
Power to escape this place!
Power not to lose the world!
What... What is this?
You desire power?
That voice... The girl who was shot?
You already possess the power you seek.
It's merely imprisoned within a cage of amnesia.
Remember...
Remember who you really are!
The power of the king!
Now... let the seal...
...be broken!
I see now.
Persistent irritation that pricked me
like thorns in my everyday life.
Yes... Heh!
It was all the phony memories implanted in me!
But I remember now... I am...!
I am...!
I am... Zero!
Lelouch. I'm not asking for forgiveness.
After all, we're friends, aren't we?
Yes... That's your answer, isn't it, Suzaku?!
Before you dispose of me,
I'd like you to answer a question.
That girl's still alive!
Impossible! She was shot through the heart!
If being powerless is so terribly wrong,
then does having power make you right?
Do you find vengeance evil?
What's your value of friendship? Is it justice?
Heh, there is no justice or evil.
The only truth that's left for you,
bait, is the simple reality of death.
I see.
Then that reality is all that remains for you, as well.
I, Lelouch vi Britannia, command you!
All of you...
DIE!
It-It can't be!
Yes, Your Highness!
Ever since that day, my heart simply couldn't accept it.
This fake life I was never able to fit into.
All the time that was lost.
These false memories planted in me,
giving me a life as one of the herd.
And yet...
The truth continues to guide me toward itself.
That's right!
It wasn't me who was wrong! It was the world!
The world has to change. So I will change it.
We've been waiting for you, Master Zero!
Please, give us your orders!
Very well...
Because, after all, I am Zero!
The one who will crush the world...!
...and the one who will re-create the world anew!
Yes... Your Majesty.
I have no intention of assigning this task to anyone else.
The one who will kill Zero...
...shall be me.
I can't forgive them! I mustn't forgive them!
My memories are my own personal and individual reality!
They are the truth, and that truth defines me!
Someone trampled them.
I was tamed like a domestic animal
then looked down upon as mere bait.
The time for payback has come!
Now, I'll give Britannia something to remember.
The true meaning of Zero's return to this world!
Because I no longer have need for their deceptive rule!