The Knights of the Round have become
members of the student council.
And while I still haven't cleared that problem,
what...
What were you saying?!
That Shirley and I were...
Yes. It's true, Shirley and you were kissing.
Mm! Uh?!
Um, I wasn't wrong in doing that, was I?
I was afraid she might discover this control room,
so I thought that's what I should do in your character.
Bad call.
You were mistaken there.
Sayoko! I've told you already!
You were acting too nice as his stand-in!
No, hold on.
Aside from this, she did a good job.
Lelouch! I know Sayoko used to be in your service but...!
Actually, to be precise,
I was working for the Ashford family.
I know that!
You were in charge of caring for Nunnally, right?
I guess the problems of the
Knights of Round will have to wait.
Master Lelouch, I have your schedule for tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Sayoko made promises to other people
without considering all the consequences.
I was instructed to maintain
his interpersonal relationships.
It can't be helped.
Quite careless for a female ninja.
I am a secret service agent.
A 37th master of the Shinozaki school...
Sayoko!
Wha... What's with this schedule?!
Allowing for three hours of sleep,
you have dates scheduled with 108 girls.
Fourteen of them are waiting for cancellations,
and they've been on the wait list for six months.
Lulu just did it so suddenly!
I wonder if I can say we're going steady...
But I wasn't able to talk to him today.
Prez! Can I have a minute with you
when we go back to our room?
There's something I'd really like to talk to you about.
Prez?
Huh?! Oh, sorry, Shirley. I didn't hear you.
No, it's okay. I just...
I've got a date with Lelouch tomorrow!
Huh?!
Oh? I heard that Giselle in class B said
that she'd go to the art gallery with him.
Yup! He's taking me out, too, to a movie.
Me, too!
Lu... Lu...!
And that confirms your schedule for today.
Since you have no classes pending,
I was able to fill all 24 hours.
At 0700 hours, you'll enjoy a homemade box lunch.
At 09:00 hours, you'll visit the art gallery.
At 10:30 hours, shopping.
At 12 noon, a trip to the aquarium,
and from there travel abroad Shinkiro.
Please go underwater until
you are 400 kilometers from shore.
You'll change clothes inside the cockpit
and proceed to the Chinese Federation,
where you'll conclude a trade treaty
in Shang Hai at 15:00 hours
You are allotted 47 minutes to
complete your business there,
then you'll return here to
see a late movie at 21:00 hours.
At midnight 02, you'll meet
your next date for a live show,
and then...
He's late!
Sorry, Shirley.
I promise I'll make time later to explain all this to you.
You can start by explaining it to me.
Lady Anya!
There's something I want to ask.
Don't tell me I have a date with a Knight of the Round!
Same Lelouch?
Uh?
That's a picture of me when
I was still a prince back in the homeland!
O-Of course not. Remarkable likeness.
But you know I'm only a commoner.
Lelouch, old man!
Ah! What?!
May I please go to your chess games with you?
Only the underground ones where you bet!
When I told him h you gambled on your games,
he begged me to take him along.
Rivalz... I swear, you're...!
Oh, brother, they never quit! Just gimme a break, already!
He's running away!
Don't go ruining my reputation!
I've got tickets for the late show in my room!
If I break my commitment, then my next date will... Ah...!
Darn it, Sayoko!
Lelouch is too frail for such a heavy schedule.
And what's up with all these women?
It's sorta like a mental problem
Who did that?! I said I wasn't running away!
Uh?!
Shirley...!
So, what lucky girl do you have a date with this time?
Um, I uh...
You not only gamble, but you run around
with other girls, too?! Ah! You're pathetic!
Wait a minute! It's just...
Uh. I forgot. Here.
This is for not explaining to you about it.
Oh, it's an apology? What, you think you can
fix what you did by giving me some silly thing?!
You've got it all wrong! I just wanted to apologize!
An apology?!
This is not good. I'm clearly doing something
wrong and don't know how to make it right.
Dammit, if only C.C. was here to help me.
Attention everyone!
I have decided on my graduation event!
And I'm going to christen it Cupid Day!
That's swell, but isn't it a bit early for graduation?
Well not for me. I'm repeating my senior year.
I can graduate as soon as I earn enough course credit.
Oh... so that's how the education system works here.
Prez, are you really planning to graduate soon?
Why not wait and do it with the rest of us?
Milly, my dear...
Madam President!
This "Cupid Day" of yours, what exactly is it?
You wanna know?
Meow.
On the appointed day, I'll have every
student in school wearing one of these hats.
The boys will get this color.
Then, if you steal the hat of your target and put it on...
And then what?
By order of the student council president, me,
those two will be proclaimed boyfriend and girlfriend!
Huh?!
Wha...?!
Hm... It's a bit rash, isn't it?
Declaring war on the Chinese Federation?
Hm, is that what His Majesty said?
Yes. He told us to take all of it.
I agree!
I say take out the Chinese Federation for good!
Those savages humiliated Odysseus,
and we can never forgive them for that.
Guinevere, I harbor no grudge for
the incident that occurred with the empress.
The war with the E.U. is ongoing,
and Area 11 is on the path to peace,
so I'd prefer to settle this without...
Oh, as if we care about what Nunnally does there!
Carine, Nunnally is around your age.
You should make an attempt to be friends with her.
This would be an easy matter
to solve if Cornelia was present.
Bismark, have you heard anything?
I haven't.
And she apparently hasn't contacted Lord Guilford, either.
Then who will lead our troops?
We can station two divisions along the Mongolian border.
Huh? Are you offering to take command, Prince Schneizel?
Battle is unnecessary.
The Chinese Federation has fallen apart.
We can gain half their territory
by rattling sabers and through negotiations.
Will that placate the emperor?
Oh? Is that what Schneizel said?
Yes, Your Majesty. Do you approve?
You, the Knight of One,
the mightiest knight of the empire, asks me that?
Your Majesty, war is merely one method of diplomacy.
However, it's far and away the least efficient of them.
Heh. Perhaps you're right.
War has historically been an action favored by idiots.
I've finally grabbed it. The tail of Geass!
And now I'll drag it from the shadows.
I'll wipe away the stain from Euphy's name at last!
Princess... Where are you now?
C'mon, Suzaku. It's Milly's graduation event.
It's like I said before. I'd really wanna go.
But unlike you and Anya,
I'm an aide to a viceroy, so I just can't.
Meetings come first.
Jeez, you really need to loosen up, my friend.
Say hi to my fiancé for me, will you?
What? You're serious about that?
You should probably give her a call after we're done here.
Huh?!
"Now" has a funny habit of not waiting around forever.
Wow, what a surprise.
I never thought I'd hear you
say something like that, Guilford.
Your rank may have changed,
but you did start out as Princess Euphemia's knight.
As the knight of Princess Cornelia,
I'd like you to see me as a source
of advice that you'll ask for when needed.
Well that's mature of you!
Anyway, can we get to the main question at hand now?
It's about the Guren, which I have taken into my care...
Took you long enough.
So, am I here for torture? Or maybe execution?
Do what you want with me.
I'll do nothing like that to you.
It's been a such a long time. Hello, Kallen.
At this rate, it'll be impossible for me
to smash the world and create a new one!
It's Cupid Day. I'm going to end my
relationship with all the girls at today's event.
Ah. That will leave you free and in the clear.
Fortunately, we were able to
get the teachers to participate in this, too.
Huh?
Villetta, you're going to steal my hat from me.
But won't that just invite weird misunderstandings?
I think Sayoko needs to take responsibility here...
Sorry, but I can't help.
I have to play stand-in
during the event for Master Lelouch.
And we've got to make sure
that some strange girl doesn't get it!
Have Shirley grab the hat!
Yes, that's definitely an option to consider.
That girl is completely head-over-heels for you.
She did shoot me in order to protect you, after all.
That's why I don't want her mixed up in this any further.
Huh?
Yes, that's right, Suzaku.
The rooftop garden's finally finished.
Suppose I can't keep avoiding the real world forever.
I'm sorry.
I really hate missing your graduation event.
I understand. You have important work to do, right?
Um, y-yeah.
Then my final act for you is
to cast my special magic spell!
Huh?
Relax! Ha, ha. You need to unwind from time to time.
Thanks a lot Prez, I appreciate it.
See ya!
Now let's get this show on the road.
Attention everyone! This is Milly Ashford
speaking for the last time as student council president!
My graduation event, Cupid Day, is about to begin!
Oh, and before you start,
make sure you're at least
two meters away from your target.
Lulu. I don't care how hopeless you are...
No! Since you are utterly hopeless,
it's up to me to salvage you!
Prez, you don't really want to be engaged, do you?
Deep down, you want me to steal you away. Right?
You should all be familiar with the rules.
If you capture your target's hat and put it on,
then you have to be boyfriend and girlfriend!
I won't question how you obtain the hat.
You're allowed to use teams or tools, as well.
Now, before we begin, I'll just say one thing.
Any club that brings me the hat of Lelouch Lamperouge
in class 3-D gets their budget increased ten-fold!
What?!
Lulu's hat?!
Prez, why?!
Tsk! This is all a horrible dream!
All right! Let's do it!
Lulu wait...
Stopping this many people at once is incredibly hard work!
Oops. Sorry 'bout that.
Now, move.
He's mine!
Huh?! ... Aagh!
He vanished! Where'd he go?!
Sorry about this.
Forget it. We're good.
H-H-Hold on.
Should that theory be accurate,
then we're the worst criminals in all of history!
Let's get out of here!
We're through fine-tuning Jeremiah!
We'd be abandoning our nation!
Freeze! My dear Bartley...
That voice... Princess Cornelia?!
Why are you here, Bartley?
Thank heaven you've come! Please save us!
Hm?
We were ordered to be here. By the emperor.
My father?
The world is racing down the path towards destruction!
Uh?!
Follow me, ladies!
Lord Gino!
I see.
It appears that Gino did come
to this school just to play around.
Anya seems suspicious about my true identity,
but not enough to prove troublesome.
The matter of the Knights of the Round has been cleared.
Now, I've only to switch places with Sayoko
and have her play along with the Prez...
I did it! Now I get to be Lelouch's girlfriend!
Of course.
Miya, right?
What's up, honey bunch?
Would you mind very much... giving me that hat back?
Okay.
So where should we switch?
Here will do.
Very well, then.
Hm? Whoa, now I'm more confused than usual.
What am I doing here?
Huh? Lelouch is gone?
Yeah, according to the gardening club.
Rugy team here!
Lelouch has been spotted at point KT-01!
Yes...!
Alert all Ashford Academy club members!
Surround Lelouch between
the boy's dorms and the central courtyard!
Sir! Yes, sir!
Hm? Agh!
The rugby team's getting that budget bonus, pal!
GO...!
Huh?!
Fair thee well!
Huh?
Sayoko! Watch what you have me say!
Or I'll come off as being kind of mental.
Sorry, it was involuntary.
Just be careful. And don't go to the rear gate.
Villetta's standing by there.
Understood.
Lelouch is more physical than normal.
I would like to let you catch me,
Miss Milly, but at the moment...
Archery and equestrian clubs,
from the side of hall, you can surround him!
Go on around the school buildings to gym number two.
The science club will probably be positioned dead ahead.
Fire!
No way!
Lelouch can't do stuff like that!
If this keeps up, he won't need my help after all.
Sayoko's overdoing it, but that's how she operates.
There's no point ordering her to stop.
Oh, well, she can take my place in Phys Ed from here on.
Glamour squad, move in!
After all, Lelouch is a warm-blooded male.
Yeah, we'll catch him off guard.
Using your bodies against me is useless!
Huh...?! Wow, I'm sort of in shock!
Where's Lelouch?!
Where'd he go?!
Nobody's caught him yet!
Attention, all students!
If Vice President Lelouch is spotted,
commence a simultaneous...
Oh boy, the Prez is in full-scale "play" mode.
Still... what's going on?
I thought Lulu was completely hopeless
but now I'm finding out he's a super athlete.
Hey look, it's Shirley!
We have to catch Lelouch!
Prez! If Lelouch is who you want,
then I, Rivalz Cardemonde, will give you what you want!
My best friend in the world!
Uh. Huh? Whoa, that can't be for real...!
It is.
The Mordred's just been launched?!
It's the Black Knights then?!
Emergency dispatch from the government bureau!
Defcon 2! Defcon 2!
A riot has erupted in the school district!
Knight police SWAT unit, prepare to move out!
Uh! I should have guessed that Anya doesn't
possess a grain of common sense, either!
Take the operation into
final phase! Sayoko, to the library!
Oh, there.
Hm... This is the spot where Lulu was acting strange.
I wonder...
Shirley... Why now all times?
Heat sources. Two places.
But which one is Lelouch?
Hm?
Watch out!
Twin Lelouches?
Knight of Six, my lady!
This is an operations area of the O.S.I.!
Please, withdraw your Knightmare at once!
This is wrong?
Yes, very wrong.
Wrong.
Say, Lulu...
Hm?
Why did you kiss me before?
Well, um, because...
...I like you.
That's a lie, I know you aren't serious.
Wrong!
Uh?
I mean... I just...
A good question.
So, you wanna do more than just kiss?
Huh?!
It's okay, even if you're not serious.
Uh! You shouldn't speak that way!
Welcome back, Lulu.
Huh?
You haven't been yourself lately, you know.
It's okay. I forgive you.
In return, close your eyes for me.
Huh?
Hurry up.
O-Okay.
You thought I was gonna give you a smooch?
Um, well, ya know... I thought there was a possibility...
Oh, you dirty boy!
No, it's just...!
Even so, I wanna try and make you
fall in love with me for real, some day.
Uh...
I told you. I said love is power.
I can see you guys still have
a lot to learn around here, don't you?
This is a school for commoners.
Things like this take place all the time!
Look at that!
How disappointing, but I'm not surprised.
I guess that's the end of game.
Butit might have meant little more this time around.
Huh?
Yeah. Maybe It did...
...a bit.
What in the world was all that uproar about?
Sorry, sir.
It looks like it was the president's graduation event.
It's unusual to say the least that
he would change plans like that.
Changed plans?
Uh, I meant she.
Shirley's plan apparently worked out quite well.
Lelouch!
Looks like you finally understand.
Hm?
You mean you did this for us?
Cause you two really wear on my patience.
Don't ever hesitate, your student days coming to an end.
Uh! Prez, are... you really graduating?
Mm-hm!
Hey, Prez!
What is it?
Thank you for everything you've done here at school.
Uh.
The last three years were so much fun!
You were the best president ever!
Thank you!
Madame president!
Congratulations on graduating from Ashford.
Mm-hm. And with that, this girl
is no longer avoiding real world!
Hello, everyone! How are you?
My name's Milly Ashford!
Beginning today, I'll be your go-to-girl for
weather information here on the weather corner!
Let's start with an update...
From student council president to a weather reporter.
How'd she qualify?
I heard she chose a talent agency while still in school.
Hmm...
She's from nobility.
She said she never likes to do anything halfway, so...
Then why'd she call off her engagement?
Did she have to?
Wow, Lloyd must be in a state of shock!
Just what I'd expect from my former fiance.
Lloyd doesn't seem upset about it.
It's all bravado.
No, the man never wanted
to get married in the first place.
You see, Nina?
I'm trying to face who I really am.
Yeah, I saw her on TV. Typical Prez, huh?
So, what do you think we ought
to do with the rooftop garden?
Right.
Well then, I'll bring back some
herb seedlings from the store.
Would you talk to the gardening club, Lulu?
Okay, see ya later!
Huh?!
This is the eighth area, correct?
Yes. But the people who were affected by the Geass power
have been deployed as secret police, haven't they?
We don't know, so we're cleaning up the situation.
You've been given a Geass Canceller,
which can destroy all types of Geass power. Therefore...
Yes, I understand.
We don't know who's under the influence of Geass.
However, once I'm done with Ashford Academy,
I'll take care of old business with Lelouch.
I'm remembering now...
I remember Zero, and the one who killed my father...
It's Lelouch!
I must give Japan its independence.
And at the same time, I have to
put together a dating itinerary with Shirley.
There are 18 hypothetical routes.
I've set up a way for C.C. and Kaguya
to send me emergency messages.
I may even get the chance to work out
rescue preparations for Kallen.
But I have no idea what Shirley will like.
What should I do? Is there someone I can consult?
I get the feeling that I'm going to
make the wrong choices again.
That worries me to no end!