The capital Pendragon's been obliterated?!
Is it true?!
They say it was a F.L.E.I.J.A. warhead.
The thing that wiped out the Tokyo Settlement?
An accident?
But I heard the F.L.E.I.J.A.s
they built are all missing now.
Stop spreading wild rumors!
It's imprudent to talk as if the
capital's been destroyed, even as rumors!
No, I'm afraid it's all true.
What?! You!
Please take me to Lelouch. It's urgent.
N-Nunnally...
It's you... You're alive!
Yes, thanks to our brother, Schneizel.
Schneizel...
Nunnally...
Do you understand what Schneizel has done?
Yes. He attacked the capitol, Pendragon
with a F.L.E.I.J.A. warhead.
If you know about that, then why?!
Do you think that using Geass on people is better?!
Both you and big brother have been
lying to me from the very beginning, haven't you?
You've kept the truth from me all this time.
But now I know everything.
Lelouch, you were Zero all along, weren't you?
Why?!
Tell me. Were you doing it for my sake?
Because, if you were that means...
For your sake?
I see my little sister is presumptuous as ever!
You think it's just natural for people to
help you all the time out of sympathy and pity?
It's so easy to criticize others
while you keep your own hands unsullied.
You are the quintessence of the
privileged aristocrat that I've rejected.
You... No...
I act for no one's sake!
It is for me, my sake,
that I take the world into my hands!
If you choose to stand in my way
by allying yourself with Schneizel,
I won't hesitate to crush you without mercy!
And without regret.
Lelouch!
Are you all right, Nunnally?
That must have been very hard for you, Nunnally.
I thought showing him the power of
the F.L.E.I.J.A. might convince him to surrender.
Schneizel. Are the people of Pendragon really all right?
Are you sure they're safe?
You needn't worry.
We gave warning for them to evacuate well in advance.
Of course, the damage to the city was significant,
but we did everything we could to minimize it.
But, now we'll have to use the weapon on people,
on Lelouch and his followers...
If they stand in the way of world peace,
we'll have no choice.
Schneizel, please...
Will you let me have the
F.L.E.I.J.A. firing switch to hold onto?
I can't fight battles or defend my country or my people.
So, at the very least,
I want this sin to be on my shoulders.
Schneizel, may I please have a word with you?
Tch!
C.C., why didn't you find out about Nunnally?!
I'm certainly not a god.
I can only read people if they're
connected to the power of Geass.
Tch! Schneizel!
You knew but you kept the truth from me all this time!
Just so you could play this card at the right moment!
Still, the way that you shuffled
the deck was more than artful.
It was remarkable and effective.
Lelouch.
Our strategic objective's unchanged.
We can't stop this just because
we found out that Nunnally is still alive...
Or the Zero Requiem will have no meaning.
Remember your promise!
Suzaku!
I am his sword.
It's my job to rid him of his
enemies and his own weakness.
And you, C.C., you must be his shield.
Huh?
Your job is to protect him.
We do things as you like.
Lelouch is your accomplice, isn't he?
My accomplice? Huh.
The F.L.E.I.J.A. they used on Pendragon
had ten times the effective range of
the one used on the Tokyo Settlement.
If they haven't developed a new model, then...
They've removed the limiter?
Bingo.
By removing both the effect range
and the detonation time limiter...
Prince Schneizel, how could you?
Yes, what about it?
You mean the people of Pendragon were...!
I made them vanish.
It was better for them than a life,
swearing loyalty to Lelouch, wouldn't you say?
They're our own people. And you told Nunnally...
Lies are expedient.
There's no need to tell Nunnally things that would
get in the way of her opposition to Lelouch, is there?
She'll never know the difference.
You use everyone?
Even your own sister?
Cornelia, what is it that people truly want?
Starvation and poverty?
Discrimination and corruption? War and terrorism?
They want the problems that are
flooding the world to go away forever.
People can't understand each other
under these situations at all.
Your theories don't justify butchering civilians.
Even civilians who have rejected war
depend on the police, don't they?
Everyone knows, don't they?
That people are driven by their own desires.
The lust that dwells within the soul of man
cannot be denied.
So why win hearts and minds or tout some shining ideology?
Why not bring peace to the world with a system and power?
In ten days, Damocles will enter
the airspace of the United States of China,
and then switch over to a secondary acceleration.
After that, we're scheduled to
ascend 300 kilometers above the surface.
From there, we will hit every
enemy nation with F.L.E.I.J.A.s.
Are you insane?!
We only agreed to use them against Lelouch!
This will destroy the world!
You're trying to control people through fear!
Mankind's history is war.
Peace is an illusion.
To turn illusion into reality is an arduous task.
It requires discipline.
And you plan to discipline the
entire human race all by yourself?!
Only a god could pull that off!
Then I shall become a god.
If that is what it takes to bring peace to the world.
You're deranged.
Magnificent!
I knew I was right to change sides and support you!
Surpassing Zero's chaos with a state of perfect
nothingness, and a kaleidoscopic transformation!
Prince Schneizel, we've made
contact with the Black Knights.
They say if you plan to kill Lelouch,
they're willing to join you immediately.
Thank you, Kanon.
Those who've experienced Lelouch's
tyranny first hand will have no alternative
but to choose the lesser of evils.
Is that why you stayed back and
let Lelouch get away with this until now?!
It was a way to minimize the damage.
But in the end, if we have to
sacrifice one or two billion lives
to achieve a state of permanent peace...
You're wrong!
Peace attained by force is not peace!
This is so sad, Cornelia.
Schneizel outmaneuvered us.
He had another escape plane
as a decoy during the battle of Tokyo.
And so...
The plane destroyed by the F.L.E.I.J.A. was the decoy.
That's right, and now he's trying to use
Miss Nunnally to control Master Lelouch.
You're Japanese, aren't you?
Why come to Master Lelouch instead of the Black Knights?
Uh...
You're devoted to chivalry as well, aren't you?
Ah. Perhaps there's some truth to that.
I'm impressed.
You didn't drop your mask in front of Nunnally.
No matter what angle I use to attack
the problem, the answer is always the same:
The conclusion I came to then wasn't wrong.
Lelouch, haven't you done enough?
You've handled this well.
You understand why I'm doing this evil, don't you?
Besides, under the rule of Democles,
people would become lifeless puppets.
That's true, but Nunnally is aboard Damocles.
Everything you've done from the beginning was for her.
I can't treat her differently any longer.
So many people have died since this began.
For their sakes, we have to see it through to the end.
Don't we, C.C.?
Yes. You are right, Lelouch.
Are you sure you want to join with us?
It means you'd be fighting against Britannia.
Y'know, right now...
Huh?
Right now, I think I understand your feelings just a bit.
Uh...
Uh, well, thanks, I guess.
I beg your pardon?
Pendragon was the capital of the Holy Britannian Empire.
With its destruction, their
internal government is paralyzed.
They're confronting our
Black Knight forces in every part of the world
so they're pinned down everywhere.
In short, the only force Lelouch can deploy against us
is the division he brought to reoccupy Japan.
But the balance of power
can be tipped for him at any time.
To minimize damage, we cannot hesitate.
The time to confront him is now!
Since Schneizel has now agreed to join us,
our forces are evenly matched with the enemy.
Our intention is not the approval
of the Damocles use of F.L.E.I.J.A.s.
It's bringing unity to the world is our first priority.
This battle...
This battle is the ultimate test.
Control of the entire world at stake!
If we defeat Schneizel and the Black Knights,
then there will be no one left to stand in our way!
This world shall be destroyed and then recreated
by Lelouch, the one, true emperor of Britannia!
Crush them!
Destroy Schneizel and the sky fortress Damocles!
Crush them all!
We have nothing to fear!
My name is the future of this world!
All hail Lelouch!
Lelouch has spread malice
and turmoil all across the globe.
As the enemy of peace, he must be wiped out.
It is time for the Black Knights,
and for us, to cast aside the
grudges of the past and join forces!
The people of the world are waiting
for our song of victory!
I pray that, for all time, this shall be
the last battle in the last war
that mankind will ever need to fight!
Oh, Lelouch...
I'll make both of you into records on my hard drive.
Are you sure Anya will be all right in the battle?
I know you promised to restore
her memory, Your Highness, but...
We need every bit of battle strength we have. So...
Oh? An open channel?
Official greetings, Schneizel.
Lelouch, if you're going to surrender, now is the time.
We have an arsenal of F.L.E.I.J.A.s, ready to launch.
F.L.E.I.J.A.s? I wonder if you dare to use them.
Considering that I have all the U.F.N.
representatives aboard the Avalon with me.
He's hiding behind the hostages he took!
I can't believe he'd go this far!
So, Schneizel, these people are from
all over the world. They're not related to you.
You're right, they're not.
Their lives are a small price to pay...
Schneizel, you can't attack!
I understand that the U.F.N. members
have elected acting representatives to speak for them.
We're prepared for the worst,
and we know how dire this is.
But that doesn't mean we're going
to throw their lives away on a gamble!
Li Xing-ke, aside from the Damocles,
our strike force consists only of the Mordred.
If you're going to tie our hands
so we can't use the F.L.E.I.J.A.s,
then I request that you put me
in charge of all our united forces.
We're facing Lelouch!
Exactly. I've never lost to Lelouch. Ever.
And I know him far better than anyone on this battlefield.
Understood.
Deploy the Shen Hu.
Transmit the command structure to all forces!
Yes, sir!
Then, shall we let the game play out, brother?
Indeed.
Kanon, it's just as you predicted.
Yes. The Black Knights are now
yours to command, your highness.
Heh. Transmit pattern Sigma to all forces.
Enemy fleets are in motion,
deploying into a wide-field aerial formation.
He's using conventional forces. Good.
Stretch our left wing!
Assume Half-Moon Spirit formation!
Yes, Your Majesty!
Their main wings are undermanned.
Have Gino's unit advance.
Keep the enemy's left wing from extending!
Yes, Your Highness!
Checking my move.
Reverse the direction of our left wing!
That'll break up our formation!
Do it!
Gino, halt your advance, now!
But why?
We should strike while they're in disarray.
It's a false opening.
I'm not buying it.
Not falling for it, huh?
Switch our battle plan to Ursa Major formation!
Sixth Unit, follow Anya and move
to the northeast, elevate 40 degrees!
Bombardiers, prep for anti-air combat!
Anya, stop there, climb 200 meters and stabilize!
What the hell?! Nobody's fighting!
You're wrong.
Contests fought between two masters are decided instantly.
An invisible battle is now raging between the two of them.
We have to hurry.
They're going to attack each other any moment now.
They're surrounding us!
Counter move!
Reinforce the front line with Suzaku's Lancelot!
Hold at combat speed four! And send out Ward's unit!
Ah-ha, you haven't changed, Lelouch.
You'd rather attack my front line
than defend your own flanks.
I now have a small window.
Xing-ke?
Heh. He's already incorporated our skill levels.
The enemy's left wing is breaking away!
Stand fast!
Live up to His Majesty's trust in us!
If we can defeat Lelouch, this will be over!
If we smash their line, it'll be a free-for-all...!
They're punching through!
They're cutting us to pieces.
Should I have Suzaku fall back?
No, that's what Schneizel wants us to do.
Draw in the battle line! Fall back and regroup!
Their fleet is damaged and falling back.
Don't lose the momentum!
Push forward!
Guren, you're too far out!
Match pace with us and we can surround them!
I understand, but...!
Don't rush!
If we beat their vanguard, we'll isolate the Avalon!
The Dreadnought is destroyed! They're breaking through!
So that's how it stands.
I don't wish to engage the
Black Knights as formidable enemies.
However, my side has motive.
For His Majesty!
It's heartrending.
Seeing soldiers controlled by the false power of Geass.
And so!
This is the moment. Smash both wings.
Bow-mounted hadron scatter cannon, now set!
Move the Seventh Squad out of the firing angle!
Gefjun control synched.
Ready to fire!
Target both enemy wings. And fire!
Zero, with all of us working together,
we can defeat you!
It seems that Lelouch badly underestimated
the fighting skills of the Black Knights.
Well, Lelouch?
Right.
They've shown great skill, forcing me to use this plan!
Dammit!
Energy chain reaction, below us!
What?!
Impossible! He timed this to...?!
All forces! Deploy radiant shields!
Zero!
I was the one who first acknowledged
his leadership and encouraged the others to follow him.
So I'm responsible for all of this.
But I don't want a new life caught up in it.
I know this is a selfish request,
but I want you stay here on Horai Island.
Please.
Ohgi, please respond!
Minami! Rakshata!
It can't be...!
He used the Sakuradite in the Fuji mines.
Yes, he has.
Destroying his own ground forces as well.
I was careless!
So, that was Lelouch's tactical plan.
But how could he sacrifice his own forces?!
This has drastically depleted the enemy's strength.
Which leaves Damocles...
...wide open.
In reality, it's you who's been checked.
And you brought it on yourself.
Nunnally, targeting is complete.
Now that the Black Knights have been smashed,
we must use the F.L.E.I.J.A.'s power.
Yes.
With this act, I will wipe away my brother's sins!
Incoming! It's a F.L.E.I.J.A.!
So, he's finally launched. Special division three!
Yes, Your Majesty!
It's useless.
It can't be stopped;
the F.L.E.I.J.A. went critical the
moment it was fired from the Damocles.
Avalon continue to fall back.
All units, charge at the Damocles.
Force them to keep launching the
F.L.E.I.J.A. warheads until their arsenal is empty.
Ohgi! Ohgi!
Ohgi, please!
This is no time to play dead!
I-I don't believe it. You two shielded us?
We were only able to protect the bridge though, eh?
You're on your own now.
Hang in there. Let's go...! Kallen!
Oh, great... Who's the guy giving orders?
Tch. Now that I've used the Fuji plan,
and considering the number of
the remaining F.L.E.I.J.A. warheads,
I'm at a disadvantage of one move.
Meaning, I have to depend on Nina now.
Can she do it? I know she hates me.
Detests me for being Zero, Euphy's murderer.
The enemy of her precious Britannia which I now rule.
And yet, to defeat Schneizel...
I wonder... Do you really think
you can defeat me, Lelouch?
Because if you do, you're at the end of your path.
A man who has not mastered
the use of the mask can never prevail.
Suzaku and I...
Together, there was nothing we couldn't do.
That's what I thought.
But now, Schneizel has proven an unrelenting foe.
The truth is, it's his detachment, his lack of desire.
A man coldly focused,
who understands Geass and possesses the F.L.E.I.J.A.s.
What strategy does he pursue?
Is there any tactic that can work on a battlefield
where F.L.E.I.J.A.s rain down from the sky?
I have one last gamble, one final card to play.
And it lies within Schneizel's own heart.