Ohgi, are you sure you wanna go through with this?
Yeah.
I have a duty to get everyone to safety.
But...!
No. I'm just sorry I did this to you.
Everyone...
In a battlefield controlled by F.L.E.I.J.A.s.
Another F.L.E.I.J.A. strike...
Twammi fleet is totally obliterated! The operation...
I'm not going to stop it!
Stay just out of the Damocles' range!
The Avalon falls back as ordered!
All units! Attack in waves and force the Damocles
to continue launching F.L.E.I.J.A.s.
How easily... It's so easy...
...for me to...
Nunnally, we're ready to fire the next one.
Right.
It renders tactics useless.
However... If I can get within a tight range,
they won't be able to use it!
A blaze luminous!
But it's so immense!
The Damocles was specially designed and built
to achieve absolute air superiority.
If it reaches a certain altitude,
we'll lose our only chance against it!
Tch! Suzaku!
Can you break through those defenses?!
I'm trying!
But their power output is in a different league than mine!
But I don't think they can fire a F.L.E.I.J.A. now.
And, in turn, our attacks
can't break through their shield.
We may as well be spectators.
Is there nothing left for the world
except to cower before the
crushing might of the F.L.E.I.J.A.s?
Well, that offers a sort of peace, too.
Mass our remaining forces around the Avalon!
We're going to launch a direct assault
on the Damocles with our hostages on board!
Sure about that?
Your return here means it's nearly figured out, I presume.
The rest depends on you and Suzaku, Your Majesty.
Schneizel!
Are you trying to kill the captives, too?!
Now that the Black Knights have been beaten...
We aren't beaten yet!
Very well then, I'll wait ten minutes.
Ten minutes?!
Aren't you talking to me because
you're already in position to counterattack?
All right, fine. Ten minutes.
That's a hefty loan, sir, considering
we need ten minutes to prep the next shot.
It saves me from dealing with them after the battle.
Are you saying you don't need the Black Knights anymore?
What purpose would a collective
military strength possibly serve?
Hey, Rivalz.
What's up, Prez?
It's amazing. I mean, when you think about it,
our student council members
are out fighting the whole world.
What, is that sarcasm?
'Cause I wasn't able to protect Nina, correct?
Don't beat yourself up. You did your very best.
I tried, but I...
No. You really did.
From behind?!
The Black Knights!
I'll defeat you myself, I swear!
Sneaking from behind, Xing-ke?
I won't let the Avalon be shot down!
Xing-ke, you'll fail!
Justice weighs on my side!
It's over!
What the...?!
Kururugi!
You dare fight in your condition?!
You turned your back on your country
in order to climb in rank,
so here is the ugly way it ends!
What is this you fight for?!
The one thing I want that I'll fight for is a future!
Your future is worthless!
I failed!
General!
Dammit!
Oh?
They've done better than I expected.
Primary float, damaged.
Damage level, 75%.
It's failed. The Avalon is falling!
I can't let them board it!
Hold it, hold it, hold it!
Okay! Now to settle things once and for a...
Huh? I'm not giving in! I've got pride, too, ya know!
I wasn't in time. Did they get in?
If we engage them in close combat,
we've a chance to take over their power
and communications, then rescue the hostages!
We hear and obey!
Holding out this long was good enough.
Land the ship in the Pacific.
You will now follow mission Apate Aletheia.
Master Lelouch...
You have served me well.
I'm grateful for the resolve you've all shown.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Should we fire another F.L.E.I.J.A. now?
We still have our blaze luminous
and should wait for criticality.
Good point.
But it's an excellent opportunity
to eliminate the Black Knights.
No, I suppose we shouldn't. That's too ambitious.
Yes, I understand.
This is a personal request from me. However...
It was Princess Euphemia's wish, too, wasn't it?
Yes, which is why I have to do it.
But for the device to be complete,
the environmental data needs to
be entered into the final program.
You should let me go with you...
No, you've done enough for me, Nina.
What you just said reveals your true feelings about this.
Yes, you've done enough for me.
For Zero, Euphy's murderer.
I won't find it in my heart to forgive Zero.
Maybe not for the rest of my life. But...
This is separate from that.
I simply had to find my own
answer to everything that's happened.
That's all there is to it.
You're truly amazing.
C.C.! Are you all right?
Well, that's a switch.
Were you really worried about me?
You're a valued combatant.
Hmph. That's why I came to pick that up.
Then... will you be escorting me?
You're going out there?
Though taking such action could
mean you'll have to kill Nunnally yourself.
I have no choice if she stands
in the way of the Zero Requiem.
Lelouch, don't you hate me for
cheating you out of your own life?
By giving you your Geass,
I affected your life and drastically changed your fate.
That doesn't sound like you, the immortal witch.
C.C... the Geass power you gave me...
It only put me on the path that would
lead to my destiny, and nothing more.
Everything that followed was my choice.
In all my life, I've never met a man like you.
C.C...
Kallen!
I'm going to stop you!
Goodbye, Lelouch.
Leave this to me! Get to the Damocles!
You stubborn...!
Stop! You're no match for the Guren!
I'm sincerely glad that you care, Lelouch.
Now go on, hurry!
Just make sure you come back! That'll make me smile, okay?
Yes! I promise you!
I have to succeed, no matter what!
This move must work!
Enemy Knightmares approaching.
The Shinkirou is leading them.
Lower the blaze luminous away from
the F.L.E.I.J.A. launch tube, immediately.
We're going to redirect our aim at the Shinkirou.
Lelouch, discarding your life at the end?
How unsightly.
Realignment complete.
Nunnally. It ends now. Can you do this?
Yes, brother Schneizel.
Blaze luminous, lowered.
Now.
Right. Entering data.
The F.L.E.I.J.A. changes
composition from moment to moment.
If we collide it with a reaction
corresponding to that composition,
we can prevent it from reaching criticality.
However, you need to input
the local environment data just prior to detonation,
within a 19 second time frame.
And, even if you complete the program,
you'll only have 0.04 seconds to execute.
With this, peace will come.
Suzaku!
Yes, Your Majesty!
Now!
It should work in theory, but...
Princess Euphemia...!
Hm?
A F.L.E.I.J.A.!
It disappeared!
It worked? They did it?
In 19 seconds and then in 0.04 seconds?
I didn't expect them to have made a toy like that.
Ready... Fly in!
They gotten through the blaze?!
They have indeed.
Enemy infiltration, alpha-three!
Where's the key?! I must find the Damocles key!
Delta block communications cut!
Float control room six has been destroyed!
Prince Schneizel!
My kudos, Lelouch. I salute you.
For forcing me to implement my final plan.
Huh?! You're really going to do that?!
Hm?
Yes.
Turn the Damocles into
a prison for Lelouch and the others.
After we've abandoned ship,
we'll obliterate the Damocles entirely with a F.L.E.I.J.A.
What a fine coffin for him.
I'm certain you'll be pleased with it, Lelouch.
If Damocles reaches satellite orbit,
even the Lancelot will be useless against it.
To win, we need to stop Schneizel.
I'm analyzing the internal structure.
I have to break the password.
What?!
Gino?
Lelouch! I refuse to accept you and your Britannia!
I'll destroy you, here and now!
Guh?! How is it so powerful?!
Gino!
Suzaku!
Lelouch, go on ahead!
There's an enemy to be defeated and someone to be rescued!
It's all up to you now! Go!
Right!
Coward!
You insist on fighting me, Gino?
Yes.
I will do whatever it takes to protect something I love!
And I'm fighting for the same reason!
To protect what?!
Is Schneizel on the control and command floor?
Or else, could he be...?
Seventh sequence.
F.L.E.I.J.A. detonation point set to within Damocles!
Damocles and the F.L.E.I.J.A.s
are simply machines in the end.
We can always rebuild them.
But, sir, you know the Toromo
Agency doesn't have the resources.
Nor does Rosenberg.
Yes... But Lelouch is now the enemy of the world.
If it turns out that our system has destroyed him...
There will be plenty of organizations
happy to build F.L.E.I.J.A.s for us.
Isn't that basically terrorism?
Besides, there's Princess
Nunnally's opinion to consider, also.
Why care for what she says? Bait has no opinion.
What do you mean... you're abandoning her?!
World peace or a single life?
It's sad to say, but one cannot
be compared with the other.
Where is it? Where's the key?
I have to stop Lelouch!
We have to hold out here
until His Majesty completes his mission!
I despise what Lelouch is now.
The Knight of Six?!
Now that's a fitting opponent for me!
You have no country! You have nothing to avenge!
You also don't have a shred of ambition!
Someone who has no reason to fight should just leave!
I've made a reason to fight! A promise!
Are you saying that you love Lelouch?!
I don't know.
But I believe the time has finally arrived
for me to stop "accumulating
experiences" and start living.
That makes you sound almost human!
Well done.
Kallen, I concede. You win.
Don't care, 'cause to me, it doesn't matter.
Bye now.
Heh.
Winning or losing, I never would have thought
that those feelings were still inside me, alive and well.
The key... Where's the key?!
It's got to be here!
I have to stop Lelouch, and it's all up to me to do it!
If only I could...
Standing by to launch.
Rendezvous point with Sir Hartgren is as planned,
no changes.
Course clear. Ceiling favorable.
Huh?
I've been waiting for you, Schneizel.
I see.
I suppose this means that you have me in checkmate.
Please tell me.
I'm dying to know.
Just how did you discover what my plan was?
You're mistaken.
What I anticipated was the pattern of your own nature.
My nature?
You don't have the desire to win.
You remember that chess match?
At the Vermillion Forbidden City?
And the coup d'etat of the Black Knights...
You only play games you can't lose.
So... you predicted that I would abandon the Damocles?
Schneizel, this time, I'm going
to make sure that you lose.
Meaning I'll be put to death.
Hong-Gu, move from corridor three to take the bridge.
U.F.N. representatives...
Xing-ke...!
Your Majesty! You're all right?
Yes! We were saved by those people over there!
That's correct.
Master Xing-ke, we are now on your side.
You all betrayed Lelouch then?
Huh?
And for a valid reason. He threatened us!
However, now that Lelouch is no longer here...
At the very least, we believe that the others
think dictatorship is wrong and will never support it.
Very well then.
Yes. The final battle will most likely
take place within the Damocles.
Ohgi... I mean the Secretary General...
Either way. You're saying he's okay, right?
Y-Yes...
My brother didn't kill me.
I'm still here after all is said and done.
In a more normal world, he'd be an excellent ruler.
He isn't driven by the ambition that egotists have.
I was a fool not to have seen that.
Wouldn't you agree?
Princess, I...
Guilford. You're never going
to stop calling me that, are you?
I have a question.
We're you intending to use the
Damocles as a tool to dominate the world?
I wasn't.
I only wanted to give everyone what they wanted.
To bring peace to civilization.
Disregarding humanity's true nature?
That's a matter of opinion.
Then you actually imagined you could maintain
the world in a perpetual state of "now."
But...
life without change might be called anything except life.
It's nothing more than experience.
But...
link those together, and they become knowledge, right?
Schneizel, you truly are superior.
So superior, you can't even see it!
Yes. Emperor Charles sought the past.
You seek the present. But I seek the future.
But the future may be prove to be worse than the present.
No... It will be better.
Because, no matter how long it takes,
people will continue to seek out happiness.
Even though that will end up making people greedy.
Your folly also knows no limit.
You're really too emotional about this.
Hope and dreams are merely names for aimless fiction.
You're restricted, since you belong
to the symbol known as a royal family,
which looks down on the world.
I've seen it over and over.
The people who struggle against sadness.
Those who seek the future.
How they all carry on, wishing for happiness.
Human nature is why I chose Geass and to wear a mask.
Lelouch, you're contradicting yourself.
You, who continually deny the will of others,
are standing here before us,
affirming the will of humanity.
That's enough. Kill me now and be done with it.
But... a F.L.E.I.J.A. will still decimate you.
We will gladly give our lives
to bring peace to the world...
Hm?
And that's how I came to my decision...
...that I'd give you the gift of the words.
"You shall serve Zero."
Then you never intended to kill me at all.
You wanted to...!
H-Highness!
Dammit! Why didn't I see it coming?
He anticipated Schneizel's thoughts
and recorded that conversation...!
Order me to do whatever you wish, Master Zero.
Schneizel... your willingness to let yourself be killed
is exactly what has led you to be defeated.
Don't move!
Zero! This story's finished!
You never should have come this far!
You shouldn't even be alive, you bastard!
What right have you to deny my existence?
You have none.
Prince Schneizel...
A man would sacrifice his
own life without any hesitation!
Such is the power of Geass!
Z-Zero... At least...
...finish me with your Geass, too.
Sorry, Diethard, you're just
not worth wasting my Geass on.
Now, Schneizel, you can begin by
canceling the self-destruct for the Damocles.
Understood. However, Nunnally is the one
who has the F.L.E.I.J.A. control switch.
It doesn't matter how strong you made your machine!
You won't beat me!
We'll see about that!
And this is the result... Gino.
No, I've done what I came to do here.
He damaged the blaze luminous system?
Now, Kallen!
Thanks, Gino!
Suzaku! I've come to end it!
Our continually crossing paths!
It's you, isn't it, big brother?
It is.
The reason you're here must be this.
Did you come for the Damocles key?
Yes. It's dangerous. Dangerous to you.
Then that's why.
Huh?
Why... I won't close my eyes to things any longer.
She's broken father's Geass?!
With her own will?!
Now, Lelouch...
Will you use your Geass on me, as well?
Perhaps I've only been wandering
since that day we first met.
I was so sick of a world that never changed.
But...
I couldn't give in to the
despair by telling lies to myself.
Yes... My name...
My personal history... The power I've gained...
Maybe... it's all been a path for me,
at the end of which I'll find the truth.
Perhaps that's what I've sought all along.
Well, then...