Acting at the request of the United Federation of
Nations resolution number one for the liberation of Japan,
the Black Knights sent a landing force into
the Britannian Empire colony known as Area 11.
Targeting the troops commanded by Bismarck Waldstein,
the Knight of One, encamped on the Kyushu coast,
the main force struck, led by
General Commander Li Xing-ke.
Using this as a diversion,
a separate detachment of Black Knights
staged a lethal assault on the Tokyo settlement...
But Schneizel, Prince of Britannia,
was waiting for them with a secret
weapon of mass destruction called F.L.E.I.J.A.
At that moment, to Zero and the Black Knights,
the very existence of this weapon was unknown.
New orders. Black Knights, Ikaruga fleet.
Gefjun Disturbers have immobilized all utilities,
communications, and pre-fifth generation
Knightmares throughout the Tokyo settlement.
The enemy's military might has been cut in half.
Hit all major facilities and
eliminate their ability to strike back.
We must achieve these goals before the
main forces under Schneizel's command arrive here.
By establishing our defense line,
we'll isolate the Government Bureau.
If we can seize Viceroy Nunnally,
then victory will be ours!
Viceroy Nunnally. It's Zero!
Zero is leading an assault!
Zero.
Zero's on his way?!
Look at that smile.
Now that's more like the real you, Kallen.
It's too bad. Your wish won't come true.
Because I and my Tristan fight for Britannia.
Our first priority is to eliminate the Gefjun Disturbers
along the railway's circular routes.
Can we dispatch the Lancelot for that?
That'll depend upon the current
state of Sir Kururugi's mindset.
The battlefield's not the place for him
to work out his self-esteem issues.
Nina, you don't know what you're doing!
If we don't act, Zero will capture the Tokyo settlement!
But you're not a devicer!
You may have designed the system,
but you have no battle skills!
With the F.C.C., I can at least
defend the Government Bureau!
But are you prepared to actually fire the F.L.E.I.J.A.?
And more importantly, are you prepared to not fire it?
Tohdoh. Have Asahina, and Chiba establish air supremacy.
Roger!
That should cover everything except their
newer Knightmares, sixth-generation and above.
Rolo!
How is the infiltration proceeding?
Sayoko and her group have gone on ahead of us.
We will rendezvous with them shortly. It's all arranged.
Good. Be sure you take Nunnally alive.
So, you've come, Suzaku.
I'm the only one who can make Lelouch,
make Zero, atone for what he's done.
Listen up, Zero. Call off your attack!
This unit is equipped with a high-yield tactical warhead.
If I unleash it, it will inflict catastrophic
damage beyond all known limits.
As if I'd believe anything that you'd say! Jeremiah!
Yes, Your Majesty!
Lord Jeremiah, is that you?! Why?!
Suzaku Kururugi, I owe you a debt.
I sympathize with you. I respect you.
However, in this situation...
Loyalty trumps all!
The Siegfried's?!
Take this! The storm of my loyalty!
You picked a bad time for piety.
Now!
Hmph.
The Sutherland Sieg seems to be effective.
Yes, but...
Huh?
We can never mass-produce a one-off
unit that uses the Siegfried's system,
that's understood, right?
What I'd really like to know is
why Jeremiah's on our side now;
he's not just some knight, you know...
That also goes for the man once
called "the Spearhead of the Empire."
What's going on?
Why? Why am I fighting against Royal Britannian forces?
Guilford!
Assist Jeremiah.
Slay Suzaku Kururugi!
But Princess, Kururugi is...!
There's no time to explain! It's urgent!
You must trust me and kill Kururugi!
Lord Jeremiah, the reason I'm here
is to put an end to this battle!
Are you saying you can do it?
Are you able to dissipate my lord's torment?
But, it shouldn't involve the people!
Lord Guilford, too?!
Kururugi! We each serve
our royal lords! It's not personal!
Suzaku!
Fire the F.L.E.I.J.A.!
You can kill Zero now!
I'm sorry, Nina. I won't unleash it.
But...! I swear. I will stop Zero!
Excellent. Once Suzaku's finished off,
there'll be nothing left to
stop me from taking back Nunnally.
Uh!
No one can defeat a Knight of the Round.
No one!
Gino, thank you.
Can't you look a bit happier when someone saves your life?
Hm? Lord Jeremiah?
So, what they said about Orange was true, huh?
Orange, you say?
That is the name of my loyalty.
This onslaught. It's all from Schneizel
Did he anticipate my moves?
That's right.
I'll be rendezvousing with
you a little later than I expected.
Yes, I understand.
We have just cleared all
interferences up to the 13th floor.
Don't worry. I promise, I'll find Nunnally.
Right. I'm counting on you.
And once you bring back Nunnally,
I'll have no further need for you, Rolo.
Big brother.
I promised you I'd find Nunnally and I will.
And when I do, I'll kill her with my own hands.
I'm the only family you need.
Master Rolo!
Emergency report from group two,
moving toward the hangars.
They say that they've sighted priority item three.
I won't! I refuse to flee this way!
The Prime Minister has personally ordered it.
My brother Schneizel?
The others cannot leave you behind,
so if you stay, all must stay and die.
Ha! You're no match for my Gareth!
Keep dreaming! We've got full air superiority!
We won't yield!
Oh, no... Tohdoh...
I owe you deeply, Asahina.
You've got future plans in the works, right?
Uh, so what's our next move?
Zero ordered us not to attack the bureau itself
until Viceroy Nunnally has been captured alive.
Zero, huh...
They're all... They're all fighting, while I'm...!
We'll defend it! No matter what!
Lord Guilford has lost his sanity,
but so long as we Glaston Knights
still perform with courage and valor,
we uphold Princess Cornelia's honor!
Answer me, Zero!
If you started this battle
because of me, then let me explain...
Filled with conceit as ever.
You betrayed your father and all Japan.
'Course you betray your friends, too. That's who you are.
Uh. What's this?
Anya? Wait!
Suzaku, leave Zero to Anya.
Which one do you think is stronger?
Your shield or my Stark Hadron cannon?
Even this shield can't withstand this for very long.
Contact lost with the Shinkiro!
Zero?
Apparently he's engaging in combat with the Knight of Six!
What're your orders for Hashimoto?
And we also have to defend Kujuukuri.
Uh... well, I, uh...
Patch Hashimoto over here to me.
Sugiyama, do we have any units we can send to help Zero?!
Uh... just Tamaki.
Yes,
Viceroy Nunnally is being put aboard the escape craft.
But until the Gefjun Disturbers
have all been deactivated...
Right. We can't use a Knightmare
without being targeted by the enemy.
Yes. Understood.
Who's going to execute Kallen Kozuki?
Sir George.
But are you sure about this? Viceroy Nunnally didn't...
It's for her own good,
despite her feeble attempts to assert herself.
Sayoko!
You're looking well.
Master Rolo has gone on to secure Miss Nunnally.
We came to give you a present, Miss Kallen. It should fit.
I think Miss Milly's former fiancé was behind the changes.
There seems to be a draft instruction manual with it.
Shall we try to get it working?
It's different, somehow...
We can't stretch our battle lines any further.
We're already at the breaking point now.
All Gefjun Disturbers in Ikebukuro
and Sugamo have been destroyed.
Now we can reinforce our lines with
5th-generation Knightmares and older.
We're also bringing the Government
Bureau's defense system back on line.
The momentum has shifted in our favor.
The lights!
We're out of time!
Kinoshita, haven't you found the viceroy yet?!
The commanders have freed Captain Kozuki, but... Uh!
Kinoshita!
Hey! Are you okay?!
I sent the data... on Zero... from my system.
That's all I can... do.
What the hell?! I can't find him!
Where's this battle Zero is fighting?!
He's my best bud!
Just a little more.
Again? Something is...!
The Mordred just... Uh!
Zero.
Face it, your Black Rebellion is doomed to fail.
They sent another Knight of the Round?
Here's a question:
What do people value most? Answer...
Their life of course!
The basic system's the same?
We're still trying to determine
Master Zero's current position.
Shall I transfer the I.F.F. data?
Yes, please.
Let's see... Guren S.E.I.T.E.N.
Eight. It could be.
Confirm activation.
Activation, confirmed.
You're good to go.
Once the Guren is launched, we'll return to our mission.
Right. You take care of the viceroy. I'll help Zero.
Agreed. Well, then...
Guren!
S.E.I.T.E.N. Eight Elements...
Launching!
Now launch!
What the...?! Huh?
Father, I let you down. Forgive me!
David!
Was that Kozuki?
But, that unit she's flying...
At this rate...
This shield's the only good thing about your Knightmare.
Valkyrie squadron, don't let him go, no matter what!
Yes, my lord!
I'm in trouble!
I used up too much energy with the Mordred!
Zero. Do you read me, Zero?!
Where are my reinforcements?!
Tamaki will be there soon.
But a picked up a fleet over the Pacific.
What about it?
Zero, it's me!
It seems to be the Britannian Emperor's flagship.
What?!
He's coming to Area 11 as well?!
No. His Majesty is not coming to the battlefield.
What makes you so certain of that?
Do you think he cares about those mundane things?
The day we call "today"?
He doesn't.
Let Zero go!
Or you'll have to deal with me,
Shinichiro Tamaki, his best bud!
Dammit! This always happens to me!
Yes! Now's my chance!
Just what I was waiting for, Zero!
To go into attack mode, you dropped your shield.
Now, I will take what you value most and blow it away!
In this position, I can't...! Nunnally!
Hm?
Huh? They got me?
Kewell!
Be careful what you wish for, Vampire of Britannia.
Really?
Is that Kallen?
Zero. I'm here.
You're elite guard,
Kallen Kozoki, is back on the battle line!
You thieves! That's mine! All mine!
Not quite. I did some of the upgrades, remember?
Oh, right.
It's actually a collaboration. What am I talking about?!
With a capable devicer, even at 60% output,
that unit can cut the other Knightmares to ribbons!
That's the Earl of Pudding's work and
Cecile's energy wings! How dare they?!
Altering my Guren without my permission!
Still, now that we've got
Kallen back in the combat zone...
It will even up the battle.
Sir Bradley, you have permission to destroy the Guren.
Irrelevant!
Killing is all one should do on the battlefield!
Ah, ah, ah!
Eleven.
Do you know the prime truth of the battlefield?
Kill a man off the field, and you're a criminal.
But kill him on it, and you're a big hero.
So.
The Vampire of Britannia wants
to be a hero now, is that it?
No, not at all.
War officially allows me to take what people value most:
their lives.
Some knight. You're barely a scoundrel.
And now...
And now what?
That's not gonna work.
Ah, but now I've got you in close range.
What?
Question: What do you value the most?
Your own pitiful life?
You think an Eleven can threaten me?!
Send a postcard.
My life! My life is taken...
...by a lowly Eleven?!
Good work, Kallen!
Now get back to the Government Bureau and get Nunnally!
I won't let you!
Suzaku Kururugi!
Easy now!
Kallen! Stand aside!
Forget it, Suzaku!
No! Deflected?! The Hadron blaster?
Kallen.
So in the end, you chose the name Kozuki over Stadtfelt.
That's right,
which means you and I do battle once again.
So, should I be happy or sad about that, Gino?
Why don't we just enjoy it?
Suzaku. Let me settle things with Kallen, okay?
It won't be easy.
I'm sorry, Gino.
This pilot isn't the kind of opponent
you can mess around with.
Tohdoh's forces have broken
through to the enemy's command ship!
Impossible! My Gareth!
Raise all the shields in Area Four!
We're just after Schneizel's head!
Assume Slash and Encircle Formation!
Tohdoh.
I'm sending you some testimony that Kinoshita gathered.
This is hardly the time!
Listen to it and you'll understand.
We can't trust Commander Zero.
Huh?
I'm going into the government bureau to capture Rolo.
Explosion detected in section 4-I of the ship!
Could it be... Chigusa?
I need to bring this battle into close range.
Suzaku! Kallen's not the one you need to fight! Hit Zero!
Your escape route is towards the Ikebukuro front.
But there are still Black Knights in your fight path.
Wait till we've mopped them up before you launch.
Master Zero, we've found the viceroy!
I see! Excellent work!
Master Rolo will escort us out of here
as soon as he steals a Knightmare.
He'll have it in a moment.
Understood! Victory is within our reach.
Kallen! Finish off Suzaku now!
He's the only thing standing in our way!
Right!
Get out of there, Suzaku!
You can't beat that Guren!
But, Zero...!
Ohhh!
Self-centered brat!
It's... It's too great.
The difference in unit performance.
At this rate,
we're going to lose Sir Kururugi as well as Sir Bradley.
Fire it, Suzaku! Use the F.L.E.I.J.A.!
No, Nina, power is in the threat.
If we actually use it...
I can't win...
Goodbye, Suzaku.
Miss Nunnally!
Kill Suzaku! Do it!
Unleash the F.L.E.I.J.A.! You can still save yourself!
But... if I do that... Even if it costs me my life...
That's right. This is redemption...
I have to accept it.
This is where I'm going to... to...
Live!
I... must... live!
Is this... F.L.E.I.J.A.?
Fall back! All units, retreat!
Why are the Britannians running?
We have to retreat, too! Asahina, are you reading me?!
Get out of the Government Bureau! Asahina!
Something's wrong!
Pull the Ikaruga back at maximum speed!
You in the Sutherland, what are you doing?
They've fired the F.L.E.I.J.A.
Fired the F.L.E.I.J.A.?
Could that be the weapon Suzaku was talking about?
Nunnally!
General Tohdoh, I tried to warn you!
Why did they use the F.L.E.I.J.A. here?!
Princess, save yourself! Princess!
Princess, you must live! Please live!
Rolo...
Yes, big brother?
Could you please let me speak with Nunnally?
Um. Well...
I can't reach Sayoko.
Listen. Big brother. We weren't in time.
Nunnally was caught in that flash of light.
I'm not asking you about anything like that now.
I just wanna talk to Nunnally, that's all.
But... Nunnally is dead!
She's dead, big brother!
Don't lie to me!
Please, Rolo.
Could you, just for a moment...
Please... let me speak with Nunnally.