Kuniko Hojo.
It's been three days.
You've passed the test.
To reward your perseverance,
I will lift your burden.
I shall end
your troublesome life.
Outstanding. There's the look.
If you lay a
finger on anyone else...
I swear to you,
they'll be the last person.
Does anyone here wish to
take umbrage with the sentence?
So we're all in accord as
to the fate of our firebrand?
Excellent. Heh.
Your update
on Digma Two, please.
Languishing in her cell, ma'am.
The child's éhlan for
stirring the pot would appear
to be spent.
At least for the time being.
Appropriately. She is condemned.
We have an alternate plan, then?
Nothing has altered.
If she's the sort to die,
she'd best get on with it.
You presume to serve me Rize?!
Is it not plain I want
Montagne Bleu san sugar?!
I am unworthy, madam.
Good work, fellas.
We're makin' progress.
Yes sir.
Huh?! Son of a bitch!
We got a shit-storm!
The bastards
have slapped her with
an outright order of execution!
What?!
They were just
talking about it on the news.
Duomo's 'bout ready to pop!
But wouldn't they have needed
to formally sentence her first?
Ya think those Atlas thugs give
a shit about legal procedures?
Then we ought to
pickle some celery.
The girl eats 'em
like they're going extinct.
And some turnips, too, I think.
You know what?
Let me handle this one.
Jumping the
proverbial gun, as men do.
So. We jump when?
That's really
not for us to decide.
I suppose not.
They say
Kuniko's on death row.
Oh, how awful!
Surely this country's
not so far gone as that.
Keep it together, soldier!
How the hell else did
you expect her to end up?
She's a damn terrorist,
not a close personal friend!
In other news, Metal Age
ringleader Kuniko Hojo
has been sentenced
to death for her crimes
against the
Japanese government.
Enough already. We get it.
"Slow news day I guess."
Does the media really think
anyone's biting their nails
over what Big Brother does with
a bunch of dirt-faced savages?
Mommy?
Who the heck keeps leaking my
email address out to spammers?!
If I needed someone
to play match-maker,
I'd have put myself out there.
Well, your company
just buried itself,
because I'm gonna set
your network infrastructure up
on a hot date
with my friend, Medusa.
How long do you
intend to let the same
big red spot
mesmerize you? Idiot.
A matchmaker service?
Like I'm lonely.
You've got a visitor.
Momo!
You're a difficult
woman to see.
Are you getting enough to eat?
'Cause I gotta say,
your little girls there
are telling me you're starved.
Maybe "the girls"
and I have gone on a diet!
Hell-bent on
cutting a lithe figure
before the
firing squad, are we?
Maybe, yeah. Make you sad?
Oh beside myself, hon.
Look at my mascara.
I'm an absolute wreck.
That thing, there. She's the
circus act who kicked up
such a stink over Digma Two's
arrest, if I'm not mistaken.
Indeed.
Doesn't she seem complacent
under the circumstances?
Well, perhaps if we're lucky,
she's tried baking a
crowbar into a sympathy cake.
Tell me. What would you do
if I were the one... you know?
Being executed?
That's a cheery thought.
Honestly, if I couldn't
keep it from happening
I don't think
I'd forgive myself.
So you'd just stumble
through a dreary half-life?
Sweetheart. Think about it.
How would that be
a credit to either of us?
You'd just be using
my death to keep yourself
at arm's length
from everyone else.
Yeah, well...
Safe to say I'll never
have to deal with your death.
Thanks for
turning it homeward, love.
Lucky for us, I have a plan.
Once you're in the ground,
I'll show the devil a little
leg and presto, back you'd come!
Let's just hope you're his type.
Bite your tongue!
Of course I am!
Who do you think put the
money up for Tropical Fish?
Silly me.
Oh, that's right. A little
short-timer care package.
Huh?
"A gown for
the gallows." Nice.
And it's hideous.
Even a drag queen wouldn't
wear this. Wow, lipstick, great.
I guess it's the thought.
Now that's
what I'm talkin' about!
Way to lump fugly
and the fulsome together
in the same package,
guys. Well, still though...
At least you
got one thing right.
Oh man. This just got real.
Sorted garbage is green
garbage. You girls got that?
Yes sir!
Hell yeah!
Scrap of nano-material!
Complete and total score!
Don't stand there
and advertise it, dumbass!
Just fish out
as much as you can.
Alright. That's all you get.
Baby, that's all I need.
Don't skimp me.
Yeah, yeah.
Three minutes. That's it.
Hold it!
Who the hell
said you could be here?
Uh.
Last I checked, this place
was off limits for inmates.
Listen, please.
I have to talk to her.
Come on. What kind of
letch do you take me for?
Kuniko!
What're you doing here?!
I just had to see you.
Do you have any idea
how much trouble you'll be in?
It's okay. I've got
the guards in my pocket.
Tomoka. You can
manage without me, right?
After I'm gone?
Don't talk like that, okay?
Sorry.
Listen-- I'm getting you out.
Don't you talk like that!
I swear on my life,
if you're cooking something up!
Relax. No one else is around.
I've got it all figured out.
No. I'm not
letting you put yourself
in danger for my sake.
Look, if you're worried
about me slowing you down,
I promise I won't.
I can't. I'm sorry.
Kuniko!
Hey. Talk to me.
Tomoka.
Someone's coming.
I'll come back.
Be careful.
I think we'll
just keep that between
the two of us for the moment.
Go.
You surprise me.
Soichiro!
That was your chance to
motivate Digma Two right there.
If it'd had been me I'd have
sluiced her brains
through the cell door window.
I didn't think the
idea was to pitch the girl
into a homicidal frenzy 'less
you want to handle the fallout.
We'll just keep that between
the two of us for the moment.
Oh that does it!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
Yeah. You and what army,
ya skinny little piece of shit!
You wanna wait
for Kuniko in Hell?!
Bitch! Think I'm
scared of you?!
Break it up and report outside
for clearing duty immediately!
Alright, ten minutes.
So make 'em count!
'bout time. Oh man.
Uh-Uh. Piss off.
Hey, I don't got my own.
Fine. At least
wait till I'm done.
'scuse me, sir?
I wanted to "pick some
flowers". Is that okay?
Sure. Go crazy.
Whatcha need the tea pot for?
Well. I'm pretty sure the trees
don't want my scent on 'em.
Yeah, okay, thank you.
Just don't take long.
I don't know about this.
Whatcha think she's gonna do?
S'not like the
girl'd survive out there
long enough to get away.
Guess this spot'll have to do.
You guys bring the stuff?
Bet your ass we did.
Alright. Let's do this.
You really think this
setup's gonna do the trick?
Hey, if I've learned anything
valuable in this playpen
it's how to
improvise some alcohol.
I know one dumb
bitch who's gonna be
in for a real nasty surprise.
Just try not to blow
yourself up. So help me though,
if you tell anyone where you got
it from, you'll wish you had...
Sure. Whatever.
Whatever my ass. Try settin'
it off without a catalyst.
Everybody's gotta
get inside immediately.
We got another
hail storm on the way!
Another one. Intense.
Wonder what's goin' on at home.
C'mon! Any slower
and we might as well
be carvin' out a god-damn tomb!
I expect this place to be
immaculate by execution day.
I've been meaning to ask.
Why that day in particular?
Bit of a red letter
day in her horoscope.
In Mikuni's as well.
There. Now it's
your turn to pick.
Hmmm. We fancy this one.
Excellent--
Lady Mikuni.
I bring good news milady,
today thy person may
venture to the
surface for a time.
Forsooth?! Hath a physic
been unearthed to make it so?
No. That goal
remains unreached.
Then 'tis put a poultice.
Oh, 'tis but a pity.
To dwell abroad
o' nights coddled
in the selfsame penumbra.
Not the selfsame.
But rather one
whose vast circumference
generously bid thee
caper where thou wilt.
Hold on, girlie!
We'll bust ya outta
that hellhole in no time!
It's that time, huh?
'kay. Let's get this
over with quickly, then.
Mind if I doll myself up?
Not if you don't
mind my mirror, no.
Much obliged.
Not a bad blade.
I notice you're
not wearing the outfit.
Oh, from the care package?
Not exactly the dress
I want to be caught dead in.
No blindfold?
I'd rather face the
end with eyes wide open.
Too bad they
don't need any help!
I'd have given my
left eye to play you off!
Present arms!
Soldiers ready!
Fire!
What did you just do?!
Nano-wire!
And adding insult to injury,
I'm not even sure
I'm using it right!
Don't think you'll
get out of here alive--
Restrain her!
Heads up!
I owe ya one! Hurry up!
Coming!
Goodbye, everyone!
I'll come back for all
of you as soon as I can!
You're damn right you will!
Good luck, Kuniko!
More like
good luck to you guys!
No! You imbecile,
you'll ignite the hydrogen!
Do what?!
Leave it to you to work
out something this elaborate.
You'd be surprised what a little
self-reflection dredges up.
Uh. Don't pat me on
the back just yet, though.
We're gonna stop a bit short.
Bingo! Mountain road!
Huh?!
Come on!
Ten point landing
Thanks a lot, Kuniko.
And thank you for
getting the two of us this far.
You're late!
What are you doing here?
Flawless intuition.
Welcome back.
Good to be back.
You scrummy Harlot!
Look at you.
Kicking ass and taking names!
Lay it on, girlfriend.
So? I guess the little goodie
bag came in useful after all?
No condemned soul
should be without one!
Took a while to
figure out the nano-wire.
But I'm pretty
sure I did alright.
You just treat it
like a you would a man,
nice and gentle, but firm.
You puzzled your way through
the carbon thread, I take it.
Ah, that. I knew
the dress had to be good
for something, and
it sure wasn't fashion.
Pretty clever
of ya, I gotta admit.
What are you talking about?
It was super ugly,
but the material in it
is what wound up
holding the balloon together.
It's unbelievably
tensile stuff.
The other girls used it to
sew various scraps of fabric.
Once they had your
basic hot-air balloon shape,
they buried it out in
the yard during clean-up duty.
Where'd you
dig up the hydrogen?
It was from the charges they use
to clear out the old forests.
Not too hard to come by when
the guards are all men, ya know?
And the alcohol catalyst?
Where did that come from?
It's clear they
distilled it from something.
We just don't know
what quite yet, madam.
Clever shrews.
A worthy spectacle
all around, I'd say.
Sufficient pretext for our
schlepping home, at least.
Shogo will be relieved.
And what of
the inmates, madam?
Not a damn one
of ya s'got the grapes!
Live as one, die as one!
Zet Vier, call the
tramps on their bluff.
Yes ma'am.
Commence operation lullaby.
Something wrong?
No, I guess it
was just my imagination.
Mine, too, in that case.
Clue me in here?
No birdsong.
Normally they're so loud
out here it's almost deafening,
but right now
they're not making a peep.
An eclipse!
'kay, that's weird.
Explains why our
feathered friends are sotto.
Mo, look!
Funny. I don't recall dropping
'shrooms on the way here.
♪ Girls and boys
rush out to play. ♪
♪ The moon doth
shine as bright as day. ♪
♪ Leave your supper,
leave your sleep. ♪
♪ Join thy friends
in yonder street. ♪
What the Hell?
Sweet pea.
Nothing's ever going
to toughen that hide, is it?
You'll always feel too deeply.
But that's as it should be.
The world doesn't have much use
for a heart that can't break.
Next time: "Divine Prophesy
of the Sun and Moon"