A whole forest overrun with
this stuff is not gonna be good.
Our future's basically
forfeit unle--
Your future's basically
forfeit either way.
What're you doing?
Talk to me--
Shut up!
It's not like I
got a fuckin' choice!
Don't do this.
There's always a choice.
Yeah, sure.
This from someone who
doesn't even know
who the hell she is.
Explain it to me then.
Why do you have to do it?
Since when is my friend a thug?
I don't have a choice
because you're a Triple A.
Fantastic. The stupid
little meatspace manqué
has an Atlas Ranking
that puts everyone else
on the hierarchy to shame.
"Imagine dredging up that
kinda intel from Zeus's core?
I mean, what are the chances?"
"Can all three of them
really be Triple A's?"
Yep. 'course, all the
other rankings Atlas doles out
are pretty much
meaningless anyway.
Just something to offset
how hopeless their lot is.
Good ol' opiate for the masses.
"The brass must
think we're idiots."
The only people the corporation
cares about are these three.
Anything happens to
them and it's goodnight.
The whole ball o' wax is done.
I believed in it.
The Atlas con.
I thought we
really had a future.
Even if its bedrock had
to be a mountain of corpses.
What do you mean?!
I'm talkin' about
human sacrifices, girl!
It was the only way to offset
the mechanical resonance!
The only way to keep
the damn thing standing up.
Do you hear yourself?
I didn't know
the whole story then.
They were kids!
So many, if you
laid 'em end to end
they'd wrap around
the goddamn Earth!
Kids like my little sister.
If I'd a known back
then what I know now...
But hindsight is twenty twenty.
It has to stop.
And this is the only way.
If you believed
in Atlas so much,
what were you doing slumming
in Duomo in the first place?
I was assigned to
you as a bodyguard...
by the Corporation.
You were special. The only
Triple A I'd ever heard of.
Do it, then. Pull the trigger.
End my life!
Freeze!
Tell me. What's so
special about a Triple A?
They're the inheritors.
The inheritors of what?
That.
But hey... You ain't
got to share it with me.
Any more than Duomo, right?
Guys like me don't have a home.
Damn you! Don't talk
like that to me!
You belong in Duomo.
You always have.
Takehiko!
No!
Madam, Hiruko's
absence is troubling.
Are we certain that
inaction is the best path?
Inundated with matters
so grave, I mean.
Construction has
been stalled yet further,
who knows for how long.
On account of
Metal Age's assault.
The daedalus encroachment
hinders repair efforts--
All things flow
along their gradient.
Setbacks of this kind are mere
corollaries of transformation.
We have left the path
laid down by others.
From here on we follow
our own lights, yes?
That was messed up. How long
had he been with you guys?
The Hell was he talking about?
What reason would Atlas
have for sacrificing children?
I've, uh never heard that one.
But if there's any truth to it--
He was a grunt
for the corporation
this whole time
and we never knew.
I never even
knew he had a sister.
Please, convince me he was
out of his mind or something.
'cause if there's
truth to any of it,
I don't know what to believe!
Sorry. I'm no expert on belief.
Thank you for saving my life.
You're a true soldier.
But, why are you here?
Because. I quit.
It's true. I guess
you could say me
and the "slags"
have parted company.
So, what're you
hoping to find out here?
I don't know.
Home is where you
hang your hat, I guess.
"Yeah, it's gonna be
pretty hard to get used to."
I suppose. Kinda weird to think
of an entire city as your house.
"But hey, you can't deny
this was a smart purchase."
Yep and all under my name.
If I'm gonna own it,
I'm gonna own it outright
from sidewalk to skyline.
"And we brought
all the syndicate
biggies under one banner."
"Neo Guild" does
have a nice ring to it.
"Music to our ears!"
We sure do lead
a charmed life, huh?
Now we can get
back to earning again.
Madam President,
we're on the line with
someone claiming
to be a Mikuni rep.
She's really angling
to be put through.
"As in the Mikuni?"
See that? A charmed life indeed.
Why does your leader
not yet deign to show?
Lady Mikuni's presence
is not to be shirked!
Gah. Calm down already.
Ta da.
You're president of
the Akihabara Neo Guild?
Yup.
And you're in sunglasses.
Hey, little thing called style.
Art thou that
shall be our sentinel?
Jackpot!
You certainly do penetrate
to the heart of things.
Allow me to bid you welcome
to the city of Akihabara.
My name is
Karin Ishida, my lady.
Thus, we are
delivered. So...
This township is known
as Akihabara, thou say'st?
We find it fierce
narrow and o'erstuffed.
Watch it, princess.
That's my home you're
talkin' smack about.
Karin. We must
impose upon thee
for immediate
medical assistance.
Miiko!
I hope these arrangements are
suitable for you, Lady Mikuni.
What's his trauma?
Surely they don't think just
dipping the kid in
water's gonna do anything?
The sickness is becalmed.
Indeed.
'kay. Eating my words now.
Miiko. We shall visit soon.
The barrier ought
to be erected forthwith
to avoid unnecessary
casualties.
Casualties? Wait, what?
Hey! Hold on!
What have I gotten into?
Charmed life. Just
remember, charmed life.
We shall subsist on
a mere fifty assistants.
And sixteen styles of
twelve-layer
kimonos shall suffice.
Hath we accord. Karin?
Yes, my lady.
We aim to please.
The Hell does she get off?!
Like I'm not already
hemorrhaging cash like
a hedge fund setting
her up in those digs!
Well, just you wait, you
little royal pain in the ass.
I'll have my ear to the ground
when you're named Atlas' heir.
Oh, and the favors I'm gonna
call in when that day comes!
Mark my words, Princess.
He was something else,
I'll tell you that.
Who'd have thought he
could've kept something
so big under wraps?
It just goes to
show you, I guess.
Folks aren't
often what they seem.
It's weird.
He told me something...
Something about me inheriting
Atlas, whatever that means.
Think he was just babbling?
I dunno. Anybody show
up to hand you the deed?
Your guess is just
as good as mine, hon.
President!
What is it?
Monitors say we've lost
contact with the Nerima Branch.
As requested. I trust
your Highness will
find them more than adequate.
Thou say'st these
are palace attendants?
Oh, yes. They're known
as "maids" in the vernacular.
But their work experience here
in Akihabara
uniquely qualifies them
to serve any and all of your
royal needs, rest assured.
Show her what ya got, ladies.
My mistress. Welcome home.
But we have not
left since your coming.
Oh, aren't you cute!
Speak truthfully.
Dost thou consider our person
as the star 'round
which thou orbit?
You betcha!
Idiot.
Oh crap! Oh crap!
Oh, yes. This is price one
pays for untruthfulness here.
I recommend honesty.
Might have to rethink
the whole charmed life thing.
So now a lie equals
death by pretzeling.
Karin.
Uh, here!
We find thy efforts to
accommodate extraordinary.
You have our thanks.
Excellent work.
Uh. You're gracious
to say so, my lady.
And yet. We puzzle
wherefore a doyen of
high fashion such as thou so
zealously consents to serve us.
I'm as good as dead!
What am I supposed to say,
"'cause I intend to take
you for all you're worth"?
Yeah, bull's-eye politicking
that'd be. Think, think, think!
Tell you her you're a big fan,
which doesn't make sense
because you didn't know
her from Adam a few days ago.
Oh man, I either come out of
this looking like a
schmuck or a sailor's knot!
May it please you.
Her yen to serve and her
happiness are intertwined.
Or so I judge
from her enthusiasm.
Thou say'st well.
Quite pleased we are indeed.
Thank you for that.
But of course. It behooves
my purposes nothing
for you to die prematurely.
Just so we're clear,
our mission is
to locate the
Nerima Branch, and if
the situation calls for it,
rescue any survivors.
Keep in mind,
conditions here may be worse
than in Ikebukuro.
So Stay vigilant.
Roger.
Hey, hon. Should your
back be in need of gettin',
don't hesitate to
call your gal, Friday.
He may have
been a son-of-a-bitch,
but not having
Takehiko in your corner
is a sad state of affairs.
You got that right.
Holy... I'd say this is
officially getting out of hand.
Yeah. That strikes
me as a fair assessment.
Photochemical oxidant
concentrations are way up.
Maybe this'll help.
Oh, crap.
The beguiling aroma
of bergamot, ma'am.
Ideal for augmenting
your ladyship's mood--
You think any
part of me augmentable
by the mere
influence of scent?
I--I do not.
Madam Ryoko. Regarding
the daedalus spread...
Photochemical oxidant
dispersal is playing havoc
with the eco system. Surface
effects are already visible.
Reports of asphyxiation
and madness are flooding in
from the outlying areas.
How shall we proceed?
Well, historically
the lower classes
never seem to get a break,
why should now be
any different for them?
Hey! Anyone in there?!
Oh my dear god.
They didn't even have enough
time to get their masks on.
President?
Okay, listen up.
The Nerima branch has cashed in.
This base is hereby
abandoned. Pull back, now.
Go. It makes no sense to
have people stationed here now.
I'm a fool. Thank you.
How many does this make?
I don't keep count.
I'll be fine, though.
If you're at the breaking point,
we can always pull out of here.
No. I'm alright.
I know it sounds scary,
but I could manage
if it was just you to take care
of. I'm just worried that you--
Don't presume to
know what's good for me.
Shion, I--
The forest is
already too far gone.
The Daeldalus are spreading
so fast there's gonna be
nothing else growing there
before we know it.
Ahh, what I wouldn't
give for that virility.
Breeding like rabbits.
Cut it out, Mo.
This is serious. If we don't
find a way to stop those things,
even Atlas won't be
able to stand up to 'em.
We'll all be
driven to extinction.
I know. The Question is,
how do we stop them?
We use the one thing that works.
Dwomp. Dwomp. Dwomp.
Gentlemen. We have here
the crème d' la crème.
Flashy-flash! Taleen!
Enough with the figurine!
Being able to see
our lovely Karin's eyes
makes this photo far superior!
Ha! You think a
paltry pic trounces
a militant belle
emerging from a tank?!
Ugh! Spare me your junk pile!
This here is precious.
Rare enough--
Hey. Mind if we come in?
Bwaaap! Bwaap!
Bwaap. Bwaap!
Kuniko has
entered the building!
Momoko alert!
Repeat: Momoko alert!
Man your battle
stations, no pun intended.
Prepare to be
made love to, camera!
Just look at 'em.
May they never know adulthood.
So. You're here, too?
Well, it doesn't really matter.
Happy to see your face.
Ready for it?
I came here to get my
hands on another bomber.
Ba-ba-bum. Despair.
Not sure what's to despair.
I'm gonna need you guys
to make it a rush
order again, though.
But don't worry. Whatever
the cost, I'm good for it.
Think of Duomo
as your piggy bank.
The thing is,
the tactical difficulties of
acquisition have changed.
Whaddayamean?
You see, Akihabara's been
more or less taken over
by brand new high-roller. The
syndicates we usually go through
are under new management.
Course, she's
cute as a button,
so you won't hear
any complaints from us.
Ding ding ding ding!
I'm sure you pervs
put up quite a fight.
Hey, don't judge us!
We're not made of stone.
We may not possess
the purchasing clout to help,
but we could arrange a meeting
with the overlord in question.
If that's amenable.
Guess it'll have to be.
What are the chances?
Whoa, it's you.
The bear!
You okay?
Excuse me.
Another Triple A
at my doorstep.
Maybe lady luck
hasn't dissed me after all.
So. Supposing you
get this bomber you're on
the hunt for,
what'll you do with it?
Bomb Tokyo. We have to.
Calm yourself, dear.
Why must doing what
needs to be done trouble you?
If it's a matter of trust,
don't feel it's necessary.
One can use without it.
Next time: "Two-Headed Fable"