Kumagai? And what
is their significance?
A favored member of
Digma One's entourage.
Also known as "Miiko."
Ah, the sexually confused one.
And what is the charge?
I'll leave that
to your discretion.
Get creative if you like.
As long as our little
nightshade is grieving the loss
of her clown, I'll be more than
content, for the time being.
Miiko.
It appears Lord Hiruko's current
vessel is waning rather rapidly.
These days he does
seem a bit more, voracious.
Here's a lark.
Let's use the airsot's maiden.
Ma'am?
Several would fit
into a vessel of that size.
I beg your pardon,
but I believe a pure
maiden is what's required.
Come now. He claims
to have the pure soul
of a maiden,
if not the natural body.
I wonder what Tarsian's response
to our unique choice will be.
My curiosity is piqued
to say the very least.
Our friends are leaving,.
Don't be so antisocial.
Come say goodbye.
How can someone who pulls a gun
on their own countrymen
call himself a soldier?
Forgive his rudeness.
Water off a duck's back.
You've been a fabulous host.
So what now?
More sightseeing perhaps?
I'm done.
It's all just same taste,
different smell around here.
More people who'll see us as
some "interesting story"
they saw on TV.
All just so content,
they couldn't give a damn
about us struggling
on the outside.
You can't take careless
words to heart, love.
I know that. I'm not stupid.
So what's your plan?
I don't know just yet.
I gotta go back home and think.
That's plan enough for now.
What the hell?
We got no leader,
we got no goddamn direction!
We ain't got shit!
Metal Age got kicked right
square in the damn balls.
It's game over, for real man.
Game on! Not game over!
She's comin' back and it's gonna
be better than ever before!
Oh yeah? Well, I don't see her!
It's like somebody died.
It's exactly like that.
Except it was their dream.
They had to give up
what they were fighting for.
What in the heck
happened to Kuniko anyway?
I bet she finally just got tired
of the whole "leader" thing.
That's a lotta crap
for a girl to deal with.
I couldn't hang
with it for that long.
Hey now. You don't have
to drag me down to your level.
Did ya miss me?
Totally!
But seriously.
Sorry I made you guys worry.
Look who's come back!
Hey, everyone!
Kuniko finally
found her way back home!
That's great news!
It's Kuniko!
Well, It's about time!
That's a mercy!
Yeah, it's true! I'm ba-ack!
Welcome home, Kuniko.
Oh thank heaven,
safe and sound.
No kidding!
I guess you can tell we've all
been a little
worried about you dear.
You're really back!
I knew it!
Can you believe it?!
What did you discover in Atlas?
I came across an old
picture of you there, Grandma.
It said "First CEO,
Nagiko Hojo".
Is that really true?
I guess it is. But I
don't understand how you could
keep something that big
from me and everyone else.
No one's seen
Takehiko around lately.
What?
He returned with the others,
but shortly thereafter he seems
to have disappeared.
I'm afraid, he too discovered
a truth in Atlas
he couldn't face.
Grandma.
I've learned being
leader of this group
means making tough choices.
Ms. Nagiko Hojo, you are
hereby exiled from Duomo.
Once every day.
What?
Stir the bran in the
pickling bed once every day.
I hope I made
the right choice.
If that was where your heart's
counsel led you my dear girl,
then it had to
have been right.
It's like I don't
know life without 'er.
It's uncharted
territory for me.
How are you supposed to deal
with losing someone like this?
Miiko was like your shadow so
how'd you feel when she left?
Like half a set o' six
inch heels. Lopsided.
But I knew if I looked here,
she'd still be knocking
around inside my heart.
Nagiko will
always be with you.
She's left an
imprint that can't be
erased by time
or miles between.
You'll carry each other
with you wherever you go.
So keep her safe in there.
Come on!
You might wanna keep
me safe too, ya loon!
My heart told me I could fly
and we did for a second there!
We did. The nay-sayers
can all go to hell!
Believe in yourself! No one
tells the sun it can't shine!
That's right!
Please. Forgive me!
I didn't mean to, I swear!
Whatever I did wrong,
I truly repent!
Purify the heavens
and the earth.
Purify the within
and the without.
Purify the six
roots of our being.
Cleanse the seven days,
the nine planets,
and the 28 lunar houses.
Cleanse the 36 guardian
gods of this world.
The purification of the within
and the without is the cleansing
of the terrible god
of the Three Treasures,
living within the hearth.
Sweep away all that is unclean
and purify the
six roots of our being.
May the young deer raise
his ears to our prayer,
and deliver it to
the innumerable gods,
that they may grant our request.
We beg this of the divine.
Oh wise and exalted one, we
have been awaiting your arrival.
We found some over here!
Yeah?!
These things are spreading
everywhere like crazy.
They're callin' 'em
"Daedalus" aren't they?
Yeah. That's what
Tok called them, anyway.
Should we be here?
I mean like, doing stuff
with the Metal Age guys?
These things're dangerous
ta everyone in Duomo,
so we gotta chip
in to get rid of'em.
We're just doing
our part to help is all.
I'm really startin'
to like the new Tomoka.
Kuniko!
'Sup?
Furukawa needs
a word with you.
He needs to talk to me?
Seriously? These are the things
that have been shooting at us?
After germination.
In about ten days or so,
they appear like this.
It takes only two months
for them to reach full size.
Unbelievably quick.
So they're very eager
to stand erect are they?
Have you figured out why they're
able to fire like cannons?
I believe the plants in
the F2 generation used Oxygen
as their primary seed
propellant, did they not?
Correct. But several generations
have passed since then.
They now incorporate
nitrogen oxides in the process.
It would appear that
evolution has blessed them
with a very sophisticated
form of photo-oxidation.
So they've made
their own improvements.
The oxygen that the plant
creates through photosynthesis
is given a boost
by the excess nitrogen
that it absorbs
through its root system.
You think the poisonous
gas released on Level Eight
has something
to do with them too?
Another kind
of Daedalus attack?
What about the time
they fired on our smokestacks
and the army barged in?
I don't remember seeing
any gas that day, do you?
They originally used
oxygen to eject their seeds.
But now, the seeds themselves
release nitrogen oxides,
which allow them to
travel higher in the air
and reach a
greater distance on land.
It seems this gas was
released at the same time
they reached Level Eight and,
in turn, leaked into Atlas.
We thought their
natural attraction to heat
would accelerate the
greenification process.
But it seems they've gone and
developed a mind of their own.
So this whole thing was
genetically engineered.
By Atlas Corp?
Just another weapon created
to cause pain and destruction.
We gotta wipe em out.
Let them have their way.
As long as we keep the amount
of heat we put off under
control, we'll be fine.
Leave the
worrying to the outliers.
Another test of their resolve.
Speaking of the outliers,
we've lost contact with
number thirteen
in the past few days.
Due to his
involvement in the skirmish
it's possible that
he is now a casualty.
Oh?
Kusanagi!
The word's going
around the base that
you resigned your commission.
Yep.
But why?
I dunno. Something
in the wind I guess.
Nah. More like the sun.
What in the holy hell
is that supposed to mean?
Hey! Kusanagi!
What is it?
It appears Digma Three
has tendered his resignation.
Why is that any of my concern?
Let him do as he pleases.
After all, he's only
third in the ranking.
No, we mustn't.
Tears are foolish things.
They bring no
salve to our spirit.
Prepare for us
a carriage at once!
Milady, where will you go?
We must make speed
to the heart of Atlas.
To wrest back our dear
companion by dint of force.
What will be thy choice?
Defiance shall be punished
by death and obedience
rewarded with Atlas rank!
Sweet mother of pearl!
Can you believe how fast
it's grown since the last time?
Crazy.
Holy crap!
I never imagined
they could get that big.
It's enough to make
a decent woman blush.
Let's burn 'em down!
Oh my! Look there!
Get outta here!
What now?
Please forgive the intrusion.
But Digma One has decided to
mount an armed
attack upon Atlas.
You don't say.
She is demanding the immediate
return of Tetsuo Kumagai.
All this to-do for a queer?
Such misguided heroism,
sacrificing others for
her ridiculous plaything.
Fear not Miiko!
What is the matter?
The gunmen ceased their fire,
but we gave not the order!
Continue firing, now!
It is she. The witch.
That's quite enough. Stop
this foolish parade at once!
Make haste!
Our enemy is before us!
Is there not one
warrior among thee
possessed of the
courage to strike?!
Slay her now! Slay her
and name thy reward!
A valiant effort.
But know even death trembles
in my presence
and bends to my will.
You ask proof of this?
The gun refuses to fire.
For even instruments of war
dare not defy the
force of my destiny.
What strange sanctum is this?
This is where the Chief
Executive Officer of Atlas,
Lord Hiruko, makes his home.
Hiruko? Our explicit desire
was to lay eyes on Miiko!
And so you shall.
The two have intertwined.
A selfless act of servitude.
The moon child has
entered my chamber!
Miss Mikuni.
I beg you, stay away!
That voice! Miiko!
Oh how we've longed for thee!
Your flesh! You come
that I may dine upon it?!
Sweet Miiko. Thou art changed.
No, made sacrifice
so I may be born anew.
Stop! I will not allow
you to harm Miss Mikuni!
Silence vessel, and know
thy rightful place as servant!
Miss Mikuni.
Miiko, 'tis truly thee.
Please my lady.
Your magnificent robes
will become damp and soiled.
That matters not to us. We
have longed to hold thee near.
Listen to me. The one you
once knew as Miiko is no more.
Leave me be and
do not return here.
Bearing witness to
the unconditional love
for which you've
shown me today
truly fills my soul
with overwhelming joy.
As certain as we
see thee, thou art Miiko.
Whate'er corporeal
form enshrouds thee,
thy spirit remains pure.
My eyes well up, fit to burst.
Now, little nightshade. It's
time to bid your slave farewell.
When I said I wanted
to get a little action,
this is not at
all what I meant.
How come they weren't this nuts
when we first came across 'em?
It seems firing at them
was a bit of a faux pas.
Plants communicate ya know.
They speak to each other
in a language made up
entirely of chemical signals.
So by introducing
the chemicals from
the flamethrowers into the air,
we essentially kicked off
an argument that's escalated
into an all-out brawl.
And now they're
all so worked up
and turned on they
can't stop popping off.
Ugh. You always sound so dirty.
How in the heck do you know
so much about plants, anyway?
It's my former life,
sweet cheeks.
Not only did I once aspire to be
a woman, but a botanist as well.
You went to college
for it? What happened?
I spent too
much time at the bars.
You've never
been much to look at.
But it seems as
though these past few days
have been exceedingly harsh.
Make so much as one more move
and I'll show you
just how harsh I can be.
I said don't move!
I have no reservations about
killing your precious oracle.
Sayoko! Thou
musn't harm Miiko!
You feel it?
Yes. This child keeps
the gremlins at bay.
The only way to control
the forces that would send
your world tumbling is by
supplying him with fresh souls!
Good. That's exactly
what you should do.
Stay where you are.
Come along now Lady Mikuni.
Yes!
Lady Mikuni will assume
her role as heir now, yes?
That decision
lies with Zeus alone.
We shall take our leave
of Atlas until it is so.
Sayoko!
You mustn't worry. I would
never lead you astray.
Let them go!
But, my lady!
These vibrations
will destroy Atlas!
Ah well. Hiruko is
nothing but a toy for Tarsian.
We can manage without him.
Quite a bold move, Sayoko.
You've exceeded my expectations.
Keep getting more involved.
It will only lead you
deeper and deeper into misery.
Looks like Kuniko
and the others are back!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
What happened?
Everyone make it?
If any of you are hurt,
come back to my
place and we'll play doctor.
Huh? What was that, dear?
I asked what you'd like
me to whip up in the kitchen?
Yes, Kuniko and the boys have
returned from their mission!
Alright! Canned tuna
and panko sounds good to me!
These massive hail
storms are to blame for it.
Whaddya mean?
They attacked the
trees, gave them the beating
of their lives and left them
broken. With the branches gone,
all those sunbeams
were finally able to
touch the once forbidden earth.
Ahh, time to
soak up some rays! Huh?
What the--?
What's going on here?!
The daedalus
rise up lightning-fast.
Hogging all the suns rays
and nutrients from the ground
before the other
plants even have a chance.
The Daedalus shoot their seeds.
The hail falls from the sky.
More daedalus grow.
Wash, rinse, repeat.
After a while, what
began as a diverse forest
becomes one giant monoculture.
What's that mean?
Nothing in it but the Daedalus.
A whole forest overrun with
this stuff is not gonna be good.
Our future's
basically forfeit unle--
Your future's basically
forfeit either way.
I used to be just like you.
I had people I cared about.
People I thought I
could protect. Not any more.
Now, I have absolutely nothing.
Next time: "A Dark
Night's Resistance"