We just sealed
the deal with Taiwan.
Three cheers for profit!
Karin!
Enough is enough, okay?!
How can you keep exploiting
the market when your
country's in a crisis?!
With the usual dash of pride.
But people are dying over there!
People die every day.
Karin!
Zhang?
Zhang is now banned
from the network.
Distractions from the task
at hand cannot be indulged.
No time for losers!
We're in this to make money.
Bleeding-heart
pansies need not apply.
Kuniko! You read me?!
Yeah. Go ahead.
Those assholes
did a number on us!
Huh? Where'd the
Diet Building go?
Don't tell me.
More of their bullshit.
Kuniko!
Momoko!
Oh, thank God!
Thought you were a goner!
Wait what is that?
Poison gas.
Our scientists are
analyzing it as we speak.
Could this be part
of the Metal Age attack?
Use of chemical weaponry
is strictly forbidden
under international law.
The world will hit Japan
with penalties that'll
catapult our carbon
debt into the stratosphere.
I can see that putting a
"crimp" in Atlas's construction.
Well, Ryoko? Your move.
This is prime minister
of Japan, Ryoko Naruse.
If the terrorist leader is
present... please speak up.
Right here!
I'm the new leader
of Metal Age! Kuniko Hojo!
I see you decided to
ditch the fascist uniform.
What'sa matter, warden?
Tired of dress-up?
Whatever do you mean?
You must be delusional.
The two of us
have never met before.
How come you're using
gas on us like a coward?!
Our conventional
weaponry was making
easy work of your forces,
so why would we risk
U.N. anctions on vermin?
You're saying that
there's some third player
on the board that
neither side knows about?
Tell me. For how long
will you keep this up?
This plague of mindless
slaughter weighs on me.
Your fellow terrorists
are still valued citizens.
To which end,
I propose a cease-fire.
Lying out of her ass.
We're "valued citizens,"
huh?! Cut the crap.
I can have that entire section
destroyed, if you'd rather.
Yeah, right.
You're gonna bomb Atlas.
That isn't a bluff.
She would do it.
If I might interject.
I will take
things over from here.
My name is Sergei Tarsian.
I serve as an arbitrator
for the U.N.'s Court of Justice.
I have authority
to settle this matter.
Arbitrator?
I'll frame the terms to
the rebel leader very simply.
If you agree to
lay down your weapons,
I will guarantee the
safety of you and your men.
If you don't, more will die.
I looked at the facts
of this case closely
before heading here.
Thus, I've already
come to a decision.
As the aggressor in this matter,
Metal Age is to lay
down its arms and withdraw.
Don't worry, Kuniko! This
asshole ain't fooling anybody!
If you looked at
the facts, arbitrator,
then you know things
boiled over like this
because of what
Atlas has done!
Metal Age...
will comply.
But, the Japanese government
is not blameless in this.
For the next three years,
therefore, the government will
slow the pace of its
greenification project,
working instead
on the refugee crisis.
We shall do our best.
That's bullshit!
You think we're
just gonna go home?!
That's enough!
Put down your weapons, you
guys. I want you to withdraw.
I know you don't want to, but
please everyone, hear me out.
If we tell the U.N. to get bent,
the world is gonna
turn its back on Japan.
I don't believe this.
And if that happens,
the people outside are gonna be
even worse off
than they are right now.
I realized we hoped for better.
But for now,
I call for a full retreat.
Forgive me. Please.
Very well.
We're done here for today.
Uh, right.
"Arbitrator,"
my pert little ass!
Come on. Chrome-dome
was totally in cahoots
with that sadistic bitch.
Hey, Momoko.
Yeah?
Do you remember how we
got out, that time with the IDs?
Huh?
Hell no! No surrender!
I'm not giving up!
Hey, man. Just calm down.
You don't wanna do this!
Yeah?
C'mon, hand it over!
You back the fuck up!
That's enough!
You think you're hurtin'?
Then what the hell ya think
Kuniko's going
through right about now?!
Where'd she go?
Couldn't tell ya. But she was
on that ledge just a minute ago.
Zhat so?
Hey!
I know this place.
Hey wait! That ain't no
place to go playin' around in!
Damnit!
♪Come on through,
Oh, come on through.♪
♪This narrow pathway,
wherever does it go?♪
♪It goes down to the
dwelling of the god.♪
♪Please allow us
to go on o-ur way.♪
So many, I never knew!
♪Those with no cause here
are not allowed to stay.♪
♪We're all here to give thanks
that the child has come of age.♪
How, Ryoko? How could you?
♪Sacred gifts you gave
we dutifully return.♪
♪Easy through the gate
from which you cannot emerge.♪
♪Hard though it may be
for you, please join us now.♪
♪Come on through.♪
My God. Yasko!
Yasuko! C'mere!
Here I am.
What did you want, mister?
Here! Happy Birthday!
Wow Really?!
I get to have 'em?!
'Course you do.
Aw, thank you, Mr. Takehiko!
You're a riot. Callin' me
mister when I'm your brother.
I gotta 'cause
you're my older brother!
They told me that you ran away!
Please forgive me, Yasko!
All this time.
I've been helping them.
They've all been what?
Bought. Somebody snatched up
all the high
carbon-debt areas worldwide.
What do you think?
Did someone purposely block
our head leases,
to screw with us?
Totes! I looked
into the money trail,
and don't go freaking
out now but it's Zhang!
Come on! Zhang's never had
the kinda cash-flow
to pull that off!
He does now!
He's probably just being a dick
'cause we kicked him off the
team! So what do we do huh?!
Beat him at his own game.
He's gonna rue messing
with Team Medusa!
Hey! Don't you die on me!
Oh no. So she lost?
This glorious pillar of heaven.
Who shall stand atop it?
We'll soon find out. Won't we?
Level Four, right?
Yup! Atlas's resident
residential block.
It's just as huge
as all the rest.
Fresh fish, right here!
Come an' get it!
Check it out!
Those look awesome!
We are a bit grubby.
So, why'd you wanna
come back here, anyway?
No reason!
Didn't feel like going home yet.
So we might as well see the
sights, as long as we're here.
Okay...
Look at 'em, Momoko!
Houses here are gigantic!
What are those sphere dealies?
Maybe we should go!
Hey! You there!
Yeah. I got a hunch your
IDs ain't exactly in order.
Oh, come on!
It's those two. Let's get 'em!
What are you doing there?
I know we look suspicious
and grubby, but we're not.
Really! Grubby, yeah
Ma'am, we're desperate!
Some very questionable
men are on our tail!
Huh?!
They're not here?!
Yes, sir. Looking at our
records, I'm not able to find
any sailors who're
staying here at the moment.
What do you mean?!
Those men and
I were all admitted
to the hospital together!
I'm sorry, but they're
not in the system, sir.
My goodness. The two
of you had quite a scare.
It was awful! Had their
fun and refused to pay us!
The things they did
to my little friend here!
When I think of how
they stole his virtue!
Wait, so your friend is a--?
Lady-boy! And a hooker.
Ah-ha. I'll help you
two out however I can.
Bless you-- You're a gem.
By the way, my name
is Momoko. This here is Kuniko.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Haruko. Now drink up.
Thank you, Haruko.
whose arbitration
proved invaluable
in forging a cease-fire.
Which, of course,
led to the
terrorists' disarmament
and subsequent withdrawal.
All that war-talk
turns my stomach.
My boy's an army officer.
Fortunately, he isn't the type
to take his work home with him.
As a mother, you must worry.
Call me superstitious,
but I make him carry
a family heirloom for luck.
I wonder why...
Why folks feel like they
have to fight to begin with?
Honestly? Part of me
thinks the boys like to go
to war to get their rocks off.
I do hear things,
though, about how tough
they have it on the outside.
Even the rain is lethal.
I'm sure I'd be angry too,
if I were stuck out there.
But Atlas is letting 'em all in
just as fast as
they can or so they say.
Well, at least the
fighting is over for now.
Uh-huh. And it's
a blessing that the
residential level
didn't take any damage.
Well, guess I
should start dinner.
Oh! I'll give you a hand.
You're a guest.
Don't worry about it.
Now, I wouldn't dream
of letting you do it all.
Singapore and Shanghai
just got bought out!
Please help me, Karin! The
water level continues to rise!
The Chongqing
head lease has failed.
All capital is exhausted. Karin.
Ishida Finance is bankrupt.
Bankrupt? We can't be!
I'm very grateful
for the help, Asian Dragon.
I see the stories of a
'leet old-school carbon-trader
are more than just tall tales.
So, is this
really what you wanted?
I'm all for making money,
but exploiting this crisis
just wasn't
sitting right with me.
Besides, Medusa was
getting out of control.
Carbon rates were losing
any real-world meaning.
I knew that letting it go on
unchecked would
have been too risky.
You are a clever young man.
Fare thee well, Karin.
I'm leaving the
carbon-trader's life for good.
I'm running off to a convent,
to spend the rest of my days
in chaste contemplation
as Sister Mary Robert. Amen.
"Don't give up, Karin.
You can't throw in the towel
just 'cause you
hit a little snag."
"It can't end, not like this!
All you need is some more money,
and you're golden!
After that, there's nothing
you can't
accomplish. Trust me!"
No quitting.
Not without a fight!
"So step one is to
raise some new capital?"
I can get us all
the money we need.
I'll wring every screed from
Zeus, and laugh while I do it.
"Ooh, the Japanese treasury?"
If I max out Medusa's
survival instinct
and disable its
need for a human handler,
it should become
completely unstoppable!
"You're switching top user
priority over to Medusa itself?"
Yeah! There's no way it can
outmaneuver Zeus if
I'm the one in charge.
But I know Medusa
can crunch the numbers
super-fast if it's on its own!
Now go forth!
Raid Japan's coffers
and bring it all back to me!
What seems to
be the trouble?
Another cyber-security
breach. Zeus is under attack.
Unidentified as of yet.
But I would wager it's Medusa.
Really?
Lengthening number-strings
one-million-fold.
Once again, the most sensitive
sectors are being targeted.
Madam, they're
hitting all the areas
that were weakened
by Sayoko's attack.
The top-secret files
will soon be compromised.
We cannot allow that
information to be made public.
We must shut down Zeus.
If we do, then our defense
system will go offline.
Atlas will be a
gigantic sitting duck.
All of our other vital systems
will be taken offline, as well.
Also, every scrap of government
data will be deleted--
Our secrets take precedence.
Now do as I have
ordered you to. Shut it down.
I have given you an order! Obey
or I will have you arrested!
What is the meaning of this?
Zeus's survival outweighs
your dusty secrets.
And speaking of your secrets,
I discovered that you took
few young carbon-traders
under your wing
and had them create Medusa.
The great serpent! The serpent
has opened the sacred doorway.
And the spirit. The spirit
must be protecteeeeeed!
Lord Hiruko!
I have located
the password phrases.
Please enter them
within the next ten seconds.
"O Sun, illuminate the
heavens and the earth alike.
O Moon, climb the sky-- Dispel
the o'er arcing darkness."
And "O Land. Enthrall
the day and the night
and hold thee
sway upon the world."
The marionette
who cuts her strings
will find herself immobilized.
You old fool, you still
think you're the puppeteer?
One more keystroke and bam!
Huh? Hold on.
What in the--?
I just hacked into Atlas?!
She runs as fast as she hacks.
Chicken stew is my
boy's favorite dinner.
Clean your plate, sweet cheeks.
Man, all those carrots.
Thanks for the food, ma'am
You're just in time!
It's good to be home.
Go and change
out of your uniform.
We have folks over for dinner.
It's a pleasure
to meet you-- Ahhh!
What? What are
you two doing here?
Uh, your last name
isn't Kusanagi, is it?
Yeah. I guess
I forgot to tell you?
Uh-huh.
Have you met Kunihito? He
looked as though he knew you.
We've crossed paths
a couple o' times.
Hey, grumpy.
Change out of your duds
and at least come say hello.
Kuniko and Momoko tell
me you guys've met before.
Some bad men are
giving them trouble.
Be a good boy and
help them out, would you?
Once again, my son has come
home to me, safe and sound.
Thank you for protecting him.
Pictures of young Nagiko?
I'm guessing they were fake.
This whole place
is smoke and mirrors.
Dunno, maybe... still...
Is that why you don't
wanna go home yet?
That's not why-- Not really.
I needed some time
to think about stuff.
Plus, I was curious to
see how they live in Atlas.
But all of it
seems pretty normal.
I dunno. They've got
it pretty good here.
They do. But they don't
realize what it's like outside,
so it's no big deal to 'em.
And those that do,
they're just glad they
dodged the bullet an'
it's not them out there.
Welcome to human
nature, my darling.
It was tasty. Y'know,
that stew your mom made.
Cooked like that, carrots
aren't the worst thing ever.
How do you fight like that?
Huh?
It's like you never
seem to feel any doubt.
Like you never have
to question what's right.
It's like, everything you
believe in hasn't crumbled away.
I wish I felt like that.
So do I.
I've got so many
doubts. Same as you.
Who are you?
How dare you barge in here?!
You'll answer to me if you
harm one hair on milady's head!
Tetsuo Kumagai.
You are under arrest.
Wait. What? You mean me?!
Winning the Atlas Lottery,
getting to serve you,
it's been like a dream.
If it was, I preferred
it to all the waking moments.
Thank you for this, Milady.
Next time: "Forest Frenzy"