Huh? What's that song about?
I'm drawing a
total blank on the words.
♪ "Our canary has forgotten
how to sing his song." ♪
♪ "Shall we leave it in the wild
to make up for this wrong?" ♪
♪ "No sir, no sir, don't
do that. It would be unkind." ♪
O Land, enthrall
the day and the night...
and hold thee.
Lieutenant! Lieutenant!
C'mon, man say something!
We thought we'd lost you!
Where am I?
Oh God! Where're the rest?!
Well, looks like
it's back to normal.
Yeah, the market's
calmed down for now.
Hopefully that
means I get a vacation
from Klaris freaking out.
Hey, uh, Karin, you mind
if I ask you something?
I was kinda wondering
what your reason was
for doing this kind of work.
I dunno.
C'mon, Karin. Spill it.
It's nothing I feel
like talking about, okay?
It's cool. No big deal.
I mean I guess, it's so
my mom and dad will be--
Oh, crap!
Huh?! Why are you shouting?!
Sorry 'bout that!
I forgot that I'm supposed to
meet up with my folks
for dinner! I gotta run!
See ya later, Karin. Zai jian!
Don't be so nosy, Zhang.
Elevator Two is in use.
Huh?!
It's a cat.
"Enthrall the day and night..."
"and hold thee." And then?
Thirsty?
Oh, thank you.
Saving our asses the
way you did took a lotta guts.
Saved you, how?
Back on the ship.
When that weird light
shot down and engulfed us.
Hard port! Now!
Hello?! Is anyone
still down there?!
We're so screwed!
Shit! We're gonna die!
C'mon! The
ship's gonna capsize!
If you hadn't
forced that door open,
we'd be drowned
as the rest of 'em.
Sorry I laughed
when you were seasick.
That was a dick move.
Hey as near as I can tell,
you guys saved my ass, too.
But what the heck was it
that cleaned our
clock so bad, anyway?
Well, it came from above,
so maybe it was a satellite?
What a worthless tub.
Do we happen to know
what sank the damn thing?
Someone hacked the
Apollo and weaponized it.
The satellite
packs quite a punch.
Even with it downed,
that ship is problematic.
Covert acts of naval
aggression are a diplomatic can
of worms we don't want to open.
Just leave it be, then.
What?
If anything comes of it,
we can have the minister
of foreign affairs
clean up the mess.
You sure he's
up to the challenge?
If he's not, he sinks.
Such is the fate of all who
fail to do their job, is it not?
Indeed.
What of Medusa?
The typhoon that appeared this
morning is hampering our search.
Thus far, it hasn't
moved at all, and trying to
force our way through it would
be unwise to say the least.
In other words, the tiger
has led us to its den.
If only we could
lure it back out.
"How did you get up
here all by your lonesome?"
If you're as smart as you are
cute, I bet it was no biggie.
I guess it's okay
for me to talk to you,
since you're not a person.
You have one new voicemail.
I bet it's from Daddy!
My dearest Karin. I hope
that all is well with you.
Your mother and
I are both splendid.
'Tis work that
keeps us away from home,
but it still
pains us to have left you
to your own
devices for so very long.
That said, we should be
homeward bound quite soon now.
We're looking forward
to breaking bread with you.
Just like the old days.
Please message us
back when you get a chance.
We miss you. Your loving Papa.
Mommy. Daddy.
I want to, I do. But--
But it's not that simple.
You wanna leave, but you can't.
Who said that?!
It's true, right?
You'd love to go out.
H--How did you get in here?!
My security system should
have spotted you a mile away!
Just come outside.
How we pine for it.
If only a brief sojourn
beyond this umbral realm.
Ah, but you're still recovering
from your last "brief sojourn".
You really should be
more careful, sweetie.
We merely desire to enjoy
a walk in the light of day,
as innumerable others
are often want to do.
Is that so unreasonable
a thing for us to yearn?
Of course, it's not.
Nothing more
natural in the world, poppet.
Art thou well?
Their winged
sovereignty is precious.
Set yourself free!
It's like falling off
a log. Really, it's easy!
Now hold on, how can you
even see me through there?!
Who are you?! And why
the hell are you here anyway?
I've come to rescue a sad,
lonely little princess
who's forgotten the
words to her own song.
Leave! Just go away!
I didn't ask for rescuing.
And I certainly don't
need anybody's help.
"Won't somebody rescue me?"
This is precisely
where I want to be.
"If I could, I'd run
away from this place."
This is home, and everything
I want, I have. I'm content--
"All I want is to eat
dinner with Mommy and Daddy.
Why can't I?"
I can't, okay?!
Yes you can.
Don't say that! Shut up!
Please! Just leave me alone.
That's just not possible.
Sorry, but you
and I are one and the same.
What're you talking about?
Come on.
Stop it! Leave me alone!
I'm not listening,
so just go away!
And stay out! What the
hell just happened to me?!
What do you mean,
nobody got in?!
I had a conversation
with him, for crying out loud!
If you've been sleeping
on the job, I am not amused!
Well, The cameras
don't sleep, ma'am.
Everything is looking
pretty copasetic over here.
Sorry, but there's no trace
of anybody in the video footage.
What are you insinuating?!
Maybe you nodded off to sleep.
Huh?!
I was awake. I'm sure of it.
Kitty, what's your
take on the situation?
Was it just a dream?
Or was he real?
He frightened me. But he...
he wasn't exactly wrong.
That's probably the reason
he frightened me so much.
Now that he's gone,
I kinda wish I could talk
to him a little bit more.
I know. Real contrary, huh?
Come back, please.
♪"Our canary has forgotten
how to sing his song."♪
That's the song!
♪"Shall we leave it in the wild
to make up for this wrong?"♪
Wait!
Please don't go!
What's taking 'em so long, huh?
We ain't gonna last much longer.
Man. If I knew that things
were gonna end this way,
I totally would've
hooked up with that chick.
C'mon, man! Suck it up!
Are you gonna give up
and die in a damn life-raft,
or you gonna go
home and seal the deal?!
I'm getting you
guys back home to Japan
if it's the last thing I do!
Go easy on 'em, Lieutenant.
We're all just trying
to keep it together.
Yeah. Sorry, I wasn't
really trying to be an asshole.
So, uh, speakin of chicks...
Got one wrapped around
your finger back at home?
Huh? Nah. Nobody
to really speak of.
Huh? Who, me?!
Come on and focus, woman!
You're in charge
of Metal Age now,
so you gotta
start acting like it!
Maybe I was having
deep leader thoughts.
Yeah? What's your
plan, fearless one?
Uh, what plan?
The plan that tell us how
we're gonna break into Atlas?!
It's not like
we can just wing it!
How 'bout this?
Go on!
Y'know, that "winging
it" thing could work!
Or maybe not. Hmm.
How did you sneak in here?
This place is supposed
to be impregnable.
Please don't be afraid.
I won't hurt you.
But, I am. Afraid.
I'm afraid of you.
But I'm afraid of everyone.
All those people, and I'm too
afraid to even speak to them!
The world outside
is just scary.
I understand.
You don't understand!
How come it's so
easy for everybody else?
I can't even bring myself
to look a person in the eye.
But you can. I know it.
Uh-uh. It's too hard.
I could never just go
up and talk to a stranger!
That part of me
has always been broken!
But I'm a stranger,
and hey, you're talkin' to me.
You're doing just fine.
You think so?
Duh?
Don't make fun.
I'm sorry.
Tell me, what's that
song you were singing?
It's about a canary.
At the end, he remembers
the song he forgot.
I know it. I think.
I used to be
afraid of people, too.
Huh?
I actually used
to be a lot like you.
The difference is other
people locked me away.
You can free
yourself at any time.
Karin, I'm glad
we had this talk.
Don't go! Just
a few more minutes.
Tonight, when the
sunset makes the sky all rosy,
come to the park out front.
Something you've
lost will be waiting.
It would seem that no
other nations were aware
of the Yamato
Takeru or its sinking.
Well that's no fun.
I suppose the foreign minister
will live to see another day.
Madam Ryoko.
The custodian of the Moon
Palace Digma has gotten rather
vocal lately with her concerns.
Is she going to
be a problem for us?
Tenacious bitch.
Always butting in.
So?
So let the shrew complain.
I do think he was
right to inquire, madam.
Maybe we should proceed a bit
more delicately with the Digmas.
Maybe so.
Madam Ryoko.
While we're on this topic, I'd
like to make a request of you.
Speak.
I'd like to have
access to any files we have
on the Digmas to
learn more about them.
Why?
As they say, "Know your enemy
as yourself, and fear nothing."
Very well. Go. Read up.
Well I guess I gotta
think of somethin', don't I?
Okay, here's the plan!
We bust in! Ta-daa!
I'm going out,
so it's up to you to
watch over everything
while I'm gone.
We're finally goin' home?
♪A canary has forgotten
how to sing his song.♪
♪Shall we leave it in the woods
to make up for this wrong?♪
♪No, sir, no, sir. Don't
do that. It would be unkind.♪
♪A canary has forgotten
how to sing his song.♪
♪Shall we whip our naughty
bird to make up for this wrong?♪
♪No, sir, no, sir. Don't
do that. It would be a shame.♪
How strange. I've spent
my entire life in there.
So you finally
found your wings?
Yeah, I guess I did.
And I finally remember.
That song, it's a--
It's a lullaby my mother
used to sing me to sleep with.
I knew you could do it, Karin.
Good bye, my little bird.
Such dulcet notes.
Pray, by what name
dost thou know yonder birds?
Ah, those little dears
are called "canaries".
'Tis a most beautiful name.
Canaries are most
fortunate to possess it.
See those two on the roof?
They were brought together
to sing just for your delight.
That's their purpose.
Verily, they sing for us alone?
Truly. And just like you
milady, they never venture
out into the
brutish light of day.
They never know of daylight?
Nor of the sun's warming glow?
Then more's the pity.
So, how goes it?
Found anything noteworthy?
Nothing. All the important
info is well beyond my reach.
Well, you had to expect that.
Wait a sec. There's another?
Never heard of Zero, huh?
Who's that?
That one was the
original Digma. A prototype.
Codename "Canary."
Defective model, they said.
Never once set foot outside the
facility, or so the story goes.
Died about five years ago.
So we lost one?
To die without ever having
known the outside world.
♪Our canary has forgotten
how to sing his song.♪
♪Place him in an ivory boat
with oars silver strong.♪
♪As he floats on the ocean
'neath the pale glow of moon.♪
♪In his heart, he'll soon
remember his forgotten tune.♪
All who bar Lady Mikuni's
path shall meet their end,
regardless of rank or station.
For the sake of that child,
I would defy the will
of the gods themselves.
Next time:
"All in Constant Flux"