How are we today?
Much better, thanks.
So, uh.
What's the outlook for
the navy guys I
was rescued with?
Oh, they're fine.
Fit as can be.
But I'd rather we
focused on your recovery.
Smear the cuticles. I dare you.
Madam. Arrangements for the
press conference have been made.
Very well then.
There were survivors from
Operation: Medusa Clean Sweep.
Sparing Digma Three,
neutralize them all.
As you wish, ma'am.
And he had the nerve to look
me in the eye and say "no."
Oh. Hey, look. Kuniko!
'scuse me for living.
Know what I think?
Now that she's president,
she's spread
herself way too thin.
Yeah. But with Momoko still
MIA you can't blame the girl
for wantin' to
throw herself into work.
I guess anything
that keeps her busy
is better than obsessing
on the worst case scenario.
S'pose so.
And of course, I've given
her plenty to worry about too.
What?
Uh-- Talking to myself.
Breaking Atlas news. Prime
Minister Naruse is about to
address the nation via an
impromptu press conference.
Greetings, my fellow citizens.
It is with a heavy heart that
I must announce the
relocation project's hiatus.
What the hell?!
I wish that it were not so.
But Atlas' construction
is too far behind schedule.
And therefore,
I'm afraid our priorities
must be temporarily shifted.
If the outliers must
wait a bit longer so that
the building
process can be expedited,
that is precisely what
I intend for them to do.
How do you justify
that decision, madam?
Why haven't we heard of this?
What about
your inaugural speech?
I am not here to answer you.
I'm here to inform the nation
that its acquiescence
is mandatory.
It's acquiescence
is mandatory?!
Oh, this stuck-up
bitch is going down!
It's time for us to
step outta the shadows
and take a damn stand!
So. What's your plan?
Take a look at this.
Uhhh?!
Wait. You want to
drop in on 'em from above?
Just random enough
to be effective.
Anyone who imagines
I just sit around
on a Tuffet all
day had best rethink it.
I meditated long and
hard on this, and boom.
Had myself a
flash of inspiration.
Anyway, as your leader
I take full responsibility
for the odds against
us on this one.
But when it comes right
down to it, I need your help.
Say n'more, chief.
If these are your
orders, we're on board.
It's up to you. 'Kay?
We'll need you to
work out the details.
What?!
Believe it, sweetheart. Get
New York in our sights pronto
and we'll be bathing in
cash. Check out the asset value
of the company I just bought.
A tenfold increase in seconds!
We can snatch up
America wholesale at this rate!
I wouldn't start popping
the champagne corks
just yet, Klaris.
Medusa. Focus on China.
Zhang, the Chinese
markets are all yours.
On it and then some.
Sittin' on your
horde all cautious-like.
Just so you know,
you're a huge wussy.
Possibly.
Take a chance for once in
your life, like I'm about to do!
Don't let her get to you.
She's just worked up.
I'll get back
to you later, cool?
Been a while since
we made this much money.
"So why don't
you seem happier?"
Hey, I'm perfectly happy.
It's just, I could use a little
shopping spree to cheer me up.
"You mean you're
gonna go outside?"
I'm not crazy about
the idea. But, he... I mean--
Maybe I should do it
as kind of a thank you.
"What if a stranger tries
to make small talk with you?
Have you thought of that?"
I haven't figured
out that part.
"So, what are you going to do?
Hey!
Hiya, Mr. Bear!
Ignore them. You're a
teddy bear. They can't hurt you.
Nicely done, Shion.
Madam.
Corporate Director
Nemoto is on the hotline.
Put him through.
Uh, Madam Ryoko.
At your service.
I--I have someone with me
here who is rather insistent
about speaking
to you immediately.
Who?
It's me.
Darling. To what do I
owe the unmitigated joy?
And may I say, the boyish look
is still working
quite well for you, dear.
Now, now. Life's far
too short to get huffy.
Come in. Please.
You've done well, sir.
We'll be using C4 to blast
through the divider walls,
so we'll need detonators.
And we're gonna want a mountain
of backup magazines if
we expect to hold out long.
I get it. Thank you.
What's up, ya pervs?
This is not a drill!
I repeat: this is not a drill!
Show me rage, Hercules!
They always like this?
So you geezers ain't
kicked the bucket yet?
Momoko not found.
Just us. Here to buy
some goodies from you guys.
Da da dada DA DAAAAA!!!!
All hail the Metal Age prez!
Wait. How'd you even know that?
Never underestimate the
otaku intelligence network.
Oh, hey. How'd your
grandma like the
Magical Gina figurine
we sent you home with?
Well, actually, she had what
you might call a conniption.
Ah! No!
Pierced through the heart.
I don't get it.
Why does that make you sad?
Whoa! Get a load of this!
An early model CZ Seventy Five!
When'd you get this bad boy?
Ah. A fellow after me own heart.
Oh man. You
old-timers got some
pretty neat
stuff hangin' around.
We didn't come here to browse.
We do, however, have a
rather hefty shopping list.
Take a gander at this.
Huh. Two hundred CK201s.
Two hundred .223 caliber rounds,
five-hundred hand grenades,
two-hundred rocket launchers.
No food rations listed, I note.
No. Not yet.
Ah. Might I suggest Type-II
rations? Great chicken stew.
Without carrots?
Uh.
Ah, get over yourself.
It ain't chicken stew
without the carrots.
Put us down for five hundred.
Excellent. Anything else?
Oh, yeah. Something vital.
Get me a kickass boomerang!
'Preciate it.
Thanks. See you next time.
Sure thing.
What are you looking at?
Uh. Nothing. Sorry. See ya!
Hey. Whatcha need?
Well. I'll take this.
And everything on the wall there
behind you, if you'd be so kind.
You deliver, I assume?
Yeah. I guess.
Right. So we're square?
Quite so. Seven days
and you'll have the caboodle.
Seven?! Make it three days
and we'll pay you double.
Whoa, whoa. Since when is Metal
Age runnin' a damn charity?
Since the start!
Well, because
it's you kids, sure.
May I ask where
the fire is, though?
Ah, no fire.
We're taking Atlas by storm.
Huh?
Dah dah daaaahhhhhhhh.
Once we're in charge.
You guys are more than
welcome to set up shop there.
It'll be a helluva
lot cleaner than here.
And, you know,
it's kinda important that
our friends live well and all.
Awe!
Bye! See ya guys in three days!
That girl. No body
pillow could do her justice.
No lie. If anyone can pull of a
coup d'etat, it ought to be her.
Still. How many anime
boutiques they got in Atlas?
We're old. Our
place, boys, is here.
How long has it been, Sayoko?
Still collecting sycophants?
School girl habits
die hard, I see.
You're welcome to pick a
few for yourself, if you like.
No thank you.
You haven't changed
your tune a bit.
Still wrapping yourself
in shriveled androgyny.
Lady Mikuni has clearly
heard the litany of Atlas.
Why has she not yet been
named as the heir? Explain.
Who knows?
Don't toy with me! You have
an answer. I know you do!
Right as always. If only
your clearance was high enough
to warrant an
explanation. Then again...
Even if it were,
threats do not entice me.
A peon in your dilemma
should be kneeling prostrate
before the superior
they would entreat.
Bow and I might
just be persuaded
to overlook your status.
Too much for you?
Then you may leave.
I humbly ask of you...
Rather, I beg.
How pathetic. Even from
you I find such an utter lack
of dignity to be appalling.
A Triple A ranking is bestowed
upon all of Atlas' heirs,
but your Lady isn't
the only candidate.
There are currently three.
So it follows that
while Mikuni might have
indeed heard the litany,
she wouldn't automatically
be named as the heir.
Disappointing, I realize.
Nonsense! There
cannot be two others!
Oh dear. Methinks the
lady doth protest too much.
Does she?
This is actually a lot more
fun than I thought it would be.
I just wish I
didn't have to case
every single shop one at a time.
Hey! Best prices in town!
Get your coupons here!
Pardon me.
Could you tell me exactly
how much Akihabara costs?
And where'd I'd go to buy it?
Huh?!
Nicely done. I think that
covers just about everything.
Good, 'cause I've
got shopper's fatigue.
You're kidding me.
Hey, wait--
I'm dealing with idiots.
What is so difficult about
the concept of buying a city?
It's called real estate,
people! I didn't invent it!
Hey...
What?
Hey there.
You recognize me, don'tcha?
From that one time?
Oh god, it's the
meatspace manqué!
Right? Eh? Think back!
I've never seen you before--
Fibber!
I said I've never seen--!
Oh give it a rest,
you've gotta remember!
Nooo--! Don't look at me!!!
The Hell was that about?
I think we've
found you a new look.
I can't get it off!
No one stands in
Lady Mikuni's way.
If Ryoko won't tell me the
identity of the other two,
I'll find it.
Biometric ID.
I'll need one more
favor from you, friend.
Ah, Zeus.
Hope you're ready!
Madam.
What now?
I'm afraid someone is
attempting to hack into Zeus.
You can ignore them. They
have no hope of gaining entry.
Madam. The would-be
interloper's speed is
nothing short of astounding.
I've never
encountered its equal.
We estimate infiltration
at thirty million seconds.
Sayoko.
The little minx
is full of surprises.
Her hacking speed
is still on the increase.
She'll broach the top secret
area in twenty-three million.
Will she?
Is that all you've got?
I'm rather worried she's
managed to get this far.
Twenty thousand
seconds now. Ten thousand.
Ma'am, she's
approaching the threshold.
She'll give up before too long.
There you are!
Detrimental breech imminent!
She's at the threshold!
Files, if you please.
What the Hell?!
Bravo. A noble effort, darling.
Miiko? Hath Sayoko
not yet returned?
No, I'm afraid she hasn't. Not
surprising when one considers
that woman's
unwavering dedication to you.
Mayhap.
My Lady!
Oh dear!
Stay where you are.
She brought this upon herself.
Seditious actions
beget ends that none but
the most naive criminal
would dare complain of.
Pardon?!
Enough!
What shall we do?
This is Momoko's earring.
What in the world?
"So much for buying Akihabara."
C'est la vie. Still though.
No place like home, I guess.
"Absolutely! At least here no
one tries to make conversation!"
The outside
world's so overrated.
"You really and
truly think so?"
"I mean, it was still
kind of fun, wasn't it?"
Hello.
What's this?
You scamp.
Take care of yourself, Mo.
That's all I ask.
Miiko?
Is't thou troubled?
No, dear.
Miiko! Thou embraceth
us so fiercely!
We'll advance along
this route, and at this point
we're gonna rendezvous with the
other squadrons
that'll be moving in.
What are we hearing
from the internal branches?
They've all agreed
to help us out.
We'll marshal around the chosen
locale as you've instructed.
And from there, make our move.
Perfect.
There's one more thing, though.
The original plan
we had to rescue Momoko.
Forget it.
If we're not all on the same
page, we'll lose our focus.
We gotta put our efforts
into realizing the larger goal.
Besides, for all we know,
a rescue mission
could be pointless.
Our first priority
has got to be Atlas.
If Momoko were here,
she'd agree one-hundred percent.
Spoken like a leader.
Too bad more men
aren't so self-possessed.
Seriously, I'd date more.
Momoko. It's you.
Sweet pea.
Momoko! Momoko!
Oh my. Someone's been at
the cookie jar, haven't they?
If they laid so much as a
finger on you... Are you okay?!
How the Hell'd
you get out of there?
Go easy on the
questions, darling.
It's been a
rather long few days.
I'm fine. Their flagship
S&amp;M cabaret left much
to be desired, sad to say.
The headliner was too butch.
Next time I think
about it, though,
I'll have to send
Miiko a thank-you card.
Miiko?
The one and only.
Seems she's in good hands.
I sense you've had a
somewhat dramatic change
of heart about Metal Age?
Yeah.
Be honest. Was it your decision?
Or did my absence
force your hand?
Oh believe me, the decision
was all mine. This is my life.
Ah. So you say.
So, are you,
like, against it, or...?
You know I've never
been one to tell the wind
which way I'd prefer it to
caper. I enjoy being surprised.
Yeah. So do I.
Honestly, I'm not
big on fighting.
But the people I
love need a protector,
and I'm the girl for the job.
So for our future's sake,
for the sake of the outliers,
from this moment forward
I'm a warrior!
Next time: "Flying Girl"