Furnace 3 is down!
Fall back to Okubo Street!
Ya think we should run?
A lady should never
entertain an unwelcome suitor.
Who the Hell is firing?
Don't know.
It's not our forces!
Why aren't we
launching a counterattack?
Engaging a force
of unknown origin
and strength is not a
strategically sound idea.
What strategy
would you recommend?
A complete withdrawal.
My incident notes will indicate
we fell back upon
your recommendation.
Furnace 2 is down!
Cut the supply--
What's the damage?
I don't know what's goin'
on in the rest of the city,
but we've lost furnaces
two and three for now!
Run!
You all right?!
Yeah, we're fine.
But we need ta--
Of course we'll go check
on the others. Come on!
Right!
That blade of yours.
I assure you I have all
the credentials to carry it.
It's been in my family
for generations, sir.
The tone it made rang
from elsewhere as well.
I heard it too, but I couldn't
tell where it came from.
Please, you have to keep moving!
Are you okay?
Yeah! Thank you so much!
Yoshihiro!
Mom!
You and those
Metal Age goons want to
take on the government, huh?
This is our home too, you know!
Don't be mean to her.
She was helping me!
We don't need her help!
Soichiro.
The attack originated
in old Ikebukuro,
and considering the target
selection and precision,
all signs point
to it being the work
of a highly
trained artillery unit.
A new guerilla faction
entering the fray perhaps?
Their skill belies a
force far more capable.
Are you implying
foreign troops have launched
an assault from
within our borders?
Although similar activity
has been reported elsewhere,
sending artillery
without other support
is illogical,
strategically speaking.
I understand.
Shion?
Yes, my lady?
You have a
youthful point of view.
Do you think we should
allow alien forces
to enter our country
without striking back?
N-No, no ma'am.
Violence shall be
met with violence!
Will age weaken
your resolve as well?
My lady!
I'll lead a recon mission
into the poison swamp at once.
Just please let him down.
That sounds lovely.
Shogo, I shall
trust the rest to you.
Of course.
Shion, I'm so sorry,
please tell me you're okay!
Forgive me, brother.
I've disappointed you again.
That's not the kind of attention
you want to garner from her.
Speaking out freely like
that can cost you your tongue.
I won't apologize for what I've
done. I had no other choice.
It looks pretty bad,
but I heard a lot less people
got hurt than they thought.
That's good, I guess.
Yeah... right.
Have you seen Kuniko around?
I'm pretty sure
she's been stuck
doing some Metal Age
thing all morning.
Huh, I thought she
said wasn't with them.
Yeah, she says that,
but you know her grandma.
You got a point.
So the attack came
from the Ikebukuro forest?
We got verification
on that, Furukawa?
Do you think someone could use
the old subway
tunnels to get there?
They probably could, but--
No way, kid!
Now don't you
go entertaining
any fantasies of
derring-do young lady.
The air in that swamp
is not only poisonous,
but'll make quick work of
that lovely complexion a girl
like myself would kill for.
Besides, this is not your fight.
But that's not true. 'Cause,
Duomo is home to all of us.
Anyway, I'm sure we have
some suits or something
we could wear
lying around. Right?
Fine, you win.
Well, Mister Tailor.
We're gonna need a 36-24-35
for bust, waist and hips.
Not for her, you moron!
Those are my measurements!
Do we need to get you a new
pair of glasses while we're out?
You're really coming with me?
I bet you give this
place another year or two
and the goddamn roots'll be
choking' up the entire tunnel.
Why did I even bother giving
that blind twit my measurements?
Change your hair
color and you could
prob'ly pass for
Miko in that thing.
My worst fears realized!
Surely we can go back.
Not a chance.
This is an emergency.
I can't go out like this!
Sweet Raquel,
if I ever get this size,
please, fit me for a coffin!
You have my word.
Nicely done Karin!
Looks like Medusa's
making a big splash!
If you're handing out kudos,
don't forget who netted
all that capital from the EU!
Since we're patting
our own backs,
I'll be sure to mention
my silver tongue was the one
who brought Ishida
Finance all the gold
from the Swiss Carbon
Banking Federation.
Yeah, yeah, I think we can agree
that we're all pretty awesome.
But, what's most awesome to me
is that we're all
rolling in dough.
Speaking of rolling, I forgot to
tell you guys, I bought Ferrari!
Cool! You pick up
the new 706 or something?
No silly, the whole company!
So how's Medusa?
Help me.
Looks fine to me.
The poor thing...
Being in constant fear of death
is no way to spend your life.
That's how it's gotta be.
That "poor" thing's
what's keeping us
outta the "poor house."
Well put, but I
still question the wisdom
of keeping Ishida HQ
on the Marshall Islands.
Those levees break
and it's all washed away.
The islands are a tax haven
and Medusa is just a program,
ya big softie. Besides,
you gotta love the realism.
Medusa has to control
those nasty carbon emissions
to keep from drowning.
I know it's "just a
program" but you gotta
empathize with
the little bugger.
I've known him since
he was just a line of code
and he's been so good to us.
Damn right!
Anyway, Karin, you got a
new target in the crosshairs?
Dunno. Let's see
what catches his eye.
Help me! Help me!
Aww. Don't worry. This sea
you're in is the carbon market.
All you gotta do
is find something out
there that looks out of place.
Those are weak spots
that you can break into.
I know you can do it, you're the
best in the whole world at that.
Weak spots. Weak spots.
There's always one or two.
Just look for a place
with a lot of carbon emissions
and not enough carbon credits.
It's like a big gap that
you can slide right into.
I found one!
I found one! I found one!
Nydamia, huh? Alright,
let's do it guys!
Ooh! Me! I'm right on it!
I found one! I found one!
Very good!
Now wait while Auntie Klaris
gets our contract ready.
All done!
Zhang!
Relax, we just
bought up a huge chunk
of their industrial sector.
Now to sell it
off for a fat profit!
Not to mention collect
our fee for getting rid of
all that yucky
monetized carbon!
Look at those
investors rollin' in!
You ready to sell off?
No, not yet.
Not 'til it hits peak.
Money is a girl's best friend!
Uh, Karin.
Yes! Yes!
Sell it all now!
Big sale on assets!
Everything must go!
Oh yeah!
Oooh, that got me soo hot!
I gotta spend
some of that cash!
I think that's
enough magic for today.
Ooh, this one looks good!
Tarsian, you know you're
being rude! Speak up!
Come on, let's play some--
Such a heavenly tone did
sing out. Do we know why?
A pertinent question, milady,
and one I posed to Atlas.
They answer not.
Miss Mikuni.
Surely that
splendid chime portends
glorious days
to come for you.
Light will shine down and fill
your heart with resounding joy.
Your careless tongue
betrays your lack
of experience in this chamber.
What could be the matter?
My heart spoke
and I simply desired
to share its joyous
words with my lady.
Tis a pity.
My prayers are with you.
What do you mean?
Your lies are sweet,
but poison to our soul.
That makes the fifth such
one to fall this month alone.
We shall begin the search
for her replacement
with all possible dispatch.
No matter. The lower
realms brim with servants
ripe for the taking.
Is that not so?
Everybody make sure your
breathing apparatus is working.
I just felt a pop in
my ears, is that normal?
The pressure in the suit keeps
the outside air from coming in
and popping your lungs
so that's good thing.
Now. Let's all check our
secondary filters, alright?
If your suit rips, that little
thing will save your life.
But it's only got enough juice
for an hour, so be careful.
Remember our
objective is strictly to
locate the enemy's artillery
squad, not to engage them.
Let's move.
Well, from the sound of it,
there's water
everywhere around us.
We must be right under a lake,
so let's keep moving ahead
and see if we can find a way up.
Be careful you guys,
'cause if you fall in
that toxic soup down there,
that's the end of it.
You'd be dead 'fore we could
even think of saving you.
According to Foorukawa's guess.
We're just about
to the launch site.
Look up ahead!
Our search is finding no
trace of enemy activity.
How come the slags're here too?
Looks like recon to me.
If the army's out here
runnin' recon like we are,
I guess that means it
wasn't them that attacked us.
A shrewd deduction.
I don't believe it. A man behind
me, and I didn't even notice.
You guys could stand to learn
a thing or two
about stealth tactics.
Metal Age not
trained ya that far?
I am partially untrained.
But fully transsexual!
This suit ruins my
figure and my aim.
Takehiko!
Kuniko, you guys okay?
Yeah, we're both fine
and making our escape!
Get back to the station,
but don't get tailed, copy?
Loud and clear!
Momoko, don't fall behind!
I'm trying sweetie!
I thought all that Judo would
be great for your stamina.
It is, but have you
ever seen a Judo match
take place during a marathon?
You always said
you were poised to be
"the crown jewel of
the Olympic team," right?
I gave up my
jewels a long time ago.
That lovely surgeon
took them as his trophy!
Oh, now I get it.
You know. They say
a tranny simply trades
his jewels for
gorgeous white pearls.
What the Hell does that mean?!
No time for that dear.
Let's focus on
our escape right now.
Come on, don't be such a tease!
What do you mean by pearls?
I'm actually
kinda curious myself!
Geez, it's so freakin'
hard to move in this thing!
You'd move a lot faster if you
weren't babbling about jewelry.
Yoo-hoo!
Don't bother.
Lemme ask you something.
Why the Hell is the slag
heap poking around out here?
Although I may be your prisoner,
I don't have to answer
any of your questions!
Why did my grandma's dagger
and yours both make
that sound earlier?
You mean there's
another dagger like mine?
You know something, don't you?
All I know is I'm not talking!
You got the kinda balls
we like in Metal Age,
so if you quit the army,
come on out to Duomo.
Sign up with us. I'll put
in a good word for ya!
What am I gonna do with you.
Stunts like that go
against the survival instinct.
There's no way I could've
done that in this clunky suit.
We need to run along home now,
that nasty swamp air
is gonna melt your cute
little face right off.
Don't try to
scare me like that.
Who was it?
It was polka dots. I mean, some
Metal Age soldiers out there.
Digma 2 again was it?
What?
Then they don't know any
more about it than we do.
You didn't recover any shell
casings, or any other evidence
of a militarized
force out there?
That's correct sir,
we couldn't find a single trace
of an enemy installation.
An unknown force
wielding an unknown weapon,
amid inhospitable conditions.
What do you mean?
Exactly what I said.
I checked with
our carbon surveillance
satellite, Icarus,
and it detected no unusual
carbon dioxide in Ikebukuro.
A battery of
artillery fire, but no CO2?
So what do you suppose
could be behind this?
You're our top analyst,
so I'm sure you have
some kind of
theory in the works.
Perhaps the forest
is baring its fangs, eh?
None? You didn't find any
metal at the points of impact?!
What the hell?!
We got nailed, and you can't
find a single shell fragment!
That's so weird.
Yeah. Well, I think it's
those bastards at Atlas
testing out some secret
weapon on our people!
Would they do that?
They're gonna
announce the results
of the Atlas lottery right now!
This time I'm goin'
to Atlas for sure!
It's my lucky day!
Give me a break.
Don't you idiots realize
this Atlas lottery bullshit
is just some great big
government scheme
to try to buy our--
Guess not.
It won't be us.
You must never forget
the tranny code, dearie.
Confidence is the
lipstick of our spirit!
I can't help it, I'm sorry.
It's our destiny to enter
Atlas and re-open Tropical Fish.
The city simply needs us there.
I know, but what about Kuniko?
If Atlas chooses us,
you know we can't take
the little scamp with us.
We'll have to leave her behind.
And our lucky winner is...
Congratulations,
Mr. Tetsuo Kumagai.
It's not fair.
Why you and not me?
I come bringing
news that will surely be
of great interest
to the Head of Atlas!
We've heard the sacred
chime of the amulets.
An incomplete utopian
world, born of man's desire.
While the meek and pure of
heart are called to enter,
the uninvited
make their own way.
Next time: "The Creation"