"Simply leave the details
to us, and I assure you
Orochi will be
brought to its knees."
Nothing like
contracting a teddy bear
to do the
government's dirty work, eh?
Minister, we're dealing
with a Neo Carbonist
whose stock portfolio alone puts
our combined assets to shame.
I strongly advise caution.
What is your organization's
interest in this proposal?
"Orochi's activities have
incurred significant losses for
our company. And every second
we let them proceed unchecked,
the carbon market as a whole
verges closer to total failure."
Yes, but what
recourse is there when we're
not even certain
where they operate from?
"We bait them out
onto a level playing field."
What? But how?
"Any country with a large
disparity between emissions
and GNP is blood in the water.
Orochi will go for
them in a heartbeat,
but if we act quickly, we can
get a lock on their location."
"By our calculations,
Kuwait is the perfect decoy
for such a scenario.
All Ishida Finance requires
to proceed is the Japanese
government's full cooperation."
What you're asking us
is tantamount to betrayal!
We cannot support
wreaking untold havoc
on a sovereign
nation's economy!
"That's not okay?"
Of course not!
It's international law!
We shouldn't
have to explain this!
Why did we think we
could bank on a child.
"Shut up!"
"Your economy is heading
straight down the crapper!
Now, you can either
go along with my plan
that will make
both of us happy.
Or keep hanging on
to old-fashioned ideas of
"international manners" while
everyone else eats you alive!"
Wow. The markets
are getting twisted.
They're getting
more than twisted.
They're on the
brink of utter collapse.
Is it really that serious?
It is indeed. That debacle
with the Saudi prime?
Just a taste
of things to come.
Stay sharp.
What we need is vigilance.
Someone, or something,
is lurking behind the scenes.
Even as we speak,
it coils in readiness for
the next unsuspecting victim.
What in the Hell are you doing?
Sir. Tendering my resignation.
I don't suppose
this has anything to do
with the mimetic armor gaffe?
Sir, yes it does.
I must atone--
Atone?! Screw-ups
don't fix themselves when
the parties responsible
throw in the towel!
Sir, I--
Shut the Hell up!
What happens when Metal Age
forks over that sample
to the highest bidder?
We're screwed! That's what...
But, thankfully,
there's a silver lining.
We marked it as classified,
but actually the tech's
just a spit-polished rehash
of the kinda crap that's
been out there for years.
All of our genuine technological
secrets are still secure.
We got a call from
the Atlas Corporation.
Evidently someone
there feels very strongly
that you
shouldn't be reprimanded.
Atlas?!
Why would
the muckety-mucks
give a stale turd about
an enlisted man like you?
My entire career I've never once
taken a call like that before.
I don't really have
an explanation for you.
I come from
humble stock, sir.
We've never
lived above level four.
That so?
There was something else.
Another rather odd request.
Sir?
You've been called to make an
appearance at the Moon Palace.
Seriously?
So, our little night flower
has taken a shine to Kusanagi?
Indeed.
Please forgive
the intrusion, madam.
Go on.
It concerns the government's
plans to bait Orochi.
I've been apprised.
Sounds thrilling.
But Kuwait, madam.
We have a relationship there.
Yes, as does everyone.
Predicated absurdly
on their oil reserves.
Its fall is no concern of ours.
And, if the gambit fails,
Ishida Finance
will be held to account.
The brunt of the catastrophe
will be theirs to deal with.
Indeed.
But if they succeed,
Kuwait grows several
hundred million marks
richer in foreign aid.
A generous estimation.
Come, it's the least we
can do to express our thanks.
Someone has to play
the mouse in this game.
As you wish.
I should consult Zeus and
make all necessary preparations.
Shion?
Ma'am.
Relieve the
chef of his position.
His overuse of salt
betrays him for an amateur.
Yes, of course.
Your cooking is the bomb!
I can't remember the last time
you've come home to visit us.
But, of course,
you're going right back out.
Look, I'm sorry.
I've got to be at some place
called the Moon Palace,
so I gotta motor soon.
Run that by me again?
I couldn't hear for
all the half-eaten veggies
knocking around in your mouth!
Give me a break for once, will
ya? I don't have a lot of time.
The brass has me all
over the friggin' map.
You know what a pain it is just
to work in this much of a break?
My, what a considerate son.
Here to unburden me of my food.
Aw. Take a pill.
I'm doin' this for you.
Old ladies go senile when they
don't got somethin' to bitch a--
Show some manners or people will
think you were raised by wolves!
Hey, Mom. Do we know someone?
Like with the higher ups?
Someone? Like who?
Nah, forget about it.
Dumb question.
So, uh. Can you tell
me anything about this
Mikuni I'm about
to be introduced to?
I mean, what can I expect?
Sir, your dagger
must be left here with me.
Oh, right.
Just be careful with it,
please. It's very old.
I assure you no
harm will come to it, sir.
Thank you.
Approach the dais,
Lieutenant Kusanagi.
Be seated.
It is an honor to be here.
We ask that your
face be not supine.
We are called Mikuni.
Scrutinize our countenance.
Is it lovely?
Um, no. Not especially.
Then eyes are
wasted on you, sir!
I highly recommend you modify
your observations to the facts!
Hold, Miiko.
Sorry, love. The boy's a fool.
Perhaps,
but one who hath spoken plainly
the truth as he doth see it.
Look there.
I'll be damned.
We would hear
depicted with equal candor
thy late dishonor, lieutenant.
Ah. Well, I--I was
captured by terrorists.
Thy captors must
have been most fearsome.
T'would seem no mean feat
to detain the likes of you.
Yeah, but.,, The one
responsible was actually
just some stupid kid.
Oh dear!
Indeed.
This surpriseth us.
Doth thine enemy boast of boys
whose dimensions belie them?
No, it was a girl.
Impressive how
long he's lasted with her.
Heaven knows it's rare.
I don't know that
I care for this trend.
He represents three such
souls who have piddled through
her ladyship's trial
without so much as a mark.
What's so special about you?
Where's your ranking?
The Hell?! I'm using
her ladyship's password!
What earthly reason
would the Atlas Corporation
have for shielding his records?
Damn it!
Research team.
What of his blade?
We've subjected it
to a battery of tests.
All our data
points to it's being,
well, basically identical.
Not a chance!
But for slight
variation due to exposure,
the contours are
virtually indistinguishable.
And mind you, it's not as though
they've been cast from a mold.
They're rather
like two masterful copies
of a common antecedent.
Would it be possible for us
to obtain a sample
for further testing?
We have to return it to him
intact. Can you craft a fake?
Not on such short notice, no.
That's all, then.
We have what we have.
The blade will
remain a mystery.
Yes, ma'am.
What are you hiding, lieutenant?
How did you come by that blade?
And why do the Atlas drones
have your records fenced off?
Ah. How frustrated she must've
been to come up empty-handed.
No doubt shaking her
fists as we speak, madam.
Clever mix
of metaphors, Soichiro.
Still, if Sayako
could trudge this far..
our Hiruko must be in agony.
One might almost
feel pity for the child.
The Moon and The Land!
They've mingled!
The day of
fulfillment is upon us!
Are you trying to
give me a heart attack?!
Your back was wide open. You're
old enough to know better, hon.
Enemies don't always
bust through the front door.
But how did you--?
It's amazing
how nimble you can be
when you check
your luggage at the curb.
Don't be such a grouch.
You have to read the
weapon's path, sweetie.
And not throw like
an angry hairdresser.
So what's eating you?
All the markets
are acting weird.
You don't say?
Son of a--!
You're putting way too
much force behind the grab.
Treat it like a lover.
Nice and gentle.
So... The markets
are all worked up...?
'kay, this'll
prolly sound nuts,
but when they fluctuate,
I can, like, feel it.
Oo la la!
Oh grow up!
Sorry.
They writhe. Then come
together like a big snake.
This, evil thing
crawling right underneath us.
It's a predator,
hunting down countries
with a sizable carbon balance.
See, it ensnares them by
offering to take out a lease
on their debt.
They can't resist.
Money starts pouring
in from overseas, sure,
but the stocks
are basically worthless.
So when push comes to shove
all that foreign investment
capital just
picks up and leaves.
The whole thing's a scam.
All it really reduces are
the index numbers themselves.
And countries struggling to make
ends meet get laid to waste.
Yeah. The victim of,
what do they call it?
A bulb economy?
Bubble economy.
Yeah, yeah. So this "snake"
creates one wherever it pleases?
In laymen's terms. Only in this
case the scale is much larger
and the cycle much shorter.
Even the strongest
countries are prey.
Oh, right. The Grande
Dame wants to see you.
Something to do
with serpents, I think.
This intel comes
to us care of a mole
Takehiko has planted
in the Atlas Corporation.
Apparently, the government
is going to try its hand
at slaying monsters.
What's their plan? No way!
Oh yes, child. They intend
to hook another country
through the gills and
dangle them like a minnow.
They can't do that!
There's, like,
a gazillion laws against it!
Kuniko. That's
no deterrent to them.
A country in dire
straits brooks no threat,
however many laws
have to be discarded.
Survival plays
by its own rules.
Alright, people. Commence!
Is this Imai
Financial Holdings?
Sell!
Now selling
shares in Kuwait Oil!
Flood the market!
Pump in whatever you have to!
Our assets are plummeting
like a skydiver without a chute.
Whatever you lose today
will buy this country's
security tomorrow,
so keep that in mind.
They've begun.
Do we have stock in Kuwait?
I pulled us out in time.
Carbon index: a hundred
thirty-eight point seventy nine.
A number for the record
books if ever I've seen one.
The Kuwaitis are buying to
drive up the value of course,
but too late.
Too late by half.
That's it for them.
As of this moment,
they're bankrupt.
And the ripple effect sends
the Middle East into free fall.
Now the EU is scrambling
to protect the euro bloc.
A hurry up and wait
game for them. Or not?
It's here!
That's him.
Take a good hard look,
child. Commit it to memory.
Kuwait's carbon index dropped!
One point fifteen. A nation
formerly up to its eyeballs
in debt has the same
credit rating as Japan.
But how?
By slapping a lien on
their oil fields, essentially.
That's a financial
vacuum no bank in the world
can resist filling.
Look there.
The smaller banks
go belly up first.
But the high rollers
know if they hang on,
the earnings are exponential.
Question is, can they hang on?
A hundred sixty-trillion?!
Is the cash investors have
lying around infinite or what?
Are the banks that reckless?!
Oh, there's a whole other
game afoot. Can't you see it?
Grandma! Check the
banks underwriting the assets
and see if
they're in bed with
the ones underwriting
the liabilities!
You see the patterns
underneath it all.
Yeah! They're
leasing the oilfields
back to the Kuwaiti government!
Bingo. And in a
moment, they'll pull out.
It's gone. Damn!
A hundred and sixty trill.
All of it right back
in the vaults. At interest.
The monster has fled.
Now clear your mind and focus.
Visualize the global market.
Let the beast
present itself to you.
Where are you?
A gap? A tiny fissure?
Got him! That's it! That's
where the bastard sleeps!
The Maldives!
Where in the Maldives? It's
still a needle in a haystack!
Zeus has it narrowed
down to twelve points,
but that's as
specific as it can get!
"They've set up
dummy corporations
to throw us off the scent."
I'm getting more impressed
with them by the minute.
Where is he hiding?
Come on. Focus!
Show me water
level stats around Esath!
Okay, see.
Those are way too low.
Oh wow.
They've dropped
thirty centimeters
just in the last hour.
That's crazy.
Is that our quarry?
Yes, it is!
Huh. Lookie there.
We're locked on.
Orochi is nested
on Esath Island, ma'am.
And this comes from where?
Evidently from Metal Age.
They're posting by
proxy on several forums.
Don't be crazy. By inference
you're saying they have
access to a system
superior to Zeus.
They might.
They do possess the Sun.
Pass the information
on to America immediately.
And as for Kuwait,
cut them a nice check.
But, mail it out tomorrow.
Yes, as you wish.
What's the matter?
How come you look so exhausted?
Slaying monsters
takes a lot out of a girl.
I'm entitled
to look exhausted.
Okay.
Geez! I'm kidding!
No, I get ya. Things are
pretty rough all over, huh?
Don't go thinkin' this has
anything to do
with Metal Age, either.
'course not. Look at you.
You're a perfectly
normal teenage girl, right?
Damn right. Who just
happens to know folks.
Folks she freeloads off of.
Thanks for
the self-esteem boost.
Good afternoon to you.
News today from overseas.
The U.S. defense
department confirmed
its fire-bombing of Ehsoth,
a small island situated among
the South Pacific Maldives,
earlier this morning.
Do what?!
Asked to clarify. A white
house spokesperson said
the attacks were "harsh,
but necessary to prevent
further disruption
in the carbon markets."
The Federation of South
Pacific Islands has logged
severe public
outcry against the action.
And tensions
continue to escalate
between the two nations.
You gotta love that
yankee flair for the dramatic.
Just thank heavens
the markets are stable.
"So. Safe to assume
this collaborative exercise
has sufficiently endeared
you to Ishida's resources?"
Uh. I think so, yes.
Typical U.S. overkill.
Three fuel-air bombs on
a nothing little isthmus.
They're stuck in last-century.
Good old fashioned
American nanny-ism.
The markets are
all responding in kind.
Not that their list of
friends was long to begin with.
The U.S. carbon
index has spiked.
Heh. So much for aid.
By this time tomorrow our
hundred million will be pitiful.
You're not appalled?
It's a write off. And
either way, getting to witness
The Sun's instincts in
action is well worth the loss.
Shion.
Yes, Madam Ryoko?
Ready my horse. I need air.
Ma'am.
Well, the markets
appear to be stable
for the foreseeable future.
Provided no one takes it
into their head to
follow Orochi's example.
Are you trying
to clean me out?!
I'd have been better off
setting my portfolio on fire!
Yes, I agreed to
help take down Orochi,
but that hit could've
totally finished me!
Boo hoo. I told
you not to short sell.
Oh, whatever! A Neo-Carbonist
worthy of the name trades
down to the last
nanosecond and you know it!
You didn't have to
pick on Kuwait anyway!
You just did
it to keep me from
getting that new outfit
'cause you're jealous--
Yeah, yeah.
Bankruptcy's a bitch.
Oh, I'll show you a--
Congratulations, Karin.
Tarsian! Don't gloat.
For your information
I'm not the least bit
surprised you're
behind this mess.
Not even a little?
Well, maybe when your pride
and joy reacts to seeing
a copycat program snuffed out
for doing exactly what he does,
that jade casing will crack.
They grow up so fast, don't
they? Forming new synapses.
Making connections.
Tying their own shoes.
That was my aim
in all this, you know.
Bravo. Is that all?
Hmmm. Maybe.
Operation Digma
Two Net. Commence.
Crashing against the bars of
her cage like a beast in heat,
l'enfant terrible spares
no thought for gratitude.
How shrill and
tedious children are.
Next time: "Sad Thoughts
of Love and Hate"