It's time. Get a move on.
Kuniko! Kuniko!
Knock it off!
Don't forget us in here!
Give 'em Hell
when you get back!
You better write!
Or just get nicked again!
This place won't be
the same without ya!
Listen up!
Today's the day!
The world's my oyster!
Good luck out there, kid.
Now, if I ever lay eyes on
you again, it'll be too soon.
Understood?
No one's here.
Momoko!
You little delinquent.
Oh, honey it's so
good to love your neck.
When'd you shave last?
When'd you eat last?
The girls are lookin' starved.
Hello! Hot-button issue!
Oi! Ya ridin' or ain't ya?
Didn't expect
to see you, old man!
Now don't start
taking that tone with me.
Oh, pumpkin.
Miiko!
These past two years
have been an eternity.
D'ya gain a
pound for each month?
Ugh! You scrummy harlot!
Enough with the tears.
Just 'cause your face
is built like a storm levee
doesn't mean you
have to use it like one.
You are just the
worst kind of harpy.
Who'd better have
brought what I asked her.
Please. I look
like a rhinestone?
Just promise to play nice.
How's this for nice?!
And that is?
A clink rag.
They had me salute this
stupid thing day and night,
so I'm owed a little revenge.
But, now I can move on.
'kay. Homeward bound, then.
Duomo become a
hustling boom town yet?
Oh yes. Poverty's the
new affluent, it's fab.
Lots of new hoi polloi
have set up tent there.
Ooohhh! Fresh meat!
The Shokuan block's been sinking
like Atlantis
in slow-mo, though.
So, you know,
there goes the neighborhood.
Yep.
Curtain in five, people!
The old lady wants to see
you first thing, ya hear?
So why doncha--
Hey! Butter troll!
Move! Ah, damn it.
Relax. One doesn't
put a tether on the wind.
She'll get where's she's
going in her own time.
Hey! She's back!
"What began as disparate
acts of civil disobedience
against the
environmental austerity
charters enacted
by the government became,
in time, the
Metal Age movement."
"When new, draconian
CO2 emissions sta-"
The polite way to absorb
knowledge is by sitting still.
Take a good,
hard look around you, girl.
These are the
relics of a bygone age.
The Carbon Market
would hemorrhage
to see the remnants
of so many felled trees.
Yet the wisdom
represented here is priceless.
Unavailable to
the idle web-surfer.
Perhaps the old
forests' greatest legacy.
Where wisdom's concerned,
the internet conceals
far more than it yields.
When, during the course of your
glory as Metal Age's leader,
you find yourself at a loss.
Kuniko! You could
at least wait to tear off
until I've said my piece!
Love ya, grandma!
So the prodigal
granddaughter has returned, eh?
What was your first clue?
Kuniko?
Whoa there, girlie,
hang on! They break you out?
Naw I'm out fair and square!
Here. Help wash down
the taste o' freedom.
Thank you!
No prob.
That's good. I'm glad to
see they haven't broken her.
Yeah.
Should I know her?
Ah. You've never
had the pleasure.
Kuniko Hojo.
Nagiko's wild granddaughter.
That's the girl
she's grooming to be
Metal Age's next president?
I'm not so sure 'bout that.
Hey, where's my souvenir?
Next time, I promise!
I'm not gonna hold
my breath, cheapskate!
Your report, Shogo.
Something I can use.
Madam.
Digma 2 has been released
from the girls'
correctional facility.
She's returned home to Sector
E-51, commonly known as Duomo.
Shion. Watch your fingernails!
My sincerest apologies!
Continue to monitor her actions.
As you wish, madam.
So the Sun assumes its Chariot.
And where pray tell
does that leave the Moon?
As she ever is, madam.
Touring the lower
realms at her fancy.
Feast your eyes on that.
What'd I tell ya, huh?
Are you sure this is legal?
I mean, Atlas has those
barricades for a reason.
Whose rank you think
got us through 'em?
Ready the gun!
All apologies
for the noise, milady.
How exhilarating
the lower realms are!
They held a BC rank?
I'll not have Miss
Mikuni's promenade savaged
by such a troglodyte!
For propriety, let us
promote them to AG.
Sayoko. Prithee let
us see all the fuss.
No, milady. 'Twould no
doubt sully your vision.
No? Thou art an icy warden!
Indeed. That I am.
Chop, chop!
The eclipse is spent!
Hey, Tokyo! I'm back!
Fine. If you insist, I'll recap.
You're familiar with
the concept of Carbon Tax?
The levy designed to diminish
global CO2 emissions. Very.
The rate of taxation fluctuates
with a given country's ratio
of carbon emissions to carbon
absorption. I'm not stupid!
'course not.
Now Japan's carbon
index holds firm
at one-point-twelve
at the moment.
Whereas your homeland is at a
whopping two-point-forty-eight.
Meaning you basically owe
two-thousand,
four-hundred eighty marks
per thousand marks of output.
Not a sustainable rate.
Spout those numbers out to
my face and I might take you
seriously, otherwise you
can just go to Hell!
Face-time is so your generation.
Get with the era, sourpuss.
Economies aren't built
on the back nine anymore.
We have that purview to thank
for despoiling the
planet in the first place.
You had your chance
and you blew it.
Carbonists do
things differently.
I'm painfully aware of that.
This monetized carbon scheme's
derailed the whole goddamn game!
Don't blame the charters for
your country's knee-jerk
reluctance to comply.
No one forced you to hedge
your bets against astronomical
tariffs by industrializing to
the hilt. That was your choice.
Sure, you figured like
every other dissenting nation
you'd outsmart the system
by balancing the penalties
against the living wage you
consistently deny
your workforce.
But that's exactly the kind of
out-moded quasi-imperialist
strategy the Carbon Tax
is designed to render obsolete.
The longer a country
takes to reduce its actual
carbon emissions, the higher the
interest rate grows on the tax.
Ergo your present impasse.
You blather to me about
imperialism when a handful
of well-heeled nations
unilaterally impose a--
If you don't like it, become
a self-sufficient economy
unto yourselves and pull
out of the global market!
Sign a contract with us
here at Ishida Finance
and we'll assume
the tax debt for up to
one-hundred million tons
of your carbon output.
It's as simple as that.
We'll transfer the lien to
our LCTI holding company
when the balance
becomes amortized across--
Thank you. I believe
I have the gist of it.
In lieu of curbing pollution,
we'll just be shrinking
an imaginary number vis-à-vis
the "monetized carbon" racket.
It's outright fraud!
I assure you
it's perfectly legal.
Quite so, sir. If it weren't,
our country would be complicit
in a charter-breaking
act from which
Ishida would have
nothing to gain.
I'd listen to the suits at
your shoulder, Mr. Abidin.
Rest easy
knowing our company
owns copyright on Medusa.
The only computer program in
the world capable of packaging
one-hundred-million tons
of monetized carbon derivatives
and cleanly,
legally, hedging
the collateralized
risk obligation.
Any other program would
spell bankruptcy so
fast your head would spin.
This is a mathematically
proven fact, by the way,
not just a pitch.
If you'd like to read my
doctoral thesis on the subject--
I have read it.
Good. Then we can wrap things
up. You're a hard sell, sir.
It doesn't usually
take me half as long
as this to secure a contract.
I remind you, Minister:
while you sit there comfortably
weighing your country's options,
your people buckle under
the weight of its debt.
Please, sir. Make your decision.
This is what I'm reduced to.
Selling my own soul to spare
my country the indignity.
Well done!
Your contract with
Ishida Finance is now official.
One point zero. Just like that.
After decades of
unmitigated toil,
it's as easy as waving
your goddamned hand.
Yep. Sign of the times.
Wow, Pudding. We busted our
hinnies for that one, huh?
"That we did, Karin.
We got some IM's from Klaris
and the guys, by the way."
Let 'em wait. I'm tired.
"Like Mommy and Daddy?"
They have very busy schedules.
I'll see what
they're up to later.
"I'll bet they'll
be super proud
of all the neat
stuff we did today, huh?"
Yeah!
Help me. Help me. Help me.
I know you're
scared, little fella,
but that's exactly what
makes you so useful.
Panic brings on
the big bad flood.
And the big bad flood is
what's keeping you on the alert.
However short-lived,
one-hundred-million tons
of CO2 doesn't
simply disappear. Yes?
Zeus monitors the flow
of debt-to-absorption
as closely as it can, madam.
But the market is an
exceptionally complex entity.
So you've no idea
who's responsible.
No ma'am.
Launch a full
investigation, tout suite.
The Carbon Market can in no way
abide anomalies of this nature.
I will not have the Atlas
project compromised.
Of course. As you wish.
Madam, if I may.
This is, confessedly,
little more than
an educated guess
on my part,
but I believe Metal Age
to be our likeliest culprit.
Yes, go on.
They may pose as a
mere guerilla movement,
but their leader's
heir apparent, Digma Two,
does possess a natural
mastery of the Carbon Market.
There's my girl.
Guilty as charged.
Don't tell me you're
hiding from yours truly.
Honey, I know that crooked
lil' mind better than you.
This place has been
your tree house since
you were knee-high
to a farthingale.
It's where you flock
to settle your feathers.
Speaking of which, your
grandmother's have been ruffled.
Ugh! I just wish
she'd give up on the whole
"one day this will all
be yours" song and dance!
I mean, I've been locked up
for two freakin' years already!
I hate how the pre-quake
geners always play for keeps.
It's her song and dance.
The wind oughtta blow
where it damn-well pleases.
The ol' girl's a battle axe;
I'm sure she can cope.
All I want for you, sweet pea,
is whatever makes you happiest.
If you just want to be
a normal teenage girl,
then knock yourself out.
Seriously, Takehiko?
They're gonna
catch Hell for that.
We better go shut 'em down.
Taking toys from
naughty boys is my forte.
Burn baby, burn!
Today's a day to celebrate!
Show those EM satellites
how much we give a damn!
What are you doing?! You're
gonna make the market spike!
You've been outta touch with the
market for a while, jailbird.
Nothing we're doing here is
gonna bump the "precious index"
up more than point-fifteen
percent. I did the math myself.
Uh, sir.
The carbon index just jumped
by point-thirty-eight percent.
You lug-head!
We throw the market
outta kilter we're gonna get
a Hell of a lot
more than a fine!
Do ya wanna bring
the Carbon Police in?!
Oh, but he did the math.
Takehiko! We got company!
But how?! It's been,
like, what? A minute?!
Kuniko!
What have we got?
Have a look!
That's not the Carbon Police!
What the? The ARMY?!
Suit up! It's the
freakin' slags!
Get to the marketplace, now!
We owed them a warning!
At least a warning shot.
I believe the
rules of engagement
are very clear
on that point, sir.
Lieutenant Kusanagi, don't
forget the pecking order.
In no way is the
Atlas Corporation
beholden to military protocol.
Nor does it have
qualms with demoting you.
So you keep saying.
If these guys have your pluck,
it ought to be a very
interesting skirmish.
Doubt they have as fancy
an heirloom, though.
Get ready!
Protect the square, guys!
Don't let the
bastards get near it!
Typical slag
mindset at work here.
We let out a little
smoke so they come in
and bulldoze an entire block.
Kuniko! Your grandma
wants you to have this.
Not now okay?!
This emblem is your birthright!
You take it. I'm not interested!
Hey--!
Now what?
You slags got no
right to be here!
Why don't you go back
to lapping up the stink
of your corporate overlords?!
Get lost! Oh, big man?!
You don't get to call yourselves
soldiers in my neighborhood
if you pull this kind of crap!
A girl?
Hello, Digma Two. Thorny
little rosebush, aren't we?
Are you the leader of Metal Age?
Uh well,
technically speaking, no.
And yet you make a big
show of cat-calling us?!
Look, it's kind of a
complicated issue, okay?
I'm really not even part
of Metal Age. Except, I...
Whatever, the point is you can't
treat innocent people like this!
Well these so
called "innocent people"
have been turning a
blind eye to terrorism.
We're terrorists for belching
out a tiny bit of smoke?!
That's not what
I'm talking about!
Then what's the problem?
Way to play fair!
No one opens fire on my girl!
Now!
Oh, hon. Your body
would make much shorter
of the shocks if your
movements weren't so erratic.
But...
Don't argue; focus.
And for the love of Dinah,
don't be caught in the
trenches without your lipstick.
There. Now you're
dressed to kill.
You wanna grab some coffee?
No!
I'm a sucker for
a man in uniform.
Hiya, boys!
You jerks!
Ow! Gah!!!
Stand down before you make
things worse for everybody!
Shut up!!!
What in the--?
Huh?
Milady.
Wherefore this strange music?
I swear I've heard that before.
The old forests shed
noxious, lethal tears.
And every so often, bitter
conflict yields kindred spirits.
Next time: "The Poison
Swamp of Ikebukuro."