It's her song and dance.
The wind ought to blow
where it damn-well pleases.
The ol' girl's a battle axe.
I'm sure she can cope.
All I want for you, sweet pea,
is whatever makes you happiest.
If you just want to
be a normal teenage girl,
then knock yourself out.
Are you the leader of Metal Age?
Uh, well.
Technically speaking, no.
And yet you make a
big show of cat-calling us!
Look, it's kind of a
complicated issue, okay?
'm not part of
Metal Age. Except, I--
Stand there and tell
me with a straight face
terrorists have helped.
You kill trees. Steal property.
Burn whatever you feel like.
Look, I'm... I'm not--
Naw, I get ya.
Things are rough all over.
Don't go thinkin' this has
anything to do
with Metal Age, either.
'course not. Look at you.
You're a perfectly
normal teenage girl, right?
I've been thinking
a lot about power.
Like, what I might have
the power actually to change.
I've seen a lot of craziness.
And the more I see, the less
I feel able to do anything.
The less I feel like
we have a real shot.
Listen, this isn't about
revenge.
For what they did to
Momoko or my friends in juvie.
I want to make
sure you know that.
My mind was made up
before any of that happened.
It's just. I wasn't
sure I was right.
I mean, you know, for this.
Now I know. I will
be Metal Age's leader.
From behind the trees and
the voracious green tendrils
that strangle
our homes, we fight.
Against those who'd turn
a blind eye on their neighbors
in the midst of
suffering, we fight.
We squandered
too much time asking.
We must demand change!
The place we once called home
is nothing but a
crumbling mass of ruins.
A toxic waste dump.
We have been patient,
we have been pure,
and our reward is
a boot to the face.
We are treated like beggars.
We stand, huddled at the gates
of paradise, hands outstretched,
and those with the
power to ease our lot,
refuse us even their scraps.
If they cannot deign to honor
our humanity and our right
to live in peace,
we will pry our due from them
by any and all means necessary.
We will take what we are owed.
We will take Atlas.
Today we will
fight for our future.
What's at stake here is nothing
less than our very survival.
Today we go to war.
Hey, easy. Just because those
things ain't armed right now,
doesn't mean you can go an'toss
'em around like potato sacks.
Who knew? Beneath that fuzz and
muscle you're a nervous Nelly.
Can it, squirt! Wanna
know some words to live by?
"Keep your cool
and keep your head."
You know I love "head".
How about I give you a
bullet in the ass, ya queen?
Oh yeah. I knew you
liked the rough stuff.
You're having entirely
too much fun out here!
Thought you'd come!
Miss President.
Uh, yes, ma'am?!
Whatever you may
discover on your mission,
you must face it
without trepidation.
I'm gonna take back our future.
So no one has to be afraid!
Yeah!
Shhh! Shhh! Shhh!
There, there.
Aw, don't cry.
We didn't mean to wake you.
I'll make sure you
have a home. I promise!
Ya know why the
chief advisor would come
all the way to
Japan so suddenly?
I'm completely in the dark.
The whole operation's been
outta whack since the
president became prime minister.
I--I do hope your journey here
was a pleasant one Mr. Tarsian.
I apologize for
our unpreparedness but
due to the sudden nature of--
I never knew the
Americans used to have
a military base way out here.
Well, what you don't
know could fill a book, huh?
Driver. Address our
leader as Miss President!
Shut up.
You're about as much of
a Metal Age member
as you are a chick.
Hey now. The reason
I came was to keep an eye
on my sweet daddy bear, and he
just bites my head right off.
Yeah, well. You better
hope I'm in this good of a mood
when I got some
live ammo in the chamber.
What?!
Hey look! We're here, guys!
I assume you're K.D.? My name is
Kuniko Hojo. Head of Metal Age.
Pleased to meet you.
Oh-kay. I'm guessing KD
stands for something, eh?
Those weird old bastards
briefed me on everything,
so let's get on
with it. Follow me please.
He's no contender
for Miss Congeniality.
Go on, Miss President.
Uh. Yeah, right.
Whoa! Huge boomerang!
Nice!
She may look like a relic,
but the ol' girl's
tough as they come.
NCT-processed reinforced
aluminum from stem to stern.
Not only that,
she's modded for stealth.
If they do spot us,
the custom-built Union
power plant engines'll
have us outta
harm's way in a blink.
She'll give those
Air Force Shinshin jets
a run for their money for sure.
Wow.
And you're gonna
be our pilot, right?
Sure you feel comfortable
trusting your lives
to man whose name
you don't know, little missy?
What is your deal?
My life is in your
hands, sir. Not only mine,
but the lives of countless
others whose survival depends
on the success
of our mission today.
Well that's a real
honorable little spiel
ya got workin' there.
Sure do hope you
don't expect me to give
more than two
shits about all that.
Huh?
But I'll guarantee you this.
You pay me to do a job and I
am gonna damn-well do it right.
That's really all I care about.
We've had enough!
We demand an end to
the inhumane
treatment inflicted on us
by the ATLAS
corporation starting today!
What? Stand down immediately!
Don't you realize
if you do this,
you'll never get
to live in Atlas?!
Try living in the slums
and tell me how you like it!
You idiots! What
you're doing is treason!
Oh, you ain't
seen nothin' yet pal!
It's time! Now!
Yeah!
What the hell's
gotten into them?
We're not equipped
to handle this alone!
Where is our backup?!
Phase one underway! Our forces
have engaged the enemy
in the Level One
Construction Zones
and also in the first
sector of Megashaft number nine.
So far according to plan.
Any military involvement?
No ground troops have
been deployed as of yet.
They seem to be
exercising restraint.
Nagiko thinks the
earlier problem with their
naval fleet may be
slowing them down a bit.
Very good. Just keep me posted.
Now all we gotta do is
cut off the head of the beast.
We got some company.
They're making easy work
of our defenses, it would seem.
The command is placing blame
on compromised radar sites,
but this ship does
appear to have been equipped
with fairly advanced
stealth capabilities.
There are many
cash-strapped nations willing
to part with military
technology for the right price.
You can never trust
those who're in need.
I say... Let's give
the Air Force commander
some proper motivation.
As you wish, Madam.
Flight Control to Crete One.
You are to treat any
illegal invasion of Atlas
airspace as a terrorist act.
If you encounter
the unknown aircraft,
you are authorized to use
deadly force at your discretion.
Roger. Flight control, out.
So if this goes south
they can make me the scapegoat.
Someone's locked on me!
Crete one! This is Crete two.
The unknown has
a lock on us, too.
They're messin'
with the wrong guys.
Unknown opening weapons
bays! Take evasive action!
What are you doing!
Are you trying to kill my men?
If they can't keep their asses
in the plane they'll have a hell
of a time on the
drop from thirteen.
That's a little
different ya know!
Listen kid. In order
to carry your crew
I got no weapons but
machine guns on this thing.
If I don't make a few bluffs
we're sittin' ducks up here.
They've always been
a gutless bunch of morons,
but they do have
some serious firepower.
Think you can outmaneuver them?
I got a feeling they're just
about to make their big move.
Hold on!
Damnit!
It would appear that we have
quite an experienced
pilot on our hands.
Our fighters will need
to be far more aggressive
if they're to take him down.
The Air Force
commander is livid.
Perhaps his missiles can
accomplish what
his airmen cannot.
No. That won't do.
A lovely red would
suit you much better.
A deep, sanguine crimson.
A little war, huh?
I smell more money.
Alright Medusa, looks like
you and I have another chance
to grab some rainy day cash.
I swear, did those idiots forget
that we sunk their battleship
the last go round? Oh well.
Oh crap!
Put a sock in it!
Those damn fools! Firing away
without a care in the world!
Hey! I got em!
What!
Alright!
You want war?
I'll give ya war!
What the hell was that?!
No! That's insane!
She's giving us quite
an entertaining show.
I now assume all duties
as commander in chief.
My first order is to
strip the Air Force commander
of his rank immediately.
Then arrest him for
endangering our citizens.
Yes, ma'am.
Soichiro, relay
this message for me.
"At this time Zeus will assume
control of all defense systems."
"Armed Forces Joint
Headquarters will reside
in a Special Executive Office
of the prime minister
until further notice."
Yes, of course.
Reon, kindly see
our visitors receive
the proper greeting they're
owed. Something very special.
Yes ma'am. I believe I have
just the thing in
mind for this occasion.
Ahhh! What a lively play
this is! Such sounds and colors!
Have you a decent bone
in your body? Hush your mouth.
Why, Miiko?
It is true tragedy.
Dying is not something
others do to entertain us.
What purpose then?
Before you now
is hope for survival.
Self-sacrifice for
the lives of others.
Self-sacrifice?
Indeed. It's what Sayoko and
I do for you, precious child.
Our needs are
secondary to yours.
Then our eyes are
witness to a joyous occasion!
Suppose you were to turn to me
and register naught
but empty space.
The warmth at
your back turn cold?
Miiko! Thou must not!
Without thy warmth!
We would surely wither away.
Please do not believe
for a moment that ours are
the only lives with
value in this world, dear.
Each one snuffed out
leaves another in darkness.
We pray thee.
Grant thy forgiveness.
Benight our naive words!
What the hell? What are
those? Friendlies?
Crete two's down!
There's no way in
hell you're gonna be able
to pull a cowboy
move like that!
There's no other way!
I never saw a machine
move like these things.
You're way outta your
league here, little girl!
No matter how tough
this gets I'll never give up
on the mission
I came here to do!
My people are counting on me,
and I won't let them down!
She's a stubborn
little firecracker.
I just hope you live
through this crazy stunt.
If I do, I'll live
without any regrets!
Then so be it. Your way, then.
Those Air Force slags may
have been gutless bastards,
but now we got an enemy
on our hands that doesn't
give a damn
about their own allies.
Thank you, sir. I have
all the faith in the world
you can pull us through, K.D.
It's Konoe.
Huh?
Konoe Daichi. That's my name.
Then I'm very pleased
to meet you Mr. Daichi.
You'd better believe
this is gonna cost you extra!
I'm trusting you
with our lives, Konoe.
I owe you one! Hurry up!
Uh. So now what?
You think we can
call our techie? Kuniko!
I've spent my whole life
running from little balls.
What are you talking about?
It appears the
artillery fire originated from
a location somewhere in the
Ota region. Near the Tama River.
Something is rotten here.
It's conjecture at this
point, but I believe there is
a connection to
the previous barrage
our forces
took from Ikebukuro.
Something is definitely rotten.
Seriously? You want
me to leave them out there?
She's not the type you need
to worry about. They'll be fine.
Must be nice to have faith
in your leaders like that.
Well, alright then! This is
about to get interesting!
Looks like we're in
good hands with ol' K.D.
Now let's do our part!
You know, I've always been
a sucker for those flyboys.
Is everybody out?
I've lost sight of our bogey!
No. That's impossible.
This will be our test mission.
These mimetic
drones haven't been
utilized in actual combat yet,
but I think we'll be pleasantly
surprised with the results.
Should prove
intriguing to say the least.
Deploy!
I'm last outta the can,
so you're clear to fall
back to a safer location!
Loud and clear!
Now get the hell out!
Damnit. My ass is grass.
Hey!
Over here!
You got it man!
President!
I won't let you
bastards kill my men!
She's a firecracker till
the end! Sayonara. And godspeed.
What's he doing! No.
Konoe, don't. Don't do it!
Konoe. No!
You may break our bodies...
But you'll never
break our spirits!
Oh crap!
I can't take my eyes
off you for a minute, can I?
Now why would you wanna do that?
Konoe!
What a relief.
Wait. What the--?
Wasn't there a huge hole
in that thing a second ago?
The city, rich in mystery,
a volley of faces
for those who dare look.
Separating truth from
fiction is no easy task.
But the core of Atlas, though
fantastic, is all too real.
Next time: "Transfigured City"