We have to act quickly.
Time is against us.
The child will be born soon.
Atlas must be
completed before then.
That dream bothering you again?
Kinda. It's just
weird I keep having it.
Been a while, too.
That voice I hear just creeps
me out. And it's all so random.
Probably just a
memory of something
you overheard in the womb.
Your birth mother lives
in Atlas, after all.
Yeah. Guess that could be why.
Did I just hear you say that?!
Grandma, what in the Hell?!
All done. Try not to slosh them.
'kay, not really pertinent!
You just dropped a bombshell
on me out of the blue!
I mean, I think you just did!
Calm down. All good things,
m'dear. Be patient.
Kuniko.
You coming with or aren't ya?
Everybody and
their dog's waiting.
Look, just give me
a second; I'm kinda--
See she doesn't drop these, eh?
Grandma!
Oh wow. It's so cool
of you to make noms.
Hey, we're not done!
Yeah. I'm sure it can wait.
Ugh! Well at least
let me get my shoes on!
Just go barefoot;
no one cares.
Okay, we gotta be quick.
You sure our intel's reliable?
Furukawa said as good as gold.
Get ready.
Right, let's do it!
Sir, yes sir!
All this fuss just for lil'
ol' me??!
And here. Also with
her compliments.
Oh, dear. Oh dear!
This is the last time I'll ever
eat Nagiko's pickled herring!
Come on. You're gonna
pickle your face
if you keep with
the waterworks, hon.
Miiko, love,
you are a catastrophe.
Now where on Earth is Momoko?
Now that you mention it,
I haven't seen her all day.
Tak is MIA, too. The Hell,
it's not like they can
put off saying
goodbye till it's convenient.
It's fine.
Huh?
Well, can you blame them
for not wanting to watch
a grown woman cry her eyes out?
Besides, I'm an absconder!
Come on.
Don't talk like that.
Everybody's thrilled for you.
S'yeah they are! I mean,
look at where you get to live!
So. You gonna become
a model citizen or what?
Uh. Well, not exactly.
I'm going on a
food binge first thing.
Some fatty Mediterranean.
Then French, then Italian.
Why am I not surprised?
Ah, but wait! Once my lil'
reward bender is wrapped up,
I'm reviving Tropical Fish!
That sounds familiar.
Is that the drag club
you and Momoko used to run?
Drag club?! Uh, please.
We put on the finest burlesque
revue Roppongi had ever seen!
Full to bursting every
night, if you can imagine.
Ah, and the two
of us back then!
The hottest ticket
in town, bar none!
You watch!
I'll sashay through those
gates and take Atlas by storm!
Just don't
think you're going
to skimp me on
the profits, Mama Rose.
Yes, I'm late,
but I look fabulous.
Sweet Ellie May!
You held on to our sign.
You bet your ass. I break
hearts, my dear, not promises.
God. How many
years has it been?
Our sacred pact.
See girls. We swore we'd
make it to Atlas one day,
and reopen the club.
Wait, you're not
actually giving me that?!
But I-I can't do it alone!
Sure you can.
I swear, you
hear me? I promise you.
Oh. Yes.
Tropical Fish will live!
Well, I guess this is it.
We'll miss you.
Do give us a shout
once you're settled in.
Done.
Oh, my. Farewell,
treasured comrades!
I'll think of you every day!
Bye-bye, Miiko!
Takehiko. You son of a bitch.
That jerk!
"Let not the hours pass but that
our thoughts align and our--"
Ta-Takehiko!
Kick some ass!
Yes. I-I'll do
my absolute best!
And you'd better believe
there'll be a VIP booth
with your name on it
when Tropical Fish reopens!
Ha! I knew you were a softie!
Enough screwin' around!
We're headin' back!
Man in need, right here!
If you have any
bread or flour...
One at a time, folks!
Keep it neat or you get diddly.
Show of hands who
wants Atlas baked ham!
Here you go. Heads up!
Easy now! Damn it, be civil!
Wow, they're goin nuts.
Stop! As far
as we're concerned,
Metal Age can take its
ill-gotten goods elsewhere!
What the Hell, man?!
Knock off the act! You guys
are bad news for all of us!
You brought down
the army on our homes!
I don't have a roof
anymore thanks to you jerks!
Hey, if the slags are trigger
happy, it's not our fault, dude!
That attack was
completely unprovoked!
Ya steal from the government,
ya expect 'em to bring
you a bouquet of roses?!
You're all a bunch of thieves!
Yeah? Who do you think
brings us medical supplies
when we need 'em, asshole?
You want a piece of me?
For your information, some
of us actually work for Atlas
and get paid a damn
good wage for the trouble!
That's all well and good
if you're able to work!
What do you expect
the elderly to do?
We're supposed to be
helpin' each other out!
What do you think
Metal Age is all about?!
Great, and when we
accept their help,
the whole damn town gets
branded as a terrorist front!
No kidding!
What good will it be if we all
get denied access to Atlas?
Hey, I know her.
Tragic. Poor woman
just hasn't been the same
since she lost her
newborn child last year.
Really.
Little thing wasn't
really even all that sick.
But our hospitals have bupkis
in the way of medical supplies.
I say Metal Age needs to
clear the Hell out of Duomo!
Can it, everybody!
Honey, don't. Easy.
Listen to yourselves!
Ha! Little Miss "Heir
Apparent" gonna weigh in now?
By all means, princess, tell us
what you know about the issue.
Seriously? After all I've done.
We got a hail storm!
Everyone get inside!
Load 'er up!
All of you back in your homes!
Right! Get us out of here!
What good'll it be if we all
get denied access to Atlas?
Bye-bye, Kuni!
See ya!
Just hurry up and get
home 'fore you catch a cold.
I saved something for ya!
Thanks.
Your wife actually managed
to scare up some ham today.
Did she now?
Clever little minx.
Well, the Metal Age
boys helped a bit.
My hats off to 'em.
Oh sweetie, I know it hurts.
Just hang in there
for mommy, okay?
Little thing wasn't
even really all that sick.
I'd forgotten
what it was like here.
The entire time I was in Juvie,
I had a roof over my head
that didn't whiz
on you when it rained.
The plumbing was functional
and the infirmary good.
Three hot squares
a day, everyday--
'course they were awful.
Ugh! I can't get
my head around it!
Miiko's been gaga
about Atlas since forever,
and Takehiko's convinced
it's a Den of Liars.
Ah, well.
Tell me the truth, Momoko,
ya think we'd all
be happier living there,
or is it just
smoke and mirrors?
I don't know.
Is happiness a chocolate
bar whenever you want one?
Not when they go straight
to your thighs, dear.
Not bad.
Know what?
You gotta taste
life for yourself.
Till I get into Atlas
and have a look around,
I'm never gonna know
whether it's something
I'd choose for myself.
You are piece of work, m'love.
As willful now as
the day they made you.
That's it. I need
to see it for myself.
Infinite wealth
is such a burden.
A girl could spend half a life
deciding what to spend it on.
Help me. Help me. Help me.
Fantastic.
Why did I program you
to be such a
whiny little nuisance?
Thanks for the heads-up.
I thought we were gonna wait
and screw with
the Saudi index later!
After we got around to nailing
Russia's balls to the wall.
That's fifty million euros
you just cost the
rest of us, cheater!
What?! I did absolutely
nothing of the sort!
What in the--?!
Master Hiruko appears
to have sensed it as well.
So then, that means...
That the amulets
did in fact resonate, yes.
Did he give any indication
of what it might portend?
Not yet. Nor has our incessant
"star gazing" yielded anything.
Of course not. Though,
you did encounter the Sun
in the outlying marshes,
did you not? Imaki?
Huh? I didn't
collide with her myself.
But the young lieutenant
involved has made a full report.
Quite so. I read
his report myself.
Ah.
Brooding over Shion again?
Forgive my making
light of your troubles
but that faraway look,
it's rather an obvious tell
that your mind
lies somewhere else.
Now that look, I like.
One fake ID, made to order.
Rockin'. How'd you
manage to get a hold of this?
The old boys in
Akihabra owed us a favor.
It may not be real, but it's
as close as you damn well get.
Those pervs
make my flesh crawl.
Are you sure
we can trust them?
Well, seein' as they're the only
outfit that can turn these out,
I'd say we don't
have much of a choice.
Why do they make
your "flesh crawl?"
Oh, sweets.
Just count your lucky stars
you don't have to meet them.
Leave me in the dark.
Uh-uh. Not till you both agree
to have me along as backup.
I know it's
not a Metal Age gig,
but say no and
you can get your own.
Oh yay.
Guess we're stuck with him.
Huh. To think
I'd live to see the day
when Kuniko would
itch to infiltrate Atlas.
Like they say,
"Till you've seen it yourself,
what do you really know?"
So, looks like we're
taking the scenic route, huh?
Don't be a backseat driver.
You have got to be kidding me--
Hey! Keep it down!
Well that was pleasant.
Damn it, quit screwin' around!
This government has blindsided
its citizens time and again,
mollifying them
with empty promises
Are those Metal Age people?
Yeah. They're the Nerima branch.
Oh dear.
I hope Miiko is alright.
Thirty-two-A,
forty-seven nine one two.
The name is Miiko.
I'd like a
Roppongi-style apartment,
if you have any to spare.
Nothing fancy, just
somewhere I can keep a cat.
I have you as Tetsuo Kumagai.
If that's correct, proceed left
to Level Eleven. Thank you.
Wait, I'm sorry, what?
I think there's been a mistake.
I need to enquire about
a proprietor's license.
Next in line please.
Move!
No, wait! I don't
think you understand--
Welcome to the Moon Palace.
Now, if you'll
kindly step forward
and check your belongings with
the attendants you see here.
That done, please form a
single-file line in front of me.
Hello there, girls.
How we doin'?
Now, I have some really
special stuff in here,
so I'd appreciate
you being extra careful.
Oh. That doesn't
look very, uh--
What are you doing?!
Oh my god!
Outta my way!
Nobody's gonna
make a liar outta me!!!
That all you got?!
The final candidate, milady.
Wh-Where am I?
The Hell are you?!
Bring forth that we may drink,
'tis time for our medicine.
Make haste!
I-- Uh, okay?
This here, you mean?
I can't believe we're
actually doing this.
I'll bet the men
here are top drawer.
Cool your jets, queenie.
Okay. Moment of
truth here, baby.
Oh no!
Hey! What the hell
you trying to pull?!
Um. I. Uh.
Oh crap.
Kuniko! Just run!
Damn it!
Hold it right--
Come on! Move!
So much for favors!
Anyone else feel like
a quick round of roulette?
You're kiddin' me!
Their response time.
This way! Hurry!
Slow down!
I don't like fast men!
Hey! Caboose here!
Intruders?
Spare me your excuses.
Construction continues,
regardless.
Shoot them.
Of course it's protocol!
Precisely. Clear away
the debris and get on with it.
Oh Hell. Don't shut
it down on us.
We're stuck in here with
a tranny for cryin' out loud.
Smooth move.
Take pot shots at the gal
who's an inch from your face.
Oh it's fine, hon.
Just his way of flirting.
Ugh. Let's take this ladder
here, just follow my lead.
So we're dancing now?
Men.
Lay off it!
Atta girl.
Run for it!
Oh crap.
Hurry up!
Wait!
Is that Duomo?
Wow. It's so... So tiny.
What's wrong with you?!
Get it in gear!
Come on!
You're gonna get us
all killed! Snap out of it!
Guys, did you see that?
All those buildings,
were houses, weren't they?
And there were
roads going everywhere.
I don't understand.
That place is gigantic!
It just doesn't make sense!
Kuniko.
I'm outta ammo. So we prolly got
about another minute to live.
Don't give up! There's
some way outta this hellhole!
Look there!
You're insane!
And now we
have an earthquake?!
It's Atlas's
Mechanical Resonance!
I'm so terribly sorry, madam!
We have to move faster.
Move it or lose it!
I'm not a goddamn acrobat!
Wait, hold on. What in
the hell are they planning
to do with all
that space down there?
Oh for the love of Ella--
We can find out later!
Hold on tight!
Crap! Geronimo!
Grab on to the other end. I
need you to be a counterweight!
Yeah, I figured! Stop yelling!
Oh god!
It's the only way to fly!
You don't have nestle so close.
No one's touchin' you
on purpose, believe me!
It's huge. You saw it!
We could all live here!
There's room! Why don't
they let us all be citizens?!
I don't understand! Why?
Hey, Momo! Check out
this cool stuff!
Whoa, is that a
vacuum tube?! That's crazy!
It's like a fossilized miracle
from the dawn of
the information age!
How awesome is that?!
Next time: "Uber-Akihabara"