Bomb Tokyo. It's the only way.
Huh? Are you serious
or just jerkin' my chain?
It's the only way outta this.
Those things are choking
the city to death right now.
If we don't wipe
'em out, they're gonna do
the same thing
to the entire country.
Whoa. You are serious,
but it's crazy.
No deal.
Why?
I'm guessing you're
not good with numbers,
or you probably would've
realized to pull it off
you'd need pockets deep
as most national treasuries.
Say what?
Unless you want
those things eating up
your little kingdom here,
you'd better get out
that pocketbook and
start makin' it rain.
Listen, in case you haven't
noticed, I run a business,
not a bank, and
definitely not a charity.
Well...
I suppose...
You could rent it.
If you can't afford to buy.
Rent an air force?
Yeah. With the
global economy on the skids
like it is these days,
countries'd do
anything for a buck.
But can you actually do that?
Money's always talked.
But right now it's way
louder than it's ever been.
Normally, I never
play the role of
a third party broker,
but these are strange times.
And if I do this,
it's on my terms.
The date and precise
time of your little bombing raid
will have to be
given to me in advance.
Yeah, of course.
No problem at all.
What's more. I need that.
Throw in the dagger
and we have ourselves a deal.
This thing? But why?
I've always had an
eye for stuff of value,
and that knife in
particular is calling my name.
As far as this
deal's concerned...
If you let me
have the pig-sticker,
I'll cover the cost for
one of the bombers in return.
It's all yours.
Superb!
You sure about that?
It's just an item.
The lives we'll save are worth
a lot more than
anything I've got.
I know. But Nagiko
gave it to you.
It's mine, but it's not a part
of me. I'm the same without it.
It's like an accessory, right?
I trust that you
can get this done?
I can. And I'll contact
you when it's all ready.
Wait!
What?
That earring you've got.
What about it?
Let me guess? Is it
"calling your name" too?
Oh that thing?
No, not my style.
No? Well.
Move your buns, hon.
It's alright sugar britches.
Miss Momo, can take all
night getting what she wants.
Chop chop, hon.
Afternoon my mistress.
Welcome home!
Tack-ky.
Not my idea, trust me.
Hark! Karin? Dost
thou bring visitors?
It's her. From that night!
You sadist!
Tranny!
Truly? These are more "trannies"
whose acquaintance we make?
No, I was born a girl!
What is your business here?
We should be asking you
that! There's a lot of freaks
in this part of town, but no
one wants what you're selling!
Hey, that little girl,
who is she?
Miss Mikuni.
She's like, uh, like,
let's just say
an Atlas super VIP.
Seriously? Oh-kay.
Karin! Why have you
sullied my lady's chamber
with this human garbage?
You're one to talk,
lady. Of course.
This woman has an item
that I thought would be
of interest to Miss Mikuni.
Then bring it hence.
The match!
No milady!
Behold! These would seem
to be two of a perfect pair.
Yeah, they are. That's crazy.
This earring is the one memento
we have to remember our mother.
Whoa! That was your mother's?
Hmmm. Hardly cause for torture.
Explain this! Wherefore
does one of thy humble station
come to possess our
dear mother's keepsake?
Hold on a second!
If that belonged to her mom,
could you be... her dad?!
Oh, come on! Even if I may
have had the proper tools
at one time,
I never used them for that!
Shocking, but women
aren't my thing.
I know, but--
To be perfectly honest, Nagiko's
the one who gave it to me.
So it was Grandma's?
Yeah. She didn't tell me much.
But she did mention that it was
something that used
to belong to your mother.
No way. If that's true,
then I guess this
girl and I are sisters.
You suggest garbage like you
and Lady Mikuni
could be related?
It's simply unacceptable!
Could'st thou be our sister?
Come on, Momoko. Clue me in.
I'm just as lost.
"Momoko". "Tranny".
Thou be'est by chance
the proprietress of what was
known as the Tropical Fish?
Huh?
I was.
Ahh! We were certain
it was thee before us!
But how? How do
you know who I am?
By Miiko's many tales of thee.
Oh my god, you know Miiko?
Miiko is one we hold
most dear in our heart.
Wait! Is Miiko
actually with you? Here?
What was that?
Tis Miiko.
Free me! Free me!
An eternity in hell awaits
those who would bind me here!
Boss! You gotta
help us out here!
Boss! This thing won't stop!
I can't take it anymore!
I swear, it's driving
me outta my mind!
So you wanna go back to begging
for handouts in
the streets, is that it?
Just shut up and
do what I pay ya for!
Who is that?
That was your friend Miiko.
What?!
She was overtaken
by the spirit of Hiruko.
Wait "overtaken"?
The hell's that mean?
Call it "possession"
if you like.
See for yourself, and perhaps
you could explain it better.
Free! Me!
Miiko. Prithee, calm thyself.
We are here. Thy dear poppet.
We bring Momoko with
us to bid thee well, Miiko.
Behold! 'Tis truly Momoko,
thy boon companion.
Prithee Momoko.
Come hither. Make haste!
Okay.
Mo. Momoko.
Momo. Momo. Momo.
Momo. Momo.
Momo. Momo-ko.
My dearest friend.
Miiko.
I mean, it's just
not possible.
It has to be some
kinda joke, right?
God I hope so.
It's too disturbing.
There's no way I'm buying
that girl and I are sisters.
And that horrible
creature just cannot be Miiko.
What the--?
Looks like it came from Duomo!
What in the hell
is going on here?
Hey! Kuniko!
What happened?!
It's those plants.
There are so many of 'em!
Is that all of them?
God, I hope so.
President!
Is that...
Yeah, there was way more.
We were sure we'd
got all of 'em last time.
But it's like tons more
just cropped up overnight.
They keep firing
those seeds everywhere.
No one's hurt? You're okay?
Yeah. No one got
seriously hurt or anything.
That's good.
We cut down every single one
of those things we could find.
But they're all over
town so we should probably
keep looking just
to be on the safe side.
Yeah, you're right. Thank you.
It looks like you've been
working your
tail off around here.
Aw, well... How did
your thing go today?
The bombing plan
got started at least.
I see.
We don't have any
time to waste, though.
As you can see, the Daedalus
infestation on Level Eight has
exceeded our
original projections
at an alarming speed.
At this point,
there is mounting concern
that it will spread
to the other levels.
Shion. That thing on your face.
It's revolting.
I can't look at you.
Please, forgive me.
Such a persistent little weed.
Pray, Sayoko.
Yes ma'am? What vexes thee?
Our visitors had
used the word sister,
but we do not fully
comprehend its meaning.
Prithee, tell us
indeed what the girl Kuniko
meant by that word.
I surmise.
It may have some
meaning that could correlate
its occurrence to the
mentioning of our mother.
That is a rather shrewd
deduction you have made milady.
The term "sister" is used to
describe the bond with a girl
that is born to the
same mother as one's self.
Sayoko. Dost thou
think it possible this
Kuniko could be born
of our mother as well?
I have a difficult time
believing that a street urchin
such as that could share
the same mother as one
so exalted as you.
Indeed. But how
then did she come
to possess our
mother's earring?
That remains a mystery.
We cannot say for
certain it was truly hers.
If it be so perhaps she
knows something of our mother.
Miss Mikuni. The one thing
of which I am most certain
is your destiny at the highest
level of Atlas, your birthright.
Other matters cannot distract
us from the path of ascension.
"Bombing Tokyo?
The girl has a crazy way
of dealing with her
problems, doesn't she?"
Just think about it.
It's gonna blow Japan's
carbon index sky high.
And if we get tipped off to
when the raid is gonna happen,
we could make a killing off
trading at just the right time.
"Absolutely right. Karin
you are a Grade-A genius!"
Tell me all about that blade!
"Exactly the same in form
and composition to Mikuni's."
But according to this report,
it's not some kind of replica,
it's more like they're
two parts of a matching set,
of three I bet.
Which means there's one more.
Now you do realize to pull
this off we're gonna have to
figure out where
the evacuees will go.
Underground?
I'm sure there are gonna be
way too many people
for that to work.
You're right.
Should you be here?
Say what?
With us. Ya know, here?
I mean this is the Metal Age
command center after all.
I thought we were
all in this together
to try and save people's lives.
You're right. And I know
just the place. Right here.
In Atlas?! That's nuts.
No way.
Sorry, but the government'll
never go along with it.
Alright, so you tell me
where we can take these people!
Well, well,
what do we have here?
Nagiko!
Looks to me like everybody's
burning the midnight oil.
I brought some snacks!
So... Momoko's earring.
Is it true that it
belonged to my mother?
That's her story at least.
I'm glad to see you've
been stirring it like I asked.
That's not why you came back.
I can't help but marvel at
the ingenuity of our ancestors.
They had rice bran
and they had vegetables.
And they managed to
make them work together
to create something
new and amazing.
Something that we, especially
you, still cherish today.
Hello, I did banish you.
Would you like to know a secret?
A couple of old nails
will help the eggplant
retain that beautiful color.
You'd probably be
inclined to just throw
the rusty old things away,
but they're still handy.
Grandma!
You're bombing Tokyo, yes?
How'd you know?
Those "Neo Guild" fools.
Raising a clamor over
trying to buy troops.
But if you want to find
a solution to your problem
it won't be done with
gun-wielding mercenaries.
You do have a person who once
held some
influence in your corner.
Not every woman can claim
to be the mother of Atlas.
But I'm not sure
that I can trust you.
You don't have to trust me.
I'm a tool at your disposal.
Just put me to use.
Like these rusty old nails here.
It's just business, really.
You get what you want from me,
and I get what I want
from you. No harm, no ill will.
Nothing more than that.
So why don't you lay
out what you want from me?
Access to the
top level of Atlas.
Now, the woman at the
head of that organization
has very little in the
way of redeeming qualities.
And, if I requested to
meet with her personally,
she'd no doubt refuse
without much consideration.
But if I were to have you at
my side, things would change.
Yeah. Why would I
make such a difference to her?
Because you just would.
She'd find it intriguing.
Come now child.
Don't ignore the fact
that you two have a history.
Or have you forgotten?
Hey, Furukawa,
where's the mimetic armor?
Thank you, sir.
I haven't seen this
thing in quite a while.
Caused me a lot of grief
when I came back without it.
Yeah, sorry.
Hey...
Yeah?
You're on board with all this?
I mean, Atlas is
where you grew up.
All of your family
and friends are there.
Are you sure you
can fight with us?
I'm not fighting, I'm helping.
Besides, I haven't
officially joined Metal Age.
So that should
make it okay, right?
This is for the
greater good. For all of us.
Okay.
Hey, love...
Courage got you here
but charm seals the deal.
Ms. Nagiko Hojo, we've
been expecting your arrival.
Madam Naruse awaits you.
Does she now?
The return of one
of the founders of Atlas.
And this is all you
can muster up, eh?
It's been quite
a while, Ms. Hojo.
Not long enough for you,
I'll bet. A peace offering.
I appreciate
the thoughtful gesture.
Do you? So what's happened
to the leadership here?
We've taken decisive steps
to ensure the future of Atlas.
Is that not the goal you had
in mind all those years ago?
Not like this it wasn't, no.
I see. I suppose you've come
to bring us enlightenment?
Tokyo has gotta burn.
Is that so?
There's no other way to erase
the harm you've done to it.
The monster you've created
has to be stopped right now!
If we don't do something, it'll
take over the whole country.
Monster, you say?
The Daedalus!
Ahh. Of course.
That was not
entirely our creation.
We simply made
some modifications.
I see. Life is just your toy?
No, we improve it.
The plant is the
pinnacle of resilience now.
We've already started
taking care of the logistics
of the bombing raid. Basically,
we're being kind enough
to clean up the mess you made
while you were
trying to play God.
So carpet-bombing a
city is "cleaning up?'
Do you realize the
amount of carbon you'll be
responsible for releasing
into the atmosphere?
My word. You can't offer
your guests a cup of tea?
It's all business
with you, eh? Have a snack.
Listen. We need you to
do your part for the people
out there and give
them a safe place to go.
Those unfortunates
are not my responsibility.
Atlas is my primary concern.
Its future is Japan's future.
Ultimately, the survival
of Atlas is paramount.
The collateral damage
from the outliers is a pity.
But we won't take refugees.
There's no room.
Ah, well. Not surprised.
Yeah, it's me.
They're not budging,
so it looks like
we're going with Plan B.
Roger.
What's that?
Madam Ryoko.
Yes?
The Daedalus on Level Eight.
They're all
ejecting their seeds.
They seem to be
mounting an attack on
the central shaft's
power terminal.
It's taking quite a bit of fire.
But why? There shouldn't
be any heat sources
in that area, it's uninhabited.
It's all logistics, my friend.
There's someone on our team
who is extremely familiar with
the way this place operates.
Atlas may be a fortress
against the outside,
but what about
an attack from within?
Cause, I bet it
wasn't in the plan.
You came here to threaten me?
Oh no. Of course not.
We're here to bargain.
Oh my, you're
quite the firebrand.
So... Do we have a deal?
Okay. I'll give you
what you're asking for.
The buildings will burn.
The work of human hands,
the dream of future happiness.
But the fire can
never erase the memories.
I wish there was another way.
But I'll go on with no regrets.
Next time: "Tokyo Airstrike"