Please stay strong.
Two-hundred kilometers an hour!
Two-eighty! Three-fifty!
Six-hundred!
And it ain't slowing down!
We've successfully
hacked into the elevator.
Those Atlas pantywaists would
never dream of going so fast!
These three
antiques actually did it.
Medusa.
Sorry in advance
if I barf on ya!
I wanna make it
to the top as much as
the next girl but
this is overkill!
Oh god. Are you
sure we're not dead?
I bet that put hair
on your chest at least.
I'd be happy to check.
I love you, Momoko.
Even at a time like this,
you've got a one-track mind.
Dammit! I'll draw
their fire from here!
Get up to Mikuni A-SAP!
Yeah got it!
Someone just earned himself
a pearl if we survive all this.
C'mon-- Go!
Wait, you're gonna
give him a gift?
That seems a little
bit formal for you!
Not exactly-- But he
might get a standing O.
I don't understand women--
Even if they're man-made!
No, Mikuni! Don't go up there!
You will not interfere
with milady's task!
I'm here 'cause o' Medusa--
It's running amok!
So?
Somebody's gotta stop it!
But without access to Zeus'
power, we haven't got a chance!
The power you so
covet isn't yours to wield!
It belongs to her!
So, the fake has returned.
Oh please. You're jealous.
Dear me. I don't
think whipping out your
withered old dust bags
is gonna help, love.
Unless you want us
to die of laughter,
keep your xylophone
ribcage to yourself.
Better a xylophone
than a pincushion!
Miiko.
Whate'er foul villain
hath cut short thy life,
they shall pay
a thousand-fold!
We swear, Miiko.
How they will suffer!
The world could end. Easily.
But then, what about,
Mommy and Daddy?
This is God's judgment. We might
as well throw in the towel.
Will Medusa destroy us?
What are you
talking about, Klaris?!
Mommy and Daddy...
would die!
America and Russia's
nuclear programs
have withstood Medusa so far.
But if either
one is compromised,
it's definitely
"game over" for all of us!
What if "game over"
is the will of God?!
This thing isn't about God.
What was that?
God's got nothing to do with it!
It's not some all-powerful
being-- It's just a program!
Nothing more than zeros
and ones we strung together!
Don't do this!
There's still time, Medusa!
In the old days, a school in
America maintained something
known as the Doomsday Clock.
What was it?
A sign of the times. As tensions
mounted during the Cold War,
they'd move the clock's
hands ever closer to midnight--
The point at which we should
expect nuclear apocalypse.
I think we'd be at 30
seconds to midnight about now.
Yet here you sit, just as
calm and collected as ever.
You're kidding, right?
Inside, I'm a moment away
from puking my guts out.
Zeus could end this.
I don't understand
why we haven't used it.
That's what I
told Madam Ryoko.
Use it to stop Medusa.
She refused.
She did?
To quote her word
for word she said,
"Just let it get up to
whatever trouble it feels like."
That's crazy.
She's willing to let
most of the Earth go
up in a mushroom cloud?
Well, she's not
losing any sleep over it.
All she cares about
is who inherits Atlas.
Speaking of that...
There's something I've
been meaning to ask you about.
What is wrong with you?!
This world's problems
do not concern me!
All that matters is
Lady Mikuni taking her
rightful place as heir!
Why so impatient,
huh? What's the rush?
The secret's out.
Shut up!
Up you go, hon.
Right!
No don't!
You're in such a hurry because
the girl is sick, isn't she?
Lady Mikuni is the
picture of good health!
Really? Her issues with
sunlight suggest otherwise.
No!
And what about that
lab where you had me tied up?
Were you not developing
new medicines in there?
A wonder cure for that girl?
Nothing's wrong
with Lady Mikuni!
Like nothing was wrong
with your own little girl?
She died, right?
How dare you speak of her?!
So tragic. I bet she had the
very same illness as Mikuni.
It's why you're
so desperate right now.
Shut up!
Look. The scalpel is
trembling in your hand.
Go to hell!
Mikuni!
If you want Atlas, fine by me!
But I gotta use
Zeus real quick, okay?!
If we don't stop
Medusa, like, yesterday,
the world as we know
it's gonna come to an end!
It will end? Verily?
Without Zeus? Totally!
Sayoko!
I warned you. I said not
to interfere. Please, go on!
No matter what happens,
you need to reach
the top of the staircase!
Just keep walking--
Don't look back!
Yes. We shall obey thee.
You're saying I did it?
The lower-ranking guards
couldn't have done it.
Meaning that just
leaves the four of us
at the top of the food chain.
Shion doesn't have
the requisite balls.
And Reon wouldn't do anything
to risk Madam Ryoko's anger.
Not with his younger
brother in her clutches.
You and I are all that's left.
The woman in the lab coat.
Why is she at
the staircase, I wonder?
You know why.
She's the Digma's attendant.
Don't patronize me.
We arrested her and had
her safely in our custody.
She couldn't have escaped.
Not without inside help. And
where was she being detained?
Oh, right-- Here.
Here in the midst of Atlas.
So, why did you keep
your suspicions to yourself?
Because I couldn't
fathom your motivations.
But now that Sayoko has made
her way into the Sacred Grove,
I thought it'd be best
to ask you directly. Why?
Soichiro.
Sayoko is my older sister.
Lady Mikuni...
Your older sister?
Ryoko asked me a
peculiar question one day.
If you'll excuse me.
Shogo.
Madam?
I wonder... Would you
like to sleep with Sayoko?
What?
I realize she's painfully drab
but she might be
quite an animal in bed.
First I thought it was
just her idea of a joke.
But her question stayed
with me for some reason.
Do you remember when Sayoko
tried to hack her way into Zeus?
I thought, "what sort of an
idiot would attempt something
that's so obviously
destined for failure?"
I decided to start digging.
That's when I found out...
We had different mothers,
but I was definitely
her younger brother.
Suddenly. I understood
why she had asked.
If I had said yes,
she would have made that
wretched act happen somehow.
She wanted me to
fuck my own sister!
Watching Sayoko taught me
the value of a hidden blade.
It isn't like the two of us
ever lived together as siblings.
I feel no filial devotion.
But saving her seemed like
the brotherly thing
to do. So I helped her out.
This is indeed a
momentous occasion.
Wouldn't you agree milady?
The moment when your dreams
of ascension will be made flesh.
Now, present the three relics.
"Earth shall be undone." Is it
true that this world is doomed,
should Zeus fail to intervene?!
The chattering of
a jungle-born simpleton.
Relinquish them to me.
Or, does avenging Miiko
no longer interest you?
Nay, it does.
These are the talisman.
There is no doubt.
These signify our divine
right as ruler of Atlas, yes?
Not entirely.
Explain yourself!
Sayoko!
She's collected
all of the blades!
How dare you refuse her this?!
You've no one
to blame but yourself.
What do you mean?!
If this child were Digma 2 or 3,
I'd have no qualms about
handing over control of Atlas.
But her? Suffice to say,
I have my doubts.
Based upon what?!
Why, the company she keeps.
You are a fugitive on the lam
from the Atlas Corporation.
Or had you forgotten?
This is a brazen act.
You accompany this child on her
coronation day and still expect
me to recognize her as the heir?
Because of me?!
She toys with
your sister. Even now.
So what'll you
do next, little brother?
Oh, I've done enough. Just
gonna tie up one loose end.
Lady Mikuni.
Abandon this
woman to her fate.
Do so, and I will
accept you as rightful heir.
But why?! It is cruel!
Should I take this to mean you
no longer wish to be the heir?
You turn your back on the
awesome power you would gain?
No, but your price
is far too dear.
Please, do it!
Milady, you sully your
smiles to grant me their warmth.
My life was a parade of disgrace
and shame. Up 'till you.
You depended on me.
Gave me a reason to
awaken with each new dawn.
You granted me
such sweet reprieve.
Ere I go, will you please grant
me one last selfish moment?
Why last?
Thy embrace is
so warm, Sayoko.
I cherish, every
moment we shared.
Sayoko! Sayokooo!
Unhand us, that we may join her!
I will do no such thing.
Sayoko gave her
life for your benefit.
That you may embrace
your fate as true heir!
We care not!
We want to be
with Sayoko! Come back!
Wherefore?! Cursed are
we to lose those we love?!
First Miiko, and now Sayoko!
Please don't leave us! Noooooo!
Lady Mikuni. Your first
new duty is at hand.
Performing the
sacred Ceremony of Guidance.
Hinder us not. We beg you.
We must become the heir
for Sayoko's sake and ours.
It must occur!
If you wanna be
the big boss, go for it.
Just gimmie a
sec with Zeus first.
Yeah. Easier said
than done, it would seem.
Elect, step forward and
affirm the verses afore me.
"Affirm the verses afore me?"
What's that even mean?
Speak up, ya dumb eyeball!
What the--?!
"O Sun, illuminate the
heavens and the earth alike.
O Moon. Climb the sky.
Dispel the o'er arcing darkness.
O Land, enthrall
the day and the night,
and hold thee
sway upon the world."
Verses affirmed.
Triple-A rating
command-string.
Hack into Medusa by
whatever means necessary
and abort all
pending nuclear strikes.
Triple-A rating
command-string!
Zeus ignores all petitions!
Unless the heir of
Atlas dost utter them!
That's gotta be a loada crap.
Karin told us she was
able to access Zeus just fine.
Speaking of, having any luck?
No. None! I can't
access anything now!
But why?!
I'm absolutely positive
the password
phrases are right!
No matter.
I don't take orders from
filthy little jungle-vermin.
Thanks for the update!
Which means Zeus won't
take orders from you, either.
No way! You can't be!
Indeed. The woman you see
standing before
you is the Zeus AI.
If you want to split hairs,
I'm not really Zeus in toto.
I suppose that
I am the interface
that enables it
to manifest its will.
I said the passwords.
What gives?
That might have meant something
back when Tarsian
first installed them.
But once I freed myself
from his meddling, they became
no more than sweet nothings.
Wait. You let Karin and
Medusa hack in, didn't you?
Oh, yes.
And then I bent
Medusa's will to my own.
Then you're the one who's
tryin' to wipe out mankind
with all those
nukes, aren't you?
That's right. I gave
the order to Medusa to
commandeer all the
world's military networks.
What the hell is your problem?!
Do you think you could
control the whole planet?
Why would I even want to?
What, is that your plan?!
It does have a certain appeal.
But the world is unwieldy.
I'm merely whittling it down
to a more manageable size.
You're "whittling
us down" to extinction!
Atlas will endure, and
that is all that matters.
With the sunlight above me,
and the ley lines below,
my nexus of power is complete.
I will live in glorious
triumph for all eternity!
Not gonna happen!
Guess again!
I had assumed you
would be rational in defeat
if no other time, but I seem
to have overestimated you.
You're as irrational
as any human being.
Is it true that none may command
thee, as thou heedest no one?
Not quite, there is
one person whose word
I will heed above all.
Who hast that power?
I am bound to obey
the heir of Atlas.
And thus, if we were
to take the reins of power,
could'st thou then put
Medusa's current task to ruin?
Yes. With Zeus's
power at your disposal,
Medusa would prove quite
an easy target to neutralize.
But if that were to happen your
quest for revenge would end.
Do nothing, and the world will
be destroyed as I intend it to.
Or you can bring your
wrath to bear upon the U.N.,
who murdered your dear Miiko.
Mikuni, listen to me!
Attacking the U.N. is
only gonna do one thing!
It'll start a war where
it's Japan versus literally
every other
country on the planet!
If you go in guns blazing,
the world's gonna bomb
itself back into the Stone Age!
Please don't do this!
If its doom is nigh,
then so be it.
What?
We shall inherit
this tower tall
and avenge our Miiko,
blood for blood!
Don't be such a
spoiled brat! You can't kill
billions of innocent people
just because you lost a friend!
And what have these
billions you would preserve
ever done for Mikuni?!
For you?
Thou knowest
nothing of our torment!
Ours is a heart
amidst the umbra.
A heart that must
needs shun the light of day.
All fear the unseen
cudgels we wield,
and so we wither
for want of love.
We starve! Thou has
never known such hunger!
Miiko and Sayoko
were all we had.
And now... Now, even
they hath been taken.
Miiko woudn't want
you avenging her death.
I mean she couldn't
hurt a fly. You know that.
Miiko once told us this.
That each life snuffed out
leaves another soul in darkness.
She said the death of anyone
is cause enough for tears.
Because she was a caring person.
And behold! Miiko is no more!
Her merciful nature hath
earned her naught but death!
For the sake of
dear Sayoko, who gave all
for our benefit,
we accept this inheritance!
For the sake of gentle
Miiko, we will grasp this
wicked world, and slay it!
Please, no.
Time for you to stand tall and
take your destiny firm in hand.
Shall we go? The
bejeweled spear awaits you
in the Sacred
Grove of Guidance.
Sorry to rain on your
end-of-the-world parade,
but I am not
gonna let that happen!
Not while you have a
visitor to keep you occupied.
Huh?
What in the hell
are you doing up here?
How'd you even get
in the room, anyway--?
I'm sorry.
But, why?
The seed of love endures
in a single-minded heart.
However, reality shakes
us from our slumber,
and the dream
called hope dissipates.
Next time: "Prelude to Collapse"