What in the hell're
you doing up here?
How'd you even get
in the room, anyway?
I'm sorry.
So Lady Mikuni.
Shall we make our way?
Hey! Hold on!
No you don't!
I'm sorry.
Is that all you
can say? "I'm sorry!"
What's wrong with you?!
Save the drama!
Momoko, you're here!
It's Haruko.
That's why he's doing this.
Bastards took his mother.
Oh my god. Is that true?!
That butch bitch.
Look, if this
is about that kiss.
Let me go on.
They're gonna hurt my mother
if I don't get up there.
My God.
Momoko, please.
I suppose I do
owe Haruko a favor.
But you hurt one little
pink hair on her head,
and all bets are off.
Sayoko!
Got a jumper!
Strange. You'd think a gal
this heavy'd have some tits.
So do you know
where she is now?
Ragged as she is,
she still ran off
looking for her pale
little charge. Ya know...
Loverboy feels the same.
So go easy on him.
I know.
Listen. If you shoot me,
will that save your mom?
It won't! You
know it won't!
I'm tryin' ta save
all of us, including her!
I am too. That's what
I've wanted to do all along.
I thought I was
doing the right thing.
That serving Atlas and Japan
was all for the greater good.
I know that!
Don't ya think that's what
I'm tryin' ta do right now?
Yeah. You're right.
Just like usual.
I'll do whatever ya need.
So cute. Like they
were made for each other.
Prithee, Lady Mikuni.
Take these sacred blades.
And sheathe them into
the slots you see before you.
Excellently done.
We're getting very close.
I simply cannot
abide this, Madam.
I ask you not continue
down this destructive path.
Shogo. There was a
time I valued your opinion,
but I fear you've gone soft.
It's no opinion.
It's a command!
Is that so?
And to think, all this time
I planned to let you
live after our little show.
Live ye shall.
We shall allow it.
You are to keep silent
while I am speaking!
Shion, darling.
Don't go! Shion!
I'm sorry, brother. Truly.
Wait!
You don't understand how I feel.
I'm not strong like you are.
No one calls on me for anything.
When Mom and Dad were getting
swallowed up by the jungle,
they were howling your name,
not mine! They didn't need me!
I have lived under your
shadow my whole damn life.
No one ever takes
notice of me. No one cares.
But Madam Ryoko. She's the only
person who makes me feel needed.
She counts on me
to do things for her.
She's the only
one who'll look at me!
Right you are, Shion.
I ask much of you.
And you comply so
willingly, so devotedly.
Because... You have no mind
of your own. It's disgusting.
Madam. Please don't.
No!
Brother!
After that speech
you still lie trembling
under your older
brother's strength.
Damn!
This is failure.
A feeling you'll get used to.
I suppose it has something
to do with your family's DNA.
That's... Godspeed.
Can you not even die properly?
I'm sorry.
Damnit kid! If you felt
like that you should've told me.
I didn't know.
But I do care about you!
You do?
Forgive me. This is more
difficult than I anticipated.
Where the hell is she?!
Let my mother go, you bastard!
No need to worry,
she's perfectly safe now.
Don't lie to me!
Maybe you should give
her a call and find out.
Like, now!
Mom?! Don't candy-coat
it, are you okay?
Where are you?
Wait, they're gone?
Where's your boss?
She escaped.
To where?
The Sacred Grove of Guidance.
Milady. You must not let that
vile woman stand by your side!
What reason have you? We seek
to become the rightful heir
to Atlas and she
hastens us to that end.
Is this not what
thou hast wished for us?
That is indeed my most
heartfelt wish for thee.
But this witch! Her
intentions are far from pure.
She will not obey you, milady!
One who intends to serve
does not dare silence
she who would be her mistress.
It's true.
The wishes of
this disgusting creature
do not interest
me in the slightest.
How dare you?!
Not the warmest way to
embrace an old college friend.
You were never my "friend"!
Oh no! And I certainly never
considered you to be my equal.
After all, I'm
practically a god on Earth!
I attended school to
ward away interminable boredom,
and you provided
the juiciest amusements!
So studiously pursuing
a life where you could
cast aside those
tattered clothes.
But all that knowledge never
helped improve your looks.
Shut up!
There was one who brought
some color to those cheeks, yes?
Please, stop.
A professor, whose name
escapes me at the moment.
Don't trample on
the image I have of him.
Are you serious?
You still cling to those
memories? At your age?
No!
Oh dear. What was
the word he used
to try to describe
you in bed, "pitiful"?
Shut the fuck up!
Damnit!
How the hell do
we make it stop?!
I think if we pull these
out, then. Well that did it.
Wasn't that one
already broken at the tip?
Is it still going?
Afraid so.
And you don't
know how to stop it?
Get back.
Hang on!
I swear, I hate when
guys blow without warning!
It didn't work. Now what?
I've got a secret that I've just
been dying to share with you.
This is the perfect time.
Your Midori's affliction.
The one shared by
our would-be heir.
There is a proven
cure for it, you know.
That's not true.
There is. A drug that I myself
developed over seven years ago.
You buried it?
Midori could have taken it,
she wouldn't have had to suffer.
She'd still be alive today!
But you buried her, and been
right miserable ever since.
You bitch!
See. Always so damn weak.
Listen! Release
Sayoko this instant!
I shall grant your wish.
No!
Sayoko!
Prepare yourself. We shall
soon descend upon Level Zero.
The land of the dead.
Atlas Level Zero.
Our largest and
most secret discovery.
The cavernous heart of Atlas.
Hidden within it,
an ancient shrine.
What we encountered
there changed everything.
The artifacts.
The remains of Himiko.
The sacred bejeweled spear.
It was as if the gods had
chosen that moment to speak.
Indeed. And we both heard them.
They told us what was required.
What they needed from us.
We knew what we had
found because they told us.
Himiko, the spear.
Yes. The thought entered
our minds simultaneously,
but it came from neither of us.
I could never
hope to explain it.
At that moment it
became all too clear
these were valuable tools.
We could use them.
Indeed, the unearthly
accrual discovered here would
prove the crucible of our dream.
We harvested Himiko's DNA
and used it as the seed
from which the bio-computer,
Zeus, was fostered.
The bejeweled spear
became the lynchpin.
Yes. Placed at
the heart of Atlas,
it soothes the
violent tremors that
threaten the
tower with oblivion.
Hiruko, the spilled blood,
and the sacred spear.
Using these tools we were given,
we could raise our monument
high into the heavens.
A tenuous stability.
By appeasing them,
we've perpetuated
the supernatural forces
that would destroy our dreams.
And now Ryoko.
What is her goal?
Can't say. Although
she is our creation,
her true motives
are far from clear.
She's freed herself
from our control.
If only we could have made
a simple terminal for Zeus.
But its unique composition
required the kind of
power that only a
lifeforce could provide.
It's the only way we
could revive that corpse.
It had to be done.
There's no future in regret.
The fact is, she's free now,
soon to learn the true cost
of casting aside her shackles.
I finally found you!
Oh? Took long enough.
We've been waiting for ages.
Still can't break through.
There's gotta be
some way to stop her.
Damnit!!
That seems
to've done the trick.
Alright.
So you're off?
Take care, hon.
Look, I'm sorry. About earlier.
If those goons had
threatened Momoko like that,
I bet I would've probably
done the exact same thing.
Don't beat yourself up about it.
I'm sorry.
Yeah? What else is new?
I understand what you mean,
but just promise me that
when I get back you'll get
over being sorry all the time.
Yeah, uh, sure thing.
Think she'll
really make it back?
Um, excuse me? That is my
daughter you're talking about.
It's quite unique.
When you blur gender lines,
you can play both
mother and father.
You wanna be a mommy?
Um. I'm not
the parenting type.
What's all this?
Nagiko!
We assumed the center
shaft would be sealed,
so we came down to
offer some assistance.
Kuniko's already
taken care of it.
We should leave
the heroics to the young.
There is something
we can do. Shogo?
Sir?
I need you to set
up a computer terminal.
Medusa, please. Stop this.
Blast it! The damn
thing seems to've established
a beach-head at the gateway to
the UN's central
defense network.
And if it makes its
way inside that network,
it'll mean the end
of the line for us.
I know! We're totally doomed!
Say your prayers, everybody!
Shut up! Come on
we're all smart!
Surely we can figure out
some way outta this, right?
Boo hoo.
There is one way.
Huzzah!
Tarsian!
Okay, genius.
What are we gonna do?
We're joining forces
to catch the beast.
You think it's possible to
contain Medusa at this point?
We have the same minds
that built the most advanced
computer system in the world at
our disposal. I and Nagiko Hojo.
Asian Dragon!
Not to mention your talents.
Oh wow, me too?
Now, let's get started!
Medusa!
You've been a very bad boy!
Poor thing.
Karin!
You okay?
Oh, yeah.
Wait! Zhang! Klaris!
Darling.
Daddy?
We've been gone
a long time, haven't we?
You've been behaving?
Mommy! Daddy!
Who's there?! Who are
you talking to, Karin?
Someone has
rerouted her connection.
She's been intercepted.
I don't know who or from where,
but they've
blocked her off from us.
Damnit.
It appears our connection with
Medusa has been severed as well.
I'm so glad to see you.
I've missed you so much.
Please, forgive us, dear.
The last few years have
been rather tough on you.
Are you two finally
gonna come home?
That's rather
complicated, sweetie.
We wanted to
talk to you about it.
Did something else come up?
Your mother and I...
Well the truth of the matter is
we're not "around" anymore.
What your father's trying
to say is we died, pumpkin.
Now, promise you'll stay
out of trouble for us, alright?
And If you're good,
when we get back we'll
all go out for a nice dinner.
You can even bring
little Pudding along, okay?
Bye! I love you!
After Mommy and Daddy's
plane went into the sky
we ran into some
really bad weather.
The pilot tried
as hard as he could,
but the plane
dropped into the ocean.
It was all over the news,
so it was hard to make sure
you didn't ever hear about it.
I guess we
succeeded with that, eh?
Daddy. What are you saying?
You see. We knew that
you already had the idea
for Medusa, and we didn't
want anything to distract you
from the work you were doing.
I bet you didn't know we knew,
but we know everything,
right, Mother?
Oh yes. This whole thing
has just been a game.
A lie so we could use you and
Medusa to get what we wanted.
Mommy. Daddy.
I don't understand.
Why'd you
do this to me?
I've been so lonely
waiting for you to come home.
We really thought
you'd figure it out.
You made it so easy.
Any normal girl would have
left the house at some point.
But you had no friends,
and no one cared that
you sat alone inside all day.
No. This is all a stupid lie!
Oh?
It's all true.
What the--?
It's an enemy cyberattack!
Some kind of news article.
An airline tragedy.
Huge loss of life, if I recall.
"Airplane crash". "Victims
include Japanese couple".
"Kosuke Ishida, and his
wife Kanon". Hold on!
Sorry. No mailbox
here by that name.
Mommy. Daddy.
No mailbox here
by that name. Sorry.
Please, no.
Sorry. No mailbox
here by that name.
Please.
Sorry. No mailbox
here by that name.
No. No!
They're gone. I'm all alone.
It's true. You're right.
I'm afraid your
lot in life is to be
one forever
shrouded in solitude.
Now. You must grab the
sacred spear, hold it aloft,
and then place it back upright.
Do this, and you shall be
regaled by all as true heir.
Never.
What?
Never. Until Sayoko
is returned to us
unharmed we shall
refuse. Return her now!
You caterwauling
infant. Fine, then.
If you do not
wish to do as I ask,
then I must rid myself of you.
Dost thou threaten us?
Do not forget we gathered
the three talisman blades!
Yes, but now that the doorway
to this tomb has been opened,
I no longer require them.
What I require is for
someone to draw the damned
spear. It need not be you.
Now!
Yes. That's the proper attitude.
Medusa has broken
through the U.N. firewall
and is rapidly gaining
control of their network.
Is this the end for all of us?
Oh, yes. We are
at its inception.
The genesis of my world.
You're going down!
Say what you will
about the world we live in,
but there's so
much worth saving.
These may be dark times,
but the dawn is coming.
The sun will
shine again on those
who still believe in its light.
Next time: "Our Shangri-La"