Mercy. You'd think
we hadn't touched
this soil in weeks
with all the weeds.
I know. Seems like
Nature's taking back
her own more aggressively.
Oh, man. I just realized.
I know. It's weird.
This is the spot
where the slags hit us.
Why is this a
topic of conversation?!
Can the chit chat. There's
work to be done. Hop to!
But-- Sir, uh.
Shouldn't Kuniko be here?
Not much we can do 'bout it.
Yeah, I guess the pressure
of havin to spearhead this gig
is wearin on her, but
whaddaya expect of someone
who thumbed up her
nose at Nagiko's blade?
So is it official now or what?
Shut your traps!
That's our future leader
you lugs are flappin' about!
You think the old
gal's in the habit of
cherry pickin' heirs
who can't cut the mustard?!
Hey, I'm not makin'
any of this up here.
Listen! If you got any
kinda faith in the old girl,
then you got faith
in her granddaughter
to take up the reins!
But sir. She's not here!
Stop eating like
a sideshow act! Ugh.
For the love of Babs, it's
low enough you're reduced to
wearing a tracksuit in public!
Are you a tranny?
Trans-sex-ual.
Tran-sickle?
Whatever. Close enough.
Give me some room, hon.
Waste not want not!
Watch closely,
one show's all ya get!
That's so awesome!
What's it called?!
Such a lovely
time our frolic was--
That was Kuniko's boomerang.
There's no question.
Which can only mean one thing.
Momoko wasn't too far off.
Still, though,
I'm sure they're both fine.
Miiko? Miiko? Where'st thou?
Oh. Sorry, lamb.
Prithee tell us when we
may once more roam the surface.
I'm afraid Sayoko
would know better than I.
But we wish that it
were so at the moment!
Surely a brief visit
would incur no great disaster!
Not with our parasol.
Darling. You know the rules.
We would go there at our own
whim and under no power else!
Mind that temper.
You might very well have
lost your keepsake
just now. Here, be still.
Perfect. Like its wearer.
We thank thee much, Miiko.
By the by, might we yet--
Stop asking!
You're quite a catch.
Entertaining at least.
But this play-acting
is getting tiresome.
Mere rehearsal.
Untie me and I'll give you
box seats to opening night.
Thank you, but no. I much prefer
men in their unedited form.
Mind telling me why someone
like you was wearing this?
Hardly your style, I think.
Where did you get it?
I told you, an outlet
mall in Gotemba.
Perhaps your little
friends have a better memory.
My what?
The brats you were gallivanting
about with out there.
Best of luck.
You've got your work
cut out for you with that lot.
Not a problem.
I'm extremely diligent.
Oh! Look at you! Perhaps
I'm not so jaded after all.
I do believe we can
have all sorts of fun.
Just give it some time, sir.
You'll get your sea legs soon.
You're pretty good
with mimetic armor.
Why not just scare
up a yak-bag for yourself?
Shut up!
There you are.
Just so you know, the ground
where that smokestack collapsed
is now overrun with some new
fast-spreadin'
kind of vegetation.
Least, that's the
best Furukawa can figure.
Hey. The Hell's up with you?
You're blue. I get it. C'mon.
What good's it do ya
just to hang your damn head?
Listen. Every last
one of us's got
loved ones we
wanna raise from the--
Sorry. I'm not
sayin' Momoko's--
We don't know anything yet.
I'm gonna go. I need
something pickled.
Wait! Kuniko!
Me and my damn mouth.
I think it's time we
head back to your chambers,
don't you, love?
Miiko. Let us play hide and
seek! Thou canst be "it" first.
What? It's a
wee bit late for that.
Thou must count to
one hundred! Prithee?
One round and we're going
straight in. One, two, three...
I want you to
tell me your name.
It's pointless to fight it.
Mo--Momoko.
Your real name. The one
given to you as a little boy.
Kenzaki.
Kenzaki Ryoma.
And your age?
Twenty-eight.
I'm no fool! I know
over forty when I see it,
so stop hedging. All right.
I'll start again from the top.
What is your actual name?
Natsuki. Masashi.
Twenty eight.
You lie!
Power of love,
sweetheart. Heady stuff.
Puts your "methods"
to shame. Ah. You know.
'course you do.
After all, you're a mother.
Those hips give you away.
I'd guess a girl? Around ten?
Shut your mouth!
You smoke.
Not in front of your daughter,
though. Am I right?
I said shut your mouth!
Tough isn't it?
Raising her alone.
You work day and night.
Trying to give her a good life.
It's not ideal.
She rarely sees you.
But you've no choice.
It's better this way.
Be little more
than a stranger to her,
than that she go without. Still,
you obsess over whether or not
she'll grow up twisted
by your absence. Poor thing.
Midori.
Pretty name.
Don't fret too much though,
'cause if she's like you,
she'll manage through the parade
of lonely nights more or less
intact. Well, she probably will.
Shut your goddamn mouth!
She loves her mommy.
Almost as much as you love her.
You're a whore!
You know nothing!
Lady Mikuni.
We cannot let you pass.
Yet we would leave.
Milady!
Tell us. How deep
doth thine loyalty fare?
How doth thou rate us?
Are we not most beautiful?
Whither must we turn
to quit this dreadful place?
Light Shield Deactivated.
Poppet! What have you done?!
Miiko. We hurt.
Raise the
goddamn shield back up!
Yes ma'am!
The light burns.
A voice! I hear a voice!
The Moon. The Sun. The Land!
It calls to them all!
The time is
upon us! The voice--
The Pillar of Heaven
must be obeyed!
Mikuni! Don't you do this!
Don't you die on me!
Poor, captive starling.
Far be it from me to
open the door of your cage.
Fantastic.
What's your drama?
Oh, only the
friggin' Atlas Corporation
getting wise to Medusa!
One of the ministers we
do business with must've sang.
No way! Why'd they do that?
Don't know,
but when I find out who,
they're gonna be a soprano.
Nevermind. I guess
there's still money to be made.
Let's just get on with it.
I have dinner
with the folks later.
What?! When in the
Hell did you make a typhoon?!
Good news.
Tarsian just restored the
old priority command settings.
You're top o' the
food chain again.
Huh? What's he playing at?
You're gonna look a
gift horse in the mouth?
C'mon, we can
get back to earning!
I--I can finally drag
myself out of the gutter
and buy clothes a
human being would wear! Ciao!
Hey! Klaris! Man.
A typhoon's developed
near the Marshall Islands.
Virtually stationary.
That's the odd thing.
It's hovering where it formed.
Possibly related to the
microwave pulse someone hacked
out of the Apollo satellite.
Someone has fashioned
themselves a shield.
We shall proceed regardless.
Ma'am.
Shogo?
Ma'am. Construction is now
twelve percent behind schedule.
And that percentage is
likely to increase with time.
No doubt the Prime Minister's
fault. Shion, darling?
Don't you pine
for the touch of
role play we
enjoyed in the prison?
Madam, 'twas marvelous.
Zet Vier.
Madam.
Round up the press core.
Consider it done, ma'am.
Bravo! I think
we have a winner!
It's not too revealing? Feels
like I might as well be nude.
Indiscretion is the
better part of pallor.
You expect me to
fight telepathically?
I expect a brilliant young
lady to be more resourceful.
Oh, so I guess the
boomerang's just for show?
A lady fights as a
last resort or not at all.
Oh, sure. And she shows leg.
Kuniko, please,
don't ever forget.
Be like the wind,
it's your life.
Can the greeting card crap!
No one's an island!
Look around you! We can't
all march to our own drum!
Oh, and that evidently means
we're not allowed a childhood?
That's not what
I'm saying. Look--!
Please, by all means clarify!
I know we live in a hard world.
It doesn't need our help.
Why feed it our children?
I'm not gonna cry,
Momoko. Not anymore.
I've made up my mind.
Things have changed.
I'm gonna make
you proud. I swear.
How is she?
She'll be fine.
Her condition is stable.
It's my fault. I should've
never taken my eye off you.
Thou art blameless.
We so cruelly tricked thee.
Canst thou ever forgive us?
Hush, my daffodil.
Milady, the fault is mine.
I move too slowly. You
languish whilst my research
creeps like jasmine.
I have failed you.
Still thy tongue.
Thou know'st we love thee
dearly not upon condition.
Your love humbles me, milady.
Just so. Though
may'st answer me this.
Wherefore the
voice in our head?
Do what?
We--We heard a
voice while falling down,
'twas like a wet
blanket laid 'cross our mind.
But I wasn't far from you and
heard not a whisper, my dear.
Then, only we were
privy to its timbre?
Milady! You must tell me
what the voice said to you!
"O Moon. Climb the sky. Dispel
the o'er arcing darkness."
"O Moon. Climb the sky?"
I know these words.
Please excuse me.
Sayoko?!
Breaking news. The Prime
Minister has stepped down,
citing emotional strain.
In Mister Umaimiya's stead,
Atlas Corporation CEO Ryoko
Naruse has assumed the role.
For more details, we go to
a press conference held earlier.
You're kidding me!
Unbelievable!
Looking ahead to the next
decade, my priority is Atlas,
and, of course, to move further
with the Greenification Project.
Is there a solution for
people living in the outlands?
Populace relocation
is also of great concern.
A review board has been
appointed to evaluate methods
which will help us
expedite the process.
Living arrangements and safety
are a concern, needless to say.
But above all else,
the people's quality of life
is this government's
raison d'etre.
What a joke.
Every word outta
her mouth's a lie.
So her name's Ryoko Naruse.
You may enter.
My sources at the
Moon Palace tell me that
Digma One has heard the litany.
Oh. I assume then
you know what's to be done?
Indeed.
What are you telling me?!
I repeat, ma'am,
the phrase satisfies
all analytic
parameters for a match.
Nevertheless, Lady Mikuni's
current ranking is unchanged.
You're to standby at the Moon
Palace until further notice.
Damn you! The
child heard Atlas' voice
as surely as
you're hearing mine!
How is that not a game changer?
Standby. That is all.
What chide'st thou?
Thy speed was frightful.
Milady, I--I swear
to you here and now.
You will feel the sun
upon your face without agony.
I was thinking it was
about time for you to show up.
I've been thinking
a lot about power.
Like what I might have
the power to actually change.
Thing is. The people
of Duomo are my family.
My life. If I don't take it upon
myself to improve their lives,
what's the point
of my being here?
Oh, child.
I've seen a lot of craziness.
And the more I see, the less
I feel able to do anything.
The less I feel
like we have a real shot.
There's a limit
to what any of us
can accomplish
on our own, Kuniko.
It's only natural you'd feel
it when confronted by Atlas.
You're right.
It's kinda overwhelming.
Listen, this isn't
about revenge.
For what they did to
Momoko or my friends in juvie.
I wanna make
sure you know that.
My mind was made up
before any of that happened.
It's just, I wasn't
sure I was right.
I mean, you know, for this.
Now I know, I will
be Metal Age's leader.
What'll be your
first triumph as president?
Storming Atlas.
I see.
There's no question
of your courage, my dear.
But you'll have to draw
on every screed of it.
Grandma--?!
I hear a voice.
"Oh Sun. Climb the sky.
Dispel the o'er
arcing darkness."
I'm hearin' things.
So this Medusa
or whatever you call it,
is hiding in
the Marshal Islands?
Precisely.
And you want us
to mobilize a task force?
Oh, no. It's already done.
The Yamato Takeru
is poised to strike.
Hold on! How did you
sneak an aircraft carrier
that size into their waters?
Well, sir, they are
called stealth carriers
for a reason, I believe.
Green light for
Phase Two, gentlemen.
Commence Operation Medusa
Clean Sweep on my order.
Sir. Lieutenant Kusanagi!
Right! Now dress her down.
Roger that! Removing camouflage.
Oh wow. I haven't
heard this song in years.
Not since it was sung especially
for me. Really takes me back.
Next time: "Butterfly Dream"