It's getting much worse.
Granted, it's been only two
weeks since the eradication
of the Daedalus, but the index
shouldn't continue to drop!
No, Medusa's to blame.
It's like it's feasting on
the world's financial resources.
And I'm afraid
Japan's first on the menu.
We're heading straight
for World War Three.
Prime Minister.
What is your plan?
We've received a report
that a detachment of bombers
is making its way toward
the Marshall Islands.
It seems that the
U.N. is taking charge
of this Medusa debacle.
We should let them lead the way.
This is the result
of your incompetence!
How will you solve this mess?
Our nation's decline
since you've been
in office is unprecedented!
We cannot afford
to let this go on!
Do the honorable
thing and resign, at once!
Tell me. Who among
you possesses the courage
or ability to take the
helm of this sinking nation?
You cry foul and
point your fingers at me,
but still you sit,
trembling in your chairs.
They've been wiped out!
The entire U.N. bombing
detachment has been annihilated.
But how?!
It's just like last time.
They were destroyed by
a massive typhoon centered
over the Marshall Islands.
The report says
Medusa's to blame.
Stop!
I got you good!
Cut it out! There are
a lot of people who want
to use the tub tonight. So stop
wasting all the hot water!
O-kay!
You little brats!
This reminds me
of our newlywed days,
before we had
a tub of our own.
I always wanted to look
sharp for my little cutie.
That's so good, oh man!
What the hell are we doin'?!
We should be
stormin' Atlas right now!
We're still Metal Age, right?!
Yeah, but we're already
on the inside, man.
We don't need to storm it.
Listen brother, the
fight's over, so just relax
and get some
food in your belly.
Come and take a seat.
Get some grub!
I'm not hungry!
You know what they say, "an
army marches on its stomach."
We heard that rumble.
You don't want it to get cold.
Not too shabby.
Miss Haruko. I'm pretty sure
everyone got a bowl at least.
Man, I'm totally beat.
Are you sure about that?
How 'bout you?
Aww, thanks. Really, thanks for
everything you've done for us.
The way I look at it,
no matter how we got here,
we're all in this
together. It's just part of
being a good neighbor. Right?
Right.
Hey pal, no cutting in line!
Oh, sorry 'bout that! She here?
"She" who?
Who ya lookin' for?
There you are! Did you
order everyone to help out
just so you could
run around all afternoon?
Hey! Don't run off
while I'm talking to you!
Is Kuniko playin' hard to get?
Sounds like her.
Tropical Fish's
stiffest competition.
Welcome to paradise, boys!
I hope you'll stay a while!
Get ready to pop that cork!
Momoko, you're
wanted at table three!
Move those buns, hon!
I've come home.
Tokyo's a big
place, isn't it?!
How invigorating to get
out of that stuffy old tower!
But the air here is a bit
overcooked at the moment.
What's wrong?
If we wanted to get
rid of it all, we did it.
Wanna take it back?
Too late.
You did what no
one else could, love.
Can I finish the job? Can I
make a new world from this?
Listen up!
I'm done mopin' around!
Gotta keep movin' forward!
I've been lookin'
all over for ya!
Why, did something happen?
Well, kinda.
Come with me for a bit.
Just tell me.
I can't put it into words.
Just come on already, would ya?!
Nuh uh! Can you at least
tell me where we're going?
I'll explain later.
No, now! I thought I asked you
to do something for me anyway.
I guess the rice cooker's fixed?
I can fix it later!
You need to do it now!
And when you're done with that,
the outside windows
need cleaning, so move!
Look, I don't have the
gear for that kind of job.
Besides, you're not
in charge of Atlas, too!
Huh. No wonder you
quit the Army, lazybones.
List-en! There's
something important you
and I need to talk about!
And I guess it's more important
than fixing the rice cooker?!
Stop. Let's break up
this lover's quarrel.
Lover's quarrel?!
With her? With him?
Simmer down. Children,
get your priorities straight.
Love always comes first.
"Love"?!
You mustn't deny
what fate demands.
Forget your troubles
and just hold hands.
Ya see? Feels right, yes?
I'm happy to entertain myself,
but an invitation to join them
would've been the polite
thing to do. C'est la vie.
Phoenix came from ashes. Right?
Look. Ya see that?
Guess not.
It's right in front
of ya. Look carefully.
All I see is burning rubble.
As far as you look.
Wait a sec. This isn't some
kinda creepy message is it?
Dunno. Could be.
I don't have time for this crap!
Let go of me, jerk-wad!
You're being silly!
Stop yelling.
Let go!
Calm down!
Don't touch me!
Are you alright?
What the--?
Thought so.
You thought what?!
Let me see that thing.
It's gone. But how?
Do you suppose
they've seen the sign?
By now? It's in
their blood isn't it?
After the
fires subsided, voila.
You think they've
been there all along?
Yeah.
If you patrol
around Atlas's perimeter,
these lines are
all over the place.
Anywhere you look,
you can find them.
Making patterns that
are part of this larger one.
Woah. And right at
the center of it all...
Atlas.
They spoke to us. Showed us
what was to be our future.
The ley lines were
revealed. It was as if
the quake swept Tokyo aside,
in order to show us
the true axis mundi.
At the nexus,
we'd construct a pillar.
We could channel Earth's
energy to lift the sky.
Praying, of course,
that would stabilize our world.
We would create a
new center of the World.
One which would attract
prosperity, emanate power.
Complete and utter nonsense.
Maybe so. But you certainly
believed in it back then, yes?
Blinded by
something, insanity or--
Whatever the case, I swore
my life and fortune to it.
Despite the most
sophisticated technology,
we could not
rectify the crucial issue:
the mechanical resonance.
In desperation,
we traveled down that dark path
that leads beyond
what science can explain.
Dark indeed. We abandoned
the light of reason
and bloodied our hands
with the act that set
the grim cycle in motion.
We tried to satisfy
the monster's craving.
Provide Hiruko with
fresh souls in which to reside.
Young children shy
of their seventh year.
The blood of many innocents
was needed to slake its thirst.
But eventually,
the tremors subsided.
A structure built
on stolen lives.
Atlas is nothing more than
an elaborate grave marker.
I don't need reassurance.
Regret is a useless feeling.
We carry our deeds
with us like it or not.
Yes, you're right.
And like Atlas,
we shall shoulder our burdens
until the bejeweled spear,
leaves the earthen
grip that holds it.
It's strange. Like we've
stumbled upon the occult.
Or a "creepy message."
Yeah, no joke. Do you mind
if I borrow this for a bit?
I don't really
like not having it.
Besides, don't you
have your own, anyway?
Oh crap!
I did, but I traded
it to that girl Karin.
What? But why?!
Well, she promised
to throw in an extra bomber
if I handed over the knife.
You are such a sucker!
Don't lecture me!
Thanks a lot, butterfingers!
It was an accident!
You okay?!
I'm fine. Just
get the damn blade!
Right!
Aw shit!
Once again did
our amulet resound
with such a heavenly tone.
Excuse me, miss.
Karin, what bids thee here?
I come bringing a
gift for you, my lady.
I think you'll like it.
How did you get those blades?!
What difference does
it make how I got them?
You've been looking
for them and here they are.
What's more, I believe
this completes the collection.
Am I right?
They bear uncanny resemblance
to the one we possess.
In fact, the very
same through and through.
'Tis true, milady. These
blades will secure your ascent
to the highest level of Atlas.
Splendid Karin.
Bless thy name.
It's an honor to serve.
Prepare a carriage immediately!
Atlas cries out,
for our triumph!
Karin Ishida you say?
Yes, ma'am. On behalf of Digma
One, she requests entrance.
It seems the
conditions have been met.
Very well. Send a party to greet
them. Out of pure necessity.
Was that smooth, or what?
"You're the
luckiest girl I know!"
I worked my tail off
to get Mikuni in place.
Surely my role as benefactor
and advocate will be rewarded
once she's
in charge. And then--
"The cash'll come rollin' in!"
Hey, Karin!
Oh look, Sister Mary Robert!
You can go back to calling me
"Klaris, the
richest girl you know."
Oh yeah? You rode my coattails
straight to the bank, did ya?
"No fair."
All's fair in love
and finance, darling.
But seriously, you gotta
spill the beans about
how you sunk the carbon index!
I'd love to tell ya how
it happened, but I can't.
Why?
Medusa's totally leaving
me in the dust here, Klaris.
I can't keep up
with the investment paths.
I even just tried asking
directly, but mum's the word.
Like it's ignoring you?
When I was hacking
into Zeus a while ago
I gave Medusa its
own top user priority.
Everything's that's
happened since then has gone on
without any input from me.
All we gotta do is play
around and spend the money
Medusa makes for us? Kick ass!
Yeah... I guess.
Alright, Medusa!
Let's see if you can make
me the wealthiest gal ever!
Karin!
Zhang!
We have a strict, no-backstabber
policy at our clubhouse,
so take your
apologies and hit the road.
I didn't come
here for that anyway,
we've got a major storm
brewing here! It's Antarctica!
Give me a break.
Now that's just stupid.
No! Listen! Medusa's taking out
its head leases on Antarctica.
What in the heck?
If you look at the ledgers
for the Carbon Bank of Japan,
there's a contract there
for the purchase of
7% of the Antarctic continent.
But that makes zero sense.
There's like, nobody even there.
"Zero" is right!
Antarctica isn't
a part of any other nation.
It's unclaimed.
Its asset value is zero.
So it's just gonna keep
buying until it's outta money?
Then what?
Then the carbon index that
Medusa artificially lowered
bounces back like crazy.
The market basically
eats itself alive until
there's nothing left of value!
Uh-oh.
There, all better!
Luckily, it's just a scratch.
Yeah! From a bullet!
That wasn't just bad luck.
Those guys were looking for us.
But who put them up to it?
Aw, stop grumbling
and let's go.
I'll tag along
and help you look for 'em.
You'll help?! That'd be great!
Come on, I said
I was sorry, didn't I?
Again? Get a room you two.
Momoko!
In the flesh. You poor thing.
Did you get a boo-boo?
It's nothing, I'm fine.
Indeed, but Mama can
make everything all better.
A little kiss and
you'll forget all about it.
No. Please don't.
Oh, almost forgot. The Metal Age
guys wanted me to tell you,
the infernal geezer
trio's made contact.
Really? That's great news!
Yes, they survived, apparently
they have cockroach DNA.
You're gonna molest me like
that and then just walk away?
I'm sorry hon, you're
just such a bad kisser.
You are the most
evil little tramp I know!
Where my bell curve's
concerned, he's barely a four.
My... first kiss.
Hiya pervs! You guys
made it through the fire!
Of course! It's the fire
within us that truly counts!
Give us a smile, dear!
Coochie-coochie-coo!
Furukawa! Looks like
you made it to Akihabara,
safe and sound!
He narrowed his
focus and took the shot!
He has the right
mettle to forward our cause!
BAUM-BOMBOMBOMBOM-BOM-BAAUUMM!
They are just so cute!
I hope poor Furukawa's
had all his shots.
Now the reason we've
broken our radio silence.
We've obtained some intelligence
you may find a bit disturbing.
War is being
waged over Antarctica.
And the commanding
general is calling the shots
from right here
in our own territory.
What are you doing?!
Medusa's gone too far.
So I need to take back control!
You don't have time!
You gotta get outta
there as fast as you can Karin!
Where's the fire this time?!
All over you,
when Titan gets there!
Oh yeah? What's that mean!
There's a humongous
warship coming!
So what? That's no big deal.
A little typhoon
should take that thing out.
Right. Over Tokyo?
Don' you get it? It's not
targeting the islands this time!
It's you!
What?!
Titan is entering the
skies over Iturup Island!
This is an airspace violation!
Where the hell
are our defenses?!
You are violating
Japanese airspace.
I repeat. You are
violating Japanese airspace.
Please withdraw immediately.
We are operating
under jurisdiction
of the United Nations.
Stand down.
They're U.N. forces.
Hiding behind the
anti-Medusa resolution.
Then why the hell
are they coming to Tokyo?
It's here. Titan is now
in the airspace over Honshu.
The U.N. forces are insisting
that Medusa is illegally being
harbored somewhere
inside Tokyo.
Should we contest and
try to stave off the attack?
Since I gave them the
coordinates, I think not.
Madam Ryoko?!
What's wrong? We do know
the Neo-Guild is the main force
behind that venomous
snake do we not?
Bring it on!
Show me whatcha got!
Karin! You're wasting
precious time with this!
Just get outta there!
We're not playing
around, this is serious!
I can't let it end like this!
They take my money,
I'm as good as dead!
I'm a Neo-Carbonist!
Cash is my life's blood!
The cloud this kicks up
should sufficiently
obscure the moon, yes?
That's the reason?
Well, that's not the only one.
Mikuni won't deign to enter
Atlas without her little pet.
And who wants that?
It's much simpler this way.
Foolish witch! Strike me down
and the pillar will crumble!
The heavens shall fall!
Miiko, calm thyself!
Milady, we must leave this
place, and that thing behind.
We shall not!
We shall enter Atlas
with dear Miiko at our side!
Vile creature!
Miiko.
Oh Moon! Soon your
light shall wane.
The end is nigh! I see it!
We must make our
way to Atlas at once.
Nothing can divert our path.
Miss Mikuni, we must
go and claim your destiny!
Worry not.
We shall return soon.
We shall fetch
thee, Miiko! We swear it!
Karin, please!
Hold on! I've just
about got him by the tail!
You're way too close to
being teddy bear barbecue!
Medusa. Come back!
Madam. Titan is now
honing in on Old Akihabara.
Gotcha!
And just when the poor night
bird was leaving her cage.
What a pity.
What was that?!
Hurry!
Okay!
Miiko!
But how?
Come, Miiko. We must
make our way into Atlas!
Miiko! Miiko!
Heart, burning for retribution.
The Moon Flower yearns to
bloom over soil awash in blood.
The writhing
serpent, fangs bared,
heralds winter without end.
Next time: "The Lost Holy Land"