Haven't heard anything yet.
Hope they're doing okay.
Come on, you.
It's time for bed.
Nuh-uh.
I wanna wait for Kuniko.
We've got incoming
video from Nerima Ward!
Holy crap!
Southeast Toshima, Rokugo Bridge
in Ota. They're everywhere!
And Ikebukuro!
Ya think it's
those guys Takehiko paid?!
Is anybody there? Hellooo.
My bad, Momoko!
That's delicate equipment
designed for your mouth, hon.
Don't jab it with your
fingers like a barbarian.
Look, pervert--
I am not takin' the bait.
"Pervert?" Surely you jest.
Whatever, man-eater.
Save it for the boys.
As lucky panties go,
white is a bit pedestrian.
Then don't look!
Betcha we'll get there
after the whole thing's wrapped.
What makes you think
they'd go off half-cocked?
The cock-and-a-half
who's leadin' 'em.
Takehiko?
He's a sweetie.
But so impatient.
Kuniko, what's your 20?
'bout time, 'cause I
wasn't feeling the love!
Where're you guys at?
Hey, ya there?
Team One here. Are you inside?
Team Three!
Damned glad to have ya!
No kidding!
That's more like it.
Now gimmie a sit-rep, pronto.
We're in. We broke
through in nothin' flat.
Team Two is almost inside.
Okay, guys.
Start laying down cover-fire.
This is Team Seven.
No sign of our target.
They couldn't find the
TV station? 'Kay, Plan B--
Join up with the team
headed to the Diet Building.
Hey, Nine through Fourteen,
check in. Where are you guys?
We're in the jungle, ma'am.
Wha--? Yusuke
from Team Nine, right?
D'you mind
saying that again?
Yeah, Team Nine.
Look, we're up to
our asses in foliage here!
"Foliage" some kinda code word?
Man-scaping issue?
This is Team Twelve!
Everything's gone FUBAR!
There's a huge
wall of fire and--!
Holy shit! Is that
the old steam train?!
Team Ten's gotta pull back!
This bridge is
gonna collapse any second!
No more crazy-talk!
Keep it together! Takehiko!
What the hell's
going on out there?!
You really wanna know?
C'mon-- Don't make
a girl beg for it.
Don't tease him, Momoko!
Just tell me
your location, okay?
We're on a goddamn island.
On an island?!
Crazy, huh? Got ocean
as far as the eye can see.
Son of a--!
Takehiko, What's going on?!
Kuniko! What do we--?!
Oh! Shit! We're surrounded!
They're tearin' us up--!
Man down!
An update, Madam.
Reon's leading ground troops
to engage the
guerillas on Level Eight.
How much damage
can we anticipate?
A mere three
percent of the structure.
Begin the repairs.
And track down any traitors.
Yes, ma'am.
Do find me, dear. I have
a lovely surprise for you.
Hey, Yusuke. I think we're goin'
around in circles, here man.
No shit. It's because all
these trees look the same!
Five targets sighted.
One o'clock.
Proceed with caution.
They're clueless, sir.
It's gonna be like
shooting fish in a barrel.
We're ordered to fire
on our own countrymen?
Sir! They've compromised
the shaft's entryway!
You're tenacious, Digma Two.
This is Level Eight, right?
I figured they'd have a tanning
salon, but this is ridiculous!
You gotta be kidding me!
Heads up! It's mimetic armor!
You cut out--
Something 'bout a medic?
Say again?
All o' that crazy
crap you're looking at?!
It ain't real!
What do we do now?
Better use your
mind's eye, girlie.
Cause looks can be misleading.
I don't see anything.
'Course you don't! The threat's
invisible to the naked eye.
Like your ta-tas!
They'll kick in sooner or later.
Huh?
Wait a sec!
This is Tokyo!
Yeah, before the big earthquake.
Too prim for my blood.
Got y'ears on, kid?
We're in pre-quake Tokyo. So...
Where's that leave Atlas?
Calm your ass down.
We're stuck in the same mirage.
Even found the Diet Building.
Really?!
Bad news is,
ammo's runnin' out.
The guys're burnin' through
it pretty friggin' quick.
Just try to hold your ground.
That's a good spot
for us all to regroup.
Time to go!
Oh man! What is
that awesome thing?!
Up til now? A guy in a suit!
Old Tokyo was
the coolest place ever!
Let's rendezvous
at the Diet Buiding!
Takehiko. Any luck reachin' her?
Yeah. How 'bout you guys?
Naw, no dice.
Nothin' but static.
So what'd she say?
She wants all the teams
to meet up at Tokyo City Hall.
Got it! Listen up, guys!
We're goin' to City Hall!
Tokyo City Hall.
That's what she said.
Rank simpletons. Like bugs,
whirling around a bright light.
Yes. Those rebels could never
defeat our soldiers, madam.
You misunderstand me, Shion.
They've no idea, you see.
The glow which
dazzles them is in truth
a fire that will
burn them all alive.
Madam Ryoko.?
Atlas was built with
but one purpose in mind.
Do you know what that is?
Damned if I know.
Gimmie a hint.
You're no fun.
Okay, fine. Ikebukuro.
I'm used to it being overgrown.
You know what I mean?
When something you've
always taken for granted
is suddenly gone, it has a way
of messing with your head-space.
And when something
new takes the stage,
like an awe-inspiring rack,
say, you'd better believe
there are gonna be people who'll
simply refuse to accept it.
So back when it
first got unveiled,
did a lotta people think that
about the plan to build Atlas?
You're flat and
I'm old. Touché.
I think that most people
were in favor of the idea.
Central Japan was ravaged
by a natural disaster--
The Second Great
Kanto Earthquake.
The resulting fires
consumed all of Tokyo.
It was every man for himself.
Damages were in the trillions.
Over ten million Japanese
were dead or missing.
People lost their homes, their
families. They had nothing.
What's worse, the
government was in no shape
to be doling out aid.
How come?
The Monetized Carbon System had
just become the global standard.
We were drowning in taxes.
Going down for the count.
That's why the
suits left 'em hangin'?!
'Cause it was too
expensive?! What the hell!
Luckily, the private sector
was there to pick up the slack.
That's where Atlas comes in?
But who had that kinda scratch?
Billions and
billions in "scratch",
and one man donated all of it.
Atlas's co-founder and
consigliere, Sergei Tarsian.
It's his support that brought
the dream of Atlas to life.
"Take this broken
land before you
and fashion something
strong," he said.
That sounds like
the old man, all right.
"Fashion something strong?"
In other words, "This
sandcastle's played out,
and high-tide's a-comin'.
Let's go back to square one."
Tokyo was abandoned
to nature in the hopes
it would help
cool down the planet,
and reborn as Atlas,
a high-tech aerie.
A habitat regulated
entirely by computers.
An edifice that
would laugh in the face
of typhoon and
earthquake alike.
A bright, shining land of
milk and honey rose above them.
All they had to do was wait
for construction to wrap up.
The Atlas Plan
rescued our country from
a grim future filled
with uncertainty.
It's been Japan's salvation
and a beacon to
others around the world.
Go on.
And now that you are
spearheading the Atlas project,
Madam Ryoko, our future
is brighter than ever before--
It's an honor to serve--
Atlas exists for one reason.
To be my source of amusement!
If you can't bear that much
in mind, perhaps I ought to
shunt you back to the jungle.
You and your brother both.
Please forgive my stupidity!
I beg of you!
Mister Tarsian awaits you.
Obviously.
There are so many,
it's hard to pick just one!
Indeed. But Brazil's carbon
index is the most vulnerable.
May I initiate a head-lease?
They burn down jungle to farm.
That's why they're in trouble.
You are one smart cookie.
Karin. We should consider
putting blinders on Medusa.
It's growing too aware.
What's wrong, Zhang?
That can't be fear that I'm
hearing in your voice, can it?
I'm not afraid! I'm just
pointing out that our program
is growing more sophisticated.
It's acting
independent of our commands,
and has demonstrated the desire
and ability to defend itself.
Besides, we're all so rich now,
we don't need the
profit at a time like this!
"But this is the
perfect time for it."
Thanks a bunch for
the chaotic market, Tokyo!
Don't be glib, you two--
This is serious!
Pardon the intrusion.
That's a nice dress.
"O Sun. Illuminate the
heavens and the earth alike."
"O Moon. Climb the sky. Dispel
the o'er arcing darkness."
"O Land, enthrall
the day and the night,
and hold thee
sway upon the world."
We have the triad.
The completion of
Atlas is all that remains.
Half a century is
but the blink of an eye.
How could people have
built all this so quickly?
Your donation made it possible.
She had a dream, and I wrote
a check. Don't canonize me.
Where the hell am I?
My Lady Mikuni
is the rightful heir.
There she goes.
I will know the true nature of
this place, from Hiruko himself!
What are your orders, Madam?
Let her scurry away.
Capture her at once.
She won't make it to the top.
It's nothing to
interrupt our chess game over.
Clearly it is. Soichiro.
Ma'am.
This tower will be
defunct if any misfortune
should befall Lord Hiruko.
You are well aware of that.
Yes. Very.
All you have to do is
put my commands into action.
I understand my role.
Is there anyone
out there?! My team's KIA!
Please tell me I'm
not the only one left!
You're breaking up.
Yusuke?
Oh, thank God!
Tell me what you're lookin' at.
I'm lookin' at...
Shinjuku? What the hell?
Head to the station.
Kuniko's nearby, isn't she?
And the others, I mean,
they're all right, yeah?
All this was just a trap?!
Motherfucker.
Yusuke! D'you read?!
We gotta go!
C'mon! Time to beat feet!
No. No more running!
Girl, what are
you talking about?
I'm sick of this crap!
Get the hell outta my waaaay!
There's more
where that came from!
Lieutenant!
Wait, Tokyo Station?!
How did we overshoot
the Diet Building?
You were in
boomerang-bitch mode.
Kuniko! Where'd you
scamper off to this time?!
Kunihito!
Been back to
Akihabara, sticky-fingers?
You tell your leader,
people are gonna die
if he doesn't surrender!
Actually, I'm the one
who's calling the shots now.
You're kidding me!
'Fraid not!
I didn't know that.
Then you need to order
your people to stand down!
You assholes are the
ones who need to stand down!
You're all hiding
behind holograms anyway!
We're trying to
defend the capital!
What about the
people left outside?!
Duomo's hanging on by a thread.
Why don't you care about us?!
How can someone who pulls a gun
on their own countrymen
call himself a soldier?
I know something's
definitely wrong here.
I've known for a while.
Then, why're you--?!
'Cause attacking us
doesn't change a damn thing!
All it does is
get people killed!
So what then? Run back home?
Nature's taking it.
There is no going back.
You have a home here.
Your family lives
in Atlas, don't you?
Yeah we do. And if I die
protecting 'em, then so be it.
Yeah, well. I'm trying
to save my people!
Hold it!
Easy, Lieutenant.
Corporate is taking
over jurisdiction on this.
The end-game. When a
pawn can topple a king.
If the queen doesn't slay them.
Momoko. I just
wanna be wherever you are!
Damn robot!
There it is!
Mate in one.
My team is in trouble here!
It looks like
Atlas is starting to
use some kinda
chemical weapons on us!
What'n the blue hell?!
Now they gas us?!
Centralizing all city
functions in this way
will conserve energy.
Our designs feature
disaster-resistant
carbon polymers that are
virtually indestructible.
Welcome to my Atlas,
city born of a dream.
All systems herein
will be controlled by Zeus,
a cutting-edge AI.
Our majordomo, as it were.
As the world's fastest computer,
Zeus will
supervise construction
and maintain
public safety with ease.
Our world is speeding
towards a carbon-based economy.
With this in mind,
our company is putting
its faith in graphite,
both as an investment
and a building material.
Standing at my side is New York
financier Sergei Tarsian.
He's contributed
50 billion dollars to
the construction
of the Atlas habitat.
Our future demands
no less an investment.
To the chosen
children for whom we've
undertaken this grand labor,
I hope you appear
within our lifetime.
Listen well to Zeus,
and do not fear your destiny.
A new world awaits you.
Come forth and claim it.
Whatever you may
discover on your mission,
you must face it
without trepidation.
Your birth mother
lives in Atlas, after all.
Hash out your
feelings. Give it time.
Life will make you choose
a path. I'm sure of it.
Kuniko! There's no
question of your courage.
But you'll have to
draw on every screed of it.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why did you lie?!
Lady Mikuni,
I am... here.
I just want to keep 'em safe.
My family. Atlas. All the
people who call it home.
I know the system
isn't perfect, but still.
Next time: "Freak Defeat"