"Why do you dig?
What drives you to do it?"
When legendary tunnel engineer
and all around badass
Alejandro Vedernikov was asked
those questions, he responded
the way any digger would.
"Because, on the other
side of that dirt lies
a new world just waiting
for me to uncover it!"
I'm gonna get all up
in that new world!
Ladies! Ready or not,
here comes Andy!
Hey, where the heck are they?
Jackpot.
Here they are, guys!
Get 'em while they're hot!
Whoa!
These are pics
from the field trip!
When did you even take these?
Oh come now, silly girl,
don't you know a magician
never reveals her secrets?
Oo-oh! One of Shrade, please!
All yours, hon!
Jeez. I look terrible.
I think you look
awesome in this one.
Oh yeah, super cute.
Oh hey, nice shot,
are you gonna buy it?
'Cause you could ditch
the two-dimensional girls
for a flesh-and-blood hottie
just waiting for a
connoisseur's eye.
Are there any of us who
don't launch you skyward?
Hey! I can't help it!
Um, go ahead, take it.
Hey, hey, look at you stud;
you're a chick magnet.
Just mind your own business.
Can I have this one please?
That one?
I guess so, long as
you've got the sheckels.
Thank you.
Say, who's that picture of?
Oh. Uh--
Don't be weird,
just let me see it!
Wonder what it is.
Amata and Andy?
Definitely did not
see that one coming.
Yo, yo, check it
out my diggin' bro!
You'll never believe what
I found in your hole!
What?
Trust me dudes, there's
no way I'm wrong about this.
It's the Book of Twin Stars,
I'm a hundred percent sure!
Sorry, never heard of it.
I know all about it.
According to the
old stories, who-
whoever holds that book
becomes Aquarion's master...
unlocks the full arsenal--
Spoken like a
plushie in the know.
Neo-DEAVA's been
looking for this bad boy
since the beginning.
So what's the deal, how'd
you find it in the first place?
Yeah, where did
you find it, Andy?
I dug a hole, to get
to-- uh, doesn't matter!
No reason to get caught
up in the details.
Miss Chairwoman, please!
We've earned the right to your
confidence; tell us the truth.
The truth about what?
Come on. You've been on
sabbatical for how long?
You wouldn't just waltz back in
here unless something was up!
Well, let's see, oh yes!
That's right, I almost forgot!
I brought you a gift.
That is not what we mean!
Don't look a
gift-horse in the mouth.
How can we do our jobs if
you keep us in the dark?!
They cannot read
with just their eyes.
The book will only reveal itself
to those special few
with eyes that cannot see.
What the hell
declension is that?
Ugh! Rih, Rih, Ribbit.
Ribbit like a frog?
What does that mean?
All my nodding
off in Ancient Lit
is finally coming
back to haunt me!
Red, help me out,
I suck at this!
Sure.
Let's see, duh, duh,
dig, dig, digger, digging.
Is it digging?
I'm sorry. He should know;
I've always owed him.
Mikono. What're you sorry for?
What could you have done?
Get ready to have
your mind blown!
Put some shoes on.
Ancient Lesson Number One,
'All socks must be white!'
Wait, what?
First line of the book, it took
him all night to figure out.
Hell yeah!
Chapter twenty three,
verse one has been dominated.
That's right, and
I figured it all out myself.
Great, but what the hell do
socks have to do with Aquarion?
Yeah Daddy's got a
little theory about that.
The writings of ancient
wrestling enthusiasts
tell us fighters
who lost their shoes
were at a disadvantage.
Shoes are important
'cause they protect our feet.
Feet are important
'cause they make us stand.
Standing's important
so we don't fall down
like idiots all the time.
White socks matter
'cause we wear 'em on
our most precious parts.
Well, second most anyway.
White clothing that covers
our precious body parts?
Her panties are teal, not white.
What color do I have on?
Take a guess.
Yeah--yeah, real funny,
laugh it up chuckles!
Ancient documents
are serious bidness!
I just don't know
what people see in her.
What ancient documents?
Andy here thinks
he found something.
Huh, let me see that.
Uh, okay.
You even know how to
read that gibberish?
Literature is my
specialty. Wait, what?
I think it says 'all girl's
tops must be fully buttoned up.'
For real?
That seems kinda random.
'No hair shall grow
past the eye brows.'
Weird.
'No one shall dye their hair.
All skirts must extend five
centimeters below the kneecap.
And no running
in the hallways.'
Those sound like school rules.
Indeed, but not just any
school rules, ancient ones.
I think it's a student handbook.
What's the matter with him?
In order to find the
most powerful Rare Igura,
we must lay siege
to Vega once more.
We've come close,
but the Iguras brought
back have been insufficient.
The dimensional
transference either killed them
or rendered them sterile.
We must keep searching
for an answer.
Speaking for myself, I think
I'd be happy with just Alicia.
Jin, the fate of Altair hangs
in the balance of our actions.
The first signs were bad enough.
When baby girls stop being born
on your planet,
it gives one pause.
When women began
dying off in droves
from indeterminate causes,
the end of life
as we knew it seemed nigh.
Eventually only men
remained on Altair.
This is not a colonization
of Vega by any means,
we only want to ensure the
survival of our species.
For that to happen, we must find
the most powerful Rare Igura,
one strong enough
to survive
transdimensional travel.
She'll be our Eve, the bride
who will bear the next
generation of Altair.
Vega's definitely
the place to look.
There's a good chance our
savior pilots the Machine Angel.
I understand what needs
to be done, Commander.
I'll go down there
myself this time
instead of piloting it remotely.
As the last son of Altair,
no other choice
remains, Jin--duty calls.
I'll dial up the
optical sensors.
I think it's definitely best
if I focus on solid ammo,
so I don't end up
like last time.
I'd better take some
infiltrator shells too,
and I'll add heavy
armor just in case.
It's the perfect defense,
a flawless shield.
Man, I looked like a straight
up jack-ass today!
I dunno, an ancient
school handbook
from who knows how long ago?
That's a pretty decent find.
You're right,
we should totally donate it
to a Neo-Kowloon museum!
Who cares?
Those geezers from back
in the day were weirdos.
Who has rules about the
length of your hair and skirt?
You're wrong!
We can learn tons from
the annals of history.
In fact, if you
want my opinion,
think things are
just a little bit
too loosey-goosey
in the here and now!
Huh?
Your clothes are skanky.
They should not be
allowed in this school!
Don't you get tired
of boys perving
out on you all the time?!
Huh? I like my clothes.
Look at what you're wearing.
What do you think
the ancient texts have
to say about you
flaunting those beasts?
You may as well come to class
oiled up and ready to go!
Oiled up?
I suggest we stall our
backslide toward Gomorrah
by taking a page
from the ancients.
First off, Zessica, no more
gallivanting about like a madam!
Man, why'm I being punished
'cause I'm fashion forward?
Hey Amata. Tell the truth,
is my outfit too much?
Well uh, it's not
my place to say.
I mean, um--
Seems somebody knows
how to get our boy up.
What do you think, Shush?
Is it me?
I mean, guys like girls
who wear skimpy clothing
like this, right?
Wow, feeling a bit naughty, eh?
Zessica!
Let me see.
I like it but you could
show a little more skin.
Don't be afraid to flaunt it.
No way, I'm not like you,
all right?!
Abductors have been
detected in Neo-Kowloon!
Here I am, you son of a bitch.
Come and get me.
We need to act fast before
he launches an attack.
Why do I get the feeling he's
not here to abduct anyone?
Zen, if it's not an abduction,
what could it be?
The Heavy Armor Radius
Gnis comes to make war.
Send out Aquarion now!
Amata at the head, Zessica
and Mikono, you're with him!
Mikono?
Why her?
No way; I can't go.
Come on!
Vector Z, ready for launch!
Vector Y, ready for launch!
Vector X, ready as I'll ever be!
The enemy Abductor's up ahead!
Get ready, Mikono,
we're almost there!
Defensive Merge! Go! Aquarion!
Aquarion Evol!
Amata, what am I supposed to do?
Just follow my lead.
This ends today!
You hear me, ugly bastard?!
Infinity punch!
This guy's tough.
Oh, I learned my lesson
from the first time
you used that trick.
You gotta vary it up.
These kids are the
Rare Iguras? Impossible.
Compared to Silvie
these wimps are nothing.
Damn you, Jin!
Don't you touch her!
Mikono belongs to me!
Me, you son of a bitch!
Ahh, screaming is such
a plebian method
of communication.
A touch more civility,
if you please.
Give over to the jealousy.
Feel it with every fiber
of your being, Kagura.
Wallow in the pain of having
the one you love stolen.
Drink it all the way down.
If you're the best
they have to offer,
let's see what you're made of.
No effect on Aquarion's
external armor!
But it is affecting
the Elements!
That's not good.
What is happening?
He's using Infiltrator ammo,
kicking up violent shockwaves.
Basically destroying
Aquarion from the inside.
Help her!
Their aura levels
are dropping rapidly, sir.
The merge is falling apart!
No!
Don't look away.
Internalize every
moment of this.
I want you to watch Jin violate
your precious bitch
right under your nose.
Stop this! Stop this!
Beyond pathetic.
There's no way in hell
one of these nothings
could possibly be our True Eve.
The Element suits have
been heavily damaged!
If we don't do something,
the shock'll
go right through the suits and
tear their bodies to shreds!
Mikono! I will not
let this happen.
Put me in right now!
High Commander! C'mon!
Zessica, watch your six!
Whoa! What was that?!
That was so weird.
I could feel the
missiles on my skin.
What's going on up there?
How odd. What could
it possibly mean?
Without the constricting
burden of clothing,
the senses become
stronger, more acute.
Remove your suits
and let nakedness rivet
you to the pulse of life!
The newfound freedom
will allow you
to sense your enemy's moves
with utmost precision.
Hold on, you're saying
the fewer clothes
I'm wearing the better I'll
be at dodging his attacks?!
We can't pilot these naked!
This is no time to
be a prude, Mikono!
Zessica?!
Well, here goes nothing!
Whoa, Mikono's doin' it too?
Mikono and Zessica's
mind levels are rising!
Both Vectors are primed
and ready to merge!
Now! Merge away!
Zessica, you're the head!
Unguarded Merge! Go! Aquarion!
Wow, my skin is so sensitive!
This feels amazing!
It's so intense!
Aquarion Spada!
I can feel Amata looking at me.
Act normal. Don't freak out.
Mikono's mind level
is still on the rise, sir!
What? But why?
She knows someone's
looking at her
so her body's getting
all hot and bothered.
I can relate.
Oh, don't worry.
There's no need to
be embarrassed at all.
Am I supposed to be afraid
'cause you decided
to merge again?
Just give up and admit defeat!
Hell no!
I can sense his every move.
The moment
he thinks it, I feel it!
How did they evade that?
Clothes off!
Strip down!
Zessica's aura is soaring.
It's about to go off the charts!
Take this, jerk!
Okay, here I go!
They make such a
beautiful music.
One that eludes me. Brava.
We are born without
clothing on our backs,
and we are made
to fight that way!
Let your skin set aboil.
Let your body be free!
No clothes!
No guard!
Attack!
Game over for me.
How did I lose to these
assholes? This is crap!
Yeah!
I'm sorry!
Why do I feel so embarrassed?
I don't understand.
Effective defense
is a good offense.
Always. Letting your guard
down is the ultimate weapon.
That was disgusting
and I will not stand for it!
It's a universal truth.
We're all born the
same way. Naked.
Sound as that strategy may be,
it's a double-edged sword.
In exchange for perfect senses,
Elements give up their defense
and leave themselves
fully exposed.
Speaking of exposed,
I believe it's best we put
our clothes back on for now.
These pics... how in the
world did you take these?!
Umm, here's
five hundred kowloons.
Enjoy!
Wait, how much?!
Put me down for one!
Me too!
Stop it! You're forbidden to
sell those, you understand me?!
Step right up!
Hey, Zess.
What're you doing
over here by yourself?
Uh, nothing. Gotta run!
Say the word "holy" ten
times as fast as you can.
Holy--holy--holy--holy--holy--
holy--holy--hole-- hole--hole!
Argh! Holes are for filling in!
Next time on Aquarion Evol:
"Anagram of Man and Woman!"