[SHRADE] The ultimate stage...
I hear it calling out to me.
[SHRADE] This new melody...
This new voice...
They'll be perfect for
the final movement!
But I need more...!
Keep playing, Aquarion,
and don't ever stop!
[CAYENNE] This energy...
Where's it coming from...?!
It's so intense!
[SAZANKA] Beautiful...
So elegant and delicate...
But forceful and passionate too!
Like its rhythm is
drumming on my heart...!
I've never felt this way before!
[SUOMI] Shrade's...
not wearing a suit...
His body's completely exposed.
That's how he's able to
engage his surroundings.
[DONAR] Good point...
But at the same time,
it means his body
is taking more damage.
He's seriously risking
his life out there.
[CREA] Oh, Shrade.
[SHRADE] Let my heart play...
This is its greatest
cadenza yet!
[KAGURA] What
I saw wasn't fiction.
It was real...
You're me... I'm you.
[KAGURA] Makes
perfect sense, really...
Explains why I wasn't
able to smell you.
[KAGURA] Our scent
is exactly the same.
[KAGURA] This picture
showed me everything
I needed to know...
Don't you see...?
[KAGURA] In the beginning...
...you and me?
We were one person.
[KAGURA]
'Til that fateful day.
[YOUNG AMATA] Hang on!
Wait...! Please!
Tell me where you're going!
[KAGURA] Remember now...?
You just watched as fate
slipped through your fingers.
You've always
been a coward.
[KAGURA] No better
today than you were then.
You can't do anything
when it really counts...!
Yer friggin' pathetic.
[AMATA] I'm pathetic?
What does that make you...?!
You were just as much a
failure at saving Mom as me...!
You were on Altair with her...!
What have you been
doing all this time?!
[KAGURA] I did make
it across dimensions...
True... Mom though,
didn't do so hot.
[KAGURA] I was alone...
But not for long.
[MIKAGE] Welcome,
frightened one...
Dark one...
A pleasure to make
your acquaintance.
[MIKAGE] Here in this
arbor, for all time...
I christen thee Kagura.
[KAGURA] Mikage raised me...
If you can call it that.
[KAGURA] I'm not broken up
about losing Mom anymore...
Never even knew
who the woman was...
Same story with our dad.
[KAGURA] There's only
one thing I care about...
And that's the
scent of my bitch!
[KAGURA] The real Silvie!
[AMATA] Damn you,
I am not a coward!
And there's no way I'll
let you have Mikono...!
You hear me?!
[KAGURA] You've
always been pathetic.
[KAGURA] You'll never
be good enough!
[MIKONO] No, stop!
Why are you two fighting?
I mean it... Stop...! Right now!
[FUDO] The moment's come at
last...
Solar Wing has awoken.
[MIKONO] Huh?
[choral music]
[AMATA] Aaaauugh!!
[KAGURA] What's the
matter, Amata...?
You say you're not a coward,
so why don'tcha man up?!
[loud rumbling]
[KAGURA] The hell?
[AMATA] Mikono!
[KAGURA] Silvie!
[CAYENNE] Mikono?!
[CAYENNE] That was Aquarion.
[SUOMI] We need a
status update, now!
[YUNOHA] Detecting high
quantum emissions...
They're coming from somewhere
near the former lake area!
[loud coral music]
[beeping alarms]
[SAZANKA] What the
heck do those mean?
[CAYENNE] It looks like Aquarion
is resonating with that thing.
[SHRADE] It's an
ancient melody...
One that's being heard
for the first time in
twelve thousand years.
[DONAR] What the--?
[CREA] There's no
other possibility...
It has to be true.
From the myths of old, this
is the Legendary Aquarion!
[MIKAGE] Solar Wing...
At long last, you
finally show yourself.
[MIKONO] Where am I?
[MIKONO] Aquarion?
[MIKONO] But it's...
different...
[AMATA] Mikono! Mikono!
[MIKONO] Amata, hey...
[KAGURA] Silvie!
[KAGURA] I've yearned
for you for so long...
For twelve thousand years,
I've been waiting...!
But you're here now
and I can finally kill you!
[AMATA] Wait, kill her,
that's what you want?!
[KAGURA] You bet your
ass that's what I want!
With every fiber of my
being I want her dead...!
Over and over and over again!
[KAGURA] But
first thing's first...
Amata... I'm gonna
tear you to shreds!
[KAGURA] Don't worry, Silvie...
I'll take care of
this waste o' space...
then we can kill each
other all night long!
[MIKONO] Wait... What?
[AMATA] I'm not
gonna let you lay
one damn finger on her!
[CIERRO] Higher-dimensional
quantum emissions
are still rising, sir!
[DONAR] Guess that settles it...
It's the real deal for sure!
[YUNOHA] Aquarion...?
The first one?
[MALLOY] All of the old
stories are coming to life.
[ANDY] Yeah right...?
History's going down right now
and we're here to
see it in person.
[DONAR] You're right...
This is a momentous occasion.
So why's the kid messing
around out there?
[FUDO] That's history too,
and a legend in itself.
[SUOMI] High Commander Fudo...!
When did you get back?!
[FUDO] Their lovers' spat...
Is not your concern!
[MIKONO] Amata!
[AMATA] No...!
I won't let you take her!
[KAGURA] Just give up...
This is something
that's been destined
to happen for twelve
thousand years...
You and Silvie were
simply never meant to be.
You can't stop fate...
No matter how
much you fight it...
Take us.
Against all reason,
fate brought you and I
together from
across the multiverse.
[AMATA] You're wrong...
With my wings,
I can overcome anything!
[KAGURA] What good
are your wings gonna do
if you can't fly...?
Go on... Fly away if you can!
[MIKONO] Stop this...!
Whatever you do, just
don't hurt Amata anymore!
[KAGURA] I hate that
smile of yours, Silvie...
Makes me wanna
kill you even more...!
Come on... Keep smiling...
Do it...! Smile!
[ZESSICA] Where am I?
[ZESSICA] What is
this place...? Am I dead?
[ZESSICA] Amata!
[AMATA] Zessica...!
You sure are a
sight for sore eyes!
[ZESSICA] I feel the same...!
But... Why are you here...?
Did you come back 'cause
you were worried about me?
[AMATA] Yeah, I get it...!
I finally understand...
I realize now what's
precious to me.
[ZESSICA] Amata.
[AMATA] Come now...
Time to wake up.
[AMATA] I can't
let you die on me...
Not yet anyway-
[MIKAGE] The time
draws nigh for you
to deliver on your promise...
Whether you wish it or not.
[ZESSICA] No!
[MIKAGE] I forbid you to die...
You swore a vow,
and freedom shant be yours
'til you uphold your
end of the bargain.
[ZESSICA] What bargain?
[MIKONO] Please, will you
both just cut it out?!
[MIKONO] Why are you doing this?
The last thing I want
is for you two to fight!
[AMATA] Sorry,
but I won't stop...
I'm gonna put an end
to this thing right now!
[KAGURA] Oh yeah...?
And how are you gonna do that?
[AMATA] You want
Mikono for yourself
because you believe
you're destined
for each other, am I right?
[KAGURA] Well... look
who's starting to catch on.
[AMATA] Destiny... is crap!
I don't care if Mikono is
the reincarnation of Silvie!
I don't care what
anyone thinks about
what happened 12,000 years ago!
I don't... at all...
All I know is I love her!
[MIKONO] Amata.
[ZESSICA] Amata?
[AMATA] That's right...
You heard me...
I love her... I love Mikono!
[KAGURA] Then let's find out
which one of us is stronger...
Me with destiny on my side
or you with your
burning emotions...
Only one of us is gonna survive!
[MIKONO] Amata, no!
[KAGURA] What the hell's this?
[KAGURA] Solar Wing!
[AMATA] You will not beat me!
No way in hell!
[SHRADE] I'm getting so close...
I hear the melody
I've been searching
for my whole lif--!
[CAYENNE] Oh shit!
[SAZANKA] Shrade!
[CAYENNE] Shrade...!
Talk to us... C'mon, man!
[SHRADE] That unearthly music...
It's... the sweetest
sound I've ever heard!
[KAGURA] Oh crap, Silvie!
[AMATA] Mikono!
[CIERRO] Shrade's vital
levels are dropping fast!
If he keeps fighting
he's not gonna make it,
we gotta stop this!
[DONAR] Emergency
Element change...!
Now! Yunoha, you're going in!
[SHRADE] Wait a second.
[SHRADE] Don't take
me out, I can do this...
Just a little bit longer!
I'm almost there... Almost...
[CREA] Element Change, hurry...!
Right now!
[YUNOHA] Yunoha Suroor...
Ready for combat!
[KAGURA] Not so fast!
[EI] The Aquarion's
higher-dimensional
quantum emissions
are beyond our
ability to measure!
[CREA] Zen...
I certainly hope you're planning
to tell me what your goal is...
Everything that's
happening here:
was it all foretold
in the Book of Genesis?
[FUDO] True legends
can only be created
by great and noble people.
Spilled blood is
the ink with which
they're written down
for posterity's eyes.
[CREA] So you're saying
you won't stop them?
[FUDO] There is no difference
between moving and stopping.
[FUDO] When you clap
your hands together
what remains between
them is nothingness.
A vacuous, empty space. Nil.
[FUDO] But sometimes...
Nothingness is deceptive...
For example, the sum zero
is obtained by adding
a positive and a negative of
equal value together...
Such is Mikono Suzushiro's
power of connection...
[MIKAGE] Dark and light...
Holy and unholy...
Good and evil...
Positive and negative.
[MIKAGE] Let the memories
that were once locked
away, be released...
And the infinite power of zero
be sprung upon
reality once and for all.
[FUDO] At this moment...
a brand new history blooms
before our very eyes!
[CAYENNE] Holy--
[YUNOHA] What's happening?!
[MIKAGE] Come to me, my love!
Come to me, Solar Wing!
[AMATA] The Legendary
Aquarion, no!
[MIKONO] Amata!
[KAGURA]
That's our cue, bitch...
Gate's wide open.
[CIERRO] Commander...!
Both Abductors--and the
Legendary Aquarion--
have entered the
dimensional warp gate!
[SHRADE] Please...
I am begging you...
One more time...
You've got to
let me back out there.
[CREA] Sorry, but no...
You will die if I allow that.
[SHRADE] You must have known
since you brought
me to Neo-DEAVA...
You must have sensed it
from the very beginning.
You knew it would
end this way for me.
[CREA] Just promise
me one thing...
When you complete your song...
You must swear that
you'll let me hear it.
[AMATA] I'm coming, Mikono!
[AMATA] Shrade?!
[EI] Both vectors have
entered the dimension gate...
We've lost contact!
[AMATA] I don't see
either one of 'em!
[SHRADE] Amata!
[SHRADE] In order to finish
composing the final song...
I've got to take back
the Legendary Aquarion!
[AMATA] We can't
take him on alone!
[ZESSICA] Trust me,
Amata, you're not alone!
[AMATA] Zessica...!
You're alive!
[ZESSICA] This is it...
This is how I can
show my love for him!
[SHRADE] Destiny Merge...
Gooo... Aquarion!
[ZESSICA] Amata!
[AMATA] Thank you... Zessica.
[SHRADE] My soul is vibrating!
[SHRADE] Aquarion... Spada!
[AMATA] Where did it go?
[SHRADE] I have you now.
[AMATA] Oh, man.
[SHRADE] Now: Time
to repent your sins...
Crucifixion Sword!
[ZESSICA] Oh, no!
[TECH A] Gate is opening!
The Mithra Gnis is
now coming through...!
Sensors show a
Rare Igura on board!
[IZUMO] The Rare Igura Kagura's
been after all this time...
Is she the True Eve
we've been searching for?
[IZUMO] Prepare for attack!
[IZUMO] If she is
in fact the one,
we can't let Kagura in
his madness destroy her!
[CIERRO] We're getting
reports of abnormal weather
and tectonic movement
all over the world!
[FUDO] As foretold, the seal
on the Legendary Aquarion
has been lifted.
The tenuous balance
it maintained
between Altair and Vega
has now shifted irrevocably.
[DONAR] We've lost contact
with the Elements, Commander...
The Legendary Aquarion has
slipped through our fingers...!
Damn! There's nothing
more we can do!
We're helpless here!
[SUOMI] What's going to happen
to the rest of
the world, Commander?
[FUDO] Never forget,
there is always hope.
This is no exception...
The Wings of the Sun
will never move
in the absence of
its chosen Element.
[MIKAGE] The moment
is finally upon us.
[MIKAGE] It's time to fulfill
the promise you made to me...
Your precious
covenant has come due.
[MIKAGE] Shall I regale you
with what moves my fancy...?
Orchid petals
scattered underfoot
and Kagura's baleful screams...
Shall I tell you
what I despise...?
Betrayals... And the liars
who perpetrate them...
And of course, him.