Tell me, Apollon,
do you remember?
The day when the world began,
there was nothing and
there was everything.
Billions of stars swirling in
a great void, light
inside of darkness.
Our souls knew each
other even then.
Our souls?
Yes.
High above it all, captivated by
the vision, your hand in mine.
Two wayward souls,
sharing one heart.
Silvie.
And now, together, we will
mend what we have broken.
You never get
tired of this, huh?
Er--sorry! I got distracted.
I'm on task, I swear--
You and Skies of Aquaria
were made for each other.
It's fine. 'sides, you're the
only reason we show it anymore.
Your scent, your essence
follows me into Eternity!
One day you'll have to
tell me what the appeal is.
Apart from Alicia, that I get,
her Silvie almost
makes this watchable.
She doesn't do anything;
just hovers there.
What is going through her head?
The man she loves is dying.
Probably thinkin'
the rent's due.
Listen, don't worry about
loadin' the reels, awright?
Just clean the
aisles 'fore you go.
And, try not to let the silver
screen spoil ya for real life.
Yes, sir.
I shall wait for you,
my brave Apollon.
For twelve-thousand years,
if I must. If I must...
Ugh, gross. Really?
How hard is it to
find a trashcan, people?
Excuse me. We're, uh...
Oh! I, uh... Sorry, leaving.
Hang on!
You're not like a fan, are you?
I mean of Skies of Aquaria?
I dunno. It was the first
time I've seen it actually.
Oh, um, never mind.
See ya 'round, I guess.
No wait!
I was kinda hoping you
might tell me your name.
If you're cool with that.
It's Mikono. Mikono Suzushiro.
Amata! I'm Amata Sora!
Huh, okay.
So...
Yeah?
It's, uh, real nice
to see some people still
care about old movies.
Question... Do you guys have,
like, pamphlets on this one?
Yeah sorry, no.
All the promotional
stuff was trashed.
Pretty much right
after the premier.
Oh. Well that's a shame.
I suppose there's always
still word of mouth, huh?
Maybe you and I could sit
and talk about it for a while.
You actually wanna talk to me?
It's gonna be a little while;
I have to finish up here.
I'm okay to wait,
long as you don't mind me
just hanging out
"for twelve-thousand years,
if I must," or whatever.
I'm a nerd, sorry--it was
just a neat line, you know?
Oh, crap! No!
No, no, no, no, no!
Uh would you mind
waiting outside?
Just so I can close up.
Give me, like, five minutes.
Ten, tops.
Surely three per
boot'll be enough.
Wow. She wants to talk.
And she's cute, so
I'm probably just dreaming.
Hang on! Wait! Please!
Tell me where you're going!
All I could do was
watch, same as her.
But that was then and
this is now. So, yeah.
Don't freak out. It's fine.
Not every girl's gonna leave.
I'm okay to wait, long
as you don't mind me just
hanging out "for
twelve-thousand years,
if I must," or whatever.
Excuse me! Dibs on your gondola!
Neo-China's teetering
infrastructure was further
compromised this afternoon
when a fleet of Abductors
swept down from the skies
in what authorities are...
I hate it when they
talk about Abductors.
Yeah, no kidding.
There's never any
good news to begin with,
but now that
everyone's being taken,
there's not much
else to talk about.
And the worst part's
gotta be not knowing
where they'll strike.
We beat 'em back,
sure, but, it's kinda like--
Well, I'm not just
gonna hide while I wait
for them to
gatecrash again.
If today's all I have,
why not enjoy it?
Like there's no tomorrow, huh?
Seems sorta appropriate,
don't you think?
You okay?
The hell is that?!
Sorry! My fault!
I really shoulda
warned you about Shush.
Seriously, what is it
about kitties and hair?
Wait, that's a cat?
Yeah, what else?
Did something
happen to it, or...?
I found him as I took
cover from an Abductor.
Poor lil' guy...
Oh, right! Let's talk
Skies of Aquaria.
You got it.
Skies of Aquaria: adapted
from a book no one remembers
about humanity's war
with the Shadow Angels
twelve thousand years ago.
Weren't the Shadow Angels
just a story to make
little kids behave?
That's part of why the
movie didn't do so hot
when it came out;
but the theme song won
like every award there is.
Yeah? It is a really good song.
The lead sang it. What's
her name? Alicia, I think.
Total triple threat.
She could act and sing,
and pretty enough
to model if she got
sick of doing those.
Yeah. She was beautiful.
It has a weird way
of making me sad.
We were supposed to
share that! Dang it, Shush!
Hey, you wanna know
something else weird?
Vector pilots, the guys
that fight Abductors,
you practically have
to be superhuman just
to get accepted into
where they're trained.
They're called Elements:
people with special powers
hand-picked by the
Aquarias themselves.
Least that's what they say.
Reminds me of
Apollon and Silvie.
Imagine sitting at the controls
of a mech that chose you.
I'd be lying if I said
I hadn't thought about it.
But, let's just say I'm not the
kind of guy who gets chosen.
I'm a nobody.
That a fact? Hey, me too.
All I'm good for is
staying out of the way.
Oh well! Guess that
makes two of us!
Uh, gotta make a pit stop.
Go on ahead, I'll catch up.
I know you can hear me, Kagura.
This is no time for games.
The Mithra Gnis is a test model.
No frills. Strictly recon.
Ooo. Something's pungent.
Hello Vega.
Ten? Really? This is
getting out of hand.
"Only good for
staying out of the way."
She makes it sound like a game,
like being a nobody is
just something you do.
How is she so cheerful?
How can you take so long?
Dad, I gotta go!
Make him come out!
Sorry! Gimme a sec!
I said gimme a sec, jeez!
What the...?!
Not now!
Mikono!
We gotta get to the shelter!
Look out!
Whoa. It's an Aquaria.
I swear, dude, every time.
Why do these freak shows
gotta be so damn persistent?
Doesn't really
concern you, Andy.
They show up,
we give 'em the hurt.
Type M is on the scene, sir.
Roger that.
May the legend guide
our hand in this battle.
The Abductors have brought
quite an entourage
with them this time.
I'm getting reports of heavy
damage at ground zero.
Chief Instructor--apologies;
Commander...
Against a fleet of this size,
do you think these boys
are our wisest option?
Of course you'd go there,
and I suppose your little ladies
are models of discipline?
We've got a massive Abductor
bearing down on the site.
A type the database
doesn't recognize.
Show us!
What the hell?!
Simulation didn't
cover this one!
Ah, damn!
It's fast, like,
seriously fast. What do we do?
Keep it together,
Malloy: I'm thinking.
We're, uh, picking up vital
signs from the Abductor's core.
What?
Someone's inside that thing!
You're trying to tell me
this one's got a pilot?
You son of a--
It's dancing circles
around these guys.
Yeah, right?
Like it's toying with them.
This is bull!
The Vectors are taking
heavy damage, sir!
Tachyon levels dropping!
Chief Instructor--
uh... Commander!
Yes, sir, loud 'n clear.
We'll make it so.
We're authorized
to deploy Type F.
You've got to be joking!
Surely they can't mean to let an
F and an M operate in tandem!
Damn right!
It's forbidden for a reason!
Our Type M is on
the verge of being torn
to shrapnel out there, damn it.
We're not letting that happen.
Damn it!
Target acquired!
Missiles, locked on!
Shit! What the--?
Hiya, fellas, don't mind us.
Just here to save ya.
No offense or anything,
but you fight like savages.
Scale it back on the
testosterone, guys.
Cayenne! I'm your biggest fan!
Whoa! Hello nurse!
Um, is this supposed to
be happening?
This is gonna be catastrophic.
Let's hope we avoid the worst.
You realize if they
merge it'll be blasphemy.
I'm well aware of
what the sacred texts
say about cross-gender
union, Donar.
But worry not; the Guize stones
will see to their purity.
They'll be kept separate!
Oh, man, heh. Somebody's scent
here is raising my hackles.
We'll snare him
in a pincer attack!
And you get to
call the shots why?
Damn it! Hold still!
Come on!
We can handle this
if you'd back off!
You're crowding us!
This is an absolute farce.
What did we expect?
None of them thought they'd
be working coed this afternoon.
What kind of move is that?!
Mix, take us down!
Copy that!
Mikono? Are you alright?
Amata! You're...
Yeah I know.
But...
I'm fine. Just a scratch.
No worries.
A little blood I can do without,
but you're a whole other story.
Type M, you read me?
A little help?
Yeah, about that...
We're, kinda out of commission
till Malloy springs back.
Figures. How'd you
pass the prelims?
Look!
It's on all fours!
That bouquet...
What is it doing?
Animal.
Mikono!
Stop trying to move!
You're hurt enough as it is!
Mikono!
Vector pilot auras are
dropping rapidly, sir!
Damn it!
The formations are breaking up!
Those poor Aquarias.
All right, fine.
No more holding back.
Oh, Mix! Sazanka!
Andy!
Damn you! Who gave
you the order to bail?!
Wha...? Nobody, sir!
Something just
pulled me out of there!
I'm fine. Send me back in!
We didn't pull you...
Unheard of.
Why would the Aquarias suddenly
jettison their Elements?
Sorry, I have to do this.
Uh, wait, why are you sorry?
Believe me, all I was
trying to do was protect you.
I didn't...
I...
Hang on!
That can't be Solar Wing?!
Oh no!
Vector Z's giving off vital
signs. No idea how, but...
Someone's on board?
How is that possible?
We've got hijackers!
Wait, that's a girl
and guy, isn't it?!
Oh dear! Mix, eject them now!
Right!
Problem.
Apparently their life
force can't be extricated
from the Vector's
energy core.
Perhaps they were...
Perhaps they were chosen.
Commander!
Where are we?
I think we're inside a Vector.
Really?
Crazy, huh?
What are the chances?
But, it just feels right.
I- I think I know
what I have to do.
Then, go for it.
Awright, move in.
Yeah, I gathered that.
Shatter the false idol.
As it crumbles to dust,
speak truth to power.
Say the name,
and inherit a legend!
Truth to power.
What is that supposed to mean?
Its name. It's been
waiting for so many years,
waiting for us to say it.
Genesis Union! Go! Aquarion!
Did he say "Aquarion"?!
Surely he couldnt've.
This is big. That name's not
been uttered aloud in years.
Wait! Stop it!
We're not allowed to merge!
I-- This-- this is amazing...
Sir! What is going on here?
Tell me, please!
It's fine!
The Guize Stones are safe.
No one's merging with anyone.
I can't handle this!
This feeling, it's too much!
I'm gonna be torn apart!
What is this? What is this?!
Something inside me
is about to break!
This is happening!
What-- what am I looking at?
It's like it's evolving. Oh wow.
Aquarion Evol!
What is that?
Whatever you are. You reek.
An ancient name bears a
new form... Aquarion Evol!
Our time has come.
The first chord of the final
cadence has been struck.
This'll probably sound weird,
but when I make ramen
I let 'em boil way longer
than you're supposed to.
I dunno. I like
soggy noodles, okay?!
Next time on Aquarion Evol,
"Forbidden Union."