[CIERRO] Reports
of fault-line upsets
and record-breaking global
weather are still rolling in!
[CREA] Now that the Legendary
Aquarion's seal is broken,
the whole planet is being
thrown into utter chaos.
[DONAR] And we can't make
contact with the Elements...!
Our only option is sending
every machine we have to Altair!
[SUOMI] But how are
we going to do that?!
The dimension gate
has already been closed!
[ANDY] Let me punch
a hole through it.
[ANDY] I know Shrade's
not here to help,...
and I know it was kind
of an accident last time...
But I did it once.
I know I can do it again!
[CAYENNE] Andy... You're sure?
[ANDY] Damn right I am...!
If I can't, then every hole
I've dug's been for nothing.
Please, you gotta let me try!
[CREA] Dig, Andy W. Hall...
Dig like you've
never dug before.
[IZUMO] Curse you, Solar Wing...
You dare oppose me?
[IZUMO] Our only goal is
to secure the True Eve...
Do your best to
avoid the core units.
Disable his artillery!
[KAGURA] Good luck with that...!
Nothin' is gonna stop me!
[IZUMO] So this is the power
wielded by Solar Wing...
Damn him!
[IZUMO] With that
strength he could wipe out
a Gnis platoon
in one fell swoop.
I'll send it back
at you, amplified!
[MIKONO] Look out!
[KAGURA] Guess he
forgot I can just reverse it!
[IZUMO] It's not
affecting him at all...
His reversal power is so potent
it's canceling my attack!
[KAGURA] Get it through
your head; she belongs to me!
[IZUMO] That's not
your decision...
Get ahold of yourself;
what could she possibly
be worth to you?!
[KAGURA] We're meant
for each other...
I'll die before
I let you take her!
[IZUMO] A selfish
child as always!
[MIX] Help has
arrived, Commander!
[MIKONO] Wait a sec, is
that... No way...! Mix!
[MIX] I fly with Izumo...
He is the future of Altair.
[SUOMI] Be safe...
Come back home to us.
[MALLOY] Been a while since I've
merged with you guys!
[CAYENNE] Get ready, the
target's coming up!
[MALLOY] All right...
Let's get this done quick
with a Brutal Merge!
[CAYENNE] That's not
gonna cut it this time!
[CAYENNE] We need a
Hot-Blooded Warrior Merge!
[MALLOY] Go!
[ANDY] Aquarion!
[ANDY] Aquarion... Gepard!
[ANDY] Mix...
I don't care what's happened,
or what your body looks
like, I'm coming for you,
and nothing anyone
can do will stop me!
[ANDY] C'mon... Haven't
I told you this before?
It's simple...
The reason holes are made is
to bring people closer together.
[ANDY] Well I'm digging
this one 'cause right now,
it's the only chance
I have to get to you.
And guess what...?
Once I find you,
I'll dig another one
straight to your heart!
[ANDY] A hole so big
I can bury myself in it!
[CIERRO] I... I think
we've got an opening!
[DONAR] Get in there
n' give 'em hell!
[ANDY] I'm on my way,
don't give up, Mix!
[MIX] What was that...?
Did somebody just say something?
No...! Must be losing my mind--
[KAGURA] Take that!
[MIKONO] Please stop!
I know the person
piloting that machine...!
That's Mix, she's my friend!
[KAGURA] Your friend?
[ZESSICA] Behind us!
[ZESSICA] Damn you... Izumo.
[MIKONO] Amata.
[ALICIA] Amata.
[ALICIA] Amata!
[AMATA] Who's there?
[ALICIA] Amata... Amata!
[AMATA] Where am I?
[ALICIA] Amata.
[KAGURA] Stay outta this!
[KAGURA] Reversal!
[MIX] Commander Izumo!
[KAGURA] This "friend" of yours
is a pain in the ass!
[KAGURA] Crush you!
[MIKONO] Don't hurt her!
[MIX] Where did they come from?!
[KAGURA] The hell?
[MIKONO] Wait,
that's Aquarion Gepard!
[MALLOY] It looks like we landed
right in the middle of it, huh?
[CAYENNE] Two Abductors
and the Legendary Aquarion,
but who's piloting 'em?
[MIKONO] Cayenne...?
Is that you in there?!
[CAYENNE] Mikono...?!
Why are you with them?!
[ANDY] Mix!
[ANDY] Mix is in that
machine, you guys!
[CAYENNE] What
the hell's going on?
Someone talk to me!
[ZESSICA] Both of those
Abductors are after Mikono,
you have to stop them!
[CAYENNE] Tell me where
Amata and Shrade are!
[ZESSICA] Unfortunately,
we lost track of Amata...
And I'm sorry... Shrade is gone.
[ZESSICA] He played
out his final song
in the dimensional rift.
[CAYENNE] So...
that's what that was...
[CAYENNE] He's really gone.
[MIX] All who oppose
Izumo must die!
[ANDY] I don't
"oppose" anything...!
All I want is to take
you back with me!
[MIX] Take me back where?
[ANDY] Back home
where you belong...
You know me...
Don't you remember
Andy W. Hall?!
[MIX] Whoever the hell you
are just leave me alone!
[ANDY] Mix, no!
[IZUMO] How can you
remain so selfish...?
Altair is your home,
do you truly not give a damn?!
[KAGURA] That's your
home old man, not mine...!
All I care about
is my Silvie...!
You and your decrepit
planet can go straight to hell!
[KAGURA] I'll fight the
world before I quit her...
Even if it means I die trying!
[ANDY] Stop it, Mix...! It's me!
[IZUMO] All this over
a single Igura...
...a mere woman.
[IZUMO] Alicia.
[AMATA] This is it...
This is where the voice
is calling out to me from.
[ALICIA] Amata!
[AMATA] Mom, it's you...
[ALICIA] Amata.
[FUDO] A true miracle
is about to occur...
The planet, the land
and the life that sleeps
within it are all
about to awaken.
[FUDO] The rebirth of Solar Wing
was a double-edged sword.
[FUDO] Will it divide
the world into factions
of bitter opposition...?
Or unite us all in
a single embrace?
[ANDY] Please Mix... Come home!
[MIX] Spacial Augmentation!
[MALLOY] Not again!
[CAYENNE] How long are you
going to keep this up, Andy?
[ANDY] As long as it
takes to get her back...!
I make the holes
and she fills 'em in!
[ANDY] That's how
we've always done it,
and that's how we're
always gonna do it...!
Just like when we first met...
And when I realized
I was in love!
[MIX] Jackass...
Why does he keep doing the
same move over and over?
And why is this all so familiar?
[ALICIA] Amata... I've waited so
long to see you.
[ALICIA] Look at how
much you've grown.
[AMATA] Why'd you abandon me?
I had nothing!
I was just a kid and you
left me to fend for myself.
[AMATA] And now you're just
laying there...
...making small talk?
[ALICIA] Amata.
[ALICIA] I've no right to ask
your forgiveness...
But there is something
you must know...
Something crucial.
[ALICIA] You deserve
to know the reason
I had to leave you...
And the truth... about
the man who sired you.
[ALICIA] He wasn't
from Vega as you and I.
[ALICIA] He's the
Commander of Altair...
Izumo Kamurogi.
[AMATA] Please tell
me you're joking.
[IZUMO] I am just as
resolute as you are...!
You will not win!
I will put an end to
the Curse of Eve
and rid Altair of this tragedy!
[ALICIA] It's true.
Your father came to Vega
in search of a woman
who was strong enough
to withstand
inter-dimensional travel.
[ALICIA] When I first met him,
I was working as an actress.
[IZUMO] My vessel malfunctioned
and I crash-landed on Vega...
She saved my life.
[IZUMO] From the
moment I first saw her,
I knew Alicia was the one...
She was the Rare Igura we'd
been searching for... But...
[ALICIA] We were also
the missing pieces
to one another's souls.
[ALICIA] It was destiny.
[IZUMO] I suppose I'm in
no position to judge Kagura...
I've been there myself...
I was ready to let Altair perish
for the love of one woman.
[IZUMO] I kept her a
secret from command,
and returned to
Altair in the hope
that everything
would work itself out...
But... Mikage
could not be fooled.
[ALICIA] He came back...
...several years later,
but by then,
you were already a toddler.
And then...
The day finally came
when your father
told me the whole truth...
about the Curse of Eve.
[ALICIA] I'll go.
[IZUMO] Are you sure...?
We have no idea what will happen
to a Rare Igura there...
It's dangerous!
[ALICIA] If it helps you,
I don't care that
it's dangerous...
I'm a hundred percent sure.
[IZUMO] Alicia.
[ALICIA] I agonized over whether
or not I should bring you...
but I couldn't...
Because if you
couldn't withstand
the interdimensional travel--
or if something
terrible befell you--
I never could've
forgiven myself.
[ALICIA] When I left you,
I never imagined we'd
be apart for so long...
I know that excuse
rings hollow now...
Nothing changes the fact
that I abandoned you.
I wanted to help save the
man I love's home world...
in honor of what he meant to me.
[AMATA] For all these years...
I've resented you.
[AMATA] But that's
over now. I'm done...
[AMATA] The real truth is...
I hated myself back
then... I was weak.
You were brave enough to go
after the person you loved.
But not me...
All I did was stand there.
[AMATA] I hope you
can forgive me... Mother.
[ALICIA] Amata.
[KAGURA] Just give
it up already, Izumo!
[IZUMO] I will never
surrender, Kagura...!
I refuse to let Alicia's
sacrifice be in vain!
[AMATA] The Legendary
Aquarion is fighting?!
[ALICIA] They both
want the girl...
Izumo and the other you.
[AMATA] Damn it! Kagura!
[IZUMO] Come to me, Iron Sea ...
Fill me with the power
I need to destroy him!
[MALLOY] Red strings...?
What the hell is this?!
[MIX] He's harnessing
all of Altair's power...
And he's channeling
it into the Ahura Gnis!
[IZUMO] Altair Cannon.
[IZUMO] Fire.
[KAGURA] Hang on.
[ZESSICA] That blast
contained the sum power
of the entire planet Altair...
[MIKAGE] How could you, Izumo?
[IZUMO] Consider that
one a warning shot...
Hand over the one
True Eve at once...
Or the next one's
between your eyes!
[MIKONO] Zessica?
[KAGURA] What the hell?
[IZUMO] Alicia, no!
[AMATA] Mother, no!
[AMATA] No...
[AMATA] Kagura!
[IZUMO] Alicia!
[KAGURA] What happened?
[ZESSICA] It's time.
[KAGURA] Here it comes...
Genesis Infinity... Punch!
[MIKAGE] Farewell, friend...
Time to say goodbye.
[IZUMO] Such immense power...
Mikage... This was
all your doing!
[KAGURA] No!
[KAGURA] Silvie!
[IZUMO] Alicia.
[AMATA] Easy...
[IZUMO] It's you.
[AMATA] I talked
to her... to Mom...
She told me the truth
about who you are.
[IZUMO] I see.
[IZUMO] Take me to Alicia...
I must see her once more.
[IZUMO] I know I cannot
ask your forgiveness...
I took your mother
away from you...
But I am truly sorry.
[AMATA] What are--?
[IZUMO] Mayflies...
I've only seen them once...
When I was little...
[IZUMO] They're extinct...
Their females died
off decades ago...
How in heaven's
name are they back?
[IZUMO] We're in Area 337...
Where Iron Sea's malfunctions
have been the most pronounced.
Could it be... that Iron Sea
itself caused the--?
[FUDO] Ever resourceful
Mother Gaia...
Goddess of Fertility.
The land that brings
forth the blessing
of the harvest is symbolized
by a feminine figure.
[FUDO] Male and female...
Plus and Minus...
Every aspect of creation,
great or small,
is ordered according
to these simple dualities.
From people to land...
From worlds to
the universe itself.
[IZUMO] Iron Sea functioned
by drawing energy
from the land; harnessing
its fertility...
It was never the intention,
but I'm afraid in doing this,
Iron Sea also compromised
the planet's ability to heal...
If that's the case...
Our hubris is at the
core of our suffering.
[IZUMO] Which means
that everything I fought for...
Was all for naught...
[AMATA] No...
You can't leave me yet!
Father! Father!
[ALICIA] It wasn't for nothing.
[AMATA] What is this?
[IZUMO] Alicia.
[ALICIA] Your life
meant something--
it wasn't for naught...
Look, we made a son
together, and he's alive.
He's not just the best of us,
he's the hope of two worlds.
[ALICIA] Amata...
You're the symbol of the
true love of your parents.
[ALICIA] But don't forget...
You must seek love as well...
Find the one...
The one more precious
to you than anything.
[AMATA] Mom, wait!
[AMATA] Don't go!
[KAGURA] Silvie...
You're my destiny...
I know who you really are,
who I really am...
And I love you...!
We belong together...!
I want to wrap myself
around you for all eternity!