[AMATA] Stop it...!
Fate's not the point...
All that matters
is who she is now.
You okay?
Fine... Yeah...!
'Cept, you'd think it was
a crime bein' late for lunch...
They forced me to
make do with leftovers.
Actually... Uh...
I was, um... kinda
thinkin' we should
probably talk about what
happened, you know?
I love you!
I mean... You understand, right?
Mikono and I...
I'm fine, okay?
I'm over it.
Girls like me...
We're used to coming
in second... Ciao!
Zessica! Hang on!
[AMATA]
Hey, Mikono.
Uh... I'm sorry.
Didn't mean to butt in.
[AMATA]
It's not like that!
We were just talking, I swear!
Mikono, please!
[CREA]
A sad harvest...
They've broken free
of the dusky clay...
Only to slouch
earthward as they ripen.
Alas, irony is
the harvester of all.
Well, 'least he's hot.
'Kay, look...
'bout this afternoon...
Pretty sure you got
the wrong impression
of what we were--
Yeah or maybe not...
Just forget it.
For the record, my sympathies
for both of you
are fairly limited...
"Love must yet be sin?"...
It's not just some
arbitrary law...
People could have died!
I suppose you're right.
Of course the flipside
to that little nugget
is something the
brass tends to overlook...
Namely, an army of lovers
would stomp the
opposition like grapes.
Yeah, but what is love?
Just a cruel trick played on us
by Mother Nature to
keep us sowin' our seed.
Romantic, Malloy.
You're talkin' about lust--
there's a difference!
Love is pure...!
Two souls entwined in a
cosmology all their own!
Hell, I'm not gonna lie, though;
under the circumstances...
seed-sowin'... would be nice...
[foreceful pioano music]
Emergency meeting?
[FUDO] Sorry to interrupt
your evening...
But missions of
vital import rarely
present themselves
at our convenience.
Or with discretion...
My hat is off sir,
to your sense of theatre.
So, uh... What're you
askin' us to do, exactly?
Dig, my boy...
Something special
waits to be uncovered.
Like, an artifact?
Classified.
'kay. Where's it at?
But... Literally dig?
Classified.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?!
[CREA] You'll be
leaving at first light.
We must keep you
in the dark for now...
But stiff upper lip...
This special
dossier will explain.
[FUDO] And mind, when
I say "classified,"
I do not mean "free for all."
Pardon... But this is...
I urge you to
overlook the crudeness
of your dossiers
and absorb the weight
of the message they convey,
difficult though that may be...
And above all else, remember:
The bananas are more
than they may seem.
Whoa-ho...! Gorgeous!
Settle down... We're
not on a field trip here.
So?!
[ANDY] This what we got
in the way of supplies?
Looks a little off
if you ask me.
What the...?!
[ANDY]
Seeds?!
Fascinating...
The breed must be uncultivated.
Bizarre fruit aside,
where exactly the
hell are we going?
I dunno...
Apparently the coordinates
have been preprogrammed...
We're all just along for the
ride.
You know where at least,
right Professor?
Unfortunately,
my only instructions
are to chaperone,
so I haven't a clue...
Not even Commander
Donar was given access
to the pertinent
details, I'm afraid.
Must be some real
cloak-and-dagger stuff.
So how are we supposed to know
what we're excavating,
or whatever it is?
Dude, hold the phone!
What if it's, like...
The original Aquarion?!
You mean like,
from the old stories?
Okay, for the sake of argument,
let's say you're right...
Can you imagine
what digging it up
is gonna unleash?
[MIKAGE] Follow the
breadcrumb trail, children.
Lead us to the witch's house.
[AMATA]
Seems like the kinda place
someone would've looked by now.
Well, I suppose in plain sight
is as good a
hiding place as any.
How the hell are we
gonna excavate a lake...?!
This is some bullshit, man!
I'm not a catfish!
[FUDO]
Instructions are forthcoming.
What?
[FUDO]
Consider yourselves at ease
until informed otherwise.
You heard the man.
[YUNOHA]
So just kick back and relax?
[MALLOY]
Sounds like it to me.
Okay... Now these
make sense... Take a look.
[AMATA]
Item checklist: swimsuits.
For those who didn't
read through the dossier,
a swimsuit will be provided...
For the moment put
yourselves on hold.
Banish thoughts of
war and take a dip.
Boys...! Kindly try not to ogle!
[MALLOY] Business on the
inside, party on the out.
Am I right, fellas...?
Nice change, prof.
[MALLOY] And don't even
get me started on Zess...
You wouldn't think she
could go skimpier, but damn.
Hello...! If this were the
school swimsuit issue...
Yeah...
Little Miss Women's Lib,
ironically enough,...
would be the cover girl.
[ANDY]
Wowza.
[MALLOY] All right, Mikono's
definitely rockin' the cute,
but uh...
Our shy little
number on the right?
Givin' her a good run.
Hel-lo...?
Jeez, what the hell
am I, chopped liver?!
[AMATA]
Mikono...
"I shall never see a
poem as lovely as a tree...
" Nature's symphony
is captivating...
N'est pas?
Might as well be jerkin' off.
[SHRADE]
We're following orders;
isn't that good
enough for you...?
Pastoral melancholy is wise.
Yeah, no...
Whatever the hell that's
supposed to mean,
dude, I'm not comforted.
Ready?
Please believe me
when I say this isn't
about the swimsuit...
But in ancient Greece,
Mix would've lived in a temple.
Yeah... Right next to Mikono...
Just look at her...
[ANDY]
Son of a bitch!
My wild oats are screaming!
Screw it...!
Opportunity's knockin'
and I'm startin' the tractor!
Service... Booya!
Oh, Andy!
Ow, easy...!
[MIX]
Yeah, yeah. Don't be a baby.
Nice bedside manner
you got there, doc...
At least a smack on
the head is nothing
compared to cupid's
arrow in your chest.
Wait, you got hit in the chest?
No, I'm just...
Being metaphorical.
You were hit hard...
I recommend you play it safe
and lie down for a bit.
Mix, wait!
The bedside manner crack...
I didn't really mean it.
Fact is... You're pretty
damn good at this.
[MALLOY]
Seriously.
She doin' bloodwork...?
What's takin' so long?
We should bring 'em
a couple of these.
Actually...
Might not be a bad idea
to give 'em a little
more time to themselves.
Speaking of which,
where the hell is Mikono?
Not sure...
Where's Zessica,
for that matter?
I am such an idiot.
What the...?
[MIKONO]
You don't mind
if I come be antisocial
with you, right?
I guess great minds
think alike, huh?
Here you go...
So you don't freeze.
[ANDY] Listen, I...
I realize you're gung ho
about love being
a sin and all...
But if I don't just...
say what I've gotta say,
I'm never gonna forgive myself.
Look,...
whatever you're talking
about, maybe this isn't--
Um... Andy?
Listen...
When all this business
with the Abductors
is done... Man...
I might as well be signing
my own death warrant,
saying this to you
of all people...
You know what: who cares...?!
When we've driven
the last of 'em back...
I want... I want
me and you to be...
To be... Son of a bitch...
[ANDY]
Say it, dumbass...!
You've got this!
Tell her there's
a hole in her heart;
tell her you know you're the
only man who can fill it,
and that your life won't
mean squat till you do!
Please... Andy...
[ANDY]
Mix!
Come on...!
Spit it the hell out...!
She needs to hear you say it!
You need to hear
yourself saying it!
Mix!
Yes?!
Please let me...
Lemme fill your hole!
Do what?
Please!
I'm begging you...!
Let me--
Oh shit!
Uhhh... Not what I meant!
I was talking about the hole in
your heart, I swear on my life!
[SAZANKA] Oh no, sounds
like trouble in paradise...
You're a... pig!!!
The one in your... heart.
[MIKONO] Okay, truth:
you'll think it's dumb,
but I've envied you
since my first day
at the Academy.
[ZESSICA]
What?
I mean, c'mon: look at you...
You always let everyone
know where they stand.
I could never have been
as straightforward
with Amata as you were.
I'm too self-conscious.
Just so you know,
I bottled it up a long time
before I finally
came out with it.
You shouldn't envy me...
Hell, take a look at yourself.
You're always
such a sweetheart...
I mean it...
A guy sees a girl like you
and says to himself:
there's one for the long haul.
Whatever...!
And I suppose you're not?
Guys fall all over themselves
trying to get to you!
I might be the one they
drool over for a while,
but you're the one they wind up
moving heaven and earth for.
See... You just bring
that quality out
in guys--in all of us, really.
Zessica...
What the--?!
[MIKONO]
That's not good.
Oh, no...! A Dimension Gate!
Amata...! Help me get
the vectors back online!
Right, let's go!
Why would the Abductors
come out this far?! Andy!
Way to go, genius.
Way to piss all over
your shot at love.
Stupid. Freaking. Moron...
Do everyone a favor: just
crawl into a hole and die.
I've got a confirmed
Dimension Gate
opening in outlier quadrant ANH!
[DONAR]
Why is it a morgue in here?
Where the hell is everyone...?!
Somebody explain this, now!
[CREA]
It's all right, Commander Donar.
[DONAR] Really? Because to
me this looks like
the exact opposite
of "all right!"
[MIKONO]
What kind of Abductor is that?!
[ZESSICA]
Let's not wait n' find out!
Andy!
Andy! What are you doing...?!
Snap out of it...!
This is not the
time or the place!
Yeah, I know...
It's not the time or place
and it's never gonna be.
What?
Deep Winter Merge...
Go...! Aquarion!
[CAYENNE]
Aquarion... Gepard!
Here's the plan:
we'll take out the freak show...
Shrade,... you take care
of everyone on the ground.
Right... I'm on it.
So cold.
Not that any of us is made
for this weather,
but this is balls.
I want everybody to take shelter
in the hole Andy's dug...
At the very least,
we'll be out of this wind.
Do you think this blizzard
is the Abductor's doing?
We're gonna be fine.
Trust me... Amata
won't let us freeze.
Damn it! We need
our Element Armor!
I can't get the heat to come on!
Oh man... I can't take this.
I'm glad we're out of the wind,
but how far down's
this thing go?
I don't like this...
[MIX]
Andy...
[ANDY] It's over...
Goodbye cruel world.
Andy's aura, sir...!
It's about to go flatline!
Excellent timing. Andy...!
You are hitting
rock bottom, my boy!
Go! Go one further!
[ANDY]
'Kay where am I...?
Bravo. Music so sublime,
the earth weeps.
[DONAR]
What the hell...?
[CREA]
A proud harvest, I'd say.
[FUDO] The seed reaches ever
upward through the clay...
Its fruit blooms, falls,
and roots in richer soil...
Thus the cycle
of life rolls on...
Thus the earth thrives!
Damn...! It's so cold!
Oh crap...!
Please not a flood!
Hey, this feels nice.
Why does it smell
like sulphur...?
Is this from a hot spring
or somethin'...? Whoa!
What the...?!
Ah...! Precious warmth!
Sorry! My bad!
Zessica?!
And Mikono...?
Amata?
Coed Bathhouse Merge...!
Go...! Aquarion!
I... I'm surging upward!
Up through the soil!
The sun's kissing my face!
[AMATA]
Aquarion Evol!
[SUOMI] The ancient alchemists
wrote in secret scriptures,
often in peril of
their own lives,
that an aggregate
of anima and animus,
male and female,
yielded spiritual
riches beyond compare.
The Elements are forging
just such a compound;
Aquarion is their crucible.
Well done...
High Commander Fudo,
you are a certifiable genius!
I think I get the bath part...
But explain the
metric ton of bananas.
Time was, shamans
in tropical climates
brandished them as totems of
fertility.
That they did...
As mystics in harsher climes
told in their midrashim
of the serpent tempting Eve
with the selfsame bounty.
Behold the fruit of Eden,
ladies and gentlemen;
the light worshiper.
As it ripens,
in unmitigated zeal
for the gift of life,
it hails to the sun.
[MIKONO]
This feels wonderful!
[ZESSICA] Like light is
coursing through my body!
Warm it up!
[DONAR]
What is that?!
Heh... The peel has been shed.
[AMATA and ALL]
Cluster Infinity Punch!
[ALL]
Break him!
Good job!
[ANDY]
I meant... I meant...
the hole in your heart...
[MIKAGE] A fragment of
Solar Wing laid bare...
Yet only a fragment.
Where, I wonder,
have you buried the rest?
[FUDO]
Have as many totems of fertility
as your wounded heart can stand.
Alas... They are totems only.
[ZESSICA]
What's up, gingersnap?
Oh, hey!
[AMATA]
Whoa... What's with the...?
[EI]
Oh wow... What are you wearing?
[SAZANKA]
Do you feel all right?
[ZESSICA]
Mmm...
I just figured it was,
time for a change.
Oh, yeah... while
I'm thinkin' 'bout it...
Your man...?
Totally turned me down.
Which is what we want...
Can't run the risk of Aquarion
going berserk on us, right...?
Truth is, it's a hard world...
It doesn't have much use
for a heart that isn't broken.
[ZESSICA] Sometimes, it's like
I don't know myself anymore.
Ugh. That's lame.
I'm a smoldering-hot,
tough-as-nails badass!
Always have been.
Always will be...
Except... What does
that mean anymore???