Feeling better, I hope.
Yeah, I am, as a matter
of fact. Thank you.
What the...?
Mikono's in the tower! Oh shit!
Calling all Elements...
Abductors detected in
the Neo-Kowloon district.
All training exercises
are suspended
pending further notice.
Elements Andy,
Zessica and Cayenne:
report back to Neo-DEAVA
headquarters immediately.
Go on, best not to
keep them waiting.
I'll stay and see to Mikono.
You should probably
go with Cayenne.
If you think I'm going anywhere
with my sister's life hangin'--
Her life is not a priority.
Your duty to ward off
Abductors, however, is.
Hey! Wait up!
Right--off you go.
As rare a species of untrammeled
beauty your union will be,
I pity that I cannot
be part of it.
Hey, sweetheart.
You reek.
You stink like carrion.
No! Mikono!
This is outrageous!
Indeed, even worse...
it bodes an unresolved tone.
Mikono!
Huh... s'like you're
made of porcelain.
You let her go, right now!
What're you supposed to be?
You don't have a scent.
How is that possible?
Everyone has a scent.
What are you,
some kind of hologram?
Meh. Whatever.
So, boy, mind if
I tear ya to shreds?
Um, well yeah, actually.
Too bad.
Hey! Come back!
Get bent, freak...
The girl is mine.
You'll have to find
your own wench.
No! No! Put her down.
I'm warning you.
Screw it! Mikono!
Asshole!
What is he?!
What the hell is that?!
He's gone to Vega, again.
Who opened the gate for him?
No, seriously;
his Gnis was on lockout.
Such a vale of years
it's been, old friend.
My, how Jin has grown.
Aw crap!
I thought this reeked of you.
When did you awaken?
When? An odd detail
to be concerned with.
An angel's kiss is eternal,
or it is nothing.
Why fuel Kagura's obsession?
I merely saw him off.
He is implacable.
He would have found
a way without me.
Love always does.
What is that supposed to mean?
Powers now at large within your
modest little theatre of
war compel him to clarity.
The Rare Igura is
to him a siren song.
Come. Some screed of curiosity
must lurk behind
that furrowed brow.
The wayward hound may yet find
a way to bridle the warhorse.
Patience,
our True Eve might even
be delivered unto
Altair in the bargain.
Go. Continue the recon.
Keep an eye on Kagura.
Take the Mithra back
by force if you must.
All over it.
Patience, darling.
Quick question.
Mind if I tear you to shreds?
Oh, be my guest. If you'll
play for the privilege.
Oh well, at least
you have a scent.
It reminds me a bit
of hers, actually.
Damm it all...
Your tone would be marvelous.
Shrade decided to
remain in Neo-Kowloon.
All to the good. Cayenne,
Zessica, Andy, get ready.
You'll deploy ASAP.
Roger that.
So, uuum, how come
Shrade's never been deployed?
I mean, you know, guess it
seems kinda wasteful is all.
What? It's just...
he does have the best
simulation record, doesn't he?
I was-- I mean we
girls were wondering.
Look, we can merge with
the opposite sex now.
We have a right to know
a little something about
who we could be
in the field with.
Shrade's a prodigy.
He started piano when he was
two; mastered Chopin by four.
But his gifts came at a price.
Every note he played had
something of darkness in it.
It was said his music could bore
into your soul like fire,
drive you mad with anguish.
Word got around about his power,
so naturally certain interests
wanted to weaponize it.
What is that sound?
Neo-DEAVA?
Are you serious?
So Shrade was actually
recruited by the chairman?
Wait a sec.
How old is the chairman?
Old.
Shrade took the
aptitude test, like you.
But, I don't think
anyone was prepared
for the results they got.
If he pilots a Vector
for even a few minutes,
it would shorten
his life exponentially.
His power's tremendous;
God only knows what
Aquarion would do to him.
When merged, Elements resonate
with each other, amplify
their collective energy.
Shrade's body can barely
support his gift as it is.
It's taken a huge toll.
Being a tuning fork
for two other Elements
would destroy him.
What is going on?!
Forgive me.
She's a bit worse for
the wear, I'm afraid.
Still, her tone is rich.
A voice one would wish to have
at their ear as they lay dying.
Mikono?
I'm so sorry.
He should know. I owe it to him.
I've always owed him.
Owed who? You mean...?
C'mon, not him?
Oh this is just great.
Be careful, guys.
Lousy sons-a-bitches!
Just leave us the hell alone!
She belongs to me.
And only me!
There he is!
Fantastic. The dog again.
One Mithra Gnis.
With all due respect,
High Commander,
how do you know its name?
That's more like it.
Come to daddy.
Cayenne!
Not you.
Let's try you.
Zess, heads up!
He wants Mikono.
Bastard'll tear the city
apart looking for her.
You're awake!
How are you feeling?
Fine, I guess. But... where...?
It's cool, we're safe.
But back there, you
said you owed that guy.
Huh? I said what?
It's all a fog.
I know I was scared.
It's like, when he touched me,
I- I was petrified, but--
But I could tell he cared.
Then it was all,
kinda like deja vu.
Come on! Get off my ass!
Back off, boy.
The wench is mine!
Hang in there, my friend.
Shrade?
Allow me.
What, like, take over?!
Are you nuts?
Give her to me,
you bastards! She's mine!
Mikono! You alright? That guy...
Amata, please,
just get out of here!
I'm feeling it...
I think I'm getting déjà vu now.
I know him.
And I'm not gonna
let him take you away.
The hell?!
Hold up, that isn't...!
What's he doing?!
Who put him in a Vector?!
Shrade, this is foolishness!
Our foe requires
a specific harmony.
You know the missing
interval here is me.
And you know
that this is suicide!
Reason with the boy!
Element Change!
Pull Andy out of there, at once!
Aw, don't do this to me.
I was so close to
merging with a chick!
Come on! Come to me!
Get offa me!
Vector Z!
Make a run for it;
don't look back!
Amata!
Please, Chairman.
We need to merge.
Out of the question!
Don't do it!
I'm ready for it, Crea.
I have dwelt in
limbo for far too long.
Aquarion's music
will set me free.
Fine.
Merge is authorized!
Shrade is the head!
Good luck, all of you.
Oh, how I've waited for this.
This shall be a
concertante for the ages.
Melodic Union! Go! Aquarion!
Oh my, it's like music is
running through my blood!
It feels so tranquil.
This is nature's music-- the
glorious sound of life itself!
Aquarion Spada!
A union with
Vector Y as the head...
Another form has been unlocked!
Shrade is this triad's tonic.
The music of his soul has
pushed Aquarion even further.
You lovely creature.
If the eye truly be
the scout of the heart,
the ear is its betrothed.
From the moment
I caught your sublime echo,
my blood pounded, staccato...
my very being crescendoed...
You are my song of songs.
Damn you, false angel!
Get out of my way!
Amata, Zessica, understand this,
please-- all things are music.
Death is only modulation.
If this fight is my elegy,
help me to make it beautiful!
Yes, sir!
You got it; we're
with you all the way!
Let us begin. Molto espressivo!
Damn it!
Look at that!
Amata's aura is spiking!
Along with Zessica's
element power,
we have achieved a truly
breathtaking resonance.
The moon above us, legato.
Its image in the water
below us, allegro vivace...
What?
Its image in us,
assai maestoso! With feeling!
Hear our Moonlight Requiem!
No!
Did they beat him?
This isn't over.
You hear me, you assholes?!
Believe you have something that,
strictly speaking,
doesn't belong to you.
Dude, why you gotta make
my job such a kick in the balls?
Seriously; what'd
I ever do to you?
Jin, what are you----?!
He's making a run for it!
Hey Shrade, we gotta
go after him now!
Shrade?
No! We're losing him!
Don't do this, man!
Stay with us!
Shrade!
Shrade!!
Mikono, you okay? What's wrong?
I-- I don't know.
It's like-- like all this is
jogging my memory?
You hear the one
about the Element
who went to the john one
night and never came back?
They say the body's
bricked up somewhere
on campus --that their
ghost still walks the halls.
Next time on Aquarion Evol:
"Midnight Girl."