I should kill you,
you son of a bitch!
Amata!
That's enough!
Like hell it is!
Let go! You bastard!
You could've saved her
and you did nothing!
Stop it, that's not how it was!
[MALLOY]
Dude! He was kinda busy
keeping Zess
from getting killed!
No, wait!
You gonna piss this
anger away on Amata...
or you gonna use it
to get your girl back?
Are you fucking kidding me...?!
If I could get her back...
You think I'd be standing here?!
Why...?
[CREA]
Sadly, no distortion field
remained once the Gate closed...
In short, the trail went cold.
This is monstrous...!
What do we do now?!
Dammit...!
High Commander Fudo picked
a hell of a time to
go on sabbatical!
He was compelled to do so.
Spurred on by portent
of worlds in collision.
Fortunately, Zen Fudo
is the sort of creature
to whom such omens
mean something only
when he feels their
verdict can be overruled.
Lo... The mighty ant...
Nature's infiltrator.
Mix...
If only I'd had
a little more time...
I... I never got to hold you...
Never got to bury my
face in those colossal...
What is wrong with you?!
She's a POW on some
forsaken rock halfway 'cross
the universe and that's
where your mind goes?!
Stupid... Flipping...
Douchebag... Pervert!
Andy, please...
You've got to eat.
[YUNOHA] That's two days
in a row without food.
The longer he's down there,
the worse I feel for him.
Yeah, right...?
I know what it
is to lose someone.
I can't bear the thought
of him going though this.
Hey, he'll be fine.
I'm gonna take
care of this, okay?
[MALLOY]
Dude, it's been a week.
[CAYENNE] I wonder if
she's even still alive.
[AMATA]
How's Zess?
[SAZANKA]
Ehh. Taking another sick day...
Whole thing's
really messing with her.
It should've been me...
I shouldn't be here... I...
Damn you, Amata.
What were you
thinking...? Why me?
You would've gotten over it...
We all know who you
really can't live without.
Oh, no. Not again...
[MIKAGE]
Fear not, child.
N-No...! Stay away!
[MIKAGE]
Quell your tears.
I know what it is to be trapped
in the half-life of
those passed over.
Wha...? What are
you talking about?
Fate cut us from the
same cloth, my dear...
The hand of love caressed
our cheek, only to recoil...
We are the Unchosen.
What say you to my
tearing that hand asunder
and making of it a salve
to mend your tattered heart?
I can open doors
for you, child...
The precious
Dimension Gate, for example.
Bear in mind...
The price will be high.
[AMATA]
C'mon, Mikono!
Can't we at least
talk about this...?
Where are you even
gonna start looking?
[MIKONO]
I don't know...
But it's up to me...
That's all there is to it.
Mikono my dear...
your power is to connect those
who've been divided
from themselves
and make them whole once more.
You must reach out to those
too attached to
their old selves...
nourish them on
their way to new life.
You said yourself
we're all in this together.
Now more than ever.
Well, this is my contribution.
I connect people...
It's what I do... It's all I do.
Mikono... Look, you can't
just tear off by yourself--
Why not?
What good am
I sitting around here?
I'm sorry, it's just...
Look, if there's a chance
he can bring us to Mix,
I've got to find him.
Then I'm going with you!
[MIKONO]
Is that a fact...?
Well what happens
when the Abductors
come back, huh?
We need you in the fray.
Not me. My power is
no use in battle...
[AMATA]
But, Mikono...
There's something...
Something I've needed
to say to you for a while.
I haven't, 'cause...
Well, frankly
'cause I'm terrified...
But if I can find Fudo...
I promise I'll tell you.
Hang on...! Wait, please!
You're such a terror...
Take it easy on
him once in a while.
[YUNOHA] Sure is a
temperamental little thing...
Wonder why it doesn't have
a problem with Kagura.
Just growls at everybody else...
Seems a bit weird if you ask me.
Yeah, well...
He's cool with girls...
Boys, on the other hand,
he's all about giving
the third degree to.
Especially if I like them...
Guess he thinks of himself
as the guardian of my virtue.
So, I take that to mean...
you really do like
Amata, don'tcha?
I'm sorry...
If I were brave enough,
I would've told you...
But when I think about Zess...
How much it kills her
just to see us together...
Still, I owe you the truth...
Just let me find Fudo...
When I get back, I'll tell
you... I promise, Amata.
[EI] A Dimension Gate's opened
up directly over the Academy!
Oh dear lord...
They want a fight,
they'll get one!
[ANDY]
The hell...?
Okay...
What do you see?
[CIERRO]
That's just it, sir... nobody.
[ANDY]
What?
Look alive, people! This is it!
Andy! Wha...?
You gotta get me up
there, now...!
This could be our only
chance of saving Mix!
Cool yer jets, Andy...
The enemy's just baiting us.
Seriously?
I am in agreement
with Commander Donar...
It's a trap.
The enemy lies in
ambush on the other side.
[MIKAGE]
Bear in mind...
The price will be high.
Zess, what's wrong?
[CREA] In any event,
given Fudo's absence
we dare not send
our vanguard battalion
willy-nilly across dimensions
into enemy territory.
Oh, bullshit!
You tellin' me we're
just gonna abandon her?!
I know she means
the world to you, Andy...
I'm sorry.
So, that's it, huh...?
We're just gonna sit here
and do jack squat...
Pardon, Miss Chairwoman.
Commander...? Or...
Chief Instructor...?
Compliments of
High Commander Fudo.
He asks that it be
opened immediately, ma'am.
A donut.
[SUOMI]
That's disgusting!
[DONAR]
What... the hell?
[AMATA]
That's weird...
[CREA]
Wait.
Zen must intend this as a sign.
What?
Perhaps he is
encouraging us to infiltrate.
What, with a donut?
They've burrowed quite deep...
So deep that the inside
and outside have become as one.
Yeah, but what does that mean?
He means the gate!
We will take this as a
direct order...! Vectors!
Deploy to Altair at once!
[CADETS]
Roger!
[MIKAGE] Step through the
looking glass, my pets...
The way is clear;
a nightmare of longing
and regret awaits.
Thank she with tresses
like emerald seed-plumes...
Whose debt,
in time, will be sown.
Patience, Kagura.
You moment shall come... Soon.
[CAYENNE]
Vector Y. All systems green.
Awaiting permission to launch.
I'm sorry...
I only hope you can
one day forgive me...
I truly do.
Cayenne?
Then who's... piloting Vector Y?
Shrade Elan...
Ready for deployment!
Shrade, come back!
The strains of an alien
music beg to be absorbed.
My magnum opus demands it...
My soul demands it.
Girls-- don't get upset
if I don't merge with you...
I'm saving it...
I want my first
time to be special.
That right...! Mix and me!
Infiltration Merge...!
Go... Aquarion!
[EVOL]
Aquarion Evol!
[ATTENDANT] The new recruit's
mind will need time
to stabilize, of course,
but so far so good.
I'm ecstatic the
specimen remained
as intact as it did...
Not an ideal situation,
alas, but still...
Indeed... Perhaps
it's a hopeful sign.
Jin is irreplaceable...
But at the very least we now
have a pilot to help
flesh out the ranks.
[TECH B] Izumo, sir...!
The Dimension Gate has opened!
[IZUMO]
It's what...?!
Damn it, Mikage
is up to something!
He knows precisely
how much energy
is required to pry the gate
wide enough for transport...
Every time it's opened,
the entropy
of Altair's dwindling
resources is hastened...
Does he not care?
[TECH B] Something came
through...! Check again!
[TECH D]
Nothing... No heat signature...
[TECH C]
No mass detected either, sir.
[TECH B]
Impossible...
Why else would the
Gate have opened?
[AMATA] Hang in there, Yunoha.
Just a bit longer.
Uh... Okay.
[ZESSICA] Is it me, or is
this place a dump?
[ANDY]
No kidding, right?
It's like... Damn...
I dunno: wall-to-wall rust.
[SHRADE]
There's the chink in the armor.
Holy crap... Those are all
headstones.
Whoa! Easy!
Are you all right?
Yeah... But...
Best case,
I'm only gonna be able
to keep them
camouflaged for half a day...
We need to find Mix
and get out of here fast.
I thought to hear
music... Instead...
I, hear a planet in
the throes of death.
Gah, slow down! Arrive alive--
I'm coming, Mix...!
Andy's en route to get
ya the hell outta here!
You know, it'd have
probably been safer
for you to stay
with the vectors.
Yeahhhh... I know.
But I wanted to see
where Jin came from...
He'd want me to.
[ANDY] Alicia? That's
Flight of the Aquaria!
[ZESSICA]
What are the chances
they'd be showing it here?
Must be popular on this world...
Like on Jin's hologram thing...
I get the feeling images
of Alicia are pretty common.
[AMATA] So... My mom's
a star on two planets?
[BUM A] Nice! Paid through
the nose for that, eh?
Hard to find one in color.
What's with
the spacesuit, kid...?
You like playin'
cosmonaut or somethin'?
I got this... Stay back.
You look like an
Igura in that get-up.
These front
pouches ain't helpin'.
Hands off!
You okay?!
You believe this guy?
I would suggest we...
dress more discreetly...
These, gentlemen might
be persuaded to help us.
Smells like a septic tank.
Just try to keep
your mind off it.
That's not the only thing...
Anybody else picking
up on the obvious?
Indeed...
The city appears to be populated
only by males... Huh...
Perhaps the entire
planet's that way.
Whoa... Dude.
That would explain why
they're after Vega's women.
Zessica, what's the matter?
I've been feeling like
I'm coming down
with something pretty much
since we landed on this rock.
Hey, so have I, actually...
It's almost like there's
something in the air...
I think you're right.
[ANDY]
Jackpot.
[YUNOHA]
Yeah, that's the place...
Jin's data spread
keeps linking back to it.
[ANDY]
Got it, Bad Guy Central.
[AMATA]
Question is...
How do we know
Mix is even in there?
Easy, we do a little re-con.
Right.
[ZESSICA]
Damn.
[AMATA]
Nice, Andy...
Talk about kickin' ass and
taking names.
Dude, wait up!
[ANNOUCER] Intruders detected
in Hanger Nineteen...!
All units to Phase One
battle stations immediately!
[SECURITY A]
We have reason
to believe the
bastards are from Vega.
That's right, men:
we've got ourselves a tangle
with alien life forms...
I know you're
fresh out of training,
but this is the hand
you've been dealt.
Stay alert, stay focused--
Don't move!
Wrong... choice... losers!
Bastard!
Unless you wanna end up
like your comrades...
I suggest you to
whatever it takes
to keep from pissin' me off!
Now listen up, buck-o...
'cause here's the deal:
We wanna tour guide...
You wanna live.
Think we can scratch
each other's backs?
There they are!
Son of a...!
Let's rearrange the plan...
The guys will stay
and hold them off.
Ladies, you find Mix.
Watch your ass, okay...?
Especially you, Amata...
Don't get dead.
No stone unturned!
Be careful.
Such a crude,
percussive cacophony...
Why don't we see about
refining your tone.
[violin music]
Contrary Twister!
'Kay, coast is clear.
Good. Get your ass up.
Ugh... Dammit...
[SECURITY I]
Any luck?
[SECURITY J]
Sorry, sir!
[SECURITY I]
Get to Sector 83, STAT!
[SECURITY J]
Roger that!
Come on... Make it quick!
Stay still.
[SOLDIER] What's the point of
treating my wound?
Hey: mouth: Shut it.
We don't need your
pals following your voice
any more than we need 'em
following a blood trail.
[ANDY]
Go!
Crap. Dead end.
[SOLDIER]
If your objective's the Tower,
this elevator's your
only hope of reaching it.
Then do us the honor.
Please...!
We're trying to save a friend!
Someone worth more to
us than you'll ever be...
Someone I'm not above
ending you to bust out.
Hey...! Come on!
You dick!
Jig's up, little man.
I have no idea why...
But you can't seem to
bring yourself to kill me.
Flap those wings, Red!
What?!
No sense both of us
gettin' caught!.
Somebody has to get
Mix out of this hellhole!
That name...
Just go. Don't
worry about me...!
There's plenty
whoop-ass left in this can!
Fly!
Andy, I...
[SECURITY O]
The hell...?!
[TECH E]
Target is making a beeline
for the Upper Block, sir!
Apparently he can fly!
Well... I bet I know
who that is...
Wait, that music...!
[distant singing music]
[signing music]
What?
Mom...
[ANDY] Don't worry, Mix!
I'm coming for you!'
Get your hands off of me,
you bastards! Mix!
That name.
[ANDY]
I need you like I need air...
Like I need sleep;
food, shelter, all of it...
Without you, I'm nothing.
Less than nothing...
There's a hole in my heart...
shaped exactly like you.