Love must yet be sin!
So, who's captain eye-patch?
One of the brass, maybe?
Umm, why is he
dressed like a pirate?
What do you mean love is a sin?!
Yeah, the walls
just got torn down!
Hell no! This sucks!
Come on! Screw that!
Welcome, Miss Chairwoman,
glad you're back.
Is he serious?
Refreshments,
just for you, ma'am.
Very kind.
So, this little girl
is the chairwoman?
Indeed, and this
is her companion--
Neo-DEAVA's High
Commander Zen Fudo.
The Chairman and High Commander
have journeyed together
for quite some time,
attempting to solve
the Aquarion's deeper mysteries.
I take your return
to be a good omen?
You must've found something
if you've come back.
Personally, I'm in the
dark regarding all this.
Speaking only for myself, of
course, Aquarion is mystifying.
Miss Suomi, are you
familiar with the story
of Apollon and Silvie?
Yes, of course.
It's a famous fairy tale,
every child has heard it.
I think there was a
movie not long ago.
'Skies of Aquaria,'
if memory serves.
Correct.
Some believe as a
condition of their victory
over the forces of darkness,
Apollon and Silvie were ripped
apart, never to meet again.
But fierce passions
are dangerous.
Unchecked, they can
herald destruction.
The brave lovers
are still divided,
and still yearn to
embrace one another.
These unresolved
feelings are what cause
the current Aquarion to
malfunction and go berserk.
Berserk?
More or less.
Which is exactly
why Neo-DEAVA chose
to place the machine's
full power under a seal.
You of course already
know this, Mr. Donar.
I do. Wish I could say I didn't.
Our enemy grows stronger
and more fierce with
each passing day.
To have even a
chance at survival,
Neo-DEAVA must
rethink its strategies.
True. We have no other choice.
It seems the forbidden powers
are our only recourse.
Curious how pastries lend
themselves to metaphor.
I suggest, Mr. Dantes,
that you eat the empty
space defining your center.
Before it eats you.
Sir, Izumo wants
to see you. Wait!
Is that really
what I think it is?
Where in the world did you get
an exact
reproduction of Alisia--?
What does he want. Well?
What is it?
Jin, we've just finished
analyzing the data
you brought back to us.
Your preliminary
theory proved correct.
The Machine Angel's
parameters depend on its form.
Told you so.
After the transformation,
it fought like a completely
different animal than before.
What's more,
during the last attack,
we detected something else:
strong readings
consistent with a Rare Igura.
You're telling me a
Rare Igura was inside it?
Excuse me, sir,
Kagura Demuri has just
deployed his Mithra Gnis.
What an impetuous fool!
Does he plan to conquer
Vega on his own?
Sir, the Dimension Gate!
Damn it.
The Mithra Gnis has entered
inter-dimensional space!
I wanna know who
opened that thing!
No, wait. He can't
have awoken yet...
Listen up, everybody.
Starting today,
Holy Angel Academy is co-ed.
That means from now
on you'll all learn together.
Now, I realize it might take
you some time to adjust,
but I trust you will all
comport yourselves like adults.
Wow! It's Shrade in the flesh.
Even the air is polluted now.
Your first assignment together
is something of a
social experiment.
You will venture out
into Neo-Kowloon
in mixed gender teams.
Understood?
Trip sounds like a complete
waste of everyone's time,
if you ask me.
Booya! Look out, ladies!
Your knight in
shining armor is here!
Mikono.
Mr. Sora, I realize
this is exciting,
but please calm yourself.
Oww, what was that? Huh?
Take a handout everyone.
A walk along the promenade,
group bungee jumping
off of Kowloon tower,
tea at an ocean-side hotel.
What is this?
It's like a date!
More like the coolest date
in the history of dates!
Almost forgot,
you'll need these, too!
What the hell are these things?
So lame.
'Scuse me, where's mine?
Oh, the commander's exempted
you from wearing one.
Listen up; here are
your group assignments.
Group A: Cierro, Enji, Yoka.
Group B: Malloy, Aika, Mist.
Please give me hotties.
Group C: Andy, Mix, Yunoha.
Yuno--who? Huh?
Andy, I do hope
you are satisfied.
Oh, uh, sure!
This freaky frog-cat
is the boom-diggity!
Frog-cat?
Outstanding.
I'm stuck with Mister
Talky McLoudmouth.
Okay, so, she's a bitch...
but check those
curves! Chub alert!
Next up, group D: Cadets
Shrade, Cayenne, and Sazanka.
Well, this should be fun.
That depends on your definition.
Come now, don't be
like that. Relax, friend.
Lay off with that crap.
Right, of course.
Okay, next group:
Amata, Mikono, and Zessica.
Looks like we're group buds.
Uh-huh.
From here, each group
will go their separate ways.
But whatever you do,
make absolutely sure
you don't miss the
boat back, understood?
Yes!
Electrocutions are
happening all over the place!
To be young again.
So what are these?
They monitor the
cadets' vital signs,
heart rate, aura, perspiration;
specs of that nature.
Should they pass
a certain limit,
an electric charge is released.
I, for one, don't approve.
What purpose does it serve?
I think it's cruel!
No, you're wrong.
I understand why it
might seem that way,
but this is critical to
maximizing elemental power,
while ensuring we
don't repeat the mistake
that led to the
Great Aquarion Disaster.
The Great Aquarion Disaster?
Nine years ago, when
Aquarion was deployed
to counter the first
charge of Abductors.
During combat, it went wild.
DEAVA lost two
Elements in the conflict.
Donar survived, but the
price he paid was high.
It cost him both arms
and the woman he loved.
Lifeless cogs.
Love's melody will
forever be ephemeral.
Donar!
No!
Aquarion resonates
with its pilots' emotions,
intensifying their power.
It amplifies the Element's
ability to do battle,
but the depth of power
correlates directly
to the intensity of emotion.
Of all the passions,
do you know which one
is the most intensely
felt in human beings?
Go ahead, take a guess.
I'd say hate or jealousy.
No. It's love.
It is?
But no matter what they do,
they cannot let their
feelings turn into actual love.
If the pilots ever
go down that path,
Aquarion will lose control.
That is the very
definition of disaster.
It happened to Donar.
We must do all we can to
ensure it never happens again.
That's why this
training matters.
If we can keep them on
the threshold of love
without letting them cross over,
Aquarion's full
repertoire will manifest;
our Elements will be
able to harness its power.
The relationship
between Amata Sora
and Mikono Suzushiro abides in
that dark, if precarious, place.
That's how they were able
to use the forbidden move.
Think of these
as love detectors.
When certain
feelings arise, zap.
The power we hope to harness
lies just short of insanity.
We're teaching them how
to master their hearts.
Exactly, because of
what I've been through,
I'm obligated to
keep my students
from suffering the same fate.
Especially Amata.
He reminds me of myself,
when I was much younger.
That's why I'm here.
It's so cute! Look Shush,
it's a cat, just like you!
She's so beautiful. Maybe the
prettiest girl I've ever seen.
Amata?
What happened?
My butt! It hurts.
Don't forget love's
forbidden, Amata.
I can't take my eyes
off that kid for a minute.
Something stinks.
The dude-to-chick
ratio at this pool
is definitely not up to par.
I wonder why they want us here,
and what's with making me wear
this lame-ass swim-suit?
Seriously though. What the
hell's the story with this doll?
Well, here I am.
They're so big. Huh?
Today's training exercise
is also intended
to be a simulation
of Element groupings.
If giving over to love is
as dangerous as
you believe it to be,
Mix would make
an excellent soldier.
The opposite sex doesn't
seem to affect her.
Wrong. Girls like that
one close themselves off
to all possibilities,
which makes it nearly impossible
to approach the Love Threshold.
I'm curious. Why are Shrade,
Cayenne and Sazanka a team?
They even told us
what to order for lunch
like we're too stupid to
make decisions on our own.
Here you are, folks.
Your watermelon juice.
Umm, is there supposed
to be only one glass?
Yes, I'm afraid that's
what was ordered.
Drink up you two.
What?
Come on, this is
part of our training,
not like we have a choice.
You'll have to excuse
my friend here;
he's a touch shy
around the fairer sex.
Uh, I see.
Two guys sharing!
And not just any two guys,
Shrade and Cayenne.
I'm in heaven!
Shrade's a rock;
it seems nothing can
knock him off balance.
It's impressive. Wish I could
say that for Sazanka,
this will be quite
a shock for her.
Miss Chairman, Shrade's
practical combat record is...
Yes, I am aware.
His health concerns
are limiting...
Shrade Elan lives each day
on the cusp of life and death.
Of all the cadets,
his natural state is the closest
to what we're looking for.
How cold.
Although, there is a
grouping we'll need to watch
more than the others:
Amata, Zessica, and Mikono.
But that doesn't make sense.
Mikono has yet to even
manifest any Element powers.
If the ring does not
take its full shape,
then the donut is nothing
but a useless lump of dough.
Mikono Suzushiro.
She is the key to
completing the ring
of our metaphorical donut.
Without her, we have only void.
Will you stop that?
Damn. If this kid keeps this up,
there won't be enough
blow darts in the world.
Why me?
When Amata looks at me,
his heart starts racing.
Wow. Gosh, he really is cute.
You sure do look happy, Mikono.
So, what gives? It's 'cause
you like him, right?
No, it's not like that!
You sure about that?
You know, he's kinda my type,
so since you're not
interested, I'll have a go.
Let's see here, what's up next?
Amata! Wanna have some fun?
Well?
Cool, I can make him fly, too.
How enlightening.
Looks like you'll fly
for anyone, huh?!
Please! It's not
"anyone," it's me!
Nothing to be ashamed of!
Again?!
Is something the matter, Shush?
Whoa! Who is that?!
I have no idea. But he
looks pretty cute to me.
This one's ripe.
Are you feeling well?
We can take a
break if you want to.
No, I'm fine.
Still disgruntled over
a harmless little bow?
Stop trying get a rise outta me.
I'm not playing your game.
Please, Cayenne.
If anyone's compelled to a
game against his will, it's me.
I've my own Abductor.
It's called disease.
We'd like to buy three jumps.
Do I have to?!
Of course, it is
part of our training.
But, if you're too
chicken you could back out.
Looks like it's just us!
Knock it off!
That is so cool!
I'm not gonna be a third wheel
on someone else's date!
See you guys later.
Wait a sec! Mikono!
Mikono, please! Wait up!
Why should I, you big jerk?!
You've been flying for
Zessica all day long!
I thought I was special,
but I guess I was wrong.
Wait, what did you just say?
Leave me alone!
Mikono, I--
Oh, wow.
Look at that sunset.
Whoa. It's just like--
Like in Skies of Aquaria.
Hey, this song.
S'like I've been here before.
You and I barely know each
other. We've only just met.
But I feel like I've been by
your side for ages. It's weird.
It doesn't feel
weird to me at all.
Do you believe in destiny?
I think we were
supposed to meet.
Mikono, are you okay?! I'm
sorry, forget I said anything.
Just forget the whole
thing! I didn't mean it!
No, please.
I don't want to forget it!
I don't want you to, either.
This is bad. Mikono's love
index is rising dramatically!
Oh no!
Stop them, now!
They're over the brink!
Commander Donar!
Can you handle this?!
Damn it! Both of them
are out of range!
Amata!
Stop it! Amata,
Mikono please don't!
You can't!
The scent of forbidden love
is like honey. Even so.
Such sweet aroma is
guaranteed to attract ants.
Hey, sweetheart.
You reek.
You stink like carrion.
No! Mikono!
This is outrageous!
Indeed, even worse...
it bodes an unresolved tone.
Mikono!
Let's talk about
what's happening
in seven days, shall we?
The upcoming
"scherzando battle" will be
the dal segno into darkness.
Isn't that right, my friend?
Next time on Aquarion Evol:
"Agitato of Life."