It's always important to bear in
mind, our ancestors composed
this hymn in full faith that
their age was the last
to see the Aquarias in battle.
Alas, their wisdom could not
prophesy the Abductor scourge.
Nor the reopening of
the Dimension Gates
through which they come.
The enemy has
decimated our cities,
driven our populations
to the brink;
yet all we can infer of them
is that the world from which
they descend boasts
technology similar to our own.
Thus has Neo-DEAVA come to
stand as a bulwark against them.
Thus stands Aquaria Type F;
a paean to the noble chosen
Daughters of The Way
that helm her,
and Type M a credit to the sons.
Great is our adversary, but if
Heaven's Children close ranks
against the darkness, dawn
will take wing-- Beg pardon?
What?
My dear, you've deployed
no less than four times
to face the Abductors from
the cockpit of an Aquaria.
Educate your fellow sisters,
if you would please.
What is it like to merge?
Pretty cool, I suppose.
No, it's beyond incredible.
That it is. Nothing
stands comparison
with offering one's purity
to a Holy Guardian when--
Still, though.
Girls are awesome and all,
but really, merging
with boys would be way
more, I dunno... fun.
Purge your mind!
Impure thoughts are the enemy's
most insidious ally, Zessica!
Hmph. Merging with boys.
It isn't possible!
But we--
The Guize Stones
keep you out of sync.
Ergo your maidenhood
is unsullied
and our Guardian
remains a sacred cradle.
Precisely!
I don't know but
I've heard tell.
Guys who fart clean
toilets in hell.
Sure sounds bad,
but I've heard worse...
Girls gonna make
this Vector my hearse.
What do we do?
Hold back!
How do we do it?
Unionize!
Come on!
I can't hear you!
Unionize!
Persuade me!
Come on!
This had better not
be all you've got!
Your nuts re-ascend
while you slept?
Maybe shock therapy'll
coax 'em back down!
Wow. I can't remember the
last time I saw you miss.
Dude. Shut up.
What, you have another
one of your visions?
Anything serious?
Wedding
gown-slash-funeral dress.
Again?
Cheerleaders, yes.
Big scary cyborg barking
at you, not so much.
When are the
higher-ups gonna get
what a great motivator
chicks would be?
The Berlin seriously
needs to come down.
Andy, we're not lettin'
our minds wander
to the other side of
the wall, now are we?
Sir! No way, sir!
'fraid we're past the point
where a friendly
taze'll do any good.
But, this...
Thanks for the tough love,
Commander Donar, sir!
Seriously, what's the
point of even being here
if the only people I get to
score a merge with are dudes?
Just a few yards away
from the promised land.
So many hotties. So many bricks.
This sucks... royally.
I'm a lover, not a fighter!
Abductors detected
in the Crest Precinct.
All Elements report to
their second-degree
intercept positions
immediately.
They don't waste any time.
Vector X ready for launch!
Vector Y ready for launch!
Vector Z ready for launch!
After twelve--thousand
long years, the dull shards
of our souls find
each other once more.
The legend renews.
The first chord of the final
cadence has been struck.
Genesis Union! Go! Aquarion!
This is big. That name's not
been uttered aloud in years.
Wait! Stop it!
We're not allowed to merge!
I can't handle this!
What is this? What is this?!
Something inside me
is about to break!
This is happening!
Aquarion Evol!
Aquarion Evol?
Now that's what
I'm talkin' about.
This is the fight you
wake up every morning
to feel in your blood!
The scent you track
to the edge of time.
Aquarion Evol?!
Who the hell is this kid?
He's using Vector Z as the head.
This form is
completely unknown to us!
This-- this is disgusting! Ugh!
It shouldn't even be possible!
The seal has been broken.
These two have shattered it.
I don't understand.
What are we doing
inside an Aquaria?
Um...
And what is "Evol?"
Look, I- I just...
This is weird.
Mikono! What are you doing?
Cayenne!
Get the hell out
of his friggin' lap!
And you, ginger, Neo-DEAVA
doesn't take terrorism lightly.
Wait, terrorism?!
Listen to me.
This isn't how it looks!
Did I ask you how it looked?
Someone wanna explain to me
how a couple civilians
are operating the head?
Guys, c'mon!
Override the merge already!
What do you think we're
trying to do?! Status?
Still not responding.
The commands
are getting through,
it's just ignoring them!
I have a good idea
where this is going.
Well I don't.
Chief Instruct-- I mean,
Commander, what is all this?
I would think
it's rather obvious;
the status quo's just
been chucked out the window.
Male and female
are able to merge.
No! Aquarion's power is far too
dangerous for mortals to wield!
Wakey wakey.
You're not done yet.
Get off your ass and
come at me full bore!
Hang on!
Everything will be okay.
What?
What the hell?
Since when has the
owner's manual said anything
about being able to do that?
Whoa, that's intense.
How is he doing this?!
Whoever this punk is, his aura
fits Aquarion like a jackboot!
Huh?
Hey, kid, how the hell
did you manage that?
I don't have a clue!
It kinda just happened!
Oh you're yankin' my chain.,
unless you're a natural...
Zessica, stop encouraging
him! Heads up!
Alright, look, we're stuck
together for the moment,
so we might as well cooperate.
Cooperate? You mean fight.
That's not what
I had in mind, asshole!
I didn't do it on purpose!
No! No!!!
This isn't our fight, Amata.
Please we can't do this.
We're not cut out for it;
we shouldn't even be here!
Let's just--
Snap out of it! We're in
this together like it or not!
There's got to be a way out!
The best thing for us is
to just stay out of the way!
Mikono! Shut up!
Mikono...
Enemy reinforcements!
And they ain't small.
Three large
Abductor Units confirmed!
Nobody called for you.
Apologies, Master Kagura.
Our orders come from Izumo.
We're to escort you back
to Altair immediately.
I can't believe you let
him put you up to this.
With respect, the Rare
Iguras have been located.
This mission serves
no further purpose.
You can tell the
old man to get bent!
Come on, come on!
What am I supposed to do?!
Right. Enough of this crap.
Welcome to Combat 101.
'kay. First things first.
Unlock the lever.
What?
Whoa!
Zessica's power has fused
with the new formation!
Her aura's resonating
with the boy's.
So this is a mixed union.
Commander,
why do I get the feeling
they've only scratched
the surface?
This is magnificent.
Master Kagura! I entreat you!
No one gets between me and
my prey, you understand? No one!
Sir!
Sorry, I'm just gonna
borrow this for minute!
Stop it! Please!
Wasn't that his backup?
This doesn't look good.
You're kidding me!
What the hell's going on?!
Oh, you smell rancid.
Not gonna lie, though.
It really turns me on.
This guy's crazy!
He ripped an arm off
his own reinforcement!
What's with the way he's moving?
It's like he's a dog!
Please go away.
Mikono...
Make him go away!
Please. Please.
Will ya lay off the whining?
Only thing it's doin'
is pissin' me off.
This is a battle, Mikono!
Get with the program!
That's not fair.
She's never done this before.
She doesn't even know
if she's in good hands.
Buck up!
Oh, what is it now?! Really?!
It's the vision I keep having.
No please, not now...
What am I looking at?
Behold the prophet of despair.
The tragic entanglements of
those around him, he foresees.
That's all fine and good,
but Commander,
how are we able to see it?
"By any other name" Aquarion has
reclaimed its forbidden past.
Its powers have awakened.
A pale bride swathed
in funeral vestments.
A union between man and
woman, ending in death.
Mikono?
Me? Why is it me?
Show me the groom's face,
damn you! I wanna see!
Who is--?
Master Kagura!
Let's have a look at you, babe.
Yeah. You're in there.
My nose never lies.
You belong to me!
Look out!
This is all your fault, jackass!
Way to drag Mikono into this.
Just had to hijack
an Aquaria, didn't ya?
Well now we're all
gonna die 'cause of you!
I- I'm sorry, I...
My emotions, when they take
over, I- I fly.
It's been that way
since I was little.
Everyone always hated me for it.
I drove them all
away... Even her.
I never asked for this power.
And I sure as hell
never like using it,
but, I didn't know
how else to save her.
Damn it.
I made things worse.
I'm so sorry.
I never should've tried to
talk to you in the first place.
I should've just
stayed out of the way.
Don't say that.
Come on, you fetid bitch!
Come out and play!
Shields are failing, ma'am!
They're not going
to last much longer!
To inherit a legend
is to become a legend;
to assume a form long forgotten.
Amata Sora, the gift is
ready whenever you are.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to
suggest you were like me
when I said all I was good
for was staying out of the way.
Please, take a look at yourself.
We only just met
this afternoon,
and you're laying
down your life for me.
See if the shoe were on the
other foot, I'd just cry.
That's not true.
You're a good guy. Thank you.
Thank you.
Her hand is so tiny.
So delicate. So warm.
Mikono!
What?
Oh, my.
Look at that bastard go!
They're not... The Aquarias.
They're not built for
that kind of velocity!
If they don't throw the brakes,
they're gonna be in orbit!
It's that kid! His elemental
power is extraordinary!
Awesome.
Is it over?
Think I'm throwin'
in the towel?!
Dimension Gate, two o'clock!
Enough. Put your toys
away and come home.
Screw that! I can still fight!
Can you, now?
Aren't we whimsical.
Damn it, boy.
Swallow your pride
and get out of there.
That's an order.
Fine!
Uh oh!
Amata, no! You gotta wake up!
Cayenne.
Amata, no!
Stay away from Mikono.
Y'hear me?
Cayenne. Zessica. Drag
those hijackers back to HQ.
Roger on the guy,
but all due respect, sir?
There's no point
bringing the girl.
She's been inside an Aquaria,
if you hadn't noticed.
We're not setting her loose.
Understood.
I don't believe it.
After all this time,
I've finally found her,
the one who'll wait.
Perhaps the winged mercury
is... No. Unthinkable.
The prodigal son returns.
Jin.
Way to bang up my Gnis, you ass.
'Least tell me the
harvest was good.
I'm in love.
Huh?
Heh, I'm 'onna make
her a very happy wench.
It's okay.
Everyone says merging is
one of the scariest
things you'll ever do,
at least at first.
So don't beat yourself up
if takes you a while
to get the hang of it.
Next time on Aquarion Evol:
"Love Index Skyrockets!"