[DONAR]
Commander Fudo's gone?
[CREA]
Yes, though he left us a note...
It seems he departed
early this morning.
He's
gone off to...
look for... the
Legendary Aquarion?
Do you think it possible
Fudo has a lead on it?
I've no idea...
I guess it's conceivable
he found something
that piqued his interest
in the Book of Twin Stars.
[DONAR]
The Book of Twin Stars?
Take this!
Oh no...! Please
tell me this isn't real!
[CIERRO]
You guys! Here he is!
[MALLOY] This is gettin'
kinda out of hand.
[YUNOHA]
Andy!
[EI] What in the world's
wrong with him?
[MALLOY]
He's a hero, why's he depressed?
[SAZANKA]
Duh...!
He's not depressed.
He's clearly digging us a
super awesome hot spring!
This is nuts...
What happened out there?
So Mix... You know
what this is about?
[MIX]
Don't bring me into this!
I don't have a clue. I mean...
Sorry, your guess is
as good as mine. Ugh!
Man... This sucks.
[ZESSICA]
A concert?
Thanks, yeah.
I'll think about it.
Don't think about it,
just come with me,
it'll be fun...
I promise... Bye.
[SAZANKA]
How many times is that now...?
The new look's really
reelin' in the guys, huh?
This tastes awfully
bland for how it looks.
[SAZANKA] I still can't
get over you laying
your cards on the
table to Amata...
No joke... That took
some serious balls.
Sorry... I feel like
my advice might
have led you down
the wrong path of action.
It's fine... I said it
'cause I wanted to.
'Sides, it helped me
get on with my life.
Really?
Think so...
Just cross your fingers
I'm not trekkin'
down another dead end.
[MALE CADET]
Miss Suzushiro!
[MIKONO]
Yes?
[MALE CADET]
Glad I ran into you...
I was going to take
this to your room.
Here you go.
[MIKONO]
Thanks a lot.
Mikono, hey!
Oh... Sorry about that...
I wasn't trying to hide
this or anything...
It's just a letter
from my Father.
[AMATA]
Your father?
[MIKONO]
We don't exactly get along.
[AMATA]
Oh.
Getting this was pretty much
the last thing I expected...
Who knows, maybe he's
just worried about me?
Well he's a parent, right...?
That's kinda their
job... Though...
I wouldn't really
know firsthand.
Oh gosh, I'm sorry...!
I remember my mom some...
'Course it was a long time ago.
But my Dad...?
I draw a big, fat blank.
[AMATA] Look, Mikono...
I think we need to talk.
Let me take a wild guess.
That guy... That's what you
wanna talk about, huh?
[MIKONO]
Stop this!
Don't do this...
Don't shoot him.
Please let him live!
[AMATA]
Okay, first...
Please know I'm not trying
to blame you for anything...
What happened happened,
but we're still gonna have
to find a way to work together!
You think I don't know that...?!
I'm supposed to connect
everybody, remember?
That's my power.
But... I don't know if I can!
Mikono, wait!
This can't be.
[CAYENNE] What's the
matter with you? Well?
[MIKONO]
Dad sent you a letter,
but somehow it got
delivered to me by mistake.
Sorry, I opened it before
I realized it, though.
Yeah, his hand writing
is like a four year old's...
I'm actually more confused
about why he'd send me
this in the first place...
You sure you're okay?
Um... Yeah...
I'm fine, I'll see ya tomorrow!
Wait, Mikono!
[MIKONO]
How could I be so stupid...?
I should have known
better than to read it.
[MIKONO'S FATHER] Her being
at the academy confounds me:
I doubt I'll ever
understand their decision...
My only hope is
that she isn't holding
you back the way
she tended to at home.
Harsh truth: the poor
girl's dead weight.
Nothing more.
If you need, say the word
and I'll have her
removed from Neo-DEAVA.
Better she's out of your hair;
at least at home
she's less of a burden.
[MIKONO]
In Father's eyes, I'm nothing...
Always have been.
[MIX]
Mikono?
[MIKONO]
You're worried about Andy?
[MIX] I am. He's rather
depressed right now...
And I'm pretty sure
it's my fault.
[MIKONO]
Yeah but...
I thought you were finally
starting to get along.
[MIX] Well, we were...
Until the field trip.
The worst part is,
I go around telling people
to say how they truly feel...
But when push came to shove,
I didn't even have the decency
to practice what I preach...
I know it doesn't make sense,
but it's like I see my father
in every single boy I meet.
Your father?
It sounds crazy, right...?
But that's why I have
the men issues I do.
So how about you, Mikono...?
You and your Dad...
Do you get along?
Oh well... We uh--
Papa... I uh...
Spit it out, Mikono.
[MIKONO'S FATHER]
Ugh... Stop wasting my time.
[MIKONO]
He was always a stern man,
and I was very afraid of
what he thought of me.
Whenever I was about to speak...
I'd get nervous he'd
be upset with me
so I'd just freeze up...
And then he'd be even more angry
that I was too afraid
to speak my mind.
I see. I guess
we'll never get it...
I mean, if we can't even
understand our own dads...
How are we supposed
to get a grasp
on what makes the rest
of them tick, right?
Hey. I've always been
curious... Boy or girl?
Yeah I don't really know.
Zessica?
Why are you
practicing at this hour?
'Cause I'm a total badass...
And at the end of the day,
that's what I was meant to be.
I know I've been a little
on the down side lately...
So I'm gonna put my all of focus
back into training.
Anyway... G'night!
Oh goodness.
[ZESSICA]
What in the world am I doing?
Just another dead end.
[ATTENDENT] Iron Sea's
operating level, sir...
has dropped below forty percent.
[TECH A] The amount of
energy we're expending
for dimensional transport is
what's hurting us the most.
[TECH C] I'm afraid we can no
longer allow travel to Vega...
If we continue to leech energy
from the civic infrastructure,
large-scale riots
will be likely.
It's the end of the line,
no point in
pretending otherwise.
Where is Kagura?
[ATTENDENT] I'm sorry, sir...
I'm afraid we don't know.
[IZUMO] No doubt this
is Mikage's handiwork...
He cares for Altair's
fate only insofar
as it caters
to his ends.
[IZUMO] Prepare the
Ahura Gnis for battle.
[ATTENDENT]
But sir?
I'll go to Vega myself.
It's time to breathe the air
of the battlefield once more...
Altair will make
one final stand.
[IZUMO] Alicia... For the
sake of bringing
this world back to
its former greatness...
I will venture out in
search of the True Eve.
And perhaps I'll encounter
something else of use.
The son you left behind...
Our son.
[CAYENNE]
You read it, didn't you?
Dad's letter, I mean.
[MIKONO]
I'm really sorry.
[CAYENNE] There's nothing
for you to be sorry for.
Don't let it get you down, okay?
That's just Dad...
He always freaks out
about stupid stuff
when he has no reason to.
Cayenne... If I'm in
the way, send me home.
[CAYENNE]
In the way?
[MIKONO]
Father's probably right...
Just by being here,
I'm holding you back
from whatever
you're meant for...
All I am is dead weight.
If I'm gonna be useless
I should do it at home.
Look at me.
Ow...! Hey, that hurt...!
What was that for?
Who cares what he thinks...?
Try and have a bit more
confidence in yourself.
Your whole life,
you've never spoken out
or stood up for anything
because you've been
too afraid of making
other people angry...
Listen... Just 'cause
someone's upset with you,
you don't have to let
your feelings get hurt.
You're not useless...
Or a coward...
Though for most of my life,
I'll admit, I thought you were.
But, then... I met this guy...
And he convinced me otherwise.
Look, I realize
I haven't known her
as long as you have...
But I think she's
changed since then...
Cut her some slack.
You may think she's a coward...
But you're wrong, Mikono's brave
and she's trying to
be a stronger person!
Amata seriously said that?
[CAYENNE] Yeah, and as much
as I hate to admit it,
he was right...
You're a completely
different person.
Honestly, I can't wait
for Dad to see it himself.
Thank you, Cayenne.
[alarm sounding]
There's a piece
I've never heard before.
It's strong...
Intense, powerful sound.
[IZUMO] The sea...
It's making me nostalgic.
This is indeed the
Vega of my youth.
[MIKAGE]
Oh, Izumo...
Do you yearn for a flower
to bloom after so long?
Or conversely,
do you seek the fruit
that fell from the tree
of your own devising?
[EI]
They're closing in on us, fast!
[DONAR] Seems we've got a boss
battle on our hands, eh?
Andy! You're late!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sure you're up for this?
Dude. I'm cool,
just get off my back.
Andy, no!
Stop it!
No digging in the
control room, man!
Forget him...
We can't put the kid
out there like this.
We've got five usable
Vectors on hand...
Use the remaining units
to back up Aquarion...!
Which Elements do we send?
You should make that call.
Cayenne. Amata... And last--
I'll go Commander!
You can't... It's too
dangerous, ladies!
Please, you have
to let me do this...!
Fighting the enemy
is all I have!
She's right...
At this moment we're
not girls we're fighters!
We can stop them...!
Please give us a chance!
I'm sorry, but no.
[CREA]
The cadets are right...
There's no point in tying
one arm behind our back;
what this needs
is a lady's touch.
[CREA] Zen... I hope
I'm doing as you would.
Fine...
Cayenne and Mix,
take the support vectors...!
Zessica, Amata,
Malloy take Aquarion!
Roger that!
I'm worried about her...
Zessica's a bit too excitable.
I agree... She's overzealous.
I have a terrible
feeling about this.
[ZESSICA] Time to merge...
I'll be the head... Got it?!
But, Zessica--
[MALLOY]
Sounds like a plan!
Okay, Heartbreak Merge!
Go...! Aquarion!
Even if it's only for battle...
I can be with Amata like this!
I can feel Zessica's heartache!
This merge is--
out of this world!
[ZESSICA]
Aquarion... Gepard!
We'll make sure these
grunts stay off your back!
[CAYENNE]
We may be in Vectors,
but we'll still take you down!
Time to put an end to this!
Valiant effort...
But I'm afraid it
will not be enough.
No way!
[MALLOY]
It barely hurt him.
[DONAR]
Damage report!
Not good, sir...
Westside barriers have
been completely destroyed!
It absorbed Gepard's laser beam,
amplified it and fired
it right back at us!
[ZESSICA]
Try these on for size!
Youthful passion is little more
than a quaint relic on Altair...
Try as you might,
I'm impervious!
Zessica, you have to calm down!
Stop shooting him,
it's too dangerous...!
Let's try to get in closer.
I know what to do, okay?!
Now...! Back me up, Malloy!
I'm with you, Zessica!
The Curse of Malloy!
Contrary Twister!
Curse of Malloy! Curse of
Malloy! Curse of Malloy!
Yeah... Feel good?!
Fragility. How interesting...
However, you will often find
that the young are far
more feeble than the old.
I prefer to avoid
wholesale destruction...
So let me demonstrate
the vast gap
between our powers.
[ZESSICA] One more time...
Contrary twister!
That will not work twice!
They need help!
Their merge just broke apart!
Malloy's unconscious!
The blast knocked him out!
Vector Y is flying on autopilot!
Put me in, please!
Element change! Mikono, go!
Cayenne and Amata,
you merge with her!
Zessica, back them up!
Don't do this!
[DONAR] You're way too
out of control today...
You need to pull
yourself together!
Amata... Cayenne...
Prepare to merge!
[EI] Incoming! Enemies
approaching the island!
Doesn't look like they're
preparing an attack...
If that's not his game,
what in the world
is he playing at?
He's tapping into our
communications, sir!
What?!
Soldiers of Vega.
Greetings, my name
is Izumo Kamurogi...
Chief Commander of Altair...
I am requesting a
parley with your leader.
Sounds like he's
top of the food chain.
That's really him?
I'm Crea Dolosera...
As the Commander of
Neo-DEAVA, you talk to me.
Well... Even your
Commander's an Igura...
A girl... I was
under the impression
women had no
talent for violence.
Perhaps there's truth
in what you say...
However... I'd urge you
to consider the behavior
of a lioness
protecting her cubs.
Touché, Commander...
Our demands are quite simple:
we require of you
the most powerful
Rare Igura among your ranks.
The most powerful girl...
The strongest we have.
[IZUMO] I have no desire
to level this world,
nor to wreak havoc
on its people...
In return for a Rare Igura,
you've have my word that
Vega will be left alone.
There's no way...!
We'll die first!
Wait one moment!
Miss Chairwoman?
[CREA] If there's even a
slim chance we can settle
this diplomatically,
then I have to consider it...
If only Zen were here
to offer guidance...
Zessica's vector is on the move!
She's heading
towards the Abductor!
If you really want
a woman, I'll go!
Take me right now! Maybe this is
what I've been
looking for all along!
Who's piloting that?
It's a Rare Igura!
Stop, Zessica, have you
lost your mind?!
You're not thinking
about this clearly!
Don't throw your life away...
There are people
who love you here!
I have to... I must!
She has a strong will...
Her spirit will serve us well...
We'll take her.
Defend Vega Merge...!
Go...! Aquarion!
[AMATA]
Aquarion... Evol!
The flying
Machine Angel of legend.
I can sense him...
I feel his presence roiling
beneath the technology.
[MIKAGE] You must be
absolutely certain...
Izumo... You must see
it with your own two eyes.
Mother... Why would
there an image
of her be there?
[SHRADE]
A strange, powerful melody
is cutting across
Amata's heartstrings.
Clear, quick...
Yet bitter... Obsidian.
Mikage, you snake...!
This is all your doing...!
Yet your actions thwarted
the machine angel...
It's really him... It must be.
[CREA] Somebody tell me
what's going on!
[DONAR] What are you doing,
Amata?! Attack him!
Zessica!
I won't let you take her...
No way in hell!
Zessica, stop it...! Right now!
Mix, no!
Are you there?!
[MIKONO]
Mix, wake up!
I'm stopping this!
Infinity punch!
You and I will
meet again soon...
I can promise you that.
It's my fault... She
sacrificed herself for me.
She's gone.
This is awful.
Mix, come back!
[MIKONO] I hated myself
for being afraid...
But maybe fear is
what gives us the power
to overcome and
get on with our lives...
I know it's time for me to take
my own step forward,
no matter what
stands in my way...
Next time: "First Reunion."