All of you are going
to be resurrected...
Come back... I need you!
[FUDO]
As time flows on
our tribulations transform
us minute by minute,
revive us second by second.
Its inexorable current
has lead to this point...
The royal road... to change!
[ZESSICA]
What happened?
Mikono, hey...
Happy Rebirthday!
Not him!
[KAGURA]
Hmph!
All you losers smell weak.
How did he get here?
Wonderful...
It's the dog boy again.
Complete the rite of
passage or stagnate...
Expand your new lives...
Let rebirth from the darkness
be a pumice for the soul.
Now, let us hope
that the lesson took.
Tell all the girls
to stay back...
He's definitely here for them.
I find that sexist!
Give it a rest already...?!
He's trying to help you!
We've got him outnumbered...
Remember your training
and give him hell...
Follow my lead!
What?
Donar, no!
Get him!
Wait...! Yeah;
I think I got this guys!
[AMATA]
Andy...!
That rocked!
No kidding,
talk about a hole in one!
You still want me to stay back?!
[AMATA]
Two peas in a pod.
[MIKONO]
Or two peas in a hole.
[CAYENNE]
Groan.
[AMATA]
Stupid reversal power!
What power?
That's what he does...!
He reverses whatever
you throw at him!
This your idea of a joke?
Put her down!
Put her down or I will kill you!
Ugh... Smells like
the rest of you losers.
Where's my rancid bitch?!
Why pick me...?
I don't understand.
Defend Mikono!
I won't let him
touch her... It's okay!
Let's get you outta here!
Malloy!
Come back!
Nice try...
But no one comes
'tween me and my wench.
That happens to
be my little sister
you're talkin' about, douchebag!
What is this?
He reverses damage
he takes too?!
[KAGURA]
You're mine!
[ZESSICA]
Those eyes.
They burn straight
through to what he wants.
[violin music]
Augh! Ugh!
[KAGURA]
That noise... Not you again!
Cut that shit out!
But it's lively arabesque
in homage to you.
Bastard... Knock it off!
[SHRADE]
Catch the hook yet...?
It's a clever inversion
of your own bristly theme.
[KAGURA]
Stay the hell out of my way!
She's mine...! You hear me?
The bitch belongs to me!
[SHRADE] He thwarted the
melody in single beat.
He's a beast but he's good...
More than good.
This could get interesting.
So this freak's into Mikono?
Uh, obviously, why else would
a guy chase a girl
around like that...?
Wow... I'd like that problem!
It's strange... Why do this?
[MALLOY]
Is that a wolf?
Oh no! It's him!
Whoa!
Oh, hell no! Reversal!
[DONAR] Just got word from
Malloy. The dog guy...
He kidnapped Mikono
and he's hiding
somewhere in the city.
You and your team
sweep the area,
we'll cover from above.
Roger that, sir.
We better split up...!
You guys go that way.
Wait...! Don't forget me!
[MIKONO]
Amata. Is that you?
Easy now... You almost fell.
Come on, relax...
There's no reason
for you to be afraid.
You're safe in my arms...
This is how you die.
Mikono!
[KAGURA] I got her... Hey!
The bitch is in the bag!
You hearin' me?
Open the damn gate and hurry!
Hello, anyone there?
Not sure I'm even
using this right...
[KAGURA]
Hello, can you hear me...?
I got what I came for...
Get me back home... Damn it...!
If you can hear me, respond...!
Hey! Don't leave me here!
Mikono...!
Amata!
[ZESSICA]
You have to calm down...
I'm sure Mikono's fine.
How the hell do you know?!
Cause I just know...
Trust me, okay?
I do... But still...
It may be hard to believe,
but there's no
way he'll hurt her...
She's gonna be fine.
And what exactly
makes you think that?
Because... Ugh!
It's like, it's written in the
stars or whatever, okay...?
I'm sorry... The two of you
are just not meant to be.
Your scent... It's so pungent.
You're insane...
But it doesn't mean
you have to be cruel!
If I'm cruel,
it's because of you...
You did this to me.
C'mon... What could I have done
to you that was so bad?
You let a universe
come between us.
But that's... Yeah fine...
Just stop talking
and get this over with!
Shut up!
Sorry.
No... I can't...
It's not right...
Not in a place like this.
Wait... How come?
Please don't!
If that's what you want,
have it your way...
I'll stop.
That's not stopping...! Ugh!
Ah, you want some of this?
Words can't
describe--how much I...
I... hate you...
[MIKONO]
Wait, he's... He's backward...
Don't believe what I say...
It's all crap.
[MIKONO]
His eyes... They're familiar...
But why...? Why do
I recognize them?
[KAGURA]
I finally found you.
[MIKONO]
What?
[KAGURA]
Come with me, Silvie... Please.
I don't understand...
You've called me that
name before... Who is she?
Silvie and Apollon...
That's the story of us.
[MIKAGE] It began beneath
the Tree of Life...
At the birth of all things,
the Great Descent.
When spirit fell to matter...
the Tree of Life was the
fulcrum point of reality...
the axis mundi around which
even the smallest creature
orbited in perfect harmony.
War boiled 'twixt the angels
and their gelded kin...
Solar Wing awakened;
pollinated the Tree so as
to protect the fragile
balance of existence.
But. The flowers wilted
before they could bear fruit...
Harmony became chaos.
[ZESSICA] Eventually the world
would suffer the consequences,
and the continuation of
life would become impossible.
So Apollon and Silvie
sacrificed their love...
Gave it all up for
the Tree of Life...
Because they knew
they had to protect it.
And because she was
willing to hold out for him.
[MIKONO]
I'm okay to wait,
long as you don't mind
me just hanging out...
"For twelve-thousand years,
if I must," or whatever.
[KAGURA] I'll be waiting
for you too, Silvie.
If it takes centuries--if
it takes eons--so be it.
Wow... That's what Apollon said.
[KAGURA]
Yeah... That's me... I'm him.
[MIKONO]
Is that true...? You're Apollon?
And that makes you...
But that can't be.
[AMATA] Hold on. So you're
saying Mikono is Silvie?
That's impossible...!
How could you think
something like that?!
[ZESSICA]
'Cause I saw it.
[AMATA]
What?
It's related to Cayenne's vision
of the whole
funeral-slash-wedding thing...
You saw it, too.
What difference does it make,
Apollon and Silvie are
just a stupid fairy tale,
why should I even give a damn?!
Because it's the truth.
And I'm ashamed to say,
I was happy when I found out...
If Mikono's destiny is with him,
that means you're free
to date around, y'know...?
Meaning we could...
maybe have a chance.
Zessica... What are you saying?
[AMATA]
A butterfly.
[ZESSICA]
Random.
[MIKONO] No! That's
impossible...! I can't be her!
You-- you're wrong!
I am not Sil--!
[KAGURA]
Silvie!
You see that...? It's her!
[ZESSICA]
Amata!
Please don't scare me like that.
[AMATA]
Mikono!
He came for me!
That jackass again?
Amata!
Give up, already...! She's mine!
[ZESSICA]
You all right?!
[AMATA]
Yeah, I'm fine...
Don't worry...
I finally did it, Zessica!
[ZESSICA]
Did what?
The special training.
I was able to do it... I just
resisted his power. Wait.
[AMATA]
Stay back...
Here... He... Comes.
I'll do my best to keep
him away from Mikono...
You find Cayenne!
Amata... Always the hero.
[YUNOHA]
Mikono! She's on that ledge!
[ZESSICA]
Amata!
Cayenne's coming to help you...!
Get out of there right now!
No, not yet...
I have to keep him distracted
so Mikono has a chance
to get out of there!
Just be careful.
Eat this...! Bastard!
Damn.
[KAGURA]
Kill you...!
I'll kill you!
Do you hear me, punk?!
You're a dead man!
This is it...
I'm gonna die here.
So be it, then.
I don't want to be
abandoned ever again...
I don't want to be born again...
It's... better down here.
[FUDO]
Amata Sora...
Be not afraid.
Darkness need no longer be
a place of panic and pain,
nor of lassitude and loneliness.
Rid yourself of
all attachments...
Trade them for understanding.
[AMATA] Yeah... No, you're
absolutely right...
I have to free myself
from the past;
break the cycle of betrayal.
Moron doesn't
know when to quit...
Stop...! Re-ver-sal!
What the--hell?!
Why isn't my power working?!
[FUDO]
Forgo your bonds...
And nothing will lead
you astray again!
No!
[gunshot bang]
[AMATA]
Cayenne!
[CAYENNE]
You're lucky I made it.
I'm gonna finish him off...
Time to put an end
to this nonsense!
Wha--?! Amata!
Take him out! right now!
[CAYENNE]
What are you waiting for?!
Shoot him... You know
he'd do the same to you!
[MIKONO]
Stop this!
Amata, please don't shoot him!
Mikono?!
Mikono.
What the hell?
Please, I'm begging you.
Don't do this... Don't shoot
him. Please let him live!
That's what you want?
[AMATA]
Mikono... Why?
[MIKAGE]
Fly. Winged sigil of rebirth...
Harbinger of forbidden
love's return. Soar.
Let death end untold
millennia of despair!
[KAGURA]
I can't control myself...
The twelve thousand
year-old stench
of fate is rising to
the surface again...
Let it wash over you,
my beloved Silvie...
Next time, "Soul's Confession."