You okay?
Yeah.
The circle of life turns...
Each soul born dies
and is born again.
Each reincarnation
struggles with misery...
And each rebirth
frees the soul of grief...
This is--
[MIKAGE] This is the beautiful
law of our existence...
Our sadness is an albatross,
for Jin is flying free,
unchained from
his mortal coil...
Though his body be lost,
his memory lives
on in all Altair
from this day forth.
Remember his sacrifice...
For though the Last Son
of Altair has fallen,
Altair itself
shall stand strong.
We have nothing to fear...
The Last Son has led us
to a secured future.
With the Rare Iguras
discovered
Altair stands at the
threshold of redemption!
[MOURNERS cheer triumphantly]
How ridiculous.
Altair has certainly
secured its future... Ha!
One of decay...
Iron Sea's power is
becoming unstable.
What we've secured
is imminent extinction.
Mikage...!
What the hell are you up to?
[MIKAGE] Merely spreading
the good news to my flock.
[IZUMO] You sacrificed Jin
Muso's life for this spectacle?
[MIKAGE] His death was a
sublime gesture to all Altairi.
For the price of
this world's salvation,
the Last Son's life
was a bargain.
[IZUMO]
What do you mean?
[MIKAGE] Our last attacks
have proven quite fruitful.
We have stirred the hornet's
nest the Rare Iguras call home.
We have discovered several
potential True Eve candidates
and finally found the
reincarnated Solar Wing.
[MIKAGE]
Jin aptly played his role...
He will be canonized
for his performance...
After all, his selfless
actions have saved his people.
After decades without sire,
we inch closer to a new
generation...
Perhaps he shall be
reborn among them.
[IZUMO] So that's what
you were really after.
Jin... Last Son...
I swear you'll be avenged.
We shall be pall-bearing them
to the Neo-Stanley cemetery.
Where's Yunoha?
She won't leave her room.
Or even turn visible.
[ZESSICA]
Oh...
Is she just going to shut
herself away forever?
Yeah I-- know how she feels...
If I had lost someone
I'd loved, I'd hide too.
Yunoha...
[FUDO]
Mikono Suzushiro!
[MIKONO]
High Commander Fudo?
His eye...
It's like he's looking
right through me.
[FUDO] Bring Yunoha Suroor
out of her room.
[MIKONO] Sir... I think
she wants to be left alone.
[FUDO]
Our mission is to foster bonds
which strengthen the connection
between gifted youths...
Merging is impossible when
selfishly wallowing in grief.
But... how is it selfish?
She's in danger...
Yunoha's Elemental power
is the ability to disappear.
With Jin Muso dead,
that power may soon
spiral out of her control...
If that were to happen...
she could erase herself.
[FUDO]
You haven't changed.
[YUNOHA] ♪ Meow, meow, meow...
Meow, meow, meow... ♪
[door knocks]
[MIKONO]
Yunoha... May I come in?
[YUNOHA]
It's open.
[door opening and shutting]
[MIKONO] I thought you
could maybe use a snack.
[YUNOHA]
I'm so sorry...
[MIKONO] Uh... I didn't
mean to bother you.
I'll just leave it here.
Yunoha's aura is
definitely fainter,
but what can I say?
[YUNOHA]
Jin asked me...
to leave with him...
Back to his home...
If I had gone...
If I'd listened to him...
He'd still be...
[MIKONO] Oh, no...
If it gets much dimmer,
she'll disappear for good.
Yunoha... Please.
Your friends miss you... a lot.
Nooo...! I can't ...
If I do, I...
I'll have to say...
say goodbye to Jin forever!
[MIKONO]
Then don't say goodbye...
I don't want to
say goodbye to him...
Or to you...! None of us do!
'Cause we love you, Yunoha...
I love you... Please don't...
Don't go--
Jin.
[singing]
Mother...
Did you leave me
for Jin's world?
I... I've got to...
[SHRADE]
So it's come to this.
Gratitude begets sacrifice...
The people we trust inevitably
push us into the fray...
Thus the proverbial
wheat is threshed.
Damn you...
We're talking
children's lives here--
Sorry.
Why aren't you in uniform?
Well, I just...
After everything
that's happened,
we decided we're
just gonna go home.
How dare you not
uphold your sworn duty?
[MIX] We Elements have
been hand-selected
as defenders of our world...
You can't just walk away!
Come on Mix,
you've said your piece.
I'm sorry,
but it's not right...!
We can't just quit any time
something bad like
this happens...!
Andy, no... you too?
Save your breath, spitfire...
I'm not leaving anytime soon...
I have to stay.
'Cause without us...
...who'd be left
to fight back...?
If I'm gonna fall into a hole...
...I'll dig it myself.
You promise?
[FUDO]
Andy W. Hall.
Time to dig.
Huh?
Like a nightmare...
Can't focus... so many to fill!
That ought to be enough...
Thank you.
So what are all these for?
Commander?
The planet Altair.
Planet Altair...
That is the world from which
Jin Muso descended to us.
Altair?
And there's more...
Jin left behind
troubling data...
Altairi intentions
have become clear...
It seems...
They plan to kidnap
female Elements!
[FUDO] As the war with
Altair progresses,
it will only become
more and more intense...
This will not be the
last time our comrades
shall be folded into
their common dust.
In order to prepare you
for the grim hardships of war...
We must bury all of you alive.
[CAYENNE]
Bury?
You're serious?
And now...
Special Training of the Grave!
[CAYENNE]
You're insane, Commander!
We just finished
burying our friends!
[MIX] Everybody knows
I don't really care
for any kind of hole...
But buried in a grave,
I think not!
Hey!
Well this is...
quite unorthodox.
[MIKONO]
What is wrong with you?!
Hold on...
Mikono, what--?
How dare you say
such horrible things
at a time like this?
You've all led lives of
self-bestowed limitations.
[FUDO]
As you sleep with the dead,
the force of your
lives will expand.
Passion...
Hatred... Attachment...
stubbornness... wickedness...
Each of these primordial
drives are distractions...
Each distraction
a link in the chain
shackling the human soul...
thwarting us mid-flight.
It is here, brave souls,
that you must experience death.
[MALLOY]
It says "Death."
[FUDO] You will journey to
the very edge of life...
...then return...
[FUDO] How will this false
demise enlighten you...?
[FUDO] That secret you must
discover for yourselves!
This sounds fascinating.
Shrade, wait!
[SHRADE]
Why...?
I'm already halfway
there myself...
Death has long held me
in its cold stare,
why not return the gaze?
Hold on! How can you--
Yunoha!
I want to be with him.
I want to be with Jin,
just for a little while.
Damn...
As deep as this hole may be...
the war is gonna draw
us in even deeper.
Filling a hole I just
busted my tail to make?
Kinda feels like dying anyway.
I will not be a
part of this farce!
Then you are the exception.
That damn eye can see through
everything, can't it...?
I hate it!
Good... yes.
Mikono...
Amata!
[AMATA]
It's dark... can't see at all...
[ZESSICA] It's so quiet...
so absolutely quiet.
[SHRADE]
Wrong...
There is sound...
the sound of bugs
crawling on the earth.
The creatures squirming
through the dirt.
[CAYENNE]
I can feel them...
the worms creeping
at me, trying to get me...
I'm going to...
[MALLOY]
I'm...
I'm going to turn into dust...
and break apart...
[SAZANKA] My body, it's...
it's rotting away!
[YUNOHA]
Decaying...
...becoming one with the
earth... becoming one...
...with Jin again...
[MIX] I'm scared...
Crumbling away... it's like...
I'll never see the sun again!
[ANDY]
Don't be afraid!
[MIX]
The fear... too much.
[ANDY]
You can do it... just hold on!
I can't!
Oh, man...!
What happened?
High Commander!
[DONAR]
This is too much!
[FUDO]
Silence!
[MIKAGE] It seems the
Wingless Ones are preparing
for their encroaching demise...
Charming.
Kagura, my boy... would
you like to join them...?
Take the same journey to Hades?
[MIKAGE]
Yes...
I will weave you into the
fabric of eternal slumber...
Rest in peace...
then raise hell.
[MIX]
I don't care how hard it gets...
I won't leave...
I just need to remember that
Andy dug this hole.
[ANDY]
I did it all for you, babe.
[MIX] If I remember him,
I won't be afraid...
it won't matter
if it's pitch black.
[CAYENNE]
I can't see anything...
Not even through my
Prophecy of Despair.
[ZESSICA]
Why...?
Why did I have that vision?
If Mikono really is
Sylvie reincarnated...
She'll break his heart...
Poor Amata will be left behind.
[AMATA]
It was...
It was her choice.
I was left alone...
I wanted to die...
Why did she go away...?
[YUNOHA] I'm ready to go...
Please let me die...
I don't want to
stay in this world...
Not without Jin...
Yunoha! Her aura's
disappearing completely!
[FUDO]
Amata's power of flight...
Zessica's telekinetic
distortions...
Shrade's haunting music...
Cayenne's clairvoyant despair
and Yunoha's ability to erase.
[FUDO] Their minds are
racing out of control...
...drawn to the end.
Hold on Yunoha!
Mikono, don't do that!
[MIKONO] We finally got to
know each other as friends...
I feel like we
really connected...
Don't leave us...!
I am not ready to lose
you like this! Please!
[AMATA]
I can't.
Amata... wha--?
[AMATA]
If I'm born again...
I'll just be left behind again.
[AMATA]
No more...
I don't want to be
abandoned ever again.
[ZESSICA]
He's afraid... Amata...
I won't abandon you!
[YUNOHA] I can't...
I can't take it anymore...
I don't wanna be left behind...
Let me stay...
I want to stay here... with Jin.
[AMATA]
I don't want to be born again...
it's... better down here.
[YUNOHA]
Being alive and alone...
[ZESSICA]
It hurts!
[AMATA]
Hurts to live.
Listen to me... stop it now...!
Don't leave me!
What the hell?
[FUDO] The shadow of death...
has catalyzed your power.
[MIKONO]
What?
[FUDO]
The end of our lives isn't
the only death
humans experience...
Think about
shedding your hair...
or losing your baby teeth.
The cells in our bodies are
constantly degenerating...
minute after minute,
and second by second.
Second... by second?
Holding on to the dusty
relics of our past selves,
refusing to progress
or to evolve--
Such behavior divides us,
cuts us off from the
universe and from each other.
Mikono my dear...
Your power is to connect
those who've been divided
from themselves and
make them whole once more.
To make... them whole?
[FUDO]
You must reach out
to those too attached
to their old selves...
nourish them on
their way to new life...
Rebirth amidst the decay...
[FUDO] Sequestered deep
within Vega's loam...
You connect every
one of them...
Linking their souls,
dangling on the precipice
between life and death.
[JIN] For ten thousand years
and two thousand more...
I've loved you.
[MIKONO]
No way!
[JIN] After another eight
thousand years passed...
I loved you even more.
[YUNOHA]
I know that voice!
[JIN]
My whole life I was alone...
I didn't care
about anybody else.
[YUNOHA]
Jin... it's you!
[JIN]
Yunoha...
When we met...
it was the first time
I actually felt
a real connection
with someone...
I felt like I belonged.
Please...
You've got to keep
living for me...
I need you... all of you.
All of us?
[JIN] I realized that
I've never been alone...
Our lives are not our own...
It's more like-- we're
all strands in a web.
[YUNOHA]
Our lives...
[AMATA] Connected to
every living thing...
He's right...
We are not alone...
in life or in death...
there's always a connection!
The earth is so warm!
We're being held up by the dead!
[AMATA]
I feel like a baby again...
cradled gently in
my mother's arms...
If I'd never been born at all...
I wouldn't be here
to experience this!
If I'd never been born...
I'd never have come here...
I'd never have met Jin...
There's nothing
to be afraid of...
in this grave or outside it!
[ANDY] There'll be danger,
sure; I know that.
But I've already
beaten the grave...
Why should I fear it?
[CAYENNE]
Another round of existence...
another round of pain
and fear... But still...
There are overtones and
sub-rhythms best heard
at the brink of death
and reincarnation!
[MIKONO] Exactly!
Never be afraid!
I'll always be here,
waiting for you!
All of you are going
to be resurrected...
Come back... I need you!
[FUDO]
As time flows on
our tribulations transform
us minute by minute,
revive us second by second.
Its inexorable current
has led to this point...
The royal road... to change!
To change?
[FUDO] When a heart allows
itself to experience the now...
[FUDO]
...thoughts... can truly merge.
[ZESSICA]
What happened?
Mikono, hey...
Happy Rebirthday!
Not him!
[DONAR]
It would seem rising
from the grave gave these
kids the boost they needed...
Which means it's time
for me to step up my game...
Guess my old taser's
due for an upgrade!
Next time on Aquarion Evol:
"Love Beasts."