Come in.
How are you feeling, Shrade?
Hospitalized, yet enlightened
by the magnum opus
that is Aquarion.
I still hear its melodic
perfection. It haunts me.
Just don't push yourself.
Your body, it can't
handle much--
I know. I don't care.
I must master this instrument,
even though hellfire
may consume me.
This is a special permission
waiver. It's yours.
Use it or don't, but
know that this struggle
will lead to an early death.
Do not lose your own melody.
This is my symphony.
Life's joys contrasting
looming death.
Well I hope you're all
happy with yourselves.
We've been sitting on our hands
for a week since the
Berlin fell, ignoring
the social barriers plaguing
both bro and betty alike!
Let's make it happen people!
We must tear down the
walls of misunderstanding!
Did I miss something?
Andy never passes
up an opportunity
to make an ass of himself.
Andy, bro, I think
that's enough--
Whose side you on?
Friends, lend me your ears.
The time has come
for a seating change!
Pick your battles, dude.
Objection! There will
be no switching!
If I have to sit next
to one of you boys,
I'll never get the stink out!
Change is good, right?!
Yeah, I'm totally for it!
All those in favor?
This'll be fun! Dibs on
the seat next to Cayenne!
Why you...
Looks like we might've
pushed a button.
This is perverse...
depraved... flat out gross!
So, how do we
pick our new seats?
We could draw
straws or somethin'.
Great idea! And since
Cayenne and Shrade are out,
I volunteer to draw for them!
Okey-doke. Grab a good
one, between two hotties,
and you're the meat in a sexy
sandwich for the semester!
Nice to meet you. I'm Malloy.
You were in the
mock battle, huh?
Nice to meet you! I'm Ei.
Pleased to meet you.
The pleasure's all mine!
Ah, why me, man? Lame.
Of all the degenerates to
get stuck sitting next to...
Nice profile.
Really?
Great seats, don't you think?
Uh, I guess so, yeah.
Yoo hoo! Doesn't it feel
like a sauna in here?
Or is it from
sitting so close to you?
It's a bit warm.
Amata!
Studly Cayenne and lovely Shrade
sitting right in front of me.
Looks like Christmas came
early for you, Sazanka.
Oh! It's just too much!
I can't take it!
This is the first time we've
sat beside each other, right?
Yeah? It'll be the last.
Thank you for coming to
retrieve me. I'm flattered.
I'm only in town for business.
I happened to be out doing
recon up the road, so--
Eyes front.
Oh dear, your timbre
is a bit discordant.
Shut up!
It was a joke, my friend.
Damn it. Everyone else is
having the time of their lives.
And here I am,
stuck with Mr. Toad's wild
handkerchief cat-doll thingy.
Wait a second. Bingo!
Look out! It's a
Tadpole-tergeist!
What?
What's going on?
What you mean that frog thing?
Have you heard?
There's a story of an Element
who disappeared
here at Neo-DEAVA.
You serious?
They say it happened
a few years ago.
A new girl arrived
here at the Academy,
but this Element was so timid,
so shy, she never
made a single friend.
Until the fateful day,
crushed by the weight
of her solitude,
she vanished, leaving
nothing but the doll.
That's just unreal.
That's just so sad.
The poor thing had only
one true friend, her plushie.
They say the doll appears
late at night, alone,
wandering aimlessly
through the campus halls.
And if you listen, you may
hear the lost girl's sad,
lonely voice, singing her tragic
song in the glowing starlight.
You sound like an idiot.
No really, Andy knows
what he's talking about.
The doll's been seen
in the guy's dorm,
pretty much since
the Berlin fell.
Oh gosh, Malloy believes it too.
It must be true.
No, I'm scared!
The whiskered
frog-demon just moved!
Andy...
Would you just drop
the act for a minute?
Drop what act?
I'm telling you, I saw it move!
Mission complete.
Excellent work, Jin.
Thank you.
But real combat is less
forgiving than a simulation.
Remember that.
And Kagura?
That upstart has been
grounded, for the time being.
An invisible door,
a passage to the future,
a gateway to the
end of the world.
Time for a closer look.
I'll knock on the door again.
So be it. Make us proud,
Last Son of Altair.
Finally finished.
Hey there. What's up?
You're out late.
Hey, get stuck cleaning?
Man, what a rip-off.
Yup, I'm about to
head back though.
Oh, is that a fact? What luck!
I'm heading to the dorms too!
Maybe you could walk with me?
Don't be afraid, tough guy!
We can watch each other's backs!
Crap.
Oh, no, are we locked out?
Yeah, we're not
getting in this way.
Oh well, we're headin'
different places anyhow.
G'night.
Hey wait!
What?
Why don't you come
in from the girl's side?
Umm, ok. Why exactly?
Zessica! Y'know, it's kinda
hard to walk like this.
Right, sorry.
Okay, what's the problem?
Are you scared?
That's so dumb!
No way in hell, buster!
I-I ain't afraid of no ghosts,
or some stupid
moving dolls, or...
They're-- They're not even real!
Wuzzat?
That weird frog-cat.
Wait. What is that
thing doing here?
Meow meow meow meow
meow meow meow meow...
No way! It's gotta
be a practical joke.
Real funny. It--
it was just a story!
You stink like carrion.
I was scared, but
that wasn't all I felt.
It was almost like
I already knew him.
What do you think, Shush?
Stop grabbing me there!
Please don't leave me!
No, not Amata and Zessica.
Come back bastard!
The stinky wench is mine!
Keep your hands off her!
Can it be done?
Can the Last Son of Altair
lead us to redemption?
No, really, I saw it!
What, the ghost-plushie?
Yeah, wandering around in
the middle of the night!
Amata, saw it too.
Without a doubt.
C'mon man, it was all a joke.
Did you think I was serious?
Dude, it did everything
just like in your story.
It was totally walking around!
I even heard it sing.
Sh'yeah, right.
It's so cute, the things kids
convince themselves
of at this age.
You're the same
age as us, douche bag.
I have a pressing query.
That is... What were you
two doing together last night?
Uh, well Zessica--
Hey? What the--?
Please don't tell
them I was scared.
I get enough flack
for the way I dress.
Um, what are you
two whispering for?
I-- we-- uh...
Why do you refuse to
answer me? You perverts!
If you sowed your wild oats on
Academy grounds, so help me--
Sowed my what now?
I saw it too!
You saw the doll walking?
Was it gaining on us?
But what I did see
was Zess and Amata
running through the courtyard...
in each other's arms!
Then she screamed out,
"Please don't leave me!"
So they were having
a lover's quarrel?
Ah-ha! I knew it!
You got it all wrong!
Listen, Mikono, it was a--
Abductors detected in the
Neo-Kowloon area.
All Elements are to report
to phase one battle
stations immediately.
Repeat, all Elements to phase
one battle stations immediately!
Analysis complete. Pattern B.
Exactly like the simulation.
The Abductor has destroyed
our exterior fortifications!
Speed clocked at 60kph!
Well that's odd.
It isn't attempting
a single capture.
That thing's done enough damage.
Zessica. You're the
head this time.
Roger!
Awright, Cayenne,
Amata. Get going!
Roger!
Mikono, I- I'm so
sorry I let you down.
The enemy's capabilities
are still unknown.
Laser range uncalculated.
So be careful out there.
Yes, sir!
We've been ambushed!
Y'think? Where's it coming from?
It's aim. It's nearly flawless!
But how?
No one can aim a laser
with that kind of accuracy,
much less in an atmosphere.
The Radius Gnis.
Zen?
He can spot a coin from
a thousand villages away,
loose a perfect arrow, piercing
straight through to its mark!
How do you know that?
One has but to look.
Merge right now!
One hit from that thing,
and your Vector's done.
Fly low and close distance!
Emergency merge! Go! Aquarion!
Aquarion Gepard!
That area is clear.
Collateral damage is expected,
so use those
buildings for cover!
Roger!
The enemy is too far out
of range for our weapons!
But there's only one
of them out there,
and we'll close in under cover.
I can read you like a book.
I'll pin you down, and cut you
to ribbons in the crossfire.
Alert! Incoming
enemy projectiles!
Missiles, or...?
What're those?
No way!
Son of a bitch!
Where'd that come from?
Those projectiles are being
used to reflect the lasers.
The enemy could attack
Aquarion from any direction!
Very unfortunate.
It would seem taking
cover is useless.
It's like we're being shot at
by an entire freakin' army!
Zessica! Look out!
Amata!
Vector Z is taking
the brunt of the fire!
Amata's aura is dropping fast!
Just hold on!
It's hit the limit!
Vector Merge breaking!
Amata!
This is my fault!
I'm not even a
fraction of the pilot
I should be to handle Aquarion!
Zessica's aura
is falling fast, sir!
Under 40 percent...
30 percent...
But Amata's the one
taking the damage!
Zessica...
A person's heart cannot
be seen with eyes alone.
Misunderstanding drives a
wedge between the best of us.
But, remember this, child:
whether we turn a blind
eye to the fact or not,
all things have their place.
Now we shall find strength in
the things that remain unseen!
Element Change!
Replace Zessica Wong
with Yunoha Suroor!
Yunoha?
Who's that?
What?!
Is that a freakin' doll?
Hi Amata, nice to see you again!
It can talk?
Amata, Zessica, I'm very sorry
I frightened you last night,
and I'm sorry I let
Mikono misunderstand
what really happened.
Honest mistake.
If you saw that frog thing
in the middle of the night,
you'd probably lose it too.
I really am sorry.
But please guys,
you have to trust me.
Let me fight by your side!
Then you're the
missing Element, huh?
Can we save the
formalities for later?
Amata, I know
I scared you before,
but will you Merge with me?
Let's do it. I believe in you.
Trans-Spectral Merge!
Go! Aquarion!
No! They'll see me!
They'll see all of me!
Whoa, I can see her!
I really see her!
Yunoha. I see the real you!
No. I don't want to be seen,
but it feels so nice.
Aquarion Evol!
The Machine Angel
gets a new dress,
which was also covered
in the simulation.
Holy crap, she's real!
The freaky ghost-frog
girl is real!
And, man, she's kinda cute!
Stop it! You're making
me blush, I'm gonna...
I missed?
What the--?!
Aquarion just vanished!
The lasers went
right through us!
Her shyness fully
envelops her, like a shroud,
but it also makes her
transparent to sources of light.
Behold Yunoha Suroor's
Elemental power.
Like gossamer cereus
blooming in the night,
so too blooms Yunoha.
We should be careful;
I can't keep Aquarion
transparent the whole time.
I'm just not strong enough.
We'll work with
what you give us!
Your power's awesome, Yunoha!
If you keep complimenting me,
I'll get shy,
and when I get shy, I...
My lasers don't even touch it!
Okay, this was never
covered in the damn sim!
Distance 800. Now close
in and let's drop this guy!
Right!
Oh, I see, you're only
invisible to light waves.
I can't see you,
but I know you're there.
Lasers don't work,
but bullets will!
Did I get it?
Okay, yeah. This is
getting a little ridiculous.
Do it now!
All right, hit him
with the Fist Unseen!
Subliminal Punch!
We-- we got him!
They won!
Did the ghost girl do that?
The Trans-dimensional
Remote Control.
Good luck with that.
Well, at least I got to see
a new Rare Igura,
before she turned invisible.
Amata!
Mikono, hey!
Zessica told me what
really happened.
I guess I jumped to
conclusions. I am so sorry!
Don't worry about it.
Oh! Yeah, meet our new teammate!
Hello, my name's Yunoha.
So, you're the ghost
of that Element
who vanished back in
the day, is that right?
Huh?
But don't you worry.
I'm not afraid of you anymore,
'cause we're totally
comrades in arms now.
Now wait just a second.
What are you talking about,
Amata. What ghost?
Umm, there seems to be some
kind of misunderstanding.
Sorry, but-- but I'm alive.
That's Yunoha Suroor,
she's a vector pilot,
just like all of you are.
I'm sorry! Not again.
Let me down!
Oh jeez, poor Amata.
He'll fly for just
anyone, won't he?
My name's Zessica Wong.
I'm pretty famous
for a 17 year old,
mostly for how much
skin I usually show.
Well, the depths of my cleavage
may be open for all
to see, but my heart?
Off limits.
Next time on Aquarion Evol:
"Revelations."