I can't abide that noise.
Such unfathomable power.
Could he really be
the one? This boy?
Boy?
Mikage, what are you doing here?
This "boy" you speak of.
My curiosity is
piqued. Indulge me.
Very well, I shall
speak for you.
He is the angel's chevalier;
the secret spring
from whence the
enemy's power flows.
He whose eyes mint
gold, whose wild auburn locks
flutter like a tattered
ensign on the wind.
You know him.
Your soul-sick heart
aches at the sight of him;
this lambent echo
of our sleeping Eve.
The fairer sex
has long departed.
And we, Altair's sad detritus,
limn the edge of extinction.
Thus we plumbed Vega.
Thus we dared let a
sister world give hope.
Iguras.
Women of rare substance
from across time and space;
a hardy stock impervious to
the ravages of this barren land.
We sought them at great cost,
desperate to infuse our
garden once again with life.
Before you, Alicia; the supine
asphodel, the one True Eve.
Our hope manifest.
Yet her sojourn 'cross
the ineffable barrier
twixt worlds
leeched her vitality,
cast her into a deep,
death-like sleep.
Our hope extinguished.
Banishment from Eden complete.
On Vega, she bore a child.
When we came for her,
the child was discarded,
perhaps in an effort to shield
it from the mother's fate.
Not that any of this
matters now, of course.
Alicia is but a fragile
doll for you to pine over.
She is condemned to sleep,
and this world, to death.
Yet in search of
comfort you fill your eyes
with the sad sight of her.
Irony of ironies.
You know nothing of Alicia.
It truly is pathetic to behold.
This fiction that you cling to.
Tis but a contentious mirage,
an infantile fantasy.
Let us be done with it.
Banish the dream as the
reality banishes you.
Damn you!
You will not lay a hand
on her. You understand me?!
Alas, all dreamers'
needs must awaken.
All mirages give
way to the source.
Jin has infiltrated the
homebase of the Machine Angel.
What we've been working so hard
for is finally within our grasp.
Consider the butterfly.
On Vega, they are a symbol
of rebirth, renewed purpose,
the promise of life.
Perhaps love shall again
play the forbidden strain.
The old curse find purchase.
Dear Kagura.
Such. A. Beast. You. Are.
Exquisite child.
That's right, feel it.
Let it uncoil in your
bowels like a serpent.
The past writhes
to be unfettered!
Every searing piece of it,
every venomous ember.
Yes. Apollon and Silvie;
their betrayal,
their reckless
inconstancy--remember!
Even now, Silvie sidles
close to your heart,
doesn't she, my boy?
You can still hear
the delicate sigh;
the voice so sweet it could
lull the angels to sleep.
She could bring bliss
to the heavens themselves.
Her beauty could charm death
itself to relax its grip,
her soulful warmth
coax a glacier;
she is the very memory of love.
You burn to know that
love, don't you, child?
You are mad for it.
You would breathe
deep the sweetness
of her bouquet and
claim it for your own.
More. You have to want it more.
Don't stop!
Yes, that's it.
Howl, you hungry beast.
Howl for love!
Yes. Magnificent creature.
Follow that implacable nose.
Seek out the answer
to this desperate hunger.
What the hell?
Izumo.
There's something
important you should know.
Whether or not the
Rare Iguras fulfill
their purpose is
of no concern to me.
Altair's needs
and my own diverge.
I want only my angel to
rise from the ashes of Vega.
Hey, you, whoever you are.
Remember this.
I'll never trust you,
and there's not a damn thing
you can do to change that.
If you ever try anything
like that again,
I'll be coming after you myself.
What was that power?
Where did it come from?
Mister Batbayar, you're
released. Come on out.
Sneak into the
girls' dorm again,
and there will be
dire consequences.
Cayenne, You know better than
to aim a gun at your classmates.
I'm leaving you in there
so you can think
about what you've done.
What's this?
Well, um, You like Alicia.
So I made this outfit.
That's your idea of her?
I know--it's not perfect. Sorry.
But The face is good right?
Oh, not so much, I guess.
Somebody forgot their manners.
Akbarjin Batbayar isn't
who he says he is.
He's an impostor!
I fail to see what
the problem is.
What?
He did pass Neo-DEAVA's
entrance exams
with exemplary marks,
did he not?
But--
I believe what the
situation calls for--
Is isolation.
Didn't Yunoha say she gets
what Jin's going through?
Granted there's a lot
we don't know about him,
but he doesn't seem
like all that bad of a guy.
It wouldn't hurt
to get to know him.
I mean, how else you gonna know
where he's coming from, right?
Yeah, that makes sense.
I suppose you're right.
Mikono, I-I have to know...
I want to know. So badly.
I just have to ask.
About him.
About that man.
His eyes looked so desperate.
You hafta forgive him. For what?
They were sad. Like a lost dog.
Sorry we're late, peeps!
Man, you wouldn't
believe those damn lines.
Hey, what's the
deal with you two
sitting together all
mopey like this, huh?
Nothing.
I forgot my juice.
Hey, can I have a sip?
Indecent!
Whoa, that's like
an indirect kiss!
An indirect kiss?!
Hey, can I have a
sip of yours too?
Oh, uh. Why not?
Wow, Zessica.
You've had a lil' taste of
just about everybody's juice.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm good.
Something's out there!
Kagura?
Close the gate now!
On the double!
We cannot let him get to Vega!
Ah, pretty beast.
A flower for the
arduous journey ahead.
You will, I think,
come to need it.
Let us pray the gold your eyes
mint scorches an object lesson
into the heart of
my beautiful angel.
At last, the time has come.
Seriously.
I don't care if you're
so parched you crackle;
a lady simply does not act like
that in front of other people.
If you don't wanna go thirsty,
then bring your own drink.
Got it?
Jus' mind your own business.
You're my friend,
safeguarding what's left
of your rep is my business.
So do yourself a favor
next time, and think first.
Hey, where are you going?
Back to the girl's dorms.
But, don't you have
afternoon classes to attend?!
Zessica, hang on!
See, look. I tried
to stitch it evenly.
Unfortunately, it didn't
work out too well.
I'm not very good at this stuff.
Aww man. This is so bittersweet!
What a beat down!
I think it's kinda awesome.
More than anything, I just
hope Jin opens up to her.
So what, you think this
isn't going to affect you?!
Listen dude, the ladies
are always thirsty for love;
I mean it's how they're wired.
Did you already forget what
happened with Zess at lunch?
What are you trying to say?
If you really want it,
bro, dig deep.
Bore a well into
Mikono's heart. Get it?
A well into her heart...
Too much is in the way.
Love's not allowed, remember?
For now, yeah.
But once this dumb war
with the Abductors is
over, it's open season.
You better lock
her down and fast.
Lock her down?
Look: Mikono's way
hotter than you, dude.
If you dilly-dally for too long,
some choad's gonna get
his talons in 'er and boom.
Uh hey, Mikono.
Can we uh-- can we talk?
Uh, okay.
Yo! I didn't mean now!
I knew there was a reason
I made the guy
my hole digging bro.
Do it like it's your job, Red.
No!
Kagura!
You have lost your
senses completely.
You are forbidden
to travel to Vega!
Go to Hell!
Kagura! Get out of the Mithra
and go back to base or
we will take you out!
Fuck you!
Stay out of my way
or you're all dead!
You decrepit son of a bitch.
The way I see it you
have two options here.
Open the gate or I smash
the Ianthe. Understood?!
Men, we're under attack.
All pilots report
to battle stations for
defensive protocols.
I don't believe it.
His strength has
become otherworldly.
What in the hell
gave him such a spike?
Blooms out of season.
But falls in a blink.
Such a flower is
the Kagura camellia.
Do we have an
accord now, old friend?
What I have done with this
life, I have done for love.
What the hell?
Sir! All units have
cleared the line of fire!
Awaiting orders!
Take the bastard out.
She's mine! She's mine!
Dear, fervent boy.
Does love not burn?
What does Mikono
have that I don't?
I know she's a total
knockout, but still.
Apollon.
Silvie.
Mikono? Something wrong?
So, what did you
want to talk about?
Um. Well, I...
Yeah?
It's about... that guy.
Lock her down and fast.
No! Wait! It's not like that!
Like what?
No! Ignore me, that
isn't what I meant!
See, the thing is, I-I, uh--
Oh crap!
What's the matter?
Uh, sorry.
Could you look over there?
Just for a second, don't
look at me. Pretty please?!
Umm, so... not right now,
but eventually, uh...
Yeah?
After this whole thing with
the Abductors is done with.
Would you-- would you want to--
Howl for me, beast.
Let it ring out.
Absence from those
we love is self from self;
a deadly banishment.
But all is not lost.
A howl may yet turn
the tide in your favor.
Yes, you have
the gift of reversal.
It's so cold.
I feel their attacks. Like ice.
Hold still, Kagura!
It reeks.
I'm sick of this.
I want her dead.
I want to take her in my arms.
Squeeze her.
And crush her to dust.
I'm coming for you.
Silvie!
Good show.
What I'm saying is,
would you...?
Are you alright?
What is this crazy power?
Mikage! This is
your doing, monster!
As soon kindle fire with snow,
as seek to quench the
flames of love with words.
Our boy is merely
answering his hunger.
Fly, Kagura. Rain hell
upon that which burns you.
Journey to the
Holy Land of Love!
That day at the movies,
when I saw your face, I took
flight for the first time.
I've been soaring ever since,
and my feet have barely
touched the ground.
I think I'm in love!
Next time: "Skies of Aquaria."