Get a hold of yourself.
It's only another
stupid nightmare.
Another friggin' ill-omened
twinge of phantom pain.
But something's up.
I can feel it.
Suomi!
Stay calm; let's focus
on evacuation.
Right.
Come on, come on!
Crap. None of you
got the right stink.
Where the hell is
my Sylvie, dammit?!
Oh, no.
Hang on!
Why, Jin? I trusted you.
Oh gosh, you're one of them.
Why couldn't I just
accept the obvious?
What?
I wasn't trying...
It was just-- It was
just sitting there.
Guys! What are you doing?!
Get to the shelter!
Mix, what the hell?!
What?
Look out!
Yunoha!
The enemy mech is taking
out our auto-cannons!
We're down to 28%!
The commons have been cleared.
Cadets are safe in the shelter.
Except, well, we still have
over twenty unaccounted for.
Dammit!
Launch gate standing by.
Repeat: launch gate standing by.
I know who it is. Has to be.
He...
Mikono, whatever's out there,
you and I are in this together.
I will protect you.
Oh Amata.
And I'll protect you. Got that?
Yes ma'am.
Okay, either get a room
or get out there
and kick some ass.
Now, let's do this!
Roger!
Right. Let's blast
him off the base.
Counterattack Merge!
Go!
Aquarion!
Aquarion Evol!
There's the stench.
Couldn't stay away, could ya?
Oh, yeah. Come to me, Sylvie!
How the hell did he do that?!
He's on our comm frequency?!
My chest. What is this pain?
Infinity Punch!
Hell, no!
The Infinity Punch!
He threw it back in their face!
Son of a...
I'm reading abnormally
high aura levels
from the Mithra Gnis!
Wait, are those-- are
those Element sigils?!
Impossible. Surely the Abductor
can't be one of our own.
Damn straight!
The power of reversal.
Excuse me, what?
If hatred is love transformed,
then light is blackest
night upended.
Fire, the twin brother of ice.
Good heavens. He's changing
the laws of physics!
There.
Jin. Where...?
Hey, sleepyhead.
What're you...?
I'm taking you back with me.
Huh?
To Altair. Okay?
That's where I come from.
Please, you can't!
Jin listen. Up there.
What do you think that sound is?
That's the people who accepted
you fighting for their lives!
So what?! Some of us
have a job to do, okay?!
Jin...
They're fighting for
their lives right now
because I sold
them up the river!
You understand that?
This whole thing was about you--
from the first line of
bullshit to the last.
Because Altair needs you.
Stop it! Let go of me!
Security breach!
One of the Vectors is attempting
to make an unauthorized
launch! Please advise!
You're kidding me!
Got a visual on the pilot?
Son of a bitch! What did
I say?! He's a damn spy!
Dude, this is crazy.
Oh, wow.
That creep.
Well, I guess we all knew he
was hiding something, right?
Permission to deal with him?
Permission granted.
Zessica, get my back!
Done!
Y'wanna play?!
What is with this guy?!
This is more than
an unlocked skill.
It's like he's
quadrupled in strength
since our last run
in with him. Now what?
Something's coming through!
Those look like
tendrils of energy.
Something from the
other side of the gate
is feeding him
concentrated light!
What are we standing
around for, then?
Close the damn thing!
I fear the light is
making that impossible.
The red strand of fate.
What did you say?
High Commander.
Reveal the skein
from whence this
tangled thread descends.
Show yourself, beast!
Very well. Ask and
ye shall receive.
It can't be.
What is going on?
You bastard!
I thought-- I thought
you liked it here.
That you liked us.
Was that all just
part of the act?
Shut up!
No. No I won't.
We took you in without question,
and not just because
it was our job.
You were one of us!
No.
You're full of shit!
Yeah, run while you can.
The scion of a
dying breed returns
to his people as
a beacon of hope.
Who are you?!
He's beautiful.
You will stop all of
this nonsense, at once!
Oh, no-- what have you done?!
Donar! Wake up!
How the years melt away.
Or perhaps I should say eons?
Shall we measure the
time in losses or gains?
What does he mean?
Nice to finally
get a look at you.
I wish I could say the same
for the regrettable veneer
you've chosen to
swathe yourself in.
Why trade your genuine
form for this shambles?
Has it eluded you?
A wise man said illusion is
the first of all pleasures.
Yet every sleight of
hand binds us to the past.
A shame your own
form is distilled only
from those vicissitudes
congruent with hate.
Perhaps. But enough philosophy.
The Wings of Apollonius,
their amber radiance.
Where do they lie?
I would know
Solar Wing's touch again.
Oh, no! That's Aquarion!
Jin, please! Let me help them!
You've got to take me back.
Please, Jin.
They're your friends.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Ah, that's the stuff.
Show me the goods.
Amata, I...
Oh, baby. Oh, baby!
My sweet Sylvie!
Silvie?!
You little bitch.
I've loathed you
since the moment we met!
My tainted Sylvie!
Stop it! Let me go!
Sylvie? Mikono!
Of course, first you die!
I'm gonna crush you slowly
like a melon. Forever.
No. No!
Mikono!
Fucker!
I've got you!
So, the lil' guy
without a scent.
We gotta stop
meeting like this, boy.
You're gettin'
to be a real pain.
You're out of your damn mind.
Rule of thumb in
my neck o' the woods,
you don't smell,
you don't exist.
You're just a phantom limb
that needs to be forgotten.
Thanks for the memories.
Let's get that heart
pumpin' backwards, huh?
Magnificent.
The net is closing on you.
Your own beacon of hope will
be summarily extinguished.
Speak, old friend.
For the sake of a
love that bridges eons.
Solar Wing. Where does it lie?
Oh, of course.
How rude of me.
Blame sleep, Donar Dantes.
You are anything
but forgettable.
Till we meet again.
That was a tulpa; a
projection of pure thought.
Miss Suomi, Raise the
Element Jammer immediately.
Yes, ma'am.
Please, no.
See ya.
Huh?
Amata!
You guys all right?!
Andy! Mix!
What a relief!
I thought you
two were pulverized!
Couldn'ta planned
it better, right?
Actually I was just diggin'
us to safety and Ass-hat
was in the wrong
place at the right time.
Bastards!
You've bought yourselves
a life reversal!
Go on, I dare ya!
Damnit!
Hang in there, sis!
Cayenne!
And Shrade!
Enough chatter. Re-board
your Vectors and merge!
Roger!
Ma'am, with all due respect the
damn gate's still wide open.
I've got this.
Trust me, I can close it.
Trust you?!
Akbar-jin Bat-bayar.
Young man...
Wait! That's not who
I am. I'm Jin Muso!
Whatever you're
called, you're dead!
You have to believe him!
He's changed. He's accepted
that he's one of us now.
Yunoha, he's using
you! Get a grip!
You don't wanna believe me,
Cayenne, that's your right.
But listen, the thing I'm gonna
do, the power to isolate?
This place is
what brought it out,
and without it the gate's
not gonna get shut!
But you were...
You need to merge with me.
A bridge too far.
Oh, no!
How sweet is
treacherous love. How costly.
Stop it! Leave her alone!
Yunoha!
What's wrong?!
Jin!
No, it's okay.
Everything in his bag
of tricks is an illusion.
You're sure?
Look, there's no time.
We've got to merge!
Alright, fine! Get it over with!
Sonata for four hands!
Go!
Aquarion!
Artillery Merge!
Go!
Aquarion!
This is it.
Magnificent!
A rich, complex timbre!
My blood is on fire!
A boundary is breaking.
This-- This is beautiful.
This is us!
Aquarion Gepard!
Aquarion Spada!
Whoa.
Well done, my friend. Brava!
Playtime's over, children!
His tone is jarring.
We'll be shaken to pieces!
Yunoha!
Aura levels dropping rapidly!
Vital signs: unstable!
He-- he's killing them!
The hell he is.
Please, don't.
You're hurt too badly.
It's just an illusion!
I'm fine! Let me
do what I have to!
I know what's real.
So do I.
What're you...?
We're in this together.
All of us.
Together.
Ditto.
We're all in sync!
What?
What is that light?
That which connects
separate eternities.
Light which sutures the void.
The Gepard form is
spawning a new arsenal!
How is this possible?!
Say hello to evolution!
I think Aquarion likes you.
We'll hold him off;
you seal the gate.
Right. Let's do this!
Roger!
Ready.
I hope you know
what you're doing.
Shielding our dimension.
Now!
They've formed
an isolation field!
Yes.
Observe the tempo carefully.
Right!
Now, from the top.
A clarifying interruzione!
Reversal!
Molto risoluto!
No!
Dimension gate is sealed!
Spada and Gepard
are fully intact!
We did it, Jin, we--
Jin?
It's okay. Totally worth it.
You were worth it.
Hey, don't cry, at least--
at least you got me out of my
shell. Right?
I want to flit away on
a gentle spring breeze,
be scattered like
a summer dandelion.
Your face waits for me
on the autumn moon,
only to be obscured by
winter's iron-gray clouds.
Without you, the seasons are...