This piano is in perfect tune,
yet the tone is corrupted.
Our latest addition.
I'm Akbarjin Batbayar.
A pleasure.
Akbal-- Akbarjin, rather
scored record-setting marks
on the Meso-Asiatic
curriculum we sponsor overseas.
He is a candidate for the
reserve Vector pilot program,
so I expect you all to
make him feel welcome.
Yeah, well, I hope
he can pull his weight.
W--whoa, actual Rare Iguras.
I betcha he likes to dig,
whaddya think, Red?
Uh... Sure, why not?
He's kinda cute. Maybe.
He's a bottom. Must be.
Wait, or, he could
be switch--hitter!
Could you at least
try to control yourself
around the newbie, please?
Hey--hey!
See somethin' you like?
You could do a lot worse.
No, it's not-- it's
not what you think,
I- I was remembering
my first day.
Did you train co-ed
back home, or what?
Give 'im a break.
You can find that online.
What kind of music
do you chill out to?
Did we come on too strong?
Or is he a jerk?
How the hell am
I supposed to survive this?
Focus, stay observant and alert.
So, know your way
around the school yet?
We'll give you a tour.
Observant. Alert.
Observant...
Uh, nevermind!
I get to show you
around campus. Hop to.
That's what's left
of the Berlin.
Used to be a dividing wall--
guys on one side,
girls on the other,
none shall pass kinda thing,
but part of it got
smashed, so now...
Hey, I'm not talkin'
to myself here.
At least look.
Dude, seriously. You got
bangs like a friggin' girl.
Don't touch me!
'Kay, fine, whatever. Happy now?
This is Neo-DEAVA's
nerve center.
It's where all our
data gets stored,
and where the brass
direct Aquarion from.
What's Aquarion?
Feel encouraged to scrutinize.
Just know you'll
see things as they are
only if your intentions
are sincere.
Yeah, anyway. Aquarion?
Somebody got railroaded
through basic training.
It's what the
Aquarias are called now.
The Machine Angels.
That's it right over there.
Go easy on him,
tough guy. He's new.
I'm not busting his balls, am I?
I might beg to differ.
Piss off.
C'mon, don't get
bent outta shape!
Now's not the time to try
and ruffle my feathers!
I just don't want
you leading him
by the collar like you did me.
You were puttin' moves
on my sister, jackass!
The hell I was!
I mean, not then anyway...
Oh, I get it,
so now she's fair game?
Wait, what? No!
That's not what I meant. Um...
Where did he go?
Sweet, so these are
all pieces of the angel.
Not like I can stuff
it under my coat.
We don't need you to
bring back the whole thing,
just one of the component ships.
Still kind of a tall order.
Only risk it if
you see an opening.
Your priority is
still the Rare Iguras;
keep your eyes peeled
for the True Eve.
All of Altair is buzzing with
the news of your survival, Jin.
Complete your mission and come
back to us as soon as possible.
Understood?
Yeah, sounds like everybody's
really worried about me.
I'm sorry?
Nothing.
Stay safe.
Infiltrate Neo-DEAVA, but don't
put yourself in the crosshairs.
Whatever you say. Over and out.
It's cool that you're
Alicia's birthplace and all,
but I'm not homesteading.
An unsecured terminal
in the dead of night,
leapfrog a couple firewalls,
find a prospective
transfer student,
make a few tweaks to his
pertinent data, and boom.
What's a little
grand larceny, right?
I can do this.
Damn right, clear a path.
I've got better things
to do than make small talk.
Oh for crying out loud,
did you bury a bone?!
When the spirit moves me, I dig.
It's a calling!
You're not the boss of me.
I don't gotta explain!
Pig.
My arms are stuck!
Sucks to be you.
Uh, okay. What the hell?
Surely I'm not the
only one to have noticed
the crumbling sense of
discipline around here.
Really? You stop me
in the hallway for this?
Don't take that
attitude with me!
Look, they just need
some time to adjust.
The wall bein' down
is new for everyone.
Well, forgive me for thinking
you of all people would be
worried about the cadets giving
in to the siren song of love.
So don't approve any more
merges, and we'll be golden.
We got bigger
fish to fry, sister.
But--!
Calm down.
You're gonna give yourself
crow's feet or somethin'.
Do not walk away from me when
I am trying to have a serious--
Ahhh! Oh dear. Eww!
Note to self: Rare Iguras
are not to be trifled with!
Come on, girls!
I got the next one!
Okay, not what I expected.
These girls are about as far
from Silvie as you can get.
Busted!
Ugh! Peeping Tom!
Aw, why's it gotta be the noob?
See? I knew something
was off about him.
We got a perv! Lock the doors!
Your story'd better be good.
What story? He was
trying to see us naked!
I say we quarter him!
Um, excuse me...
Don't get mad, I think this
is all a big misunderstanding.
He just got turned around.
I used to all the time.
I even wandered into the
boy's locker room once.
Oh, it was awful.
Who is she?
Well damn.
Truth: you stumble in here by
accident or are you a creep?
The first one! I swear!
R-really! Cross my heart!
Yo! Sheepdog, or--
Don't help me... Akbar-John?
Sorry.Your name's kinda tough.
Let's shorten it to Jin. Cool?
Andy. Put 'er there, Jin.
Or be a dick!
These people.
Hey, sheepdog.
How ya feel about holes?
Sorry?
Holes! You know!
Holes? Seriously?
Clearly alone-time isn't a
prized commodity in this one.
Oh and then he was all, like,
"you don't even know"
You believe that?
Like I'm not trying to deal
with my own issues over here,
right? What a jerk!
That's exactly what's going on.
He's not happy unless
he can make you feel bad
'cause there's
nothing you can do.
I'm telling you, walk away.
He's not worth it.
What the hell? Word salad;
that's all this is.
It's like Rare Iguras
only speak in code.
Mind if we sit here, or...?
Oh, hi, guys. Sure. Be my guest.
You about to go invisible again?
Nah, I'm fine now. Thank you.
What's the matter?
Um, I'm not really
good with apologies,
but I owe you one, so I'm very
sorry for freaking you guys out!
Aw, totally ancient history.
Water under the bridge;
Mikono just let herself get
a little freaked out, you know?
So it's my fault?!
No! I-- forget I said anything.
Oh, well, you have
point, though.
I mean, I did--
You're good together.
Huh, you think so?
That's sweet of you.
Oh... Hey, Jin.
Jin?
Yep, we kept butchering
the poor dude's name,
so Andy came up with
something short and sweet.
I'm gonna go out on
a limb and say he's shy.
I'm worried about him.
Uh, I-- Not like that.
I just know how hard
it is when you're new.
Yeah.
Thing is, I didn't know
I could vanish till
they transferred me here.
Everyone crowded me;
wanted to ask questions.
They meant well, sure,
but it was so overwhelming.
I just didn't know
how to respond, I guess.
Before too long,
I was the wallflower.
I withdrew; people
stopped noticing me.
It made me start thinking.
How cool would it
be if I could really,
just, you know, disappear.
Poof. And sometimes,
if you wish hard enough,
well, you know the rest.
Explains a lot.
Nobody's fault
but my own, really.
They reached out to
me in the beginning.
I just didn't reach back.
I'm pretty sure Jin's going
through the same thing.
That's the girl from the
locker room, isn't it?
Not a triumphant
stance, I notice.
Dude, make friends with the sun.
You look like hell.
You're in a unique position
to judge. Bad dream?
The wedding dressed
as a funeral again?
That and a one-eyed giant.
A Cyclops? New wrinkle.
What do you think it means?
If I knew I wouldn't be sulking.
Anyway, got something you
want to unload on me?
As it happens,
I do--a new sound,
one I'm quite certain
you need to be aware of.
Go on.
It's rather small, stands out
against the cacophony
of this place, though.
I can't be sure, of course,
but I believe it might have
something to do with
our stray Abductor.
Okay, that's weird.
What am I looking at?
Now they make even less sense.
Didn't think that was possible.
Son of a--!
Sorry! My fault!
That belongs to me. Oh, Jin!
Where'd she go?!
Um. Here.
Thank you very much.
I hope I didn't break
your gadget, though.
What are you talking about?
It's okay. I-- I don't think
it's wrong to have or anything.
You kinda threw me for a loop,
I mean, you know, vanishing
into thin air, which is cool.
Really?
Well, yeah! Gives you privacy.
Huh-- I guess it does.
I'd love to have that power.
It'd get all these
people off my back.
I dunno. It sorta gets old.
Nuh-uh!
No, seriously, it's lonely.
It'd be bliss!
No-- it wouldn't.
Trust me, you'd hate it.
When I think of all the
people who put themselves
out there for me, and the
way I- I just ignored 'em...
Sorry, not your problem.
Well--
A new sound that stands out
against everything else.
A one-eyed giant.
It can't be a coincidence. This
kid's got something to hide.
Mix-- Elemental Power:
spatial augmentation.
Filling holes, basically.
Huh, interesting.
Index 112; aura pattern Level A.
Yo, Jin-dog! Wanna get
your fingernails dirty?
Aw, c'mon man.
You're the reason
these things have locks.
Another stupid hole;
gimme a break.
Aw crap. Yunoha Suroor--
Elemental Power:
optical fluoroscopy.
I've poured over your data,
Jin. Excellently done.
Thanks.
Thus far, everything seems
consistent with our predictions.
Odds are favorable that
one of these Rare Iguras is
who we're looking for.
Our True Eve may be within
a stone's throw of you.
Yeah, good luck
trying to wrangle her.
Take it from me,
boss, they may look all fragile
at first blush,
but they got skills.
No joke, their secret
weapon is crazy.
And that would
be what, precisely?
Crying.
What? I'm not following you.
Look, the one that shot me down.
It turns out, she and I...
Has she found you out?
No, not exactly.
The more dangerous
they are, the better.
Bring her back with you.
Huh?
I suspect our True Eve won't
turn out to be a Rare Igura
who's anything less
than willful, my boy.
No kidding? You're in?
Ha! Had a feelin' you'd
come around eventually!
Fair warning. It's a
little intense with him.
Aw, Red. Don't be jelly.
There's plenty
Andy for everybody.
Ugh! Dude. Please.
Hey, hey! It's okay.
We're all DBs here
now, aren't we?
Kinda wasn't in
the mood for this.
Respect. Nice.
Take it in. This is why we
risk it all for the dig, dude.
Our Paradise Found!
What's the hold up, Red?
A gentleman doesn't
keep the ladies waitin'!
Drag-ass. Least be
enthusiastic for Jin's--
Wait a minute.
Great.
Jin! You there?
Shh!
Real good way to get
the hole filled, dude.
Keep it on the QT.
Always about the
hole with you, huh?
Found you. 'Kay, then.
Just doin' my job. No choice.
Jin, what're-- ?
Be cool, I just--
I wanted to, uh--
pick up where we left off.
About being lonely
and stuff, you know?
This is too much. What do I do?
I mean, he's-- he's
reaching out, I guess.
That's good, right?
Maybe for both of us?
Never mind, then. No, wait!
Did you hear that?
That was totally a stun-gun!
One-man panty raid?
This isn't what it looks like.
I just wanna talk to her.
My ass! If you think I buy
you as a transfer student
you're out of your damn mind.
Cayenne, wait!
Get off me! I just
have some questions!
Ease off, man.
I don't think so!
Stop! He's telling the truth!
Heads up!
Okay, didn't see that comin'.
Son of a bitch. He's an Element.
Whoa, was that-- was that me?
The tone is still a bit jarring.
But perhaps it is beginning
to make sense harmonically.
Isolation can be a gift,
and yet, for all our
fortress building, life is
guaranteed to find its way in.
What then, dear boy?
So weird. She's like, every
other thought in my head.
The last time I felt this
way was when Alicia came out
for the cameras in big,
poofy bloomers. Except worse!
Next time on Aquarion Evol:
"Call of the Wild."