♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the Eleventh Universe's Pride
Troopers challenged Hit,
demonstrating their
spectacular abilities
and effectiveness as a team!
[DYSPO gasping]
Wait a minute.
What are you doing, Goku?
[NARRATOR]
Seeing this impressive display,
the fight-loving Goku couldn't
help but join the fray.
[DYSPO groans]
[yells]
Uh.
The only thing you'll be
taking with you is pain.
[yelps]
[K'NSI groans, screams]
K'nsi!
So now what?
Is this the part where
you and I start fighting?
I'll let you go for now.
As thanks for your help.
If you make it all
the way through,
we're gonna settle this
once and for all.
That's how this is gonna end.
Heh. Fine by me.
[NARRATOR] The battle for cosmic
survival ramps up... now!
[NARRATOR] "A Valiant Fight!
Master Roshi's Blaze of Glory!"
[FUTURE ZENO] So how many
fighters are left now?
[ZENO]
Well, let's see.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight...
Uhh... Uh.
One, two, three,
four, five, um...
Uh, there is a lot!
Lots and lots!
[MAGETTA]
Whoot-whooo!
[ROSHI]
Hmm...
[BIARRA grunting]
Well, now. Looks like we're
down to less than half.
Guess it's about time
I stepped up.
[ROSHI grunts]
Easy target!
[ROSHI]
Heh!
[gasps] He got away?
[ROSHI chuckles]
[CAWAY gasps]
Transforming your energy into
a big ol' mallet like that--
for a pretty young thing
such as yourself,
it's an impressive technique.
[CAWAY]
Oh, gee, thanks.
And y'know, for an old goat,
you're pretty spry.
Listen, I've gotta warn ya,
you don't have the power
that it would take to stop me.
I'm only telling you that
'cause I'd rather not
raise my hand to a girl.
Oh...?
You talk a big game Gramps,
but you have no idea
what I'm capable of!
That's where you're wrong.
I've been watching
this whole time.
Ever since this crazy
tournament began.
Sizing up who uses
what techniques,
and how strong everyone is, too.
[CAWAY] Oh, really?
Well, in that case...
Then I wonder, do you know
about my other signature move?
[ROSHI]
Hm?
[CAWAY]
Mm... Heh.
[ROSHI gasps]
[CAWAY laughs]
Her move is seduction?
Then she's in for a surprise.
Roshi went through
some intense training
to brace himself against
just this kinda thing.
There's no possible way
it could work on him.
[laughing]
[chuckles]
It worked on him! [groans]
[ELDER KAI]
Hubba, hubba!
Get a load of those shoulders!
Stop that, please,
this does not befit a Kai!
[gasping]
Come to mama!
Whoot-whooo!
[MAGETTA]
"Whoot-whooo"?
[ROSHI laughing]
[CAWAY laughs]
Ha, not in a million years!
[ROSHI sputters]
[yells]
[ROSHI grunts]
[CAWAY gasps]
Whew, that was close.
Almost trimmed my beard.
[CAWAY]
What... But... But how?!
How does such a decrepit
old man have so much power?
[CAWAY grunting]
[CAWAY screams]
[gasps]
[ROSHI grunting]
[CAWAY whimpers]
[ROSHI]
Up until recently,
I let frivolous desires
dictate my life.
But now, I've pushed all those
silly distractions aside.
[CAWAY whimpers]
[ROSHI]
Do you know what that means?
[CAWAY whimpers]
[ROSHI growling]
[screams]
[ROSHI] It means all the energy
I once squandered
is filling up my body to the
point it can't be contained.
It's exploding inside me
like hot, burning magma!
[whimpering]
[ROSHI]
Just remember, you're the one
who awakened a dormant volcano.
So, you'll have to deal with
the burn that comes with it!
[screams]
No! Help! I don't want that
gnarly dude anywhere near me!
[sighs] Whoa, that was close.
How could you?!
Huh, not too shabby.
Though he did have me
nervous there for a second.
Yeah. It was obviously
just an act.
Or, at least I think
it was. Heh, heh.
In that case,
great work! Bravo!
[ROSHI sighs]
[ROSHI]
All right, who's next?
You wanna challenge me,
or you just gonna keep hiding?
[DERCORI] Oh, so you knew
I was here all along?
[DERCORI laughs]
I've been watching you fight,
too. Studying your moves.
The talisman artist of
the Fourth Universe.
That could work.
You'll be the perfect
palate cleanser for me.
Don't you patronize me!
[ROSHI grunts]
[ROSHI] Hm? Not even warm.
It's just an illusion.
That's right,
they are but mere mirages.
[ROSHI grunts]
[DERCORI yelling]
[ROSHI]
Hm?
[DERCORI] So, you really
have been watching me,
and believe you are
prepared to defend.
But, my mystical technique is
all about sewing uncertainty,
with 76 talismans to strike
and 129 to confuse.
Think you can tell
the difference, old man?
[ROSHI panting]
[ROSHI]
It's another illusion.
Now, where'd she disappear to?
What the...?
[ROSHI groans]
[DERCORI]
I've got you now.
Is that the real her
or just a decoy?
Hm?
As you can see, I've
pinned down your shadow.
Now you're stuck there,
unable to move from that spot.
[ROSHI growls]
[DERCORI]
My world is a very dark place
that light barely reaches.
I don't do so well
in bright locales.
But on the other hand, get me in
the dark and I am unstoppable!
Oh, great. On top
of the illusions,
now she's powering up?
You'll never lay
a finger on me now!
You're probably right.
But lucky for me,
I'm the perfect guy to
deal with your nonsense.
[DERCORI growls]
Is that a...?
[ROSHI] My teammates
are all pretty good
when it comes to meeting
strength with strength.
Problem is, they're
a little too earnest
when it comes to doing battle.
They tend to get tripped up
by opponents who fight dirty.
[ROSHI] Fortunately,
they have me to handle
sneaky folk like you who rely
on all manner of trickery.
Because I've got no problem
with getting down in the gutter!
Evil Containment!
[DERCORI screaming]
[ROSHI grunting]
[screaming continues]
[ROSHI grunts]
There. That's two down now.
Yeah, that's what I
like to see, old man!
Why not seal the rest of the
competition while you're at it?
Hey, that's no fair!
Just what is your deal?
They explicitly said no bringing
outside equipment into the ring!
If that gadget's allowed,
then why not restoratives
and poison needles, too?
I didn't hear you raising
a stink when your fighter
started using
talismans as weapons!
That's just energy
shaped like talismans!
So it's completely
on the up and up!
Well, my guy's attack
is energy-based, too!
The jar's just an accessory!
So it's on the up and up!
It's cheating!
Up and up!
[QUITELA]
Cheating, cheating, cheating!
[BEERUS]
Up and up and up and up!
[QUITELA, BEERUS chattering]
[ZENO]
It's allowed.
[BOTH gasp]
It is fun, so I say
it is allowed.
Very allowed.
[BOTH]
Yes, sires.
Thank goodness they
ruled in our favor.
I just hope Master Roshi is all
right after that fight with her.
[KAIS gasp]
[KRILLIN] Using the Evil
Containment Wave
on someone as strong as her
must've taken a heck
of a toll on his body.
[ROSHI sighs]
Hey. I'm two-for-two,
you guys. Sweet!
[sputters]
Well, he seems all right to me.
Woo-hoo! Heh, heh!
Gah!
Whoa, hey! The heck was that?!
[ROSHI]
Hm?
You took out my friends.
Two of them.
Now prepare to pay
dearly for that.
Are you kidding?
Does everybody in
the Fourth Universe
wanna get their
butt kicked by me?
All right,
come at me, pipsqueak.
[GANOS growls]
You old geezer!
[yelling]
[GANOS grunting]
A transformation, eh?
I'm gonna tear you apart!
Whoa, he transformed!
He's a lot bigger now!
[FUTURE ZENO]
That was super cool!
[ZENO]
Super-duper cool!
You wrinkly old bag of bones.
I'll break you!
[GANOS groans]
What a bland attack. I could
see it coming from a mile away.
Damn it! I let my anger
get the best of me.
You're like an old,
rotted-out twig.
You're easy to snap!
Why can't I get you?!
[ROSHI]
Your face may have changed,
but your fighting style hasn't.
Up, up, down, down,
left, right, left, right.
[GANOS]
It's talon time!
Grand Eagle!
[ROSHI]
Nope.
[GANOS grunts]
What the--? I've gotta be
ten times faster
than you, Grandpa!
[GANOS groans]
Yeah, and you've got
more power than me, too.
[groaning]
[ROSHI] But see, I have
something you don't...
...experience.
Show these whipper-snappers
how it's done!
[GANOS groaning]
And that makes three-for-three.
One old man took out three
of our best fighters?
I'm not out yet...
Now I'm really angry!
[GANOS grunts]
[GANOS yells]
This could get a little ugly.
[GANOS grunting]
[ROSHI groans]
[ELDER KAI]
Oh!
Ooh, that one had to hurt!
This is bad!
[GANOS]
Ha!
Well! I have to say
that was a surprise!
[QUITELA laughs]
He underestimated the
advantages of youth.
Oh? And what do
you mean by that?
[QUITELA] They are resilient
and impressionable.
Surrounded by the best
fighters in the cosmos,
Ganos gets stronger every
minute he's in the ring.
Ah, to be young
and still growing!
[GANOS yells]
[GOKU] Roshi! Hang on!
I'll be right there!
This is no time to be
worrying about your master.
You enjoy that?
Must've rattled your old bones.
[ROSHI groaning]
It looks like you're running out
of steam there, eh, Grandpa?
[panting]
[ROSHI] I've gotta do
something about this punk
or he's just gonna
keep getting stronger
till he's powerful enough
to threaten even Goku.
I'll have to nip
this in the bud.
You are... getting sleepy...
You are getting... so tired...
Ooh!
When you hear me sing...
--...your eyelids will drop.
--[GANOS] So tired...
[ROSHI]
Sleepy boy...
Enough!
[GANOS screams]
Did he just shock himself?
His singing was bad, but...
[GANOS groaning]
If you had tried something
like that five minutes ago,
it might've worked on me.
What in the...?
[ROSHI groans]
[KRILLIN gasps]
Well, he lasted longer
than I thought he would.
He's an inspiration to feeble
old codgers everywhere.
[ROSHI groans]
[panting]
I can imagine you must have been
a pretty decent fighter
in your time.
But unfortunately for you,
that time has come and gone!
[ROSHI groaning]
Still trying to get back up?
Stop embarrassing yourself!
Just accept your limitations and
ease gracefully into retirement!
My limitations--
can go straight to hell!
No! Don't do it, Master Roshi!
Yeah, don't push too hard!
[ROSHI]
Goku... Krillin...
You're the ones who
showed this ol' fossil
he still had something
left to give.
That it was too soon
to let the limits
of age sentence him to sit
idly by on the sidelines.
You boys, who were
never content to stop,
who kept aiming for and climbing
greater and greater heights,
want me to take it easy?
Oh no you don't!
[ROSHI yelling]
[GANOS]
Come on, just go down already!
Now listen to me, boys!
[BOTH gasp]
Always remember these words:
work hard, study well,
and eat and sleep plenty!
That is the Turtle Hermit way!
We must master the art of peace
in addition to the art of war!
Shut up and fight!
[ROSHI] The Turtle Hermit School
will be with you... always!
This will be my greatest,
most powerful Kamehame-Ha!
[GANOS grunts]
Oh, come on, Ganos!
Not you, too?!
I knew you could do it,
you old coot!
Hold on, that's no old coot--
that's Master Roshi!
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[KRILLIN gasping]
Master Roshi, no!
Wait, you can't do that!
You aren't allowed to
go back in the ring!
Goku, please!
Roshi!
Hang on, we're in the middle
of something here!
Outta my way!
Master!
Master Roshi!
C'mon, wake up!
You've got to get up, Roshi!
Please, Master Roshi, wake up.
Wake up! Wake up!
Come on, Goku!
You can do it.
Wake up for me, please!
Master Roshi...?
[coughs]
[GOKU, KRILLIN gasp]
[ROSHI coughing]
[GOKU]
It worked! You're alive again!
Hey, where'd all those
spunky little angels fly off to?
Oh, Master Roshi!
Oh, Master Roshi, you're okay!
[GOKU]
Thank goodness...
[ROSHI] That's enough now.
The fight ain't over yet.
Get up and lend me
your shoulder, boy.
[GOKU sniffles]
[laughs]
[KRILLIN exhales]
Oh, what a relief.
[BEERUS]
Hey, Curly.
Yes, sir?
That old fossil. Just what did
you say his name was again?
[GOKU]
Man, I really thought
you'd crossed over
to Other World.
[ROSHI laughs]
I did!
There were cute, spunky
angels everywhere!
Far as the eye could see!
[GOKU chuckles] You sure
you weren't just dreaming?
[ROSHI]
Well...
[ROSHI, GOKU laugh]
[NARRATOR] And so, Master Roshi
overcame his own limitations,
and pressed on.
Thirty-four minutes remain until
the Tournament of Power
comes to an end.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super!
When the time has come
to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever in my mind
as I look up to the sky
I was watching you
from your left side
Was trying to get
a good look at your face
The tears in your eyes;
were you laughing or crying?
Your long hair in the way
Blocking the thoughts inside
When the time has
come to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever I will wait,
for the light to show the way
For us to meet again
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
So there's a
crackerjack marksman
from Universe Two
who's after us,
and his aim seems to find us
no matter where we hide!
There's a flurry of attacks
and even I can't tell
where they're coming from!
If this keeps up,
we're in serious danger
of being taken out!
Vegeta! Tien!
We've got a make-or-break
fight ahead of us here!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Find them Out! Deathmatch
with a Furtive Attacker!"
Whatever that means...
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?