♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
only three teams were left
in the Tournament of Power,
and the remaining fighters
were doing all they could
to keep their own universes
from being erased.
Hoping to keep Vegeta and Goku
fresh for the final battles,
Gohan tried to defeat a trio of
warriors from Universe Three
on his own, but they revealed
a surprise technique.
[KOITSUKAI]
Koitsukai!
[PANCÉA]
Pancéa!
[BORARETA]
Borareta!
[KOITSUKAI, PANCÉA, BORARETA]
Combined!
[VEGETA, GOKU, GOHAN yelling]
[NARRATOR] Facing this
newly combined fighter,
the Saiyans were forced
to battle as a team,
and Gohan unleashed
a massive blast
he believed would
finish the job.
[GOHAN] I never would have
gotten this chance without Dad
and Vegeta's help, and there's
no way I'm gonna waste it!
Here's my full power!
[GOHAN yells]
Ha!
[NARRATOR] Gohan's attack
brought Koicéareta to his knees,
but still, the Third
wasn't ready to quit.
[PAPARONI laughs]
[PAPARONI]
I was hoping I could avoid this,
but you leave me no choice.
I'm going to knock
every last one of you
out of the Tournament,
even if it costs me my life!
You're about to face the
ultimate, secret technique
of the Third Universe, from
which there is no escape!
[NARRATOR]
Now!
[NARRATOR] "All-Out War!
The Ultimate Four-Fold Union vs.
the 7th Universe's
Total Offensive!"
[laughing]
I thought they were finished,
but they've still
got another play.
Tch. These fools just
don't know when to quit.
You thought you could walk all
over me. You'll regret that! Ha!
[gasps]
[VEGETA, GOHAN grunting]
[A18 gasps]
[ALL gasping]
Just what in the cosmos
are they doing now?
[growls]
[growling]
[roars]
Look at the size of that
guy--he's gigantic!
Huh. Big deal.
[AGNILASA growling]
He's got a huge amount
of power to match.
Hey, 18, do you think
they're gonna need our help?
I do.
This new combination
packs quite the intensity.
Fortunately, I've got
the perfect view to watch
how Goku and his little
companions respond.
Impressive. I never
would've guessed
the Third Universe had a trick
like this up their sleeve.
Wow! So big!
Yes! And strong, too!
[BOTH]
I am in awe!
Doctor Paparoni
does not disappoint.
His design's even
better than expected.
[MOSCO beeping]
Lord Mosco is pleased, as well.
He says our prospects
look excellent.
It was our greatest survival
strategy and no team
can match it. Now, unleash
your wrath, Agnilasa!
You are the mightiest
of all warriors!
[AGNILASA growls]
What is that monstrosity?
They just built something
big to try to frighten us!
But if I were scared
would I be laughing?
[laughs]
[roars]
[GOHAN, VEGETA, GOKU grunt]
[growling]
[GOKU grunting]
[VEGETA, GOHAN grunt]
[A17, A18 grunting]
[FRIEZA]
Ah!
Hmph.
[JIREN grunts]
Does that monster really
think he can get away
with takin' on our team as well?
[AGNILASA growls]
It takes more than sheer
size to be a warrior!
Let's see how you do up
against a Saiyan prince!
You like big? Then have
a Big Bang Attack!
[AGNILASA grunts]
What the--?
[AGNILASA laughs]
[growls]
[BOTH gasp]
[laughs]
Heads up!
[roars]
Their combined power and speed
are both on a whole new level!
Yeah, and they're gigantic!
Now we know why that
Third Universe doctor
was so confident they could
still win this battle.
[roars]
[roaring]
[A18, A17 grunt]
[AGNILASA grunting]
Lovely.
Now we have to fight
a huge monster.
[ALL]
Uh...
His power's incredible.
We don't have much of a choice,
but I don't think we can
stop him unless we
all fight together.
You don't have to tell me.
That's obvious.
Let's move in fast from
different angles to confuse him,
then we'll all attack at once.
[GOKU]
All right, let's go!
[AGNILASA growls]
[VEGETA, A18 grunt]
[GOHAN] All the moving targets
are mixing him up.
He doesn't know who to track.
Okay!
Do it!
[VEGETA yells]
[GOKU yelling]
[GOHAN yells]
[yells]
[A17 yelling]
[gasps]
[roars]
[FIGHTERS groan]
[GOKU groans]
[gasping]
Oh, come on!
They all charged in quickly at
the same time, and yet he was
able to accurately counter
every single one of them!
If that massive beast can track
five moving targets
simultaneously,
then he's even more dangerous
than we thought.
[BOTH]
Wow!
Goku and his team
are getting pounded.
They're in trouble!
[GOKU groaning]
Hey, you guys, you okay?
[A18]
Yeah.
[A17]
I guess so.
[GOHAN]
I'm fine, too.
[GOKU] So, do you think
he can sense our energies
at that ridiculous speed?
That's not it.
18 and I are different.
We don't emit that
kind of energy.
Then how do you think he did it?
My guess is he can send
out ultrasonic waves.
Much like a dolphin or a bat.
Those appendages where his ears
should be look
well-suited for that.
He can probably pinpoint
all our positions instantly,
from any angle.
Damn. That's gonna
be a real problem.
Watch yourselves! It looks
like he's about attack.
[AGNILASA roars]
Uh!
[yelping]
Dad, no!
[GOKU groaning]
His fist! It just warped
across the ring!
Is he strong enough
to bend space itself?
How's that even possible?
[laughing] He's a true
marvel of engineering!
[AGNILASA grunting]
[FIGHTERS groaning]
[GOKU groaning]
[gasps]
Kakarot! Behind you!
[GOKU gasps, groans]
[GOKU groans]
[ALL gasp]
How dare you!
Sorry. There go my
limbs once again,
acting on their own accord.
[chuckles]
Thanks for saving me, Frieza.
If you hadn't kicked
me like that
I would've flown
right out of the ring.
I hope you can forgive me for
not having a softer touch, Goku.
Dead though I may be,
I still have things to lose,
and there are many reasons
why I need you to
stay in this battle.
[GOKU]
Heh. There's nothin' to forgive.
It takes more than a simple
kick like that to hurt me.
[GOKU laughs]
[FRIEZA laughs]
Hey, what do you say you
help us fight this guy?
Are you going to say please?
[AGNILASA roars]
[FRIEZA]
Hm?
Here goes.
My, he is tall.
[AGNILASA roars]
He didn't even punch!
Are you trying to crush
me in your palm?
[AGNILASA growls]
Perhaps you chose to come after
me instead of that Saiyan chimp
because you believe
I am easier prey.
Well now you are going to pay
dearly for that assumption!
[yells]
[roars]
If that beast gets a hold of us,
then what's he planning to do?
[roaring]
[A18 screams]
[gasps]
He's got 18!
[roars]
I don't believe it.
It looks like he's actually
planning to swallow her whole.
I don't think she can get away.
No, this can't be happening!
[gasping]
Uh!
[gasps]
[grunting]
Huh?
Are you all right? That must've
been pretty scary, huh?
Well, I wouldn't recommend it.
Huh?
18, are you sure you're okay?
Yeah.
[sighs] That was way
too close for comfort.
I guess he's realized if he
tries to knock them from
the ring, one of their many
teammates can save them.
Eating them is a clever idea.
What are you praising him for?
[roars]
[BOTH grunt]
[GOKU grunts]
Ha!
[VEGETA growling]
[yelling]
[screams]
It's not just his
power and speed,
he's got all sorts of
tricky techniques, too.
This guy is one heck
of an opponent.
[A17 grunts]
[A17 grunting]
[AGNILASA growls]
[A17 grunts]
[A17]
Not good!
17!
[A18 grunts]
Uh!
Win this for us, all right?
What are you doing?
Come on, I know you like
this warm and fuzzy stuff.
18, no!
Contestant 18 is eliminated.
That brings the Seventh Universe
down to five warriors.
[ALL]
Mm?
Sorry I couldn't
hold out any longer.
Hey, I was the first to go,
so you won't hear
any criticism from me.
In fact, I think you've done
more than enough for
our Universe, babe.
I sacrificed myself so you
could keep going, 17!
You better not blow it, okay!
Yeah what she said!
Make it count, brother-in-law!
[A17]
Understood.
That blast looked rough, 17.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
With 18 out, we'll all
have to fight even harder.
Trust me. I know what I'm doing.
[AGNILASA chuckles]
Wow! The big one grew wings
and now he can fly!
That's amazing! Yay for flying!
Man, is there anything
this guy can't do?
[AGNILASA roars]
That bastard! He thinks
he can beat us all
by destroying the ring! Ha!
We'll stop him,
no matter what it takes!
[yells]
[FRIEZA grunting]
[yelling]
[GOKU]
Okay, let's do this!
[roars]
[GOKU]
Ha!
[VEGETA growls]
[GOHAN]
Ha!
[A17 yells]
[roars]
[ALL yelling]
We're not gonna
let you stop us!
We're losing ground!
[growling]
[A17 grunts]
17, wait!
What're you doing?
You four keep hitting him hard.
I'll handle this.
--What?!
--[GOHAN] 17!
[A17 yells]
[roars]
[yelling]
[AGNILASA roaring]
[A17 grunts]
[A17 groaning]
[AGNILASA groaning]
[BOTH]
17!
[groaning]
How are they able
to drive it back?!
It appears that punch has
compromised his energy reactor.
This is their chance!
That's it! Do it, Seventh!
Let's go!
[groaning]
Everyone! Give it one last push!
[yells]
[GOHAN]
Ha!
[VEGETA yelling]
[FRIEZA screams]
[GOKU]
Ha!
[AGNILASA groaning]
[ZENO]
Koitsukai...
--[FUTURE ZENO] Pancéa...
--[ZENO] Borareta...
[FUTURE ZENO]
Paparoni! Heh, heh!
I'm so sorry we've
let you all down.
There's nothing to
apologize for, Doctor.
While the result
is disappointing,
we know you and your colleagues
have done everything
in your power to prevent
this unfortunate fate.
All of the Third Universe's
fighters have been knocked out.
The team is eliminated.
According to the rules,
the entire Third Universe
will now be obliterated.
[BOTH]
Bye!
The only thing we can do now
is accept this as our destiny.
I harbor no regrets.
[MULE grunts]
[chuckles]
Thanks for everything, pal.
We're outta here.
[BOTH]
Squish!
He finally came out
of that thing.
Nice attack. We're still
in this thanks to you, 17.
I don't see what's so heroic
about hogging all the fun.
I'm impressed.
So how did you know
that was his power source?
I suppose being an Android
gave me an inside track.
[GOKU laughs]
Well, you certainly were
thinking on your toes.
And we should thank Frieza, too,
for joining in the tag-team.
It would've been tough
to win without you.
[FRIEZA] Hmph. Yes,
credit where it is due.
I'll add it to the ledger
of all the ways you owe me.
Hm?
Are you finally done
congratulating yourselves?
Ha. Are you finally ready
to fight like men?
Well then.
I hope you enjoyed the last
triumph of your lives.
[GOKU laughs]
Try all you want,
you cannot defeat me.
Well that ain't how
I see it, Jiren.
[NARRATOR]
Like so many before it,
the Third Universe has been
erased in the blink of an eye,
and now only two teams remain.
Will the winner be the Seventh
Universe, led by Goku?
Or will it be the Eleventh,
led by the unflappable Jiren?
With only nine minutes left,
the Tournament of Power is
set to enter its final phase.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super.
A 70 centimeter squared window
Today the sun broke
through the clouds
The rain is fin'ly gone
Gonna open up
the window for once
No reason, just because
This room has been
stained with the sighs
Of everyday regret
Now it's time to clear the air
Every moment was consumed
with my thoughts of you
Knowing in my heart those dreams
won't be coming true
I've always wanted nothing more
than to see your face
I move on knowing that your
mem'ry can't be erased
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And with only our team
and the Eleventh Universe
left in the Tournament,
I'm ready to finally get
that rematch with Jiren.
But Vegeta's got other plans,
and launches his own
all-out attack.
Careful, Vegeta.
You're one of the strongest
fighters in the cosmos,
but even you are gonna
struggle against Jiren.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"With His Pride on the Line!
Vegeta's Challenge to Be
the Strongest!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?