♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Beerus, Whis, and Goku
traveled to Universe Ten
to speak with Zamasu,
a Supreme Kai in training
whose energy closely
resembled Goku Black's.
Would you mind goin'
a quick round with me?
Just for fun!
[ZAMASU]
You want me to fight you?
[GOKU]
This sensation.
Was that the same
as Black's energy?
No. But it was awfully close.
[yells]
[GOKU chuckles]
Not bad! You know,
for just a plain ole Kai,
you're pretty strong.
Let's do this again
sometime, okay?
[NARRATOR] With no clear
answer, the link between
Zamasu and Goku Black
has only grown more puzzling.
What is the true explanation?
The mystery continues now!
[NARRATOR]
"He Who is of Saiyan Blood.
Trunks's Resolve."
[birds chirping]
♪
[exhales]
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
The showdown is coming.
[chuckles]
Make no mistake...
you're going down!
[yells]
[FUTURE TRUNKS yells]
[gasps]
[panting]
Damn it!
[DR. BRIEFS]
All right. That should do it.
At least enough
for one trip, anyway.
[yawns]
[PILAF]
Another all-nighter, huh?
You've got quite
the work ethic, Bulma.
Honestly,
it's kind of disgusting.
But let's see what you've got.
Hm?
What sort of primitive
programming is this?
[laughs]
Time for the great Pilaf
to give his imperial touch!
You don't master
world-domination
without learning how to code!
Let's see, a few changed
parameters here, a UDF there.
Oh yeah!
Now we're looking snazzy!
--[BULMA sighs] Huh?
--[keyboard keys clicking]
Hands off! I didn't say
you could touch that!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I just thought this
emergency boot disk program
had a little room
for improvement, okay!
Oh yeah? What would a
runt like you know about--
Hey. Hold on.
Yeah. You're right!
That is better!
--Well, I try.
--I've gotta keep my eye on you!
[shrieks]
Whatever do you mean?
I'm not plotting anything!
Lookin' good! Okay!
Let's make our final push and
get this thing ready to launch!
Can I breathe now?
[MAI] What do you think
he's doing down there?
Image training, I'd say.
Did you just make that up?
It's an excellent
mental exercise.
You see, he's picturing
his opponent.
Most likely that guy Goku Black.
And he's figuring out
different moves.
[yells]
[FUTURE TRUNKS groans]
[chuckles]
[FUTURE TRUNKS sniffs]
Wow. He's focusing so hard it's
like it's really happening!
Come on, we should scram.
We don't want to derail his
train of thought here. Huh?
[MAI]
Mmmmmm!
Come on! Please, Mai!
You have to stay with me!
This is it for me.
Can you grant me something
before I go, Trunks?
One last wish?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Anything.
[heartbeat thumping]
That's not what
image training's for!
[FUTURE TRUNKS] I still can't
imagine winning against Black.
What the--? Aah!
[MAI, SHOU screaming]
[groaning]
[BOTH groaning]
I'm terribly sorry, my lord.
Inter-universe travel
is complicated,
and the two of you
were bickering so loudly
I couldn't concentrate properly
and misjudged my braking speed.
You can't fool me--I know
you did that on purpose.
[WHIS laughs]
Oh, don't be absurd.
Are you guys okay?
[GOKU laughs]
[WHIS]
And that's how it went.
It sounds like we're
no closer than we were before.
You couldn't find anything
that ties Zamasu to Black?
No proof.
But Black's energy
reminded you both of Zamasu.
That's gotta mean
something, right?
What if Zamasu used his powers
to disguise himself as Goku?
Or actually transformed
into a mortal?
Can't gods do all sorts
of amazing stuff?
Well, now that I've seen
Zamasu again in person,
I think there would need to be
something else at play
to explain their disparities.
The energy from Black
was so intensely negative
it was almost suffocating.
Zamasu's energy
was similar in other ways,
but not nearly as malicious.
Furthermore, I'm quite skilled
at sensing deception,
and Zamasu seemed to have
no idea who Goku was
while Black spoke as if
he knew of Goku quite well.
We also inspected
their Time Rings
and they're all safe in storage.
So at present, what we're left
with are two similar
but not identical energies,
and no other evidence
to tie them together.
Of course the phrase
"at present" is key.
It's still possible his energy
could darken in the future,
if he harbors enough
dangerous ideas.
Hmmm. I'm not
so sure about that.
Seems like a pretty big leap
from him to Black.
Zamasu didn't strike me
as that bad of a guy.
And I should know--you can
learn a lot about someone
from fighting them.
You mean you fought Zamasu?
[GOKU]
I sure did! And I have to say,
he had some
pretty cool techniques!
But you still won, right, Goku?
[GOKU chuckles]
Yeah, I did.
No way!
While it's true
that Zamasu is a deity,
he's only a
Supreme Kai in training.
For someone with
experience fighting against
a great Destroyer like myself,
he was a piece of cake!
Yummy!
[BEERUS]
That's my plate!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Goku's even fought this god?
This... Destroyer?
[BOTH grunting]
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Maybe I don't have to worry
about getting stronger.
Maybe he can take care
of Black all by himself.
[VEGETA grunts]
[WHIS]
Delicious as always, Earthlings.
Sorry to eat and run,
but please thank the chef.
[GOKU] By the way,
where's Krillin and Piccolo?
[BULMA]
They left a while back.
Dang it. Who am I gonna get
to fill the holes
in my yard this time?
[GOKU]
Don't look at me.
[VEGETA]
Hey.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Yes, Father?
Come with me.
It's time to train you for real.
[gasps]
[birds chirping]
[growls]
[growling]
[ZAMASU]
Master Gowasu.
[GOWASU]
Mm.
Tea tastes a bit off today.
[ZAMASU] Same kind as
I always use, Supreme Kai.
You suppose it's just
a bitter leaf, then?
Yes. That must be it.
[MALE BABARI 54A growls]
What's that?
[GOWASU] I am monitoring
a planet known as Babari.
Not long ago, a species of
sentient bipeds evolved there.
I'm watching to see
what becomes of them.
[MALE BABARI 54B grunting]
[GOWASU] Mmm.
Their violence is troubling.
[ZAMASU] Would it not
be wise to deal with them now,
before they cause more problems?
Hm? What do you mean
"deal with them"?
I mean, exterminate the
entire species of course.
How can you suggest that?
You know very well that's the
role of a Destroyer, not a Kai!
[ZAMASU]
Then what should we do?
What's the alternative?
Do you believe these savages
will ever reach enlightenment?
[GOWASU] We'll watch them
for another millennium or so.
See how they progress.
[ZAMASU] What's the point?
They'll never be civilized.
You never know.
I do know. I've seen
more than enough examples
from other worlds to predict
how this story unfolds.
There are no mysteries
to the mortal soul.
Fine. If you refuse to listen,
then why don't we take a look?
A look?
[ZAMASU] I'm intrigued. Isn't
that the box the Destroyer
and attendant from Universe
Seven came to check?
[GOWASU] Indeed.
Behold, the Time Rings.
As the name suggests,
these bands allow one to move
beyond the normal
constraints of time.
[MALE BABARI 54A roars,
grunting]
Disgusting.
I hope a thousand
years from now,
these creatures of Babari
are not so shackled
to their primitive drives.
So that artifact
actually allows the wearer
to travel through time, master?
Yes. But there are
distinct limitations.
The rings take us to the future,
and then always bring us back.
[ZAMASU]
What about going to the past?
[GOWASU] That is not
the purpose of the rings.
And even if they could,
such movement
is strictly forbidden.
Interacting with
history is complex,
and fraught with danger.
You remember the four
emerald-colored rings
that were inside that box?
[ZAMASU]
Of course.
[GOWASU] Each was created by a
significant change in history,
which has produced
a separate timeline.
An alternate reality.
What does that mean?
"An alternate reality"?
It is possible to effect
the flow of time in a way
that creates a parallel stream.
And judging from
the bands in that box,
this has happened
in recent years.
For mercy's sake.
What sort of fools
would attempt such madness?
But I digress, my point is
the Time Ring can take us
to the Babari's future.
[ZAMASU]
Indeed.
[GOWASU]
Or should I say, it can take me.
[gasps]
As a precaution, the
Time Rings only transport those
with the full rank
of Supreme Kai,
and have the correct
Potara Earring to prove it.
Mere apprentices like
yourself do not qualify.
So I can't go with you?
[laughs]
You may borrow one of mine.
I will promote you to Supreme
Kai, temporarily, of course.
I am humbled, master.
Just make sure you
put it on your left ear.
I trust you know why.
If I put it on my right ear
while its pair is on your left,
we would merge
together, correct?
[GOWASU] Yes. It would combine
us together into a single,
far more powerful Kai.
But the transformation
would be permanent.
How 'bout it? Want to
join with me forever?
Eeh!
Uh. No thanks. Perhaps some
other time, master.
[GOWASU laughs]
All right. Touch the ring
and say "one thousand."
We'll travel
that many years ahead.
[ZAMASU]
Mm!
[BOTH]
One thousand!
[gasps]
Let's see.
Look! Fire and shelter.
They're starting to civilize!
[MALE BABARI 54C growls]
[BABARI growling]
[GOWASU]
Aaaah.
[ZAMASU] This proves it.
As long as mortals exist,
the multiverse
will have no peace.
You haven't trained me
since back when
Cell was on the loose, remember?
'Course not. You think
I keep some kind of diary
under my pillow?
[FUTURE TRUNKS] Well I haven't
forgotten it, Father.
A year in the Hyperbolic
Time Chamber with you.
I'll always remember that.
[FUTURE TRUNKS panting]
[VEGETA] Guess you're not just
worthless garbage, after all.
As gifted a warrior
as I clearly am,
it would have
taken me a little longer
to reach this new level
of power on my own.
By that, I mean
transcending Super Saiyan.
Wait, what?
[VEGETA bellows]
You see? This is the
glorious power that goes
beyond Super Saiyan!
This is Super Vegeta!
[exhales]
There, Dad, you see?
No need to hold back!
You can spar with me
at full strength.
Use your Super Saiyan 3,
like Goku did.
[laughing]
What, did I
say something funny?
[VEGETA grunts]
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Whoa! What level is that?
We call this
Super Saiyan Blue.
[GOKU snoring]
That energy!
Is that Vegeta and Trunks?
Yeah, now we're talking!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
I can't sense his energy.
But I can feel this power
in the air--it's overwhelming.
What is this? Uh!
While it's true
that Zamasu is a deity,
he's only a
Supreme Kai in training.
For someone with
experience fighting against
a great Destroyer like myself,
he was a piece of cake!
Could it be?
What happened to
all that machismo, boy?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
That must be it.
Father and Goku have
discovered how to summon
this blue energy from the gods.
This... divine power.
They must've learned it
from fighting that Destroyer!
Ha! Soiling yourself
before we begin?
All right fine.
I'll give you a handicap.
If you can manage to land
a single blow against me,
we'll call you the winner.
[FUTURE TRUNKS] You'd be
a fool to underestimate me.
I'm glad to see you can
talk tough, at least.
[FUTURE TRUNKS bellows]
[VEGETA grunts]
Still relying on that bulky,
lumbering transformation?
You disappoint me.
[yells]
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
He fell for it.
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA] So that lame form
was just a ploy to draw me in
and catch me off guard?
[yelling]
Grading on
a hundred-point scale...
[FUTURE TRUNKS groans]
...I'd give you 30 at best.
Hey! What'd you bring me
out here for, Goku?
Do you realize how close I am
to fixing that time machine?
I'm not taking a nature walk!
Just watch, okay?
What was that, a fighter jet?
Your husband and your son
from the future
are doing some training.
I figure that's a show you
definitely don't want to miss.
Uh, what?
[VEGETA grunting]
And you're letting them fight?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
He's way too strong!
[yells]
[groaning]
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
This Super Saiyan Blue.
If Father and Goku
have this in their arsenal,
they can stop Black for sure.
It's gonna be okay.
My own strength
doesn't matter now.
[VEGETA grunts]
Look at me, dumbass.
Wipe that smile off your face!
Stopping Black.
Is that your only goal?
You think it ends there?
Think about the next threat!
In a year, or five, or ten!
Or think about your pride!
If Saiyan blood
flows in your veins,
if you're my son as you claim,
then I won't tolerate
you losing to anyone!
You'll be the best,
or you'll be nothing!
Stop, he's been through enough!
Just let them
do this--it's okay.
It may seem harsh,
but it's how Saiyans work.
[grunts]
What are you doing here?
--[FUTURE TRUNKS grunts]
--[VEGETA groans]
--[BULMA gasps]
--[GOKU] Oh boy.
Damn you! Uh--
So that counts
as landing a blow, right?
I guess that means I win.
[laughs]
I hear you.
And I will get stronger.
Stronger than Black,
and stronger than you.
[VEGETA]
Hmph!
That's how you answer
your son--by walking away?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Thank you, Father.
For everything.
See...?
Oh boy. You Saiyans
are all nuts.
[WHIS] Here we go.
Who's a good stir fry?
Aren't you done yet?
[WHIS] Can't rush perfection,
my lord. I'm almost done.
Whis!
[WHIS]
Uh, I'm terribly sorry, but, uh,
would you mind
answering that for me?
I am knuckle deep in sauce.
He can't talk right now.
Call him back, would ya?
Aah!
[shrieking]
Grand Zeno, sire!
Yay we praise thee,
noble person!
With all our pleases
and our thank yous--
Oh lord, am I quoting Goku?
Oh, Grand Zeno,
what an unexpected honor!
I hope you're having
a splendid day.
Uh... It's an okay day, I guess.
I'm calling because I want you
to arrange something
for me, you see.
And what would that be,
Grand Leader?
Well, I'd like
to see Goku, you see!
[BOTH scream]
Get ready!
Instant Transmission!
Two fingers placed
right between the eyes
Get ready!
My hair will stand up!
'Cause I got
all the power of a Saiyan!
Ohhhh HEY!
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! (KAMEHAMEHA!)
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! It's what you need
Feel the magic of the beat
(Woo-hoo)
DANCE! It makes you smile
Nothing else can
quite compete (yoka yoka)
So when the world is lame
Don't play that game
You know that every problem
can be answered the same
Just let go and feel the rhythm
Everybody dance
with all your might!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
I can't believe the ruler of all
universes is asking for me!
What's he want, and how
do I have time for this?
We still haven't figured out
who Goku Black is,
how he's tied to Zamasu,
or if we're strong enough
to save Trunks' future!
But when the Omni-King calls,
I guess you have to listen.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"I'd Like to See Goku, You See.
A Summons From Grand Zeno!"
Be sure you don't
miss it, okay?