♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
with Goku and friends having won
the Tournament of Destroyers,
the leader of all twelve
universes appeared:
the childlike Grand Zeno!
And then I got an idea
that was very good!
A tournament with all
the universes together!
I think we should try it
sometime--wouldn't that be fun?
[DESTROYERS, KAIS sigh]
[NARRATOR] Under the terms
of his bet with Champa,
Beerus took possession
of the Super Dragon Balls
and summoned the Super Dragon!
But after all the fighting
and scheming,
the wish Beerus ultimately
made wasn't for himself,
but rather for
the benefit of Champa.
That was very kind of you, sir.
Kindness has nothing
to do with it;
I just want him to owe me.
[NARRATOR] And so,
the quarrel between Destroyers
comes to an end,
as Goku and the other heroes
of the Seventh Universe
return to Earth to celebrate,
and begin a new adventure. Now!
[NARRATOR]
"A Chaotic Victory Party!
Showdown at Last?
Monaka vs Goku!"
[WHIS]
A victory party?
[BULMA] We've all got free time
now. Why not celebrate?
Right, and I assume
this party means there'll be
plenty of delicious Earth foods?
Oh, tell us what kind?
Don't serve anything
'til we get there!
[BULMA] Great! The fun
starts at noon tomorrow!
Oh, I almost forgot!
Can you invite Monaka for me?
If it wasn't for him
beating Hit,
there's no way
we could have won!
Thanks! See you soon!
[BOTH]
Mmm.
[BEERUS] If we let Goku
anywhere near Monaka,
he'll insist
the two of them spar
so he can test his strength.
You could always tell them
the truth about Monaka;
that he has absolutely
no powers at all.
[BEERUS] I can't! It would
eliminate a critical source
of Goku and Vegeta's
motivation. Besides...
I am a Destroyer God.
If it were to get out
that we occasionally lie
to get our way,
it would diminish our
authority among the mortals.
Understood.
It would also
make me look foolish
to the Omni-King, Grand Zeno.
So, it sounds like
you're continuing this lie
to protect your behind?
There a problem with that?
No...
[BEERUS] Good! We'll just
tell them Monaka can't make it
because he's busy
with work. Are we clear?
[WHIS]
Yes, yes. As clear as crystal.
[CHIAOTZU, MARRON laugh]
[MARRON]
Whee!
[laughs]
[indistinctive chatter]
It looks like
Gohan, Videl, and Pan
won't be getting here
until late this afternoon.
So, if we start family bingo,
I'll be down three cards.
Hey, Chichi.
When's Goku getting here?
I haven't heard from him
since he went out
in the fields to work,
but he swore he'd be back
in time for the victory party.
Oh. Well, feel free to
start on the appetizers, folks!
No, we'll do nothing
'til Beerus gets here!
It's just snacks.
You know he's weird at parties.
Don't forget what happened
at your birthday!
Let's not risk triggering
one of his bad moods
the moment he gets here!
Yeah, don't give him
an excuse to go on a rampage.
As long as a certain
tubby pink someone
doesn't eat all our food,
we're fine. I hope.
You can relax.
I figured Buu would pig out,
so I made him his own feast!
[BUU]
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm!
[JACO gasps]
It looks like the special
desserts I ordered
got here just in time.
I paid for next-day delivery
on this yummy caloric infusion!
[ALL gasp]
I got a special order on a
pallet of sweets for Jaco?
Wait, aren't you Monaka?
Yes. Hi. Hello, there.
What are you doing
working as a delivery man?
Oh, right. When I'm
not at tournaments,
I do deliveries for
a cosmic shipping company.
--No way!
--[KRILLIN] Uuh.
So, on top of being super
strong, you have a real job?
You're the perfect
male role model!
The most impressive man ever!
[GOKU snoring]
Ah-choo!
[snoring]
[MR. SATAN] Wait!
Hey, hey, hey. Remember me?
We met at the tourney? You're
the strong man, Kinako, right?
It's "Monaka."
How awkward! I'm so sorry.
But, what I'm not
sorry about is that amazing
business offer I made you.
What do you say we
go into business together
and I make you the mascot
of my training dojo?
Your face would
look great on a hat!
Uuuh...
And what better way
to advertise than a man
in a costume on the street?
Wait 'til you see how well
we captured you in foam latex!
Hey! Sometime today!
[PIIZA]
Hold your horses, I'm coming!
Aah!
Uhhh...
What do you think?
That's pretty spot-on, right?
[PIIZA grunts]
Piiza! That's against
the mascot code!
I'm sorry, Mr. Satan.
It's just so hot in this thing!
Ugh. I can't!
You two figure this out later!
You're gonna
scare off our guest!
Go get some punch and
enjoy the victory party!
Victory party--what?
Wait. Lord Beerus didn't
invite you for me?
No, ma'am.
Ha. All for me.
[GOTEN] Hey! You don't get
a whole box for yourself!
--[GOTEN] Let's share!
--[TRUNKS] No! Jaco bought
enough for everyone!
[MONAKA groans]
Ah! My bad!
[BOTH gasp]
[GOTEN]
Are you okay, Mr. Monaka!
[sniffs, cries]
Hold on. Are you really crying?
[MONAKA sobs]
He's the strongest guy
in the universe?
Something isn't adding up here.
[KRILLIN]
Hey, Piccolo. Am I crazy?
Or is Monaka not as strong
as Beerus says?
I'm staying out of this one.
[VEGETA gasps]
Beerus and Whis are coming now.
It's so nice to see
you all again! Smells great.
Thanks for waiting. Let's eat.
[MONAKA sobs, sniffs]
--[BEERUS] Eeh!
--[WHIS] Oh! This is bad.
Monaka? What's he doing here?
You answer me first,
Lord Beerus!
Why didn't you invite him
like I asked you to?
Was that too much to ask of you?
Uh. Oh, right.
Did you not do that
'cause you didn't want us
learning he's
a useless weakling?
[yells]
Bulma, don't wind him up!
I was right. Monaka's not
a fighter at all!
[WHIS]
Ahem!
Lord Beerus, it appears
that everyone on Earth
is now wise to your Monaka ruse.
Thank you for noticing.
Although, your scam's
biggest target isn't here yet.
If Goku finds out I lied
to him, it will cause me
all sorts of problems.
Listen up, peons!
The truth about Monaka being
a weakling must be something
Goku never-ever knows!
[ALL gasp]
Hey, what's up, Lord Beerus!
Aaaah! You startled me!
Never startle a Destroyer!
Ah! Monaka! I'm so glad
you came to the party!
Now we can fight each other
to see who's stronger!
Goku, no! How dare you come
to a party dressed like that!
You're embarrassing me!
Now, go home, clean up,
and change your outfit!
Uh. You're the boss, Chichi.
Sit tight.
I'll be right back, okay?
All right, guys, I just
bought us a few minutes.
Now let's figure out
how to keep Goku
from learning the truth
about this poser.
Good work. He's lucky
to have a wife as fine as you.
Wow, thank you for
the compliment, Lord Beerus.
Whatever. Since when is it
okay for deities to lie?
--[BEERUS] What?
--[CHICHI] Hey!
Stop that, Bulma!
Lord Beerus only lied
about Monaka's strength
to keep Earth in this universe!
By claiming there was
a fighter stronger than
the both of us,
Lord Beerus motivated us
to reach new heights
in our training.
Without that lie,
we would have lost for sure!
Aren't you clever.
Ahem. Everyone,
please listen to me.
Okay. If Goku were
to learn that Monaka
is an easily frightened pink
troll in a dead-end job...
Aah!
[WHIS] Well, he is likely to
lose his motivation to train.
He'll just be
going through the motions.
That is not good for
any of us in this universe,
because we need Goku to become
much stronger than he is now.
The other universes'
Destroyers are quite volatile.
If our team loses the all-
universe fighting tournament,
I shudder to think
what awful fate
will befall
this universe's Earth.
[ROSHI, KRILLIN,
TIEN, YAMCHA gasp]
--I'm back!
--Wha--! Already?
All right, Monaka,
let's throw-down!
Eh!
Hold on. You can't just
take liberties like that!
Apologies,
your destructiveness, sir.
May I please fight him?
Not yet. If you
really want Monaka,
you must first do
one trillion sit-ups for me!
Only when you've done those
will I let you fight!
That's all?
Awesome! I'll start now!
Thanks, Lord Beerus!
Augh! Hey!
One trillion, I mean it!
He's really doing
a trillion sit ups!
Guys, come on.
We got another
few minutes to find a way
to protect Monaka's secret.
Yeah, but if
they're gonna fight,
how do we keep Monaka
from ending up a pancake?
[GOTEN]
Hmm...
Got it! We'll trick
Dad into thinking
Monaka can transform and
swap him out for a real fighter!
That might work.
Oh! Brilliant idea!
And your Dad's gullible
enough to fall for it!
Wait, what is this plan?!
[TRUNKS]
Lord Beerus, listen up!
[whispers]
Okay. So, here's the deal.
You're gonna put on
that costume of Monaka
and then you're
going to go over there
and you're gonna fight.
You want me
to fight as Monaka?
Uh--
[chuckles]
[grunts] Whis. Do you
really think I'll have to
go through with this
silly dress-up plan?
It's shameful for a Destroyer!
The only shame is your lie
about Monaka, my lord.
Yeah, you brought
this on yourself!
--[BEERUS growls]
--Trunks! You shut your mouth!
[GOKU] Phew! 'Kay. Well,
that's a trillion sit-ups.
[BEERUS]
Uh. Huuuuh?
You ready to rumble, Monaka?
[sobs]
That's too fast!
Even at one sit-up a second,
it would take three million
years to do a trillion of them!
No way you were doing
an honest count, Goku!
My counting was totally honest.
One trillion,
two trillion, three trillion.
[laughs]
That's all wrong!
What comes after a trillion?
It's two trillion, right?
You cheater! That's not
what I meant by trillion!
Look, he can't even do
two chores at the same time,
let alone count to
a trillion while exercising.
You still haven't
figured him out
after all this time, have you?
[BEERUS] I don't care!
Do it again and do it right!
[GOKU] I just wanna do some
light sparring with him?
Why're you being
such a stickler about this?
Now where should we
do this fight?
How about... here?
Hey! Come back here!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS panting]
Lord Beerus!
We got it!
Aah!
I'm not wearing that!
Chiaotzu! Slow him down
and buy us some time!
[CHIAOTZU]
'Kay, I'll try.
Uh. Whoa, I can't move!
I'm stuck!
[GOKU grunts]
[CHIAOTZU grunts]
I... I got nothing left! Ugh!
[yells]
Sorry about this, buddy!
Solar Flare!
Aah!
Now's your chance!
Beerus, switch!
Lord Beerus. Goku is
expecting a strong Monaka.
[BEERUS grunts]
[BEERUS] In all my eons I've
never heard of a Destroyer God
doing something so humiliating!
♪
Wow! So, that
bright flash was you
getting bigger, huh, Monaka?
I didn't even
know you could transform!
And your energy even feels
a lot like Lord Beerus's now!
[BEERUS shrieks]
So, not only
can you change size,
you've got
god-level powers, too!
This is gonna be great!
[BEERUS]
I'll put Goku away quickly.
So, I can be done with
this asinine farce!
[BULMA] Hold on, boys! Don't
have your big fight around us!
This is supposed to be
a classy victory party!
Take your fight over there!
C'mon, move!
Uh, okay Bulma.
Hmm? Now, be a big boy
and go clean up your mess.
Okay, Mr. Monaka?
Remember, that if
he learns the truth,
he could lose
his motivation to train.
I doubt a disinterested Goku
will go over well
with the Omni-King.
I wouldn't want anything
to happen to you.
[BEERUS]
Eeh!
Bulma! Can you please
show Lord Beerus some respect?
This seems like an
all right spot for our fight.
Ow! Now that's more like it!
[chuckles]
[BEERUS AS MONAKA]
Eh?
[yells]
Oh yeah?
Looks like Lord Beerus
is having some trouble.
He's worrying more about
the costume than fighting well.
Aaugh! I can't believe
we forced a god into this
humiliating scam! So, Bulma!
What's our fallback plan
if Beerus gets sick of this
and decides he'll just
destroy the earth instead?
Uh, good point. Maybe we
did get too carried away.
At the time,
it seemed like it'd work.
Hey, let the record
show I was against this
from the start, okay?
[GOKU groans]
Take this!
[gasps]
What the--?
[BEERUS grunting muffled]
What are you guys doing here?
I... It's appears
we were pulled!
I think Monaka has
the power to control
other people's bodies
from a distance!
[VEGETA]
Mhmmm!
Ah! My arm. No!
Monaka's controlling it--
watch out Goku, no!
You're a bad actor,
you know that?
[PICCOLO]
Says you.
Whoa! No! Run, Kakarot!
Now he's taking over
my body! Aaah--!
What?
[BOTH yell]
[BEERUS AS MONAKA bellows]
[ALL groan]
Oh, no no. I think
Beerus has snapped!
[laughs intensely]
Huh?
[BEERUS AS MONAKA bellows]
It's like he's just
having fun with this now?
With that mask on,
we can't know either way!
[WHIS] I agree with Krillin.
He is enjoying himself.
Having to fight in that costume
as if he's someone else
must be a novel experience.
Plus, the nature of the
Tournament of Destroyers
rendered him only a spectator,
so I'm sure he's itching to do
a little fighting himself.
Lame costume aside,
this whole fake fight
might be a real treat for him.
Mmm. Mmm-mm!
Just as that was
a real treat for me!
[yells]
[BEERUS AS MONAKA grunts]
Ah! It wasn't cheap
getting that costume made!
[yells]
One more big punch!
[BEERUS AS MONAKA]
Don't get cocky!
[GOKU groans]
[yells]
[BEERUS AS MONAKA yells]
Hey, hold on. I thought
this was gonna be sparring!
If they keep this up,
it won't just be my party
that's ruined,
but all of Metro West!
Eh...
[BULMA, TRUNKS, GOTEN, YAMCHA]
Huh?
He-heh. Awesome.
This was so worth the wait!
Now. Let's take this fight
to another level!
[whimpers]
[yells]
[BOTH yell]
Huh?
That's enough. We don't want
a friendly exhibition
destroying the city, now do we?
[whispers]
Your hand's sticking out.
[BEERUS AS MONAKA
chuckles nervously]
Oh, come on,
let us fight a little longer!
You do know Lord Beerus is
the one ordering the stop?
--[GOKU] Uh...
--[BEERUS AS MONAKA] Wha...?
[PUAR AS BEERUS]
Enough, fighting.
You both did really good.
Aw, man. Guess that's that.
We'll fight another day,
Monaka. Hm. Bye!
Well, at least the party
can finally start, huh?
[BEERUS AS MONAKA groans]
[exhales]
I'm glad that's over with.
Man, that was actually
a pretty awesome fight.
Too bad all the
drama earlier made Monaka
black out and he missed it.
--[TIEN gasps]
--[laughs]
--[VEGETA] Oh, come on!
--[BULMA] Seriously?
Uh, what's going on?
[YAMCHA chuckles nervously]
Did I say something wrong?
[BEERUS AS MONAKA growls]
I wore this ridiculous
costume for nothing!
[ALL shriek]
[VEGETA] Now we're going to
have to fight Beerus again!
Oh, wow! Monaka, you can even
split yourself up
the way Buu does!
That's so amazing!
[BEERUS AS MONAKA]
Ehhh?
Wow! Knowing you're
out there just pushes me
to train harder than ever!
Man! After all that,
I am starving!
Guys! Let's eat!
What a day!
[WHIS]
You handled that well, my lord.
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
It's done. What a silly farce.
Go on. Tell me I deserved that.
Well, honesty is
the best policy!
[BEERUS]
Mm. All right!
Time for this Destroyer to eat!
[OOLONG]
Hmm.
[sighs]
♪ Closing Song ♪
Wow
It's hard to say
Don't wanna stay
I twist and fight,
can't find my way
I must believe, that fear
and trouble can even be fun
if you think the right way
Wow
I don't wanna draw the line
I gotta see it through some way
Fight for what I know is mine
The dream I had of me that day
Wow
Don't care if they
call me greedy
If they hate me, make me blue
Don't care if they laugh at me
'Cause I will make
the dream come true
Wow
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Bulma? Korin? What are you
suddenly doing here?
Wait. I'm the one who
suddenly appeared to you ?
Something's gone wrong
with my energy!
Piccolo! What am I supposed
to do to take care of Pan?
Next Time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Goku's Energy
Is Out of Control?
The Struggle
to Look After Pan."
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?