♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Beerus the Destroyer arrived
on King Kai's planet,
and asked Goku
about the powerful warrior
who had appeared
in Beerus' dream.
Super Saiyan God,
let me think.
I mean I know all about
regular Super Saiyan, sure.
But that's a "no"
on the God stuff, buddy.
[NARRATOR] Despite the
warnings from King Kai,
Goku challenged Beerus
to a sparring match
and received a rude awakening.
A very small display...
of a Destroyer's power.
[NARRATOR] After easily
knocking out Goku,
who had gone all the way
up to Super Saiyan Three,
Beerus and his servant Whis
set out for Earth,
where Bulma is throwing
a party for the ages.
[BULMA] Come on, the rest
of the gang is here, too.
Let's go over and
make a big entrance together!
Yeah, sure.
Let's go see Yamcha.
Oh I see. You can't even
pretend to be happy?
[VEGETA]
Of course not!
Okay fine! Suit yourself!
[NARRATOR] King Kai has warned
Vegeta that Beerus is coming,
and any insult could mean
the annihilation of Earth.
The planet's fate
is in his hands. Now.
[NARRATOR]
"Don't Anger the Destroyer!
A Heart-Pounding
Birthday Party."
[GOKU grunts]
[yells]
Stop it, Goku. You can't!
As the Kai of your quadrant
I expressly forbid you
from going to that party!
What are you talking about?
You're the one
who said I should go
because you were worried
about my social life,
whatever that means.
That was before
I knew Lord Beerus
was going there too!
That's the only reason
you want to go now
and you know it!
Well yeah,
I'm not gonna argue that!
Y'know, after all these years
it still blows me away
how great these Senzu Beans are.
I'm totally healed up!
[KING KAI] What was
I thinking, giving you one?
I guess you just
looked so pitiful.
Maybe you should eat one too.
You sound sick, King Kai.
Of course I'm sick.
Sick of trying
to make you listen!
I'm telling you, Goku, all this
stress you're causing
is taking years off my life.
I'm not really sure
if that's possible.
I mean you're already dead.
[grunts]
[GOKU] Sorry! Just relax.
I won't go, okay?
[KING KAI] Well hallelujah!
He actually does have ears!
Now that I know
how strong he is,
I can see how amping
him up really could
be dangerous for the universe.
[KING KAI] Yes! Exactly!
You're finally getting it!
[GOKU] Mmm. Aw, but just
sitting here is totally hard!
I don't know how long
I can keep this up, King Kai!
[ALL gasp]
[fog horn blares]
[MARRON giggles]
Listen ladies,
I love him, but sometimes
he really drives me
up the wall, you know?
[TRUNKS]
Move!
[GOTEN wails]
[GOTEN That's not fair, Trunks!
I still had a shot!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS arguing]
[YAMCHA grunting]
[ROSHI]
Ooh-ho-ho-ho. Eee...
[BULMA]
Creep!
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA] Kakarot,
beaten in two blows?
What kind of creature
could do that?
Damn it.
Pull yourself together!
Prince Vegeta does not
tremble before any foe!
[VEGETA]
Beerus the Destroyer.
Why is that name familiar?
I'm sure I've heard it
before but when?
[BEERUS] Well, if it
isn't Prince Vegeta.
[gasps]
[VEGETA]
Huh?
[VEGETA gasps]
I'm losing my mind!
--[BEERUS] Boo!
--[VEGETA yells]
[BEERUS]
Hm.
Greetings.
[VEGETA]
Who are you?
Telling you that
is a waste of time.
Considering that you won't
be alive for much longer.
[VEGETA grunts]
Why, you--
[VEGETA]
What's happened to my body?
I can barely move!
[VEGETA]
Aah!
[KING VEGETA
breathes quaveringly]
[BEERUS] Can your miserable
little brain comprehend
why I'm so angry, Saiyan King?
[BEERUS]
Answer me.
Because I promised
to fulfill your mission
in the time you
gave me, Lord Beerus,
but it took longer
than I thought it would.
[BEERUS]
Wrong.
[YOUNG VEGETA]
Father's being humiliated!
How can he take that?
Just who is this filth?
[BEERUS] I consider myself
a rather flexible deity.
I know you mortals
have your limitations.
But there is one thing
I cannot tolerate.
The callous arrogance
of those who do not
pay the respect
a Destroyer is due.
[KING VEGETA groans]
[YOUNG VEGETA gasps]
[BEERUS] I ordered you to find
me the most comfortable pillow
in all the universe. And I know
for a fact you obtained it.
Your tenacity was impressive,
although your methods...
a bit severe.
[BEERUS] I bet you don't even
know how many creatures
you killed in that raid.
Of course being what I am,
I could've accepted all that
if you'd actually
given me the best pillow
instead of keeping it
for yourself.
And trying to fool me
with the second best.
[KING VEGETA cries out, groans]
Bastard! That is
the king of all Saiyans!
[yells]
[groans]
[VEGETA] Of course! That's who
Beerus the Destroyer is!
No wonder he could
beat Kakarot in two blows!
[BEERUS] You know, I spared you
as a child because I hoped
you'd grow up strong
enough to entertain me.
Oh well, another Saiyan
disappointment.
I should have destroyed
your planet myself.
[BEERUS]
Now then.
Why don't you prove I'm wrong
and tell me something useful
about this Super Saiyan God.
A Super Saiyan God?
Seems letting me down
is your kind's specialty.
Wait, let me think.
[BULMA sighs]
[BEERUS]
Mm?
[BULMA]
Huh?
Please tell me
you're not doing pushups.
[VEGETA groans]
[BULMA]
Are you okay?
[VEGETA]
Stay back! Get out of here!
[BEERUS]
That's not a very nice way
to speak to a woman,
Prince Vegeta.
[VEGETA grunts]
[BEERUS] Nothing to
worry about, my lady.
He's just had too much punch.
[BULMA]
Who are you guys?
I'm sorry,
we should have told you.
My name is Whis, madam.
And this fine gentleman
over here to my right
is Lord Beerus.
We were just
passing by your planet
when we saw Vegeta and thought
we'd stop to give our regards.
Oh you're from space, huh?
I guess I should have
put that together.
Well this is
a pleasant surprise.
To tell you the truth, I didn't
think Vegeta had friends.
No, stop!
I'm Bulma, Vegeta's
wife, believe it or not.
It's both an honor
and a pleasure to meet you.
Today's my birthday and
we're having a little party.
Though I guess it's a "big
party" when you rent a ship.
You're both welcome
to join us if you'd like to.
My, my, what a generous
offer, Earth Woman.
Thank you. Honestly my nose
has been tantalized
by some most intriguing aromas
since we came aboard.
In that case, let's go!
[VEGETA]
Wait!
[BULMA]
Everybody, listen up!
Allow me to introduce Vegeta's
friends, Beerus and Whis!
[BEERUS]
A pleasure to meet you all!
[cheering]
[BEERUS]
Why thank you, thank you.
You're entirely too kind.
[BEERUS]
Hmm?
Hmmm.
[chuckles]
Hello.
[VEGETA] He seems
to be in good spirits.
We might actually survive this,
assuming nobody makes him mad.
[BUU]
Mmm, mmm, mmm!
[VEGETA] I'd say those two are
most likely to screw things up.
[BULMA]
This is my old friend, Yamcha!
Salutations.
[laughs] Don't be
so formal, bring it in!
Ah!
Compared to all these
Saiyans and kids,
I'm kind of an old-timer.
But the fact is--
and I don't want to say this
too loud and embarrass people--
but I'm one of the greatest
martial artists here.
So I totally get
why you're nervous.
But this is a party, man.
No one's gonna start a fight!
You can relax, bro.
Could you be more stupid? Augh!
[KRILLIN]
Okay, who's hungry?
--[ALL gasp]
--[KRILLIN] Ha-hah!
What is that?
I don't believe
I've ever had this before.
[KRILLIN]
It's a party special!
Russian Roulette Takoyaki!
[ALL gasp]
[VEGETA]
Uuuh...
The way the game works
is most of these are filled
with delicious octopus
but one has wasabi instead,
and you won't know
'til you bite down!
So try your luck and
let's get this party started!
[VEGETA]
Of all of the--
They're not playing
your childish game!
Okay, who ordered
the party-pooper?
Yes, no one likes
a pooper of parties.
[laughs nervously]
I've never heard of
this "wasabi" you speak of,
but this roulette aspect
adds a fascinating
mystery and visually
it's quite pleasing.
[WHIS] That drizzled
topping reminds me
of the ultra-sweet blackfruit
sauce on Planet Banna.
Although, the smell of it
is another matter.
Quiet, Whis.
I'd rather be surprised.
Wow. So you're volunteering
to take the first bite, huh?
I guess you really do
know how to party, don't cha!
[KRILLIN]
Let's cheer 'em on, guys!
Go Beerus!
[ALL] Go Beerus!
Go Beerus! Go Beerus!
[KRILLIN]
Together now!
[ALL] Go Beerus! Go Beerus!
Go Beerus! Go Beerus!
[VEGETA] It's all right,
no need to be alarmed.
There are so many,
and only one has wasabi.
His chance of choosing
the bad one is infinitesimal!
Please, please, please!
[intense music plays]
[gasps]
[cries out]
[VEGETA]
This is it; it's over.
[BEERUS grumbles]
It's great!
[echoes]
[gasps]
Inside a warm and fluffy
ball of powdered grain
lurks the chewy sensation of
an eight-armed Earth mollusk!
The combination's inspired!
I can't believe
I've never tried it!
And the sauce adds
a perfect counterbalance!
[WHIS]
Mm! I agree, it is tasty.
I'll add it to our
normal menu at once.
There's no wasabi.
I got lucky!
What are you talking about?
The wasabi ball
makes it even better.
It's like finding
the buried treasure!
Darn. Not in mine.
I don't think my heart can
take all these close calls.
Relax, buddy.
A little fun won't hurt ya.
[KRILLIN screams]
Why is it always...
gotta be me.
[BEE panting]
[PILAF]
Well this feels pretty nice.
Yeah, I'm satisfied
instead of dizzy
and feeling my stomach
trying to eat itself.
I totally forgot
what that was like.
When you're
feelin' this awesome,
takin' over the world seems
like way too much trouble.
Mhmm. It kinda does.
Wait, like hell it does!
World domination
is everything!
It's the only reason the
fearsome Pilaf Empire exists!
We will never quit,
never surrender!
Not even to a buffet bar!
I'm telling you, the Dragon
Balls are on this ship! See?
[PILAF grumbles]
If you're done imagining
things on the Radar, sir,
could you help
pack the leftovers?
[PILAF]
Yeah, I guess.
[GOTEN grunts]
[dramatic music plays]
[GOTEN]
Here goes nothin'.
Whoa!
[chuckles]
[GOTEN]
Aw, man!
[TRUNKS]
I'm not done yet!
[GOTEN] Knock it off. That's
mean! I'm already soaked!
Those two are only
half-Saiyans,
and hardly out of
their training pants.
And the older one doesn't
seem the fighting sort.
[sighs] Once again
the trail has gone cold.
Where is that
Super Saiyan God hiding?
[VEGETA]
Sorry for the wait!
A pyramid of takoyaki,
Your Grace!
Oh, nice work.
[WHIS]
Thank you.
Well at least
the food here isn't cold.
Yes, indeed,
but my stomach is filling up
and I don't know
where else to look,
on this planet or otherwise.
Maybe I'll just go home
and take another nap.
[VEGETA]
Yes, that's right, you monster!
Get back to your own world!
--[BEERUS] So, Prince.
--[VEGETA] Yes, sir!
That Saiyan on
King Kai's world--
oh, I've already
forgotten his name.
[WHIS]
Goku, my lord.
Yes, that's right: Goku.
What exactly is your
relationship to that fighter?
He's my enemy.
But we've made a truce.
A truce, you say?
And you accept that?
[grunts]
Saiyans have changed
during my nap--
or at least those who survived.
You've become downright gutless.
Uh, I'm sorry!
[GOTEN]
We didn't mean to! Aaah!
[cries out]
[BEERUS growls]
[VEGETA]
What have those rug rats done?
[WHIS]
Are you angry, my lord?
[BEERUS]
Do I look angry?
[WHIS]
Well, yes.
[BEERUS] No, Whis.
I wouldn't say I'm angry.
Furious is more like it!
[BULMA]
Huh?
[yells]
[ALL gasp]
What in the world is he doing?
I dunno.
[VEGETA yells]
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH]
Aah.
[VEGETA grunting]
Prepare yourself
for the chewiest
and fluffiest octopus
you've ever tasted!
[KRILLIN] Can you hold
the wasabi this time?
Hard to stay angry
when the Saiyan Prince
plays the jester.
And getting mad does
stimulate your appetite.
But if you've had
your fill of appetizers,
there's a dessert called
pudding that seems to be
--a specialty here.
--Pudding, you say?
Yes, it's most delicious with
a velvety texture to die for!
Then why are we waiting?
Show me at once!
Of course.
Here I was getting mad at you,
but you care so much
about making my party great
you've put on
an apron and everything!
You've really turned
things around, honey!
You've no idea!
[BUU]
Mm, mm, mmm, mmm, mmm!
[chuckles]
Hm?
Excuse me, sir, but the
pudding vendor over there
tells us he's
completely run out.
Would you mind sharing a
pudding with us, from your...
...ample collection?
See! I told you
this would happen
if you hogged 'em all,
but did ya listen? No!
[BEERUS]
Oh, is that the pudding?
So smooth. So jiggly!
I can't wait!
We're sure sorry
about that, brother!
He's had plenty.
Take as much as you like!
No, Buu eat.
All pudding is for Buu!
Now Buu...
Sorry, I don't think
you understand.
You see we're visiting
from far across the universe
and I'm afraid if we don't get
to taste this delicacy now,
we may not get another
chance for centuries
and then your civilization
may not exist.
It's quite dire.
[BUU]
Hm. Blalalalala.
[screams]
[BUU]
Haa!
Hm! Buu the strongest!
So Buu eat what Buu want!
Buu no have to share!
So is that how the
little blob wants to play?
Damn it. What now?
Let me step in here!
I am a peace
ambassador of sorts--
[BUU, BEERUS]
Shut up!
[groans]
[BULMA, OOLONG gasp]
No. N-No, stop!
What a pity. Ugh.
Better eat fast.
[BUU grunts]
Buu make you fly!
Huh?!
You know, I consider myself
to be a rather flexible deity.
[BUU hollers]
And though I try to shrug off
the constant shortcomings
of the witless masses,
there's one thing
I cannot tolerate.
[BUU yells]
[BEERUS] And that is the
callous arrogance of those
who do not pay me the respect
a Destroyer is due.
[BUU hollers]
[chuckles]
[VEGETA]
It's all over.
Our lives. This planet!
We don't stand a chance!
♪ Closing Song ♪
I see all these kids
As I walk to school
Their colorful backpacks
All unique and cool
I can't help but wonder
which color I'd choose
If I were still a kid
Where would I run off to? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
How am I lookin' now that
I've grown into an adult? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
Do I look like I'm proud
of who I've finally become?
Oh, I know I've made mistakes
But I'm tryin' to get it right
And I'm willing just to wait
For the moment I can shine
This anthem
Is a story for all time!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And I guess that whole
"Don't Make Beerus Angry" plan
didn't work out!
Now all the greatest fighters
on Earth are jumping in
to stop the Destroyer,
and I don't think
Bulma's gonna like the way
her party's turning out!
Buu, Gotenks, Piccolo,
Tien, even Gohan
is showing what's he's got!
But what about Vegeta?
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"How Dare You Do That
to My Bulma!
Vegeta's Metemorphosis
of Fury?!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?