♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Goku transcended
to the level of a deity
to battle Beerus the Destroyer,
and their intense fight
shook the entire Earth.
Come on. No!
Damn it!
[NARRATOR] Goku became
stronger than ever
and gave all he had,
but it still wasn't enough.
And after the Saiyan's defeat,
Beerus was about to make good
on his threat to destroy Earth.
But it seemed the
Destroyer's lazy lifestyle
caught up to him.
With all his energy tapped,
Beerus fell asleep,
thus sparing the planet.
[WHIS] Convincing
performance, my lord.
But you know,
you can stop pretending now.
I wasn't pretending, Whis.
I did fall asleep!
[NARRATOR]
New adventures begin now!
[NARRATOR] "Valiant Mr. Satan,
Work a Miracle!
A Challenge from Outer Space."
[GOTEN] That was
delicious, Mom. Thanks!
I'm going to Trunks'
house now, okay?
I'm glad we could spend
this time together, Chichi,
especially since I'm going back
to King Kai's world to train!
You're joking right?
'Course not! I'm all
healed up from battle
so why would I wait?
I've gotta train
harder than ever now
so I'm as strong as Beerus
and ready for
the next time we fight!
I should've known that's
why you're wearing that.
You can't go!
That's not fair, Chichi!
You said it was fine
before Beerus showed up!
You know, when I got us
that hundred million zeni?
But I thought I told you,
we spent that already!
[GOKU groans]
Seriously?
Basically! And we're
saving the rest!
And besides, Gohan and Videl
are about to have a baby!
And we can't have our
grandchild look up to a grandpa
who does nothing
but fight crazy aliens!
From now, on you're gonna
work for a living
like everyone else and
be a responsible role model
for our family!
And that's final!
But Chichi. Come on.
I have to train.
[CHICHI] You've trained enough
and fought enough.
You're not a young man anymore.
Just do it. This should
last you till dinner.
[CHICHI]
Here.
[grunts]
[VIDEL] All right, I'll get
started on dinner.
Ah! No Videl,
what are you talking about?
You shouldn't be
worrying about dinner!
I can take care
of all the cooking.
You just put your feet up
and try to relax, okay?
I'm not gonna stay
in some protective case
till the baby comes. I'm fine!
Yeah of course you can!
But if you're gonna carry
our child for nine months,
the least I can do
is make you guys some food.
What are we gonna do
with your Mom, huh?
Take our eyes off her one second
and she tries to do it all!
Now you watch Momma
and make sure she relaxes,
and I'll get to work
on food, okay?
Hah.
[GOHAN]
All right, here I go.
Today's daring mission: dinner!
Your daddy's a real handful.
We'll just have to
make him happy
and eat some cookies
while we wait.
Okay, let's see.
Now where does
she keep those recipes?
[VEGETA]
He transcended.
When the Super Saiyan God
power expired,
he found a way to fight
like a deity on his own!
And he thinks he can
leave me behind again!
I will surpass you,
Kakarot. I swear it.
I'm all good
on the nostril hair front!
All right!
[MR. SATAN] Okay, Buu,
I'm goin' out for a bit.
Come on, Bee! Who wants
a ride in the car?
Aw, who's a good boy?
[HOST 15A]
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to this
extraordinary event!
Whether you've traveled
here to Satan Square,
or you're tuning in
from around the world,
you all experienced the
mysterious phenomenon
that literally shook the globe!
Now the truth about that mystery
is about to be revealed!
[distant car horn honks]
[HOST 15A]
He's here, folks!
Our fearless hero,
Mr. Satan, has arrived!
[CROWD cheers]
[camera shutters click]
[panting]
[MAN 1] Earth arrival
in 13 minutes, sir.
[MAN 2]
And you're sure about
your intelligence-gathering?
The Arch-Enemy isn't there?
[beeping]
[MAN 1]
Affirmative. The Cursed Ones,
They-Who-Will-Not-Be-Named,
The Nemeses whose brainpower
rivals our own
have not been seen.
[MAN 2]
Perfect.
[CROWD chants]
Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
[MR. SATAN]
Yeah!
[cheers]
Thank you!
Welcome, Mr. Satan.
Thank you for coming,
even though you must be
exhausted after
your last huge battle.
Why don't we jump
right to the point
and talk about the strange
phenomenon that shook the world.
I'm told you were
in the thick of it!
It was the work
of the Great Destroyer!
What? The Great Destroyer?
And what does that mean?
So what is that exactly,
like a weapon,
or a ship,
or a criminal mastermind?
No, it was way
worse than that!
I'm talkin' about a
diabolical deity coming down
from the blackness of space;
a god feared
throughout the cosmos!
[CROWD gasps]
Devastator
of countless planets,
the Destroyer God
known as Buh-Buh-Uh.
Buh-- Known as big trouble
to any world he targets,
and ours was next on his list!
He was gonna blow up the earth!
I discovered this while chasin'
down a criminal syndicate.
They were in league
with this uh-Buh-Buh...
Buh-ligerant
god monster, yeah!
I hacked into the crime ring's
dark Net, and found 'em!
They were summoning him
to their evil cruise ship
in the South Sea!
So I went there and
broke up the crime ring
and simultaneously
confronted the Destroyer!
The god monster
whose name is definitely,
uh, Lord Beevis!
--[CROWD gasps]
--[MR. SATAN] Yeah!
[MR. SATAN] Yeah, Beevis was
his name and a dark aura
was pulsing out of his body,
shakin' the whole Earth!
[HOST 15A hollers]
Testing, testing,
sibilance, one-two.
[MR. SATAN] Naturally,
I faced him immediately,
since I'm more or less incapable
of experiencing fear.
[yells]
[BOTH yell]
But I'll be
honest with you guys.
Not even I had the power
to put him down.
He was stronger than you?
There's no way!
It's true, my loyal fans,
I was in a desperate pinch.
But in that darkest moment
there came a great miracle!
From the depths of
my finely-honed body
sprang an all-new power!
[bellows]
[yells]
I became what I can
only describe as a god!
[CROWD cheers]
And they're
buying this crap?
[MR. SATAN] After I tapped into
this well of celestial might,
the Destroyer was doomed!
[yells]
Yeah! Yeah!
I threw him down!
And then I whacked him
in the noggin like that!
[bellows]
That's how I drove
the fearsome Beevis away!
[cheers]
Let me get this straight.
You're telling us
that was the cause
of those shockwaves we felt?
They were from the Destroyer
monster you defeated?
A truer tale
has never been told.
Well folks,
you heard it here first.
Our great champion has saved
the planet once again!
[CROWD cheers]
[MAN 15B]
What is that?
It looks like a meteor.
It's headed right for us!
[CROWD yells]
It's not safe, sir.
Get out of here, now!
[BOTH gasp]
What the--?
Is that a spaceship?
[gasps]
[MR. SATAN gasps]
[HOST 15A] It's an alien!
An alien has just beamed down!
[CROWD murmurs]
A real live alien?
Did it come here
for revenge?
It can't be.
[ALL gasp]
We are ready to receive
you now, Ambassador!
Uuh!
[ALL shriek]
Oh thanks, you guys!
--After you.
--Thank you.
--[GROUP gasps]
--[SNACKIAN AMBASSADOR] Huh?
[GROUP gasps]
[SNACKIAN AMBASSADOR]
Hmm.
[GROUP sighs, shrieks]
They seem scared.
[sighs] This happens
everywhere we travel.
I'm starting to believe I really
do have a scary face.
Earth people! There is
no reason to fear us!
This gentleman is an ambassador
from our fare Planet Snack.
We've learned
there's a hero here
who has battled Lord Beerus
to exhaustion!
And we have come
to pay our respects
for this astounding feat!
Say what now?
So like, you guys
aren't here for revenge?
To prove it, we'll perform
the Snackian salute,
honed over centuries as our
most sacred sign of respect.
[BOTH] We salute you yes,
we're "S-N-A-C-K"!
[GROUP]
Aah!
Our scans suggest
this is a victory party.
Is the hero who fought
the Destroyer present?
Uh, yeah,
that's right, Snacks.
I'm the one who took
care of that Destroyer.
That's a surprise.
Look up there!
[SNACKIAN AMBASSADOR]
Hmm.
Wow! It's truly an honor
to meet you, human.
The story of you saving your
world from the feared Destroyer
is spreading quickly
across the universe.
[laughs]
Aw, it was nothing.
That Destroyer
was no match for me--
I felt kinda bad for him!
I've brought you something.
In honor of your
inspirational victory,
my planet hereby presents you
our most distinguished medal.
This is incredible
news, folks.
Our mighty warrior,
Mr. Satan, has gone
from hero of Earth to
hero of the entire universe.
[GALBEE]
Not so fast!
Eeh!
Something wrong, Galbee?
In the custom
of our warriors,
I can't acknowledge him as a
hero until we meet in the ring.
If this man really
bested the Destroyer,
it should be easy for him
to prove his strength.
I must apologize,
but it is our tradition.
Galbee is the official hero
of Planet Snack,
so it would be a great honor if
you would join him in combat.
[MR. SATAN] There's no way
I can fight that guy!
He's 200% muscle, at least!
Forgive me for asking
but it would mean a lot.
Oh, I do love to spar,
but I'm kind of recovering
from saving my own world.
Breaking news! After
achieving universal fame,
Mr. Satan has been
challenged to fight
Planet Snack's great hero!
Hey! Pipe down, doll face!
[CROWD chants]
Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
[MR. SATAN] How do I
get out of this one?
If I refuse,
it'll ruin my whole rep!
Oh, I got it!
[groans]
My bowel issue's...
flarin' up. Be right back.
[phone rings]
Come on, Gohan.
Pick up the phone, I need ya!
[GOHAN] Aaah!
We've got water everywhere!
What do I do?
That's not in the recipe!
That's weird;
he always picks up.
I guess I'll try Vegeta.
[phone rings]
What is this,
Don't-Answer-Your-Phone Day?
Um, Mr. Satan,
is everything okay in there?
[MR. SATAN] Yup, all good!
I'll be right out!
This is bad;
there's no way around it.
Well, maybe most
of the crowd left.
[CROWD hollers]
What the what?
We hope the fighting
ring we've built is
up to your standards. Please,
battle as hard as you like.
I wonder how Galbee
will do here.
It's always harder to fight on
your opponent's home turf.
[MR. SATAN] This is bad!
Bad bad bad bad!
[GALBEE]
This earthling is clever;
masking his energy as if
he's an utter weakling.
And he's unguarded, too,
trying to lure me in.
I'm ready when you are, hero!
[HOST 15A] Is this
the start of the match?
No, it appears our champion
is still warming up.
[MR. SATAN] Come on, can't a guy
get one decent miracle?
Like Goku or Vegeta
jumping out of the crowd?
O-Or Krillin, or maybe
that weird green guy?
Shoot, I'd settle for
Goten or Trunks--
can't they skip school?
Quit stalling and fight!
[HOST 15A] Ah-ha!
He's still stretching!
What an elaborate routine!
Oh, it's Mr. Satan.
Looks like a match!
[MR. SATAN]
This is hopeless.
[GOKU]
Woo-hoo! Mr. Satan!
Give 'im all you've got!
Hi!
[MR. SATAN]
Goku! It's happening!
I've been saved from on high!
Things have somehow
gotten weirder.
[MAN 15C]
Who is that guy?
[MAN 15D] Is that one of
the the champ's students?
You're here in
the nick of time, Goku.
What are you, a mind reader too?
Well my tractor's got
a busted thinga-ma-jiggy.
First I went over to Bulma's
place to ask her to fix it,
but no one was home there.
So I was looking for
someone else
who could help me out.
And then I saw you down here.
You're here for your tractor?
[GOKU] You're a worldly guy.
You must know things.
You can help fix it, right?
Before we get to
that boring stuff,
what do you say you step in
and fight this alien for me?
Uh. That big guy?
[MR. SATAN]
Yeah, how 'bout it?
A little morning training?
Thanks, that's real nice
of you, but I shouldn't.
I'd feel bad
hogging all the fun.
Don't be silly, I don't mind.
I'm a gracious guy!
And I can fight him
myself any time I want!
If you're sure it's okay,
I guess I could go a few rounds.
The truth is Chichi isn't
letting me train right now,
and my muscles have been itching
like crazy for a fight!
Ah man, thank goodness.
Hey, your name's Galbee, right?
Well you'll have to
fight this man first,
and prove you're worth
my precious time.
You're joking.
You want me to battle
some unproven amateur?
This is an unexpected
development.
I should say so.
He looks like a backwoods
commoner to me.
I've never been so insulted.
Is this how you treat all
the guests to your planet?
[MR. SATAN]
Just you wait, big boy.
You're in for a shock.
All right, let's get
this thing started.
Come at me, any way you like!
[CHICHI] That's what I call
a good shopping trip!
It's gonna take my boys
quite a while
to eat their way
through all of this!
What am I doing here?
Sure it's a lot of cooking,
but I love having Gohan over.
And we have to make sure
Videl's eating healthy
now that she's eating for two!
[gasps]
Why is Goku here?
--[CROWD cheers]
--[CHICHI] Huh?
[HOST 15A]
Mr. Satan's alternate
is looking confident, folks!
Seriously? Goku,
what are you doing?!
I told you to go to work!
[GOKU]
Aah! Chichi?
Oh no! I'm in big trouble
now! Help me out, quick!
I can't just fly away now
that everyone's watching me,
so just give me
a good punch, okay?
Wha--?
Come on, make it fast!
Hit me right here!
[MR. SATAN]
Satan Punch!
[GOKU]
Ooh! Waaaah...
I forgot my tractor--aah...!
That hurt!
--Don't run from me!
--Very mature.
Wait! You just can't go!
[GALBEE] What a punch!
Splendid technique!
Hero! I can't wait
any longer! Let's fight!
Oh my! Mr. Satan is
fighting Galbee after all!
And our champion
is just barely evading
the strange visitor's attacks!
His dodging skills
are impressive.
[HOST 15A] This is
certainly an unconventional
approach to fighting.
[MR. SATAN] If he lands
one punch, I'll be toast!
[HOST 5A] It seems
our hero is conserving
his incredible power
in what I can only assume
is a complex strategy.
Why isn't he fighting back?
He couldn't be scared
to fight, could he?
[MR. SATAN]
I'm losing the crowd!
Hey, maybe he didn't beat
that Destroyer monster.
[MR. SATAN] My whole
reputation's at stake!
There's no choice.
I've got to fight!
[MR. SATAN] Just stand
your ground, Mr. Satan.
You can do this!
You did it before, right?
You stopped that crazy blast
to protect Videl!
You just gotta dig deep!
You ain't destroyin' nothin'!
Earth's defender says no way!
Prepare for my
new divine power!
[bellows]
Did he just say
his "divine" power?
[yells]
Yes! I'm now a fightin' god!
[GALBEE gasps]
[MR. SATAN]
Now's my chance!
[panting]
[barks]
[screams]
I hate dogs!
What was that?
[SNACKIAN SECRETARY] He seems
to be afraid of that creature,
which now that I think of it,
does resemble a--
[BOTH scream]
[SNACKIAN SECRETARY]
Wait, Ambassador.
We still have to
say our farewell!
[BOTH] We salute you yes,
we're "S-N-A-C-K"!
[MR. SATAN]
Uuuh...
I thought you said
they weren't there!
The scanners failed.
We should issue a quarantine.
It could take us thousands of
years to conquer those things.
And incredibly, after just
one punch from our champion,
Galbee and his colleagues
have fled in terror.
Wow, I'm stronger
than I thought.
[BEE whimpers lightly]
Ooh.
You see that?
That's what I can do
with my new "Godly Power,"
a term I intend to trademark!
[CROWD cheers]
[HOST 15A] It's another
huge win for Earth's
living legend!
[MR. SATAN]
What a relief.
[GOTEN]
Dad's out late, huh?
I'm sure he's just working
hard to finish planting.
Because he knows he'd be a fool
to step foot in this house
until the job is done!
[GOKU gasps]
Chichi's really mad
at me this time.
I guess that means I'm
sleeping outside tonight.
Aw man, but I'm so hungry.
I look back
to when I was young
Reminisce on all that I've done
In my hands, I held
The dreams of my childhood,
that now've come to pass
So let's ride upon
the wind and journey to
A world we've never known
(It's a brand new story)
Now, a new chapter starts
Shining Star
In the night be
my compass and guide
Take me to where I belong
The warmth we once shared
Will always be there
Its magic lives on in our hearts
Shining Star
Give me strength
from your light up above
Show me the way to be brave
My hands still hold onto hope
that together we'll manifest
All that we dreamed of
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
I sure wish Chichi
would let me practice,
and I'm not the only one
with the training bug.
Krillin's remembering
the old days and wondering
if he can
get stronger, too.
Looks like the best shot
for any of us to level up
is to have the same
teacher Beerus has.
But someone else might
get that chance before me.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Vegeta Becomes a Student?!
Win Over Whis!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?