Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me go back to the start
Wishing on the starlight
In the sky, let's paint a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of God
Kyo-Let's☆Mo-Let's☆Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic
I don't care 'bout limits, no regret
Make me tougher even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo' try me
So-Zets☆Cho-Zets☆Dynamic!
Let's Go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going power pumpin' up
something greater waiting not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Beerus' brother Champa,
a fellow Destroyer,
arrived from the Sixth Universe.
Say, Beerus!
Let's have a contest, huh?
A contest? What exactly
are you proposing?
I mean a fighting
competition, obviously!
And if I win, we trade
Earths with each other.
[NARRATOR] Champa suggested a
five-against-five match-up
between their universes,
offering to give up
the Super Dragon Balls
he'd collected
if his team should lose.
All right then.
I could use a good battle!
[NARRATOR] The high-stakes
face-off has been set in motion
and it's ramping up quickly.
Ah! Hell yeah!
[NARRATOR]
Now!
--[BEERUS] Hm!
--[CHAMPA] Hm!
[GOKU chuckles]
[BOTH sigh]
Now we just have to decide
where to hold this competition.
Oh, I know the perfect place.
Why don't we do it on
The Planet With No Name--
the one that's floating
in neutral space?
That way neither of us will
have home-team advantage.
But, Lord Champa.
[CHAMPA]
Huh?
That world only has
a tiny sun nearby
to shed any warmth or light.
It's a rock
with little to offer.
Not even an atmosphere.
It's quite desolate.
[CHAMPA]
Hmmm...
Well, this is your idea, Champa.
So, you figure out
how to make it all work.
Trust me, I will.
Hey, as long as
I'm in planning mode,
you want me to draw up
the competition rules, too?
It shouldn't be too hard.
--Hm?
--[GOKU] Oh, hey, I know.
Let's make it like the
World Martial Arts Tournament.
And what might
that entail, Saiyan?
You lose when you surrender
or if you step outside the ring,
and there's no killing
or weapons allowed.
Huh...
You can't boost your
natural power by cheating,
and there should be
a written test
for anyone who wants to enter.
We don't need some mindless
monster on either side.
You need a brain big enough
to understand the rules.
[chuckles]
Yes, that all sounds
reasonable to me. Champa?
Yeah, you in? Your lordship?
[CHAMPA]
Mmmm, hmmm...
Oh, all right, fine.
So, the games shall begin
at seven o'clock sharp,
one week from today, by the
Eighth Solar Calendar. Good day.
[WHIS]
Hm.
That equates to five
of your Earth days, Goku.
[GOKU]
I can't wait!
And Champa, remember,
you wanted this contest.
So, don't back out on me.
[CHAMPA]
Hmph! Don't be absurd.
You just make sure
you keep your word, Beerus.
Guess that goes double for you.
[CHAMPA] Pft!
Oh, I almost forgot. Here.
[hollers]
Boy, that was close!
[CHAMPA chuckles]
Consider it a parting gift.
[GOKU]
Gee, thanks, Lord Champa!
Are you sure about this?
If you lose, you'll have to
give up the six wish orbs
you worked so hard to collect.
[chuckles]
You saw that klutz
fumbling around with the egg.
[laughs]
His reflexes were awfully slow,
even for a mortal!
If that's the best
Beerus has to offer,
then we have absolutely nothing
to worry about, Vados.
[chuckles]
The Seventh Universe's Earth
and all of its
delicious goodies will
belong to us soon enough!
[GOKU] Man, things are starting
to get interesting now.
That was heavy!
[VEGETA] This competition
is merely a waypoint for me.
What I'm really after is the
title of "Number One Warrior."
Someday, I'm going to
take them all down!
Beerus, Whis, Champa, and Vados!
[chuckles]
Yeah, guess neither
of us wants to be
runner-up to those guys.
By the way, these matches
are five-on-five, right?
So, I wonder who else
Lord Beerus is gonna pick
to fill out
the rest of our team.
Ha. It doesn't really
matter who they are.
They won't even
have a chance to fight
if I crush every one on the
Sixth Universe's team myself.
Wait a minute,
you can't hog all the fun.
That's it,
I'm calling it right now!
I'm gonna be the leadoff guy
and fight first!
No way! Do you honestly
believe I would allow that?
[GOKU] You have to!
I called it! Ha-ha!
[BEERUS]
Hey, you two!
Get a move on
or we're leaving you here.
[VEGETA]
Yes, sir!
--[GOKU] Huh?
--Right away, sir!
[chuckles nervously]
Huh?!
How'd you wind up
in this situation?
I don't know,
it sort of happened.
--It's not like I take notes.
--[laughs]
I think what's
truly important is that
we come up with
a device capable of
finding the remaining
Super Dragon Ball.
I don't suppose you can
help with that, Bulma?
Well, yeah, sure, that
shouldn't be too big a deal.
If the Super Dragon Ball's
really that huge,
then hopefully its signature
will be strong enough
to compensate for
the increase in distance.
I just need to tweak the
Radar's design. But you know...
Know what?
There's a much easier way
to find this thing,
don't you think?
[chuckles]
Just gather up
the earth's Dragon Balls
and have Shenron
tell us where this
Super Dragon Ball is hidden.
--[BEERUS] Oh!
--That could work.
Great idea!
Oh, yeah!
[chuckles]
Must admit, I'm impressed.
Turns out, you really are more
than just an overbearing nag.
[WHIS]
Oh!
[BOTH yell]
Been a long time
since I've seen someone
strike you like that, my lord.
Augh! You little--!
[chuckles nervously]
Oh, never mind.
In light of your smart proposal,
I'll let it pass this time.
[sighs]
Hey, Vegeta!
Ah, yes, sir!
[BEERUS]
Go fetch.
Yes, sir!
The Dragon Radar! Honey! Bye!
Whoa, wish he'd
obey me like that.
[GOKU chuckles]
[VADOS] My goodness,
transporting these
Super Dragon Balls is
getting to be quite tiresome.
[CHAMPA snores]
Wake up, my lord. We're here.
Already? That was fast.
The Planet With No Name, huh?
That just won't do.
I know! I'll come up
with a brilliantly eloquent
new moniker for it!
I shall dub thee...
The Nothing Planet! Ha!
You certainly possess an
uncanny gift for naming things
and a poetic way with words
befitting a Destroyer.
[CHAMPA chuckles]
No, do I really?
Stop it, you're flattering me!
Mm. You know, sir,
whenever you think that hard
about something and give
your brain a good workout,
it consumes a massive
amount of calories,
which is quite beneficial
for your diet. Thirsty?
I've told you,
I don't need to be on a diet.
[VADOS] That juice
is freshly squeezed from
the bitter niganiga greens
of Planet Yago.
[CHAMPA]
Ah! Yuck!
[VADOS] Now, to turn The
Nothing Planet into something--
something appropriate
for a tournament, that is.
Where should I start?
That's about
the right size, I think.
[CHAMPA]
Huh?
Aah! Not bad.
[coughs]
[yells]
I had to check and make sure.
Can't have it break
during a match, you know.
Ooh, look. Not even
a scratch. Nice work.
[VADOS]
Naturally.
[CHAMPA]
Moving on.
[inhales]
Ah, now that is some
nice high-quality air!
Yes, I was trying to reproduce
the fresh, crisp air
found in the high plains
of Planet Sorert.
Great. So, what's next?
The fight ring.
What size, my lord?
[CHAMPA] Fifty standard lengths
a side ought to be sufficient.
Make it too big and
the spectators can't
be close enough to the action.
[VADOS]
Now item three.
[CHAMPA]
Concession stands!
That's the one thing
we can't do without!
[VADOS]
Oh, all right. Fine.
It's so beautiful!
[laughs]
Try to use restraint. Now then.
[CHAMPA]
Mmm? Aah!
[BULMA]
Okay, here we go.
I summon forth
the Eternal Dragon Shenron!
You really get things
done quickly, don't you, Vegeta?
Precisely what
I look for in a gofer.
You don't thank people
by humiliating them!
Ignore him, sweetie;
you did good.
[VEGETA]
Aah!
Hey! Are you nuts?
You know I hate
your sneak attacks!
[BULMA giggles]
[ALL gasp]
[SHENRON roars]
I am the Dragon, Shenron.
I shall grant you
any three wishes.
Now speak your first wish!
Here.
Oh, Lord Beerus, sir?
What a humbling surprise!
Though you seem to be on Earth
quite a lot these days.
Yes, well, at the moment,
this planet is
turning out to be crucial
to both the Sixth
and Seventh Universes.
Oh? Really?
[BEERUS] Anyway, we could use a
little bit of assistance today,
which is why
I'm willing to put up
with your whole pompous routine.
Oh...
[BEERUS]
Now, go ahead.
[BULMA] Okay. Shenron,
we want you to tell us
where we might be able to find
something in the Sixth Universe.
It's the last Super Dragon Ball.
--So...?
--[GOKU] Uh...
[WHIS]
Hmmm?
I can't.
[ALL]
You can't?
Space is so very vast.
I'm afraid my powers are not
so almighty that I can
pinpoint one object floating
in its boundless expanse.
Let alone, locate it in an
entirely different universe.
I see. So, it seems
we've bumped up against
the limitations
of Earth's Dragon Balls.
Well, that's
disappointing, isn't it?
Well, guess it's not
gonna be that easy after all.
Uh. I'll get to work
on that radar.
We'll see if science
can beat a dragon.
You really are a useless
lizard, aren't you?
Forgive me, sir.
[clears throat]
Perhaps you have
another wish for me, maybe?
Just go away.
That's my bloody wish.
Oh. Farewell.
Honestly, that was almost
too pitiful to watch.
Huh. Feels like I'm
forgetting something.
Ooh! Oh, right, King Kai!
I'm supposed to ask Shenron
to bring him back to life!
[BULMA] Can't you just
do it next time?
I guess.
Uuh!
--[GREGORY sighs]
--[KING KAI] Oh, no, no...
[CHAMPA] It sure is relaxing,
going into a contest
you know
you can't possibly lose.
Just picturing Beerus weeping
in defeat works up an appetite.
Why, I could scarf down
ten bowls of rice right now.
[VADOS] My lord, have you
picked the five contestants
you want to fight on our behalf?
Well, let's see, those
two fighters at Beerus' place
looked like Saiyans,
didn't they?
That means our team
oughta have some Saiyans, too.
We'll go scout talent
as soon as you fix that.
Fix it? What's wrong?
You didn't make me
handsome enough, Vados!
I mean, you put my head
on some fatso's body! Really!
Oh, good grief.
[WHIS]
Mmm, that beef stew was divine.
Earth's bountiful
delicacies never cease
to satisfy my palate.
Yes, and that's why I refuse
to lose Earth to Champa.
That was excellent.
Now then, I'm afraid that
we really must be getting back.
Obviously, we still
have to tell Monaka
about the competition
so he can prepare.
[GOKU] Whoa, hold on,
who's this Monaka guy?
Oh, we didn't tell you?
He's a warrior Lord Beerus
has chosen to fight for us.
Really?
You and Vegeta go fill
the remaining two slots
and let me know when
you're done. You got that?
Wait. This guy you know--
is he super strong?
C'mon, tell me!
[BEERUS] Well, of course,
he's tremendously strong.
Okay, tell me more!
What's he look like?
Like is he an earthling?
Or from some other planet?
He's not a deity, is he?
Come on, you gotta
gimme something here!
Leave me alone!
[GOKU]
Aaah, sorry!
If you must know,
Monaka just happens to be
the strongest opponent
I've ever gone up against.
What? Strongest ever?
Aw, for real?
Come now, Saiyan.
Don't tell me you thought
you were the toughest
I'd ever faced.
I thought I'd made
that clear to you before.
[chuckles]
You're number two, Goku.
Second-best. Disappointed?
[VEGETA grunts]
You hear that Vegeta?
Another fighter!
Is that awesome or what?
I can't wait to meet this guy!
I will never
understand you, Kakarot.
So, when do I get to spar
with this Monaka guy?
Like, is tomorrow okay?
Not a chance.
Your opponents are the fighters
from the Sixth Universe.
Focus all your
attention on them.
Well, okay, but who knows
what kinda competition
they'll turn out to be.
And if you're worried
it could affect us
for the tournament,
does it really matter?
I mean, even if we lose
and the earth moves
to a whole other universe,
nothing changes for us.
What? Bite your tongue!
Have you forgotten
the debt you owe me
for not destroying
your precious little planet?
If you don't try as hard
as you can to win this thing,
you'll have to answer to me!
Okay, okay, I got it, chill.
And anyway, just so you know...
[BEERUS]
Hm?
I always give it
everything I've got,
no matter what!
Tell Monaka I said hi!
[yawns]
Mornin'! You're up early.
Hey, what's that?
The Super Dragon Radar,
of course.
Whoa, no way! Really? Wow!
I can't believe you built it
in one night. That's so cool.
How can you be
so laid back about this?
You know we're short on time;
take this seriously.
Have you guys forgotten
what they said yesterday?
I'll be back to pick you up
in five of your Earth days.
Please be ready
at one o'clock sharp.
Okay, awesome!
I have to say
this other Destroyer
doesn't sound too bright.
I mean, if these
Super Dragon Balls really can
grant any wish,
no matter how impossible,
then he wouldn't need
to make this wager.
He could just use them to ask
for an exact copy of Earth,
couldn't he?
Or even say,
"I wish to always
have delicious food."
He doesn't need the earth.
[BEERUS chuckles]
As clever as you may be,
young lady,
your problem is that you still
think like a mere human.
Hey! What does that mean?
To deities like us,
Super Dragon Balls
are inconsequential baubles,
little more than an excuse
to compete over something.
Just think about it.
The Sixth and Seventh
Universes are counterparts
to one another. So, I'm sure
if you poked around enough,
you'd probably find some
Super Dragon Balls here, too.
[gasps]
Deities such as myself
don't make wishes.
Though if we did,
it might be more like,
"Wipe out all of existence!"
-[BEERUS laughs]
--[BULMA gasps]
[BEERUS]
Or something similar.
Now, that would be
truly exciting.
[GOKU chuckles]
Yeah, but if you did that,
there wouldn't be anything
good left for you to eat!
And where would be
the fun in a universe
where nothing at all exists?
Well, maybe you're right.
[laughs]
Let's go, Whis.
Yes, sir.
[BULMA gasps]
[GOKU]
Tell Monaka I said hi!
The look on his face
when he said that.
Listen, we don't know
what kind of dangerous wish
Beerus would make
if he got the chance!
Bulma, stop!
[GOKU] Whoa, he was
just joking around!
No need to get
all worked up about it!
Just a joke? And how
can you be so sure of that?
I don't know.
If what Beerus said is right,
and there's a possibility
our universe has
Super Dragon Balls, too,
then I say we use this thing
to collect them all first!
That way if he does
make a horrible wish,
we have the chance
to cancel it out!
Cut it out, Bulma!
Why should I?
Look, Beerus may be
the God of Destruction,
but he'll still act rationally
if he feels he's respected.
[BUU hollers]
Much as I shrug off
the constant shortcomings
of the witless masses, there's
one thing I can't tolerate.
And that is the callous
arrogance of those
who do not pay me the respect
a Destroyer is due.
I really don't think
Beerus would wipe out
all of existence
without a good reason.
Yeah, I agree.
Say what you will about the guy,
but he didn't blow up the earth,
even when he told us he would.
--[VEGETA] Precisely.
--[GOKU] Yeah.
[VEGETA]
Bulma?
[GOKU]
Mmm?
If you boys won't help me,
that's no problem.
I have other ways
to get what I want.
Hey, wait!
Who are you calling?
Ah, hi, sis.
[BOTH]
Bulma has a sister?!
[TIGHTS] Oh, hey, Bulma.
Long time no talk.
[BULMA]
You're pals with Jaco, right?
Last time I saw him,
he mentioned something
about upgrading his ship.
He was inspired by
the Frieza Force's tech.
[TIGHTS]
Mm-hmm, he was super psyched.
[BULMA] So, has he told you
how long it will take him
to get to Earth
with that upgrade?
[TIGHTS] Uh, yeah,
I wanna say fifty minutes.
He told me his ship
was gonna be way faster now.
So fast it'd be
downright nauseating.
Can you believe that?
[BULMA] Listen, could you ask
him to come over to my place,
like, now?
[TIGHTS]
Sure, I'll tell him. No sweat.
Hang on, just gimme
a second. Let's see.
Ah, so that's it.
At this point,
the angle is crucial.
[ringing]
[gasping]
Oh boy, that was close!
I am an elite patrolman
who's doing
supremely important things!
What do you want, Tights?
[TIGHTS] Hey, my sister wants
you to get over to her place
as quick as possible. Cool?
Oh, you're talking
about Bulma, right?
Whenever she's involved,
trouble is close at hand.
Uh, tell her you couldn't
get through to me,
or just make something else up.
[BULMA]
I heard that, Jaco!
[gasps]
Oh! I spent a whole day on that!
[BULMA] Quit your whining and
get your butt here pronto,
or else I'll send
my husband to attack
Galactic Patrol Headquarters!
[JACO] But in the time
it'll take me to get there...
[BULMA]
Vegeta, you're on!
[JACO yells]
Okay, okay! Hold on, Bulma!
I'll be right there!
Lickety-split!
And that's how it's done.
I'll thank you not to
use my good name
to threaten people!
Yeah, Bulma, but what good is
calling Jaco here gonna do?
I'm not telling
you jerks anything!
Why don't you go
and do some of that
training you love so much?
--Okay.
--Cool. Be careful out there.
Hold on, are you serious?
You're not actually
supposed to leave!
We haven't tested
the Super Dragon Radar
I worked so hard to build!
Why isn't this working?
It's not reading
anything at all.
[BULMA chuckles]
Hey, what's going on?
What are you up to?
Aw, can't figure it out, boys?
Do you need me
to explain it for you?
You can be
such a pain sometimes!
Listen. We're all the way
on the edge of the universe,
so we can't search
every part of it from here.
And I can't make the Radar
any more powerful,
so to find
the Super Dragon Balls,
we're gonna have to go
to the center of the universe.
Well, how long's
that gonna take?
Depends on the ship.
I'm not gonna let Beerus
get whatever he wants.
And that means getting
to those Super Dragon Balls
before he does,
no matter what! Uh!
[GOKU] Hey, that's fine and all,
but try not to let it
get in the way
of our tournament, okay?
Are you kidding me?
You guys care more about
this stupid tournament
than the fate of the universe?
[chuckles]
The universe'll be fine!
Don't worry about it, Bulma.
Besides, I've gotta
meet this Monaka guy.
Goodbye to our adventure
In twilight we must go our separate ways
And try to discover the path to our own destiny
I can't find the words
to tell you how much our parting hurts
I hope you know I'll always love you
And all that we shared will be remembered
How could I forget your face?
All my memories erased
I can still hear the melody of your voice
Petals fall in from above
Fade away, all that we love
In the twilight,
fade away,
fade away
Sayonara,
fade away,
fade away
Hey, it's me, Goku!
I can't wait for this tournament!
I'm sure the 6th Universe is putting
together an All-Star squad of fighters
so we've got to do whatever it takes
to build a great team too!
Even if that means giving away
one of the Super Dragon Ball wishes.
I hope Beerus is cool with that!
Next time on Dragon Ball Super:
Make sure you don't miss it, okay?