♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Zamasu and Black
jumped into battle
with Goku, Vegeta, and Trunks
when the three Saiyans
returned to the
dark future timeline.
And despite Goku's
formidable strength,
Goku Black quickly
took the upper hand.
[NARRATOR] Compelled to
defend his own world,
Trunks tried to fight
the invaders himself.
Open your eyes!
You are a vile sinner!
You both enabled
and inspired us!
You helped to light
the flame of our justice.
You helped to launch
Project Zero Mortals!
[GOKU BLACK] So the next time
you mourn your people,
remember they're dead
because of you.
[NARRATOR]
Rather than discourage the
young Saiyan fighter,
Zamasu and Black's harsh words
have compelled him to a
shocking new level of power.
But will it be enough?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Black!
This ends... right now!
I'm gonna kill you myself!
[NARRATOR]
"I Will Defend the World!
Trunks' Furious
Burst of Super Power!"
You actually believe
you can defeat me?
[laughs]
I'd like to see you try.
You Saiyan idiots never give up.
[yells]
Be careful, Trunks.
[VEGETA] Is he really planning
to sacrifice himself?
[FUTURE TRUNKS yells]
[GOKU BLACK chuckles]
[FUTURE TRUNKS groans]
I can't believe it!
[FUTURE TRUNKS yells]
Wow, he's holding his own.
[groans]
[gasps]
[GOKU BLACK] You must pay
for your sins against time.
And die!
[FUTURE TRUNKS yells]
Impossible!
Maybe I am a "sinner,"
but I don't care!
I'll do whatever it takes
to save this planet!
[yells]
[BOTH]
What the--?
[FUTURE TRUNKS yells]
[VEGETA] Don't bother standing.
I'm not gonna let you help.
[FUTURE TRUNKS yells]
--[GOKU BLACK grunts]
--Kiss your project goodbye!
[GOKU BLACK growls]
All right!
[panting]
[gasps]
He's still on his feet!
I'll admit I didn't think
you were capable
of reaching this level of power.
But it does make
for the perfect dessert.
Aw, what's wrong?
I thought you were going to
save your precious little home.
Trunks, hang on!
Father, no!
[FUTURE TRUNKS screaming]
[FUTURE MAI gasps]
Trunks!
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU BLACK]
Only one more left.
When we're done cleansing
this world of Saiyans,
we will eliminate the rest
of the mortals as well.
[chuckles]
[GOKU BLACK, ZAMASU]
Hm?
Seems he's not done after all.
[FUTURE TRUNKS yells]
Masenko ha!
[yells]
Father! I want you to take Goku
and get back
to your timeline, okay?
I'll hold them off and
give 'em everything I've got.
But in case I fail, you need
to find a way to defeat them!
--We can't just go!
--Do you take me for a coward?
I'm not going to leave you here!
[GOKU]
No, he's right.
It's the only way
to save his future.
You agree with this?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Father! Hurry!
[VEGETA grunts]
Get the time machine ready.
[BULMA gasps]
[GOKU groans]
[VEGETA]
The senzu beans! Take them!
Don't worry. I'm gonna
make sure he survives.
[FUTURE TRUNKS groaning]
[GOKU BLACK]
Uh? Nice try.
No you don't!
--[GOKU BLACK] Huh?
--[BULMA] Here we go!
[VEGETA]
Don't you die!
Well, that's a shame.
It's no matter. We'll see
them again soon enough.
First, you'll have to
deal with me.
[SHOU, PILAF snoring]
--They made it back!
--[PILAF, SHOU, MAI gasp]
[TRUNKS]
It's Dad, Mom, and Goku!
And big me's not in there!
So he stayed?
Well, that must mean
the future changed, right?
[PILAF]
We're un-apocalypsed!
Hooray for future us!
Oh, thank goodness!
Didn't I tell you
doubting imbeciles
to have faith
in my divine power?
[BULMA]
You liar!
Have faith in your
divine power my butt!
You said gods
affect time differently,
and you killing a Kai
would change Trunks' future
and make it better!
Well, his future's
exactly the same!
What, it didn't change?
[BULMA] All I saw were ruins,
and Black and Zamasu
on a rampage!
We walked into a nightmare!
They almost blew us
out of the sky!
Then where's the big me?
[BULMA]
Still fighting.
He stayed and
took them on alone
to give us
enough time to escape.
[BOTH gasp]
Interesting.
So it didn't change.
Honestly, I had a feeling
that might be the case.
[BULMA]
What are talking about?
You were insulted
we didn't believe you!
Well, it was insulting,
but Trunks made
a convincing argument.
You're not really helping
the situation, Lord Beerus.
How can you be
so casual about this?
--No, Bulma! Stop!
--[BEERUS] Hm?
And why should I?
Because all that
matters right now
is finding a way to prevail!
If we waste this chance,
Trunks stayed there for nothing!
I know, but still.
--[VEGETA] You three!
--[MAI, SHOU, PILAF] Yes!
[VEGETA] Make yourselves useful
and take him inside!
[MAI, SHOU, PILAF shriek]
Aw, come on, Vegeta.
I'm already banged up here,
you don't have to throw me.
[TRUNKS]
Goku.
--[SHOU] He's in bad shape.
--[PILAF] Get a stretcher!
This time he came back
even worse than before.
[WHIS] Did they mention
anything about the other gods
in that timeline?
Yeah. They mentioned it,
all right.
They said they killed
all the gods,
and they were
the only ones left.
Hmm.
[BULMA growls]
[BEERUS]
Mmm.
[VEGETA] And Black's not some
puppet copy of Kakarot,
like we thought.
Zamasu used the
Super Dragon Balls
to steal Kakarot's actual body,
then jumped to Trunk's
alternate timeline,
recruited that Zamasu,
and wished for him
to be indestructible.
[WHIS]
He commandeered Goku's body.
So that's why Black's energy
feels like Zamasu.
Well, that means all our
questions have been answered.
Come on, Whis, we're leaving.
You're just walking away?
[BEERUS] I already eliminated
Zamasu from this reality.
If he's running around
a different timeline,
that's none of my business.
You people can do
whatever you want from here.
Oh, come on!
[WHIS]
My lord has spoken.
Good luck in all your
battles, earthlings.
[BULMA gasps]
No more ramen for you!
Dad, wait--!
[VEGETA] Don't follow me, boy.
I need to think.
[GOTEN snoring]
[GOTEN]
Uh? Trunks?
[KRILLIN]
Uh, Goku's missing?
[CHICHI]
What else do you call it?
He hasn't come home!
[KRILLIN] Is he still off
dealing with Black?
Usually he comes home
when he's hungry,
so I started cooking
lunch while I waited.
But I just kept
waiting and cooking
and waiting and cooking
and now look how much I made!
[KRILLIN] Now, that's what
I call a power lunch.
I've called Bulma but I
can't get through to her!
If you know where he is
you better tell me right now!
I have no idea, okay?
You lying to me?
[KRILLIN] Come on, Chichi,
give me some credit.
Do you see the uniform?
I am a man of the law,
servant of the people!
I would never keep something
from a worried citizen!
[CHICHI grunts]
[KRILLIN chuckles]
And speaking of my sworn duty,
it's time to patrol!
Don't you dare!
I'll see ya later,
Chichi, good luck!
[CHICHI]
Krillin!
Come on, Mom,
let me take you home.
You don't have to worry--
Dad'll come home eventually.
He always does.
He should come home now!
--[GOHAN] Huh?
--[CHICHI] Uh!
Is that Trunks and Goten?
After bedtime?!
[VEGETA]
Just hang on, Trunks.
I'll find a way to
defeat them. I swear it!
[BULMA]
The answer is obviously no!
You kids are strong,
but you don't even
have a chance against them!
They're too powerful,
even for Goku!
[VEGETA]
Hm!
But we want to do our part!
We can't let them
wreck his future!
[BULMA]
I get how you feel, I do,
but you going there won't help!
Just let Goku handle this!
[TRUNKS] But Mom, big me's
fighting them all alone!
I can't sit around
doing nothing!
[BULMA] Even if I did
think you could help,
can you imagine
what Chichi would do
if she found out I let her
precious Goten go to the future?
So for the last time,
leave it to Goku--
he's our best chance!
You two can wait here
and see him off, okay?
[TRUNKS]
But Mom!
--[VEGETA] I--!
--[CHICHI] Bulma!
--[BULMA gasps]
--Hey, I'm up here!
Oh. Great, just what I need.
You two run and hide, and don't
come out till she's gone!
Oh, hey there, Chichi.
What are doing out so late?
Goku is missing. Do you
have any idea where he is?
[BULMA]
Goku? Uh, no, beats me.
We're sorry to just
drop in like this, Bulma.
My dad hasn't
been home in a while,
so we're getting
worried, you know.
Yeah, that is a mystery.
[CHICHI] Knowing him,
he's probably gone off
to fight some other
battle-crazed bonehead!
What, at this hour?
[chuckles]
Oh, I seriously doubt that!
[CHICHI] What about Trunks and
Goten? Are they out here?
[BOTH]
Eek!
[BULMA] What? Uh. No.
Ha. Why do you ask?
[CHICHI]
I saw them flying around.
Sneaking out at night, like a
couple of juvenile delinquents!
[SHOU]
Bulma!
Your dad said he successfully
increased the efficiency
of the time machine
fuel production
and it should be ready soon!
Hold on, a time machine?
Oh, it's just a code name
for our newest model.
[TRUNKS] Uuh! Dad?
Oh no. I mean, hey?
[CHICHI]
Goten! So you are here.
What do you think you're
doing out here this late?
Care to explain?!
[BULMA chuckles]
Uh, boys will be boys.
[PICCOLO]
So they're still a threat?
[CHICHI]
What? Who's still a threat?
Bulma, what are you
hiding from me?
[BULMA]
Nothing! I'm hiding nothing!
--[GOKU] Bulma.
--[CHICHI, GOHAN] Huh?
[GOKU] You got anything
good to eat around here?
Now that the pain
is starting to fade
I'm noticing how hungry I am.
--[BULMA] Oh, boy.
--[CHICHI] There you are!
Oh hey, Chichi.
Goku, why am I
seeing bandages
and a gigantic hole
in your outfit?
It's just a little
flesh wound.
I got beat up by my own body!
What the heck does that mean?
[laughing]
[GOKU] Hey, Gohan,
are those lunch boxes?
Did you make those for me?
What? Well, yes, but Goku...
[GOKU] Thanks, Chichi!
You're too good to me!
Oh man, these are great!
Nobody cooks like you do!
This'll help me feel
a hundred percent in no time!
[CHICHI]
Yeah, yeah. Can we get back
to what you were saying, please?
What was I saying? I forget.
[CHICHI] You were telling
me how you got hurt!
[sighs]
Look, here's the truth.
There's something
really bad happening
in the future with older Trunks.
[BOTH]
Huh?
After all that mess
with the Androids,
his world's in trouble again?
This time there's a
phony Goku wreaking havoc.
Or to be more accurate,
the Supreme Kai
from the Tenth Universe
stole Goku's body
and now he's using it
to terrorize the entire planet!
That's right. And I swear
I'm gonna make him pay.
Not only did he take my body
without even asking,
he killed Goten and Chichi
with my own hands!
What?! You mean Goten is dead?
Oh, Goten you didn't tell me.
Did it hurt? Was there bleeding?
I don't see a halo.
Are you guys sure?
He looks fine to me!
Now now, calm down, Chichi.
It hasn't happened yet.
It's in the future,
or at least a version of it,
where Zamasu successfully
takes down his master.
That frees him up to
get the Super Dragon Balls
and then Goku's body.
I'm lost. Can we see a
flow chart or something?
[BULMA] Look, all you need to
know is this Zamasu guy is bad,
and he takes Goku's body--
you with me?
Then he crosses timelines
to the version of reality
Trunks is from,
and teams up with
the Zamasu who exists there.
Then they start
decimating Trunks' future!
Trunks takes his time
machine looking for help,
arriving in our timeline
a little while ago.
So the reason Goku's
been away from home, Chichi,
is that he and Vegeta
have been traveling
to Trunks' future
to stop these creeps!
[GOHAN] So is that
why Trunks came back here?
[GOHAN]
I had no idea.
Well? So, did you win yet?
Actually, we lost
pretty bad and had to
come back twice already.
[BOTH gasp]
Are you kidding me?!
You lost twice to the guy
who killed Goten?
Or kills or sometimes
kills or whatever?
As his father
you should be ashamed!
I was watching when
Goku first fought him,
and he didn't seem strong enough
to give you this much trouble.
[VEGETA] Trust me.
They're the real deal.
One battle with Kakarot
was enough to show Black
how to reach his own
god-level of Super Saiyan,
and he gets stronger each fight.
Then there's the other Zamasu.
They used the Super Dragon Balls
to make him indestructible.
And since they're two
versions of the same fighter,
their coordinated attacks
are devastating.
I hate to admit it, but we
can't defeat them head-on.
Okay, so then
what can we do?
Figuring that out is the
whole reason we came back!
Well, yelling at him
isn't going to help!
But we have to do
something fast,
or the big me is done for!
Wait, why isn't Trunks here?
He took a stand
against both of them
so that we could get away.
Come on, Dad, there's gotta
be something you haven't tried.
I've been thinking,
and there are other techniques.
The problem is
we're dealing with
two strong opponents at once.
Fighting to a draw may be the
best we can possibly hope for.
[GOHAN sighs]
[PICCOLO]
There's one way to win.
What, Piccolo? Let's hear it!
Containment.
Care to elaborate?
There's an ancient
technique called
the Evil Containment Wave
that Master Roshi tried
a long time ago to trap
the old King Piccolo.
[ALL]
Hmmm.
--[ROSHI growls]
--[KING PICCOLO yells]
--[ROSHI] Evil Containment!
--[KING PICCOLO screams]
[ALL] King Piccolo?!
Talk about a throwback!
If you can keep them still
long enough to catch them
in the wave and
your aim is right,
then the technique
could trap them both.
[GOKU] Oh right, that was
back when I was just a kid.
We wouldn't have to take them
out, we'd just seal them away.
[VEGETA] And you're positive
it would hold them?
Yes. If the seal
remains unbroken,
they'll be locked away forever.
Why didn't we
think of this before?
All we have to do
is bottle them up
and they'll be gone for good?
Then all those
survivors will be safe,
and they can rebuild the earth!
[GOHAN chuckles]
--[TRUNKS] Aah!
--[GOTEN chuckles]
He could be okay.
Bulma. How soon can we leave?
The machine should be
fueled up in about 12 hours.
Going back to the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber?
[VEGETA] Of course.
Maybe we'll seal them.
But not until I've given them
my own brand of punishment.
The Evil Containment Wave.
How do I do that again, exactly?
[KRILLIN] Master Roshi
can show you, right?
--[PICCOLO chuckles]
--[GOKU] Oh, yeah!
I'll gladly show you myself.
Nah, that's cool. Roshi's
the expert, right? See ya.
Ah! I...
[BULMA] Well, Piccolo, you can
still show us if you want.
[ROSHI]
The Evil Containment Wave?
Yeah! You can teach me
tonight, can't you?
[ROSHI]
What enemy could he be facing
where he needs to resort
to a technique like that?
[GOKU]
Just like old times! Please?
Well, I can't think of
any reason I shouldn't, Goku.
Assuming, that is,
you understand
how truly dangerous
this power can be.
I do.
All righty, just don't
say I didn't warn ya!
--Turtle!
--Huh?
What? Me? Whoa wait, why me?
[GOKU yells]
Evil Containment!
[TURTLE screaming]
[grunting]
--[yells]
--[TURTLE hollers]
What, I missed?
[TURTLE yelling]
Big rock, big rock!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I'm way too old for this.
[TURTLE groans]
You need more focus, kid.
Try it again.
--[GOKU] Right!
--[TURTLE] Huuuh?
[laughing]
Okay, you ready?
[TURTLE hollering]
[screaming]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU] Missed again?
Okay, third time's the charm!
[TURTLE]
Uuuh! No! Please, have mercy!
I'm supposed to be retired!
[GOKU yells]
It worked! All right! Yeah!
Hey, that's it!
Then you just put the lid
back on the jar,
tie some string around it
to hold the enchanted charm,
and the seal is good to go!
Hang on a second.
I'll go whip up the charm.
[GOKU]
Thanks, old man!
You can thank me by
taking me out some time
to meet some
smokin' young hotties!
[groans]
[GOWASU]
So despite your actions,
the future was unchanged?
Are you gonna
harp on that, too?
[whispers] You would know
far better than I, attendant.
Did I say something wrong?
The earthlings have been
condemning my lord
over his miscalculation,
and now he feels responsible,
which is quite a rare thing.
That's enough!
Now let's talk about Zamasu.
Obviously I could
annihilate both versions
without even breaking a sweat.
But that would require
jumping through space-time,
which is forbidden
for Destroyers.
[GOWASU] Understood. I will do
all I can. It's my duty.
All this is happening because
I chose Zamasu as my apprentice.
A grave mistake.
♪ Closing Song ♪
1, 2, 3, I'm hungry
Nothin'  but
fried rice fantasies
I want fried rice,
I'm so hungryyyyyy-yeah!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And I'm sorry to keep
Black and Zamasu waiting,
but when we do get there,
we're gonna stop them for sure.
[GOKU BLACK laughs]
This rubble will be
your graveyard.
[GOKU]
Ha! Did you hear that, Vegeta?
Black is feeling confident.
Why don't you take a turn,
and show him the results
of your latest training.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Don't You Disgrace
Saiyan Cells!
Vegeta's Fierce Battle
Commences!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?