♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
with universal
survival at stake,
the Tournament of Power
was narrowed to two teams.
Goku, Vegeta, Frieza,
and 17 against Jiren and Top.
[TOP]
You demon.
Farewell, Trooper.
I'm more for poetic justice.
Ha!
[TOP screams]
[NARRATOR]
Up against the ropes,
Top revealed a shocking secret.
He was the Eleventh Universe's
next Destroyer-in-training.
[TOP] I won't be fighting
for justice any longer.
That side of me is through.
[yells]
[BELMOD] All that remained
was for him to make
the decision and
accept the mantle.
Yes! We have now witnessed
the birth of Top the Destroyer!
[NARRATOR]
Bestowed with the immense power
of a Destroyer God, Top has
quickly overwhelmed Frieza.
The battle continues... now!
[NARRATOR] "Surpass Even a God!
Vegeta's Sacrifice Strike!"
[FRIEZA groaning]
It would be so easy for me
to expunge your helpless soul
from existence, but that
would only disqualify me.
[FRIEZA groaning]
[groaning]
Trash deserves to
be tossed, correct?
[thud]
[FRIEZA groaning]
[A17] Sorry, my hand
must have slipped.
It wasn't my intention
to pummel you that hard.
[TOP]
You.
I have to give you credit for
surviving this long against me.
Well fought, but there
is no way you can win.
You so sure?
'Cause I say as long
as I'm still on my feet
I've always got a chance.
[yelling]
So you're refusing to submit.
Then you leave me
no choice, fighter.
[A17 yells]
[TOP]
Perish!
[gasps]
[TOP yells]
That failed. So now what?
[TOP]
Hakai!
[A17]
What?
[TOP grunts]
Hide all you like,
I will find you.
[gasps]
[TOP]
Hm?!
I told you hiding is futile.
[TOP]
Hakai!
Hm?
[yelling]
[TOP gasps]
[ALL gasp]
He's buried Top under
that huge pile of rubble!
He used Top's destruction
power against him!
Nice work, 17!
[TOP]
Hakai!
[TOP yells]
[A17 groaning]
As with your teammate,
I cannot destroy you
and stay in the fight.
I'll have to
finish you like this.
Feel my grand power
and be vanquished.
[A17 groans]
[laughing]
You really got me.
It's rare that I'm
made so helpless,
and it does wonders
for my motivation.
You've inspired me, Destroyer.
Consider this my way
of saying "thank you."
[yells]
[TOP grunting]
That's a technique
I call "paralysis."
Now it's you who's
unable to move.
And it's not the only gift of
gratitude I'm sending you.
Ha!
[laughing]
Uh?!
[TOP grunts]
Meaningless.
[growls]
[yelling]
[TOP grunting]
[TOP]
Ha!
[FRIEZA groaning]
[TOP yells]
[FRIEZA screams]
[yells]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[yelling]
[FRIEZA] You simply
don't know when to stop!
[yelling]
[gasps]
[BOTH grunt]
[TOP]
Do you understand now?
You can attack me all you like.
But with the Energy of
Destruction shielding me,
you have no chance.
I will remove both
of you from this ring
of shattered rock
and send you to the seats.
Be grateful you are not
immediately destroyed.
[VEGETA, GOKU grunting]
Ahh, Goku and Vegeta.
[JIREN]
You're both getting cocky.
[VEGETA, GOKU grunt]
[yelling]
[BOTH gasp]
17! Frieza!
Ah, man, they both got
nailed by Jiren's attack!
Are they all right?
It would be tough for anyone to
take one of his shots head-on.
Damn it all.
[VEGETA grunts, yells]
[yelling]
Now you will have to face me.
[growls]
[TOP yelling]
That's just great. Your dad
and Vegeta just got split up.
When they were together, they
at least seemed to be holding
their ground against
Jiren, but now...
Agreed. If they
realign like this,
then the tide is going
to turn against us.
Jiren's strength already
seemed insurmountable,
and with Top's transformation,
our numbers will not be enough.
This could quickly become grim.
Go, Vegeta! Get outta there!
[VEGETA groaning]
[TOP yelling]
[VEGETA grunting]
[yells]
[VEGETA]
Final Flash!
[TOP]
Hakai!
You'll need more than your fancy
Destruction Energy to stop me!
[yelling]
[TOP growls]
[TOP yells]
[VEGETA]
What?!
[growls]
[TOP] So is that the most your
power-up affords you, Saiyan?
You still cannot defeat me,
warrior. Accept your fate.
I guess it pays to become
a Destroyer, doesn't it?
Well, I'll still claim
those Super Dragon Balls.
And I'll keep the promise
I made to Cabba.
I can't afford to lose!
What?
[VEGETA groans]
[VEGETA grunts]
It's hard to believe
he's the same warrior.
He's nothing like
the man I faced before.
[yelling]
[VEGETA grunts]
After all your lofty talk of
justice, now you only destroy.
That's quite a shift for you.
I have no use for justice if
it cannot save our universe.
[VEGETA yelps]
[TOP]
Ha!
[VEGETA groans]
[groans]
[TOP]
And what of you?
You fight merely to keep a
promise to a fellow Saiyan.
You think such a trivial cause
can compete with a
Destroyer's resolve?
I ordain what will
and will not exist.
That's my cause.
And to serve it,
I forsake all else.
[yelling]
[VEGETA grunts]
Vegeta! Get out of the way!
Perish, Seventh Universe--
and be no more.
[VEGETA]
You've forsaken all else,
and dare to call
my cause trivial?
I fight for Bulma.
For Trunks and Bulla.
I fight for the oath I made
to a fellow warrior.
For my Saiyan pride.
I fight for all I've built,
and all I am!
Unlike you, I won't abandon
all that to play god!
[TOP]
Huh?!
[yells]
[TOP groans]
Whoa, where'd that come from?
Way to go! That shot
was incredible, Vegeta!
[VEGETA yelling]
[VEGETA yells]
[gasps]
You think your Destroyer
form will save you--
that it gives you
the strength you need?
Well not if I have anything
to say about it!
--[VEGETA yells]
--[TOP groans]
Come on!
Damn it!
Do what it takes, Top,
use your Hakai.
Focus on his attacks and
destroy them with your power!
As long as his body survives,
that's all that matters!
Our universe will remain,
no matter the price.
Hakai!
[yelling]
[TOP]
What?
[TOP groaning]
Only a failure abandons
his principles and pride!
[TOP groaning]
Do you actually think
I'd let you stop me?
[TOP]
Hakai!
[VEGETA grunts]
I'll hit you with an attack
you won't be able to destroy.
[yelling]
Astounding.
He's amassing a tremendous
amount of energy.
[gasps] He wouldn't!
[chuckles]
The key to defeating you
is to obliterate you
so completely
your regeneration
won't be possible.
[BUU gasping]
[VEGETA]
Goodbye to you all.
Bulma...
Trunks...
And, yes, even you Kakarot.
[whimpering]
[VEGETA grunting]
[yells]
[screaming]
[yelling]
Vegeta, you're not really gonna
use that suicidal move, are you?
[VEGETA yelling]
[yells]
[TOP yelling]
[screaming]
[yelling]
[yells]
[gasping]
[TOP screams]
[DYSPO gasping]
What happened?
[TOP groaning]
You fought most admirably, sir.
[BELMOD]
Hmph.
But Top, how could
he defeat you?
Wow, I thought that
fight was amazing!
Yes, and so did I!
Very, very super amazing!
Contestant Top of the
Eleventh is eliminated
from the Tournament of Power.
Where's Vegeta?
Did he really do it?
Did he lay down his own
life to knock out Top?
It can't be. Vegeta...
[ALL gasping]
[KRILLIN gasps]
Wait, look!
[GOHAN]
It's him!
[pants]
Don't count me out yet.
He's really okay!
Thank goodness!
It's astonishing he could
detonate that much energy
and still have
the strength to survive.
Guess we can thank
Super Saiyan Blue
and that even higher
power he reached.
Vegeta's vastly more powerful
now than he was the last time
he used that technique
against Majin Buu,
when it cost him everything.
You mean he's so much
stronger now his body
could weather the blast?
That's so awesome!
But even though he's
still in one piece,
he's completely
drained his energy.
Look at him. He's barely
staying on his feet.
17!
Yeah, he's okay, too!
Though it looks like he's taken
some real damage of his own.
They'll have to be careful,
but now there's only
one opponent left.
As tough as the Seventh is,
I never imagined Jiren
would be alone in the ring.
[DYSPO]
It's up to you, Jiren!
Heh. How disgraceful.
Although it shouldn't
have surprised me.
[gasps]
[GOKU]
What are you talking about?
[GOKU yelps]
[VEGETA, A17 grunt]
It's stunning you could
find so much power
without sacrificing
your ideals.
You've fought hard
to defeat Top.
Well done.
[VEGETA growls]
Hmph.
[GOKU grunting]
Heh. There's something
I would like you to see.
[yelling]
Well, this should
be interesting.
[TOP yelling]
What the hell?
[NARRATOR] With his daring
and explosive technique,
Vegeta has defeated
Top the Destroyer,
leaving Jiren as
the only opponent left.
But even though he is
outnumbered four to one,
Jiren has begun to unleash
his hidden power,
becoming an even
more incredible foe.
Four minutes remain in
the Tournament of Power.
Next time, on Dragon Ball Super.
Whirling all around
and then back again
The song that connects you
to the heavens
Strength that goes
beyond all measure
Expanding to a beat
that won't end
The meteors fall like rain drops
Astrological tears
from my eyelids
A strong emotion
from deep within
Has been awakened
A spark of possibility
Shines softly like a star
in the night sky
A wish from long
ago now shoots by
And I'm awakened
A never-ending melody,
so enchanting
You're always the one
who makes me tremble
The meteors keep falling down
Surging right into my heart
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Now that Jiren's unleashing
his hidden power,
he's even more off-the-charts,
and I don't care how
many fighters we have,
it's hard to see how
we can take him down!
Jiren's breaking up our combo
attacks like they're nothing!
And with Vegeta and me
in serious trouble,
it looks like it's up to
17 to get us through!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"The Approaching Wall!
A Hopeful Final Barrier!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?