♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
as contestants continued to drop
out in the Tournament of Power,
Caulifla and Kale reached
new levels of strength,
and teamed up against a weakened
Goku, two against one.
But he still wasn't making
it easy for them.
[GOKU]
Ha!
[KALE grunting]
[screams]
You've got talent I've
only rarely seen.
But you both still need to
learn how to finish a fight.
Hey, take it easy!
Damn it. I'm a disgrace!
Hey, Kale.
We've been saying together
we're the toughest force
in the cosmos, haven't we?
Yeah, that's right.
Ha!
[NARRATOR]
On the brink of elimination,
the two Saiyan women used their
Kai's Potara earrings to merge.
No, it couldn't be!
[KEFLA]
Hmph.
This is Kale.
Plus Caulifla!
We're Kefla!
[NARRATOR] Thanks to
the exponential power-up
of this merging technique,
Kefla easily overwhelmed Goku
with superior
strength and speed.
[KEFLA] Now you'll see
the real depth of my power!
[NARRATOR] The battle roars
into its next round... now!
[NARRATOR] "Goku vs. Kefla!
Super Saiyan Blue Beaten?"
[GOKU screams]
[groaning]
How's that?
[GOKU grunting]
Fusing with Potaras--
I didn't see that coming.
This power flowing through me...
It's freakin' awesome!
[GOKU growls]
Her energy's wild!
There's just no telling
how high it's gonna go!
All right, you've got it!
Now harness that power
and put Goku to bed!
There's no one in the cosmos
who can stop me now!
[KEFLA laughs] Guess I need
to step off the throttle.
I've got so much power
it's easy to overshoot ya.
But I won't miss again.
[GOKU]
Huh?
[KEFLA yelling]
[groans]
[KEFLA]
Ha!
[GOKU grunting]
Your strength and speed
are in a whole new class
than when you two were
solo, that's for sure.
Ha, ha. Don't fall for me yet!
[GOKU grunting]
I'm only gettin' started!
Let's dance!
[KEFLA grunting]
Man, she's off the charts!
[KEFLA]
What's wrong--feelin' dizzy?
Why don't you go lie down!
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU groans]
Hell yeah, this power
totally rocks!
[laughing]
[BEERUS growls]
Damn it!
Hey, Champa! You know you're
breaking the rules, don't you?
[CHAMPA] Aw. I think
you're just jealous.
Why don't you use
the Potaras yourself?
[BEERUS growls]
So we can be disqualified, too,
when they realize they're
illegal enhancements?
Yeah, nice try.
[sighs]
I like it! Merging
is so fun to watch!
Yes, and fun to watch is good!
[BOTH]
Merging! Merging!
Merging! Merging...
The Omni-Kings have spoken;
the use of Potara
earrings is allowed.
What?! Hand them over now, Kai!
For our victory, the Potaras
will not be necessary.
I trust I don't need to
explain why, Lord Mosco.
[MOSCO beeping]
Lord Quitela.
We will abstain as well.
Of course. There's no need.
[laughs]
--[TOP growling]
--[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA] Who do those uppity
Saiyan females think they are?
Their energy's
climbing even higher!
[TOP grunts]
[groaning]
[VEGETA]
Oafish bastard!
[TOP] If you're so enraptured
by Goku's battle,
then I'll let you watch it
in peace from the bench.
Oh, screw you!
[screaming]
[SAONEL, PILINA yelling]
[GOHAN grunts]
Big mistake.
Ha!
[GOHAN]
Masenko Ha!
[GOHAN grunts]
[PILINA groans]
Pilina! Are you okay?
I will be soon.
[yelling]
Should we tell 'em
how impressed we are
with their basic Namekian
techniques, Gohan?
[BEERUS] All right. Once we
have our own merged fighter,
we'll be back in control.
Well then, may I suggest
Androids 17 and 18
as candidates?
[gasps] Hey now, that's my
wife you're talking about!
Oh yes, they are twin
siblings, aren't they?
That would make them
well-suited for merging.
Good thinking, Supreme Kai!
We could call them Android 35;
that has a pleasant ring to it.
If I may, sirs.
While a combined warrior
would be formidable,
it would also create
the possibility that two
of our fighters could be
eliminated with one wrong move.
Yes, that's a good point.
Fine, no merging!
Um. But wouldn't the power
gained make the risk worthwhile?
Not in a contest where the
biggest team is the winner!
And that's final, Kai!
[sighs] I hate it when
Mom and Dad fight.
It seems unlikely that any one
fighter can stop Goku or Jiren.
Perhaps melding Zarbuto
and Rabanra together
is the best option we have.
Merging bodies is beautiful.
I would love to witness that.
All righty.
You do the honors.
Get ready, Zarbuto and
Rabanra. Be very careful.
[PELL]
It's simple,
just put them on each
of your opposing ears!
[RABANRA grunts]
Darn this thing.
[PELL]
Hurry up!
I can't get it to stay on me.
Take your helmet off, genius!
And I did my left ear--
you do your right!
[ZARBUTO gasps]
[KEFLA]
Coming through! Out of my way!
[gasping]
[ZARBUTO, RABANRA scream]
[gasping] My sacred Potaras!
How can this be?
Treasures turned to dust.
There's beauty in that, as well.
Got sloppy.
Huh? I don't know who you are,
but if you're looking to fight,
that's fine with me.
Come on, muscles. Bring it on.
[CATOPESRA] Looks like you
got caught in that explosion
and injured your leg.
I was just leveling the playing
field so you'd have a chance.
[CATOPESRA] Heh, at least
your spirit's intact.
Very well!
Prepare to be vanquished!
[A18]
He's fast.
[CATOPESRA grunts]
[gasps]
[CATOPESRA] When did you
get here, foul villain?
Says the guy in a mask
about to punch a
lady in the face.
[CATOPESRA exhales]
There's no place for pity
on the battlefield.
[A17]
I'll try to remember that.
[CATOPESRA groans]
Bye-bye now.
[CATOPESRA screams]
Do you mind?
I don't remember asking you
for help with that twerp.
Sorry about that, sis.
Next time I'll call ahead.
Face the facts, Goku.
I'm on fire!
You won't get away!
[yelling]
Dammit.
Ooh! A big explosion!
Those are my favorite!
[ALL gasp]
That looked rough!
He's on his heels.
Tells you all you need to
know about Kefla's power.
Sorry to say it, Beerus!
Goku was already overreaching,
and now his stamina's
being taxed even more.
I don't care how good
your little pet Saiyan is,
he doesn't stand a chance
against both of them combined!
Don't let up until
you finish the job!
Knock him out, Kefla!
[BEERUS growls]
Damn it all!
[ALL gasp]
He's all the way up
to Super Saiyan Blue!
[TIEN] Does this mean Goku's
back to full strength already?
Heh. It's about time.
I've been waitin' for this.
Speaking of time, I was
trying to buy a little more,
but if I hold back any longer,
I'll be in major trouble.
Took you this long
to realize that?
Well, better late than never!
Then I guess I'll have
to crank it up!
[KEFLA yelling]
Crazy! Her energy's reaching
all the way up here!
I still can't believe how
massive Kefla's power is!
This time, Goku,
we fight for real.
[growls]
That's it, Kefla! Go all
in and blow him away!
My Lord, may I remind
you we're talking about
Goku at Super Saiyan Blue?
It might be wiser to
test the waters first.
Goku may have come a long way,
but he still hasn't recovered
his full stamina
from when he fought with Jiren.
So you believe that Kefla at
her lower Super Saiyan level
can handle him?
[CHAMPA] Oh, I do now.
Her energy in her current form
is much stronger
than I expected.
Ha, ha, ha. Of course,
I'm hardly ever wrong,
but this was a miscalculation
I don't mind at all.
Heh, heh, heh.
Just don't get scared
and piss your pants.
Yeah, same to you.
Let's do this!
[KEFLA yells]
[GOKU grunting]
[grunting]
They're amazing.
[KEFLA]
Fat chance!
Heh.
[GOKU]
Hmph.
[yelling]
[yells]
Both of their energy levels are
rising even higher, my lord.
Just how far are
they going to go?
Are they trying to shred
apart the entire ring?!
Fuwa! Double fuwa!
[yelling]
[yells]
[JIREN grunts]
[TOP groans]
[VEGETA grunts]
[panting]
[TOP groans]
Kakarot finally got his act
together and went Blue again.
Ha! If you're struggling
this much in that form,
then you're clearly still
running on fumes, Goku!
Even if I am, Kefla,
you won't surpass me!
Maybe I'll turn Blue myself;
you want to see that?
Heh. If you can, go for it!
Oh, trust me, I will. Right
after I show you who's boss!
[GOKU grunts]
[BOTH]
Whoa!
Kefla's fantastic!
And don't forget Goku!
Got a present for ya!
Whoa.
[yelling]
Kaio-ken!
Oh, my! He's at Blue
plus Kaio-ken!
That multiplies the awesome!
Multiple awesomes!
Though I do hate to say
this about my nemesis,
this is an impressive
battle to watch.
Now which one will be crowned
king or queen of
the Saiyan mountain?
Such suspense!
I think I'll treat myself
and watch this show
all the way to the end.
Goku's obviously overextending
himself in this fight.
That Kaio-ken technique boosts
his power in the short term,
but it's a huge drain
on his energy.
Using it when he's run-down
will cause big problems later.
Goku was confronted with
the fearsome power of Kefla
at Super Saiyan, and not even
his Blue could push her back.
While he's well-aware of
the dangers of Kaio-Ken,
he must have determined it
was his only hope to win.
Hang in there!
Find a way to win,
buddy! You have to!
Come on, Kefla. The real
fight starts right now!
Yeah. I can see that.
Damn, you're awesome!
I couldn't ask for
a worthier challenge.
This win is gonna feel great!
[yelling]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU yelling]
[KEFLA grunts]
My arms are tingling from
that punch. That's crazy!
This is sweetest fight
I've ever had!
Freakin'-A, man! I just keep
getting more and more pumped!
[KEFLA yells]
[GOKU]
In that case, I will too.
[GOKU yells]
I'm gonna crush you! He's gone?
Huh?!
[GOKU]
Hmph.
[KEFLA groans]
[screams]
[GOKU]
Hmph.
Yes! He nailed it!
Nicely done, Goku!
Could that have been
a finishing blow?
Don't quit yet. You're strong!
You should still have
enough to get back up!
You can do it!
I gave you those earrings and
you're still mucking it up?
Don't lose, or I'll
make you sorry!
You hear me?!
You've got no excuse!
Don't waste those Potaras
or you'll pay big!
I'm like a payback expert,
and I'll make you pay big like
no one's ever paid big before!
Oh, shut the hell up!
I'm sick of hearing your voice!
[KEFLA grunts] That gut-punch
really stung, Goku.
Savor it. 'Cause it's the last
one you're gonna land!
Heh, heh. Now that's
more like it.
[KEFLA]
Hmph.
She sure is tough.
And that was no glancing blow;
she took the full
force of his punch.
There's no doubt.
Even merged, she must have
reached her body's limit.
Yet somehow, she's
managed to break through
and keep fighting him.
Must be her Saiyan blood--
like Goku, she transcends and
finds new stores of power.
[growls] Even Saiyans hit walls.
And Goku's about to reach his.
He has to win with
his next strike.
Do you hear me, Goku? End this!
Ya ready? Here goes! Ha! Ha!
You really think you're gonna
get me with that same attack?
Ha!
What?
[KEFLA yelling]
[GOKU groaning]
[GOKU grunting]
Gah!
It can't be!
No! Goku!
[KEFLA chuckles]
Terrific attack, Kefla!
With Goku knocked out
of the Tournament,
the Sixth Universe will have
a clear path to victory!
Just finish the job!
Throw him over the side!
I woulda liked to keep
going for a little longer,
but you're obviously spent.
You know what that means.
It's time to take
the plunge, Goku.
[GOKU grunting]
Huh?
[GOKU]
No. This isn't over yet, Kefla.
He got back up!
[CHAMPA laughing]
He's downright woozy!
You've got this! Just lay
into him one more time!
Hurry, Kefla! Finish him!
[KEFLA] Heh, heh.
Still want to go at it, huh?
Well that's okay with me!
Just remember you asked--
when you're choking on my power!
[KEFLA gasps]
[ALL gasp]
All right, what the
hell just happened?
[KEFLA] That was a fluke! Just
blind, stupid luck, you hear me?
And I guarantee you won't be
so lucky this time around.
When I drill these
right into your skull!
What? How did he do that?
His... His eyes!
[CHAMPA gasping]
No way!
Look at the form he's
taken... that glow!
[KRILLIN] It's incredible!
Just like when he fought Jiren!
[TIEN]
Yes, it's unmistakable.
And once again, he's
shattered his own limits.
[BEERUS growling]
I never thought he'd
achieve this divine feat
again in the Tournament.
That we would have the
pleasure of seeing it twice.
Well this time I'll make
sure to soak it up.
Heh. Autonomous Ultra Instinct!
I am looking forward to this!
Yes! I will enjoy him very much!
[gasping]
[NARRATOR] The extreme battle
against the merged warrior
Kefla has once again propelled
Goku to the vaunted level
even Destroyers
struggle to master:
Autonomous Ultra Instinct.
They are extraordinary
Saiyans who refuse all limits,
and continue to find
new levels of power.
Will Goku's Ultra Instinct
spell the end for Kefla,
or will she find some way
to match his heights
and keep her Universe's
hopes alive?
Nineteen minutes remain in
the fateful Tournament of Power.
Next time, on Dragon Ball Super!
A 70 centimeter squared window
Today the sun broke
through the clouds
The rain is fin'ly gone
Gonna open up
the window for once
No reason, just because
This room has been
stained with the sighs
Of everyday regret
Now it's time to clear the air
Every moment was consumed
with my thoughts of you
Knowing in my heart those dreams
won't be coming true
I've always wanted nothing more
than to see your face
I move on knowing that your
mem'ry can't be erased
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Thanks to Kefla's amazing
power-ups forcing me
into a corner, I've somehow
managed to reach
Autonomous Ultra Instinct again!
But she's still not giving up,
and launches another
massive assault.
With these reflexes I can dodge,
but can I figure out
how to attack?
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Signs of a Turnabout!
The Autonomous Ultra
Instinct Erupts!"
Make sure you
don't miss it, okay?