Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me go back to the start
Wishing on the starlight
In the sky, let's paint a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of God
Kyo-Let's☆Mo-Let's☆Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic
I don't care 'bout limits, no regret
Make me tougher even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo' try me
So-Zets☆Cho-Zets☆Dynamic!
Let's Go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going power pumpin' up
something greater waiting not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Super,
Bulma and Jaco journeyed
into space to learn more
about the Seventh Universe's
Super Dragon Balls,
which Bulma hoped
would protect Earth
against the
unpredictable Beerus.
Salutations.
I am Master Zuno.
[NARRATOR] Bulma hoped
Master Zuno would help
with his encyclopedic
knowledge of the cosmos.
But, what he revealed stopped
their mission in its tracks.
Can you tell us everything
about the Super Dragon Balls?
That's my next question!
Very well, I shall give you
a comprehensive answer
on these cosmic artifacts.
Super Dragon Balls
are extremely rare
and only number seven.
They are divided between the
Sixth and Seventh Universes.
[yells]
[bellows]
[VEGETA bellows]
[panting]
Well, you sure don't
make it easy on me.
Every time we fight, you find
flaws I didn't know I had.
[VEGETA]
Hmph!
[VEGETA] Same's true for me,
much as I hate admitting it.
But, I'm glad he came.
I can tell I've made progress.
I can't wait to fight,
and crush, that other team.
[GOKU]
So, this is Monaka guy.
What do you think he's like?
--What?
--That guy Beerus picked.
I'm just wondering
what makes him
the toughest opponent
Beerus has ever faced.
This obsession
of yours is pointless.
Focus on the team
you'll be fighting.
But I can't help it.
We know the Sixth Universe
has strong fighters,
but we don't know
how strong they really are.
[VEGETA] If Beerus
expected a cakewalk,
he would have just relied on us.
The fact he didn't
is all you need to know.
Oh, yeah, right!
You sure are a genius, Vegeta!
[VEGETA]
Compared to you I am.
So, there's gonna be
six awesome new fighters,
including Monaka,
for us to face.
Man, I am super duper pumped up.
[VEGETA]
You sound like a child.
Can't you act your age for once?
[GOKU]
I am acting my age!
You said Saiyans
keep our youth till we're
about eighty, right? Right?
I don't mean your body,
I mean your brain.
Uuuh...
[VEGETA] We're not here to chat.
Let's get back to work.
You got it.
[WHIS] Good day, everyone.
Are we all ready to go?
[ALL]
We're ready, Whis!
[WHIS] Excellent.
We'll begin transportation
to the tournament venue shortly.
Please form a single-file line,
and board the hexahedron.
And no shoving!
Let's try to be civilized.
[TRUNKS]
Whoa, sweet!
[GOTEN]
Where's the door?
Is this thing
really a spaceship?
I don't see any engine!
No, not a spaceship;
a hexahedron!
And you board it like so.
[BOTH gasp]
There, you see--it's simple!
Just step through,
and the smart-wall
will allow you to pass.
[ALL gasp]
The first leg
of our flight will be to
Lord Beerus' world. We'll meet
up with my lord and Monaka
and continue to the site.
Travel time will be
approximately three hours.
While our final destination
will have facilities,
this vessel,
as you see, does not.
So, use the restroom
before boarding, okay?
[ALL]
Okay!
[GOTEN giggles]
[WHIS]
I don't see our Saiyans.
They realize
they have to be there
to fight, don't they?
I've given up trying to care.
I haven't heard a peep from 'em
since they flew off
to train in the Time Chamber.
[JACO]
A-hem! Sorry I'm late.
[BULMA] Oh yeah,
I forgot you were coming.
When a protector
of your galaxy finds room
in his busy schedule
for you, it'd be nice
if you'd at least
pretend to care.
[BULMA]
Huh? Who is this?
Oh, please tell me
that's your new girlfriend!
What's wrong with you?
That's no date!
That's our galaxy's
most important mortal!
Our Galactic King!
Oh, that's neat--
it's good to meet ya.
[GALACTIC KING, JACO gasp]
Goku and Vegeta
better get here quick.
What's the point in going
if our own fighters don't show?
The Earthling does not seem
to be impressed with my visit.
It's just her species, sire!
What we see as
casual indifference
is actually their
highest form of respect!
[WHIS]
Heh.
There you are!
[GOKU] Sorry, you really
lose track of time in there!
Seeing as how it's a Hyperbolic
Time Chamber and all.
You know how it is.
But, we stayed an extra week!
We trained a ton!
[BULMA, WHIS, JACO,
GALACTIC KING gasp]
[BULMA] We're not going
till you shower!
There's no way I'm sharing
that box with your stink!
[indistinctive chatter]
[GOKU]
Thanks for waiting, guys!
I kinda forgot
what a shower feels like!
[VEGETA]
Hah.
[WHIS]
I'm glad you're refreshed.
So, is everyone here?
[KRILLIN]
Wait for me!
Huh? Krillin,
where've you been?
So, were you
summoning the dragon?
Goku! You don't
have tell the whole planet!
All right, all right,
nothing to see here.
[muffled] That does it,
Whis, we're all here.
[WHIS]
Wonderful. Here we go.
[GOTEN]
No way!
What is this place?
This is so cool! Ha-ha!
[sniffs]
Hey Goten, do you smell
something rotten?
[sniffs]
Yeah, big time.
[BUU laughs]
Buu make a stinky!
[GOTEN] I guess in space you
can't open a window, right?
[ALL laugh]
Smells to me like Majin Buu
just made a Majin Poo!
[laughs]
[MR. SATAN] Man, these guys
can't take a joke.
[JACO]
Hello, scrapbook!
[laughs]
You're welcome
to take pictures, patrolman.
But please, no posting them
on the Galactic Net.
My lord does value
his privacy here.
[GOKU]
Huh?
Hey, look Vegeta,
that's gotta be him!
The strongest mortal
Beerus knows!
[VEGETA] He doesn't look
that impressive to me.
Yeah, well, let's not
underestimate him just yet,
and Beerus should know, right?
[BEERUS]
You're late.
Apologies for that, my lord.
But, between the showers
and the defecation,
we just couldn't get moving.
So, you're Monaka aren't you;
the fifth member of our team?
Well, we've been hearing
a lot about you, man!
Good to meet you!
My name is Goku!
Okay.
You are speaking to the most
important weapon we have.
Considering your
utter lack of tact,
you should talk to him
as little as you can.
[GOKU] I was asking Whis what
he could tell me about you,
and he said your name
means "great pontas "
on your world. Is that right?
Yes, pronunciation aside.
It sounded interesting, but I
don't know what pontas are.
Does that mean
strength or something?
It means nipples.
[GOKU chuckles nervously]
I have large,
shapely nipples.
I have ever since I was born.
You don't say.
[chuckles nervously]
Good to know! I guess.
And, this is why
I don't want you to talk.
You got it.
Even up close he still doesn't
look that strong, does he?
Not at all.
I am very confused.
Hey. Whaddaya say you
practice with me real quick?
Nothing big,
just a short little spar--?
Goku! Did I not
already tell you
to save your energy
for your actual opponents?
Okay, okay,
Lord Beerus. I'm sorry!
[BEERUS]
Let's go.
[GOKU yells]
[MONAKA sniffles]
Just how much
brain damage do you have?
Well, I didn't mean to hit him!
I just wanted
to see his reflexes
and I figured he'd duck!
I'm so sorry, dude.
I didn't mean anything
by it, I swear!
Fine. Don't worry
about it. Dude.
[BOTH grunt]
[CHICHI]
Here you go!
I can't believe you
packed a grill, Chichi.
Well, Goku didn't give me
the space picnic he promised.
So, I'm making one myself!
Here, Vegeta!
This is the first decent meal
I've had in three years.
I apologize on what
you're about to witness.
No, thank you. I can't
eat that sort of organism.
[gasps] Watching what you eat
to stay healthy, huh?
That's impressive, man!
I couldn't live without meat!
[WHIS] Almost there.
Just a few more galaxies.
And... wa-la!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
So, they really exist, huh?
Man, they're huge!
They really are
the Super Dragon Balls!
[BULMA]
This is unbelievable, Whis!
When you said they were
as big as planets,
I thought you were exaggerating,
but they really are!
I mean you could actually
live on these things!
[KRILLIN]
Yeah, imagine the power!
No wonder you could
wish for anything.
I think that's more
than enough sightseeing.
Whis, let's go!
[WHIS]
Understood, my lord.
[TRUNKS, GOTEN]
Aw, yeah!
[PICCOLO] Seems like a lot
of trouble for a tournament
they'll only hold once.
Lord Champa
only had a few days--
did he build
all this stuff himself?
No, Saiyan, Destroyers
do not build anything.
And even if we did, my brother
would never be capable of this.
It would just
be paper and sticks.
[CHAMPA]
I heard that, Beerus.
Want to say that to my face?
[BULMA]
So, that's Champa?
Yes. The Destroyer
of the Sixth Universe.
Honestly, I'm shocked
you didn't back out.
Of course I came, Champa.
As if I'd miss the opportunity
to see your face when you lose.
And, take your precious rock
collection for myself.
Glad you're confident.
It'll make taking Earth
much more fun.
[BEERUS] By the way...
I know about your
dirty little secret, Champa.
You stole some of those orbs
from my universe, which
explains your trespassing.
What're you talking about?
We know there are
only seven of them
spread across our two universes,
so that means you must've
taken some of ours!
[shrieks]
Who told you that?
[BEERUS] I knew you were
up to something.
Wait! I did no such thing.
If you weren't my
twin brother I'd destroy you
for such a theft.
Not that it matters.
They'll all be mine soon anyway.
You should be using this time
preparing for
inevitable failure.
[VADOS]
Are you two done yet?
If so then I can escort
you all to the arena now.
As you can see, we have
ample seating for everyone.
Are those seats
made outta rock?
Ugh. Don't you have
cushions or something?
Trunks is right!
We came a long way for this,
so you could at least
make us comfortable!
No one forced you
to come, Earthling!
I think she has a point, Champa.
What kind of a host
allows their guests
to sit in such cut-rate seats?
Honestly, I'd be humiliated
if I were the one responsible.
You take that back!
--[BEERUS] Whis!
--Yes, my lord.
I always do enjoy redecorating.
Now, let's see.
[ALL gasp]
[whispers]
You're making me look bad.
Why didn't you make
it fancy? I know you can
do better than
stone bleachers!
Sir, it would be
disrespectful for an artist
to create a work
of art her patron
would not appreciate
or understand.
That's my older sister for you.
Yes. She was just trying
to operate on your level.
You should thank your attendant
for being so
well-heeled, Champa.
[BULMA]
Good luck, boys! Do your best!
Okay!
[SUPREME KAI]
Hello, Goku.
It's been far too long.
Hey. You guys have
your own bodies again,
but I thought once you fused
together you couldn't go back.
That's normally true,
and as much as we hate
relying on their power,
we asked the Namekians
to separate us
using their Dragon Balls.
We tried to make do,
but after a while
we just couldn't bear it.
Oh, so that's why
I couldn't find your energy.
I was still looking for
the two of you together.
What's up, Kibito?
It's good to see ya again!
Good to see you too, Goku.
When we heard about these
matches we couldn't resist!
[GOKU]
And how are you, old-timer?
Staying busy?
Oh, you bet. Mostly just
watching beetle wrestling
and keeping up with
my favorite magazines.
You know I nearly
had an aneurysm
watching your battle
with Beerus.
[GOKU chuckles]
Yeah.
That Seventh
Universe mortal is being
awfully familiar
with his Supreme Kai.
He certainly is.
[GOKU]
Hey guys, what's up?
I'll take a shot
in the dark here,
are you the Supreme Kai
from the Sixth Universe?
Why, yes, I am!
How did you know that?
You got the same haircut!
It's good to meet ya!
Come on, Goku.
[GOKU] Right, sorry!
Catch ya later, okay? Bye!
Knock 'em dead!
Um, excuse me.
But are you actually
friends with him?
With that mortal?
[ELDER KAI chuckles]
We've been through
a lot together;
it's a long story.
[GOKU] So, that's
the other team, huh?
Uah! That looks like a robot--
isn't that cheating?
But I don't know,
maybe he's some kind of
--Goku, look!
--a robot-like person?
[screams]
Whoa, that looks like Frieza!
I guess their universe
has one, too!
And that bear guy
looks pretty tough.
[CABBA]
Hello, gentlemen. Sorry.
This may seem like
a strange question,
but are the two of you Saiyans?
Well, yeah,
how'd you know that?
I see. So, there were Saiyans
in your universe as well?
Still are! And I should know,
'cause I am one!
--You're kidding me!
--You're a Saiyan too?
No tail. Did you cut it off,
or did someone else do it?
What do you mean a tail?
Actually, the clothes
you're wearing do look familiar.
The Saiyans in our universe
dressed that way
in the old days,
before Frieza enslaved us.
Frieza? Is that a person?
Sorry, I don't know
what you're talking about.
I've never heard
that name before.
[VEGETA] Sounds like
our history's different,
like the two Earths.
Let's see if we can
get to the bottom of this.
What's the name of the planet
your Saiyans call home?
[CABBA]
Planet Sadla, of course.
Planet Sadla?
You're telling me that in your
universe it still exists?
Uh, yeah, you mean
it doesn't in yours?
That's right.
What we call our "birth world"
was destroyed in a civil war.
After its decimation,
we conquered another planet
and called it Vegeta.
Wait a minute, what do you
mean you conquered it?
Like you took it from
another civilization?
Yes, that's what
conquering means.
Don't tell me you have
a problem with that;
your Saiyans are
warriors are they not?
Well, yeah, we're warriors,
but we don't take
what doesn't belong to us!
Other races hire us
to fight injustice,
not create it ourselves!
Wow, your Saiyans
sound like nice people!
They're like, totally different.
[VADOS]
Boys, do you mind?
We do have
a written exam to get to.
--[GOKU] I hate exams.
--[PICCOLO] Let's go.
If we have time,
I'd like to hear more
about your Planet Sadla.
There's no need
to look nervous.
We were conquerors in
the past, but not anymore.
Well, in that case,
you got it. I'd be glad to.
[VEGETA] Of course, I won't show
you any mercy in the ring.
[CABBA]
Oh, yeah. Neither will I.
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU groans]
What you see before you
are simple questions
designed to ensure
you possess the most
basic degree of intelligence.
You have ten minutes
to complete the test.
Score higher than
fifty points, and you pass.
[whistles]
[GOKU]
Okay, I can do this.
So, the kid goes to the store
and buys thirteen breads.
Or, uh, thirteen loaves
of breads, whatever.
But on the way back
from the store
he runs into three friends and
gives them all two loaves each.
Because he's obviously
a nice guy.
No reading out loud
or you will not pass.
--[GOKU] Eeeh!
--[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU] Then how am I
supposed to think?
[VADOS]
Quietly.
[BEERUS grunts] What do you
mean we're down to four?
We haven't even
started fighting yet!
We couldn't do
anything about it!
Once Buu falls asleep,
there's no waking him up.
Trust me, we've gone
through this before!
[VEGETA grunts]
I told you he wasn't
a good choice for our team,
but you wouldn't
listen, would you?
Don't blame me; you're the one
that suggested the stupid test!
[VEGETA grunts]
Err! That's enough! It just
means you're responsible
for an extra opponent now.
--[WHIS] Lord Beerus?
--What do you want?
I'm sorry,
but we have to decide
the order of
our contestants now.
[growls]
[sighs]
Fine. Monaka fights last.
Use rock-paper-scissors
to decide the rest.
That works for me!
[GOKU, PICCOLO, VEGETA]
One, two, three!
[rings]
[TD REF]
Ladies and Gentleman!
Thank you for
your incredible patience!
The Sixth and Seventh
Universes Invitational,
The Tournament of Destroyers,
will now begin!
So, hold on to your hats
and get ready for the show!
Now, the singing of
the joint universal anthem!
[BULMA, CHICHI]
Huh, what's a universal anthem?
♪
♪ It's a big universe,
and there's two! ♪
[ALL gasp]
[TD REF]
That was beautiful. Thank you.
[ALL groan]
And now, the first
match will begin!
Let's see who we've got!
From the Sixth Universe...
Contestant Botamo!
And representing
universe number seven...
[TD REF]
Contestant Goku!
Goku in the first match.
That's quite a start.
Not holding anything back.
Give him hell, Goku!
[CHAMPA]
One of the Saiyans, huh?
He was the one
so eager to fight! Ha!
[chuckles]
[rings]
[TD REF]
You may begin!
Goodbye to our adventure
In twilight we must go our separate ways
And try to discover the path to our own destiny
I can't find the words
to tell you how much our parting hurts
I hope you know I'll always love you
And all that we shared will be remembered
How could I forget your face?
All my memories erased
I can still hear the melody of your voice
Petals fall in from above
Fade away, all that we love
In the twilight,
fade away,
fade away
Sayonara,
fade away,
fade away
Hey, it's me, Goku!
The tournament I was excited for
is officially under way!
And leave it to that tricky Champa to
recruit a fighter whose moves I can't see coming!
And he doesn't seem fazed
by any of my attacks, either!
I could really be in a jam.
Oh well! You know how I like to fight!
When things aren't going my way,
it's time to level up!
Next time on Dragon Ball Super:
Make sure you don't miss it, okay?