♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super...
[snarls]
[yells]
[BOTH yell]
[NARRATOR] The battle
between Goku and Frieza,
an epic grudge match over
ten years in the making,
had finally begun.
After their first round
resulted in a stalemate,
Goku revealed a power level
never seen before.
[yells]
[NARRATOR] Learning from
the divine energy
he harnessed in
his fight with Beerus,
and from his recent
training with Whis,
Goku transformed to a level
beyond even Super Saiyan God.
A transformation
he could make on his own
without help, or rituals.
So, what are
you calling this,
Super Saiyan
with blue hair dye?
[chuckles]
That's funny.
I'd say it's a little more
complicated than that.
I know you don't
have the patience
for the full story, Frieza.
But I got a taste of something
called Super Saiyan God
and then tapped into
that power on my own,
and it's the Super Saiyan
level of that.
[snarls]
[NARRATOR] Frieza claims he's
been hiding something, too.
Could it be enough
to match Goku?
Well, I've held up
my side of the deal
and shown you my real power.
It's your turn.
[NARRATOR]
"A Full-Throttle Battle!
The Vengeful Golden Frieza"!
[chuckles]
You say you have this
"Super Saiyan God" power.
So, are you honestly
suggesting your strength
is on the level of
some immortal deity, Goku?
As far as I
understand it, it is.
[laughs]
I merely came to settle
a score, and yet here I am
getting to face
the God of Monkeys!
I'm honored to share the sky
with you, oh holy one.
I bet you are.
Well, whatever your power is,
you've obviously trained
very hard to attain it.
I am gracious enough to give
a compliment where it's due.
And I don't like to brag,
but I gotta admit
it was some hard training.
I barely got through it.
Classic obsessed Saiyan.
You can't be happy unless
you're punching something.
You've seen my real power
and you're still
making jokes about it, Frieza.
I take it that means
you think you can match this.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
This is bad. Goku just
showed his ace card
and it doesn't look like
Frieza is nervous at all.
It's like he doesn't even care.
Either this is some
sort of desperate bluff
or Frieza's actually
hiding power
that's comparable to Goku's.
Yeah, the way
this thing is going,
we're about to see
one hell of a crazy fight.
Hey, don't worry!
You've got this, Goku!
You're gonna knock the stuffing
right out of this loser,
I can totally tell!
Still not helping.
[JACO]
Oh, nice!
[camera shutter clicks]
I've never even heard of
a Saiyan with blue hair.
This could be a huge deal!
--[KRILLIN] Huh?
--[camera shutter clicks]
Jaco, come on.
It's hardly the time
for a photo shoot.
Well, as you're
so fond of reminding me,
I am a Super-Elite
Galactic Patrolman,
and it's my duty to document
interplanetary conflict.
I need these photographs for my
official report to command!
And what's going to happen
when they get the report?
Let's see,
if I have to guess...
I'd say Earth will be declared
a max-warning-level
Ultra Hazardous Zone.
And, as standard
risk management procedure,
they'll send a mega-missile
to blow it up.
[shrieks]
Give me that!
[JACO gasps]
What are you doing?
What do you think
I'm doing, patrol clown?
I'm saving the planet from you!
Well, what are you
waiting for, Frieza?
I've held up my side of the
bargain so now it's your turn.
Stop building it up
and show me your power.
Because, I'm not
gonna wait much longer.
Very well, Saiyan.
I'll show you now.
[gasps]
[yells]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[screams]
Stop trying to sneak up
on me. It's not gonna work.
[snarls]
[chuckles]
There's a method to this
you're too thick-skulled
to understand. I've been
gauging your strength.
The true fruits of my labor
are sweet, indeed.
I wanted to ensure
you deserve a taste.
So, you convinced yet?
[chuckles]
Yes Goku,
I believe I've established
you aren't bluffing.
Aren't you the one
who makes fun of me
for being so honest? I hate
lies, you've gotta know that.
Ugh! This is getting
ridiculous, Frieza!
Stop basking
in your damn spotlight
and show us what you've got!
[FRIEZA]
You're like an eager reader,
jumping ahead to the final page.
[neck cracks]
Sorry to tell you, Goku,
but this story
does not have
a happy ending for you.
I forgot how much
you like to talk.
[FRIEZA]
Here you go.
As a reward for your
foolishly noble honesty.
You may have the privilege
of being crushed
beneath the weight of my
full and unbridled power.
[GOKU chuckles]
[bellows]
[grunts]
Hey Gohan. You know
what's happening up there?
Frieza's finally
showing us his true power.
He's what? So,
all this time he's been
holding something back?
That's right.
Then why didn't
anybody tell me that?
That's all we've been
talking about.
It's not our fault
you don't listen.
[FRIEZA bellows]
[bellows]
[chorical music plays]
Whoa. That is awesome.
What? It can't be!
No. How could Frieza
change that much?
His power.
It's off the scale.
Seems Frieza is more of
a monster now than ever.
This can't really
be happening, can it?
It's all a nightmare right?
Hey! Would you cut that out?!
How many cameras do you have?
This is official business;
don't interfere.
It's sad for your world but
I've got a galaxy to protect!
[hollers]
What camera?
I don't have a camera.
No, no, I'm just
staring at the dirt!
[laughs]
From the shock
in their every gasp,
I can tell our little
crowd of spectators
seems quite astonished
by my new form.
Believe me Frieza, no one's
more surprised than I am.
I know gold's a bit
gauche but I wanted
to ensure you grasped
my new position.
At the very top of the
universe's pecking order.
And now for the sake
of your feeble little mind
we can keep the name
simple as well.
We'll call this Golden Frieza.
It really does
look pretty gold.
Of course, I hope you
realize my appearance
was just a final touch.
This iteration has far more to
it than a shimmering façade.
I figured.
Since you were so cocky.
I thought whatever you were
hiding was gonna be good,
but I wasn't expecting this.
Judging by the amount
of energy I'm feeling,
it would appear that I'm the
winner of this race for power.
Well it ought to be
one heck of a battle,
I'll give you that much.
You'll give me far more,
including your life.
That's just not
gonna happen, Frieza.
But like I said, we'll have
a pretty good fight.
There's really no
point arguing about it.
Our battle will make
the truth painfully clear.
Agreed.
[FRIEZA] Farewell, Goku.
I wish to say that now.
[GOKU]
Why?
[FRIEZA] In terms of
true battle in this form,
this will be my maiden voyage.
I'll be venturing out
into the uncharted frontier.
Despite my best efforts,
I might kill you
sooner than I intend.
So, for the sake of closure
in case that does happen,
I'm bidding you goodbye
from the start.
I've always had a problem
with your arrogance, Frieza.
But as powerful as
you seem to be right now
you might actually be right.
While I'm eager to
test my own new power,
I'll at least admit
I feel nervous, too.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Now die!
[yells]
How's this?
[GOKU groans]
[yells]
[BOTH yell]
[bellows]
[FRIEZA growls]
[yells]
[WHIS] Hello! Bulma?
Can you hear me?
Hello? Whis is that you?
[WHIS] I'm flying through
space as we speak.
I simply must try
that strawberry sundae.
I'll arrive in four minutes
and thirteen seconds.
What? Where have you been?
[BEERUS] Goku didn't even
offer to take us with him.
I could have been
feasting half an hour ago.
He's going to pay for that.
[yawns]
Hello.
Whis! You can't just
stop like that!
I nearly bit my tongue,
you careless twit!
Apologies, Lord Beerus.
But I've encountered
someone unexpected
and I'm quite sure
you'll want to know whom.
Huh?
[BEERUS growls lowly]
[CHAMPA chuckles]
[BEERUS] I've heard
of people getting lost
but you're taking it
to new heights.
Ha! Snoozy Beerus
is awake for once.
Guess there is
such a thing as miracles.
You wanna go?
[grunts]
You're in the
Seventh Universe, Champa.
Surely you know the Destroyer
of the Sixth Universe
has no business being here.
[CHAMPA grunts] Relax, we were
just taking a short cut.
Honestly. Why do you feel the
need to be such a stickler?
[BEERUS] Don't try to fool me
with ridiculous excuses,
I know you too well for that!
And you better not
have come here
to steal our delicious food!
Eh?
[laughs]
As if I would waste my time
on the disgusting concoctions
you call food in this universe!
The cuisines in the Sixth are
the finest in all the realities,
I would never eat here!
Then what's the real
reason you came?
I'm just on a stroll.
I like the view.
Look at your belly, Champa.
You're not
the strolling type.
Ooh?
[BOTH growl]
All right.
You wanna battle then?
[growls]
Well that's fine by me!
[CHAMPA]
Vados! Let him have it!
[VADOS]
Huh?
[BOTH]
Uuuh...
Are you sure it wouldn't
be better to fight him
yourself, my lord?
He's not worth my time.
[BEERUS grunts]
Heh. That should be my line.
Forgive me, Lord Beerus,
but we should be going.
Yes. You're right,
let's move on.
We have business
as well, Lord Champa.
All right, twig,
I'll let you live this time.
I'm the one who's
sparing you, butterball.
[BOTH growl]
Come on, Vados, let's go.
[VADOS]
Yes, my lord.
He's up to something.
[CHAMPA]
I forget, Vados.
How many have we
collected so far?
[VADOS]
We have five.
The last two will be harder.
We'll have to
be more careful now.
I don't want Beerus
and Whis finding out
till we already have them all.
[laughs]
[GOKU yells]
How do you like this?
Your power is pathetic!
Aaah!
[GOKU yells]
Well, it's stopping you!
You're a speed bump.
Nothing more!
Frieza! You just
keep on impressing me!
I never could have imagined
you'd get this strong.
You should have
realized my superiority
while you still
had time to flee!
You could've at least
saved yourself!
[yells]
Guys, take cover!
[JACO yells]
Hang in there, Dad.
If he can't win this,
we're toast.
He's up against
unbelievable power.
Keep on pushing, Goku.
Find a way.
Come on! Why aren't Vegeta
and Goku fighting together?
It doesn't make sense!
[gasps]
[WHIS] I apologize
for keeping you waiting.
[ALL gasp]
Hi, Lord Destroyer, sir.
Glad you're here.
I didn't know
Beerus was coming too!
Yes, well, when you're
offering a strawberry sundae,
what did you expect?
Where is this dessert?
We've come a long way for it.
So, if it's not
as good as it looks,
you'll be paying the price.
It's in Jaco's ship;
I'll get it now.
Just don't blow us up
if it's a little melted.
Oooh...!
Wow, it looks even more
delicious in person!
I know ice cream's
good and all
but how can they eat
when there's a mad tyrant
lighting up the sky?
It would seem
deities operate on
a completely different level
than the rest of us do.
Fantastic!
Cold, sweet, and rich
all at the same time;
it's even better than I hoped!
No doubt we've made the right
decision traveling here, Whis.
Oh, yes,
I couldn't agree more!
[yells]
My brain!
I ate it too fast, but it tastes
so good I don't regret it!
Your dairy confection,
ice cream.
That's the base of
this sundae, is that correct?
Uh, yeah that's right.
[WHIS]
Ooh-ho!
[FRIEZA yells]
Interesting,
these red things look like
the brains of those
giant frogs on Planet Manu.
Yes. They are
quite similar, my lord.
[sniffs]
No, wait!
It's some sort of fruit!
That's even better.
What a strong burst of flavor!
Try it, Whis, it's great!
Yes, I know.
I'm having one now.
This dessert's
simplicity is deceptive.
It's very good, Bulma.
What? Oh, yeah,
glad you like it.
[BEERUS] Speaking of good,
look at Frieza.
He's clearly gotten
stronger, hasn't he?
Yes. It seems Goku's
having some trouble with him.
He's made the most
of those wish orbs.
Guess those years in Earth's
hell motivated him.
Indeed, my lord.
He must have finally
done some training
to achieve that form.
[giggles]
--[FRIEZA yells]
--[GOKU shrieks]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
I hate to admit this,
but I'm having some
real trouble here.
[laughs]
You say that like
it isn't obvious.
There's no way around it,
you really are impressive.
It took me years of blood and
sweat to reach this level,
but you've caught up to me
like it's nothing.
Don't be surprised, Goku.
I commend you for
putting up a good struggle,
but even a monkey with god-like
powers is still a monkey.
And still the inferior race.
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA]
You will die as I did.
I am going to rip you apart
until you're in
far too many pieces to count.
As I told your son,
you won't die alone.
Next, I'll kill Vegeta.
Then all of your other
dear old friends.
I only hope you're
punished as I was,
and you're all hung up
from the same damn tree.
Aah!
What? Beerus is here?
You forgot to say "Lord."
That's not polite, Frieza.
I guess you must be
thinking even more
highly of yourself than usual.
Yes, Lord Beerus. Forgive me.
But why are you here?
I thought
that was obvious.
I came here to eat
this delicious sundae.
But Lord Beerus, I'm on this
planet to claim vengeance,
are you planning to intervene?
Why would I possibly
care about that?
You may do
as you please, Frieza.
Just do it farther away
from my ice cream.
I don't want to confuse your
battle dust for sprinkles.
You seriously didn't
come here to stop me?
Not unless you keep
making me repeat myself.
I take no sides in this battle.
I'm a Destroyer god
not an arbiter.
Wait! You mean you'd
really let him win?
It's not my fight now, is it?
What are you talking about?
If Frieza wins
he'll kill us all!
How could you let that happen?
Don't annoy me.
Relax, as long as
you keep supplying me
with delicacies
like this, I'll at least
make sure
your life is spared.
You just stay close to me.
How's this?
[ROSHI chuckles]
[whispering]
Yoohoo, Bulma.
So, is that actually
Lord Beerus the Destroyer?
As in he actually exists?
Yeah, that's right.
I tried telling you before!
You think you could
get a picture of us?
And make it look like
we're friends.
Again with the camera?
Come on, it's just one shot.
Don't be rude about it.
Earlier you said
it was for some report,
but that wasn't even true, huh?
You want a picture of Beerus
for the same reason
you want pictures of Goku
and Frieza fighting.
For your own stupid photo album!
That is both ridiculous
and offensive!
This is my super-elite
galactic duty!
Oh, okay. Well feel
free to ask him yourself.
I'm sure he'll understand
it's for your job.
Eh?
[BULMA] But don't blame me
if the guy disintegrates you
right out of your boots.
[JACO]
What? Disintegrates?
[laughs nervously]
Never mind. I don't
think the lighting's
very good right now.
All right, Goku.
Shall we recommence
with my revenge?
[GOKU grunts]
[yells]
When I'm done with you there
won't even be ashes to bury.
[yells]
[groans]
[NARRATOR] Not even Goku's
massive boost in power
appears to be enough.
Earth's best hope
hangs by a thread.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super!
I look back
to when I was young
Reminisce on all that I've done
In my hands, I held
The dreams of my childhood,
that now've come to pass
So let's ride upon
the wind and journey to
A world we've never known
(It's a brand new story)
Now, a new chapter starts
Shining Star
In the night be
my compass and guide
Take me to where I belong
The warmth we once shared
Will always be there
Its magic lives on in our hearts
Shining Star
Give me strength
from your light up above
Show me the way to be brave
My hands still hold onto hope
that together we'll manifest
All that we dreamed of
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And Golden Freiza's
power is intense!
He's dishing out attacks
I can't counter!
I hate to say it, but if he
keeps on going like this,
I won't be able to win.
But that's where
the good news comes in,
because this fight
won't keep going like this.
We've got one more surprise!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"A Chance Appears
in a Tight Spot!
Launch a
Counteroffensive, Goku!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?