♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Super,
Frieza was brought back from
Hell with Earth's Dragon Balls,
and he wasted no time plotting
revenge against Goku.
[FRIEZA] If I train in earnest
for the next four months,
my body should be capable of
an enormous leap in strength.
I can easily shatter
through the power ceiling
of that monkey race.
[laughs]
I can't wait to reap the harvest
this training will bring.
[NARRATOR] Those four months
came and went,
as Goku and Vegeta
continued their own training
across the universe,
and had no idea
Frieza was headed for Earth.
With no guaranteed way
of contacting the Saiyans,
Goku's friends gathered
to confront
the Frieza Force on their own.
[ALL gasp]
All right guys, they're here.
But that's massive.
Can this resurrected Frieza
really be that strong?
Damn it.
Hell was a womb,
and the dream of vengeance,
my umbilical.
Now I am reborn
and will suckle
the sweet milk of victory!
[laughs intensely]
[NARRATOR]
The dreaded Frieza Force
descends on Earth. Now!
[NARRATOR]
"The Start of Vengeance!
The Frieza Force's
Malice Strikes Gohan!"
[FRIEZA FORCE yells]
Nothing annoys me more
than uninvited guests.
I told Chiaotzu this fight
was too dangerous for him.
Don't worry about it.
I think it was a good call.
Bulma made me
promise I wouldn't even
mention this to
Goten or Trunks 'cause of
how reckless and
overconfident they are.
They'd prob'ly go
straight for Frieza.
I was hoping Goku and Vegeta
would be here by now.
Well, at least we have Buu.
Wait a second.
Uh, do we have Buu?
Yeah, about that.
When I went to get him,
he was asleep.
We tried everything
to wake him up:
shook him, shoved him,
even tickled him,
but nothing worked.
Eventually I had to give up.
So much for my
"Let Buu Handle It" plan.
That means it's
us five against all them?
Least I had time to get
some senzu beans from Korin.
Hopefully these are enough.
Tell me, Gohan.
Have you been keeping up
with your training?
Because it doesn't look like it.
No, not really.
But don't worry,
I can still go Super Saiyan
when I need to. Probably.
[KRILLIN, ROSHI]
Huh?
Hello, everybody!
What are you doing here?
You see that
alien horde, right?
I haven't heard
from Goku or Vegeta,
so I figured I needed
to warn you.
Since you won't take
cell phones anywhere,
I had to come!
Come on, Jaco!
What are you waiting for?
We clearly need all the help
we can get in this fight!
[JACO] Negative. I just
said I'd drop you off!
That's the deal.
Are you kidding?
I thought you were
the Super Elite
Galactic Patrolman,
a blazing shield of
a zillion stars or whatever!
[JACO] Did you just
slogan-shame me?
Okay fine, I'll take on
some of Frieza's men,
preferably the weaker ones.
Strike a pose!
So who's Mister Spaceman?
Beats me. Bulma seems to have
a lot of weirdo friends,
and I'm not talking about us.
[choral music plays]
[FRIEZA]
Hmmm.
A Galactic Patrolman
and a rag-tag bunch of misfits.
At least there's variety. Ha-ha!
That's Frieza
in the chair, huh?
I can tell he's bad.
He's practically
oozing wickedness
out of his face.
What are you and your army
doing here, Frieza?
[FRIEZA] Is that
not obvious to you?
I'm here for revenge.
I don't see Goku,
is he not here yet?
No, but he's coming soon!
Just you wait!
[FRIEZA]
Hm? Hmmm.
Look, the little bald one.
I have a distinct memory
of killing you on Namek.
That was a great deal of fun.
[hollers]
Hope you aren't
afraid of heights.
[yells]
No, Frieza! Don't do it!
[grunts]
Goku!
[laughs]
It seems the Dragon Balls
can resurrect
the powerful and the pathetic!
Well, I don't care how many
times you come back.
It only affords me the
opportunity to end your life
in even more brutal
and creative ways.
[chuckles]
No need to feel left out,
because if Goku
doesn't join the festivities
I plan to execute all of you.
The sheer grief
that would cause him
would at least
make the trip worthwhile.
I don't know how you talk
such a big game, Frieza.
We've already
kicked your butt twice!
Gohan, you defeated
Cell as a kid!
You should be able to
handle this gas-bag easily.
Well, I could handle
most his men, I guess.
But this is
really serious, Bulma.
Sure, we've gotten stronger.
But then again, so has Frieza.
I can sense it.
I don't know how,
but he's clearly
had a major power-up.
He's like a different fighter.
He's too strong for me now.
Maybe it's
some kind of trick!
That isn't it, trust me.
You're really sure?
I can't win, Bulma!
[BULMA]
Uuh...
[chuckles]
[BULMA laughs nervously]
Uh. Sorry Mister Frieza.
Goku is still on his
way back from Earth
though he really
wants to see you.
You mind waiting
just a bit longer?
I can make you some tea!
I've already spent years
waiting patiently in Hell
for the chance to get
revenge against that Saiyan.
I can wait longer. Why not.
I'll be generous
and give him
ten more seconds to show.
Ten seconds?
Oh come on!
Stingy bastard!
That's one, two...
[neck cracks]
--[ROSHI grunts]
--[TIEN grunts]
[JACO, BULMA holler]
--[FRIEZA FORCE chuckles]
--[SORBET chuckles]
And eight, nine, ten.
All right, soldiers!
Show no mercy!
[FRIEZA FORCE yells]
[grunts]
Okay, let's do this.
Six against a thousand,
that's uh...
That's about
170 space-trolls a piece!
Doesn't have to be pretty,
we just have to hold out
till Goku
and Vegeta get here!
They're weaker than us,
so don't hurt 'em
more than you have to.
You're pretty confident
for a guy who doesn't
remember where
his fighting clothes are.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
Let's go!
Six against a thousand.
I doubt there's been
a more lopsided fight
in history--
our soldiers will
have a field day.
Don't be so sure of that.
Huh?
--[ROSHI grunts]
--[FIGHTER 1, 2, 3 groan]
[ROSHI grunts]
Uh!
Whaaa...?!
It should hardly
surprise you, Sorbet,
this outcome was obvious.
While I've been gone, you've
let the Force deteriorate
into a sideshow of weaklings
unworthy of bearing my name.
[grunts]
Now why does
that one seem familiar?
[gasps]
Ooh.
[FIGHTER 18 groans]
[FIGHTER 19 groans]
[FIGHTER 20, 21 yell]
[FRIEZA FORCE groan]
--[gasps]
--[chuckles]
That's Goku's son;
no question about it.
The one who was only a welp
back on the planet Namek.
It's so touching
to see children grow,
and he's clearly developed
a soft heart like his daddy.
He possesses
considerable strength.
Yet if you watch him
closely, you'll notice
his attacks are
deliberately non-lethal.
Like his father,
he wants to be a noble man
of great moral clarity.
He's so forgiving
and pure of heart
it makes me want to vomit!
Our soldiers aren't
fighting with their heads!
They should use their
numbers and work together
in a coordinated, assault!
If they funnel the six
of them together
they can crush them all! Huh?
[yells]
That may be the most asinine
military advice ever uttered.
Or at least the most boring--
why would we funnel them
together so they can
help each other out?
No, I have a strategy
that's much more fun.
Come on. Just get in there.
They need you.
Krillin! Look out!
He almost had you!
Uh. Yeah. Sorry!
[chuckles]
What's wrong with me,
I can't stop shaking.
I'm all locked up!
[chuckles]
Gentlemen of
the Frieza Force!
[ALL gasp]
I shall award any planet
in the universe
to whichever one of you
can deal a fatal blow
to this miserable
maggot in orange.
--[KRILLIN gasps]
--[FRIEZA chuckles]
He's not serious.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Aw yeah, that planet's mine!
[FRIEZA FORCE yells]
Oh, no! Krillin, run!
Delicious. Like a pack
of dogs picking off the weak.
Damn! Krillin, hang on!
[chuckles]
Time repeats its cycle,
only the details change.
Once again the pitiful
bald one will fall.
And Goku's heart
will be ripped wide open
by the twin talons
of sorrow and rage.
But this time when the
mad monkey comes charging,
I'll be ready for him.
[ALL chuckle]
[distant banging]
Let's take a break.
[VEGETA, GOKU pant]
You collapse on
the ground like a child.
Are you really
too tired to stand?
Don't worry.
I think we got this.
Hm!
It takes a great deal of
patience to teach you two.
Yet despite my efforts
at tutelage, it seems
you learn best by beating
each other silly all day.
I honestly don't know
why you bothered
traveling across
galaxies for this.
You could have
simply stayed home
and brawled in some
back alley or schoolyard,
or wherever it is
you enjoy trading punches.
I should have dropped
you off in a desert
or dried-out riverbed and had
you figure it out yourself.
[slurps]
I guess you have
gotten stronger, Saiyans.
So, you ready
to fight me again?
[GOKU] Uuuh...
I don't think so, Beerus.
We're not close to being
ready for that yet.
Even if we have upped our game
you can still
beat me in your sleep,
and I know because
you actually have!
Your energy is on
a whole other level.
[grunts]
Speaking of dropping
them some place Whis,
why haven't you taken them
to you-know-where?
That is certainly
part of my plan, my lord,
but I hardly think they're
at that stage right now.
Well if the goal is for
them to get stronger quickly
I can't think of a better way.
And besides I'm getting sick of
all the noise they're making,
so that wasn't a suggestion.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Lord Beerus.
What kind of place
are you talking about?
That's odd.
Go on, Whis, let them
see it for themselves.
All right, my lord.
As you command.
[BOTH gasp, yell]
Heh. 'Bout time
I had some peace.
Now I believe we're
well past due for snack time.
[WHIS exhales]
Yes, my lord.
Hopping to it.
Are you ready peewee?
I hope you remembered
to kiss your family goodbye
when you left.
[KRILLIN] What's my problem?
I'm paralyzed!
If I can't get a hold
of myself, I'm done!
You know,
I would offer to save
a lock of your hair
for them to remember you by.
Too bad you don't have any!
[ALL laugh]
Ha!
All right. Let's get to it.
Just go!
Krillin retreat!
Time to claim my prize!
[gasps]
You lucky--
What the--?
[KRILLIN]
Huh?
This is no time
to play with your food!
[grunts]
[pants]
I ducked.
He was so slow
it wasn't even hard.
What are you
surprised for, Krillin?
Cell, Majin Buu, Lord Beerus!
Not to mention Goku and Vegeta!
You've spent years all these
years with a front-row seat
to the greatest displays
of fighting techniques
in the universe.
You've absorbed
more than you know!
These third-rate scrubs
won't be able to touch you
with their attacks, as long as
you keep your eyes open!
[FIGHTER 35]
Shut up, old man!
Do you really think so?
Have a little faith in
yourself and your training!
You're a proud student of the
Turtle School of Martial Arts!
That was a fluke!
I'll destroy you!
[ALL groan]
[KRILLIN exhales]
[BOTH gasp]
[yells]
Just what was the point
of that blast?
It missed us by a mile!
Was he trying to scare us?
[KRILLIN yells]
[FIGHTERS groan]
Nice one, Krillin!
I forgot how fun this was!
[FIGHTER 46, 47, 48 groan]
Hm! That's the spirit, kid,
but I can't let you outdo me!
Here's the signature technique
of the Turtle School
from its creator
and founding member!
Ka...me...ha...me...
Ha!
[FRIEZA FORCE yell]
[exhales]
Uh-oh.
Tri-Beam Ha!
Special Beam Cannon!
[yells]
[FRIEZA FORCE groans, yells]
[gasps]
Oh no,
look over there!
[FIGHTER 49]
Huh?
--[JACO] Bam!
--[BULMA] Ugh!
[FRIEZA FORCE groans]
They're even a greater
humiliation to my name
than I thought they were.
They call themselves
a conquering army
yet they can't
overpower one runt?
Lord Frieza!
Do you know why
I have officers?
So that if any of
my army ever fails me
I know exactly
who to murder first.
Hey! Sisami!
It's about time. I was getting
tired of watching this.
Leave no one standing,
that's an order!
Gladly.
[laughs]
Sisami is the most
powerful soldier
in the modern day Frieza Force!
[TAGOMA huffs]
He's gonna send you all
to the next world!
Before you even
have time to pray!
This one's
definitely fighting
in a higher weight class.
Give me some room;
he's mine.
Sure you don't need
some help with this guy?
Yeah, Piccolo,
I'm not a kid anymore.
Suit yourself.
[bellows]
[yells]
You really think
you can stop me
with your little
amateur fireworks show?
[yells]
That's it! Break his back!
[SISAMI grunts]
My daughter was born this year.
And I want my little girl
to have a happy life
on a peaceful planet.
So, when guys like you come
around threatening that peace,
well, that's a major
problem for me.
I'm the strongest soldier
in a force that's
conquered trillions!
You think I'd cry over one
scrawny wimp and his kid?
Why would I care?!
[GOHAN] So you won't
leave peacefully?
Too bad. Then I
don't have a choice!
[yells]
[SISAMI gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[SORBET gasps]
[FRIEZA]
Huh.
[SISAMI groans] What?
Tagoma, you traitor.
That's not real.
I-It can't be.
Gohan! No!
I got you.
Hey! What the hell
was that for?
I assumed that
would be obvious.
I waited for
the perfect opportunity
and struck a surprise
blow to eliminate
the enemy's best warrior
and guarantee our victory!
And you took
our best warrior too!
Uuugh!
You build an empire on the
bones of your soldiers, sir,
not by crying
each time one falls.
It's no wonder our Force
was weakened under you.
[SORBET]
Who do you think you are,
talking to me like that?
I am your superior!
[TAGOMA grunts]
--[SORBET gasps]
--[FRIEZA] Ooh.
This is bad. His heart's
completely stopped!
He can't even
swallow a senzu bean!
Move!
[gasps, pants]
[KRILLIN] Gohan, here's
a senzu bean. Eat it.
Who is that bastard?
Actually I should thank you,
Commander Sorbet.
You're the one who
convinced Lord Frieza
I should be healed so I could
be his training partner.
[TAGOMA groans]
[FRIEZA]
Good work, Tagoma.
I relish the idea of you
crawling on your belly
for the rest of your life.
But this routine is
far more advantageous.
Not only have I climbed
yet another level,
you're providing me
vital practice for Goku:
how to beat someone to
the very brink of their life,
and yet hold them there
as long as I like.
[TAGOMA gasps]
[FRIEZA] Yes, you're
a veritable treasure.
I've never had a training
partner. It's delightful!
But that's enough for today.
Drag yourself to the
Regeneration Machine
and make sure you're
healed by morning.
For if you're not,
you really will have to die.
[gasps]
[TAGOMA] After countless
regenerations, I understood.
True power is ruthlessness.
True power is terror, absolute!
I'm not the coward
I used to be.
I've become a warrior
worthy of serving Frieza.
And I will prove
how worthy I am!
[laughs intensely]
--[SORBET gasps]
--Frieza, my lord!
If I kill them all myself, will
you make me your commander--
your right hand man?
Not only that,
but you can have
all the planets you want.
Even a minor galaxy
if you desire.
[laughs]
Excellent,
Lord Frieza! Thank you.
Now I'm even more excited
about spilling their blood.
[SORBET grunts]
Unbelievable. It says
he's even stronger
than the old Ginyu Force!
Yes. I remember
seeing them once.
They were legends
back in their day.
But that was
a different age of power,
and I have a feeling
they'd be useless now.
[BOTH gasp]
Did you feel that?
There was a crazy
spike of energy
I don't recognize.
Well, what are you
waiting for? Come on!
There's something
really cool going on
and we're missing it!
We can't just stick around here
kicking a soccer ball, can we?
'Kay! It's in
that direction, right?
I think so!
[GINYU FROG croaks]
I look back
to when I was young
Reminisce on all that I've done
In my hands, I held
The dreams of my childhood,
that now've come to pass
So let's ride upon
the wind and journey to
A world we've never known
(It's a brand new story)
Now, a new chapter starts
Shining Star
In the night be
my compass and guide
Take me to where I belong
The warmth we once shared
Will always be there
Its magic lives on in our hearts
Shining Star
Give me strength
from your light up above
Show me the way to be brave
My hands still hold onto hope
that together we'll manifest
All that we dreamed of
[GOHAN]
Gohan here.
We were making quick work
of Frieza's other soldiers,
but Tagoma's
in a different class.
With my dad and Vegeta
in some strange realm,
we've got to hang in there,
but this guy might even
be stronger than me.
Hold on-- now he's acting
like a different person.
There's something crazy
going on here.
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Change! An Unexpected Return!
His Name Is Ginyu!!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?