♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[BEERUS]
Baseball, you say? Huh.
[WHIS]
Huh.
[CHAMPA]
That's right, brother!
To cultivate friendship
between your universe and mine!
Vados tells me games of sport
are ideal for that.
We can work up
a good sweat, too.
[laughing]
Uuh. And since when do you care
about making friends, huh?
If I may interject, Lord Beerus.
I think promoting inter-universe
camaraderie through sport
is a fantastic idea.
You're endorsing this?
And where exactly
are you suggesting
we play this
"ball of bases," Champa?
Good question, I hadn't
even considered that yet.
Hmm.
Since I'm pushing it,
it's only fair I come to you.
How 'bout Earth?
Fine, just don't expect to win.
I look forward to
the challenge, brother.
[laughing]
What a pushover--
He fell right into my trap!
[VADOS] Easy on the
vulgar chortles, my lord.
How do you expect me not to
laugh at my brother's idiocy?
He has no idea
the whole thing is pretense
to get to this Earth
and gobble up
all their delicious
cuisine! Sucker!
Like I care about being chummy
or getting stupid exercise!
I'll order my pawns to do the
work while I fill up my belly!
You don't think you'll
want to compete, sir?
[CHAMPA]
Eeh?
If your brother's team prevails,
that's not going
to bother you at all?
'Course not! Who cares?!
We'll just say "good game"
and celebrate with a big feast!
It's my most perfect plan yet.
[VADOS]
If you say so, my lord.
Though of course, some moderate
exercise from playing
would make the food
taste even better.
And if Earth cuisine of
the Seventh is as special
as we've been told, my lord,
the enhancement from exercise
would make the meal
a downright
otherworldly experience.
Tell me, Vados. If I did
want to play this baseball,
how exactly does it work?
[VADOS]
Let's start with the basics:
"the ball and the bat."
[NARRATOR]
"A Challenge From Champa!
This Time, a Baseball Game!"
[WHIS sighs]
What an absolutely
beautiful day for a game.
I couldn't agree more.
To make the teams
evenly numbered,
I'll serve as what
they call "the manager."
My not playing gives
their team a massive handicap,
but that's no excuse.
I don't care if this is a
friendly game, you will win.
Understood?
--[YAMCHA, GOKU] You bet!
--[TRUNKS] Uh!
Relax guys,
long as I'm team captain,
you've got nothing
to worry about!
How come Tien and
Chaotzu aren't here?
You did tell 'em
about this, right?
Actually no, I figured
they wouldn't want to.
Besides, a sport this intense
might be too dangerous for them!
[KRILLIN laughing]
Now let's go out there
and work up a sweat!
--[MAGETTA] Vroom. Vroom!
--[ALL] Yeah!
[VEGETA]
Hmph!
All right,
you sporting gentlemen,
can we have both teams
line up at home plate?
Wait a sec. I don't see Hit.
Don't you want him
playing on you team?
Well duh, but being
a covert operative,
he's not easy to track down.
Well that stinks,
I wanted to face him!
And hey, what are Vegeta
and Goten doing on your side?
I thought this was
your universe against ours.
We needed even teams.
Which is why I volunteered.
You think I'd skip
any opportunity
to crush you in something?
Uh...
[chuckles]
And I thought it'd be fun
to play you, Trunks!
You won't get
the best of me, Goten!
Now that we've dispensed
with the obligatory bravado,
let the goodwill game between
the Sixth and Seventh
Universes begin.
"Goodwill" being
the operative word,
which means that
all acts of destruction
are hereby strictly forbidden.
Let's have a friendly game
with good sportsmanship.
No broken bones
or planets, please.
Now let's all bow and say
"good game."
[ALL]
Good game.
Okay, guys, let's go!
I'll lead the way!
Woo!
Come on, let's see
some pep in your step!
Wow, it's been a long time
since I've seen Yamcha
this fired up.
[MARRON]
Yum!
Are you sure about Yamcha
being the captain of the team?
Abso-freakin'-lutely!
Yeah, don't worry.
He may not fight much now,
but he sure can play ball.
Right! Just aim at
my chest, Piccolo,
and try not to add any spin!
Yeah, that's it! Nice throw!
[BULMA giggles]
[BULMA] It's the rest of
the team I'm worried about.
I'm not sure they even know
first from home plate.
How am I supposed to play
with these giant webby things?
[BULMA sighs]
[VIDEL] Yay, Gohan!
You can do it, honey!
[CHICHI]
Make me proud, Goku!
[A18] Krillin, just try
not to screw up.
[BULMA]
And work up an appetite, guys!
We're havin' a huge feast
after the game!
[CHAMPA]
Ooh!
[CHAMPA] The trap
is sprung! Now for that
flavor-enhancing exercise!
[CHAMPA laughing]
Hey, Dad!
I don't care what they
call this type of fight,
I'm always pumped to put
my skills to the test!
Yeah, I know.
So, what are the rules
to this baseball thing,
anyway, Gohan?
I'm not exactly sure, myself.
[GOKU giggles]
That's awesome.
I know this, though.
You're supposed to
take that white ball
and throw it into
this leather glove.
So let's start with that
and we'll learn as we go.
All right, sounds good.
You just leave it to me.
Let's go!
Now the traditional
commencement:
--Play ball!
--[siren wails]
--[CHAMPA grunting]
I call for time!
[BEERUS groans, growls]
[CHAMPA chuckles]
[BEERUS growling]
I don't care if he
is a Destroyer, Goku,
you cannot let my brother
hit one off you!
Throw that ball
at maximum power!
[GOKU]
Maximum? Are you sure?
Do I look unsure?
All right, Beerus,
you're the boss.
[yells]
Ha! You don't scare me.
Do not disappoint me!
Why don't you take the screaming
down a notch, Lord Beerus?
It's a friendly game.
It's just for fun.
A battle is a battle,
and I'll win no matter what!
[GOKU yells]
Whoa, Dad! Easy!
[ALL screaming]
[gasps]
Uuuh...
And that is Strike One!
[CHAMPA growls]
Come on, you call that a strike?
What was left of it
went right down the middle.
I've heard of a breaking ball,
but that ball broke apart.
[YAMCHA]
Ow! Ow, ow! Ow! Aah!
Man! I'm all for Goku
bringing some heat,
but that was like,
thermonuclear!
Uh. I guess I'm out of
practice putting my guard up.
That impact
nearly obliterated me!
Let's give it another shot, huh?
You must be tougher
than you look, Earth boy.
--All right!
--Here we go!
[laughs]
Baseball is awesome!
Goku, this is meant
to be a goodwill game,
and I specifically
warned you that
all acts of destruction
were thus forbidden.
Annihilate anything else
and I'll have no choice
but to eject you from the game.
Aw, that's no fun!
Well, we can't have that!
I'm changing my pitcher!
Hit the showers, Goku!
I'm afraid that's
not allowed, my lord.
What are you talking about?
Barring injury, the starting
pitcher cannot be changed
until he has finished pitching
to at least one batter.
[BEERUS growls]
Fine, from now on
throw it softly, Goku.
You understand me?
Uh. Yeah, sure,
whatever you say.
All righty, nice and soft.
[CHAMPA]
Aaaaauh!
[ALL gasp]
Well, you can't say
he isn't trying.
[ALL snoring]
[VEGETA grunts]
[TRUNKS]
That's a funny-looking fly!
[GOTEN]
Let's catch it!
--[VEGETA] Tch!
--[CABBA] Eeh!
[MAGETTA]
Sigh.
Ker-plunk?
[BUBIBINMAN]
Hm?
[CHAMPA grunting]
Nice try, Saiyan!
[BUBIBINMAN yells]
--[CHAMPA grunts]
--[BUBIBINMAN screaming]
[GOKU]
Aw, man.
He definitely hit that.
Don't worry about it, Dad.
It's a foul ball.
[GOKU] How's it foul?
Does it smell bad?
That means it's Strike Two.
[GOKU]
Seriously? That's dumb.
[BEERUS]
You got lucky, Goku!
Now throw it harder
and strike him out!
[GOKU]
Uuuh. Now harder?
I feel like I'm getting
some mixed signals here.
Okay, I'll split the difference
and throw it just right!
[grunts]
This one's mine!
[GOKU groans]
[CHAMPA]
No doubt about it!
A massive homerun!
Champa is the champ!
[laughs]
Got it!
Yeah! Now that's
an explosive defense!
[chuckles]
I'm a baseball natural!
[CHAMPA]
Uuuuuuh...
Lord Champa's out!
[CHAMPA]
What?!
Nice, Trunks! Very creative!
Yeah, way to use your head!
[CHAMPA grunts]
No, no, no, no, no!
That must be against the rules!
One would assume so,
my lord, but unfortunately
the rule book says nothing about
affecting the ball with energy.
That's quite an oversight.
This is ridiculous!
In your face!
[laughing]
Of course you'd rub it in,
you smug braggart!
[BEERUS]
Na, na, na, na-nuh!
Du-dee, du-dee, doo!
I'm not really sure
what happened with that,
but apparently it was good?
[YAMCHA] Technically. But if
Trunks hadn't stepped in,
that would've been a home run.
So why don't you let me
handle the pitching from here?
Let the Yamcha show you
what it's like
to dominate on the mound.
[chuckles]
My turn!
I'll rip that ball to shreds!
[YAMCHA]
Watch and learn.
This is how it's done.
I like to call this the
Wolf Fang Pitching Fistball!
[YAMCHA grunts]
[BOTAMO yells]
[YAMCHA]
Hya!
[BOTAMO groans]
A swing and a miss!
Strike One!
[YAMCHA chuckles]
That's a brand new
finishing move I invented
just for today, combining
my Wolf Fang Fist
and Spirit Ball for the
ultimate, unhittable strike!
--[MARRON, PAN giggle]
--[VIDEL, CHICHI, BULMA] Ooh!
That's my Yamcha.
He's the greatest!
Yeah, for a washed-up fighter,
that's not bad at all.
You ready for more?
[BOTAMO grunts]
[WHIS]
Strike Two!
[YAMCHA grunts]
[BOTAMO groans]
Strike Three!
You are outta here!
Wow, he got him out fast.
Two down and one to go.
It's an honor
to have this "at bat."
[CABBA]
Watch closely, master.
I'm going to hit this and prove
I'm worthy of your teaching.
[YAMCHA]
Hmm.
[chuckles]
[CABBA grunting]
That's three strikes
and three outs!
The top of the
first inning is over!
[YAMCHA] Oh yeah!
Nobody escapes the wolf!
[PUAR]
You're cooler than cool, Yamcha!
[BEERUS] Yes, far less
worthless than I thought.
[VIDEL]
That was great!
[A18] I had no idea
he was good at something.
Yeah, my opinion of Yamcha
is definitely improving.
[chuckles]
Aw come on, guys.
It wasn't that cool. Stop it!
I'm kidding it was way cool,
so keep the cheers comin'.
[laughing]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[WHIS]
Bottom of the first inning!
Play ball!
I think I've got this
little game figured out.
[chuckles]
Get ready. It's gonna
be coming back hot.
[VEGETA]
Hmph!
[BULMA]
Good luck to both of you!
Just have fun out there, okay?
[giggles]
[YAMCHA chuckles]
You can't beat me at this.
It's a shame you believe that.
[VEGETA grunts]
[YAMCHA groaning]
[WHIS] Ooh. He's hit
by a pitch-- dead ball!
Yamcha, oh no!
Whoa, did you just
peg him on purpose?
Of course, 'cause unlike
the rest of you
I'm not messing around!
You just have to take out
their team to win, right?
Oh, good point. Leave it to
Vegeta to cut to the chase!
[WHIS] You're clearly missing
the objective, Vegeta.
Next time you hit a batter,
I will have to
eject you from the game.
[VEGETA]
What?
[BOTH] You're not
allowed to hit people?
[BOTH sigh]
What sort of a contest makes
hitting against the rules?
[YAMCHA] If you don't see
the beauty of baseball,
that's your loss, Vegeta.
And all the more reason
for me to win.
[GOKU]
Okay, time to give this a shot.
All right, there's no one out,
with a runner on first.
Are you ready to lose, Kakarot?
We'll see about that, Vegeta!
[yells]
Perfect, I'm going all out, too!
[VEGETA chuckles]
Just try to hit this!
Don't you dare miss, Goku!
Humiliate him, Vegeta!
[yells]
[grunting]
[yelling]
What's this?
Does he honestly believe
I'm going to let him
overpower my best pitch?
[yells]
[GOKU grunting]
Whoa, is he allowed
to do that, Whis?
So you're still
not ready to give up?
[yells]
Then let's see if you can
handle this. Final...
Wait a second, he's distracted.
It's the perfect time to steal!
--Steal what?
--You lost focus.
I've got you now, Vegeta!
Oh, son of a bi--!
[BOTAMO grunts]
And that's an out!
[YAMCHA hollers]
No you don't!
[GOTEN]
Uuh!
Ha-ha, lucky me!
You'll never make it, go back!
Cabba, get it to me!
[CABBA]
Incoming!
[YAMCHA, CHAMPA panting]
[yelling]
[YAMCHA groaning]
Yamcha, oh my gosh!
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH]
You're out!
[VADOS] Lord Champa. That counts
as obstructing the runner.
And that means he is
safe at second base.
[BOTH]
Are you kidding me?
[BEERUS] They maliciously
attacked my player
on the basepath, ump.
Don't you think that's
grounds to eject them both?
I should eject you
off this world!
Do mind your temper, my lord.
Remember you only have
to last until dinner.
[CHAMPA]
Tch!
Please be okay, Yamcha.
I'm lost without you!
Change!
Hey Puar, was I asleep?
I just had the craziest
baseball dream.
[PUAR] Yamcha, thank goodness!
I was so scared!
[PICCOLO] Great. Turns out
most of us have no idea
how baseball works.
Oh. Wait a minute. Gohan!
Uh, yeah? What's up, Piccolo?
You got any advice?
You didn't make the trip to
the Tournament of Destroyers
and you probably couldn't tell
just by looking at him.
You see that player over there
who looks like a robot?
That's Magetta,
and he can't fly.
If you hit one over his head,
there's a good chance
it'll get past him,
and we can score.
I got it, thanks, Piccolo.
Okay, I'm ready!
Yeah, yeah, lets do it.
[YAMCHA]
What am I even doing here?
I'm totally out of my league!
At this rate, I'll be lucky
to walk off the field alive.
Come on, Yamcha!
Keep my head in the game.
We are going to win this.
[grunts]
Excellent hit, Gohan!
[MAGETTA]
Vrrroom, vrrrroom!
[BOTAMO]
Magetta!
[MAGETTA]
Ka-dunk! Boom!
What? A combo technique?
They're a better team
than I thought.
[YAMCHA]
I can still make it!
[CABBA]
He tagged up! Pick him off!
[CHAMPA]
Let me! Gotchya!
--[thwack]
--[YAMCHA groans]
No! Poor Yamcha, not again!
And that's what
you get for trying
to compete with me, Earthling.
Safe!
[CHAMPA]
What?!
My lord, you must
tag runners with the ball
in your hand or glove--
Throwing the ball at him
does not count as an out.
[CHAMPA] But Cabba
told me to pick him off!
Yes, but I'm afraid
you didn't understand
the meaning of the phrase, sir.
[CHAMPA growls]
[YAMCHA]
I will make it home.
Oh, I'm not sure about that,
unless you're carried
there on a stretcher.
But of course, this is
just the sort of player
you get with a lousy manager.
Did you dare just call me lousy?
If you're fragile team
can't handle playing against
the big boys, then you
should forfeit. And we'll win!
And your savage players
would only win by cheating!
You're the savage, brother!
I'm sophistication personified!
[CHAMPA] In what way?
You're a mayhem-loving vandal!
[BEERUS]
No I'm not! You are!
--[CHAMPA] No, you are!
--[BEERUS] You are!
[CHAMPA growls]
No, you are!
[CHAMPA]
No, you definitely are!
[CHICHI]
Everybody run!
[BULMA] Hey you guys,
take cover over here!
Hold on, didn't somebody
tell me once
that if Destroyers
start fighting each other,
it could rip a whole
universe apart at the seams?
Then we probably shouldn't
have front row seats!
No! You are, infinity!
[yells]
You dare strike me, you weenie?
[BOTH grunting]
That does it!
Oh, I agree!
[yells]
[ALL screaming]
[MAGETTA]
Danger! Danger!
Guys, hold on to me.
I'm gonna use
Instant Transmission, okay.
I said hold on, not squeeze!
[CHAMPA grunts]
You're going down!
--No, you are!
--[CHAMPA] You are!
[BOTH yell]
[VADOS, WHIS]
That's enough, my lord.
Have you forgotten it's
one of the greatest taboos
of the cosmos for Destroyers
to fight each other?
Are you trying to obliterate
this whole universe?
[CHAMPA, BEERUS groan]
You've completely
ignored our warning
that acts of destruction
are forbidden.
By our authority as umpires,
we hereby rule
you're in gross violation
and declare this game over.
Are you saying after all
that fuss it ends in a tie?
Actually, no, the
Seventh Universe team wins,
one run to nothing.
What, but how?
See for yourself, Lord Champa.
Look down at home plate.
[CHAMPA]
Huh?
Heck of a play!
Well done, Yamcha!
[KRILLIN] He stole home
when no one was looking!
Hey, the way he's lying in that
crater kinda rings a bell.
Yeah, a very painful bell.
Don't remind me.
Well, I'm glad we won, you guys.
But I think I just gave new
meaning to the term "sacrifice."
[ALL]
Yamcha!
[cheering, laughing]
[CHAMPA grunting]
[ALL grunting]
Keep at it, fighters!
They will not
defeat us next time!
--[BOTAMO] Sir, yes sir!
--[MAGETTA, CABBA] Sir!
My lord got so wrapped up
in the competition
he didn't even remember
about the meal.
[laughs]
♪ Closing Song ♪
1, 2, 3, I'm hungry
Nothin' but fried rice fantasies
I got a passion for the dish
Nothin' compares to what it is
I don't get my fill
I'm like a monster
Those ingredients
No one could possibly resist
They got me so bewitched
Make it spicy and I can't say no
Seasoning is everything,
I think so
Bon Appetit
I'll burn the world
straight to the ground
If I can't have
that greasy mound
My hanger's not to be ignored!
1, 2, 3, I'm hungry
Nothin' but fried rice fantasies
I want fried rice,
I'm so hungryyyyyy-yeah!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And I hate to break it
to you guys,
but this next adventure
might end with me dead.
There's an awesome fighter
who's out to get me,
and apparently he's lurking
somewhere close by.
Even though I can't sense his
energy, he's definitely near.
I've got a ton
of respect for him,
but I hate this hide and seek!
Just come out and face me!
I'm always up for a fight!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Goku Dies! An Assassination
That Must Be Executed."
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?