♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Goku joined Vegeta
on Beerus' world.
And after doing surprisingly
dangerous housework,
the two Saiyans endured
a grueling training regimen,
in the hopes it would lead to
a whole new level of power.
While far away
in another star system,
the remnants
of a once-mighty army
seemed to be hatching
plans for a comeback.
And the appearance of
two mysterious figures
signaled a serious threat
for the universe.
[CHAMPA]
Yes, this must be it.
This time I'm sure. Go on.
[CHAMPA sighs]
Guess I was wrong.
[NARRATOR]
The adventures continue now!
"Despair Redux!
The Return of the
Evil Emperor, Frieza!"
[screeches]
[BATS screech]
All right, everyone.
Time to start the day!
[cheerful music plays]
[yawns]
[BOTH giggle]
[FAIRIES, ANIMALS laugh]
[BOTH laugh]
[music and laughter continue]
[snarls]
--[FAIRIES laughing]
--[FREIZA grunting]
[ALL laugh]
[snarls]
Good morning, Pouty-Pants!
--Try to smile!
--I bet you'll like it!
[PURPLE FAIRY] Don't you
want to feel warm and fuzzy?
[FAIRY C]
Come on, smile!
[FAIRY A] Let's hug
and do the happy dance!
Damn you!
Shut your stupid fairy faces!
[alarms blare]
[FRIEZA FORCE gasps]
Status report!
[STAFF A]
Yes, sir. I'm afraid
the first and second
battalions were both wiped out
before we could execute
the command to retreat,
and half of the third
battalion is currently
missing in action, commander.
What? You're telling me
that we've lost
sixty percent of our soldiers?
We can't afford any more losses,
or we won't even be able to call
ourselves a fighting force.
What should we do, sir?
[SORBET] We are the
dying embers of an empire.
To survive,
there's only one option.
We have to bring
Lord Frieza back to life.
[ALL gasp]
What are you saying, sir?
Bring him back?
[SORBET] Have you
tracked down the remaining
Namekian survivors yet?
[STAFF A] No, sir. Our drones
still can't find them.
[SORBET]
Hmm.
--[TAGOMA] Commander Sorbet.
--[SORBET] Hmm?
Even if we were able
to bring Lord Frieza
back to life, there's
no way we could recover.
It's impossible.
[SORBET] Tagoma, you clearly
don't understand Frieza's power.
[exhales]
[SORBET] Our exalted leader
controlled the majority
of the civilized universe.
His rule was absolute.
Countless galaxies
trembled at his name!
Why? Because he had no mercy.
He knew that fear was power.
Get ready! Nothing perks up
a lack-luster day
like a good show!
What beautiful fireworks.
I could do this a million times
and it would never get old!
[SORBET] If Lord Frieza returns,
that fear will spread
like a virus. Our army
will reign once again!
This model simulates
Frieza's power,
and the likely response
from all known systems.
Seventy percent of
the universe could be ours.
[TAGOMA] There are
so many factors, sir.
Is this kind of
prediction possible?
Tell me, Tagoma,
who was it who kept
the Frieza Force from crumbling
after Frieza's demise
and sustained it
all these years?
You did, Commander Sorbet!
You're damn right it was me!
If not for my
intelligence and tactics
none of us would be here today!
There are no flaws
in my calculations;
you can be sure of that.
When we do bring Frieza back,
he'll be stunned
by what I've accomplished.
All right.
Chart a course for Earth.
What?
But sir. Don't you think
Planet Earth is too dangerous?
I know they
have Dragon Balls
and that Earth woman
knows how to find them,
but she's in league with that
Saiyan who defeated Frieza!
What's wrong with you?
You think we're
in a position right now
where we can hang back
like frightened children?
If we can't
find the Namekians,
then what else can we do?
Earth is our only option
and a risk we have to take!
Show the feed
from the spy drone!
Evidently that woman
isn't the only one
capable of finding
the Dragon Balls.
Tagoma! The two of us
are going to Earth.
--Sir!
--Commander!
May I have permission
to join you, sir?
Denied. It seems the
Earth Saiyans can detect
substantial power levels
without using a Scouter.
Obviously, more troops means a
bigger risk of being noticed.
You'll run the ship
while we're gone, Sisami.
Understood. Please forgive me
for speaking out of turn.
If that's the case, commander,
shouldn't Sasimi and I
be the ones to go
so you can stay onboard?
It's our job to
keep you safe, after all.
You honestly expect me
to stay up here?
I will not leave the
resurrection of Lord Frieza
to underlings!
I'll bring him back myself.
[BOTH bellow]
[VEGETA, GOKU groan]
[GOKU yells]
[yells]
Okay, boys. I think
we're done for now.
[BOTH pant]
You two have
definitely improved
since our last
sparring session--
which counts for
something I suppose.
But you're still woefully
lacking in speed.
Look, I even had time
to sign both of your tops.
Whoa, no way!
When did you do that?
You really are amazing, Whis!
[VEGETA grunts]
[WHIS] Let's focus
first on you, Vegeta.
[VEGETA]
Yeah, what about me?
You're clearly
an extraordinary fighter
in your own right.
Yet despite your hard work,
you're always one step
behind Goku, aren't you?
And you just
had to bring that up?
[WHIS] Do you know
why you're Goku's lesser?
Please.
Teach me, oh wise one!
You walk through life
with a chip on your shoulder
and your nerves wound too tight.
This tension
makes it hard for you
to move and fight
at your full potential.
So a key lesson for you
is to learn to relax
and get rest when
you have the opportunity.
The way Goku does.
You gotta admit,
he has a point.
I do love me a good nap!
Tch!
But you have problems, too.
[GOKU]
Huh?
[groans]
Being too relaxed can also
be a significant weakness.
And don't even get me
started on your issues
with overconfidence
during a fight, Goku.
No matter how strong
you are physically,
if you let your focus waver,
you're set up to fail.
I've already noticed
quite a few times
when you're so sure
of yourself that you
completely let your
guard down in battle.
[laughs]
He's got that one right.
Maybe so, but I still think
that was a cheap shot.
[WHIS]
Hm.
Well, we had better pick up
the pace of your training.
[gasps]
Uh...
[clears throat]
Peek-a-boo!
--[PAN giggles]
--[PICCOLO chuckles]
[PICCOLO]
Uh, uh... Peek-a-boo!
[PAN laughs]
[PICCOLO]
Peek-a-boo, peek-a-boo!
[babbles]
[PAN laughs]
[PICCOLO chuckles]
--[GOHAN] Hey, Piccolo.
--Aah!
Sorry, we didn't mean
to get back home so late.
[PICCOLO] Oh, Gohan. I hardly
even noticed you were gone.
--[PAN laughs]
--[VIDEL] Hi, pumpkin!
Can you say "thank you"
to your Uncle Piccolo
for babysitting?
He's just the sweetest guy
in the world, isn't he?
[PAN laughs]
[gasps]
Hey you look worried,
Piccolo. What's wrong?
You clearly need to
pay better attention, Gohan.
I'm sensing bad energy
in that direction.
Oh yeah, now I feel it.
So, what do you think?
I don't know.
[PILAF] We're almost there,
I'm sure of it.
Should be just up ahead.
Look, there it is!
[MAI, SHOU holler]
It's the One-Star!
Do you realize what
this means, you guys?
Yeah! We have the full set!
[SHOU]
We've finally done it, sire!
We've found all seven!
[MAI] All the terrible
stuff we've been through.
For once it was
actually worth it!
There were some unpleasant
moments, weren't there.
We braved stormy seas!
Stared at the sun!
Battled beasts
with too many teeth!
And now all the benefits
of absolute power
will be ours to enjoy!
[chuckles]
Soon the entire world
will bow before
the great and well-fed
Emperor Pilaf!
[SORBET]
Don't be so sure of that.
You're giving those
Dragon Balls to me.
[PILAF]
What? Who are these bozos?
There's no way
we're giving these up!
You ever heard of
finders keepers?
[screams]
[MAI, SHOU whimper]
You're going to be working
for a true emperor now.
[ALL]
What? Emperor who?
[chuckles]
[PILAF]
Oooh...
And after all the hard work
we did to find them, too.
Mmm! I just can't do it!
[BOTH]
Huh?
We're the ones who earned
those wishes. It's so unfair!
Yeah, we know that, Mai,
but we don't have a choice!
They're too strong!
My sword definitely
can't beat space-lasers!
[SORBET]
What's going on?
I told you no delays!
[MAI, PILAF, SHOU]
Sorry!
[PILAF groans]
[MAI whimpers]
[SHOU whimpers]
[PILAF grunts]
Eternal Dragon Shenron!
By your name, I summon you!
Now let's do this!
[rumbling thunder]
Ooh!
[ALL holler]
What's going on?
Why is the sky so dark?
This can only be one thing.
It's Shenron.
[roars]
He's bigger than I thought!
I am the dragon Shenron.
I shall grant you
any wish. Now speak!
So uh, you're not the
kind of guy who's gonna
kill us after this, right?
No. It's in our best
interest to keep you alive
since there's a chance we'll
have use for you later.
[MAI, PILAF, SHOU]
Thank you, sir!
Now Commander!
This is our only chance!
[SORBET mumbles]
You can do this.
All right.
Let's just hope this works.
I wish for Frieza!
Bring him back to life!
Who's this Frieza guy?
Are you deaf?
You told us we could
wish for anything!
Of course, it can be done.
But his body was cut
to pieces and obliterated
many years ago,
and I cannot restore it.
Hey, Frieza!
[yells]
--[FRIEZA groans]
--[TRUNKS yells]
There is little point
in returning his soul
to that form.
What? He'd be in pieces?
Great, I hadn't even
considered that.
--[TAGOMA] But think about it.
--[SORBET] Hm?
With the new regeneration
machines we use
for our troops, we should
still be able to repair him,
even if the damage
is quite severe.
Of course. That should work.
Especially with
Lord Frieza's resiliency.
Hey! I don't care
what shape he's in,
just bring him
back like I said!
It's unwise to
be rude to a dragon.
[SORBET grunts]
Sorry...
Pretty please
bring Frieza back to life?
That better?
A foolish choice,
but very well.
[yells]
[clanging, squelching]
Granted. Now speak
your remaining two wishes.
[SORBET] What? I didn't
know I'd get three!
Indeed. When Earth's
guardian was replaced,
my powers were altered as well.
Today I have the ability
to grant you three.
But there are limits.
If the wish
requires great power,
such as bringing back
a planet's population,
that would
consume two wishes.
So choose wisely.
Hey. I didn't know that!
What else could I
wish for then?
I could have King Cold
brought back too
and then we'd
really be unstoppable.
What about a more
powerful fleet, sir?
I want a million zeni
in large bills!
And I want the most
delicious ice cream
in the whole world!
--[SORBET grunts]
--[MAI, SHOU whimper]
All right, I got it!
[gasps]
Yay! I got mine, too!
[SHENRON]
No extra charge for the ice.
Your wishes have been fulfilled.
I bid you farewell.
[grunts]
You'll pay for that!
[MAI, SHOU, PILAF shriek]
I was going to keep you
around to search for
the Dragon Balls again,
but after that fiasco...
--[TAGOMA] Commander, wait!
--[SORBET] Huh?
There's no time for that.
The Saiyans may know
we're here.
We have to move quickly!
--[pattering]
--[SORBET] Hm?
Look at him go.
This is Lord Frieza, after all.
And with his strength
and our tech,
I'm positive we can
put him back in one piece!
[ALL]
Uuh...
[ALL shriek]
All right, let's move out.
[PILAF, MAI, SHOU]
Excuse us.
[SORBET]
What do you want?
[PILAF] I think
you missed a piece.
[GINYU FROG groans]
[croaks]
[SORBET] Hmm.
Good work, Earthlings.
We'll remember you when
we come back to this planet.
But next time
we'll have Lord Frieza
and our soldiers, too.
I'm still confused.
Who's Frieza, and why doesn't
he come pre-assembled?
How should I know?
Whoever he is,
it doesn't sound like
it's very good for the earth.
I know!
We'll build a spaceship
to escape to another planet
and build my empire there!
Sire, I don't think
high-tech spaceship building
is our specialty.
[PILAF] I know we can
figure out something
with that million zeni
you got us!
Way to think on your
feet there, Shou!
But sir!
He should have asked for
a hundred million zeni.
That would've been
a hundred times better!
And this coming
from the mastermind
who wished for some ice cream?
At least my wish
isn't gonna melt!
I couldn't help it.
You know how long it's been
since I've had some?
It's inhumane!
[PILAF]
Would you morons shut up?
I just realized
something terrible.
I'm the only one
who didn't get his own wish.
That's okay, sire.
With all this money you can
pay to eat anything you want,
and that's kinda like
making a wish, right?
Yeah, sir, and don't
forget you're gonna have
the world's
best ice cream, too!
You're right. That is good!
Okay, soldiers!
First we'll make ourselves
totally sick on ice cream
and then we'll rally
--and hit a buffet!
--[SHOU, MAI] Right!
[PILAF] So, what are
you guys binging on?
[SHOU]
I don't know!
[PILAF] 'Cause I'm going
Mongolian barbecue!
--[MAI] Ooh, yeah!
--[SHOU] Good idea!
It's gone now. I wonder
what that was about.
I think we're in trouble.
[PAN laughs]
[TAGOMA] Our scanners aren't
picking up anything, commander.
Looks like we got away before
the Saiyans could react.
[SORBET] See, you were
fussing over nothing.
I told you it was
a brilliant plan.
To be honest,
I still have some concerns.
About what?
I still question if
reviving Lord Frieza
is the best way to return our
force to its former glory.
What?! Augh!
You're seriously
still doubting that?
Just think about
what happened!
The moment that
word spread that Frieza
and his top lieutenants
had been wiped out,
the universe stopped
taking us seriously!
That's when the first
planets rebelled!
And that's when
the struggles for power
among our own
leadership started, too.
Maybe it's too hard for me
to imagine his true power.
I barely saw Frieza back then
and only from afar.
He always seemed so small
and insignificant.
Hmm. I only met him
a few times myself,
but trust me it was enough.
I've never encountered
a more terrifying presence.
Well, I hope you're right.
If he's not
as strong as you say,
we'll be bringing back
an old dictator
just to lead us all to our doom.
[SORBET growls lowly]
[SISAMI]
Let me guess, Tagoma!
Are you still whining about all
the things you're scared of?
As if what our
lord needs to see
when he wakes
is a spineless officer!
I'm just smart.
[SORBET] You'll all stop your
sniping when Frieza returns.
[beeping]
Huh?
At last!
Lord Frieza is back!
[beeping continues]
[groans]
[FRIEZA FORCE gasps]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[intense choral music plays]
--Hm.
--What's wrong, Kakarot?
[GOKU]
I'm not sure yet.
I just got a really
nasty feeling.
[VEGETA]
You just wanna slack off
so you're imagining things.
I don't think so,
but I hope you're right.
[ALL gasp]
[FRIEZA]
Mmm.
[neck cracks]
[retches]
It's been a long time
since I've felt like this.
It's a rare feat to
catch me by surprise. Heh.
I've actually been brought
back to the living world.
[NARRATOR] Frieza, once feared
throughout the universe
as the Evil Emperor,
has come back to life.
Much has changed
since the end of his reign,
but one thing is certain:
he will be seeking revenge.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super!
[chuckles intensely]
I look back
to when I was young
Reminisce on all that I've done
In my hands, I held
The dreams of my childhood,
that now've come to pass
So let's ride upon
the wind and journey to
A world we've never known
(It's a brand new story)
Now, a new chapter starts
Shining Star
In the night be
my compass and guide
Take me to where I belong
The warmth we once shared
Will always be there
Its magic lives on in our hearts
Shining Star
Give me strength
from your light up above
Show me the way to be brave
My hands still hold onto hope
that together we'll manifest
All that we dreamed of
[GOTEN]
Hi! Goten here!
And a lot of cool stuff
is starting to happen!
Like a spaceship lands on Earth
with an alien inside!
He wants to see Bulma, but first
I've got see his spacesuit!
Plus, my dad and
Vegeta are fighting,
and you never want to miss that!
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"A Warning from Jaco!
Frieza and 1,000
Soldiers Close In."
[GOTEN] Be there! Or
you're gonna be sad, okay?