♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
thanks to Gohan's
boost of energy,
Goku locked on and transported
himself and Vegeta to Earth
so they could face
the resurrected Frieza.
Here at last, Goku.
I've been waiting
a long time for this.
Finally I can claim the revenge
I've dreamed of
for all these years.
[bellows]
[NARRATOR] Their first
battle brought about
the age of the Super Saiyan,
and now Goku isn't even
sure he needs that power.
Will this rematch be
the dawn of something new?
Very well. The black-haired
Goku's pelt will look
just as good on my wall.
[NARRATOR]
Their fight begins, now!
"Clash! Frieza vs. Goku--
This Is the Result
of My Training!"
[chuckles]
[FRIEZA grunts]
♪
[BOTH chuckle]
[BOTH grunt]
[grunts]
[yells]
They've both got
incredible energy.
[KRILLIN] To be honest
it's freaking me out.
This isn't like
the fight with Beerus;
you can feel
the hate in the air.
So, that's your friend
I've heard about;
the one Frieza lost to
on Planet Namek, right?
You got it.
And that guy's your husband?
[BULMA]
'Fraid so. That's my Vegeta.
You mean the
infamous Saiyan Prince?
That Vegeta?
Yup.
Hey! Don't make me
tie you down!
[JACO] Let go of me!
This is cruelty to aliens!
You seriously
want to run away?
Yeah, of course I want to run;
aren't you paying attention?
These guys are giants and
we're gonna get squashed!
Please don't make me
stay down here!
But you have to!
Isn't protecting this planet
part of your job description?
Please, Princess Bulma Vegeta--
or whatever you go by--
let me go!
Hey Goten,
are you feeling that?
[GOTEN] Yeah.
The energy's crazy huge!
I know! I want to
watch 'em fight so bad!
Mhm. But we have to
do this mission.
[TRUNKS]
So, let's do it!
We'll just finish
as fast as we can!
We'll dash to the Lookout
and talk to Dende
and then fly back
to the fight at hyper-speed!
Then we can
still catch the best part!
Let's move!
[DENDE]
Oh, Piccolo.
Goku and Vegeta, you have to
win this fight, please.
You have to save the earth
so Piccolo's death
wasn't for nothing!
[GOKU, FRIEZA grunting]
[yells]
[GOKU yells]
Despite my endless well
of hatred for you,
I suppose that
I am grateful in a way.
Grateful of me?
Come on, are you just
trying to make me sick?
[FRIEZA]
No, it's true.
If not for my desperate
need to destroy you,
I never would have dreamed of
exerting myself as I have.
I'm a different person now.
You've opened my eyes
to what's possible.
[GOKU grunts]
But the blade cuts both ways.
While such effort
has strengthened my body
it's inflicted indescribable
damage to my pride.
Effort is a humiliation!
No superior being should have
to toil and sweat and stink
like some lowly beast!
Training is meant for the
monkey, and not for the master!
How long do I
have to beg, Bulma?
Forget it, you're not leaving!
--Wait a second.
--[JACO] Huh?
[BULMA]
I just noticed something.
You and Frieza
sort of look alike.
[gasps]
Oh yeah, I kinda see it.
He couldn't be on
Frieza's side, could he?
[gasps]
Why is everyone here crazy?
[FRIEZA]
I hate you.
Your voice, your face,
everything about you!
Why don't we stop talking
and start fighting, Frieza.
[FRIEZA grunts, chuckles]
You're right, Goku.
I've milked this long enough.
I present without further ado
the punishment you deserve.
[chuckles]
We'll start with anguish.
Your priceless mental suffering
when I kill your puny friend!
--[GOKU] Krillin!
--Uuuh!
Aaah!
Are you okay?
Yeah, thanks, Goku.
That was close.
Look out!
[GOKU groans]
Very well then;
we can focus on you!
[yells]
I can't even
follow their movements.
No way. They're too fast
for you, too?
Yeah.
Dash left!
Jump! Spinning right!
Uppercut!
High kick! Quick knee!
Yes! He got him!
Oh, no! I spoke too soon.
You can watch at that speed?
Well at least
your eyes are good.
Don't insult me.
Think quickly.
Aah!
Bulma!
[VEGETA]
Yaaah!
[yells]
Frieza!
--[GOKU hollers]
--[FRIEZA laughs]
Listen to me.
I'm the one you're here for.
So, you fight me
and keep the others
out of it, understand?
[laughs]
You're living
a fairytale, Goku.
I will do whatever is
required to get my revenge
and cause you maximum torment.
If you want to
talk about revenge
I've got my own to take.
[laughs]
You're living in a deluded
fairytale world, Goku.
I will do whatever is
necessary to get my revenge
and cause you maximum suffering.
And then you flail about
with no strategy.
You'll die for nothing just
like the pathetic Namekian!
[grunts]
[GOKU] Usually I feel excited
when I get to fight someone
as strong as you are.
But what I'm feeling right now
is entirely different.
Well, of course it is, Goku,
because I'm not
just some fighter.
I'm the total definition
of exceptional.
No, you're the definition
of evil, Frieza,
and you're right, anger takes
over me when I fight you.
Because I'm disgusted
at what you are!
[FRIEZA] You can have
all the anger you want.
Bathe in it. All the
revulsion and animosity
your tiny brain
is capable of are nothing
compared to what I feel for you.
You cannot know my rage!
[yells]
[BOTH yell]
[BULMA, JACO gasp]
[JACO]
My spaceship!
[coughs]
[gasps]
Oh no. My favorite picture.
This is the real tragedy.
I guess all that effort
you put into training
was worth it, huh?
What?
I never would have
believed somebody could
get this much stronger
in just a few months!
You said I filled you with rage
and yet you're complimenting me?
It's exactly this
sort of absurd chatter
that makes me hate you so!
Going after my eyes,
Frieza, really?
[FRIEZA] Of course.
I told you, this isn't
some game where we play nice.
This is revenge,
you reeking ape!
Tch! What are those
imbeciles doing?
How long are they
going to warm up?
[FRIEZA] While we're
drudging up past remarks,
I couldn't help
but eavesdrop on your
father-son moment earlier.
You told him
the Namekian Dragon Balls
could be used to bring your
green friend back to life.
Yeah. So, what if I did?
I simply want you
to know that won't
be an option, and I'll
make sure of it myself.
After I'm done with you,
I'm not only going to annihilate
this planet's Dragon Balls
but the Namekians'
enchanted orbs as well.
No one's coming back.
Ha! Just when I think
you can't get more evil
you go and surprise me again.
[grunts]
But it doesn't matter.
I'll never let that happen!
You're going
to need more power.
[FRIEZA] Funny. That's exactly
what I was about to tell you!
--[GOKU hollers]
--[FRIEZA] Huh?
[groans]
Huh?
[grunts]
Come on, Vegeta!
What was that?
[FRIEZA]
Hmm?
Damn you, clown!
Enough already!
Sorry, but enough
of what, already?
[VEGETA yells]
Stop it!
Why are you fighting me?
Shut up! Like you don't know!
[chuckles]
Well, how flattering.
It seems no matter
how far a pet strays
he never forgets
who holds the leash.
What's Vegeta up to?
If that's a strategy
it's way too clever for me.
I have no idea.
What the hell is he thinking?
We're trying to
stop a damn invasion!
Did he hit his head
too many times while training
and turn his brain into mush?
I think his brain's
been mush for a while now.
Wait, is it possible?
[TIEN] He served
Frieza a long time.
We can't know
how that changed him.
Now his old master's back,
stronger than ever.
Could he have gone back
to Frieza's side?
That's my husband
we're talking about!
There's no way
he would ever betray us!
[KRILLIN]
I'm with Bulma.
Vegeta would never
turn against his family.
He's one of us now.
[TIEN] Well, I sure
hope you're right.
[GOKU gasps]
Come on. What's wrong
with you? Talk to me!
[FRIEZA]
Yes, Vegeta, talk.
We're all dying to know
what's going through
that head of yours.
You always had
a pragmatic streak.
Did you realize
you're on the losing side
and want to return
to your old master?
Congratulations on
coming back to life, Frieza.
That couldn't
have been easy. Bravo!
[claps]
You may hold
a smattering of applause,
although I do deserve it.
[clapping echoes]
[snarls]
What is this? Now Vegeta
wants my job, too?
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Hm?
[VEGETA chuckles]
I'm all for you showing
respect, Saiyan Prince.
But how long are you
going to keep that up;
it's starting to bother me!
You're offending my ears.
Knock it off!
[VEGETA] Your mere existence
offends me, Frieza.
Why don't you quit that?
What did you say to me?
You come to my home
whining about
a few months of effort.
And have the nerve
to talk of your revenge?
You should keep your mouth shut!
[grunts]
No one speaks to me like that.
[bellows]
[VEGETA] How long did you
think I'd stand aside
while you screw around
with your training wheels on?
Don't ask me to be patient
if you won't even
use your full power!
I'll kick the crap
out of both of you!
Oh, okay, Vegeta, so that's
what this is about?
You really shouldn't
worry me like that.
Man, I thought it was way worse.
It's not funny! I didn't stop
my training to come here
so I could just watch this
fight from the sideline!
That's why you attacked him?
What a miserable
disappointment you are, Vegeta.
For a moment
I thought you and I
could have some fun again.
I always thought
you shone brightest
while I was
keeping you as my pet.
Like a tiny insect
glowing in a jar.
[chuckles]
I was never
your servant, Frieza.
I only used you
for my own agenda.
Whatever helps you
sleep at night.
I really don't care,
so long as you
don't interfere with
my revenge against Goku.
If killing him's
so important to you
then why don't you
get on with it?
Because I had
to wait a long time
and I only get to do this once.
You can't blame me for wanting
to savor it, can you?
This is my special day, Vegeta,
and I need you
to wait a while longer
so I can make sure
it goes exactly as planned.
I'll be more than happy
to murder you after that.
Ha! I would sure as hell
love to see you try.
But, just don't
blow him off 'cause of
all the crazy stuff
we've been through.
I don't know how he managed it,
but he's a whole lot
stronger than before.
[VEGETA] Really? You think
I can't sense that?
Clearly you have
been through "crazy stuff"
as you so
eloquently describe it.
I heard of your
defeating Majin Buu
so it was obvious
you'd improved yourself,
but you're even stronger
than I guessed.
[GOKU] Well, don't say
I didn't warned ya.
Fine. I'll give you
more time to fight.
But I won't wait much longer
so you'd better
both make it count!
I actually thought
I had a decent shot
at taking you on without
powering up, Frieza.
I guess that was
pretty dumb, huh?
Well it's a bad idea
to piss off Vegeta,
so I'd better get serious.
Good thing I trained so hard
or I might be frightened.
[laughs]
I knew it! You've been
holding back
something major, haven't you?
[FRIEZA chuckles]
That's well-deduced for
such a simpleton.
Indeed. The same as you have.
Then how 'bout
we do like Vegeta says
and go all in.
No more tricks
and no reserves, okay?
Very well.
Go ahead, monkeys first.
Are you sure about that?
I'd really hate for you
to get discouraged.
[chuckles]
But fine, Frieza,
I'll show you first.
You know I can sense that,
so don't even try it.
Just having some fun.
[gasps]
[bellows]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[ALL grunt]
[VEGETA grunts]
[snarls]
I'm not sensing
Goku at all anymore;
it's like his energy
just vanished.
That happened when
he was a Super Saiyan God.
Did he learn
how to do that again?
No, I think it's something
different; look at him.
His hair. His aura. It's blue.
A good point. I remember
when he was fighting
with Lord Beerus it was red.
That ceremony on the ship
basically turned him
into a deity.
Is it possible
he's even stronger now?
This is total insanity.
How far is Goku gonna go
before he's satisfied?
Well, at least we get to watch.
[KING KAI] So, he's got the
power of a Super Saiyan God,
but now he doesn't
even need energy
from the rest of the
Saiyans to get him there?
[sighs] What kind of
training were they doing
on Lord Beerus' world?
And why'd they think
that was a good idea?
[snarls]
That's a decent form,
I suppose.
Don't try to
sell it short, Frieza.
You and I both know
it's an incredible jump.
It's changed
my whole idea of power.
So what are you calling
this precious level:
Super Saiyan with blue hair dye?
[chuckles]
That's funny.
I'd say it's a little more
complicated than that.
I know you don't
have the patience
for the full story, Frieza.
But I got a taste of something
called Super Saiyan God
and then tapped into
that power on my own,
and it's the
Super Saiyan level of that.
[FRIEZA] So, a Super Saiyan
who's as strong as
a Super Saiyan God yet
is not a Super Saiyan God
is now the Super Saiyan
version of that?
You really do need to work
on your descriptions, Goku.
I nearly bit my tongue just
trying to spit it all out.
Well, I've held up
my side of the deal
and shown you my real power.
It's your turn.
I look back
to when I was young
Reminisce on all that I've done
In my hands, I held
The dreams of my childhood,
that now've come to pass
So let's ride upon
the wind and journey to
A world we've never known
(It's a brand new story)
Now, a new chapter starts
Shining Star
In the night be
my compass and guide
Take me to where I belong
The warmth we once shared
Will always be there
Its magic lives on in our hearts
Shining Star
Give me strength
from your light up above
Show me the way to be brave
My hands still hold onto hope
that together we'll manifest
All that we dreamed of
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
I can never forgive Frieza for
the terrible things he's done,
but I have to admit
his power's impressive.
His speed and strength
are about the same as mine.
And with his brand new form,
is it possible
he's even stronger?
This could be really bad news!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"A Full-Throttle Battle!
The Vengeful Golden Frieza"!
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?