♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
time was almost up in
the Tournament of Power,
with Goku and Jiren
locked in a final battle
to keep their Universes alive.
After the seemingly
invincible Jiren
increased his power
to even greater heights,
it appeared Goku would
have no way to answer.
But then...
[GOKU yells]
[NARRATOR] Goku's body radiated
with a blinding glow,
as he, at last, achieved
the full, divine level
he'd been searching for.
This mortal really
is something else.
This is the true power,
complete in all its majesty.
This is Autonomous
Ultra Instinct.
[NARRATOR] The ultimate
showdown... now!
[NARRATOR] "The Greatest
Showdown of All Time!
The Ultimate Survival Battle!"
[JIREN grunting]
All right, Jiren.
The real fight starts now.
So it shall, Goku.
Look at this new
form he's taken.
Judging by his appearance,
it seems he's finally mastered
true Autonomous Ultra Instinct.
How far can this
ability take him
once Jiren is fighting all-out?
Will this change the equation?
Or will it prove to be one
last bump on the road
to Jiren's victory?
It should be most
fascinating to witness.
[JIREN groaning]
The speed of complete
Ultra Instinct is incredible.
I never imagined a mortal
could be so sublime.
Surely it's too much
for even Jiren to take!
Who cares if it's true Ultra
Instinct, it won't matter!
Jiren will never lose.
He can't lose!
I hope you're not letting that
power-up go to your head!
[JIREN growls]
[JIREN grunts]
[JIREN groans]
[JIREN grunting, yelling]
You canceled out that blast!
[JIREN groaning]
[JIREN yells]
[JIREN yelling]
[JIREN grunts, yells]
[yells]
[JIREN growling]
[JIREN groaning]
[JIREN groans]
After all his struggling
against Jiren,
now he has the upper hand!
That's Dad for ya!
If the fight continues
like this,
then the salvation of the
Seventh Universe is assured!
[panting]
It's madness. Jiren actually
looks overwhelmed.
Does this mean Goku
has in fact catapulted
over the power of our champion?
[growls] It's not possible.
I cannot lose!
I won't accept defeat!
Might makes right...
and might alone.
Without strength,
we have nothing!
If I don't win,
then all my effort,
all I've struggled to achieve,
all of it will have
been pointless!
I'll lose everything,
just like I did before.
And I absolutely refuse
to go through that again!
[JIREN]
I cannot...
I will not!
[yelling]
[ALL groaning]
[ROSHI] That power's ferocious!
Like a firestorm!
[TIEN] Jiren's energy is
climbing even higher!
[A18] What the hell is
goin' on down there?!
[yelling]
Jiren's power level
just completely exploded!
How can this be?
Kakarot backed him
into a corner,
and it seems the prospect
of him losing made him
relive all the trauma
from his past.
That must have been
the motivation
that Jiren needed to finally
unleash all of his hidden power.
Goku had the edge. Damn it!
[GOKU grunts]
[JIREN grunts, yells]
[yelling]
It doesn't matter how high
you climb, I will not lose.
Never!
[GOKU yelping]
[yelling]
[JIREN yells]
[GOKU]
Uh?
[JIREN yells]
Ha!
[GOKU yelling]
[JIREN yelling]
[GOKU grunting]
[JIREN growls]
Huh?
It's over!
[GOKU screaming]
Goku!
[gasping]
[KRILLIN, TIEN gasping]
[GOHAN, A18 gasping]
You're still holding on after
taking that pummeling, Goku--
you're even tougher than
I gave you credit for.
[GOKU grunting]
[groans]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU screaming]
[yelling]
[GOKU groaning]
This is bad!
Brilliant! Jiren,
you've got him!
[gasping]
[GOKU groaning]
Goku!
Come on, get up, buddy!
Every time that it's
really mattered,
no matter how impossible
it's seemed,
you've always found
a way to bounce back!
And it's never mattered
more than this, Goku.
I believe in you.
You can stop Jiren!
I know it! Just dig deep,
and get up!
[GOKU grunting]
[gasps]
[gasping]
[JIREN]
He can't have any strength left!
This shouldn't be happening!
Believe it. This fight's
not over yet, Jiren.
[JIREN growls]
Tell me how.
How do you stand up no matter
how many times you fall?
Answer me, Goku!
[GOKU]
Because Vegeta, and 17,
and all the others gave
everything they had
so I could keep going.
If I do quit,
I betray that trust.
And I refuse to let
all of them down.
It's useless!
Your ideals mean nothing
in the face of my power!
[yelling]
You say they don't
mean anything.
I'll show you that they do.
How dare you?!
Goku's increased his speed--
he's even faster
than he was before!
Impossible!
How is he doing this?
[PICCOLO]
That should be obvious.
[BELMOD, KHAI]
Huh?!
Goku can reach these
heights because
he's not just fighting
for himself.
He fights for all of us.
That's the difference here.
[TOP gasps]
[ROSHI]
Piccolo's right.
Behind every one of Goku's
strikes is a whole community
of people who've
grown up with him,
strengthening him
over a lifetime
of unimaginable challenges.
Each one has been crucial.
They've been his friends and
family, his allies and rivals,
inspiring and
pushing him forward.
Goku doesn't imagine
for one minute
that he's gotten
this far on his own.
He's pushed all of
us forward, too,
shaping us into the
people we are today.
[KRILLIN] A lot of us started
out as his enemies.
We were hostile and misguided.
But he earned our
respect, and trust,
and showed us a different way.
[TIEN]
Even as he fights his opponents,
he has a funny way
of drawing them in.
That's just the kind
of man Goku is.
Yes, I've seen it myself.
[TOP grunts]
[yells]
[JIREN yells]
[GOKU screaming]
[GOKU yells]
[JIREN groaning]
[JIREN yelling]
[GOKU yells]
[JIREN groaning]
[GOKU]
This is our power, Jiren.
[JIREN]
To hell with your friendship.
To hell with your trust.
Putting faith in such things
would mean denying
all I've that witnessed
in my life up until now.
I know better than to believe
in that kind of
so-called "strength."
I know how easily
it's ripped away!
I'll show you!
[gasps]
[JIREN panting]
How dare you?!
The source of strength
you rely on is fleeting.
They will all be turned to dust!
Just like that rock!
[GOKU growling]
[GOKU] The truth is,
I ain't no hero of justice,
or anything else like that.
But anyone who tries
to hurt my friends...
...is gonna pay!
[JIREN groans]
[GOKU yells]
[yells]
Go on, Kakarot!
Now's the time
to put Jiren down!
[JIREN grunts]
[gasps, growls]
[JIREN groans]
Ha!
[JIREN screaming]
[yelling]
[groaning]
Jiren!
[JIREN]
What's the matter?
Why don't you finish me?
As incredible as you are,
now you have to admit what
I've been saying is true, right?
You understand, don't you?
[growls] Don't waste time
trying to preach to me.
This fight is over.
Throw me off the edge.
What are waiting for?
Hurry up, Goku!
[grunting]
[growls]
[groaning]
[JIREN gasps]
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU groaning]
[panting]
[screams]
[KRILLIN]
Goku!
[BEERUS]
What's happening to him?
The divine power beyond
his own limits...
I didn't know it was taking
such a toll on his body.
Oh, no.
But Goku had won the battle!
It was completely over!
We all saw it...
Jiren was through!
[screaming]
[JIREN gasping]
Hurry up Jiren, throw him over!
[gasps]
Did you come all
this way to lose?
[GOKU groaning]
[JIREN gasping]
Jiren.
What are hesitating for?
You can claim the Super Dragon
Balls and get your wish!
Just do it!
[JIREN grunting]
[JIREN] You are a true warrior,
Goku, there can be no doubt.
I regret that our spirited
battle must have such
an inglorious end. What a shame.
[GOKU groans]
[JIREN] But though you will
soon vanish from existence,
know that you shall live
forever in my memory.
[JIREN]
Farewell.
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU yelps, groans]
[gasps]
[BEERUS]
It's... Frieza!
[panting]
[A17 grunting]
And look, 17!
I thought he didn't make
it after that explosion!
I wasn't sure either.
It was a gamble.
I guess I just got lucky.
You never cease to
amaze me, Brother!
Jiren! You have to get rid
of them while you still can!
You are almost out of time!
[grunts]
Goku's looking pretty
useless now.
We're gonna have to
handle this ourselves.
Yes, obviously.
[NARRATOR] Goku harnessed
a power far beyond
what his mortal
body could handle,
and he has paid a heavy price.
Only a few moments remain
in the Tournament of Power.
The victor will be crowned.
Next time, on Dragon Ball Super.
Whirling all around
and then back again
The song that connects you
to the heavens
Strength that goes
beyond all measure
Expanding to a beat
that won't end
The meteors fall like rain drops
Astrological tears
from my eyelids
A strong emotion
from deep within
Has been awakened
A spark of possibility
Shines softly like a star
in the night sky
A wish from long
ago now shoots by
And I'm awakened
A never-ending melody,
so enchanting
You're always the one
who makes me tremble
The meteors keep falling down
Surging right into my heart
[GOKU]
Hey. It's me, Goku!
When I collapsed,
I thought we were finished.
But no, this fight
isn't over yet.
Our team's got one last
trick up our sleeves,
and we just have to
hope it's enough.
It's a shocking climax to
the Tournament of Power,
with the fate of the entire
Cosmos on the line!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super,
"A Miraculous Conclusion!
Farewell Goku!
Until We Meet Again!"
Make sure you
don't miss it, okay?