♪ Opening Song ♪
[BEERUS, OOLONG]
One. Two. Throw!
[screams]
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Oolong lost a game
of rock-paper-scissors
in which the earth's very
existence was at stake.
With nothing less
than the fate of the planet
hanging in the balance, our hero
made a last-ditch effort
to give Beerus what he seeks.
Stop right there!
Well like I said,
I don't know who or what
a Super Saiyan God is,
but there might be a way
to bring one here, because I
know exactly who we should ask!
Just give me a little time
to put this into action, okay.
Please? Can you do that?
All right. A teeny
little bit of time.
Thank you!
You won't be sorry!
How can you find someone
you're not sure even exists?
I'm asking our old friend
Shenron for help!
[NARRATOR] "Thanks
for Waiting, Lord Beerus.
A Super Saiyan God
Is Born At Last!"
Thank you, boys.
[BEERUS] Hm, those look
like wish orbs.
[WHIS] Earth's Guardian does
seem to be a Namekian after all.
Is it just my imagination,
or did wish orbs use
to be a little bit bigger?
Eh... I could be wrong.
No, my lord, your mind
isn't playing tricks on you.
The earth's wish orbs do appear
to be on the smaller side.
Ah.
Eternal Shenron! By your
name I summon you forth!
[SHENRON roars]
[roars]
[PILAF] Oh no, it's a storm!
A storm is coming!
Row faster, you guys!
Row with everything you've got!
Pilaf, sir!
You have gotta see this!
Yeah, see what?
I-Isn't that?
[ALL]
It's Shenron!
So then, that means
that they really did
have the Dragon Balls there!
[growls]
You see? Do you see that?
I told you. So I was right
all along, now wasn't I?
[growls]
Come on! We're going back
to that ship on the double!
[SHOU, MAI]
Huh?
Don't "huh?" me!
[SHOU, MAI]
Huh?
Row!
Row until your little arms
fall off! Dragon ho!
I am Shenron.
I shall grant you
any wish. Now speak!
Hey, sorry to cut
right to the chase.
But, uh, have by chance
heard of this thing called
a "Super Saiyan God"?
And if you have, well,
then I want to use my wish
to bring him here. That okay?
I'm aware of
the god you describe.
Awesome!
Now we don't all have to be
destroyed by Lord Beerus,
which is kind of a load off.
Wait, what? Did--
Did you say Lord Beerus?
[BULMA, GOHAN]
Huh?
Hey.
Uh... H-Hi, Lord Beerus.
Nice to meet you. Big fan.
Uh, please forgive me for
looking down on you
from way up here.
It's just my height.
I don't think
I'm better than you.
In fact, I know I'm not bet--
Don't worry about it.
Just hurry up
and summon a
Super Saiyan God for me.
I'm getting bored.
Ah, well, the truth is,
I can't exactly summon one
right at this moment,
I'm afraid.
It's kind of
a whole thing, you know.
[ALL gasp]
Say what?
[KRILLIN]
Uuh...?
What is he talking about?
Oh no.
What was that?
Uuuh... Yes, Lord Beerus.
The problem is, and I humbly
regret to inform you of this,
but although the Super
Saiyan God is spoken about
in Saiyan mythology,
no such deity exists
in the present day,
unfortunately.
However, if you would
like to know the method
for creating one, then it would
be my great honor to tell you.
Uh--yes, now. Okay.
The process is described
in the written legends
of Planet Namek.
Five Saiyans with righteous
hearts must join hands
and instill their
inner light into another.
With his friends' energy
flowing through him,
this Saiyan shall then take the
form of a Super Saiyan God.
And that's pretty much
everything you need to know.
So uh...
[GOKU]
Oh! Five, ten.
[BULMA] Vegeta!
You're supposed to be some
big Saiyan prince, aren't you?
So why didn't you
know anything about this?
I have given you
the knowledge you desired.
Your wish has been fulfilled.
Now, if there's nothing else,
may I please be excused?
[BEERUS]
Hmm.
[GOKU]
Uh...
Very well, then.
Lord Beerus, it truly is
a thrill for me to meet you
and I look forward
to seeing you again sometime.
Now, I bid you farewell!
Shenron sure was
in a hurry to leave.
Yeah.
Well, let's go.
Get on with it already.
Uh, hey, did anybody
follow all that stuff?
'Cause I got kinda really
confused halfway through it.
Basically, if I understand
what Shenron was saying,
is five Saiyans have to hold
hands with each other
and then combine their energies
and channel them
into another Saiyan,
who will supposedly
turn into some sort of deity.
And that's one of those
Super Saiyan God things,
like Lord Beerus asked us for?
Yes. I think so.
We're screwed.
He specifically said we need
Saiyans with righteous hearts.
Even if you include
the half-earthlings,
we've only got four.
Uh, think you
miscounted there, pal.
There's five of 'em.
Vegeta's really cleaned up
his act, you know.
His heart's plenty
righteous nowadays.
Yeah, I'm not so sure.
Hold on! You're just
being prejudiced!
He's a good man
and a great father!
He even takes his family
on lavish vacations!
[GOKU]
Come on.
Don't make that face, Vegeta.
Let's give it a shot!
[grunts]
Come on! Why does
Kakarot always get to
play the hero
in these situations?
No need to get all
worked up about it.
If this thing actually pans out,
then we'll let you
be the one next time. Okay?
Wait! Are you serious?
Well, Kakarot.
Are you feeling any different?
Well I'm feeling somethin',
that's for sure.
But I don't really know
if I feel like a deity though.
What does that even feel like?
Dad, your energy
is far and away--
the most intense it's ever been!
I've never felt anything
like it before!
Yeah. It's strong,
I won't deny that.
Good. Then I definitely
get to try it out next.
Oh. Well, now,
that isn't quite right.
Was I the only person
who was listening
to Shenron's instructions?
Now then. I want you all to
think very hard about this.
If it takes five Saiyans
to give their light to another,
then that means you need
five-plus-one Saiyans,
or six, if I'm not mistaken.
We need six?
Aaah! Oh, no!
That's one more
than we have here, right?
[VEGETA]
Ha!
If there are only five
of you Saiyans, then...
...it seems
your luck has run out.
Kakarot, I was a fool
to ever expect
anything but
utter failure from you !
Yeah, sorry
'bout that. My bad.
Math was never really
my strong suit.
[BEERUS grunts]
[WHIS humming]
Excuse me.
No, Videl. Go back!
It's just--I wonder if
a Saiyan inside my belly
might work under
the circumstances.
At least, a quarter Saiyan.
[ALL]
Aaah!
Whoa, Videl.
Do you mean that--?
Are we really gonna have a baby?
Like, for real, for real?
[giggles]
[hollers cheerfully]
Oh, yeah! Woo-hoo!
Yeah! I'm a grandpa!
Nice work!
Take it easy, Dad!
Oh, sweetie, this calls
for a celebration!
So when are you due?
When's the shower?
Have you picked out a name?
No, I haven't
gotten that far yet.
Oh, you just leave
everything to me!
We've already got
a Goku and a Gohan...
So tell me, how do
you feel about "Gomen"?
[GOHAN]
Huh?
Hey, does this mean
I'm gonna be a grandfather?
Nice! Congratulations!
Gee, thanks.
[laughs]
[growls]
Quit your yammering and create
a Super Saiyan God already!
Yeah, but-- even if
the baby inside Videl
is a quarter Saiyan, I just
don't know if that's really
gonna be enough
to make a difference here.
[GOHAN] But Dad,
if there's even a chance
that this could save the planet,
then don't we at least
owe it to the world
to give it a shot?
Yeah, okay. I mean,
I do think that it'd be
pretty awesome to become
a Super Saiyan God.
Everyone, focus on channeling
your inner light into Dad.
From your heart.
[GOKU]
Hmm.
Hey, nothing's happening.
Maybe Vegeta hasn't changed
as much as we thought he did?
D-Don't try to
pin the blame on me!
Okay, well.
Then it's gotta be
the unborn
baby's fault, right?
Maybe the kid's heart
isn't all that righteous?
Hey, don't say that
about my kid!
Yeah, it's rude!
All right, I'm sorry!
Let's just try it again
and concentrate
even harder this time. Okay?
Please give it all you've got!
This has to work!
It just has to!
Go on, make me proud, Videl!
Huh?
Huh? Ah!
Videl, look.
Your belly's glowing!
My body--it feels warm.
Aah. Divine energy.
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH gasp]
[PICCOLO huffs]
Ugh, what is it now?
[ALL yell]
Hey Videl, how do you feel?
Are you all right?
[VIDEL]
Mhmm.
Oh wow, my body
is starting to feel
a little achy all over.
[VEGETA] You know,
you're about to become a God.
Maybe you should just
try to stop whining.
Or if you'd rather,
I'd be more than happy
to take your place, Kakarot.
They're glowing. It looks
like it's working this time.
Seems something
is about to happen.
[WHIS]
Yes, Lord Beerus.
The rather ordinary energy
he possessed moments ago
has transformed.
Oh, my word.
Is it over?
No, not yet.
Incredible!
Now it's starting to rain?
How come you get rain
and I get hail?
I think it's working!
Kakarot's done it!
[BEERUS] So... will I finally
get to meet a Super Saiyan God?
It would appear so.
Oh, Goku!
Unbelievable.
It seems I may have been wrong
about your
premonition after all.
[WHIS]
Oh.
[BEERUS gasps]
Well, did it work?
That was a lot, Videl.
Are you feeling all right?
Uh-huh.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[CHICHI] Goku? Is that--
Is that really you?
He looks so much younger now.
So, Dende,
what do you think?
Hm!
[BEERUS] Well, well. Seems this
was worth the wait, after all.
[GOKU]
Ugh, yeah.
I'm sorry it took me
so long, Lord Beerus.
It's unbelievable.
Goku actually did it.
This cannot be good.
Okay, now I'm really
getting excited.
♪ Closing Song ♪
I see all these kids
As I walk to school
Their colorful backpacks
All unique and cool
I can't help but wonder
which color I'd choose
If I were still a kid
Where would I run off to? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
How am I lookin' now that
I've grown into an adult? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
Do I look like I'm proud
of who I've finally become?
Oh, I know I've made mistakes
But I'm tryin' to get it right
And I'm willing just to wait
For the moment I can shine
This anthem
Is a story for all time!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And this is super cool!
It looks like
I've actually become
an honest-to-goodness god!
I've got some sick new power!
There's no way
I can lose this time!
Uh-oh, I think I just
overshot Lord Beerus.
Huh? What the--?
None of my punches
seem to be landing!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Show Us, Goku! The Power
of a Super Saiyan God!!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?