♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the Saiyans used an ancient
ritual to temporarily
transform Goku
into a Super Saiyan God.
And though his new power
was difficult to control,
its potential seemed tremendous.
[GOKU grunts]
[yells]
I've been waiting
for you to try this move!
What the--?
First up, a forehead flick.
--Aah!
--Followed by a nice neck chop!
That's enough!
[GOKU]
Ow! Right in the face!
[chuckles]
Maybe the neck chop
was a little much,
but at least I got you back
for that forehead flick.
Flick, flick!
[chuckles]
I can respect revenge.
Nothing worse
than losing a fight.
Your preliminary tests are over.
Now the real
battle of gods begins.
That's what I like to hear.
And if you think
this is getting fun now,
wait until I go all out!
[NARRATOR] With the
stunning transformation,
it appears Goku can
finally battle Lord Beerus
on equal footing.
But can he actually win?
The battle continues, now!
[NARRATOR]
"Let's Keep Going, Lord Beerus!
The Battle of Gods!"
[GOHAN] Come on, Bulma,
can't this thing go any faster?
That last splashdown shook
something loose in the engine.
Then can't you
fix it or something?
We're gonna lose 'em!
Look, if you're gonna
complain the whole time
why don't you just
use your flying technique?
We'd love to
but that's not an option
at the moment. Right?
Yeah, I'm all out of energy too.
Out of energy now?
That's some pretty
lousy timing, boys.
[GOTEN, GOHAN laugh]
[PICCOLO] That's most likely
a side effect of
the Super Saiyan God ritual.
Not that it matters.
This isn't a fight we can
get involved in, anyway.
It's in your hands now, Goku.
[GOKU]
Hmph!
[BEERUS]
Heh.
[chuckles]
I'm ready when you are,
Great Super Saiyan God.
Okay. Let's try this out!
[BEERUS]
Aaaaaah! Heh.
[yells]
[BEERUS hollers]
[GOKU]
Whew!
[laughs]
That attack didn't
faze you at all, huh?
Good grief, Saiyan.
Do I seriously have to
provoke you even more?
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU]
Uuah!
Even with my new power-up,
your attacks
definitely still sting.
I've got another
present here for you.
I made it myself.
Wow, Beerus.
That's a whole lot bigger
than the last one, isn't it?
I suppose I'm just
a generous guy.
[yells]
[grunts]
Think carefully.
This energy orb is far
too heavy to just toss away.
[yells]
[grunts]
Huh?
[GOKU grunts]
Aah!
[GOKU yells]
[grunts]
[yells]
Huuuh?
[GOKU grunts]
[yells]
Can't you just close
your eyes and track their power?
You guys love that trick!
That won't work this time
because we're blind
to deity energy.
[BULMA]
Well that's sure inconvenient!
[GOTEN] Gohan, look,
I see something!
Whoa! Incredible!
[BULMA]
It's actually kind of pretty.
[GOHAN] You wouldn't think
that if you saw it up close.
It must be intense.
[grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[yells]
Yeah! You can do it, Dad!
Huh? What do you see?
[BEERUS exclaims]
Wow! It's awesome!
[GOKU hollers]
All right, Dad!
He's stronger than ever before!
[GOKU screams]
[BEERUS groans]
Unbelievable. He's actually
going toe to toe
with a Destroyer.
[BEERUS chuckles]
[GOKU yells]
Toe to toe? At least!
I think my dad might even
be more powerful than him!
[GOKU panting]
I should've known this
wasn't for real, Lord Beerus.
Huh?
I mean, you're not fighting
with your full power, are you?
Hm. What gave it away?
[laughs]
Yeah. Sorry about that.
I just figured a gung-ho
competitor like you
needed help pacing
yourself so you didn't
get exhausted too early.
[KIBITO KAI]
Great Ancestor.
I don't understand
these fighters.
Does that mean Lord Beerus
was allowing himself
to be pummeled by Goku
when he could have stopped it?
Yes. It would appear so.
But why would he do that?
It's not about winning.
Beerus is training him
to use the Super Saiyan
God power fully.
Then he'll simply crush Goku
with his true might.
[KIBITO KAI]
Mmm!
But what would be
the point of doing that?
Uh... For fun, I guess?
Eeh!
He's unpredictable.
And that is what
makes him so scary.
[laughs]
Well don't worry Beerus,
I'm not mad at ya.
I bet when you're
as strong as you are
there's hardly anyone
who stands a chance against you
at your maximum power,
which means you never
get a chance
to have a decent fight.
And that's why you--Uh!
Don't try to understand me.
You have no idea.
[GOKU yells]
[groans]
[yells]
Come on. Show me something
worthy of a god.
[muffled screams]
Are you really going to let me
slam you into the ground
without a fight?
Dad, no!
[GOHAN] Come on, Bulma!
We have to hurry!
[BULMA]
Yeah, I know that!
But the engine's
all out of whack!
I'm not a freaking magician!
[PICCOLO] The Super Saiyan God
transformation is incredible.
But against the power
of a Destroyer,
it still might not be enough.
[BEERUS humming]
[GOKU breathes heavily]
It's a good thing
you escaped at the moment
of the explosion,
Super Saiyan God.
Or you'd be nothing
but a pile of ashes.
[GOKU groans]
[coughs]
What a bore.
I'm half asleep now.
You bore me. You bore me!
You were supposed
to be different!
Supposed to be worthy!
But you put me to sleep
like everything else!
Is a little bit of excitement
too much to ask for?!
[GOKU]
Will this wake you up?
[groans]
[breathes heavily]
Congratulations
on the cheap shot.
But this level of power
you're showing me--
well, how should I put it?
It doesn't have
any effect on me at all!
[gasps]
[PICCOLO]
Down there, that island!
[BULMA] I know! I told you,
don't order me around!
Hey, what is that?
It's Goku!
He looks injured!
[screams]
[yells]
They keep going
higher and higher!
[grunts]
Take us up.
[BULMA]
I know!
[yawns]
[BEERUS]
Yoo-hoo, Saiyan God!
How long are you
planning to nap?
I'd like to get on with it,
if you don't mind.
Honestly. I'd really hate
for destruction to serve
some kind of a purpose.
It makes it so much less pure.
But if it's the only way
to tap your full power
then I have no choice.
No, you wouldn't!
[BEERUS]
Hm.
Wait! Don't do it, Beerus!
You have yourself to blame.
Are billions of lives
just disposable toys
for you to play with?
But of course they are,
Goku. I'm a deity.
What's more important:
one backwater world
or a battle of gods?
It's not even a question.
You won't be able to
deflect or crush this one,
so you'd better start
taking this seriously.
That was simple enough,
wasn't it?
I just had to blow it away.
Bright idea, let's scale it up.
[gasps]
Well? Motivated yet?
You want to see the real
power of a Super Saiyan God?
Then that's what you'll get!
Heh.
[bellows]
[BEERUS]
Yes. Very good.
[bellows]
[BEERUS] That's it,
you've found the source.
Now tap it all the way.
[bellows]
Here they come.
Ka...
...me...
...ha...
Ha!
Aah!
[GOKU breathes heavily]
[gasps]
[BEERUS]
My mistake.
[gasps]
[BEERUS] I seem to have
the wrong person.
You're clearly not the rival
I was looking for.
[gasps]
Goku!
[GOKU] You sure are
strong, Lord Beerus.
What do you know?
I never knew... there was...
there was anyone...
there was anyone out there
that was that strong.
So strong... So strong...
Beyond strong.
And... I don't understand.
Somehow...
Somehow I'm... Somehow...
Somehow I'm... Somehow I'm...
I'm just excited.
In fact, I've never
been more excited
in my entire life.
[GOTEN, GOHAN gasp]
Was that... Goku?
Hm?
[exhales]
Let's keep going, Lord Beerus,
if you're still game.
Looks like this Super Saiyan God
power's not finished yet.
It's going to keep on
lifting me higher
until I can match you,
fist for fist.
Well, I doubt that.
But I do like
the look in your eyes.
So I'm going to
honor your progress
by showing you more than
a taste of my power.
[chuckles]
Now you'll get a full course.
Mmm.
[NARRATOR] Amazingly,
the Super Saiyan God power
has not yet reached its limit,
as Goku continues to grow
stronger than ever before.
How will this
battle of gods unfold,
as Goku and Beerus enter
the next planet-shaking round?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball Super!
♪ Closing Song ♪
I see all these kids
As I walk to school
Their colorful backpacks
All unique and cool
I can't help but wonder
which color I'd choose
If I were still a kid
Where would I run off to? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
How am I lookin' now that
I've grown into an adult? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
Do I look like I'm proud
of who I've finally become?
Oh, I know I've made mistakes
But I'm tryin' to get it right
And I'm willing just to wait
For the moment I can shine
This anthem
Is a story for all time!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And I think I'm
finally figuring out
what a Super Saiyan God can do!
This is where the battle
with Beerus gets really good.
But wait a second, why is
Supreme Kai talking in my head?
He's telling me
to stop fighting!
Why would I want to do that?
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"The Universe Will Shatter?!
Clash! Destroyer vs.
Super Saiyan God!"
You definitely don't
want to miss this one!