♪ Opening Song ♪
[bellows]
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Lord Beerus the Destroyer
defeated Goku in battle,
and it seemed the loss
had sealed Earth's fate.
But their intense fight
exhausted Beerus,
and the fearsome
deity fell asleep
in the middle of
his destructive blast.
And so, having narrowly
escaped Armageddon,
the people of Earth
returned to their normal--
and not-so-normal--lives.
Goku wanted to resume his
training on King Kai's planet,
but Chichi had nipped
that plan in the bud.
The saga continues, now!
Aw man, I guess that means
I'm sleeping outside tonight.
[NARRATOR]
"Vegeta Becomes a Student?!
Win Over Whis!"
[KIBITO KAI] Not much
is happening now.
All's quiet again.
But something's wrong.
There are two more worlds
missing from their systems,
and I didn't even
see what happened!
Beerus' rampage must have
been worse than we realized.
But are you sure?
I'm not seeing
the rubble in space
like with the other planets
we know he destroyed.
It's like something
different happened to them;
more like they vanished
through some act of magic.
Aah! There you go, that's it!
Just a bit more to the right!
Show me something!
Yeah, that's good,
that's good! Oh yeah!
Great Ancestor. Dare I even
ask what you're staring at?
Get out of my way, boy,
it's the best part!
Stop it; you're a Kai
not a peeping Tom!
[ELDER KAI] Hey! Move!
You're spoiling the fun!
[KIBITO KAI]
Great Ancestor, please!
[ELDER KAI] Oh look,
it's a shooting star!
Oh...
Blast it, he lost!
Wait, who lost?
Just what exactly have you been
watching out there, anyway?
What? Horned beetles?
That's right
and they were having
a doozey of a fight.
Hang on a minute,
what did you think
I was looking at?
Oh-Oh, nothing I just-
Well it's that- I thought, uh-
Hey look, it's a shooting star!
[ELDER KAI]
Hmm!
[chuckles nervously]
[GOKU snores]
Ha! Goku!
[laughs]
[gasps]
Oh, hey Krillin, what's up?
I was worried
I wouldn't find you.
Where else would I be?
Well I figured you'd
go back to King Kai's planet
to train some more,
but then I heard a rumor
you were playing farmer
or something.
Yeah. Believe me,
I wish I could be
training right now
more than anything.
But Chichi told me I can't go!
She says I'm
about to be a grandpa
so I have to start
acting like a grown-up!
Ouch, buddy. That might
be the toughest demand
anybody's ever put on you.
It's not exactly your forte.
I told her that the kid's
gonna have Saiyan blood
and we're not really
"day job" kind of people.
But Chichi's gotten even
more strict than when
Gohan was born, and she
won't listen to me.
[KRILLIN] Well,
it is her first grandkid.
Anyway, enough about her.
You think you could drive
this thing for a while?
I guess.
I can feel myself
getting weaker
just riding that thing all day.
I need to keep training non-stop
to find a whole new level.
It's the only way I'm ever
going to catch up to Beerus.
It's crazy, huh?
Every year the gap
just gets wider.
[GOKU]
What?
Back in the day,
when we were kids
training under Master Roshi,
I could at least
sort of keep up.
[laughs]
[KRILLIN] Wait, I think
that stone might be a decoy.
I'll check it out for you.
[laughs]
Wait, Krillin,
you're cheating!
Give me back
that stone right now!
[KRILLIN] But you kept pulling
further and further ahead.
Skip two three four, skip--
[KRILLIN]
And look at you now.
Going toe-to-toe with Beerus.
The guy's an actual god!
Yeah, that is funny.
And you're still the same
size as back then, too!
Goku!
I didn't say that was bad!
[KRILLIN] Goku, would you mind
slugging me? Just once?
[GOKU] What? You're
asking me to punch you?
That's right.
I want to feel for myself
exactly how strong
you've gotten.
You do know that
would hurt a lot, right?
Well yeah.
Are you sure about this?
I'm sure.
[GOKU]
It's really gonna hurt!
Yeah!
It's really, really
gonna hurt! Really hurt!
Yeah!
Okay, then get ready!
Right!
[yells]
[BOTH yell]
Ah! Krillin!
[KRILLIN grunts, hollers]
--[KRILLIN yells]
--[GOKU] I gotcha!
[thud]
[chuckles nervously]
[A18]
Come on, don't squirm.
[yelps]
Hey, I can't
treat your wound if you
keep jumping like that.
What on Earth were
you thinking asking Goku
to smack you, anyway?
Look, it made
sense at the time.
I wanted to know
how strong he'd gotten
and feel it first-hand.
[whimpers]
You're clearly
feeling it now.
You're a hopeless fool,
you know that, right?
Here I go! Catch!
Gotcha!
[KRILLIN] Man, he's strong.
And I don't regret it.
[giggles] Hooray
for Goten, all right!
I've kinda been
wondering if I was right
to give up martial arts
when I did.
But now I've got my closure!
And it feels great!
[bones crack]
Maybe you should
wait to say that
after I'm finished, honey.
Aw, come on! I think
you're enjoying this!
Wow, you really are
amazing now, Goku.
Can't wait to see what
your next level's like.
I know you'll get there...
Yeah, Krillin's right.
I've pushed myself
my whole life.
And I can't stop now.
Well, no one's
watching me, right?
[exhales, grunts]
It's training time then!
[thunder crashing]
[grunts]
[yells]
[VEGETA panting]
[VEGETA] Is this truly
the best I can do?
I will be the strongest
this time, Kakarot.
I will claim the power
of the gods,
and I will do it
all on my own!
[birds chirp]
[hollers gleefully]
All right, here it goes!
[WHIS shrieks]
[hollers gleefully]
Ah, it's delicious!
My, this is
absolutely exquisite!
Crispy and crunchy,
yet spongy at the same time!
It's like
a ballet in my mouth!
Oh. What is this
liquid called again?
That's tempura sauce.
[WHIS]
Right! Tempura sauce!
Such a fragrant
bouquet! I love it!
The sauce alone
is a work of art!
You have done
magnificently, chef.
[CHEF 16A]
Uh, thanks.
Let's try the shrimp
and vegetable next.
[CHEF 16A]
Sure, coming right up!
[WHIS]
Mmm. That lively sound.
[sniffs]
That rich aroma.
Oh thank you, Bulma,
it's even better than the last.
I can always count on you for a
fabulous culinary adventure!
Of course, Whis,
don't mention it!
I mean that's what indispensable
friends are for, right?
Yes indeed!
Oh-ho-ho!
An inspired combination!
On their own I find
decapod crustaceans
too small for my taste.
But the added heft
here is great!
[giggles]
Like I was saying,
I'm so glad we're friends!
We're lucky Beerus
didn't destroy the earth
so I could show you
all this food!
And naturally if he comes back,
you'll use your sway
to keep my family safe,
at least.
I mean isn't that right, Whis?
Aaah-mmm!
Well, that's
difficult to say...
[BULMA]
Hm?!
[hollers gleefully]
This is brilliant!
I know.
[BULMA] You're back sooner
than I expected, for once.
I wish you would've told me.
You do realize some couples
communicate, right?
And in case you haven't noticed,
you're totally filthy.
Every time you come back
from a training binge,
you track mud
all through the house.
It's like, "Oh, I forgot
my living room was
a mud-wrestling pit!"
Are you listening to me
or am I talking to myself?
Honestly, Vegeta,
it'd be nice if you could
at least make eye contact
after being gone so long.
Did you forget
how to speak or what?
[VEGETA gasps]
Whis, it's you!
Salutations, Vegeta,
it's been too long.
[VEGETA] What's going on?
Why're you here?
Who, little old me?
Oh-ho-ho!
I simply dropped by
to share a meal with Bulma.
With Bulma?
Didn't I tell you?
Whis and I have become
really good friends.
He visits every now and then
and I take him to lunch.
Just having lunch
with my wife are you?
Bulma has been
introducing me to some of
the most sensational
cuisines I've ever tasted.
Earth seems to have
an endless cornucopia
of flavors and
cooking techniques.
Honestly, I'm not sure I'd ever
get tired of coming here.
If it wasn't for our
wonderful friendship,
you wouldn't have tasted
any of those things!
Don't you forget!
I doubt you'll ever let me!
And of course I'm grateful.
If you've been coming here,
then why the hell didn't I know?
Why are you getting
so mad, Vegeta?
Oh! Now I get it!
You're feeling jealous,
aren't you?
A charming and dignified
alien going to lunch
all alone with
your beautiful bride.
I can understand why
that might make you worry.
No, I don't
give a damn about that!
What?! You could
at least pretend!
Yeah, sure, fine, babe.
Is Beerus here?
Lord Beerus is currently
on his home world
enjoying a bit of rest.
Is that so? Then I demand
you take me there
to see him immediately!
I'm going to show
that arrogant feline
the true power
and might of a Saiyan!
[BULMA]
Vegeta...
[chuckles]
Spit it out!
Have you completely
lost your mind?
You know how close Beerus
came to destroying Earth.
What if you get him mad and
he decides to finish the job!
Shut up! You don't
understand, Bulma;
I have to fight him!
It's the only way I can
find out how far I can go!
I'm sorry to burst your
self-delusional bubble,
but you don't stand a chance!
Beerus nearly killed Goku
and that's after Shenron
helped him
find that new power.
Tch. And that's what
gets me the most--
it should have been me!
Take it out on a boulder
and stay out of my way!
The whole reason I'm
making nice with that guy
is so if his master comes
back to blow up the earth,
I can at least keep
our family safe.
And I'm not gonna let you
screw that up! You hear me?
[grunts]
[BULMA] Lover's quarrel;
shall we go?
Indeed. I can't wait
to taste the dessert
you've arranged for me, Bulma.
I admit I have
quite the sweet tooth.
[VEGETA] Hold on! I'm not
done talking with you!
[VEGETA] If that's
how you want to do it,
I'll stop you by force!
What's happening?
Some sort of energy.
It's-It's holding me back.
It won't let me attack!
[gasps]
Who the hell
are you actually, Whis?
You're more than just Beerus'
servant, aren't you?
[WHIS]
Oh. Did I neglect to mention?
Sorry-Yes, I am
Lord Beerus' teacher as well.
His... teacher?
Wait. Come again? You mean
like his fighting teacher?
Yes, that's right.
So you're even stronger
than the Destroyer?
[chuckles]
Oh, I don't know about that.
Well all I know
is I'm hungry!
Ready to go have
that dessert I promised?
Yes, of course!
Is this the one they
only make ten of a day?
Actually, it's only five!
Honestly?
You're Beerus' teacher?
May I be so bold? I'd like
to offer you a bit of advice.
You've achieved
considerable power,
through what I assume is
intense physical training,
but if you continue
focusing on power alone,
you'll never defeat Lord Beerus.
The most crucial skill
you lack is a method
for controlling your energy.
If you can learn that...
...I suspect you'd be able
to surpass your fellow warrior
who always seems
one step ahead.
You mean Kakarot?
Unfortunately, it won't be
easy to learn that control.
Bye!
What is with you today?
This skill you say
I need so badly--
controlling my energy--
can you teach me that?
[intense music plays]
Make me your student, please!
And I won't let you down!
Would you give your crazy
obsession a rest for one minute!
I told you, Whis and I
already have plans!
[WHIS]
I'll train you...
[gasps]
...if you agree to become
a Destroyer one day--
I guess I should have
led with that.
All right, Bulma,
shall we go now?
[BULMA] Absolutely.
Sorry he's being annoying.
[WHIS] Oh, it's no bother.
I'm all for having goals.
Hold on!
[chuckles]
What if I said I could
feed you the most
delicious cuisine on Earth?
Think that might
change your answer?
The most delicious food on
Earth; are you sure of that?
You bet I'm sure!
And you have my guarantee it
will blow your feeble mind!
Okay, that's enough!
You can't just swoop in
and steal my thing!
[WHIS]
Food that blows the mind?
Huh?
[VEGETA chuckles]
I-would-not-pass-this-up.
Do we have a deal?
Oooh. Sorry, Bulma.
Whis, wait! Oh, come on,
this is ridiculous!
Get ready!
The tempura here is...
...so crispy! Tender!
Crunchy! And divine!
One bite and you'll be
in flavor heaven!
[laughs]
It will literally
melt in your mouth!
It is delicious, I agree.
You mean you've had it?
Bulma brought
me here earlier
and we had a fantastic meal.
[grunts]
In that case then...
[exhales] The aroma here
is like nothing else!
This place serves the best eel
with a killer secret sauce!
Oh yes, I remember.
It was exceptional!
What?! So you've
been here too?
[VEGETA] How 'bout
this noodle shop?
[WHIS]
Mhm!
[VEGETA] How about
this steakhouse?
[WHIS]
Uh-huh!
[VEGETA] And the world's
best food stand?
[WHIS]
My favorite was the beef!
[BULMA] Don't forget
about the radish!
Been here too? How nice!
[grunts]
You leave me no choice!
I'll just have to
cook you my own dish then!
Ha! Brace yourself!
Vegeta's world-famous
gourmet rice omelet!
Do you even know
how to crack an egg?
[VEGETA]
Silence!
You can do this.
Fingertips only.
Aah!
Careful now...
Gently-gently!
Like you're holding a child!
[grunts]
Come on!
You weakling shells!
This might be
a good time to go.
How disappointing.
I was hoping he'd actually
pull something off.
Wait! Don't leave!
--Aah!
--[chirps]
Give it up, Vegeta.
We both know you've never cooked
a rice omelet in your life.
[grunts]
You've got some nerve
criticizing my cooking skills,
Miss Microwave Dinner!
[gasps] Hold on.
Whis, can you tell me
everything that Bulma
has fed you so far?
Let's see: tempura,
the eel, the food cart,
beef stir-fry,
a softshell crab soup,
and a rather wonderful meal as
part of a tea ceremony, why?
[VEGETA laughs intensely]
Just as I suspected.
Bulma's fed you good dishes
but she's holding back
the greatest food of all!
Well that's quite
a provocative claim.
[VEGETA] It's true.
I'm talking about a meal
she can't go one week
without eating!
[gasps]
Vegeta!
All right,
you have my attention.
What is this irresistible fare?
[timer dings]
[VEGETA]
Perfection in a cup.
Hmm. So you're
telling me that this
is the most delicious meal
on your entire planet?
[WHIS]
Hm. Hmmm.
[WHIS gasps, moans]
I think my mouth is in love!
It's wonderful!
The texture is so velvety
and the broth is superb!
And the noodles
slide down my throat
like they've been spun
by a galactic silkworm!
I never dreamed such food heaven
could come in a paper cup!
I'm not sure what I should
think about this, Bulma.
It seems you've been hiding
this one from me on purpose!
That's my guilty pleasure!
No one's supposed to know!
Got him!
[WHIS chuckles]
Bulma certainly was mad
when you showed me the ramen;
even angrier than
I expected she would be.
Hm? What does that mean?
Are you saying you knew
she was hiding them from you?
I wouldn't say that exactly,
but I did have a hunch.
It was awfully nice
of her to give you that
handsome new uniform,
though, wasn't it.
I think you look nice in gray.
[VEGETA]
This is for me? Why?
Well, I can't let you
leave the planet
in those filthy rags.
We'd become the laughingstock of
the intergalactic community!
[WHIS]
We'll be arriving shortly.
Welcome to Lord Beerus' world.
I look back
to when I was young
Reminisce on all that I've done
In my hands, I held
The dreams of my childhood,
that now've come to pass
So let's ride upon
the wind and journey to
A world we've never known
(It's a brand new story)
Now, a new chapter starts
Shining Star
In the night be
my compass and guide
Take me to where I belong
The warmth we once shared
Will always be there
Its magic lives on in our hearts
Shining Star
Give me strength
from your light up above
Show me the way to be brave
My hands still hold onto hope
that together we'll manifest
All that we dreamed of
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
I can't believe Vegeta gets to
train on Beerus' world
while I'm stuck
back at home. It's not fair!
But Chichi is on me like a hawk,
and for some reason
Gohan is watching me too!
Plus, I don't know how
to get to Beerus' world,
and who knows when
Whis will come back.
Hey Bulma, you think
you can help me?
I'm too scared
of Chichi on my own!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Pan Is Born! And Goku Goes
on a Training Journey?!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?