♪ Opening Song ♪
[BEERUS]
My mistake.
[groans]
[NARRATOR] After seeing
potential in Goku's new
divine powers,
Beerus changed course,
deciding that the
Super Saiyan God was not,
in fact, arch rival material.
Beerus seemed stronger
than Goku's mind
could even comprehend,
but Earth's defender
wasn't ready to quit.
[GOKU] Somehow I'm...
I'm just excited.
In fact, I've ever been more
excited in my entire life!
Let's keep going, Lord Beerus,
if you're still game.
Looks like this Super Saiyan God
power's not finished yet.
It's going to keep on
lifting me higher
until I can match you,
fist for fist.
Well I doubt that.
But I do like
the look in your eyes.
So I'm going to
honor your progress
by showing you more than
a taste of my power.
[chuckles]
Now you'll get a full course.
[NARRATOR] Goku has left
mortal limits behind,
and enters an uncharted sea
of seemingly endless power.
Can he find his way
and save the earth?
The divine battle
continues now!
[NARRATOR]
"The Universe Will Shatter?
Clash! Destroyer
vs. Super Saiyan God!"
[GOKU]
Hmph.
[BEERUS]
Hmm.
Did we make it in time?
Good luck out there, Dad!
You can take 'em!
Whaa!
[PICCOLO]
What the--?
What is that,
an electrical storm?
Oh, great! Aah!
What the heck's
going on, Piccolo?
Their energy seems to be
charging particles
in the atmosphere.
[GOTEN]
Aah! We're gonna fall!
[PICCOLO]
Bulma, do something!
[BULMA]
I am doing something!
[GOHAN] It's okay, Bulma!
You've got this!
Shall we go a little higher?
Yeah, if you don't mind,
I'm sure it's safer that way.
Enjoying the show?
Looks like a neck cramp
waiting to happen.
[WHIS huffs]
Impressive, isn't it?
A crystal-clear picture.
It's like being there without
having to dodge the blasts!
Prince? Ahem.
You're welcome to
watch this, you know,
though a "thank you"
wouldn't hurt!
Huh?
That's weird. I could've
sworn he was right behind me.
Huh, where'd he go?
Okay. What should I do now?
Hmm.
Nice try, Lord Beerus.
But you won't be able to
sneak up on me like before.
You do realize that, right?
[BEERUS]
I suppose I do now.
[chuckles]
From now on, no more
cheap tricks.
Yeah. That sounds good to me.
[grunts]
[growls lowly]
[bellows]
[yells]
[growls]
[BOTH yell]
[PEDESTRIANS murmur]
[gasps]
What's going on here?
Their impacts are creating
energy shockwaves,
like earthquakes
creating tsunamis.
And these waves gain strength
the farther they travel.
The consequences will be dire.
The whole universe as we
know it could be ripped apart.
[gasps]
Imagine if they keep
hammering at each other,
continuing to channel
more strength with each blow.
[bellows]
[ELDER KAI] The damage
will increase exponentially
as the growing shockwaves
travel across the universe,
causing a chain reaction
of destruction!
Galaxies will explode like
strings of firecrackers!
All the planets, all the Kais,
even Goku and Beerus
will be lost.
Until nothing remains
but an empty void.
[gasps]
[ELDER KAI grunts]
Aw, what was I thinking?
I never should have
allowed the Dragon Balls
to be used in the first place!
If mortals needed
treasure to hunt,
I should've just had them
find seven dirty pictures!
Or even better! Seven IOU cards!
Good for a motor-boating session
from a hottie so smokin'
her jugs would have had their
own gravitational fields!
Now that would have led
to adventures worth watching!
Let's try to focus
on reality, shall we?
How many more of those
impact waves do you think
the universe can withstand
before it starts to crumble?
Not sure. I'd say two more,
if I had to guess.
Two more, is that it?
[ELDER KAI] I don't know.
It could be three, maybe.
[KIBITO KAI]
This is incredibly important!
We need the exact number!
Uuuh... Let's just
be safe and say two.
[yells]
[BEERUS]
Heh.
[chuckles]
[GOKU] I just hope
my bones don't shatter.
[BEERUS]
Mmm. Hm.
[KIBITO KAI]
Lord Beerus! Goku!
You have to call off
this fight immediately!
I know you can hear me!
Please, stop!
[GOKU]
Hm!
What now? It's hopeless.
[ELDER KAI] I'm afraid
they're both too obsessed
with battle to stop,
you know that as well as I do.
[bellows]
[GOKU bellows]
[BEERUS yells]
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH grunt]
[yells]
[BOTH yell]
[GOKU grunts]
[BULMA groans]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[GOHAN, GOTEN exclaim]
Now we're seeing what a
battle of gods is really like.
[shrieks]
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
[PEDESTRIANS gasp]
[REPORTER 12A] We're reporting
live from Satan City,
where a second
mysterious shockwave
has just rippled through!
What could be the cause of this,
and should we
scream like babies?
[ALL yell]
Yes, I think we should!
Oh, good.
Looks like we've got him!
We now have
an exclusive interview
with the world's savior himself!
Mr. Satan, thank you
for speaking with me!
The city is in crisis! Can you
tell us where you are?
Well, sure.
I'm actually at
a swanky birthday party.
[REPORTER 12A]
What?!
Uhhh! I mean, uh...
That's what it looks like
to an untrained regular person.
But it's really a front for
a supervillain syndicate!
The party's really
a black market auction
for stolen mega-weapons!
[REPORTER 12A] Amazing!
So you've infiltrated
the auction
to catch the crooks!
Are they responsible
for the shockwaves?
Well it's a long story,
but yes they are!
[REPORTER 12A]
Great, we've got time!
Tell us exactly
how they're causing them!
Be the eyes
for our viewers at home!
Sorry, what? I can't
hear ya, the signal's bad.
[REPORTER 12A]
Mr. Satan!
What'd you say?
Aw shucks, I'm losin' ya!
[phone beeps]
[phone rings]
Gohan, what the heck's
happening up there?
You gotta stop
these shockwave things.
They make me look bad
and they're dangerous!
Videl's down here
with my future grandbaby!
Are you hearing me?!
[GOHAN] Sorry, but we're
kind of in trouble, too.
Yeah, what kind of trouble?
[menacing music plays]
[yells]
Huh?
[MR. SATAN]
What the jumpin' mackerel?
[gasps]
That was a close call,
wasn't it?
Does this mean
we're safe now, blue guy?
[WHIS]
In short? No.
Lord Beerus promised
that if Goku wins,
he won't destroy Earth.
And he tends to keep his word.
But I don't believe
their battle
has reached its conclusion.
Not quite yet. Hm.
[BOTH panting]
[GOKU panting]
[BEERUS panting]
[exhales]
It's exactly what
my dream foretold.
Your progress so far
has been remarkable.
I was wrong to doubt you.
You might be worthy, after all.
Thanks, Beerus. But I
wouldn't have gotten here
without your help.
[grunts, yells]
I bet it seems strange.
Me showing gratitude
for these powers by
using them against you,
but I know that's what you want.
So consider this
next attack my thank you!
[BOTH gasp]
This would be
their third shockwave.
If you're right, ancestor...
then we're doomed!
[BEERUS, GOKU grunt]
[growls, yells]
[yells]
[BOTH growl]
[grunts]
[yells]
[bellows]
[growls]
[yells]
[bellows]
[BEERUS]
Brace yourself!
[GOKU]
Bring it on!
[yells]
It worked!
[ELDER KAI]
What the--?
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[growls]
[groans]
[chuckles]
Tremendous accomplishment.
His skills are off the charts!
So what happened?
Where is the shockwave?
[ELDER KAI] By slamming
his fist into Beerus's
with just the right
angle and force,
he neutralized the attack and
canceled out its energy!
This prevented a shockwave
and strain on his own body!
I'm glad that worked.
I meant to do that with
the second flying punch
but I was off a little.
But I'll chalk that up to
your skills, Lord Beerus.
You definitely don't
make things easy on me.
[BEERUS] Unbelievable.
This Saiyan upstart
is experimenting
with new moves
in the middle
of his fight with me?
[chuckles]
[BEERUS growls, yells]
Not even satisfied
with divine power?
You're already trying
to reach a higher level!
Heh. You're damn right!
If you truly understood
your divine power,
you wouldn't take it so lightly.
[GOKU huffs]
[BEERUS growls lowly]
[GOKU inhales]
Ka...me...ha...me...
Witness the power!
Ha! Ha! Ha!
[BOTH gasp]
That makes three.
[PEDESTRIANS groan]
I don't know what to say,
folks. It's beyond words!
This strange shockwave
has surrounded us!
And I'm being told
it's everywhere!
Reports are flying in
from across the globe!
All I really know is
it feels like it's very bad!
I hate to alarm you but
I think we're in big trouble!
[KING KAI yells]
This is it!
I don't know what to do!
I just keep
running in circles! Aah!
So, after all our work
and our struggles,
this is how it ends?
I don't want to admit it's over,
but I don't see any way out.
The story of this cosmos
has reached its final page.
Farewell, Great Ancestor.
Here, boy. A parting gift.
My favorite magazine.
Hot, right?
[shrieks]
So... this is it.
I finally reached
the limit of this power.
That's too bad. I give you
all the credit, Lord Beerus.
You're as strong as they come.
It's torture to say this,
but you've won.
I just can't
keep this up anymore.
[yells]
It was a valiant effort, Goku.
How can that be?
[GOKU]
I can't believe it either.
[grunts]
[gasps]
The Super Saiyan God power just
spoke to me loud and clear.
And there's no mistaking it.
It's telling me...
...to keep on pushing
even higher!
[bellows]
[yells]
[vivacious music plays]
[NARRATOR] The entire universe
is now shaking from the impact,
as two divine powers collide.
Are the Supreme Kais correct?
When this blinding light fades,
will there be anything left?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball Super!
♪ Closing Song ♪
I see all these kids
As I walk to school
Their colorful backpacks
All unique and cool
I can't help but wonder
which color I'd choose
If I were still a kid
Where would I run off to? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
How am I lookin' now that
I've grown into an adult? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
Do I look like I'm proud
of who I've finally become?
Oh, I know I've made mistakes
But I'm tryin' to get it right
And I'm willing just to wait
For the moment I can shine
This anthem
Is a story for all time!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And I keep thinking
I've got Beerus figured out,
but then he just shows me
an even crazier move!
What kind of technique is that?
He's got the
whole Earth shaking,
and apparently
he's still holding back!
But I don't care
how strong he is,
there's no way
I'm gonna lose!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Goku,
Surpass Super Saiyan God!"
You'd have to be nuts
to miss that!