[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the brutal Tournament of Power
had nearly reached its
dramatic conclusion.
Goku had perfected his
Autonomous Ultra Instinct,
and was one strike
away from victory.
But then...
[JIREN gasps]
[groans]
I regret that
our spirited battle
must have such
an inglorious end.
What a shame.
[GOKU groaning]
[JIREN] But though you will
soon vanish from existence,
know that you shall live
forever in my memory.
Farewell.
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU groaning]
[NARRATOR]
With only moments to spare,
who will win the battle royale
and claim the
Super Dragon Balls?
The Tournament ends... now!
[NARRATOR]
"A Miraculous Conclusion!
Farewell Goku!
Until We Meet Again!"
[JIREN] So much effort, just to
keep a fallen ally in the ring.
That will do you no good.
Does the trust you
place in your friends
really make you so blind?
Trust in friends?
I think you're trying
to make my vomit.
If I need to pummel
him again, so be it.
He's just some extra insurance.
But I do intend to claim the
Super Dragon Balls for myself.
So if you're smart,
then the only one
you should be trying
to pummel is me.
I don't sense that astounding
power from you anymore.
Seems to me you've
lost your edge.
[JIREN grunts]
Here goes, Jiren!
You've had a taste of defeat,
and now you'll get
the full course!
Served up by yours truly!
[JIREN growls]
[FRIEZA, A17 grunt]
[FRIEZA grunts, yells]
[FRIEZA]
Hmph!
[BOTH grunting]
I can't believe how
incredible those two are.
[FRIEZA panting]
My, my. What's happened
to your stoic poker face?
You seem a bit winded.
Shut your mouth!
That hard outer shell of
strength has been cracked
and now you're quite
fragile, aren't you?
It's as though I can hear the
screaming in your tortured
and wounded soul.
I think you're terrified
of being weak and
helpless once again.
[JIREN grunts]
[gasps]
[JIREN]
You say I'm fragile.
That my "shell of strength"
has been cracked.
Well, let's see how fragile
you think I am now!
[FRIEZA grunts]
[groans]
Your rage is making you sloppy.
[JIREN groans]
This time you'll get more
than just a scratch.
I've learned your tricks!
[A17]
Wanna bet?
I didn't ask for help!
[A17 grunts]
[gasping]
No. This can't be.
[ALL gasping]
They got him.
They really did it.
[chuckles]
They're awesome,
that's for sure.
Both of 'em are.
Not too shabby, Android.
You didn't just slow him down,
you brought him to his knees.
[A17]
It was a risk I could take.
'Cause if I failed,
I knew you'd be
here to do the rest.
Now go finish the job.
Hmph. I've earned
the trust of a robot.
How'd I get so lucky...
[gasping]
Well, Jiren.
You did your best.
I know ya did.
[footsteps]
[FRIEZA] You no longer have
the nerve to look at me, do you?
What a shame.
I would have enjoyed watching
the expression on your face
as I delivered this final blow.
[FRIEZA]
Hm?
What are you doing, Jiren?!
Kneeling down at
your enemy's feet?
Is this honestly the way that
you want your fight to end?
Get up! Come on!
What an obnoxiously
loud friend you have.
[JIREN]
No. I don't have friends.
Why would you spend all those
years honing your strength,
rejecting everything
and everyone else,
just to surrender?
For the sake of your own pride,
keep fighting to the end!
Even if you no longer believe
in your own absolute power,
I have not lost faith.
And never will.
Jiren, you are the strongest.
No one is stronger than you.
Nothing could
make me doubt that.
[JIREN gasping]
Oh, please.
I really am going to wretch.
That's enough!
Uh!
[gasps]
Frieza, get out of there!
[JIREN growls, yells]
[BOTH]
Ha!
Keep pushing!
[FRIEZA]
Don't tell me what to do!
Raise your energy higher!
Hold on! You can't lose!
[GOKU grunting]
[screams]
[A17, FRIEZA grunting]
Away with you,
petulant vermin. Away!
[BOTH gasping]
[GOKU]
Sorry about that, you guys.
[FRIEZA, A17 gasp]
Didn't mean to leave you
like that, but I got this.
How the hell are you
still standing?
[GOKU]
I could ask you the same thing.
Me and Frieza can
take the lead now.
You can back us up 17, okay?
[FRIEZA]
Hmph. I don't need to share
the limelight with you
either, monkey.
[GOKU]
No, Frieza!
We've all pushed ourselves as
far as we can go on our own,
you know that.
The three of us need to do this
together to get this done.
Or our universe is doomed!
[JIREN]
So, Goku.
[GOKU]
Huh?
Once again, you have returned.
And once again you will fall!
[yelling]
[FRIEZA, GOKU, A17 yelping]
[SPECTATORS gasping]
Jiren's focusing an incredible
amount of energy now.
[VEGETA]
Damn it. He did it.
He's finally out
of his own head.
[GOKU]
Jiren is truly amazing.
He's gotten this strong
all on his own.
We still may not be
enough for him,
even with all three
of us teaming up.
[FRIEZA] You do remember your
promise, don't you, Goku?
To bring me back to life?
Come on, Frieza!
Will you keep your
word or won't you?
As long as you hold up
your end of the bargain
and help us win,
I'll hold up mine.
By now, you should know that
better than anyone, don't you?
Uh!
Don't you, Frieza?
[FRIEZA growling]
[FRIEZA] Hmph. That
sickening naiveté of yours
is what I quite
despise most of all.
But for my own self-interest,
I should probably thank you.
You guys done yet,
or you wanna hug too?
[FRIEZA]
Nothing would repulse me more.
[ALL yelling]
[yells]
♪♪
[FRIEZA, GOKU yell]
[JIREN grunts]
[BOTH grunt]
[ALL grunting]
Go go go go go the distance...
Frieza and Goku are actually
fighting side by side!
Fight fight in the ultimate
battle just for fun...
[JIREN screams]
[yelling]
Your strength is
awesome I can tell
And I'm into it
Wanna test my limits,
so let's go
Show me how hard you hit
Power growing,
boundaries breaking...
[JIREN yelling]
[GOKU groaning]
[groans]
[GOKU, FRIEZA grunt]
'Cause we both have
strength that won't stop...
I need you to throw me, Saiyan!
Huh? Oh, yeah!
...no way we'll give in
Fight fight in the
ultimate battle...
[GOKU]
Alleyoop!
[yelling]
Nothing to prove
Let your power
shine like the sun
Is he gonna take himself
out to get Jiren?
Would Frieza do that?
[JIREN growls]
[FRIEZA screams]
[FRIEZA screaming]
[GOKU yelling]
Go go go go go the distance...
[A17]
Do it!
Goku! Frieza!
[ALL]
Go!
[JIREN] This must be the secret
of the Seventh Universe.
The power of Trust.
[BOTH yelling]
[A17 gasping]
Uh!
[GROUP gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Jiren!
[groaning]
Ha, ha, ha! Way to go, Frieza.
Silence.
Don't make this worse
by thanking me, Saiyan.
I need no other gestures,
as long as you keep
your word to me, monkey.
Yeah. Consider it done.
[GRAND MINISTER]
Contestant Jiren is eliminated.
The Eleventh has been defeated,
and they will now be expunged.
[TOP]
Jiren...
We thank you.
You thank me?
I ignored you during
this whole Tournament.
My ambitions were my only goal.
[GOKU]
Jiren.
I know we just barely finished
the battle of our lives,
but I'm already hungry
for the next fight.
Maybe you don't want
to hear this, but...
I feel like we've gotten
stronger, together.
And I think that's worth a lot.
[GOKU grunts]
I hope to see you again, Jiren.
What an incredible warrior.
[GOKU]
Yeah.
[GRAND MINISTER]
Contestant 17.
You've prevailed.
What will you wish for?
Hmm...
[gasping]
Wait, are those...?
Ah! The Super
Dragon Balls. Heh.
[GRAND MINISTER]
Emoc htrof, enivid nogard,
dna tnarg ym shiw.
Peas and Carrots!
[ALL gasp]
[A17 grunting]
[GRAND MINISTER]
It is time, 17. Make your wish.
Is something wrong?
[ZENO]
He can ask for anything.
Yes, anything at all.
And he'll get it.
[BOTH]
What will it be?
Uh?
All of the universes that
have been erased...
I wanna bring them back.
Say what?!
[gasping]
What?!
[VEGETA]
Hmph!
[gasping]
You're sure that's
what you want?
Super sure?
I've got an island of
creatures to protect.
Can we move this along?
[GRAND MINISTER]
Desire neeb evah taht sesrevinu
eht lla erotser!
[SUPER DRAGON roars]
[ALL gasping]
Uh! What in the...?
What happened?!
[CAULIFLA]
Kale! I think it's okay!
We're alive! We're alive!
[KALE]
Caulifla!
You did it.
You made good on your promise.
Thank you, Master.
[CAULIFLA]
Cabba!
Come on, let's go train, and
reach Super Saiyan Three!
[CABBA]
Wait? You mean, right now?
Don't expect me to
thank you, Brother.
[TOP]
What's troubling you now?
The last thing Goku said
was that he hoped we
would meet again.
But I've spent most of my
life as a captive to my past.
I doubt I can build
connections with anyone.
[TOP] Jiren, how can someone
so strong be such a coward?
[JIREN gasps]
[TOP] In that last battle,
I watched you try to make good
on the faith we had put in you.
That moment you climbed
back on your feet.
Was that not the
start of something?
An actual connection
between you and us?
Maybe.
I say we should see them again,
and the next time we'll win.
Heh.
I agree.
[JIREN]
Until next time, Goku.
We shall meet again.
[A18]
17!
[A17]
Uh?
[KRILLIN]
Whoa, be careful!
You did it.
But you're sure that's okay?
What about your wish
for your family?
You wanted to take
that cruise trip, right?
[A17]
Don't be silly.
It's fine. I got to rescue
all those universes.
It would be a pretty jerk
move to leave them erased
like that just so I could
have a little family time.
Well, thanks for
making that choice.
Maybe you're
rubbing off on me.
[GOKU]
Hm?
I hate to say it,
but you two are becoming
more and more alike.
Eh?
[FRIEZA]
Can we wrap this up?
If it's all right
with you, Goku,
I'd like you to escort
me back to hell now.
What's the big rush? You've
still got plenty of time, right?
If staying here means
watching you nitwits
enjoy your happy ending,
I think I'd rather be tortured
by singing fairies.
[WHIS] Well, considering
how you've helped,
maybe I should give you
your happy ending, too.
Boop!
Uh?!
[ALL gasping]
Whoa, it's gone!
Wait, he's alive?!
Consider it a little gift
from Lord Beerus.
He said at the end
of the Tournament
you performed most admirably.
Hmph. Sure that's wise?
Because I have no intention
of changing my wicked ways.
[GOKU]
If you do act up,
I'll just put you down again.
Oh, good.
I can't wait to see you try.
[ZENOS]
Goku!
Yo, Zennies! We did it!
[ALL laughing]
That Tournament
was so much fun!
Fun and awesome!
I must admit,
I was not expecting
Android 17 to make
such a wish.
[GRAND MINISTER]
Well, our great Omni-Kings
predicted this would
be the outcome.
[ALL gasp]
Grand Minister!
They believed whichever warrior
made it to the end would have
enough virtue to show compassion
for the other universes,
and prove the whole cosmos
worthy of existence.
Wait, so what would
have happened
if the victor had made
some other wish instead?
A selfish wish would have been
viewed as a damning indictment.
And Their Majesties would
have eliminated all of reality.
[ALL gasping]
So in truth it was a challenging
game of survival for all.
And perhaps the
Grand Zenos believed
the challenge itself is
what would save them.
That through intense struggle
Goku and the others
could overcome their weaknesses.
And show that
mortals can change.
[ZENOS] Hey, Goku! So what
should we play next?
--[BEERUS screams]
--[GOKU] Let's see...
I'm terribly sorry,
Grand Zenos.
But this poor mortal is just
too exhausted to think!
For now, we will have to
take our leave, Grand Zenos!
Ladies and gentlemen
of the Seventh,
your fighting was exemplary.
And of course, so was
your life-saving wish.
[SUPREME KAI, ELDER KAI, BEERUS]
Thank you, sire.
[ZENOS] Hey, Goku, will
you come visit us again?
Yeah! Of course I will!
Keep it real, Zennies!
--[ZENOS gasping]
--[GOKU laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
[ZENOS]
Yeah!
[GOKU, ZENOS laughing]
♪♪
[NARRATOR] And so, at long last,
the great Tournament of Power,
which decided the fates
of all the universes,
came to an end,
and Goku and his fellow warriors
returned to their daily lives.
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
My loyal subjects.
Your patience was not in vein.
For as you can see...
...the emperor of this
universe is back.
[VEGETA, GOKU grunting]
Don't hold back on me, Kakarot.
Where's that Ultra
Instinct of yours?
[GOKU]
I can't do it.
What?!
Guess I was lucky, getting
pushed to it at the Tournament,
'cause now I can't repeat it.
Oh? Then when I find
an even greater power
you're going to be
in real trouble.
Oh, yeah? Dream on, Vegeta!
Oh, shut up!
You think I'm ever going to let
you get ahead of me again?
[GOKU grunts]
Bring it! Heh!
We'll never stop
getting stronger.
[yells]
Of course we won't!
Only a fool would put limits on
the strength of the Saiyan race!
[NARRATOR] This is the journey
that will never end.
The struggle to push
beyond all limits,
and redefine the
meaning of power.
New and mightier
foes will arise,
new adventures will begin,
and Goku and his fellow
warriors will be ready.
Until then, we bid you farewell.
Whirling all around
and then back again
The song that connects you
to the heavens
Strength that goes
beyond all measure
Expanding to a beat
that won't end
The meteors fall like rain drops
Astrological tears
from my eyelids
A strong emotion
from deep within
Has been awakened
A spark of possibility
Shines softly like a star
in the night sky
A wish from long
ago now shoots by
And I'm awakened
A never-ending melody,
so enchanting
You're always the one
who makes me tremble
The meteors keep falling down
Surging right into my heart