♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the Tournament of Power
heated up as Goku
was targeted by
a group of warriors
from the Eleventh Universe.
[TROOPERS]
And we are the Pride Troopers!
[NARRATOR] In the wrong place
at the wrong time,
Caulifla and Kale were
swept up in the attack,
and things looked bleak
for the Saiyan duo. Until...
[KALE]
I just hate everything about...
...the way I am!
[NARRATOR] Kale came through
for her sworn sister,
but there's no time to rest,
for the battle rages on, now!
[NARRATOR]
"The Power of Love Explodes?
The 2nd Universe's
Witchy Warriors!"
[ZENO]
There's Universe Two.
[FUTURE ZENO]
Universe Three.
[ZENO]
Universe Four.
[FUTURE ZENO]
Universe Six.
[ZENO]
Seven...
[FUTURE ZENO]
Nine...
--[ZENO] Ten.
--[FUTURE ZENO] Eleven!
[ZENO] Hmm, they have
lost many fighters.
[FUTURE ZENO]
Very many.
Uh? Sanka! Sous!
I think it's time we showed
off our true power.
How about it, girls?
Thanks, a lot 17.
18. I really appreciate
the help.
You can thank us later--
when this is over!
[GOKU] Now, where are you,
Jiren? You owe me a fight.
My fellow warriors!
Attention please!
[TOP]
Hm?
[GOKU]
Uh?!
Uh...?
[GIRLS laughing]
[KRILLIN]
Hm? What's going on?
Okay, girls. Are you both ready?
This is a fitting stage for us.
We certainly need
a high platform.
It's happening!
And now lovely flowers shall
bloom over the battlefield!
Huh? What is she talkin' about?
[CHAMPA] This is combat,
not a garden party!
[ALL]
Huh?
[VEGETA]
What is this crap? Just fight.
All the way from
beautiful Universe Two,
we are Brianne de Chateau!
I'm Sanka Coo!
And I'm Sous Roas!
Let us blossom!
And let us sing out the song
of love and victory!
[ALL]
The song of love and victory!
Now to transform.
[SANKA COO, SOUS ROAS]
Yeah!
[BRIANNE]
Formation!
Brianne! Brianne!
Bri-brianne!
[SANKA COO]
Formation!
Sansan! Kakkun!
San-kakkun!
[SOUS ROAS]
Formation!
Su-su! Suro-suro!
Su-su-ro-suro!
[GOKU]
Uh...?
[gasps]
Awesome, looks like maybe
they're powering up!
Well, in that case,
I wish they'd end the song and
dance and just get on with it.
You bite your tongue.
Show respect for the ritual.
These ladies are summoning
their warrior spirit!
[BOTH]
Whoa!
[GOKU laughing]
Uh?
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
[PER gasping]
Who did that?! How rude!
17, why did you have to do that?
They had left themselves
wide open.
Is there a problem?
So were just you not
paying attention or what?
They were getting
ready to transform
and then you had to ruin it.
Yeah, so?
[BRIANNE]
Hey, you!
Now look here! There's a
meaning to every aspect
of our transformation ritual!
You can't just interrupt
us in the middle of it!
[TOP]
Yes, that's right!
[TOP grunting]
When a warrior strikes
a pose, that's justice!
You, sir, violated the code!
That's true. If we're
gonna do this,
don't you wanna fight 'em
at full power?
Huh?
[GOKU chuckles]
[BRIANNE]
Thank you for understanding.
[TOP grunts]
[BRIANNE] Though that doesn't
mean we'll go easy on you!
[TOP] Of course!
Pose as hard as you like!
[GOKU]
Yeah, don't hold back!
We wanna see what
you're really made of!
--[GIRLS] As you wish!
--[GOKU] Cool!
That imbecile!
You should always
crush your opponent
before they have
a chance to go all out!
Clearly you don't know Goku.
That's not his style.
[clears throat]
Once again, let's start
at the beginning.
And now lovely flowers shall
bloom over the battlefield!
Are they really starting
from the top?
[CHAMPA] We have to sit
through this again?!
All the way from
beautiful Universe Two,
we are Brianne de Chateau!
Along with Sanka Coo!
And I'm Sous Roas!
Let us blossom,
and let us sing out the song
of love and victory!
[ALL]
The song of love and victory!
Now to transform for real.
[SANKA COO, SOUS ROAS]
Yeah!
[BRIANNE]
Formation!
Brianne! Brianne!
Bri-brianne!
[SANKA COO]
Formation!
Sansan! Kakkun!
San-kakkun!
[SOUS ROAS]
Formation!
Su-su! Suro-suro!
Su-su-ro-suro!
[BRIANNE]
Happiness to one and all!
I send you my love!
Ribrianne!
The thunder of the wild!
And the roar of love! Kakunsa!
The strike of love,
with dreams and magic!
Roasie!
[ALL]
Transformation complete!
This is the ultimate form
of Universe Two's
glamorous champions!
While our mortal level
may not be the highest,
the power of our love is the
greatest in all the cosmos!
[GIRLS]
Mwah!
[BOTH gasp, cheer]
[ALL]
Ahhh...
Woo hoo!
Oh boy, those young ladies just
got at least ten times prettier!
I don't know.
I kinda think they were cuter
before they transformed.
Well, beauty is in the eye
of the beholder, after all.
Preferences differ
from person to person.
And universe to universe.
[TOP]
Well done! That is justice!
Huh. I guess there's all
kinds of transformations.
Yeah, but will you show us
what you can actually do?
All right. Here we go!
[ALL]
May our feelings...
...find their way to you!
[BRIANNE]
Love!
[SANKA COO, SOUS ROAS]
Ha!
[BRIANNE laughing]
[sniffing]
What a putrid odor.
[sighs]
[GANOS screams]
[TOP grunts]
Must not inhale.
The light of love.
Once intoxicated by its
sweet aroma, it's all over.
You'll be unable to resist,
utterly consumed by
its awesome power.
[RUMSSHI] Aww, come on!
Snap out of it, you guys!
You're embarrassing me!
[chuckles]
Looks like this technique's
got some real bite to it.
How is our team?
Oh! They appear to be
holding up quite well.
One way or another,
they're all staying strong
in the face of this
assault. Even...
[WHIS] ...the one we're
most concerned about.
Thanks, Puar.
I just want you to know,
you didn't become
that beautiful,
spunky girl for nothing!
Master Roshi!
Excellent self-control, sir!
[ROSHI] I think we've lost our
foothold here, though.
Change of plans, guys.
It's time for us to split up
and fight on our own.
[PICCOLO, TIEN]
Right!
Just try not to get sloppy and
tossed off the edge, Old Man!
Right back atcha!
Hope you enjoy our
heartfelt gifts of love!
[BRIANNE laughs]
[BEERUS growls]
You mean to tell me
Universe Two was hiding that up
their sleeves this whole time?
They may not look that tough,
but they've turned this whole
competition upside down.
Precisely. Beneath their lovely
exterior lies great strength.
And now, let it wash
over all of you!
Huh?!
[VEGETA] Heh. Really?
That's your full power?
After such an
excruciating buildup,
I was expecting more from you
than just a light spritzing
of love potion.
My aren't we impatient?
That was just
a little amuse-bouche.
To whet your appetite
for the main course.
Universe Two... Attack!
[VEGETA yelling]
[BRIANNE yells]
[BRIANNE, VEGETA grunting]
[BRIANNE laughs]
[BRIANNE]
Take this!
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA]
Well, well, well.
So your transformation wasn't
just for show after all.
If you liked that, you'll
love this! Heh, heh!
Fireball of Me!
Maidenly Explosion!
[BRIANNE]
Maidenly Rush!
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA grunts]
Uh.
What was that wretched feeling?
I hate to bail out, but ew!
[DYRASEM laughs]
[PICCOLO, DYRASEM]
Huh?
[BRIANNE]
Outta my way!
[DYRASEM groaning]
[PICCOLO]
Huh?!
[DYRASEM screaming]
And Contestant Dyrasem
of the Tenth is eliminated.
[RUMSSHI] You weren't even her
target, just collateral damage!
You're a disgrace
to our universe!
A happy accident!
Maidenly victory number one!
[ZENO]
Where's Dyrasem...?
Oh, there!
[BOTH]
Ha!
That maiden's amazing!
Very amazing!
[HELES] Hmph. I hope you
enjoyed that display of
"Ribrianne's Maidenly
Explosion Strike of Love."
Now then, who's next?
[SOUS ROAS]
Ya! Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha...
Goku's losing ground, and fast!
Ah, yes, dear Roasie.
Yatchaina-ken master!
Using this martial arts style,
her jabs becomes sharper and
stronger the more she strikes!
[GOKU]
Uh?
[SOUS ROAS]
Ya! Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha...
[SOUS ROAS yelling]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU groans]
[HELES]
Delicate, and yet, intense,
her attacks change constantly,
just like a young girl's heart.
Yatchaina!
And last up!
[SANKA COO yells]
[SANKA COO yelling]
[SANKA COO grunting]
[yells]
[HELES]
Kakunsa is a beast warrior
with passionate
animal instincts.
She's a confidant hunter
who knows what she wants,
and always catches her prey.
Admit it, I got my claws
in you, and fangs, too.
I've got you in my sights now!
I'll teach you to mess
with our transformation!
I will make you pay!
She's bouncing off the rubble
like a freakin' pinball!
Clever girl, taking that
torn-up platform there
and using it to her advantage.
Clawing, biting, bounding
from peak to peak.
Seems she truly is
a creature of the wild.
Yes indeed she is.
And this ring's jagged wasteland
is the perfect setting
for her to show off
her savage moves.
There's no way to escape from
her relentless, untamed attacks.
Trying to evade her is
an exercise in futility.
The stamina of a beast
warrior never lets up.
At least not until her prey
exhausts all of its energy.
Well, this is going
rather poorly.
[SANKA COO]
Heh.
[SANKA COO] I've got this prey
in my trap now!
[gasps]
[BOTH gasping]
[HELES]
Is that a barrier?
Poor thing. You really
thought you had me, huh?
[SANKA COO growls] You were just
pretending to be worn out?
[A17] Guess my stamina's
not so bad, either.
I laid out a trap and you
charged right into it.
[SANKA COO growls] You were
supposed to be my quarry!
It turns out you were
the quarry all along.
[SANKA COO groaning]
[screams]
Bye now.
[SANKA COO screams]
Oh yeah! That girl
is outta here!
[BIKAL grunts]
[SANKA COO yells]
Nice save!
It's nothing. You were amazing!
[SANKA COO] I couldn't
have done it without you.
Thank you for the assist.
[BIKAL] There's no need
for you to thank me.
It's my duty. I would do
anything for you.
[SANKA COO]
Oh, Bikal!
[BIKAL]
Oh, Kakunsa!
Wow, what a truly
beautiful sight to behold!
That's the power of love!
When you're feeling it,
nothing can stop you!
This is hardly
the time or place.
I thought for certain she'd
be out of the ring for good.
Me, too.
Those winged warriors can be
a real pain in the patootie.
[KRILLIN]
C'mon, 17.
[footsteps]
Do you need something?
Just noticed you were
having some trouble.
Do you want a little help?
[A17]
Don't worry about me.
Fighting that little beast
made me start thinking about
the animals I left behind
on the island,
and so I let my guard down.
Now to fight like I mean it.
[BIKAL] All right, I'm off to go
see if the others need any help.
Okay. I think I can take
down this prey on my own.
[BIKAL]
Happy hunting, Kakunsa.
[gasps, screams]
What?!
[BIKAL yelps]
[BIKAL screams]
Oh, Bikal!
It appears that she's in no
condition to continue fighting.
[GRAND MINISTER]
Bikal from the Second Universe
is out of bounds,
and therefore, eliminated.
[FUTURE ZENO]
Boop!
[growling] You bastard!
How dare you hurt my Bikal!
The flyers ruin it
for the rest of us,
so that's why I took care
of your friend first.
[SANKA COO] Why you lousy,
no-good, dirty, rotten,
arrogant, smug, insensitive...
Can I offer some maidenly
assistance? Where'd you--?
Stay away!
That wicked creature
is my quarry!
He's going to pay for
what he did to Bikal!
Oh Kakunsa. As you wish.
You've got love on your side!
[yells]
That move may have
worked on me earlier,
but now I've got
you pinned down!
Huh?
[SANKA COO]
What? But how?!
He's using the light
as a foothold?
That was the entire point
of his last attack. Yeah!
[CHAMPA]
Is he even allowed to do that?
[ZENOS laughing]
Looks like it to me.
[yells]
This fight has been instructive.
I do appreciate the lesson.
[SANKA COO grunts, screams]
[SOUS ROAS]
Uh?! Kakunsa!
Hey, not bad, 17.
But when we were
sparring on your island,
you didn't use anything
like that move,
which means you were
probably holding out on me,
isn't that right?
[GOKU laughs] I bet you've got
all kinds of secret powers
you're keeping hidden from us.
[GRAND MINISTER]
Kakunsa of the Second Universe
has been eliminated.
[ZENO]
Boop!
Yeah! Nice work!
Well, I'll be, he took two
of 'em out, back-to-back!
Yeah, that sounds
like 17, all right!
[SANKA COO growls]
[BRIANNE] It wasn't enough to
interrupt our transformation.
You had to knock out
Bikal and Kakunsa, too.
I swear, you will pay for that!
Maidenly anger!
[NARRATOR]
One after another,
warriors are falling
by the wayside.
Now, only 39 minutes remain to
decide the fate of the Cosmos.
The Tournament
of Power continues,
next time on Dragon Ball Super.
When the time has come
to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever in my mind
as I look up to the sky
I was watching you
from your left side
Was trying to get
a good look at your face
The tears in your eyes;
were you laughing or crying?
Your long hair in the way
Blocking the thoughts inside
When the time has
come to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever I will wait,
for the light to show the way
For us to meet again
[GOHAN]
Uh, hi there. It's me, Gohan.
Hey, Piccolo, we should
take on the fighters
from the Tenth
Universe together.
Huh? I don't get it.
None of my attacks are landing.
But I'm not giving up!
I'll unleash all of my power
if that's what it takes
to claim victory!
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Gohan, Get Ruthless!
Showdown with
the 10th Universe!"
Make sure you
don't miss it, okay?