♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the Tournament of Power
is almost here!
Eight universes will fight!
The losers will be destroyed!
Goku has begun to assemble
a team of ten contestants,
starting with
Krillin and Number 18.
[GOHAN]
Not so fast, guys.
[NARRATOR]
But first, Gohan wanted
to test Krillin's strength.
[KRILLIN]
Solar Flare!
[GOHAN groaning]
I call that one the
Hundred Times Solar Flare.
Let's push each other
and get better together.
With a little creativity,
and a lotta hard work,
we can make all our moves
a hundred times stronger,
and win the Tournament of Power.
That's a good point.
I really do lack experience.
Oh no, I almost forgot!
Hey, Number 18?
Do you know where
I can find Number 17?
You're kidding me, aren't you?
Dende keeps an eye
on the whole planet.
I bet he knows where
to find Android 17.
Oh, yeah, I forgot about Dende.
C'mon, gang! We gotta fly!
[NARRATOR]
The hunt continues, now!
"The Universes Go Into Action--
Each With Their Own Motives."
All right, Dad.
I'm gonna head off
and talk to Piccolo now.
Oh, yeah, good thinkin'.
That shouldn't be too hard.
Knowing Piccolo, he'll agree
to enter the tournament
before you can even
finish asking him.
Of course. He is a martial
artist at heart, after all.
I'm sure he can't resist
the chance to fight
the strongest warriors
in the cosmos.
Honestly, I gotta say
I kinda feel the same way.
Well, tell him
I said "hi," okay.
Will do. I'll see ya later, Dad.
All right then.
I'd better pick up the pace
and get to the Lookout.
[GOKU]
Huh? What was that?
What the--?
Ugh. He sure is getting
amped up, isn't he?
Greetings, colleagues.
Welcome to the
Eleventh Universe's
Sacred World of the Kais.
[GOWASU]
Mmm.
Now then,
my fellow Supreme Kais.
I humbly request that
you keep this proposal
by Grand Zeno a secret from the
inhabitants of your universes.
If you don't mind.
[GOWASU]
Yes, that's fine by me.
But hold on. At the moment,
we appear to be missing
the Supreme Kai
of the Seventh Universe.
That's because I chose
not to invite him.
This whole Tournament of Power
nonsense was suggested
by one of his subjects,
after all.
Enough! Get to the point!
Chit-chatting in
a futile quorum like this
is a waste of our time!
Just what are you up to?
[CAE] Actually, I was hoping to
discuss our present situation.
And like I just said,
we can't change it,
so why should we bother?
I'm too busy trying to
put a team together!
--[HUWA] Fuwahhh.
--[CAE] Hm?
What to do? What to do?
Fuwawa. What to do?
Aw, quit your moaning,
Sixth Universe.
What's there to be
concerned about?
This sounds like fun to me!
A bare-knuckle brawl!
And that's something the Second
Universe can win easily!
[laughing]
[EA] With all due respect
to my brawny colleague
from the Second Universe,
perhaps you are
unaware of the superior
intellectual prowess
of the Third Universe?
[PER] Lotta good
smarts'll do ya, brainiac.
It's called the
Tournament of Power!
Sheer brute force is all
that's gonna matter! Ha-ha!
Ugh, for goodness' sake.
You musclebound cretins
exhaust me.
What was that?
Oh gee, I'm sorry. Should I
stick to smaller words?
[CAE]
Now, now.
How rude! I think I'm insulted!
Well, you should be!
[EA, PER growl]
Calm down, both of you.
And act like Kais!
[EA, PER gasp]
[KUR laughing]
What a war of words.
How dreadfully unseemly.
As I was saying...
We should approach Grand Zeno
and ask him to
reconsider this contest.
I propose that with one voice,
we Supreme Kais request
each of our universes
be granted a short reprieve
from this annihilation,
and in that time,
we shall achieve
the mortal level of seven
the Grand Zeno desires.
Is this the ludicrous scheme
that you called us
here to discuss?
What good will begging do us?
The Omni-King has already
made up his mind!
I doubt it'll work.
And if we upset him,
it's entirely possible
that he'll simply do away
with all of us
right there on the spot.
Now, I, too, am quite busy,
so if that's all.
What to do? What to do?
Hwah. Just what to do?
Sadly, I must agree.
Then they leave me
little choice.
I had hoped to forge a mutually
beneficial agreement
so that all eight
universes might survive,
but if they won't help,
only one will be spared.
[CAE] And while it gives me
no pleasure to say this,
it's clear that
my Eleventh Universe
will be the lone survivor.
After all, we do have
the strongest warriors
in the cosmos.
[GOKU]
Wow, they're really goin' at it.
[BUU grunting]
[MR. SATAN] All right, Buu,
let's go again!
[GOKU] Hey! Is this
part of Buu's training?
[MR. SATAN]
Oh, hey there, Goku!
Buu was pretty worked up
after the Zeno Expo,
so we dove right in.
He hasn't rested at all
since we've been back.
Too busy getting
his body into shipshape.
Is shipshape a new form?
I'm just sayin',
he might give you
a run for your money!
[GOKU]
Hm? Whoa!
Wow! He is in good shape!
He's got a good coach, so...
Oh. Look, Goku!
Yay! Buu have lotsa fun
playing with doggy-man.
Doggy-man strong!
Buu meet more fun guys
at big contest.
And lucky Buu get to
play with them all.
Buu can't wait!
Yeah, I can't wait either!
Well, whaddaya say, Goku?
How'd you like to mix it up
a little bit with Buu right now?
For practice.
You bet. I was just about to
suggest the same thing myself.
[MR. SATAN] All right,
if either of you go outside
the perimeter of my estate,
then you lose the match.
Got it? Begin!
[laughs]
[GOKU]
'Kay. Let's go! Haha!
[BUU laughing]
[BUU grunts]
That was awesome, Buu!
You didn't just
boost your speed,
you boosted your power, too!
[BUU chuckles]
Yeah! Buu strong!
Buu will clobber everyone!
[MR. SATAN] No, Buu!
You can't clobber these people!
You gotta find a way to
push 'em outta the ring to win!
[BUU]
Buu no kill anyone?
That's right. You can't.
If you kill anybody,
you're disqualified.
Oh. Then Buu do this!
[yelling]
[GOKU grunting]
[BUU laughing]
Hm!
[GOKU grunting]
Trying to force me out with all
these blasts isn't gonna work!
[BUU]
Hmm... Hm!
[GOKU grunting]
[BUU]
He-heh!
[grunts]
Ringout! That's my boy, Buu!
You won the fight big time!
Oh yeah!
Ow! Man, I didn't expect that.
Nice job! That was
so amazing, Buu!
Sneaking up on me while
my vision was blocked,
and then shoving me
out of bounds.
Oh, and distracting me with
that volley of energy blasts
was a brilliant move!
I'm really impressed, guys!
[BOTH chuckle]
Y'know, you really do
have a remarkable talent
for fighting, Buu.
[MR. SATAN] Just to be clear,
you will try to not fall
out of bounds so easily
in the real tournament, right?
[GOKU] Of course. I'm learning
a lot from all this sparring.
Well, I'm glad
we could help you out.
I wish I could be there for ya.
We're all counting
on you to win.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
It'll all be fine.
Oh, and 18 is in.
We got her on board,
just like you suggested.
Oh, good. She is a toughy.
That cost me a fortune.
And as we speak, Gohan is off
trying to recruit Piccolo too.
Hey, it sounds like you're
making some excellent progress
building the team.
That's awesome!
Well, I gotta track down
Number 17 now
and see if he'll join us.
Thanks for sparring with me,
Buu! That was fun!
Yeah!
[GOKU]
Later!
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
[yawns]
Oh boy. Buu sleepy.
Buu need night-night.
Yeah. Well, you've been
pushing yourself so hard
this whole time, Buu.
C'mon, buddy, let's get you
in bed so you can rest.
[yawns]
Wish I could, too, but I
don't think I'll be able
to rest too easy. Not till we
win the Tournament of Power.
[MALE ATTENDANT 85A]
Mister Top. Welcome back.
[TOP]
Take good care of her.
Yes, of course, sir.
[BAR PATRONS chatting]
[TOP growls]
[CASSERALE]
What's wrong?
Why the long face, sir?
[TOP]
General.
[CASSERALE] You're a hero,
protector of this universe.
Our leader.
You're a warrior who all
these people look up to.
Someone who they turn to
when they need reassurance.
But with such a grim
look on your face,
you're going to cause
widespread panic.
[TOP]
Mmm.
Maybe there's reason to panic.
Unless we battle flawlessly,
they'll be doomed.
I heard that you accompanied
Lord Vermoud on his journey
when he was summoned to have
an audience with Grand Zeno.
Tell me everything
that happened.
[beeping]
[BOTH gasp]
[DISPO]
A mysterious space creature
has landed on Planet Daldon
and is causing
massive devastation!
Requesting immediate
backup! Come in!
Leader?
[TOP]
Mm. Get us there, quickly!
[CHAMPA]
Hey, listen up!
I understand all the
Supreme Kais got together
a little while ago.
You other Destroyers
wouldn't happen to be
plotting some kinda
funny business at the
Tournament, now would you?
[RUMUSH]
Heh.
We would never do anything
as ugly as that.
[SIDRA]
Mm.
[VERMOUD]
Hm.
[laughing]
As if we would dare to cheat!
If we were to get caught,
Grand Zeno would
surely eliminate us.
[CHAMPA]
Hmmm.
[MOSCO beeping]
Lord Mosco is asking why is it
that you haven't invited
the Seventh Universe's
Destroyer to join us here.
Indeed. I would surely
like to know that as well.
[CHAMPA grumbles]
[QUITELA chuckles]
Because the Seventh
is the home to the mortal
who caused this problem
in the first place.
That one who calls himself Goku.
That's why Beerus
is on the outs.
[chuckling]
Distinguished guests,
with due respect,
you are in fact
all indebted to Goku.
For if he had not
suggested the so-called
Tournament of Power
to the Omni-King,
then all of the universes
with subpar Mortal Levels
would have already
been eliminated.
But thanks to Goku,
you have a chance
to earn yourselves a reprieve.
In debt to Goku?
I won't hear of it!
His conduct at the Expo--
it was beyond detestable!
[RUMUSH]
I must concur.
The irreverent way
he addresses the Omni-Kings
would be too familiar from
us gods, let alone mortals.
And it cannot be allowed!
Of course I know it's wrong,
yet still I find the man
to be oddly fetching.
[VERMOUD chuckles]
It's a shame
for the rest of you,
but it doesn't really matter
to me since no one else
can match the Eleventh's team.
Not when we have
the Pride Troopers,
led by the legendary Top.
[ARAGHNE growls]
[MALE DORAKIYAN 85A laughing]
Pay attention!
We, the Dorakiyans,
will be taking over this planet,
effective immediately!
[laughing]
[DISPO]
Oh, no you won't!
[ARAGHNE grunting]
[MALE DORAKIYAN 85A] Oh, you're
pretty speedy, aren't you?
Well, it's gonna take more than
fancy dance moves to stop us!
[ARAGHNE roars]
[MALE DORAKIYAN 85A]
We'll crush you Pride Troopers,
you bumbling batch
of bush-league brawlers!
Don't you dare diss
the Pride Troopers!
[ARAGHNE groans]
Huh?
[MALE DORAKIYAN 85A laughing]
Did you really think
you could stop us that easily?
Sadly for you,
this is farewell.
[ARAGHNE growling]
[ARAGHNE groans]
[MALE DORAKIYAN 85A]
What the--?
[TOP]
Halt, evil doer!
We are not going to let you
get away with this!
[MALE DORAKIYAN 85A]
Who's there?
Hello, Dispo! Sorry we're late.
Leader! And the General!
[MALE DORAKIYAN 85A]
Ugh! You called in
your fellow Pride Troopers?
I sure am glad you two are here.
I could use the help.
[ARAGHNE growls]
--[TOP] Here we go!
--[DISPO, CASSERALE] All right!
The warrior of freedom,
I am Top!
The warrior of
sonic speed, I'm Dispo!
The warrior of force,
Casserale!
[ALL] The light that keeps
the peace in the universe!
We are the magnificent
Pride Troopers!
And that light will now
purge this darkness!
[MALE DORAKIYAN 85A]
Uuh! You Pride Troopers
are such party
poopers! Get them!
--[ARAGHNE growls]
--[TOP yells]
[TOP]
Justice Flash!
[BOTH]
Double Cannon Maximum!
[ARAGHNE groans]
[MALE DORAKIYAN 85A]
Uuh! That's impossible!
Araghne can't be defeated! Aah!
For those who invade
sovereign worlds,
we offer zero leniency!
[MALE DORAKIYAN 85A yells]
Listen up, Dorakiyan!
And heed my words!
As long as we stand guard,
the brilliant light of freedom
will never be extinguished!
[DISPO] Really?
The stakes are that high?
This Tournament of Power,
it sounds like a nightmare.
The end of the whole
universe as we know it
is not something
to take lightly.
Hm. I agree. Which is why
we'll need the missing member
of the Pride Troopers.
I believe that he is
off training on
another planet right now.
That's true--we won't be able
to win this tournament
without Jiren.
Mm. We have no choice
but to interrupt his training.
Yo!
--Goku!
--Long time no see. Welcome.
[GOKU] Wow, I leave you
alone for a little bit
and you just keep getting
bigger and bigger, dude.
Hey, now!
Show him some respect!
It's all right.
So what brought you here, Goku?
I'm guessing it has
something to do with
Grand Zeno's big tournament.
What? You know about that?
Well, Supreme Kai and
the Destroyer stopped by here
earlier and I may have
overheard a few things.
So, um, you're sure I can
leave the job of
putting a team together to you?
[laughing]
I do have some experience.
In that case, I'm asking you--
no, begging you
to please do this for me.
Well, don't beg!
Pull yourself together,
you're our Supreme Kai
for goodness sake!
You can at least pretend
like you have a spine!
I'm sorry, I will try
to pretend, sir.
So, Lord Champa, where would
you like to begin our search?
Oh, I think you know where.
You've gotta fight
Saiyans with Saiyans.
Cabba it is, then.
[VADOS] It's nice to see you
again, Mister Cabba.
Pardon the intrusion,
but we'd like
to request your
assistance once more.
Hey, punk! I need someone
stronger than you
for this battle! I want Saiyans,
do you hear me?
Bring me more Saiyans!
[PICCOLO]
Yeah?
I knew that I could
find you here.
Look, Piccolo.
I need to ask a favor.
[PICCOLO]
I've been anticipating this.
I'm gonna take that
neglected body of yours,
and whip it into shape.
Good.
[GOKU] If you already
know what's goin' on,
that speeds things up.
Time's running out. So, can you
please tell me where 17 is?
Sure. I've kept tabs
on him for some time.
He lives on a large island
in the south.
Do you want me
to show you the way?
That'd be awesome, thanks!
[NARRATOR] The Seventh
Universe's team is
coming together quickly,
while the other universes'
strategies are starting
to fall into place.
Which one will
ultimately prove victorious?
Only 37 hours remain until
the Tournament of Power begins.
Next time on Dragon Ball Super!
Boogie Back!
Wish we had better timing
To explore this attraction
Put on a smile, it's showtime
And I'm just playing a part
Let's get lost in the rhythm,
dancing dancing heart
Head over heels
I'm falling falling down
(Boogie Back!)
My heartbeat
keeps growing faster
Every step that I take
brings me back to you
(Boogie Back!)
Give me happy ever after
Let the dream
of our love come true
Boogie Back!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Oh, look, I found you!
You are Android 17, right?
Anyway, I'm glad
our universe still has
someone as fierce as you around.
Though, I'd better
spar with you,
just to see how strong you are.
Whoa, who are those guys?
Stay out of our way!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"First Time Exchanging Blows!
Android 17 vs. Goku!!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?