♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super.
The Tournament
of Power raged on,
with five teams still
fighting desperately
to stop the annihilation
of their universes.
Goku challenged Jiren
of the Eleventh Universe,
who seemed to be the strongest
fighter of them all.
But despite the Saiyan's mighty
effort, he fell into his own
exploding Spirit Bomb,
and appeared to be defeated.
[NARRATOR] As the warriors
and Gods of the Seventh
were seized with despair,
a blinding light filled the
ring, and Goku rematerialized,
his body glowing from the light
of a brand new power.
It's so wonderful!
I hoped for this.
But I have to admit,
I wasn't sure
if the Saiyan would ever
be able to achieve it.
[BEERUS growls]
Autonomous Ultra Instinct.
[NARRATOR] Goku's ascension
was a marvel to all,
but when he couldn't sustain the
new level, Jiren cast him aside,
leaving him at the mercy
of another old foe.
[FRIEZA] My, my, doesn't this
feel familiar?
It's like Namek all over again.
[NARRATOR] "An Extra-
Dimensional Ultimate Battle!
Hit vs. Jiren!"
[FRIEZA] Seems you lack
the power to scurry away.
Making this infinitely easier.
You wouldn't.
[FRIEZA] Luckily,
I've found this blind spot.
No one can see
what happens here.
Shall we? No sense in delaying
what must be done.
[GOKU screams]
[gasps]
My power...
[FRIEZA chuckles]
I've shared some of my energy.
Only a small pittance.
But enough.
Now you can move,
even in your sad state.
I'd say we're all
square, Saiyan.
[FRIEZA] You see, I still need
you to be my little work-monkey.
Most of all I want
you to deal with
that anomalous creature Jiren.
Heh, heh. I'm not about
to try that myself.
So please, do the best
you can, won't you?
Oh, I almost forgot.
Tell me, Goku.
Did you hear the Gods a-chatter?
When you were sparkling so?
No. Why?
Seems that power level you
demonstrated has a name.
Well, among divine
individuals, anyway.
Autonomous Ultra Instinct.
I just thought you should know.
"Autonomous Ultra Instinct"?
[grunts]
If I could reach that again,
could I defeat Jiren?
[growls]
[JIREN grunts]
[groans]
[JIREN grunting]
[JIREN]
Time skipping.
[ZENOS]
Ooh!!
[ZENO] That red-suited fighter
is super strong.
I like him very much.
His name is Jiren.
Yes, and the other one
he's fighting is named Hit.
[HIT] So these are the attacks
Goku was up against.
Now I've faced them, too.
And I must say...
they are intense.
Tell me, assassin.
Do you really think
you can stop me?
Like I said, that's my job.
[TOP]
Hit surprises me.
He still stands.
That's impressive.
[HIT grunts]
[HIT growls]
[JIREN grunts]
What was that?
Hit is able to use the time
he accumulates by skipping
to create a small
pocket dimension,
which he then slips
into to avoid attack
or confuse his foe,
while leaving
a phantom image of himself
in normal space-time.
It is usually most effective.
I don't believe it--Hit slipped
into another dimension
and Jiren still saw it
coming and got away?!
He's formidable,
to say the least, sir.
[HIT groans]
[JIREN grunting]
[yells]
[HIT groans]
[JIREN]
Huh?!
[HIT groaning]
His counters are flawless.
Even against my Time Skips.
[JIREN yelling]
[HIT groans]
Despite all his noble efforts,
Hit has failed to
land a single blow.
Oh, my! It's awful, what to do?
[BELMOD]
Hmph.
Jiren is not fooled by
any of his deception.
No! Clearly not! So why does
Hit keep Time Skipping?!
[FUWA]
Ohh! What to do? What to do?
Indeed. Hit is a smart fighter.
If the Skips don't work,
why won't he change tactics?
How many times must you fail?
End this futility.
[HIT] And how many times
must I tell you?
I will do my job until the end.
Jiren is amazing.
His defenses are airtight.
But it looks like Hit's cooking
up a new plan to stop him.
[BOTH yelling]
What the--?
[PILINA grunts]
If you guys are lookin'
for a fight...
...we've got you covered.
[SAONEL, PILINA grunt]
Look at that.
A "Namekian," huh?
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH yelling]
[BRIANNE grunting]
[VEGETA growls]
[yells]
[BRIANNE yelps]
[BRIANNE yells]
Don't expect that absurd
attack to work on me!
[BRIANNE screams]
[VEGETA grunting]
[yelling]
[SOUS ROAS yelling]
My brave and beautiful Roasie!
My love will keep
you safe, Ribrianne!
Not for long!
[yelling]
[VEGETA]
Ugh. Running again?
Where are you?!
Hey, are you gonna be okay?
I'm fine. But do you
really think we can win?
Uh?
The Second is strong.
But we're quickly losing ground
to the other universes.
I think I'm frightened!
You Fool!
[BRIANNE gasps]
Uh. Roasie?
Love never quits!
Never tires! You know that!
Love shields us,
and love conquers all!
[gasping] The power of love.
Of course you're
right, Roasie!
If I don't believe
in love's power,
then who will?
Thank you, Roasie! Thank you!
[JIREN grunting]
[HIT groans]
[CAULIFLA] I can't believe Jiren
is schooling Hit like this.
This is looking bad
for our team.
Come on. It's time for us
to get in there too.
Please, not just yet.
I think Hit is about to
launch a counter move.
Based on what?
He's carefully keeping his guard
up whenever Jiren moves in.
This lets him learn Jiren's
style, all while minimizing
the attack damage. Let's wait.
Hit may just be looking
for the right window.
I think I've finally got his
timing down, and how he reacts.
I can finally finish the job.
[HIT grunting]
[yelling]
[JIREN grunts]
[HIT]
To successfully turn the tables,
this is the one strike
I need to land.
It will confine you
to a time prison.
Ha!
Jiren!
Nice work, Hit!
Fuwa!
One attack changes nothing.
I will prevail.
[JIREN grunting]
[GOKU]
He's stopped Jiren from moving!
Guess that's the strike he's
been planning for a while now.
[JIREN grunting]
[CAULIFLA] The ultimate
assassin strikes again!
Looks like Jiren can't
even twiddle his thumbs!
Oh, wow! So that's
what Hit was up to?
Yeah.
Jiren, what is wrong with you?
Attack!
Hit saved all the time
from those skips
and now uses it to trap his foe.
It was a last-ditch effort,
but it seems to be
working quite well.
Oh, yeah! Keep him frozen, Hit!
[JIREN grunts]
[HIT growls]
Now's your chance!
To do what?
Don't interfere with Jiren.
Leave him to me.
But while he's contained,
there's much more
you three can do. So move!
We must save the Sixth Universe!
He's right, ladies, let's go.
We need to seize this
opportunity and finish our job!
Say what now?
I'm saying that it's time
for us to kick some butt
and win this thing
for the Sixth Universe.
Why did you say that in the
first place. Kale, Come on!
Right!
Hit's actually
coordinating with Cabba
and the other Saiyans
warriors now.
Well that's unusual, isn't it?
Normally Hit works alone, like
he can do everything himself.
[VADOS] Perhaps Hit must rely
on his teammates because
he intends to devote all of his
energy to this technique.
He may be planning to
keep Jiren imprisoned
until the tournament's end.
How can one triumph,
and save one's universe,
when a foe is too
strong to defeat?
The reigning master of
assassins, in his cold
calculation, has determined
this is the only answer.
He must act contrary
to his every instinct,
and rely on others to
achieve deliverance.
It is a testament to his
unshakeable resolve to succeed,
no matter what.
I see. Brilliant, Hit!
Keep him pinned
until time runs out!
[JIREN grunting]
[HIT grunting]
At this rate,
I won't have enough to keep
him trapped until the end.
He's simply too powerful.
In that case, I'll have to
risk it all in one bet.
Assassins hate to gamble,
but I have no other choice.
[JIREN grunts]
One last play.
[HIT] My job is to save
the Sixth, and I won't fail!
[yells]
[HIT gasps]
Ah! Jiren stopped him with
the force of his eyes!
[HIT grunting]
[JIREN grunting]
What?
[JIREN] Do you know what
the pride of an assassin
is good for?
Nothing!
[HIT gasping]
[GOKU gasping]
That can't be! Hit put
everything in that move!
How could it fail?!
[VADOS]
He's like no other.
I'm shocked. It seems that Jiren
possesses the power to
transcend time itself, my lord.
But how can he
do that? No way!
Astounding. His strength
is so great.
Not even time can bind him!
Ha, ha! There you go,
Jiren! Get 'em!
He's in a different
league, my lord.
Yes. He is the pride
of the Eleventh Universe,
there's no doubt.
[HIT yelling]
[JIREN]
Ha!
[HIT groaning]
[gasps]
[CABBA, CATOPESRA grunt]
[KALE, CAULIFLA groaning]
[HIT grunting]
[gasps]
[HIT groans]
This fight is over.
[JIREN grunts]
[HIT screaming]
[BOTH gasp]
There's no way!
It can't be!
Contestant Hit of the Sixth
Universe is eliminated.
[screams]
No! It can't be!
Ha, ha. He never had
a chance against Jiren.
Ah... [sighs]
He just got lucky,
don't sweat it.
My defeat was guaranteed
the moment that attack failed.
I gambled it all, and I lost.
Oh well, the loss
wasn't all in vain.
I think Cabba and the others
were inspired by the way
you fought!
We can still win this!
[VADOS]
Perhaps, my lord.
However, Hit's loss
is significant.
Your odds have dropped
profoundly.
[CHAMPA growls]
Hit believed we could win.
And I am going to prove
that he was right!
[GRAND MINISTER]
My, my, look at that.
Coinciding with the fall
of the mighty Hit,
50 of the 100 tacks
have expired as well.
Let it be known!
The Tournament of Power...
...is halfway done!
[ZENOS cheering]
[GOKU]
Uh...
Halfway done, already?
Time certainly flies when
you're destroying universes.
Just 50 tacks left.
Halfway done.
Jiren.
Understood.
You can take it from here.
The fighters who hoped
to challenge me...
...have already failed.
[BOTH]
Whoa! What's he doing?
A remarkably bold fighter.
He's begun meditating, sires.
Even though half the
allotted time remains,
Jiren is evidently certain
of his team's victory.
Now, I'm not complainin'
or anything,
but it's kind of anticlimactic
to have all this time
and no one who can
pose a real threat.
That's some nerve.
Acting like there's no one
left who's worth his time.
That's what you think, huh?
You think you can just float
there and ignore me?
[CATOPESRA]
If we're going to defeat him,
this is our best chance.
[BIARRA]
Yeah.
It's like he's just begging us
to knock him off the edge.
[DYSPO]
Oh. Look at this.
While I commend your courage
for wanting to face Jiren...
[BOTH]
...you're finished!
[BIARRA]
Go! Now is our chance!
[DYSPO]
What the--?!
[CATOPESRA]
Ha!!
[CATOPESRA yelps]
[BIARRA]
What just happened?
Why is it so hard for
your small minds to grasp?
You cut-rate amateurs
aren't qualified to
fight against Jiren!
If you're not strong enough
to pierce the energy barrier
he has raised, there's no point
in fighting him at all.
Jiren...
[NARRATOR]
By defeating the assassin Hit,
Jiren has once again shown
the vastness of his power.
Will Goku be able to reach
his Autonomous Ultra
Instinct level again?
And even if he can,
will it be enough to topple
this incredible opponent?
The Tournament of Power
is halfway finished,
and the great battle to decide
the fates of the universes
is about to enter
a whole new phase.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super!
A 70 centimeter squared window
Today the sun broke
through the clouds
The rain is fin'ly gone
Gonna open up
the window for once
No reason, just because
This room has been
stained with the sighs
Of everyday regret
Now it's time to clear the air
Every moment was consumed
with my thoughts of you
Knowing in my heart those dreams
won't be coming true
I've always wanted nothing more
than to see your face
I move on knowing that your
mem'ry can't be erased
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
The body-expanding Monna
from the Fourth wants a fight,
while Namekians are taking
on Piccolo and Gohan.
With my energy low
I've got to be careful,
so Vegeta and Cabba will
try to knock out Monna--
if they don't knock
each other out first!
When Monna turns into a giant,
can Cabba harness his
Saiyan pride and win?
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"A Saiyan Oath!
Vegeta's Resolve!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?