Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me go back to the start
Wishing on the starlight
In the sky, let's paint a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of God
Kyo-Let's☆Mo-Let's☆Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic
I don't care 'bout limits, no regret
Make me tougher even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo' try me
So-Zets☆Cho-Zets☆Dynamic!
Let's Go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going power pumpin' up
something greater waiting not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super...
You may begin!
[bellows]
[FROST] Welcome to the world of
trickery, deception, and murder!
This is my domain, and soon it
will be adorned with your blood!
[VEGETA]
You make me sick!
[yells]
[groans]
[NARRATOR] In the
Tournament of Destroyers,
Vegeta defeated the villainous
Frost with a single blow.
Way to take it to him!
All right!
[NARRATOR] The Saiyan prince
seemed ready for any foe,
but a sudden rule change
threatened to turn
the competition on its head.
As you can see,
the ring has been enclosed
in a brand new cubic barrier!
Since this structure
is outside the ring,
touching any part of it
during your match
will now mean automatic
victory for your opponent!
[MAGETTA]
Chug, chug, chug!
[NARRATOR] Vegeta's next
opponent was Magetta,
a robot-like giant
from the Metalman race.
With his seemingly
indestructible body
and a host of powerful attacks,
it was clear this battle
would put Vegeta to the test.
Vegeta hoped
to gain an advantage
by going Super Saiyan.
But fighting inside
the cubic barrier presented
daunting new challenges.
Not only is it harder
to dodge Magetta's
fearsome lava attacks,
but another change
is happening in the ring--
a change Vegeta is only
now beginning to realize.
Is it too late for Vegeta
to understand the truth
and find a way to prevail?
[VEGETA panting]
Something's wrong
with this heat.
[MAGETTA]
Chugga-chugga-thwack.
[NARRATOR]
The battle continues, now!
[MAGETTA]
Clang-clang!
Ratchet-hiss!
[panting]
[TD REF] We seem to have
reached a stalemate.
Contestant Vegeta
has stopped his onslaught.
Has he run out
of ways to attack?
[panting]
What the hell is going on?
Obviously, he's emitting heat
but I've trained
for extremes like this.
There's something else.
Why do I feel so weak?
[CHAMPA giggles]
Champa, my lord.
Your giggling's in poor taste.
Oh, relax!
[giggles]
Something's fishy.
My brother only laughs like that
when he's up to no good.
Like when he stole the steak I'd
been aging for two centuries
and replaced it
with a rubber chew toy.
Vegeta! You gotta
get down while you can!
What, why?
Explain, Goku. Now!
Vegeta is not getting
enough oxygen in there,
and near the ceiling
is the worst place to be.
It's because of
that new barrier.
Thatand the Metalman's
physiology
are a dangerous combination.
The air inside is getting
increasingly thin.
So, I'm right! He doesn't
care about safety;
it was all just a trick!
Hey, Champa!
Yeah, what?
[BEERUS] You rigged that barrier
to suffocate my fighter!
That's an outrageous
accusation, Beerus.
I don't know what
you're talking about!
There is nothing
abnormal about it.
You've sealed off the air!
[CHAMPA] No, we haven't!
Look at the bottom edge, genius!
[CHAMPA] We knew
ventilation was important,
and as you see,
air's getting through just fine!
[breathing heavily]
[CHAMPA] Now is it possible
Magetta's using his combustion
and lava to exceed
the airflow capacity?
Perhaps. But we
can't account for
every tactic a fighter takes.
If you had a problem
with the barrier,
you shouldn't have
approved it at the start.
[growls]
You gotta get to the floor!
At least you'll have a better
chance of breathing there!
Quiet! Ugh!
I won't let you
tell me how to fight!
I know what I need to do!
I will not be grounded!
If my oxygen's running out,
that just means
I need to deal
with this quickly!
[MAGETTA]
Ratchet-hiss!
[VEGETA] Though that's
easier said than done.
Even talking makes me
light headed.
Come on! Why's he
have to be so stubborn.
It's like he's staying up there
just to prove a point!
[grunts]
If Vegeta doesn't act fast
he's gonna pass out!
Come on, Dad, you got this!
I'm gonna pass out first!
[sighs] Like I just
demonstrated with Bulma,
a fighter's gotta be
fast on his feet.
[whistles]
[MAGETTA]
Hiss, thwack!
[TD REF] Trouble for Contestant
Vegeta as Contestant Magetta
once again unleashes
his dreaded lava saliva!
Ah! Hot-hot-hot-hot-hot!
This is getting serious!
[MAGETTA]
Churn, churn!
That opening on his head
should be a weak point.
[MAGETTA]
Chugga-toot!
[squeak]
[VEGETA] Ugh! There's
something else in that steam.
[yells]
--Vegeta!
--Dad, no!
[BEERUS]
Aah!
Stop!
[TD REF]
The Saiyan manages to stop,
just before
touching the barrier!
[VEGETA]
This is ridiculous!
[exhales]
Awe! He's a tough one.
That was too close.
That isn't fair! He just
set off some kind of bomb.
How's that not a weapon?
[TD REF]
Checking now! Nope!
That's a
naturally-produced attack,
and therefore
technically not a weapon!
He merely ignited his own
explosive intestinal gas!
[MAGETTA]
Choo-choo! Toot.
[panting]
[VEGETA]
He's making a mockery of me!
Oh, come on!
These rulings are ridiculous.
I'm beginning to think
this referee's been bought!
I don't think so,
Lord Beerus.
As bizarre as
this match might be,
I find the judgments to be
fair and well-informed.
[BEERUS growls]
In all my battles
over the years,
I've never seen anybody
fight like this Metalman guy.
I wonder how I'd do against him.
He's already shown us
how strong his iron body his.
It's stood up to everything
Vegeta's thrown at him.
And the conditions in there
are taking a toll.
Vegeta's losing stamina
by the minute.
It's about all he can manage
just staying away
from those lava attacks.
Throw in those walls boxing him
and the odds don't look good.
You sum it up well, Nameckian.
The proud Saiyan prince
may have finally met his match.
Come on, Vegeta!
If you lose,
you'll answer to me!
[VEGETA]
I'm sick of all this chatter!
Shut up and let me fight!
[bellows]
[yells]
[VEGETA] You think you're
indestructible, Metalman?
Let's see you stand up to this!
Whoa! I know that stance!
[TD REF] What's this?
Contestant Vegeta is
building up a massive
amount of energy!
[MAGETTA]
Chugga-chugga-chugga.
Tang tang!
That burns, ow!
Not to be outdone,
Contestant Magetta turns up
the heat even higher!
--Careful, honey!
--Go, Dad!
[TRUNKS]
Whoa, that's hot!
If it's this bad on
the outside of the barrier,
I don't even want to know what
it feels like on the inside.
How can he stand it?
Hang in there, Dad!
Make him pay!
[MAGETTA]
Chicka-chicka.
Ratchet-whir.
[yells]
[MAGETTA] Kachunk-kachunk.
Tang, tang, hiss!
What?
[VEGETA]
Nice try!
[GOKU]
Aah!
[VEGETA yells]
[GOKU]
Vegeta, look out!
[MAGETTA]
Tang!
Oh great!
[MAGETTA]
Chugga-thwack!
[VEGETA yells]
[MAGETTA]
Ker-plack.
Damn it, no!
Is that it?
I think so.
[yells]
[WHIS]
Huh.
[TRUNKS]
It's over! He lost!
[VEGETA grunts]
♪
[GOKU] That's no good.
So, he's out?
Aaah!
Oh yeah!
--[GOKU] Huh?
--[BEERUS] Eh?
[CHAMPA]
Uuuh...
[TD REF]
Huuuuh... Huh.
He's safe! No ring out!
What? Are you insane?
How can that
possibly be true, ref?
He's clearly outside of
the ring--don't you have eyes?
[TD REF] Please direct your
attention to the screens.
Contestant Vegeta
has actually landed on
a small fragment
of the damaged ring!
By definition, he is, in fact,
still standing
on the ring floor!
And thus it is not a ring out!
No way!
Talk about a close one!
Go, ref! Way to
make the right call!
My dad's the coolest ever!
Ah! That's completely absurd!
Who hired this miserable
freaking joke of a referee!
You did, my lord.
Wait, I did?
[growls]
[laughs]
There's nothing I love more
than watching my brother cry!
Guess it was Vegeta's turn
to be saved by a technicality.
I know it's tempting
for us to celebrate,
but try to imagine
how our proud Vegeta
--feels about this.
--[GOKU] Hmmm.
Not too good.
[chuckles nervously]
[VEGETA] What sort of
cruel prank is fate playing?
How much humiliation
am I supposed to take?
A warrior wins
with his might!
He does not need some
god damn rule to save him!
These restrictions
can go to hell.
Oh, man, I don't think
this is gonna be pretty.
[VEGETA]
You! Referee!
Um, yeah,
what do you need?
[VEGETA] The rule is we can't
touch the barrier, right?
Uh, yeah.
That works.
[MAGETTA]
Clang, clang.
[VEGETA bellows]
[TD REF yells]
[MAGETTA] Chugga-chugga-
chugga-chugga-grind.
[VEGETA yells]
[MAGETTA]
Clang-clang.
So, that's what a Seventh
Universe Saiyan can do!
All he's done
is lose his temper!
He can scream like
a raving idiot all he wants,
it won't get him
out of this trap.
I think the one
acting like an idiot
right now is you, sir.
Say what?
[VEGETA yells]
[KRILLIN]
What the--?
[VEGETA yells]
[bellows]
[GOKU]
Aah!
Look at that!
Whoa.
I'm finally starting
to see how he could be
the toughest guy
in the whole universe!
He didn't even flinch!
[ALL groan, gasp]
Amazing! I can't believe
he has that much power!
This is your fault!
You should've made the barrier
strong enough to
stand up to any attack!
I told you
it could be better.
But you were impatient
and ridiculed my warning.
You called it
"perfectionist drivel."
Well, next time ignore me!
[VEGETA inhales, exhales]
Now that I can
actually breath,
you don't stand
a chance against me.
Go on, honey!
Get as mad as you need to.
This punk deserves it!
Send him back
to the junkyard!
This is power.
[grunts]
[yells]
[gasps]
Whoa, that technique!
Careful, Vegeta!
You know we're still
sitting here, right?
[yells]
[grunts]
[MAGETTA]
Chugga-chugga-toot!
[VEGETA yells]
[MAGETTA]
Chicka-ta-chicka-tang!
Ratchet-thwak!
[yells]
[bellows]
[GOKU gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[PICCOLO gasps]
[CABBA gasps]
[VEGETA]
Final...
Flash!
[MAGETTA]
Whir-hiss!
Ker-plunk, a-plunk!
[BULMA, TRUNKS gasp]
[MAGETTA] Cling-clang-
cling-clang-cling-clang!
Grind. Grind. Grind.
Whir hiss-hiss-
hiss-hiss-hiss-
hiss-hiss-hiss-hiss-
hiss-hiss-hiss-hiss!
He's right on the edge--
you're almost there!
Push him all the way!
[MAGETTA]
Hiss-hiss-hiss-hiss.
Whir, waggle
waggle waggle.
[yells]
There's no escaping me now!
[grunts]
You like that?
Because you're finished,
you pathetic pile of junk!
[MAGETTA]
Chicka-chicka-klunk-hiss.
Clacket-a...
Ring out: Contestant Magetta!
Contenst Vegeta wins the match!
[VEGETA]
Hm!
--He did it!
--Nobody beats my dad!
Now we've lost Magetta, too?
I guess you should have
given me time
to strengthen that barrier.
You are so annoying!
[growls]
[VADOS] Cheer up.
It was a spirited battle,
and we're not finished yet.
All we can do is
focus on the next match--
though, clearly, I'll need to
make some repairs first.
I need some water.
Well done, Vegeta.
That's two now.
Crushing the ring was a little
bit excessive, if you ask me.
Don't give him a hard time--
that guy was like a tank!
He wasn't going down
the normal way.
It was far from the
easiest way you could have
defeated the Metalman,
but I suppose a win is a win.
Say what?
[MAGETTA]
Sniff, sniff, sniff.
[GOKU]
Whoa, is he crying?
[MAGETTA] Sniff, sniff.
Clickety, thunk!
Hard to believe
that's the guy who seemed
indestructible
a few minutes ago.
We have Vegeta's
"pile of junk" comment
to thank for that.
As you see,
Magetta was
rather hurt by the remark.
Despite their
literal thick skin,
the Metalman race are
extraordinarily sensitive,
and the right insult
during combat can reduce them
to a puddle,
rendering them helpless.
You knew that the whole time
and didn't say anything;
even when Vegeta
was about to lose?
Well, I'm glad he didn't!
Just think of
all the great fighting
we woulda missed out on!
[WHIS laughs]
My thought exactly.
I'm sure you feel
the same way, Vegeta.
I mean, if you just
wanted a quick win,
you could've
powered up at the start.
[VEGETA]
Hmph!
That guy in black--you're
curious about him too, right?
He looks like a serious threat.
Now it's my turn to fight.
[NARRATOR] Saiyans from
two universes collide,
next time on Dragon Ball Super!
Goodbye to our adventure
In twilight we must go our separate ways
And try to discover the path to our own destiny
I can't find the words
to tell you how much our parting hurts
I hope you know I'll always love you
And all that we shared will be remembered
How could I forget your face?
All my memories erased
I can still hear the melody of your voice
Petals fall in from above
Fade away, all that we love
In the twilight,
fade away,
fade away
Sayonara,
fade away,
fade away
Hey, it's me, Goku!
The Saiyans from the 6th Universe
may be a lot different than us
but they're still a warrior race, and it'd be
a bit mistake to think this fight's gonna be easy.
After all Vegeta's gone through in this
tournament, I'm worried where his head's at.
Could the old, evil Vegeta make a comeback?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Super:
Make sure you don't miss it, okay?