Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me go back to the start
Wishing on the starlight
In the sky, let's paint a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of God
Kyo-Let's☆Mo-Let's☆Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic
I don't care 'bout limits, no regret
Make me tougher even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo' try me
So-Zets☆Cho-Zets☆Dynamic!
Let's Go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going power pumpin' up
something greater waiting not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the competition
between the Sixth
and Seventh Universes
began at last.
[yells]
--[BOTAMO hollers]
--[GOKU grunts]
Ladies and gentlemen,
that's a ring-out victory!
Contestant Goku of the Seventh
Universe is moving on!
[NARRATOR] Goku handily claimed
victory in the first match,
then moved on to Frost,
the Sixth Universe's
counterpart to Frieza,
and Goku seemed
to be winning that round, too.
[FROST] "No matter
what happens, never give up.
Get back on your feet."
That's right. The same
encouragement I give
my liberated orphans is the
encouragement I'll use now!
[grunts]
[yells]
[chuckles]
[GOKU moans]
This match is over.
[NARRATOR]
In a dramatic upset,
Goku was inexplicably stunned
and flung from the ring
taking the powerful Saiyan
out of the contest.
The Tournament of Destroyers
moves forward
to the next
unpredictable round. Now!
[FROST panting]
Match over! He's out!
That means Contestant Frost
of the Sixth Universe
is the winner!
Oh yeah!
Oh, he lost.
I wasn't expecting that.
How could he lose?
He let too many of
Frost's attacks get through.
Must have rattled
his brain or something
and caused him
to lose consciousness.
That nincompoop!
What was he doing?
--Krillin!
--[hollers]
This is your fault!
Remember when you said
you weren't sure which one
you should be cheering for?
Are you happy?
'Cause that's why Goku lost!
Yeah, but you were
doing it, too.
Oh, no! Goku!
[GOTEN]
Mom!
Goku, no! Get up!
[TD REF gasps]
Goku!
You scared me!
Uh... What happened? Hmmm.
Oh, I lost.
Well, that's too bad.
[CHICHI] Oh, Goku! I thought
you might be dead!
--[CHICHI sobbing]
--Everybody's watching us.
[FROST panting]
You okay, warrior?
--[CHICHI grunts]
--You're pretty good, Frost!
I don't even know what move
you used to knock me out!
To be honest with you,
I'm not sure myself.
I was just getting desperate.
Although, there is one thing
I can say for certain.
You raised the bar,
pushing me to new heights.
You made me a better fighter.
[GOKU]
Uh...
[chuckles]
It was tough, but I had
a good time. Thank you.
Uh. Oh wow, I don't
know what to say!
[chuckles]
[clapping]
[laughing, cheering]
Nice! Good show!
I can hardly believe it!
You guys both did
a great job out there!
[cheering]
Incredible.
I wish we had royals
as fine as this
in the Galactic Patrol.
[JACO]
Hmph!
Well, that's that.
I lost, Chichi.
So, you can watch
without worrying now.
Uh... Man, I'm so ashamed, sirs!
--Oh, you're ashamed?
--[VEGETA] Hm?
[BEERUS]
You think that absolves you?
If you had just
taken the fight seriously,
you would have won!
Yeah, maybe. Hard to say.
You know, I really thought
I'd be able to take him
at Super Saiyan, but boy
was I wrong on that one.
What're you gonna do?
Tell you what, I won't make
that mistake again next time!
Next time? This was the match
that mattered, Goku!
If I lose this tournament now,
I'll never hear
the end of it from Champa!
Hey! Beerus!
--[BEERUS] Ugh.
--[GOKU] Huh?
You're not upset, are you?
You sure look upset.
What? No, I'm all good.
It's all good.
Oh, so you're saying
that wasn't your team's
star fighter who just lost?
Poor Beerus. Little Beerus!
[BEERUS snarls]
Your lordship.
Composure. Deep breaths.
[BEERUS]
Oh... Grrr...
You put up
a heck of a fight, Goku,
and showed a lot
of heart out there!
It's not important
who won or lost!
Only that you tried
to do your very best!
--[GOKU chuckles nervously]
--[BEERUS chuckles]
[WHIS chuckles]
Moving on now.
The next contestant
from the Seventh Universe
to face off against Frost
will be... Piccolo!
Do I have any hope
of winning this?
[GOKU]
Hmmm...
Probably not.
Wow, that's harsh.
Way to soften the blow.
So, do you think
I should forfeit?
[GOKU] Nah, I mean, Vegeta's
gonna have to fight him next,
so if you can manage
to wear Frost down,
even a little bit, that'll be
a big help down the line.
So, that's all I'm
good for around here, huh?
You know,
there's really no need
for you to fight
in your final form.
Why don't you take
it easy this go around?
Oh, don't worry.
I would never want to kill you,
and I'm too weakened from
the last match to do so.
That being said, I certainly
don't plan to lose, either.
Everybody has such little
confidence in me. Heh.
[FROST]
Huh?
[TD REF]
Aaah!
[groans]
The fight will
commence momentarily.
[GOKU chuckles]
[VEGETA] There's no way
Kakarrot was knocked out
by an attack that weak.
Something else
is going on here.
Yes? What is it?
Oh. I can just see better
from here, that's all.
[VEGETA]
Hm!
[JACO]
[rings]
[TD REF]
Begin!
Since you've had
the benefit of seeing
every trick up my sleeve, all I
have left now is my resolve.
That should be more
than enough to stop you!
Huh?
I know what's comin'!
It's his Special Beam Cannon!
This'll be awesome!
--[VEGETA] Tch!
--[GOKU] Huh?
To me, it seems like
a desperate effort
from a fighter who knows
he's too weak to win.
It looks like you're
preparing to unleash
some kind of
spectacular technique.
But it takes time,
doesn't it?
Requiring you to focus
and build a tremendous
amount of energy
before you use it.
[PICCOLO grunts]
Yeah. He does have a point.
Yes, an obvious flaw.
That's it! Don't stop now!
[PICCOLO grunts]
Yes! I haven't
seen that in a while!
Heh. Those feeble moves
won't do much
against a foe like Frost.
--[PICCOLO grunts]
--Nice try, but no!
[FROST grunts]
[PICCOLO groans]
Your concentration
is impressive.
However, with that wound,
you won't be
dodging much anymore.
Hm?
Duplicates?
Hey! These matches are
supposed to be one-on-one
not one-on-thirty!
Hey, ref! Yellow card him!
Or better yet,
you should make it red!
Disqualify him now!
That tactic is permmitted.
There are no rules against it.
A lowly mortal referee
does not contradict a Destroyer!
How dare you?!
Shut up! During the matches
the referee outranks
even us deities!
You don't really
mean that, do you?
Well, of course I don't.
That's absurd.
[FROST yells]
Aw, what's he waiting for?
He should fire now, right?
Not yet. Piccolo's
still charging up.
[KRILLIN] He's trying to win
the match with one go.
It'll take all he's got!
[FROST]
He's stalling for time.
And I can't see his face
through all that light.
I find both of these
things disturbing.
[FROST grunts, yells]
[PICCOLO groans]
If Frost knocks his hand away,
he'll lose that attack.
He's too close in!
Get some space!
[PICCOLO groans]
--[FROST yells]
--[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO]
Oh no!
--[FROST yells]
--[PICCOLO groans]
Looks like I win.
[PICCOLO]
Oh, really?
What the--?
[FROST]
What is this?
[PICCOLO] You played
right into my hands, Frost.
Two things are gonna happen.
I hold you in place as I
charge myself up. And, then...
...Special Beam Cannon.
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH]
Hmm.
[FROST] I was paying close
attention to that energy
you were focusing.
When I saw it slip
out of your fingers
I thought you'd lost
all chance at victory.
And so you let your
guard down, didn't you?
Are you saying...
getting shot in the leg
was all part of your plan
to lower my defenses?
--[PICCOLO] Hm.
--[FROST chuckles]
Well, you got me good.
Guess you literally had
this trick "up your sleeve."
I can't possibly
see any way for me
to dodge your
finishing attack now.
[PICCOLO]
May not look like much,
but in the Seventh Universe
I pass for resourceful.
In the end,
underestimating me
will prove to be
your biggest mistake.
[JACO gasps]
You ready? Special Beam--uh!
[PICCOLO breathes heavily]
Now's my chance!
Damn it!
--[FROST chuckles]
--Piccolo!
If I had taken that blast,
I would have lost for sure.
You put up a good fight, though.
[PICCOLO groans, coughs]
[ALL gasp]
My beautiful dome!
I thought it was shatterproof!
I'll fix it. Don't worry.
[TD REF panting]
He can't continue,
but he is alive.
And Frost is the winner!
Aw, man.
--[WHIS gasps]
--[BEERUS] Uhahuaagh!
He lost?
Oh my goodness.
[CHAMPA giggles]
[VEGETA]
I don't get it.
What sort of move is he using
to stun them like that?
Objection!
--[OOLONG, KRILLIN] Huh?
--What's goin' on, Jaco?
He cheated!
In what way?
Frost has been using a weapon
which is prohibited
by the rules!
Weapon?
Check out his right arm.
Open your eyes.
It's something sharp and pointy.
You can't sneak
anything past this guy!
Hold your tongue!
Baseless accusations
are beyond the pale!
That's right!
I know Mr. Frost well.
I fought alongside him
on Planet Mayonnai
and can attest to his character!
He's a hero
who risked his life
to rescue its citizens from
marauding space pirates!
He would never cheat!
They're right.
Frost doesn't seem like
the kinda guy who'd fight dirty.
Wait! Are you sure?
[JACO]
Hm-hm-hmm!
Anybody who doubts
these eyes will be wrong
every single time.
Referee! Search his damn body!
Uh, okay.
What sour grapes!
Besmirching this man's
good name just because
you lost! But all right.
Just know, if they
find nothing on him,
I will personally destroy you.
[JACO]
Uh, never mind then.
[BEERUS]
No. Search him.
If Champa destroys you,
well, then so be it.
It's no skin
off my nose, after all.
Yeah, I guess
it is just Jaco.
Referee! Frisk the man already!
[JACO]
Mmm.
[CHAMPA chuckles]
[gasps]
Ah.
The world, it's--
it's spinning... Ah...
[JACO]
A-ha!
What is the meaning of this?
I assure you
this is not a weapon!
It's part of my body!
No. No way.
There are some clear signs
of trickery at play here!
For violating the rules
of the tournament,
Frost is disqualified!
Which means the
winner is... Piccolo!
Oh-ho! Bang!
Nice going, Jaco!
For the first time ever
you actually seem useful!
Are you kidding me here?
I don't get it! Why would
somebody as honorable as him
ever do something
that's so underhanded?
Gentlemen.
The truth is quite simple.
This is who the great
Mr. Frost truly is.
You see, those space pirates
who attacked Planet Mayonnai
are part of an underworld
crime syndicate,
and Mr. Frost here
is the group's leader.
That can't be!
[ALL gasp]
You accuse me of
such terrible things, Vados.
I'm so hurt.
[laughs]
Yes, I start my own wars.
But then I resolve them
and buy up all the
war-ravaged land
at bargain prices.
After that, I make a killing
off the very lucrative
post-reconstruction profits.
I'm tellin' ya,
it's quite a business model
I've cooked up here.
I'm the problem
and the solution.
Aw!
That's funny.
Now he doesn't seem to be
all that different from Frieza.
He passes himself off
as a noble savior
to provide cover for
all his nefarious plans.
Hmph! Even in another
universe, there's no way
Frieza could ever be
legitimately good at his core.
[ALL booing]
[PICCOLO] So, if anyone's gonna
walk out of here a disgrace,
looks like it'll be you, Frost!
You can tell yourself that,
but we both know
who really won. Turns out
you underestimating me
was your big mistake,
Mr. Resourceful.
Are you nuts?
How could you go
and pick that creep
to be on my team?
My lord, you never
asked me to take
the candidates' morality
into consideration.
In fact, I believe your
exact words to me were,
"I don't want to
be bothered with this.
Just find fighters who
will do whatever it takes
to win their rounds,
no matter what."
[CHAMPA grunts]
Well, best of luck.
I hope that you give it
your all in the next match.
[CHAMPA grunts] You really
think you can just walk away
after bringing this
kind of shame on me?
I will destroy you!
[VEGETA]
Hold on!
There's no need for threats.
And no need to disqualify him.
'Cause I'm up next. Got that?
And I'd like to
beat that bastard myself.
But, your teammate
Piccolo's loss
has been reversed already.
That means he's scheduled
to fight in the next match.
Piccolo says
he forfeits. Right?
[intense music plays]
Yeah. I think I'll do that.
Hey, wait!
I just called dibs on destroying
this embarrassment!
How dare you try to
take that away from me?!
Why not go along with this?
Our loss will be reversed,
and one of their men forfeits.
In terms of numbers, we win,
and we don't have to risk
anything in the process.
You've got a point.
Unless, of course, you would
prefer to lose to Lord Beerus?
[CHAMPA grunts]
Hey, Frost!
If you win this match,
I'll wipe the slate
and forgive you
for tarnishing
my sterling reputation!
And then if you
can pull of a victory
in the next round,
I'll even consider
rewarding you the way
we agreed. Got it?
Heh.
How gauche. The smirk
of a self-satisfied egotist.
Does that remind you
of anyone, sir?
Hey, Vegeta! Defeat
this guy once and for all!
Then I can relax! You got that?
Vegeta! You've got this!
[FROST] So, you want me
to keep my victory?
You must be
pretty sure of yourself.
Don't blame me if you wind up
regretting this in the end.
Shut up.
Your voice annoys me.
Oh, really? Too bad.
[VEGETA chuckles]
Goodbye to our adventure
In twilight we must go our separate ways
And try to discover the path to our own destiny
I can't find the words
to tell you how much our parting hurts
I hope you know I'll always love you
And all that we shared will be remembered
How could I forget your face?
All my memories erased
I can still hear the melody of your voice
Petals fall in from above
Fade away, all that we love
In the twilight,
fade away,
fade away
Sayonara,
fade away,
fade away
Hey, it's me, Goku!
Man, Frost turned out to be
a pretty bad guy, didn't he?
I hate to admit it,
but he sure had me fooled!
The good news is, Vegeta won't make the same mistake I did.
He won't put up with any dirty tricks.
And I for one can't wait to see him go after Frost at full power.
Next time on Dragon Ball Super:
Make sure you don't miss it, okay?