♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Goku, Gohan, Piccolo,
and Tien engaged
in a two-on-two battle royale
in order to prepare for
the Tournament of Power,
and find out just how
strong Gohan had become.
But the fight quickly
became hazardous.
[TIEN]
Now call off the fight, Gohan!
Same goes for you!
Yeah. Maybe he's right, Son.
[NARRATOR] It looked as
though the sparring session
was over, until...
--[GOHAN] Dad, wait.
--[GOKU] Hm?
I'm not done. Let's go again,
you and me, one-on-one.
[GOKU]
You got it, Gohan.
Let's go!
[yells]
[BOTH grunt]
[NARRATOR] Gohan demonstrated
a power that tested even Goku.
At last, the mighty
Gohan had returned!
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN, GOKU yell]
Let's keep pushing
each other, Son.
As far as we can.
[NARRATOR] "Which Universe
Will Win Their Place?
The Mighty Warriors
Gradually Assemble!"
[ZENOES]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[ZENO grunts]
[FUTURE ZENO]
Uh. Uh...
[ZENOES]
Rock, paper, scissors!
I'm bored of this game
now, aren't you?
Yes, it's no fun at all.
[ZENOES]
Come here!
[GRAND MINISTER]
Yes, sires? You beckoned?
[BOTH]
This game is no fun now.
It is boring, and boring is bad.
Plus our hands and heads
are starting to ache.
Tell us something fun
to distract us from
how bored we are.
As you command, sires.
Please observe the latest news
update from the Cosmos.
[BOTH]
Ooh, what is it? What is it?
[GRAND MINISTER]
Well, apparently,
your friend Goku's 7th
Universe has now selected
all of the contestants for its
Tournament of Power team.
I bet Goku picked
a team that's great!
Yes, I can't wait to see it!
[ZENOES laugh]
[SUPREME KAI]
Nicely done, Goku.
We finally have all of
our competitors lined up.
Your recruitment skills are
better than we thought.
I must admit, you did
a decent job, Goku.
Aw, it was no
big deal, honestly.
Hold on.
Does anybody know where
Vegeta ran off to?
Well, he went to the
Lookout so he could train
in the Hyperbolic Time Chamber.
So wait, he went
to train on his own
without even telling me?
Man, that's totally uncool.
[WHIS] Well, perhaps that's
because you've been so busy
sparring with other fighters
that you left him to
fend for himself.
[MR. POPO]
Hold it!
If you destroy the room again,
you're banned for life.
[VEGETA]
Hmph.
He's definitely going to break
it again, I just know it.
[VEGETA grunts] Only one
warrior will defeat Kakarot
and be the last man standing
in this tournament.
The whole Cosmos will know
the glory of Prince Vegeta!
[GOKU] Hm... So how should I
use this time we've got left?
Well, I'm happy to draw out your
untapped abilities so you can
break through whatever
limitations you still have,
if that floats your boat.
Whoa, you can do that?!
That sounds like a
tremendous idea.
Forgive me for throwing
cold water on your proposal,
but the process of drawing out
someone's latent abilities
would take at least 25 hours
to perform, and we don't have
that much time before
the tournament begins.
Oh, yeah. Darn it.
I guess you're right.
[GOKU]
What?!
Aw man, and I was
gettin' all excited, too!
That's quite the
wasted opportunity.
You can say that again.
[growls]
[GOKU]
Hey, Whis.
I hate to ask you for another
favor, but do you think
you could you spar with me
until it's time to go?
[WHIS]
Certainly, I don't mind at all.
[GOKU]
Awesome! Thanks.
I know it'll help.
Well, let's go.
Right now, every second counts!
Goku is really on
top of things, huh?
So what are we waiting for?
Let's start the tournament now.
Yes, yes, we should
just start it right now!
Your majesties.
I know how eager you
are to start, however,
we must honor the already
agreed-upon schedule.
In contrast to Goku's success,
there are several universes
that appear to be having some
trouble putting teams together.
[ZENOES]
Is that true?
Indeed.
[RO growls]
[CIVILIANS screaming]
That's right, you better run!
And leave all your precious
belongin's behind for us!
I am the king of this world now,
and nothin' can stop me!
Yee-haw!
[MOJIITO]
What is the meaning of this?
I'm afraid it's kind
of our fault, sir.
As soon as we told them about
the possible Armageddon,
they started rioting.
Guess they don't
have faith in us,
because they're planning
to abandon this universe
and flee to another one.
Forget about them, how
many fighters have you
recruited for the tournament?
Uh... let's see,
including the three of us,
we're up to a total of three.
[ALL] Uh. We are so
unbelievably sorry, sir.
[SIDRA growls]
And now Hakai!
[screams]
All right, let's try our
luck on a different world.
This one's a lost cause.
It would appear
that everybody there
is thinking only about
themselves now.
The unbridled panic
and chaos on display
is positively disgraceful.
[ZENO] I'm curious,
which universe do you think
is going to win the tournament?
You know what?
I think Goku's universe is
going to win the tournament.
But you know what else?
The 6th Universe is decent,
too, so they could win.
[GRAND MINISTER]
Astute observations, sires.
As those two twin universes
are linked counterparts,
their respective strengths
appear to be evenly balanced.
[ZENOES]
Really?
[grunts]
[footsteps]
[FROST grunts]
[gasps]
Long time no see, huh?
Hit? How did you...?
Control yourself.
I'm here on an assignment.
[FROST whimpers]
What is it?
Did you come to assassinate me?
[FROST]
All right, if you must.
Please, just get it over with.
I'm not going to struggle.
I have no grand delusions
that I could ever stop you.
[FROST]
And I make it a rule
not to waste time
fighting the inevitable.
[FROST grunts]
[screams]
[FROST screams]
I won't let you take me out!
[gasps]
[HIT grunts]
[FROST]
Oh, come on.
Huh?
For a moment there, Frost, you
fought like you really meant it.
You've improved mightily.
It appears living life on the
lam has sharpened your skills.
But I don't understand, why
are you showing me such mercy?
I'm here at Champa's request.
To pass along an invitation.
[FROST]
Hm?
[HIT] The Omni-King is holding
a martial arts tournament,
and you were personally selected
to be one of the ten warriors
who will represent
the 6th Universe there.
We could really use somebody
with survival instincts
as keen as yours.
Or at least that's what
Lord Champa said.
[FROST exhales]
I see.
All right, come with me.
If you refuse, then
I'll have no choice but
to kill you right here.
Oh, don't be preposterous.
I wouldn't dream of refusing.
In fact, I will
gladly take part.
After all, this is
an opportunity for me
to restore my honor.
[chuckles]
Only thing is, you can't use
your little poison needles.
Violate the rules, and you'll
be eliminated on the spot.
Eliminated, huh?
Now let's go.
[FROST]
Gladly.
And if it comes down to it,
I'll risk my life for
the sake of my universe.
[HIT]
We'll see.
Just be sure to remove
the poison needles
from your heels, too.
You don't miss anything, do you?
[chuckles]
Try the Capsule
Corporation's latest--
I love you more than
the day I first met--
...for our top
story tonight--
[sighs]
What's taking them so long?
Oh, they're probably just
saving the best for last.
Yeah.
--[knocking]
--[ROSHI] Hey!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Hey, Yamcha, get your butt
up to the roof, right away!
There's something
important I gotta ask ya.
Hurry up, old geezer.
You're gettin' heavy! C'mon!
It's Master Roshi. I knew it!
My invitation to the
tournament's finally here,
and in suitably
dramatic fashion!
I knew your patience would be
rewarded eventually, old pal!
[BOTH laugh]
[YAMCHA]
What? You want Puar?
[BOTH gasping]
Yup, that's right.
I need Puar to transform himself
into a beautiful,
spunky girl for me.
Okay, and why in the world
would you need that?
You sweet, simple boy.
[ROSHI] As great as I am,
I still have one weakness.
And now I wish to
overcome that flaw.
The insatiable
thirst that consumes
my overly amorous heart.
[gasping]
[YAMCHA laughs]
[YAMCHA]
Pretty sure that's not possible.
If you need a shape-shifter,
ask Oolong!
Well, for some reason,
he refused.
One time I was trying
to get back at Bulma
and may have taken things
a little too far.
I don't wanna get into details,
but the whole thing left
me mildly traumatized.
I want to be nice,
Yamcha, but also, ew.
Gee, Puar, I'm sorry, but it
sounds like Master Roshi
could really use your
help right now.
I think you should do it.
[whines]
[ROSHI laughs]
[PUAR] Please! Keep your
hands to yourself!
[ROSHI screams]
Guess I'm not cured yet.
Let's try again.
[PUAR]
Hey! Watch it, would ya!
That is not okay!
--[ROSHI laughs]
--[PUAR whines]
[OOLONG sighs]
[ROSHI] Look, I'm trying,
toots, but I can't help it!
[ROSHI screams]
[ROSHI groans]
[ROSHI chuckles]
I'm sorry! It's no use!
My grabby little hands
have a mind of their own!
[PUAR] Does this really
qualify as training?!
[PUAR yelps]
Is it cool if I jet? This is
resurfacing a lotta memories.
--Uh, wait, before you go...
--[OOLONG grunts]
At some point, they are gonna
ask me to join the team
for the tournament, right?
I mean, surely they
have to want me there?
Uh, yeah, I'm sure they'll
get around to it.
Eventually.
[YAMCHA]
Wha...?
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU grunting]
[WHIS]
Interesting.
You keep leaving your
side open to an attack.
[GOKU grunts]
Hey, wait!
I recognize this move!
That won't work on me!
[WHIS groans]
[GOKU grunts]
[WHIS] My goodness,
is nothing beneath you?
[GOKU laughs]
Sorry about that, Whis.
You asked for it!
You reminded me of that guy,
Top, and it set me on fire!
[GOKU yells]
Okay, now I say we start
fighting for real!
[BAR PATRONS chatter]
[TOP]
Hmm...
[DISPO]
Why isn't the general here yet?
[TOP]
Hmm... I don't know.
I called him,
but still no response.
Casserale, come in.
[alarm blares]
[TOP]
This is Top.
Once again, I'm issuing an
emergency return order.
Casserale, come in.
[SPACE CAT 91A whimpers]
[CASSERALE grunts]
[TOP sighs]
Casserale! Come in!
I'm on an important
mission, sir.
I can't leave till it's done!
This is an emergency!
The fate of the universe
is at stake here!
I know, but if I can't even save
the life right in front of me,
then how am I supposed to
save the entire universe?
Bah! He hung up on us!
I'm sure he couldn't help it.
Whatever he's doing,
it must be important.
[CASSERALE grunting]
[growls]
Obviously, I could just leap
up there and grab her, but...
If I startle her and she
touches that power line--
I can't take that risk!
[GRAND MINISTER]
The fighters from the 11th.
One of whom battled against
Goku in the Zeno Expo,
could also potentially
win the tournament.
Top and his compatriots
are incredibly strong warriors,
not to mention, on
a personal level,
they're of
outstanding character.
Oh, that's right, I forgot.
Yes, then the 11th team
might be the winners instead.
[GRAND MINISTER]
On the other hand,
the 11th Universe's counterpart,
the 2nd Universe,
could also be a
formidable contender.
It's a most exotic and
fascinating locale, sires.
[music plays]
[CROWD chattering]
[BRIANNE]
Attention, ladies and gentlemen!
I'm gonna try my
darnedest to be chosen
as one of the 2nd
Universe's Idol Warriors!
Don't even start.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Did you get lost on the way
to the pop idol auditions,
miss thang?
'Cause these are tryouts for a
martial arts tournament, sugar.
This ain't your scene, girl,
so keep on walking, m'kay!
Oh, I'm sorry,
were you talking to me?
For future reference,
I'm Brianne de Chateau.
[BOTH gasp]
And as you'll see...
...I'm stronger than the
both of you put together.
[BRIANNE laughs]
[BRIANNE]
Formation!
Brianne! Brianne!
Bri-Brianne!
♪♪♪
[RIBRIANNE]
Happiness to one and all!
I send you my love!
Ribrianne! [laughs]
My transformation
is complete!
Now, brace yourselves!
It's time for your punishment!
Prepare to receive
my feelings for you!
[RIBRIANNE]
Pretty...
...Cannon.
[BOTH gasping]
All you good boys and girls,
don't try this at home, 'kay!
[RIBRIANNE laughs]
[ZENOES]
'Kay!
Uh? Heh.
She's a good reminder
that we should keep an eye
on the strong women
of each universe, too.
Ooh, that's a great point!
I'm feeling even
more excited now!
And moving on to
Universe Number 10...
It appears they have assembled
a full team, as well.
And by the looks of it, they
seem to be doing something
most amusing in order to foster
unity among their team members.
[music plays]
[GOWASU]
Hmm...
Yay! Woo-hoo!
How's it look?!
Everyone in sync?
[GOWASU]
Looks fantastic!
I bet this "We Dancing" video
featuring our mighty warriors
breaking it down will get us
billions of views on GodTube.
[KUSU laughing]
[ZENOES laughing]
Wow, this dance
is so much fun!
I can't wait for the
tournament to begin now!
[GRAND MINISTER]
Yes, I thought you'd like that.
Oh, dear.
It appears there's a problem
brewing in Goku's universe.
Huh? What is it? What is it?
Oh, no, did something
happen to Goku?
[sighs]
[laughs] Man, I worked
up a good sweat!
Thanks, Whis, you really
put me through my paces.
You're quite welcome.
It was my pleasure.
Nothing like a
well-earned treat
after a grueling
workout, am I right?
Oh? Did you work out while
we were training, sir?
As far as our general
strategy goes,
I think we should hunker down
in the center so we're not
forced out of the ring.
That makes sense,
but I fear all the other teams
will have the same idea.
Thus the center will likely be
the most intensive battle zone.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
[BULLA breathes]
[BULMA laughs]
[phone vibrates]
[BULMA]
Wonder what he wants...
Hey, what's goin' on?
"The Tournament of Power"?
Never heard of it, but yeah,
Goku sure loves those
competitions doesn't he?
Uh-huh. Yeah.
All right. Don't worry,
I heard ya, loud and clear.
Yeah, I'll go tell
everyone right now.
Uh, hey, everybody, I just got
off the phone with Mr. Satan.
What is it, Bulma?
Is there something wrong?
He said that Buu won't be able
to enter your Tournament
thingy after all.
Uh!
Apparently he fell asleep
and won't wake up.
[gasping]
From what Mister Satan said,
it sounds like he's
hibernating or something
and could be in a deep sleep
for another two months.
Now what?
This puts us in a
tricky spot, Dad.
I'll go over to Buu's place
and see what I can do.
Well, it's worth a shot.
Wait, I'll come with you.
I'll make sure that
pink puffball wakes up,
even if I have to
knock him senseless.
Hey, Whis.
Am I remembering it wrong,
or did that lazy slob fall
asleep and leave us down
a man at that little tournament
we had with Champa?
Yes. It was just as you've
described it, my lord.
How dare he embarrass me again
by pulling that same
nonsense a second time!
I will not let him
get away with that!
Besides, that ill-mannered
glutton's been on my bad side
ever since "the
pudding incident"!
Oh my, you're still holding a
grudge against him over that?
[BEERUS]
Let's go! Now, Goku!
[BULMA]
He... already left.
[BEERUS grunts]
[NARRATOR]
The 7th Universe team
now finds itself in a
perilous situation.
Will Buu's sleeping habits leave
them down a member?
Time is running out, with only
four hours and ten minutes
to go until the
tournament begins.
Think quickly, Goku.
What are you going to do?
Boogie Back!
Wish we had better timing
To explore this attraction
Put on a smile, it's showtime
And I'm just playing a part
Let's get lost in the rhythm,
dancing dancing heart
Head over heels
I'm falling falling down
(Boogie Back!)
My heartbeat
keeps growing faster
Every step that I take
brings me back to you
(Boogie Back!)
Give me happy ever after
Let the dream
of our love come true
Boogie Back!
[GOKU]
Hey, it's me, Goku!
If history's taught me anything,
it's that nothing
can wake up Buu.
And without him,
we don't stand a chance
in the Tournament of Power.
Oh no, now Krillin and 18
are backin' out, too?
Well, that's no good!
At this rate, our universe
will be wiped out for sure!
Next time, on Dragon Ball Super:
"A State of Emergency!
Failure to Reach Ten Members!"
Make sure you
don't miss it, okay?