♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the ocean-churning,
sky-scorching battle
between Super Saiyan God Goku
and Lord Beerus the Destroyer
had nearly reached its peak.
As the power of both gods
apparently swelled
to their maximum,
Beerus believed he had won.
It was a valiant effort, Goku.
How can that be?
[GOKU]
I can't believe it either.
[gasps]
The Super Saiyan God power just
spoke to me loud and clear.
And there's no mistaking it.
It's telling me...
...to keep on pushing
even higher!
[bellows]
[yells]
[gasps]
[NARRATOR] As their
divine energy collides,
onlookers stare up with bated
breath, hoping the universe
will not be ripped apart. Now!
[NARRATOR] "Goku,
Surpass Super Saiyan God!"
[KIBITO KAI gasps]
We're here.
We're all still here!
The chain reaction.
It didn't happen!
It seems that last
shockwave was a false alarm,
representing a tiny
fraction of their energy.
It's mostly still up there.
[gasps]
[GOKU grunts]
[grunts]
[yells]
[BEERUS]
Heh.
[chuckles]
No way!
[grunts]
[yells]
Such power.
[ELDER KAI] Yes, we're lucky,
at least for now.
The destructive force of their
colliding blasts is cataclysmic,
but most of it didn't escape
in that shockwave as I feared.
It's made a
super, super, super
high density ball of energy,
not unlike a collapsing star.
But on a much larger scale.
And if that orb explodes,
then it's doomsday for sure.
[gulps]
[GOKU growls]
[BEERUS grunts]
[growls]
[ALL gasp]
[PARTY MC 2A]
Whoa...
[REPORTER 12A]
Can you see this, folks?
The distortions continue
rippling through our city
and across the globe!
They seem weaker now,
but much more frequent!
Is "omen of doom"
too strong a phrase?
This reporter thinks not!
This is crazy!
Kinda feels like
the world's ending!
[WHIS]
Most likely, yes.
Wait, are you kiddin' me?
I did not anticipate
a Super Saiyan God
possessing this much power,
and unfortunately the
consequences are most dire.
It seems the best
we can hope for would be
to limit the annihilation
to your star system
and a few of
your closest neighbors.
I'm speculating that's what
my lord will attempt.
But if the energy ensnared in
that orb expels completely,
well, it will prove even gods
can be caught unaware.
Uuuh... Could you explain
that with smaller words?
There are two
fighters having a fight
and their powers
are very big and scary.
They will make your planet,
and maybe everything, go boom.
Uhh.
Mhmmm!
[yells]
[VIDEL gasps]
So it's over? But--
Blue guy!
Can't you just save us all
with your magic glow stick,
like you did before?
Before I simply
caught an airship.
That's a far cry from
stopping a concentration
of divine energy with the power
to destroy this universe.
[MR. SATAN groans]
Then, can't you
tell your pal or lord
or whatever to
stop fightin' up there?
Please! I'm beggin' ya!
I'll be your best bud!
[WHIS]
Mmnh.
I got it!
[MR. SATAN]
Will ya do it for this?
[WHIS]
Oh?
What?! An all-you-can-eat,
anywhere-in-the-world voucher?!
Oh! I have to admit,
that is awfully enticing!
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
[WHIS] Oh dear.
What do I say to that?
Say "yeah"!
It's so tempting!
It's not fair!
Of all the things,
why did he have to pick that?!
[clears throat]
Sorry but I must decline.
[MR. SATAN groans]
But aren't you gonna die too?
[GOKU grunts]
[BEERUS growls]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU yells]
[BEERUS growls]
[yells]
Your resilience is astounding,
but let's end this!
There's nothing more
tiresome than a stalemate!
[GOKU yells]
[BEERUS growls]
[bellows]
[BEERUS yells]
No! It can't be over!
[MR. SATAN]
You ain't destroyin' nothin'!
Earth's defender says no way!
Go, Dad!
You're all better?
I'm comin'! Hang on!
Thank goodness you're here.
[MR. SATAN groans]
[ALL whimper]
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH gasp]
[MR. SATAN]
What?
Huh? Huh?
Did I do that?
[GOHAN] How do you feel, Videl?
Are you and the baby okay?
We're fine.
[GOHAN] I thought that
blast had us for sure,
but it looks like
everyone's okay.
What did we just see?
The orb disappeared.
Ancestor, what happened?
[ELDER KAI]
Hmmm.
I stopped it, but how?
[gasps]
The power of love!
Like you hear about
in all those old legends
and rock songs and stuff.
It was my love for Videl
and my grandbaby.
It was so pure
that it conquered all!
It did!
[laughs]
The World Champ strikes again!
[phone rings]
[phone beeps]
Yeah? Savior here.
[PIIZA]
Sorry to interrupt, sir,
but we're getting
flooded with calls.
Everyone wants to know
what you're doing about this.
[MR. SATAN]
Your timing's perfect!
Set up a post-victory press
conference, right now!
A what?
[MR. SATAN] Don't you
get what just happened?
I just saved the whole world
from explodin', that's what!
I need you to set up
an autograph party, too,
and bring a big box
of my favorite pens!
No, no, the banquet
hall's too small!
Reserve the big dome for this,
with the extra screens outside!
Yeah of course...
Well my goodness, Lord Beerus.
I never expected you to
take such an extreme measure.
The surprises continue.
[panting]
I've neutralized
the energy that had built up
between us, so we can
resume with a clean slate.
But how, where did it go?
Not your concern.
It's a complicated technique,
requiring a one hundred
percent power up.
[GOKU]
You powered up just now?
Yes.
They almost
destroyed the universe,
and Beerus wasn't even
using all his power?
You're saying after all that,
with me barely hanging on,
you were still
holding back your power?
Would've been sad otherwise,
don't you think?
I'm a Destroyer,
elite among gods.
I can't max out
against some Saiyan deity.
Using full power to
defeat you would have been
too humiliating to take. It
would have been better to die.
Ahhh!
So that's what this is about?
Protecting your image?
Yes. Or at least that's how
I felt until this moment.
But now...
Errr--I don't care about
the embarrassment anymore!
The other gods can think what
they want, say what they want,
laugh all they want;
I don't care!
All that matters to me now
is beating you, Saiyan!
I'll use everything I have,
every depth of power,
as long as I can crush you!
[GOKU]
Huh?
[panting]
[chuckles]
All right, Beerus,
let's do this.
Why are you smiling like that?
Were you holding back too?
Is that possible?
No, I was using
every bit of power I had.
Some... new strategy then?
I'm out of those too.
I've tried every one.
[BEERUS]
Hmmm.
You're a strange one,
aren't you?
I guess so.
And I could say
the same thing
about you, Beerus.
[GOKU groans]
Come on, I thought
we were past the cheap shots.
t's not my fault
you have a bad habit
of dropping your guard.
You clearly weren't bluffing
about having more power.
Your punches
are totally different
than five minutes ago,
it's incredible!
If you haven't noticed,
your strength
is still increasing too!
[GOKU groans]
[yells]
Here you go!
One hundred percent!
Believe me, I'm not
holding back either!
Here's one you won't
be able to dodge.
Huh?!
[GOKU grunts]
Let me go!
Not today!
[groans]
Head-butting
is for street fights,
not a battle of gods!
Yeah well,
it worked, didn't it?
Didn't even hurt.
You liar.
They're both
fighting harder now,
channeling more
divine energy than ever.
But they aren't
making any shockwaves,
like all the force is going
straight into each other.
Why would that be?
The shockwaves were a show.
[KIBITO KAI]
Huh?
And now...
they're both just fighting
like they want it to end.
Hm? Seems your time's up.
I'm going to pretend
I didn't hear that.
[yells]
[sighs]
Listen, there's nothing
to be ashamed of.
What?
Again and again,
you've managed to overcome
your own limitations
and reached heights
no Saiyan mortal should.
Though your divinity
was borrowed,
you challenged me like few have.
It's a magnificent achievement.
Would you please stop
talking to me like it's over?
Well that was crazy.
Right guys?
That looked scary,
everyone okay?
Yeah, I'm not sure
what happened but it was fun!
Hey! It's Dad,
I feel him again!
Me too. But hold on,
if we can sense his energy...
...then that
would mean he's...
Yes, your deduction is accurate.
As established, you couldn't
sense him in this battle
because his energy was divine.
You sense him now
because he has reached
the time limit of the power
that ceremony afforded him
and returned
to his normal range.
He is again a Super Saiyan,
no longer a god.
If that's true, then--
But my dad
can still win, can't he?
[WHIS]
I'm afraid not.
Cheer up. He doesn't
know your dad.
You know, you were wrong before!
You said our
solar system would blow up
and maybe
the universe too,
but then nothing happened!
And you're wrong now!
Well, that's fair enough.
I'm not all-knowing and
though it's most unlikely,
I do hope you're right.
My lord hasn't been this
active in nine hundred years,
and that makes him
even more unpredictable.
So I suppose there's a small
chance we can cling to.
But in any case,
I've got my souvenir
to commemorate this planet
if it is reduced to dust,
so I should be heading out now.
Stay here. We're telling you
it's not over yet.
You will kindly
remove your hand.
[PICCOLO grunts]
I said remove it.
What was that for?
[PICCOLO] Was that
some sort of message?
Is he suggesting there's
nothing to worry about?
[BEERUS]
I cherish my strength.
But it comes with
its own breed of sadness.
Once again, I must
bid farewell to an opponent
who brought me so much fun.
Don't you understand, Saiyan?
The lights have gone out.
Our party is finished.
Ah!
Your Super Saiyan God
power has played out.
You're once again
unworthy of my time.
[yells]
What the--?
[groans]
Yeah!
[BEERUS groans]
What's happening?
Uh... A fight in space?
But your god power has run out!
[GOKU]
What?
Just look, you idiot!
The glowing red aura of your
Super Saiyan God power is gone.
You're normal again!
You seriously
didn't notice that?
Well, no. When did
it happen? That's strange.
I guess I did lose it but
I'm not feeling weaker at all.
What's going on, Lord Beerus?
How the hell should I know?
[GOKU] I don't know.
Don't gods know that stuff?
Ahem.
Even though the Super
Saiyan God power expired,
your body has learned
from the experience
of fighting in god form.
Merely feeling that level
of power was enough
to push you to new heights.
In a sense, the god power
is part of you now.
The red glow of Saiyan
divinity may have left you,
but the strength now burns
within you like a flame.
Am I wrong?
Well, honestly I don't know.
And it doesn't matter, right?
All that matters is that
I can still win this thing.
Oooh! Why have I allowed
myself to dignify such a fool?
Am I missing something,
because I think
I'm getting a bit lost.
I should be careful.
Or your battle-obsessed
simplemindedness
could rub off on me.
[chuckles]
Although, seeing how I've
acted, maybe it already has.
I'm getting antsy here.
Can we get back to the fight?
Sure. Bring it on.
[bellows]
[yells]
[GOKU chuckles]
[laughs]
[BOTH laugh]
[screams]
[yells]
[NARRATOR] Our hero's time
as a diety is gone,
but his incredibly
enhanced power is not,
ushering in a new era
of Saiyan might.
It's no longer god versus god,
but god versus Goku.
To this point, they've been
showing off their powers,
but now they're both
ready to move in
for the knockout blow.
Only one question remains.
Who will win this fight?
The thrilling conclusion,
next time on Dragon Ball Super!
I look back
to when I was young
Reminisce on all that I've done
In my hands, I held
The dreams of my childhood,
that now've come to pass
So let's ride upon
the wind and journey to
A world we've never known
(It's a brand new story)
Now, a new chapter starts
Shining Star
In the night be
my compass and guide
Take me to where I belong
The warmth we once shared
Will always be there
Its magic lives on in our hearts
Shining Star
Give me strength
from your light up above
Show me the way to be brave
My hands still hold onto hope
that together we'll manifest
All that we dreamed of
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And I've had a lot
of fun in this fight,
but I know when
it's time to get serious.
I don't care
how strong Beerus is,
I won't let him
blow up this planet
and everybody I love like
it's some meaningless rock!
The divine energy is gone, but
he still has to get through me!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"This Is All the Power I've Got!
A Settlement between Gods!"
You've been through
this whole battle with me.
Make sure you don't
miss the end!