♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[GOKU groaning]
Goku!
Hang on, Dad!
[PICCOLO]
Stay with us. You hear me!
I can't feel
a heartbeat. He's dead.
[PICCOLO gasps]
[GOTEN whimpers]
[GOTEN]
Dad, no!
[sobbing]
[NARRATOR]
"Goku Dies!
An Assassination
That Must Be Executed."
--[ANIMAL chirps]
--[GOKU grunts]
Goku!
Come on in, lunch is ready!
[GOKU]
I can't sense it.
I can't sense his energy.
[GOTEN]
Huuuuh...?
[CHICHI]
Huh?
[GOKU]
No. He won't let me sense it.
[rustling]
[GOKU]
Chichi, there are three roaches
crawling behind the fridge.
Why would you say that
while we're eating?
[GOKU]
Huh?
You know, you sure
have been acting
pretty weird today, Goku.
You're just pecking
at your food like a bird
and wearing that silly
outfit since you woke up.
Oh.
[laughing]
There's a good reason
for it, Chichi.
You see, uh...
[GOKU grunts]
[shrieks]
Ah! Oh, sorry
'bout that, mail dude.
[MAILMAN 71A]
Um, here's your mail, sir.
[CHICHI, GOTEN]
Huh?
What's wrong with Dad?
[VEGETA grunting]
[BEERUS]
Hey, Whis.
Oh, good morning, Lord Beerus.
Yes, good morning.
I assume your star student
already reached his peak?
Pardon?
[BEERUS] Well, I haven't
seen Goku showing up for
his training sessions lately?
That sees a bit odd.
So what exactly is he doing?
Uh...
"Uh"? Don't you
"uh" at me, Whis!
Get it straight! We could be
summoned to participate
in a martial arts tournament
at any moment,
depending on Grand Zeno's whim,
and Goku is the
Seventh Universe's anchor!
[VEGETA]
He thinks the anchor is Kakarot?
[WHIS] Well, sir, I suppose
it's possible he's continuing
his training back on Earth.
[BEERUS] How can you be
so apathetic about this?
If Goku's fighting skills fall
even the slightest bit short
of Grand Zeno's
very demanding expectations,
do you have any idea
what will happen to us?
[VEGETA grunts]
[BEERUS]
Whis! I'm making you responsible
for getting Goku
into shape! Hmph!
[WHIS]
As you wish, sir.
Hm.
[VEGETA]
Look at him. He knows something.
Right, now then, Vegeta,
I say we resume our training.
[VEGETA] Something fishy's
going on with Kakarot,
and you know
what it is. Don't you?
[WHIS]
Uh!
I haven't the faintest idea.
[VEGETA] Uh! Oh,
suit yourself. Don't tell me.
I'll just redouble
my efforts so Kakarot can't
outpace me with
whatever he's doing.
Well, it is quite remarkable
what he's putting
himself through.
--[VEGETA grunts]
--[WHIS] Whoopsie.
I knew it, so he is doing
some kind of special training!
[WHIS laughing]
Don't just laugh it off!
Give me the same
coaching he's getting!
Ah, but you've only
completed a mere handful
of your 100 sparring
drills so far.
[VEGETA grunts]
[yells]
[WHIS]
Hm.
Then let's turn things up
a notch and speed them through!
[yells]
[GOKU] Okay, did I get
everything Chichi asked for?
[GOTEN] He's had his eyes
closed this whole time.
That's weird, right?
[GOHAN] Maybe, but Dad's
always doing something weird.
He prob'ly just thought up
some crazy new kinda training.
[GOTEN]
Oh no, look! After him!
Hey, Goten, wait!
Why? What for?
Dad's gonna recognize us if
we're still dressed like this.
We need disguises.
There!
[GOTEN grunts]
Here, put this on.
Man, that's totally lame.
I'll just wear these.
Aaah...!
You used to think my Great
Saiyaman outfit was awesome.
[GOKU] Hmm. My instincts
say to go this way.
Hmm.
[PEOPLE shouting]
[GOKU] Focusing all my energy.
Yep, it's this way.
[MAN 71B]
You're blocking our view!
--[MAN 71C] I can't see!
--[WOMAN 71A] Get outta the way!
We're so sorry!
[WOMAN 71B] This is
a highly emotional scene!
--[GOHAN] Excuse us.
--Yeah, our bad!
[GOKU]
No, no. This way.
I'm definitely
sensing something.
Oh, no!
What is wrong with him?
Oh, come on, Dad!
What in the heck
is he doing in here?
Aw. Jeez. I can't
take this anymore!
I'm opening my eyes!
[GOKU screams]
This isn't right at all, is it?
[yells]
[GOHAN]
'Scuse us, just passing through.
--[GIRL 71A, 71B] Aah!
--[GOTEN] Sorry!
Are you here?
Where are you?
Sounds like he's
looking for somebody.
Yup.
[GOKU]
Where are you?
Are you up there?
[car horn honking]
Outta the way!
[groans]
Oh, hi Bulma.
[BULMA groaning]
What is wrong with you,
dashing out in front
of a speeding car?
I could've be--
[BULMA gasps]
[GOKU]
Uuh.
[BULMA]
Oh. Uh. Ah!
Hey! I was trying to punch you!
[GOKU chuckles]
Sorry about that!
--[BULMA] Sheesh!
--You see that?
Normally, he'd never dodge
one of Bulma's punches.
Yeah, that's odd.
I'm gonna find out what's up,
even if it means
inviting him to dinner.
[GOKU] Oh, boy!
Everything looks delicious!
Wow! This tuna is fantastic!
Piccolo, you gotta try this!
Come on, join us! Eat something!
[PICCOLO]
I'm grilling!
Do not interrupt
the grill master!
[GOKU]
Well, if you don't hurry it up,
I'm gonna scarf it all down!
Om-mm. Mm. Mmm! Mmm!
Amazing! That entire
feast was so yummy!
I hope they grill up
some more food soon!
--[GOTEN] Hey, Dad.
--[GOKU] Uh?
You got a sec?
Oh yeah, I've been
meaning to ask,
why were you following
me around today?
[GOHAN, GOTEN gasp]
So you knew the whole time?
[GOKU]
Of course I did. Duh.
Okay, well in that case,
who were you looking for?
Yeah, tell us! We wanna know!
[GOKU]
Hmm. All right, boys,
but whatever happens,
you gotta promise
not to tell your mom,
you hear me?
Don't worry Dad,
your secret's safe with us.
Mm. Yeah, we promise.
[GOKU]
Hm.
Well, the truth is...
somebody's trying to kill me.
[BOTH]
Huh?!
♪
[thunder rumbling]
[distant sirens wailing]
Our top story tonight,
one of the universe's
most wanted criminals,
Frost, remains at large.
And according to a statement
released by Cabba...
[GIRL 71C gasps]
Mm.
[GIRL 71C]
Huh?
[chuckles]
Just look out there,
such a beautiful city.
[laughing]
♪
[MAN 71E]
It's true!
[MALE BODYGUARD 71A]
Hmm.
[MALE BODYGUARD 71B]
What's wrong?
[MALE BODYGUARD 71A]
We have any visitors
scheduled for this hour?
[MALE BODYGUARD 71B]
Nah, none that I've heard about.
Mm.
[BOSS MAN 71A]
Hmph.
[ding]
[MALE BODYGUARD 71A gasps]
There's no one in here!
[MALE BODYGUARD 71B]
Keep lookin'!
They gotta be close by!
[HIT]
I've come to kill you.
[BOSS MAN 71A]
Huh?
Oh yeah, and who
are you supposed to be?
If you must know, I'm Hit.
Aah! Wait, did you say Hit?
Th-The legendary assassin?
What are you morons
waitin' for? Shoot the bastard!
Are you deaf? Come on, move it!
It's no use.
Time has stopped for
everyone except you and me.
Take this!
[HIT]
Your resistance is pointless.
[BOSS MAN 71A grunts]
Hey, listen!
I've got loads of money!
How much do you want? Hell,
you can have my whole fortune!
I'll even throw in this tower!
Not a chance.
[BOSS MAN 71A groans]
[groaning, gasping]
[MALE BODYGUARD 71A]
Boss!
[MALE BODYGUARD 71B]
The boss is down!
[MALE BODYGUARD 71A]
Sir! Are you all right?
C'mon, get up!
[MALE BODYGUARD 71B]
I don't get it!
What just happened?
[MALE BODYGUARD 71A]
Well, don't just stand there!
Hurry up and call an ambulance!
[MALE BODYGUARD 71B]
Right!
[HIT]
On to the next target.
[HIT chuckles]
[crunch]
[GOKU yawns]
Oh man, I ate way too much!
[GOHAN] For someone
facing imminent danger,
he sure has a healthy appetite.
But hey, that's Dad for ya.
[PICCOLO]
What's wrong, Gohan?
You've been acting a little
funny all night long.
[GOHAN]
Who, me? N-No.
Why are you suddenly
so concerned about Goku?
[GOHAN]
Uuuh.
[PICCOLO] Gohan, there can be
no secrets between us.
[GOHAN]
You're right.
[PICCOLO]
So what's going on, huh?
[GOHAN]
Well, the truth is...
[GOKU]
Hm?
He's finally on his way.
Hm!
[GOKU] I don't want anyone
interrupting this fight.
Come on. Follow me, Hit!
So wait, you believe
that your father's life
--is in jeopardy?
--He says so.
[PICCOLO] Come on. There aren't
many people out there
who could possibly
pose a threat to him.
He told me who it was.
It's that Hit guy.
You mean Hit from Universe Six?
--[GOHAN] Well... yeah.
--[PICCOLO gasps]
Where did Goku go?
I'm not sure.
[BOTH gasp]
[GOHAN]
Dad!
[VEGETA grunting]
[yells]
All right, now how many
drills are left?
Really, are you asking me ?
Why, I had simply assumed
that you would be
keeping track of them
yourself, Vegeta.
Oh. Yeah,
I was totally counting.
There's just three more, cool.
Ah, ah, no cheating.
You actually have 13 more to go.
Aaah. So you were counting then.
[GOKU]
All right, come on out, Hit!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU]
Behind that rock.
It's faint, but I can
sense his energy there.
[GOKU grunts]
I can't feel Goku's
energy anymore--
you know what that means!
He must've turned
Super Saiyan Blue!
Dad's energy just disappeared!
Odds are he's getting
ready to fight Hit.
Come on, Piccolo, we can't
let him do this alone.
[PICCOLO] I'm sure that's
the last thing Goku wants,
but you're right.
I have a really bad
feeling about this.
Goten, you stay here.
Aw, don't try an' treat me
like a little kid!
I'm coming, too!
[GOHAN]
But Goten.
All right then,
both of you, follow me!
[BOTH]
Right!
[gasps]
This isn't personal.
I was hired to kill you.
[GOKU] You sure managed to sneak
up on me pretty easily, huh?
Even with all the training I've
been doing this past year.
Then again, I'd expect
no less from you, Hit.
[chuckles]
Of course I could just
claim that I killed you
and you could go into hiding.
How would the great Goku respond
to such a merciful offer?
Well, for starters, I'd say,
"Thanks, but no thanks."
[HIT] Yes. That's exactly
what I thought.
Now then, it's time for me
to make the donuts.
Turn around and face me.
[GOKU] So you can't kill me
with my back to you, huh?
[HIT] Normally I don't mind
sneaking up on my prey.
It makes it easier on them.
They have less time
to be afraid.
But you're different.
I've decided my single strike
to you will be head on.
A single strike? Hm.
Long time no see, Hit.
How's it goin'?
This is goodbye.
Your Time Skip ain't
gonna work on me anymore.
[HIT] You really think I'd use
the same technique on you again?
Do I look that charitable?
So you're admitting I can
outmaneuver it now.
You're gonna have to
get more creative
if you want to bring the pain.
There will be no pain.
Like I said, it will
take just one strike.
Sorry, but I don't think so.
[yells]
--Huh?
--[GOKU] I didn't hit him?
[GOKU] That's definitely
not Time Skipping.
If punching won't work
on him, maybe this will!
[GOKU]
No, that wasn't his attack.
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU] There's no way a punch
can hit me from that distance!
[yells]
[GOKU groaning]
Oh, no!
[continues groaning]
I will be back.
Once the dust has fully settled.
Goku!
Hang on, Dad!
[PICCOLO]
Stay with us, you hear me!
I can't feel
a heartbeat. He's dead.
[PICCOLO gasps]
[GOTEN whimpers]
[GOTEN]
Dad, no!
[sobbing]
♪ Closing Song ♪
1, 2, 3, I'm hungry
Nothin' but fried rice fantasies
I got a passion for the dish
Nothin' compares to what it is
I don't get my fill
I'm like a monster
Those ingredients
No one could possibly resist
They got me so bewitched
Make it spicy and I can't say no
Seasoning is everything,
I think so
Bon Appetit
I'll burn the world
straight to the ground
If I can't have
that greasy mound
My hanger's not to be ignored!
1, 2, 3, I'm hungry
Nothin' but fried rice fantasies
I want fried rice,
I'm so hungryyyyyy-yeah!
[GOHAN]
Uh, hi there. It's me, Gohan.
I don't know what to say.
Dad dying like this.
While it's not the first time,
it's still a shock.
[GOTEN]
Hey, Dad! Dad!
Are you really dead?
You can't be!
[GOHAN] I don't understand.
It's impossible.
How on Earth was he able
to overthrow Dad so easily?
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Will He Strike Back?
The Unseen Killing Technique!"
[GOHAN] Make sure
you don't miss it, okay?