♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
no sooner had the Tournament
of Power begun than
the warriors from the Ninth
Universe targeted Goku.
[ROH laughs]
You like that?
Once you're ensnared
in their deathtrap,
you can never get out!
There is no escaping from the
Trio of Danger's ultimate combo,
the unbreakable
three-sided attack!
Or as I call it...
...the "Dangers Triangle"!
[NARRATOR]
However, with Vegeta's help,
Goku was able to fend
off his attackers.
[BROTHERS]
Triangle Danger... Beam!
[VEGETA yells]
Final...
[GOKU]
Kamehame...
[GOKU, VEGETA]
...Ha!
[BROTHERS whimpering]
[BROTHERS groan]
[SIDRA]
That's...
That's all ten of our
fighters... eliminated!
[ROH]
Grand Zeno, no!
[ZENOS]
Bye-bye!
[ZENOS laugh]
[BEERUS]
Hey, Whis.
What happened to the
Ninth Universe itself?
[WHIS]
Huh... It's as they said.
It's all just been erased.
Absolutely everything and
everyone is gone, my lord.
[NARRATOR] With one of the eight
universes being wiped out,
the consequence of losing
has hit home for the
remaining fighters.
The stakes have never been
higher than they are now.
[NARRATOR] "Show Them!
Krillin's Underlying Strength!"
So they're gone forever, huh?
Yeah. Though I guess
we've already seen
a universe get erased before.
In Trunks' future.
[VEGETA]
Hm. You're right.
[GOKU] When Zenny decides
something has to go,
that's the end of it.
And that's why I'm gonna keep
fighting with all I've got.
I'm never gonna give up
until I win.
Well, you may think you'll
be the last man standing,
but the one who gets
the Super Dragon Balls
will be the great Vegeta.
Oh, well. It appears
I'm all that's left of
the Ninth Universe, which
was under my supervision,
but I can't say this is
entirely unexpected.
Yes, the Ninth Universe
was obliterated,
but it was a necessary culling.
In truth, those eight universes
should have thanked Goku
for this grand tournament.
If not for him,
they would be gone already.
Instead, one will be
able to survive.
The losing universes must be
destroyed, to eliminate the weak
and bring the Cosmos
into balance.
For ultimately, is that
not the true purpose
of this Tournament of Power?
[FIGHTERS murmuring]
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
Roh, the Ninth's Supreme Kai,
and their Destroyer
god, Sidra...
I can no longer feel
their presence.
No, of course you can't.
Once they're erased,
they become nothing.
That's what being erased means.
But they were gods.
And they were snuffed out
without any hesitation.
[CHAMPA]
That's why they're so scary.
Those Grand Zenos.
They mean business,
that's for sure.
--[VADOS sighs]
--Huh?!
[VADOS]
Farewell, Lord Champa.
I don't know how long I'll
continue after you're gone,
but I'll try to be strong.
[CHAMPA]
Darn it, Vados! Shut it!
We're not out of this thing yet,
and quit reminding us how
you won't be erased!
We get the point!
[laughs] I'm sorry, my lord,
but if you want any hope
of surviving, you'll need your
warriors to pull off a miracle.
[CHAMPA growls]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[KRILLIN]
Just breathe, Krillin.
You knew from the start
that seven of eight
universes would go down.
Nothing's changed.
[exhales]
[inhales, exhales]
All right.
[PICCOLO chuckles]
What's wrong? You startin'
to lose your nerve?
Just thrown for a bit
of a loop, that's all.
[GOHAN]
How 'bout everyone else?
We all good?
Yeah. At least for now.
Pretty intense to see a
universe wiped out that quickly.
Really makes you think.
--Yeah.
--It sure as heck does.
[FRIEZA] Look at those brightly
colored little pipsqueaks.
I find the disparity between
their syrupy, childlike voices
and their astringent actions
to be quite vexing.
But hear me now.
There will soon come a
day when Emperor Frieza
shall reign over you.
[A18 grunts]
You seem upset about something.
Uh, did you not see?
A universe was just wiped out.
That must freak you
out a little bit.
Not really.
If we lose, we cease to exist.
We already knew that.
Domestic life has
softened you up, sister.
Uh!
No, I'm glad.
It's good at times.
But right now we both need to
remember that we're androids.
The infinite energy kind.
We never get tired.
And that should give us an edge
over these organics, right?
That's an excellent point.
Well, I'm ready if you are.
This fight appears to have
reached a standstill.
[BEERUS]
The Ninth led off with
an aggressive,
coordinated attack,
and paid for it by being
the first extermination.
[ELDER KAI] Now that it's
sunk in for everybody that
the Grand Zenos were serious
about annihilating universes,
teams may be realizing
they can't be so reckless.
They're probably rethinking
their strategies.
Perhaps, but time will
not just wait idly by.
All the fighters
have stopped fighting.
I wonder why they stopped.
Don't worry, sires,
they should resume shortly.
In fact, I see a few
resilient warriors
getting back into action now.
[VEGETA]
Okay, Kakarot,
try not to waste all
your energy showing off.
Same goes for you.
Try not to have too much fun.
I make no promises.
After all, I owe this guy
a serious beating.
[yells]
Hey, outta my way!
You'll have to go through
me first, tough guy.
[VEGETA grunting]
Aren't you adorable.
[CHAMPA] Sorry, Brother,
your guy's outta luck!
I guess he forgot my guy's
body can absorb hits
without taking damage!
Yeah that's the spirit,
Botamo, attack!
Don't hold back!
[yelling]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[BOTAMO gasping]
[VEGETA grunting]
That throw won't
work on me this time!
I figured as much.
[BOTAMO stammers]
[BOTAMO gasps]
[VEGETA yells]
Oh, yeah!
Excellent work,
Vegeta, very clever!
Now, toss him over!
No, wait! Time out!
Time out! Hey, this isn't fair!
You can take your
timeout on the bench!
[screams] Not Botamo!
What are you waiting for?!
Somebody help him!
[MAGETTA]
Hoo-ahhh!
Chugga-chugga-chugga.
Boom Boom.
[VEGETA groans]
[growling]
[BOTAMO grunting]
[BOTAMO]
Ha, ha!
[BOTAMO chuckles]
[VEGETA]
Hmph.
[DIUM laughing]
[DIUM caws]
[KRILLIN gasping]
[GOHAN grunts]
[DIUM gasping]
Okay, just remember--
as long as one of us makes
it to the end, we all win.
Be patient, and don't fight
any more than you have to.
That shot almost got me, boy!
Ca-caw!
But if someone does
try and come at us,
that's when we make 'em pay.
[DIUM cawing]
Lord Beerus told me to use
whatever tricks it
takes just to survive.
But I've gotta at least try
to take a few of 'em out!
Destructo Disk!
Triple Blades!
[DIUM caws]
[gasping]
[ROSHI]
Ha!
[DIUM squawks]
You bird-brained fool,
what were you thinking?
Pay attention!
They had you outnumbered!
I'm sorry.
I thought I'd wing it.
Hey, Vegeta!
Remember how he wilted
when you called him names!
Insult the bastard!
You ugly bucket of bolts!
You belong in a junkyard!
Go recycle yourself
you hollow,
rust-covered tin can!
[laughs] Not gonna work!
We took some precautions against
that weakness this time!
Since our precious Metalman
loses his fighting
composure when insulted,
we're simply not going
to let him hear you.
[MAGETTA]
Ka-chug.
[VEGETA gasping]
[BEERUS]
Ahh!
Sensitivity to insults was about
the only weakness he had.
Invincible body with
an iron will to match.
Together, we are the
mighty Bota-magetta!
[MAGETTA]
Toot-toot!
[VEGETA] That's ridiculous!
You're just covering his ears!
[MAGETTA]
Bloosh!
[VEGETA]
Get off of him!
[VEGETA grunts]
Bota-magetta is invincible.
[MAGETTA]
Kerplunk! Kerplunk!
Ah! Damn it! What a joke!
Oh, my.
Android Number 18 is fighting
exceptionally well now,
and making swift work of
that warrior from the Fourth.
[SHOSA grunting]
[A18 yells]
[SHOSA groans]
Huh. Oh, don't be pathetic.
Get up.
Huh?!
[WHIS]
Oh, dear.
Has she beaten the life
out of the poor fellow?
But wait, killing opponents
is against the rules.
Oh, she'll be disqualified.
What a disaster.
Well, that could've gone better.
I guess I took it
a little too far.
[SHOSA]
Ha, ha!
[A18 screams]
[SHOSA grunts, yells]
[A18 grunting]
You see that?!
It's Shosa's famous
playing dead routine!
Oh, yeah. Suck it, Beerus!
Suck it! Suck it!
[BEERUS gasping]
Oh, no!
[screams]
Huh?
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Ya!
[A18 gasping]
It's not like you
to mess up like that.
Don't worry, I won't
let you live it down.
[KRILLIN laughing]
[A18 growls]
Shut up, it's not funny!
[KRILLIN]
Sorry.
[ALL sigh]
That could've been
such a touching moment,
but he had to ruin it.
[A18 growls]
Well, I hope you enjoyed that,
because I'm gonna
make you pay for it!
[laughing] It's cute you
think so, but no, you won't.
The two of you are
about to become
the next fighters eliminated.
Because I'm a nice guy,
I'll give you the chance
to bow out on your own.
Otherwise, I can't be
held responsible for how
this fight ends--when you're
a mangled, pulpy mess.
So just keep that in mind.
[QUITELA laughs]
Ah that's our Shosa, for you.
Wild, isn't he?
Wild's a funny way of
saying duplicitous!
Playing possum's a dirty,
rotten trick and you know it!
If someone sucker punches you,
then you hit 'em back
twice as hard, you hear me?!
Twice as hard!
Y'know that new
move we practiced?
Wanna try it?
Sure, let's take it
out for a spin.
Okay.
What are you two
babbling about over there?
If you won't fight me, then I'll
just bring the fight to you!
Let's go!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[yells]
[A18 yells]
[SHOSA groans]
[SHOSA growling]
[KRILLIN]
Here!
[SHOSA]
Huh?!
[KRILLIN, A18 grunting]
[SHOSA gasping]
[yells]
[SHOSA] It just keeps getting
faster, and bigger, too!
[A18] Take this, you
possum-playing weasel!
Oh, yeah!
[SHOSA gasping]
[SHOSA screaming]
Got him!
[A18]
Hmm...
Hey, up high, 18!
You got it.
[KRILLIN laughing]
[A18 laughs]
That fight was fantastic!
And fun-tastic, too!
[BEERUS]
Well done! Nice teamwork, guys!
That really hurts!
[SHOSA cries]
I'm so terribly sorry.
This is just embarrassing.
[KRILLIN gasps]
[MAJORA grunts]
[KRILLIN groaning]
Ow, ow, owie! [gasps]
[MAJORA grunting]
[KRILLIN screams]
[A18 yells]
[MAJORA groans]
Thanks, guess we're even.
They just keep comin' out of
the woodwork, don't they?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I guess that's just what
a battle royale is like.
Well its clear they're
all targeting us now.
If it weren't for Goku,
they wouldn't even have a
chance to save themselves,
but they'll never show
him any gratitude.
[MAJORA laughs] You managed
to catch me by surprise.
I must've let my guard down.
But you won't be so
lucky a second time.
Do you honestly think you
can best one such as me?
Hey, 18, ya might wanna
put these on now.
'Kay.
Wait, those are mine.
When did he snatch 'em?
Here I go!
[MAJORA grunts]
Hundred-Times Solar Flare!
[KRILLIN]
What the--?!
[KRILLIN groans]
[gasps]
I don't understand.
What just happened?
How was he able to attack
in that blinding light?
[QUITELA laughs]
[KRILLIN groans] Why didn't
my Solar Flare work on you?
[laughing]
[MAJORA] My eyes have long since
lost their power of sight.
[gasps] So that's why
it had no effect.
But then how could you
tell where we were?
Your aim's annoyingly
accurate, y'know!
That is the question, isn't it?
There's only one thing
I think it could be.
[MAJORA]
Hm?
He's tracking us...
by using our scent.
[KRILLIN]
Our scent?
[A18] Yeah that's right,
I'm betting he
probably had to develop
a pretty impressive sense
of smell to make up
for losing his vision.
A brilliant deduction.
You're quite perceptive,
aren't you?
Okay, fine.
Now that I know how you did it--
You believe you can defeat me?
Huh?
I know I can.
[A18 sighs]
Krillin!
Well... Though your
bravery is impressive,
trust me, you should keep
that bravado in check.
[KRILLIN] It's not really
bravado if I can back it up.
[MAJORA growls]
You're making a grave mistake.
Unless you want me to
tear you limb from limb.
Well go ahead and try it!
I'm not scared.
Stop it!
It's all right.
Just let me handle this.
[A18]
Huh?
I've got a surefire way
to outmaneuver this guy.
You must actually be delusional.
[laughs] I've never heard of
anything so preposterous!
With my heightened
sense of smell,
I can track your exact location.
There's no way around that.
I'll come after you
with everything I have.
[sniffs]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[KRILLIN yells]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[MAJORA]
I've got you now!
[KRILLIN]
H'ya!
[MAJORA]
Huh?!
[screams]
What is that offensive odor?
Gah! The stench is overpowering!
[KRILLIN]
Good!
Ka...
...me...
...ha...
Ha!
[MAJORA groaning]
[MAJORA screams]
And Contestant Majora
of the Fourth has
been eliminated.
[FUTURE ZENO]
Tap, tap!
Let's see... Majora, Majora.
Boop! He's gone.
[ZENO]
No more Majora.
They're dropping so quickly now.
Yes, it's exciting!
[groans] What a disgrace!
Success!
Yeah, but the way you
won was disgusting.
When we get home,
I'm washing those shoes.
Or better yet, burning them.
You're exceeding my extremely
low expectations for you!
Oh, yeah! Hear that?
I am absolutely
Krillin' it today!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[FROST]
How quickly the tide can change.
[KRILLIN]
Uh?
[KRILLIN screams]
[A18, BEERUS]
What?
[FROST chuckles] Carelessness
is your greatest foe.
You mess with him,
you mess with me!
[FROST] A tempting proposition,
but I have places to be!
[A18 gasps]
[A18]
Turning tail like a coward.
Sheesh, way to
blow it, big time!
Shame on you, Curly!
Uh. Yeah...
it's still Krillin, sir.
I only learn the
names of winners.
I'm sorry! You can call
me whatever you like!
You performed admirably
out there, Krillin.
I'm not too upset
about your loss.
Then you should tell
that to your face!
Well, no sense dwelling on it.
What's done is done.
But you'd better
cheer extra loud.
That's literally all you
can do at this point.
Yes, sir.
Sorry, guys. My bad.
Now you're gonna have to fight
even harder 'cause of me.
[NARRATOR] The Seventh Universe
has just lost its first fighter.
As the Tournament of Power
grows more and more intense,
can Goku and his
teammates defeat the best
in the Cosmos to secure victory?
Forty-three minutes remain
until time runs out,
and the fate of all competing
universes will be decided.
The battles continue,
next time on Dragon Ball Super.
When the time has come
to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever in my mind
as I look up to the sky
I was watching you
from your left side
Was trying to get
a good look at your face
The tears in your eyes;
were you laughing or crying?
Your long hair in the way
Blocking the thoughts inside
When the time has
come to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever I will wait,
for the light to show the way
For us to meet again
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Finally, we get to see some
Saiyan-on-Saiyan action!
And Super Saiyan 2 Caulifla's
power is off the charts!
But don't sleep on Kale!
She's rocking some
incredible energy, too!
Whoa, is this what Saiyans
are supposed to look like?
I can't let them
have all the fun.
I'd better start
powering up, too!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Rampage! A Crazed Warrior's
Savagery Awakens!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?