♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[TOP] Is that the
extent of your power?
[yells]
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
all but two universes
had been eliminated
from the Tournament of Power
and from existence itself,
leaving Universes
Eleven and Seven
to duke it out
for the right to survive.
Determined to do his part,
Vegeta challenged the
seemingly invincible Jiren.
And though he had not reached
the Ultra Instinct level
that had propelled Goku,
the Saiyan Prince believed
there was another
road to victory.
[VEGETA] But I'm the one who's
going to crush you, Jiren.
And I'll do it my way!
Final Flash!
[NARRATOR] Jiren took Vegeta's
immense assault head-on,
then countered with
a punishing blow.
I commend you for harnessing
so much power
in your last attack.
[VEGETA screaming]
Vegeta!
[gasping]
[NARRATOR] With Vegeta
gasping on the ground,
the battle continues... now!
[NARRATOR]
"Body, Soul and Power Unleashed!
Goku and Vegeta!"
[gasping]
[VEGETA gasping]
[VEGETA groaning]
[GOKU]
Vegeta!
[groaning]
[JIREN]
Now, warrior...
[GOKU gasps]
[VEGETA grunting]
[JIREN]
...time to sleep.
[VEGETA gasps]
[SPECTATORS murmur]
Jiren is a fearsome
foe, no doubt.
[BEERUS growls]
Poor Vegeta.
Heh. You should just be grateful
Jiren called him a warrior.
That's a great honor,
comin' from him.
Our mighty champion does not
bestow that title often.
It's his way of praising Vegeta
for showing the courage
to confront him and holding
nothing in reserve.
Of course the fact remains that
despite all of that effort,
Vegeta never even had a chance.
[growls]
Wow. You sure are arrogant.
[FUTURE ZENO]
Now, warrior, time to sleep.
Jiren is very cool, isn't he?
And very strong!
[VEGETA grunting]
Hang on, Vegeta.
[VEGETA panting, groaning]
[VEGETA]
I can tell, Jiren.
You still aren't using
your full power.
I'm tagging in. Jiren!
[yells]
It is time, Goku.
[GOKU chuckles]
Aw, yeah! Let's wrap this up.
[DYSPO grunts]
[DYSPO laughs] Now you're
feelin' my real power!
That'll teach you to run your
mouth off to a Pride Trooper!
[DYSPO laughs]
Huh?!
[FRIEZA] If that's all
you can muster, "Trooper,"
you shouldn't feel so proud.
[gasps]
--Wha--?
--He wasn't hurt at all--
not even a scratch!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[DYSPO]
But how?
Funny. Because, long ears,
that's exactly what I
was about to ask you.
As in, "But how did you think
such a miniscule attack
could be sufficient to topple
a top-tier titan like me?"
A grievous insult,
which I do so abhor.
[DYSPO gasps]
Tch.
[A17 yells]
[TOP grunts]
[TOP]
Justice... Flash!
[yells]
--[GOHAN] Ha!
--[TOP] Fool!
[TOP grunts]
[BOTH groan]
[A17 grunts]
[TOP]
Justice!
I'm sorry, 17.
That was my mistake.
Don't try a combo move
like that again.
Huh?
We won't win this
with tandem attacks
we've never even practiced.
All we'll do is get
in each other's way
and completely waste our
two-against-one advantage.
Okay, you got any better ideas?
[A17] Naturally. Let's think of
it as a division of labor.
I'll go on the attack
and keep him busy.
You watch and wait
for the right moment.
Then knock us both
towards the edge.
All right. I got this.
[TOP]
Hm?
What happened to your teammate?
I work better alone.
[A17 grunts]
[TOP grunts]
[TOP yelling]
[A17 grunts]
[TOP grunts]
[screams]
[TOP]
I've got you in my grip.
--Do it, Gohan!
--[TOP] Hm?
[GOHAN]
Ka...
...me...
...ha...
Ha!
[TOP]
Hm?!
Huh? No!
--[TOP grunts]
--[A17 groans]
17, move!
[TOP]
What?
Your plan almost worked.
[A17]
Tch.
[VEGETA grunting]
What is Goku doing creeping
toward Jiren like that?
He's carefully marking
his distance to him.
The Spirit Bomb failed.
So did Vegeta's Final Flash.
Long-range attacks
are pointless.
He has no choice
but to close in.
Yet Jiren's proven
you can't charge in
berserker-style, either.
Goku has to use every trick
he has to make a tiny opening
in Jiren's defenses,
then go all out.
Yeah, and that's if making a
tiny opening is even possible.
[GOKU grunts]
[yells]
I am curious--what do you
think Goku is doing?
He keeps moving in close
but then runs away again!
Could that be a strategy?
I wonder, too!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU gasps, groans]
[JIREN grunts]
[panting]
They're like energy land mines!
So that's what all that
scurrying around was about.
Goku was using those
Instant Transmissions to plant
explosive bits of energy
in the ring at Jiren's feet.
Goku must be hoping that
one of those blasts
will surprise Jiren and
make him drop his guard,
even if only for a moment!
That could be the window Goku
needs to launch his attack!
Kakarot, above you!
[gasps]
How did he get up there?
He must have leapt up the moment
that first mine detonated!
Destructo Disk!
[JIREN grunts]
[GOKU gasping]
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU grunting]
[yells]
Ha!
[gasping]
[JIREN]
It's over.
[groans]
[gasps]
[chuckles]
Destructo Disk, times six.
[JIREN]
What?
Take this, Jiren!
--[ALL gasping]
--He did it!
[BOTH gasp]
I gotcha, Jiren!
[chuckles]
Destructo Disk, times six.
[JIREN]
What?
[GOKU]
Take this, Jiren!
Heh, heh, heh.
Oh, I better move!
Wow, Goku. You borrowed
the move I used against you.
Hell yeah!
That was awesome, Goku!
There's no way Jiren can
be stopped that easily!
[JIREN growls]
[VEGETA gasps]
You fooled him for a moment,
but it'll take a lot
more than that.
Yeah, you ain't lyin'.
[VEGETA gasps]
Here he comes.
That's the part of the
ring where I put down
all those energy booby traps.
He's walking straight
through them.
He's not even trying
to avoid those blasts!
[growls] He's a monster.
[groans]
[GOKU groans]
[yells]
[GOKU screams]
[groans]
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU gasps, grunts]
Unbelievable!
His energy is so intense!
I can feel Jiren's power
surging higher now.
It's been a very long time since
I've seen him fight like this.
[yelling]
[GOKU grunting]
[ALL gasping]
--Whoa!
[GOKU grunting]
[gasps]
[gasping]
[BOTH]
Hmph.
Jiren's finally showing a tiny
glimmer of his actual power.
That was nuts. What kind
of technique was that?
You think that was some sort
of special attack, mortal?
For the almighty Jiren, that is
nothing but an ordinary punch.
[ALL gasp]
[GOKU groaning]
In all my years...
All my fights...
I've never taken
an attack like that.
There's no doubt. You really
are incredible, Jiren.
But I won't quit.
No matter the odds,
I won't back down now.
[JIREN grunts]
[VEGETA grunts]
Kakarot is right.
Any fool could see you've been
the strongest, at least so far.
But I'll still find a way
to knock you out
and win this Tournament.
When the dust settles,
I'll be the one claiming
the Super Dragon Balls.
[JIREN grunts]
[BOTH]
Here we come, Jiren!
[VEGETA, GOKU yelling]
[yelling continues]
[GOKU]
Kaio-ken!
[KRILLIN gasps]
With that multiplier,
he's tapping into all
the energy he has.
We'll just have to hope
that it's enough to end this.
[VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA]
I have to...
But only one universe
can survive.
That means no matter
how hard I fight,
there's no way to
keep that promise.
I'm going to win this charade.
And when I do, I'll use
the Super Dragon Balls
to bring you and
your universe back.
What? You would do that?
[VEGETA]
I gave my word,
from one Saiyan to another,
and I have to keep it!
I'll shatter through my limits,
in my own way, on my own terms.
And then, Jiren...
I will defeat you!
[VEGETA yells]
Just look at that energy!
It's not like the Blue
power he's shown so far.
He's tapping into
something greater.
[VEGETA yelling]
Wowie, what is he doing now?
Whatever it is, I like it!
It appears Vegeta has
crashed through his
limitations, as well.
He has coalesced a power
within himself that is
far beyond the Super
Saiyan Blue level
he has displayed in the
Tournament up to now.
Now you can finally see my all.
[ALL gasp]
Amazing! So this is
what Vegeta looks like
when he breaks through
his own limits, huh?
Bring it!
[BOTH yell]
[GOKU, VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA, GOKU groan]
[BOTH grunt]
They got him!
A joint attack.
Are Goku and Vegeta
actually working together?
Well, it appears you both
have sharpened your attacks.
[BOTH yelling, grunting]
[VEGETA yells]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU, VEGETA groan]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA]
Hmph.
Awesome! They're
overpowering him now!
Yes. With both of them attacking
like this, they could win.
Jiren's off his rhythm.
He's making mistakes.
Goku and Vegeta
are not accustomed
to fighting as a team,
so their combination moves
are far from harmonious.
And yet that actually appears
to be confounding Jiren
and playing to their advantage.
This is it. The breakthrough
they've been searching for.
[NARRATOR] At long last,
the champions of the Saiyan race
have launched an effective
counterattack against Jiren.
Goku has amplified his Super
Saiyan Blue with his Kaio-ken,
while Vegeta has reached a level
we've never seen before.
With this combined assault,
Jiren seems to be
backed into a corner.
But can he truly be defeated?
Only seven minutes remain
in the Tournament of Power.
Next time, on Dragon Ball Super!
Whirling all around
and then back again
The song that connects you
to the heavens
Strength that goes
beyond all measure
Expanding to a beat
that won't end
The meteors fall like rain drops
Astrological tears
from my eyelids
A strong emotion
from deep within
Has been awakened
A spark of possibility
Shines softly like a star
in the night sky
A wish from long
ago now shoots by
And I'm awakened
A never-ending melody,
so enchanting
You're always the one
who makes me tremble
The meteors keep falling down
Surging right into my heart
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Vegeta and I are amping things
up in our fight against Jiren,
hoping we've finally
found an advantage.
But that's not the only
action in the ring!
Gohan's about to find himself
in a tough spot against Dyspo,
and it looks like Frieza's
happy to jump in!
Come on, you guys, let's see how
the two of you fight as a team!
Next time, on Dragon Ball Super:
"A Storm-and-Stress Assault!
Gohan's Last Stand!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?