♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Super,
Trunks was reunited
with his old master, Gohan.
At first, Trunks was confused,
barely recognizing
his former mentor
in his newly domesticated state.
However, spending time
with Gohan's family
ultimately motivated Trunks
to fight even harder
for a peaceful future
in his own timeline.
Meanwhile, after sensing
something familiar
in Goku Black, Beerus
and Whis realized his energy
closely resembled that of
someone in the Tenth Universe.
With Goku in tow, they're on
their way to see him, now!
[NARRATOR]
"Uncover Black's Identity!
Off to the 10th Universe's
World of the Kai's!"
[GOKU sniffing, grunting]
Knock it off.
[GOKU]
Aaah, I can't take it anymore!
Come on, Lord Beerus, what's
this Zamasu guy's deal, huh?
Please, you gotta
gimme something here!
For crying out--
Whis, will you take this?
Of course. Huh.
Where do I start?
Zamasu began as a lower diety,
with a rank equivalent
to the one you call King Kai.
But due to his impressive
aptitude for martial arts,
he's now being groomed
to take over
for their Supreme Kai one day.
Whoa, seriously?
[BEERUS growls]
Yes, quite.
Hey! Give the
Destroyer some space!
Uh! Sorry 'bout that,
Lord Beerus.
[BEERUS] Just remember, if I
were to shrug you off right now,
you would instantly turn into
a cloud of cosmic dust.
Oh, okay--there's no need
to get so dark.
[BEERUS]
Hmmm.
Try to place nice.
[birds chirping]
[clink]
[tea pouring]
Master. Your tea is served.
Oh, my. What a lovely,
subtly sweet aroma.
Let's see how it tastes.
Tea made by one pure
of heart is unclouded
and always the most
delicious to boot.
Thank you very much, master.
[GOWASU] The fact you can
make this cup shows me
your heart is
where it needs to be.
Now as long as you keep
training your mind and body,
without letting pride intervene,
and continue to monitor
the affairs of mortals
to gain understanding,
you'll be in good shape.
[ZAMASU]
Master Gowasu?
[GOWASU]
Hm?
[ZAMASU]
There is something that's been
weighing on my mind lately.
[GOWASU]
Go on, tell me.
These mortals we watch.
Are they creatures truly worthy
of our protection, sir?
With respect, I've observed
more mortal dealings
than I care to count.
They thrive, quarrel, perish,
all on an endless loop.
And so it seems to me,
for them to keep doing this
is the height of futility.
[GOWASU] Ah. That is the path
mortals must take.
What sense does it make for us
to protect these flawed beings
when they persistently
repeat the same tragic mistakes?
Would it not be more
merciful on our part
to put a halt to their hopeless
cycles once and for all?
[GOWASU] Aah.
The role of the Supreme Kai,
and all other Kais, is creation.
We are not meant
to have a direct hand
in our creations' affairs
if we can avoid it.
You do understand that,
don't you?
[ZAMASU] So, you would
have me do nothing,
and just ignore
the mortals' perpetual folly?
No, no. We don't simply
ignore the mortals.
We watch over and nurture them.
That is the position
in which we find ourselves.
Only one among us is permitted
to directly interfere
with their kind.
That's the Destroyer.
[ZAMASU gasps]
[sighs]
[GOWASU] Zamasu.
I want you to listen to me.
Always remember
where your place is.
And make an effort to
get to know mortals better.
Is that understood?
Yes.
[GOKU]
Yahoo!
Yeah! We're here at last!
Whooooa!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Oh, my.
Well, well, if it
isn't Lord Beerus.
Hi.
It's been far too long, Gowasu.
This is my apprentice,
the Supreme Kai in training
Zamasu.
It is a pleasure
to make your acquaintance.
[ZAMASU]
A mortal?
Hi, I'm Goku. Are you that
Kai dude that's s'posed to be
like, all super strong
and stuff?
[ZAMASU]
What's a mortal doing here?
[WHIS]
Sir, it would appear
that this is his
first time seeing Goku.
Yes.
Now, now,
why don't you go ahead
and introduce yourself properly.
Oh, right. Properly.
[clears throat]
I am called Goku,
your Kai-ness, at your serving.
[BEERUS chuckles]
Sometimes I wonder
if he does this on purpose.
In appreciation of you
braving the weather
as we gather here
on this auspicious day,
I hope this is to your liking.
At least he made an effort.
--[giggles]
--[GOKU] Nailed it.
In Seventh Universe terms,
he hails from Planet 877,
which is located in
the heart of 4032 Green.
Right. He's a Saiyan
who resides on
a palate-enticing world
known as Earth.
A Saiyan, you say?
[ZAMASU]
Who is this creature?
And what's he doing
traveling with a Destroyer?
[gasps]
Wow, not bad. You seem
pretty buff for a fancy Kai.
Do you work out a lot or what?
How dare you touch me, mortal!
Stop that at once, Zamasu!
Zamasu!
[ZAMASU grunts]
[BEERUS]
Hmm...
Please pardon his
outburst, Lord Beerus.
Now then, to what do we owe
the great pleasure
of your visit?
I can't wait anymore!
Would you mind goin'
a quick round with me?
Just for fun!
[ZAMASU]
You want me to fight you ?
Oh, come on, pretty please?
You gotta do it!
I came all this way
just for that!
[ZAMASU]
Show respect!
[GOKU yells]
You two can get to that later.
Ow, not cool, Lord Beerus.
I mean, I asked him
nicely didn't I?
--[GOWASU] Uh...
--[BEERUS] Whis.
Yes, sir. We're hoping that
you can help us solve a mystery.
Recently a troubling
individual appeared on Earth
in the Seventh...
wearing a Time Ring.
A Time Ring? What is that?
[GOWASU]
Hm.
[WHIS] As if that
weren't vexing enough,
this fellow was not
a Supreme Kai.
But that would not be possible!
And just wait till you
hear what he looked like.
He was a dead ringer
for that ridiculous fool
stretching up there.
One, two. One. Uuh?
Who is he?
Do you have any idea?
Strange.
Hey, why are you
starin' at me so hard?
You're making me self-conscious.
Is there something on my face?
[ZAMASU]
Eeeh.
Well, all that is rather
inexplicable, isn't it?
Indeed; it simply
doesn't add up.
Tell us. Are all
of your Time Rings
where they should be right now?
Of course.
I store them carefully
in a very safe location.
That's good to hear,
but would you mind
if we checked them out,
to be sure?
Yes, if you insist.
Well, Zamasu?
[ZAMASU]
Uuuuh...
Zamasu! Let's show Lord Beerus
and his associates
to the temple.
Yes, master.
[GOKU gasping]
[groans]
Will you behave yourself?
It seemed as though Zamasu
was unaware of the existence
of the Time Rings
before we mentioned them.
You're right.
I'm very sorry
to keep you waiting.
[GOKU]
Uuuh?
[GOWASU]
As you can see,
all rings are present
and accounted for.
Ah. Indeed.
I guess the search
continues, huh?
Yes. For a moment
you had me worried
I'd made some grave mistake.
But now that we see
all is in order,
I have to ask why you
came to the Tenth Universe
for answers to a problem
that occurred in the Seventh.
Oh, right now we're just going
from universe to universe,
paying a visit to them all.
[GOWASU]
Is that so?
[ZAMASU]
Get away from me.
[GOKU] Aw, don't be
such a stick in the mud!
Just fight me, okay!
Come on, I know you want to!
Mind your uncouth tongue
when speaking to me, mortal!
[GOKU] Oh, right, I gotta
do that formal thing.
[clearing throat]
[clears throat]
[GOKU] Uh, sir, it would be
your utmost pleasure
to please engage
in fisticuffs with me.
Your Kai-ness. Sir.
[GOWASU sighs]
Oh, just go ahead
and spar with him.
Master Gowasu, I...
This could provide an
excellent opportunity for you
to get to know
the mortals better.
[sighs]
As you wish.
All right! Yes! Hey, thanks!
You know, you're pretty
cool for an old-timer!
Don't thank me.
It is an important facet
of his training.
[GOWASU]
Let's see how well he's able
to keep his heart in check
against this mortal.
Now Zamasu, of course you will
have to pull your punches.
--[BEERUS] Uh.
--[GOKU] Uuh!
Hold on! Nobody's pulling
anything, okay?
You better face me
with everything you've got,
you understand me?
Excuse me?
You should listen to the Saiyan.
Don't hold back
even a little bit.
Are you mad?
Why would you say that?
Because if you
hold back, you'll die.
[ZAMASU]
Hm?
[grunts]
[chuckles]
[ZAMASU growls]
But why? Why would
the Tenth Universe's Kai
have the same energy as Black?
So, Trunks, how 'bout
Gohan's little girl?
She's a real cutie, huh?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Huh? Oh. Yeah.
She seems like
a pretty happy baby.
Actually, you know, I've got
a little one of my own now.
And she is quite a handful.
[FUTURE TRUNKS] Uh! Does that
mean that you're married
and settled down, too?
My big mouth.
That's great. So tell me,
what's your wife like?
Eeeh...
Wow. These stars
sure are starry!
Okay, now I get it!
She's someone I know, isn't she?
[KRILLIN chuckles nervously]
[A18]
Long time no see, Trunks.
[gasps]
It's Android 18!
[KRILLIN]
Uuuh...
Wait, Trunks, just calm down!
That's her! That's my wife!
We got married! 18's my wife!
Hi, Dad!
[MARRON giggles]
Hug time!
[KRILLIN] Marron, shouldn't you
be in bed by now?
Yeah!
[KRILLIN] What are you guys
doing here anyway?
Well, you didn't come home,
so we came to check on you.
[KRILLIN] Sorry. There's been
a lot goin' on. Don't be mad.
Is he scared of her?
I've heard what you did.
You killed me off
in your timeline.
Isn't that right,
you arrogant little punk?
Well, it was you
or mankind, so yeah.
Then I demand retribution.
I'm gonna make you pay.
[gasps]
Hmm. I gotcha!
I was just kidding.
I'm so lost.
--[A18, MARRON laugh]
--[KRILLIN] Okay, okay.
Android 18? Really?
I'm gonna go see how my mom
and the others are doing.
Whoa, I wonder what's
gotten into him.
[chuckles]
The space-time gyros
are locked into place now.
Whew, I think we've
earned ourselves a little break.
[BULMA'S DAD]
Uh! Good idea.
[ALL exhale]
Hey, Mom,
how's it going in here?
Not to worry! Everything's
moving along smoothly.
Oh, hello, Trunks.
[gasps, sighs]
[SHOU]
Hm?
[PILAF growls]
You're mine, Black!
Just look at that, Shou.
Based on what I can interpret
from Mai's gushy reactions,
she's clearly
got the hots for that
young blue-haired lad
from the future.
Okay, listen. Even normal
relationships between
men and women
are delicate things.
And this one adds time travel,
which complicates everything!
They are full-on star-crossed!
[SHOU snoring]
[PILAF]
Wake up! Ooh!
For Mai's sake,
we have to make sure
that this sapling love tree
bears some fruit!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Hm?
Oh no, he's gonna find
out she's stalking him
like a total creeper!
Will these two crazy kids
ever get together?
This situation
calls for urgent action.
Commence Plan A!
Roger that!
Who is that?
Go on, show yourself.
Uh!
[SHOU hollers]
Whoa--hey, are you all right?
No, I'm far from all right.
I think I scraped
my leg pretty bad.
I'll go and find you
a first-aid kit.
That's not necessary. I just
need a small bandage.
[MAI gasps]
[PILAF] Take this and
don't ask any questions.
[MAI]
What're you giving me that for?
When the time comes,
this will be very useful to you.
[MAI]
If you say so.
[gasps]
Could this be that time?
Here, I have a bandage.
You can have it.
Thanks. You're so
thoughtful, Mai.
She's not just a diehard
resistance fighter,
she's also got a softer,
more nurturing side, too.
And men find that kind of thing
to be irresistible, don't they?
Huh?
"Huh?" Oh, don't you
"huh" me, you big lug!
Wow, you're so kind
and caring, Mai!
That's something about you
that gets my heart
fluttering, you know?
--[TRUNKS giggles]
--[MAI] Okay...?
It seems like
the younger young lad
fell for our scheme instead.
How could our plan
have possibly failed?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Huh?
I really like how you're
just so darn sweet and nice
and considerate and stuff.
Still, this kinda works out
just as well, doesn't it?
I mean, they are
the same person after all.
I guess you're right.
[MAI shrieks]
Hey, Pilaf, don't do me
any more favors!
You got that!
[PILAF]
Ow! What was that for?
So what,
are you guys, like,
rehearsing a play or something?
[SHOU, PILAF]
So clueless.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Uh...
All right then.
Let's give it a go!
[gasps]
[GOKU chuckles]
What happened?
The mortal transformed!
[BEERUS]
Hm!
Yes, the form he's taken
is called Super Saiyan.
[ZAMASU]
Super Saiyan?
His energy is exponentially
higher now.
You know what?
I haven't fought a deity
since Lord Beerus.
[gasps]
You fought a Destroyer?
[chuckles]
Is that true?
This mortal has gone
toe-to-toe against you before?
Something like that.
My goodness. This doesn't
make any sense to me.
How is it possible
he's still alive after that?
Okay, I'll kick things off!
Ha!
And now, you're finished.
[GOKU yells]
[ZAMASU gasps]
[GOKU]
Huh?
[yells]
[GOKU]
This sensation.
You feel that? Just now?
Indeed.
[GOKU] Was that the same
as Black's energy?
No. But it was awfully close.
[GOKU yelling]
[ZAMASU] This is the power
of a mere mortal?
Unbelievable.
Who is this person?
He's not even a deity,
and yet his strength
rivals a Destroyer's!
Did you just suggest
that he rivals me?
[gasps] No, not you!
Please forgive me.
[ZAMASU] I never imagined
a lowly creature
could be this strong.
[yells]
[ZAMASU groans]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU chuckles]
Not bad! You know,
for just a plain ole Kai,
you're pretty strong.
Even the Supreme Kai
from my universe wouldn't
last five minutes with you.
Let's do this again
sometime, okay?
[ZAMASU growls]
Zamasu!
[yawns]
Well, I've seen the rings,
which is all we came for,
and I still haven't had
my after-dinner dessert.
"Dessert," you say?
Come on, Whis, let's go.
Yes, my lord. Well, if you'll
please excuse us then.
Why yes, of course.
Hey, Lord Beerus,
everything okay?
[BEERUS]
Everything's fine. See ya later.
Uh! Bye!
Hey, wait up!
You guys are my ride!
Between the antisocial psyche
that's clearly lurking
within him and the energy
that he projected outward...
--Yes?
--I'd say our suspicions
that Zamasu is Black have been
circumstantially corroborated,
although there are elements
we can't yet explain or prove.
Well if you and I believe it,
then maybe I should just
dispense with him now,
while I can.
Hmm. Are you guys
sure about this?
You know, he really didn't seem
like such a bad guy to me.
Yeah, that's just because
you're too trusting of people!
It's just that the energy
I felt was similar,
but it wasn't exactly
the same as Black's.
As I said, there are
still mysteries to solve.
[GOKU]
And now that I think about it,
the tingling sensation in
my hand that I got from him
kinda reminds me of when I was
fighting you, Lord Beerus.
What? How dare you
compare him to me!
We're on completely
different levels!
Yeah, that guy
still has room to grow,
so he could wind up even
stronger than you someday.
Good point, Lord Beerus.
How can you compare us?!
I'm much better!
If you mouth off to me
one more time,
I swear I'll drop you
and I won't even look back!
Aw, there you go again.
You know, you don't have to be
such a grumpy-pants
all the time.
[ZAMASU] Master Gowasu.
I want to thank you
for encouraging me
to fight against the Saiyan.
[GOWASU]
Mmm.
My understanding of his kind
has grown much deeper
because of the encounter.
So I see. Has this helped to
assuage the feelings of disdain
toward mortals that have
been bubbling up inside you?
[ZAMASU] I'm deeply ashamed
of how callow I've been.
[GOWASU] Then, I assume you've
learned an important lesson?
[ZAMASU]
Yes.
[GOWASU] You should know,
coming to this realization
is an important step.
Indeed such reflection
is what it means to grow.
[ZAMASU]
Yes, master.
[GOWASU] Zamasu, go and fix
another pot of tea.
[ZAMASU]
Yes, master.
Oh, I've learned a lesson.
Mortals are even more
dangerous than I thought.
Know this, Goku,
I will never forget you.
Get ready!
Instant Transmission!
Two fingers placed
right between the eyes
Get ready!
My hair will stand up!
'Cause I got
all the power of a Saiyan!
Ohhhh HEY!
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! (KAMEHAMEHA!)
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! It's what you need
Feel the magic of the beat
(Woo-hoo)
DANCE! It makes you smile
Nothing else can
quite compete (yoka yoka)
So when the world is lame
Don't play that game
You know that every problem
can be answered the same
Just let go and feel the rhythm
Everybody dance
with all your might!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Well, Trunks, I hope you got
enough to eat while I was gone.
After all, we're about to
go back and defeat Black
and you're gonna
need your energy.
Ooh, you're sparring
against Vegeta?
Careful, he's a lot
more awesome now
than he was last time
you saw him.
Just stop dwelling on whatever's
going through your head
and hit him as hard as you can!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"He Who is of Saiyan Blood.
Trunks's Resolve."
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?