♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
preparations began for
the Tournament of Power,
where eight universes will fight
and all losers
will be destroyed!
[BEERUS] If you're going to rush
me then pick them yourself!
Although, you'd better
make sure they can win.
[NARRATOR] While Beerus
dialed up the pressure on Goku,
Whis sought to free up Vegeta
by accelerating the birth of
his and Bulma's new daughter.
Oh, I've got the perfect
name for her!
We're calling her, Bulla!
[VEGETA] Hey, just hold on
a minute there!
This is ridiculous! I wanted
to give my daughter
a traditional Saiyan name!
[BULLA laughing]
Well, I'd say,
now there's one more thing
we need to fight to protect.
Yeah.
Mark my words, Gohan,
we're gonna win
that Tournament of Power!
You know it.
[GOKU]
Well, so long.
I'm heading over
to Krillin's place now.
[NARRATOR] This will be a
tournament where second place
means universal destruction!
Goku needs the best team in
the cosmos and he needs it now!
[NARRATOR]
"Goku the Talent Scout.
Recruit Krillin
and Android 18."
You're too fast.
I can't keep up.
Sorry, I'm just excited
to get Krillin on the team.
[BAD GUY 84A groans]
You guys never learn.
[WOMAN 84A]
Thank you!
[KRILLIN]
Are you hurt, ma'am?
I'll be okay.
In fact, I owe you
my life, officer.
The police are working hard,
but there're still a lotta
bad guys out there,
so please be careful.
[CATS meowing]
[BAD GUY 84B groans]
[KRILLIN]
All right! Now you can cross!
[KIDS giggling]
[KRILLIN] Don't worry,
I'll show you, ma'am.
It's right up here on your left.
[OLD WOMAN 84A ]
What a kind man you are.
[KRILLIN]
Hey! Pull over!
[BAD GUY 84C]
Ooh.
[POLICEMAN 84A] Yeah, thanks
for the assist there, Krillin.
No prob.
[sighs]
[GOKU] Yo, Krillin.
Busy day at the office?
[KRILLIN] Hey, what're
you guys doing here?
Heya, Krillin,
it's been too long.
Do you have a few minutes
you can spare?
Yeah, what's going on?
Ahchoo!
That was a big one.
[GOHAN] Sorry this took
so long to explain.
[KRILLIN] It's fine.
I got the afternoon off.
Let me see if I've
got this straight.
So there's a
Tournament of Power.
But you can't fly, use weapons,
and, or destroy people.
And it's a battle royal,
where you can only
get eliminated by ring-out,
with eight universes
fighting in teams of ten.
Mmhm. Yeah, I might
be able to swing that.
So does that mean
you're gonna join the team?
On the other hand, starting
my return to martial arts
in a cosmic tournament
kinda freaks me out.
Okay, but we don't have much
time before this thing starts.
We need a "yes"
or "no" right now.
[KRILLIN]
Hmmm.
--[A18] Honey, just say "yes."
--[KRILLIN] Uh?
If you don't enter the
Tournament, what was the point
of spending all that money
on a home gym?
The point is it's convenient
and keeps me in shape.
If you just wanna stay in shape,
you need to find a cheaper,
more efficient way.
Might as well just get
a gym membership.
We don't just want Krillin.
18, will you be
on our team, too?
[A18]
Hm. No, I won't.
I'm not into working for free.
Besides, I have little
Marron here to watch.
I'm sure Bulma would let you
drop off Marron at her place.
It's really fun!
There's an aquarium,
a playground,
and a brand new baby.
Yay!
[giggles]
[A18] Hmm. But why
do you need me so bad?
This whole tournament
is just for fun, right?
Uh, yeah, it's just for fun!
[whispering] Are you sure
we shouldn't tell them that
if we lose Grand Zeno will
wipe out our whole universe?
[whispering]
We can't start a panic, Dad.
--[A18] Hey.
--[BOTH gasp]
I can see you whispering.
What's going on?
[GOKU, GOHAN]
Nothing!
[A18] All right.
What aren't you telling us?
We told you everything
there is to know, I swear!
Well... there is one little
thing we didn't tell you.
It's the grand prize!
Whoever wins
gets ten million zeni!
But if we split it up it's
only a million for me, right?
[GOKU] Uh, no--it's, uh,
ten million each!
Almost sounds too good
to be true.
I know!
[A18] And you swear you're
not just making this up?
Yep. That's exactly
what they said.
[A18]
Hm. How interesting.
Ten million zeni happens
to be just my price.
And since you hit
the magic number...
I'll join your team, Goku.
All right! Thanks a lot, 18!
Having you join
is a load off my mind!
Hold on. You're not
just recruiting me
'cause you really want 18's help
and figured we were just some
kind of package deal, are ya?
We want you both equally!
C'mon, Krillin, are you
on the team or not?
All right, all right, I'm in.
[GOHAN]
Not so fast, guys.
--[KRILLIN] Uh?
--[A18, GOKU] Huh?
Sorry, Krillin.
We need to do something first.
[KRILLIN, GOKU]
Huh?
[KRILLIN]
I know why we're here.
This tournament's
all about ring-outs,
and these rocks
are perfect for seeing
if I can fight without
getting knocked off.
[GOHAN] Sorry to test you
like this, but I need to see
where you're at.
So show me your best stuff.
In a battle royale as big
as this, we'll be surrounded
at all times by friend
and foe alike.
I'm looking at everyone's powers
and how they handle themselves
so I can make our team strategy.
It's okay, I understand.
A battle royal is tricky.
To be honest, I'm pretty
nervous about this setup, too.
[laughing]
Aah!
[KRILLIN yells]
[GOHAN] From what I've
always seen of Krillin,
I doubt he'll
help our team much.
But Dad must want him
for a reason,
so I need to find out
for myself.
I told Gohan how great Krillin
is now that he's training again.
You still haven't
told me everything.
[GOKU]
Uh?
I can see the serious look
in Gohan's eyes.
This is for more than
just bragging rights!
What? Nah, Gohan's
just eager to win
his hundred million zeni.
A few minutes ago,
you said ten million.
Where'd the extra
zero come from?
Uuh!
[A18 grunts]
Oh, look! The guys are just
about ready to start fighting.
Come on, Krillin!
Let's see your new
training in action! Ha-ha!
Are you sure you're
supposed to root against
your own son like that,
Uncle Goku?
Uh!
Oh, yeah. Go, Gohan. Woo!
[KRILLIN]
All right!
Gohan! Ready when you are!
I'm eager to see
what you can pull off!
You know, I've been thinking
about this, Gohan.
This tournament won't be
an anything-goes killing spree.
There's gonna be a lot
of limits on what we can do.
Yeah, I'm well aware.
[KRILLIN] I'm not sure
you fully appreciate
what that means, Gohan.
[MARRON]
Good luck, Daddy!
Go get him, okay!
[KRILLIN]
You're easily distracted!
--[GOHAN] Huh?
--[KRILLIN grunts]
It's not much of
a test if you're gonna
pull your punches, Gohan!
[KRILLIN yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[KRILLIN]
Solar Flare!
I'm not done yet!
[yelling]
Wow, that's bright!
[groaning]
Impressive.
Is this a new technique?
--Want these?
--Yeah. Thank you.
[GOHAN] Even with my eyes
closed it's blinding.
I can't even sense his energy.
Where'd he go? Aw, man.
[GOHAN groans]
[KRILLIN]
Down you go!
[KRILLIN laughing]
That's a ring out!
I call that one the
"Hundred Times Solar Flare."
So you've multiplied it.
It overwhelmed my senses.
That's an amazing technique.
Well done, Krillin. This has
certainly been educational.
I got some other new
techniques up my sleeve,
but I'd rather keep them
a surprise for now.
Yay! Daddy won the round!
Well, I guess spending all that
money on a fancy home gym
was worth it after all.
Okay, Marron, that's enough
fighting for one day.
It's time for us to go home.
--[MARRON giggles]
--I like what I see, Krillin.
[gasps]
Now it's my turn to push you.
[GOKU chuckles]
Well, Krillin, ya beat me
fair and square.
[KRILLIN] Sorry for
literally blindsiding you,
but I'm glad I passed your test.
You weren't expecting that
from me, were ya?
--[KRILLIN] Gohan.
--[GOHAN gasps]
Let's push each other
and get better together.
With a little creativity
and a lot of hard work,
we can make all our moves
a hundred times stronger,
and win the Tournament of Power.
With my fighting
experience and moves,
and your strength,
we'll be sitting pretty!
That's a good point.
I really do lack experience.
Thanks again, Krillin.
[KRILLIN]
Hey, don't mention it.
All right, Goku!
Now that I've passed, I guess
that makes this official.
I can't wait to fight!
[GOKU]
You don't have to wait at all.
Huh?
What say we take this
somewhere else
and have our own battle.
I want in on the fun,
too, ya know.
[chuckles]
You got it.
[GOKU]
Mr. Satan said we can fight
as hard as we want up here.
[KRILLIN]
Sounds good.
[thunder rumbling]
[GOHAN] Dad, wait! Don't use up
all your energy now
when the tournament starts
in just a couple days.
I know, don't worry about it.
If I think you're
taking this too far,
I'm stopping the match.
[GOKU]
Got it.
[KRILLIN]
Do the same thing for me.
[A18]
Guys, hold on.
Krillin hasn't recovered yet
from his fight with Gohan.
Can't this wait at least
a couple hours?
--[KRILLIN] No, it can't.
--Huh?
You wanted me to
put my training to use.
[A18]
But this is too much.
Goku just saw you use
an ambush attack.
You're not getting away
with it a second time.
Do I really need to remind you
who you're about
to go up against?
Oh, yeah, I know.
More than you ever could.
Mama, is Uncle Goku
gonna hurt Daddy?
Daddy's gonna do just fine.
C'mon, Gohan, can't you
talk him out of this?
He's not gonna listen to me.
I mean, you're a
fighter, too, 18.
You understand, right?
Of course, I understand!
I just don't enjoy having
to see my husband depressed
after learning
how outmatched he is!
[MARRON]
Mama. But you said he'd be okay.
Uh. Not only will Daddy
be okay, he's gonna win!
--Are you sure?!
--Oh, yeah!
Let's go, Krillin!
Don't let him win this!
[MARRON]
Good luck, Daddy!
[KRILLIN]
We're following the rules for
the Tournament of Power, right?
[GOKU]
Right.
[KRILLIN] This reminds me
of our fight way back
at the World Martial
Arts Tournament.
--[KRILLIN] Goku.
--[GOKU] Hm?
[KRILLIN] Promise me that
when we get in the ring
you'll fight me as an opponent,
and not as a friend.
Oh, yeah, when I fight you,
I'm going all out!
[GOKU, KRILLIN laughing]
I hope that rain's not an omen.
Thanks, Mom.
[KRILLIN grunts]
Destructo Disc!
[GOKU grunts]
Solar...
Flare!
[GOKU]
Aah!
[KRILLIN yells]
Ha!
[GOKU]
You're trying to push me off.
[yells]
Now! Uh!
[GOKU]
Hmm.
Found ya!
Ha! I knew you
were gonna do that.
He's doing better
than I expected.
--I'll say.
--Daddy's winning! Yay!
[GOKU]
Okay, what else you got?
Wait a few seconds
and you'll see.
[GOKU]
Hm?
Uh!
[KRILLIN]
Gah! That was so close!
[GOKU]
How'd you do that?
[KRILLIN] Remember when I was
launching those Destructo Discs?
Not all of them
were aiming for you.
Ah! So three of them
distracted me,
while one was cutting a hole.
Worked like a charm.
It might be called
the Tournament of Power,
but our wits are gonna be just
as important as our strength.
You're right.
Charge in without thinking
and the other fighters
will eliminate you easily.
[KRILLIN grunts]
[chuckles]
[yelling]
[grunts]
What's your plan, Krillin?
Another Solar Flare?
Whoa. That's Super Saiyan Blue.
I've watched Goku before
when he's gone Blue,
but never like this.
Never as his adversary.
He hasn't even made a move
and he's already
got me sweating.
There's such a huge gap
between them.
I hope Krillin's got something
left up his sleeve.
No, he doesn't.
[A18] One on one,
with that power difference,
there's nothing he can do.
But the tournament's
not like that.
You said it's a
battle royal, right?
[MARRON]
Daddy!
Don't give up, Daddy!
Hey, Goku!
I'm havin' a great time.
Same here, pal!
[GOKU, KRILLIN] Ka... me...
ha... me...
[GOKU, KRILLIN]
Ha!
[yelling]
--[A18 grunts]
--[KRILLIN groans]
Krillin, are you okay?
[panting]
[exhales]
That was awesome.
I can't stop shaking.
Honey, why'd you do that?
Why stop the fight?
--[A18] I didn't stop it.
--Huh?
I gave you the backup
you needed!
What's your mom doing?
Teamwork! Go Mom!
[A18]
Hey, Goku!
We've talked about how
this tournament has rules,
and it's not
just about bulldozing
your opponents with raw power.
But there's another aspect
that's just as important.
As a battle royal,
it doesn't have to be about
what you can do all by yourself.
[KRILLIN]
What are you saying, 18?
If you get in trouble
on your own,
we'll fight together as a team.
We could pull off some mean
combos, don't you think?
Oh, yeah!
[BOTH]
Let's go, now!
[KRILLIN]
If you want it to be fair,
you can team with Gohan.
Nah, I think that's enough.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[KRILLIN] Goku!
Are you throwing the match?
[GOKU] No, I wouldn't say that.
I can tell I haven't figured out
how this tournament
is gonna go down yet.
What if I'd started the match
without even
considering teamwork?
That's kind of scary
to think about.
There's clearly a lot
I can learn from you guys.
I see that now.
And there's a lot I can learn
from you too, son.
Thanks, Dad.
You know, Krillin. The one
thing I know for sure
is that you're my best friend.
I'm counting on you, pal!
And 18, of course!
[A18]
Huh?
[chuckles]
You hear that, partner?
[KRILLIN, A18 laugh]
[GOKU chuckles]
Uncle Goku, Uncle Goku!
Because you stopped the fight,
I think that makes
Mommy and Daddy
the winners today! [giggles]
Aah! Mmm! Awe...
I think you've got
a point there, Marron.
Uncle Goku is a loser, hooray!
[GOKU] What? You little stinker!
They didn't defeat me!
[GOHAN]
It's okay, Dad, just go with it.
[GOKU] Look, there's
a big difference between
getting knocked out
and walking away, son!
[GOHAN]
All right, all right.
[MARRON]
Mommy and Daddy are the best!
[BOTH laughing]
Oh no, I almost forgot!
Hey, Number 18?
Do you know where
I can find Number 17?
You're kidding me, aren't you?
I mean he's super strong, right?
I never met the guy,
but if he's anything like you,
he'd be great
to have on the team.
[A18] To be honest,
I'm not sure where he is.
When we last talked,
he said he was
working at an animal sanctuary.
But he didn't give me
an address and I didn't ask,
so he really could be anywhere.
Well, that makes this
tricky then.
Though, I gotta say,
I'm surprised to find out
that 17 loves animals so much.
I was just as surprised
as you are.
[KRILLIN]
I have an idea!
Dende keeps an eye
on the whole planet.
I bet he knows where
to find Android 17.
Oh, yeah, I forgot about Dende.
If there's anyone who can help
find 17, it's gotta be him!
C'mon, gang! We gotta fly!
[NARRATOR] The hunt
for the ten best fighters
in the Seventh Universe
continues!
But the Tournament of Power
is now a mere 38 hours away!
Will Goku have enough
time to find Android 17,
let alone convince him
to join their team?
The clock is ticking!
Next time
on Dragon Ball Super!
Boogie Back!
Wish we had better timing
To explore this attraction
Put on a smile, it's showtime
And I'm just playing a part
Let's get lost in the rhythm,
dancing dancing heart
Head over heels
I'm falling falling down
(Boogie Back!)
My heartbeat
keeps growing faster
Every step that I take
brings me back to you
(Boogie Back!)
Give me happy ever after
Let the dream
of our love come true
Boogie Back!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
My journey to recruit
the most powerful fighters
in the universe
keeps getting crazier!
But getting 17 is a must!
The other universes'
guys will have
power levels through the roof!
We need the best of the best
to have any hope
of defeating someone like Top
and his friend, Jiren!
I'm getting more
excited by the hour!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"The Universes Go Into Action--
Each With Their Own Motives."
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?