♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Goku, Vegeta, and Trunks
journeyed to the future
to face Goku Black, but found
the mysterious lookalike
had reached an overwhelming
new level of power.
And the battle
turned even more dire
when Zamasu appeared with
a seemingly indestructible body.
In a narrow escape, the Saiyan
trio returned to the present,
where they spoke with Whis
and arrived at a new theory--
that present-day Zamasu
will take the Time Ring
from his master then
use the Super Dragon Balls
to create Goku Black.
You believe Gowasu, Supreme Kai
of the Tenth Universe,
is in imminent danger,
is that what you're suggesting?
[NARRATOR] Whis, Beerus,
Goku, and Universe Seven's
Supreme Kai have
raced to Gowasu's home,
where they will
try to save his life.
Gowasu. I have
brought your tea, master.
[NARRATOR] "Protect The Supreme
Kai Gowasu. Destroy Zamasu!"
[ZAMASU] What are these
meddlers doing here?
Well, what a pleasant
surprise this is.
It's the Supreme Kai
of the Seventh Universe
along with its
Destroyer Lord Beerus,
his attendant Whis,
and, let's see...
You were, Goku, correct?
[GOKU]
Huh?
I didn't realize you were here.
Please forgive me
for not greeting you sooner.
Now tell me, to what do we owe
this delightful second visit?
Last time you were investigating
the sudden appearance
of someone in your universe
wearing a Time Ring--
which, incidentally, allowed me
to learn about
that curious artifact.
And you were checking with
all the other universes, too.
Have you learned anything more
about this fascinating mystery?
Their reason
is now more focused.
This time they've
come to see you.
[ZAMASU]
Huh? But what for?
It's embarrassing.
But this punch-happy fool here
won't stop begging me
to fight you again,
so I said I'd ask,
just to shut him up.
I tried to tell him
you were far too busy.
But once he gets an idea
in his head, there's no point.
Nuh-uh. What are
you talking about?
Ow! Hey, easy!
Why'd you punch me again?
What did I do now?
I thought I told you
not to say a word!
[GOKU]
Okay, okay, I'm sorry.
But you still
didn't have to hit me!
Have you ever heard
of a friendly reminder?
I'm being "friendly"
by not destroying you!
[ZAMASU] Perhaps they're more
capable than I thought.
If that's what you want,
then I'd be happy to.
[ALL]
Hm?
Last time I was too reluctant.
I simply forgot how hard it is
for mortals
to restrain themselves.
A good host does not disappoint
his guests. Let's begin.
[BEERUS] No, no! You're clearly
in the middle of your tea time--
it was our impropriety
for coming uninvited to ask.
I'll be sure to give this one
a severe chewing out
when we get back home.
Oh, my lord, look at the time.
I didn't realize
it had gotten so late!
We're completely off schedule,
and you're overdue
for your rest.
[WHIS]
Hm.
[SUPREME KAI]
Mm.
We all know how cranky I can get
when I'm feeling sleepy.
[yawns]
I need that nap pronto!
That yawn seems fake.
--[BEERUS growls]
--[GOKU] Ooh!
Oh, silly me! I nearly
forgot to give you
your present, as well.
I'm on quite the roll today.
And what is that?
Premium tea leaves and
several sticky rice cakes
with an assortment
of sweet fillings.
A most delightful snack from our
planet Earth in the Seventh.
Aaah. That does sound tasty.
Surprisingly springy,
aren't they?
They are indeed. I believe
it has something to do
with the glutinous nature
of the rice grains.
And just wait until
you taste what's inside!
One bite and
you'll be transported!
It's indescribable!
You'll never think of bean paste
the same way again!
And please, make sure
you have it with the tea;
the pairing is
absolute perfection!
There's no denying it;
we do have a soft spot
for cakes and tea around here.
Thank you for this generous
gift. You're welcome any time.
Until we meet again,
Supreme Kai.
Now, Saiyan.
[GOKU] Ooh! Are you guys sure
leaving is a good idea?
Just keep walking, Goku!
[GOKU groans]
[ZAMASU]
Hmmmph.
A rare and
special treat, Zamasu.
Let's enjoy it together.
Yes, master. I'd love to.
[GOKU]
Aah! Hey! Whis, catch me!
[WHIS giggles]
--Ow, come on!
--Well, then? What do you think?
It's as we suspected.
There's no doubt about it.
He plans to kill Gowasu
in cold blood.
[GOKU]
For real? How do you know?
Zamasu's aura completely reeked
of murderous intentions, Goku.
The only stench fouler
is when my lord breaks wind.
That's both rude and untrue!
I'll have you know
mine smell like roses!
You're saying you could
sense it in his energy?
But I didn't sense
anything from him at all.
Well, of course,
Lord Beerus is a Destroyer,
which makes him
highly attuned to
these destructive inclinations.
Naturally, the same
goes for his attendant.
[GOKU] What about Gowasu?
You think he knows?
I would say he probably
hasn't noticed it yet.
He's a Supreme Kai like I am
and I didn't sense
Zamasu's bloodlust.
[GOKU]
Then what are we doing?
We've gotta get back
and save him!
There's no need to panic, Goku.
If Zamasu is going to
kill a Supreme Kai,
then I'll end his life
without hesitation.
But I can't take action
against a high-level deity
without some proof.
[GOKU] But you said
he's gonna do it!
What good is proof
if Gowasu's already dead?
We understand your concern,
but we're talking about
the future Supreme Kai
of the Tenth Universe.
An outside Destroyer
cannot simply obliterate him
because he harbors
dark intentions.
Such an act would throw the
entire multiverse into chaos.
For the moment,
all we can do
is watch what happens next.
Here is your special
Earth tea, Master Gowasu.
Oh. Well, that's unusual;
its green.
[inhales]
The aroma is striking, as well.
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
What if he put poison in there?
Lord Beerus!
Let's see what this
Earth tea tastes like.
[exhales]
It has a gentle flavor that's
most soothing to the soul.
[GOKU, SUPREME KAI exhale]
[footsteps]
I can't believe they slipped
through our fingers like that.
I was so close to having
Goku's head on a platter.
His fate doesn't matter,
though, does it?
They've seen they can't win
and will stay away
if they even have half a brain.
In fact, it's best if Goku
survives as long as possible.
On the off chance we do
need to elevate your power,
then fighting him seems to be
the best way to do it.
You can hunt him
down at the end,
then kill him slowly
with painstaking precision,
enjoying every blow.
And on the subject of
you improving your abilities,
I'm beginning to wonder
if we should have used
the power of
the Super Dragon Balls
to give you an
indestructible body as well.
I must say, it's a
very enjoyable gift.
[GOKU BLACK]
Hmph!
[yells]
Thanks for the concern,
but I've got
all the power I need.
This new level will make me
the ultimate sword for justice.
And when your sword is mighty
enough, you don't need a shield.
Just wait. I'm going
to become even stronger.
Heh! I was right
to think the vast power
this body gives me
would be indispensable
to our glorious plan
for the multiverse.
But we call it
Project Zero Mortals.
It's ironic, don't you think?
Here we are
destroying all mortals,
and yet we require
mortal power to succeed.
[FUTURE MAI] How long
can we hold out like this?
[HARU]
Mai!
[BOTH giggle]
Hey, look, Mai!
Yajirobe was hiding them!
Wow. Thanks for
ratting me out, kid!
--Try one!
--What? No, that's okay.
You kids can
keep them for yourself.
C'mon! Please!
Thanks, Haru.
Oh, they are really good.
--[BOTH giggle]
--Let's eat, too.
Okay!
[HARU]
Here.
--These are amazing!
--The best!
[FUTURE MAI]
I have to hold out.
Even if I'm the last one willing
to fight, I'll never give up.
I won't let
these smiles slip away.
It looks like the transfer
mechanism is shot again.
I'll have to replace the casing
with a stronger metal
or next time it could
burn out completely.
[FUTURE TRUNKS] I ran away.
And left her behind again.
Like a coward.
Do you think he's okay?
He's been hardcore
moping like that
ever since they got back.
He must be depressed.
If his head were
any lower, it'd drag.
This is your chance, Mai--
let's talk strategy!
Say what?
It's a well-known
fact of science that
whenever people are depressed
and you're nice to them,
they'll melt in
your hands like butter.
[MAI]
That doesn't sound like science.
The trick is to place
your hand on their shoulders
and speak oh-so gently.
It's not your fault, Trunks.
You're great--
it's the world that's bad!
Then to really seal it,
you gotta make him cry!
Oh, Trunks, I know
how badly you feel
because your heart's so big,
but don't blame yourself.
I know how easy it is
for me to say
'cause I haven't
gone through what you have
and I can't imagine your pain,
but it just breaks
my heart to see you sad
'cause you're such
an amazing guy!
--Mai!
--That's it, let it all out.
You don't have to do this alone.
Just feel safe in my caring
and non-judgy arms!
You've been bearing
the whole world on your big,
hunky shoulders,
so you can at least let me
carry your sadness for you.
Oh, Mai. Oh, Mai!
My sweet, sweet Trunks!
[BOTH crying]
You have gotta be kidding me.
--[BOTH] Huh?
--Just go away!
[SHOU, PILAF]
Sorry!
Honestly, what's wrong
with those guys?
They have no idea
what he's going through.
[TRUNKS]
Hey, big me!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
What do you want?
What is he doing?
I want you to
pull yourself together!
You lost one fight and now
you're moping like a baby!
That's not our style!
[MAI]
Oh no! That's not gonna help!
Hello? Are you listening?
[sighs]
I'm sorry, kid,
but can you please
just leave me alone?
Huh?
Poor you. It really sucks
to find out my future self
turns out to be such a weenie.
But at least it explains why
you couldn't keep Mai safe.
How could he say that to him?
I'm sorry--did that upset you?
Well, you and I both know
it's the truth!
Don't just stare at me,
you big wuss!
If that bothers you,
then fight me!
Come and make me shut up!
I'm not scared of you!
[yells]
Let's do this! Come and get me!
Or if you won't,
then I'll just bring it to you!
[TRUNKS yells, grunts]
What's the matter?
Get back on your feet!
You call yourself a Saiyan?
[FUTURE TRUNKS grunts]
[GOWASU giggles softly]
[exhales]
[sighs]
That attendant
is not exaggerating.
These cakes and tea
are an exquisite pairing.
You should have
some too, Zamasu.
No, thank you, master.
I'm not really that hungry.
But I can tell that you were.
You've got some
powder on your face.
Hm? My goodness,
how careless of me.
[SUPREME KAI] He hasn't made
the slightest aggressive move.
Are you positive he intends
to strike him down?
There's not a doubt
in my mind, Kai.
Well, all I can tell is he
sure enjoyed those snacks.
--This is making me hungry!
--[GOKU'S stomach growls]
Have patience, Goku--
I doubt it will be much longer.
Excuse me, master.
[GOWASU]
Hm? Something on your mind?
Yes, sir. I have realized
I was mistaken, after all.
I've had some more time
to reconsider what you told me
after our trip
into the Babari's future.
About the interplay
between good and evil.
[footsteps]
[ZAMASU] You told me
that one can succumb to evil
and then come out
with a new understanding.
Thanks to you, I see the role
dark deeds can play.
Such ugly acts can be necessary
to achieve a more perfect end.
Yes, Zamasu.
I knew you were wise enough
to understand
if given enough time.
I'm pleased
you've seen the truth.
--[ALL gasp]
--No way--he wouldn't!
Lord Beerus!
--[GOWASU grunts]
--[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[GOWASU mumbles]
[exhales]
That was a close call.
[ALL sigh]
I should be more careful.
They get stuck in your throat.
An obvious hazard, but I was
too delighted to notice.
[grunts]
Do something!
We can't keep watching
from the sideline!
If we don't act now, he'll die!
Why are you waiting?
[ZAMASU growls]
[GOWASU]
Uh!
[gasps]
Did you already forget
about my power?
Oh yeah, of course!
That whole
Temporal Do-Over thing;
you can just
wind back the clock!
That's the certainty we needed.
Then I believe it's time.
[ZAMASU growls]
[GOWASU]
Hm?
Huh?
Just what do you
have there, Zamasu?
A massage glove?
Uh, no, I-I don't know.
I'm sorry,
did I get in your way?
Lord Beerus, wh-what's going on?
How long have you been here?
An excellent question.
I was under
the impression you'd left.
[WHIS] Sorry, there's one more
matter we need to discuss.
[GOWASU]
What matter?
That your beloved apprentice
is currently trying to kill you.
[gasps]
What are you talking about?
See for yourself, Supreme Kai.
Zamasu, what is this?
[ZAMASU gasps]
If I had not placed that
kitten mitten on his hand,
then your long life would have
come to a most abrupt end.
Zamasu, I need you to
explain yourself immediately!
[ZAMASU]
Hmm.
[SUPREME KAI]
Allow me to explain for him.
Zamasu's objective
is to kill you,
and claim the Time Ring
for himself--
giving him immense power.
That can't be!
I'm afraid so, my fellow Kai.
And with you gone,
there would be no one
in this universe
to impede his plans.
Just what plans are those?
Our guess? He's going to use
the Super Dragon Balls
to make himself indestructible.
Then use them again
to create a counterfeit Goku,
so he can eradicate all mortals
from the living world.
[GOWASU grunts, growls]
I thought you overcame
those impulses
and turned over a new leaf.
Zamasu!
You have
misunderstood me, master.
There is no other leaf,
there is only divine justice,
and it demands
that I serve it well.
Evil must be destroyed.
No matter the price.
Zamasu.
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
I assume Zuno tipped you off,
though I admit I'm impressed
you deduced my whole plan
from what I asked him.
We didn't have to
guess much at all.
I saw the future
with my own eyes.
What's that?
You traveled to the future?
Yeah, that's right--I did.
And thanks to you,
whole cities were in ruins.
Countless lives
were completely destroyed!
Is that a fact, Goku?
That means in this future
my dreams have come true.
Well, all the more reason why
I can't let you interlopers
get in the way of them now.
Sorry Kai,
but your luck has run out.
[BEERUS]
Hakai.
[screaming]
Not to be.
[TRUNKS panting]
What's your problem?
[panting]
Come on, don't tell me
you're quitting already.
I've got plenty
of fight left in me!
Funny, getting a
pep talk from yourself.
I hear you loud and clear.
We don't have to keep going.
I will win this.
No matter how strong
the enemy is.
Hm!
Thanks, little me.
You've got grit.
It's about time you got
the message, future me.
[MAI sighs]
[BOTH grunt]
[TRUNKS groans]
[BEERUS] Again, Whis?
That's definitely on purpose!
Please, forgive me, my lord.
You see, this is exactly
why I said Supreme Kai
should take us back!
Ow! My butt!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
You destroyed Zamasu?
[WHIS] Yes, my lord did
it with one shot.
Now Black won't be created
and the future will be
safe from his tyranny.
That's awesome! Victory party!
That means we won't
be pulverized
in the future too, sire!
Yeah! All right!
[FUTURE TRUNKS] Your future's
saved, but not mine.
When we used the time machine
to stop the Androids,
my world didn't change.
That's how it works.
That may be the case
when you ignorant mortals
meddle with the laws of nature,
but divine action
is not so sloppy.
And when I kill a god, it will
affect all flows of time.
So, Trunks and I are safe?
You're positive this changes
his timeline, too, Beerus?
'Cause if you're wrong, you're
gonna be hearing it from me!
Are you openly questioning
a Destroyer's wisdom?
[BULMA] I didn't say you're
wrong! I said if you are!
[GOKU]
Everything's fine, Trunks.
I mean, he is a deity!
He's the one who should know!
I hope so. But I
need to see for myself.
Get ready!
Instant Transmission!
Two fingers placed
right between the eyes
Get ready!
My hair will stand up!
'Cause I got
all the power of a Saiyan!
Ohhhh HEY!
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! (KAMEHAMEHA!)
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! It's what you need
Feel the magic of the beat
(Woo-hoo)
DANCE! It makes you smile
Nothing else can
quite compete (yoka yoka)
So when the world is lame
Don't play that game
You know that every problem
can be answered the same
Just let go and feel the rhythm
Everybody dance
with all your might!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And we're gonna jump back
to the future with Trunks
one more time to find out
if it's peaceful or not.
And I think you can pretty much
see how that's gonna go.
We'll hear another
big revelation, too.
Goku Black may not be a servant
copy of me after all.
Well, whoever or
whatever he is, know this:
I'm ready to take him on!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Into the Future Again.
Goku Black's
True Identity Revealed!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?