♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the alien Monaka surprised
everyone by showing up
at the Tournament of
Destroyers victory party,
and Goku was eager to fight him.
All right, Monaka,
let's throw-down!
Hold on. You can't just
take liberties like that!
[NARRATOR] To prevent Goku
from learning that Monaka
was actually much weaker
than advertised,
Beerus took drastic measures,
disguising himself as Monaka
and taking on Goku.
--[GOKU yells]
--[BEERUS AS MONAKA hollers]
[gasps]
[NARRATOR] It was a close call,
but Beerus managed
to get through the battle
without Goku learning the truth.
Go on. Tell me I deserved that.
Well, honesty is
the best policy!
[BEERUS grunts]
[NARRATOR] "Goku's Energy
Is Out of Control?
The Struggle to Look After Pan."
[GOKU]
That was great, Chichi.
Eeeh. What in the world's
come over you?
You're already done?
But you normally eat
twice as much, at least!
Yeah what's wrong, Dad?
You feel okay?
I don't know.
I'm just not hungry I guess.
Let's see if you have a fever.
Doesn't feel like I do.
Oh, you're not
dead again are you?
I'm pretty sure I would've
noticed if I was dead, Chichi.
Plus, I've been
through that twice before
and this feels different.
Okay, but that
makes it sound like
you do feel something's
wrong, and so do I.
I mean this is beyond abnormal!
When do you not want to eat?
I didn't want to
make you worry.
I do feel funny, though.
[MALE BAKER 43A]
Thanks for shopping!
[GOKU] Let's see, I got
the pork, got the chicken.
Aw man, I forgot the
horse meat! Gotta have that!
What the--? Hey!
Why can't I turn around?
It's like my body
stopped listening to me!
Go that way!
[hollers]
[yells]
[sighs]
Man. That was close.
Oow!
Wow. That's a pretty big bump.
What's causing this? You never
lose control like that.
[GOKU]
Hmm...
I would say
you should see a doctor.
But I can't imagine what they
would say after examining you.
You'd prob'ly break
their machines. Oh, I know!
Why don't you ask King Kai?
I bet he's seen this before!
It'll be okay, Chichi.
You're making too big
of a deal out of this.
All right. Fine, I'll go.
I'll be back soon, okay?
[GOKU]
Uh! Huh? Hm. Huuuh.
Where am I? This definitely
isn't King Kai's place.
That's weird.
Remember, Vegeta.
Trunks has his big field day
at school tomorrow. I want you
to at least stop by.
Oh, hey Bulma.
[screams]
What's wrong?
Ah! Kakarot?
Uh, what's up?!
--[GOKU screams]
--Explain yourself right now!
I didn't come here
on purpose, okay?
Then why the hell are you here?
Trust me, I'm just
as confused as you!
Look, I wouldn't come here
just to see your boobies.
Yours are too saggy now.
What's wrong with you?!
Sorry, I'll go!
You're not King Kai.
Gotta admit, you're right.
[ARALE] Pokey poo, pokey poo!
Pokey, pokey poo!
Uh--
Oh, hello!
What the--?
Still not it.
This is major. It's way
worse than I thought.
[KORIN chuckles]
[GOKU]
Finally.
[KING KAI]
Hmm.
[GOKU] So, what's wrong
with me, King Kai?
[KING KAI]
Mmm. Mmm!
Do you think it's serious?
[GOKU] I said,
do you think it's serious?
Are you trying
to scare me to death?
I can't; you're already dead!
You're really gonna
go there, Goku? Really?
Hmm. Looks like "Delayed
Onset Energy Disorder," or DOED.
And what's that mean?
Well, it's where
you lose the ability
to control your energy.
This says it can take effect
a few days after you use it
in an excessive or unusual way.
Excessive, huh?
[gasps]
Times ten!
The Kaio-ken technique.
So, according to this
it's like a strained muscle.
You just need to go easy for
a while so it can repair itself.
You'll be okay.
But you're lucky.
The Kaio-ken is
dangerous for anyone,
and with your level of power
it's downright crazy!
So how long is a while?
An hour? A day?
Hard to know.
Come on, give it to me straight!
This is important!
There's no telling
when that Omni guy's
gonna hold the tournament,
so I gotta be ready!
That's exactly why
you need to rest--
so you don't rip yourself apart!
The Kaio-ken
wasn't your only gamble.
That fight with Hit, when you
were predicting his moves,
you weren't just guessing.
You were forcing your way
into the future
for an advantage, weren't you?
Yeah, so?
So, you're pushing
yourself to the very limit
of what a mortal being can do!
If you keep straining yourself,
the connections between
your body, mind, and energy
will unravel and you won't
be able to fight at all.
You won't get any stronger.
Are you sure?
Ooh.
[KING KAI] Look, Goku. If you
won't accept your limits
or rest when you need to,
maybe you need
to hang up the towel
and stop fighting altogether.
You can be
a full-time grandpa.
Whoa, don't say that! I'll rest!
[laughing]
I gotta admit, Goku,
it's kinda hilarious
making you squirm like that!
Hey, that's not nice.
Why would you like that?
You have a grudge
against me or somethin'?
Of course
I have a grudge, Goku!
You see this halo?
[GOTEN snoring]
[sighs]
I hope Goku's okay. My poor guy.
Okay, enough moping!
I gotta be strong and
help him out of his funk!
I'll whip up his favorite meal
and make it so good
he won't resist whether
he's hungry or not!
He'll eat the whole thing
and feel like
his normal self again!
[CHICHI]
Huh?
Aah!
Flying's really hard when
you can't control your energy.
I keep forgetting that.
Aah!
I think she's mad.
Uh, hey honey. I'm home...?
[CHICHI]
What home?!
[PROFESSOR'S WIFE]
Thank you, I love it!
I've been a huge fan
ever since he won the 24th
World Martial Arts Tournament!
You must be so proud!
[laughs]
Well, anyway. About Gohan.
[PROFESSOR'S WIFE]
I do apologize. Go on, dear.
Mm. You have a baby
to get home to.
So, let's cut to the chase.
Sounds good, uh, sir.
Your presentation at
the conference the other day
was impressive, Gohan.
You got a lot of people
talking in that auditorium.
Thank you very much, professor.
Which leads to my offer.
[phone buzzes]
Sorry, it's our sitter.
I need to take this, sir.
[chuckles nervously]
--[GOHAN] Hey, Piccolo.
--[GOKU] Hey, son!
--[GOHAN] Wait, Dad?
--[GOKU] Yeah, it's me.
So, I just heard some
fancy professor wants you
to be his assistant
or something.
[GOHAN] Um, yeah. I mean,
I'm finding out about that now.
Are you at my house?
With your mom and brother.
It's actually kind of
a long story.
What? Is there anything wrong?
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Seriously?
I'm just glad no one was hurt.
Well if he said complete rest,
that's what you've gotta do.
You've hardly ever
gotten sick, Dad.
Are you sure
you're all right?
Yeah. Yeah, of course
you can stay.
As long you need to;
we've got plenty of room.
Videl and I have to
get things in order here,
but we should be home
by noon tomorrow.
And that's what
I call good intel.
[GOKU] All right, son.
Do I good job, heh.
Wow, an assistant professor
at a real live college!
Aah! My Gohan's a
trailblazer. It's incredible!
He'll be the first Saiyan
in the Seventh Universe
with a respectable job!
He sure will.
[CHICHI grunts]
Don't think this gets you
out of the doghouse,
Goku! Not even close!
Do you know how much
it's gonna cost
to rebuild this place
after you became
a flying wrecking ball?!
It's a good thing we have
that hundred million zeni
from Mr. Satan or
we'd be totally ruined!
I thought you put
all that money toward
Goten's school or something?
[chuckles]
Wait a second. Does that mean
you've been fibbing?
[CHICHI] Well, I had to
say that so you'd work
instead of running off to train!
Not that it made any difference.
And I did say
we should save the rest,
which we are,
for Goten's education.
[BOTH]
Hey.
Piccowo?
[CHICHI]
Are you leaving?
[PICCOLO] Of course I am.
I said I'd look after Pan
because that job's
important to Gohan
and I didn't want him
to miss it.
But now you can watch her.
Agreed? No offense
but I have work to do.
Yeah, that's cool!
I trust you can handle
the baby food, Chichi?
I've got two boys,
thank you very much!
I'll be fine! I'll see
what they've got
and throw something together!
Pan likes hotcakes made with
tuna and tofu leftovers,
finely chopped carrots,
onions, spinach, and broccoli.
And definitely no celery because
she hates celery, got it?
Yes, sir!
She's a fast crawler
and likes to explore
so keep an eye on her
at all times.
She likes her fish book
and when you
make her bunny go hop-hop.
And, if she cries at night
just sing to her.
No way! Let me get this
straight. You actually sing?
[PICCOLO grunts]
Anyway, Pan gets shy,
especially when
her parents are out.
I'm the only person
who's been able to
hold her without her crying.
So, if you can't figure out
how to calm her down,
just let me--oh.
--[giggles]
--Ooh see boo!
Sorry, were you
saying something?
Uh, okay.
Bye Piccolo!
[PAN giggling]
[door clicks shut]
Oh. I forgot to mention,
brush her teeth before bed
with the baby toothbrush using
only water; no toothpaste.
I know she doesn't
have all of her teeth yet
but it's crucial
for good oral hygiene!
Also, I think
you're out of wipes,
but I think there's more
in the cabinet right above--
[GOKU sighs] I've gone a full
day without exerting my energy.
I don't know how people
can live like this.
Are you feeling any better?
No, not really. The truth is,
if I had to fight you right now
I would probably lose.
That bad, huh?
[giggles]
It's crazy.
All of a sudden it feels like
I've turned into
an old man, Piccolo.
You are an old man now,
ya grandpa.
[GOKU] Oooh, you like
those stars, Pan?
If Grandpa was feeling
better, I'd take you
way up in the sky so you
could have a better look.
[giggles]
But don't you worry.
One day you'll be a Super
Saiyan flying all by yourself!
Yaaah!
[laughing]
[PAN]
Dada! Dada!
Hey, I'm not your Dada, silly!
I'm your Grampa!
[PAN]
Dada! Dada!
[GOKU] Grampa! Grampa!
Grampa's making you fly!
[GOKU, PAN laughing]
[GOKU, GOTEN snoring]
[PILAF laughs]
Today is the day!
You'll see why it was worth
blowing all our money
on my latest greatest
power suit when it
defeats our old foe
and paves the way
for world domination!
But emperor, you act like
that power suit's
the reason we might win.
When we all know it
wouldn't stand a chance
against Goku
if he was feeling okay
and could use his
actual power, right?
So?
You sure we should do this?
What's with the
cold feet, you guys?
Well, whenever we
tangle with these guys
it always ends badly, sir.
What if we just keep
working at that restaurant?
I know it's not exactly
ruling the world,
but it's fun and they let us
take home the leftover food!
Remember that stew
last Tuesday?
Yeah and we even
got free bread!
Only partly stale! We were
in doggy-bag paradise!
[SHOU, MAI]
So fantastic!
[PILAF growls]
Hey! That isn't funny!
[panting]
[PILAF]
The plan doesn't change.
We tell the wife and kid
they won the lottery,
and the green guy that
he's getting money back
from a class action lawsuit
he didn't know he was a part of.
But they all have to pick up
the money in town today!
Yes, sire! I have to admit,
it is a brilliant plan.
We'll get 'em all out of
the house except Goku.
You're a criminal
mastermind;
there's no doubt about that!
Tee-hee. That's right;
bring the praise.
I pretty much
invented the bad guy act.
Newbie villains
have nothing on me!
[PAN giggles]
[giggles]
[PILAF shrieks]
What is that?
Relax. It's only a baby.
Gohan's I think.
How in the world did you
get out here on your own?
Wasn't anybody watching you?
Your grandparents
are hopeless, aren't they?
Uh-ha!
How could you let this happen?!
[MAI, SHOU, PILAF shriek]
[PAN]
Piccowo?
[PICCOLO] I told you
to watch her at all times!
I told you she likes to explore!
I thought you came back
so you could watch her!
Who cares whose fault it is,
we just have to find her!
You're right,
let's start looking.
[PICCOLO] We'll split up
to cover more ground.
Look everywhere. Inside and out!
[MAI]
Run!
That was way too close.
Though technically we hadn't
done anything wrong yet.
I mean, it's not like
we ran off with their baby.
[MAI]
Um, speaking of that.
Of what?
We've got a complication.
Hi!
[screams]
What the--?
What were you thinking?
Toss her out right now!
What are you talking about?
She's just a baby!
If you want her
off board, you do it!
As if I could be that cruel!
I'm a villain not a monster!
[crying]
Awe! It's okay.
We're just having a talk.
[sniffs]
Uh, hey, emperor?
Are you smelling that?
I think it could be--?
[MAI, PILAF, SHOU]
Baby doo-doo!
[PILAF]
Open a window, quick!
[MAI]
These windows don't open!
[SHOU]
I can't handle this!
My sense of smell is way
too strong for soilage!
[giggling]
I don't trust that giggle! Aah!
[PILAF] If you're about to spew,
don't turn toward us!
[MAI]
I second that!
This isn't funny, baby!
[alarms wail]
[giggles]
--[PAN giggles]
--[MAI, SHOU, PILAF scream]
I broke the controls!
We can't stop!
[SHOU]
We're doomed!
Oh! We need a miracle!
I don't care what happens to us,
but someone or something's
gotta save this baby!
[GOKU grunts]
Where is she?
Pan!
[hollers]
[MAI, PILAF, SHOU]
She's flying?
[giggling]
How's this happening?
Since when do babies
know how to fly?
No idea. But she is
part Saiyan, right?
[MAI]
Who cares--we're saved!
[giggles]
[screams]
We aren't saved just yet!
We still have to land!
[PAN giggles]
I'd say she's got
a bright future.
Yeah, you think? One more
archrival to add to the list.
We'll fall back for now.
But they haven't seen
the last of me yet!
[GOHAN] We're home!
Where's our baby girl?
Dada! Mama! Dada!
Were you a good girl, sweetie?
Yo.
You look tired--
is something wrong?
Honestly, we couldn't
find Pan for a while
and we were convinced
she'd gotten outside.
We left to look for her,
then when we got back
she was on the couch.
We figure she was
sleeping under her bed,
or maybe in a closet
or some other
little nook the whole time.
Yeah, she's been doing
a lot of that lately.
I'm sorry she caused
you all so much trouble.
Hey Pan. Grampa's not
feeling very well
and he needs to get his rest.
You shouldn't have made him
run around like that!
Grampa!
[GOHAN]
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
Grampa! Grampa!
[GOKU chuckles]
Grampa! Grampa! Grampa!
It seems like she's
already talking more
since her nap. Babies sure do
grow up in a flash.
[GOKU]
Yeah, no kidding.
At this rate, she'll start
flying when she's three!
Don't be ridiculous, Goku.
I'd... say two.
[ALL laugh]
So, what about the new job,
Gohan--did you get it?
[GOHAN]
Actually, I turned it down.
[PICCOLO, GOKU, CHICHI gasp]
Well, the hours were
pretty nuts and it seemed like
he'd never be home.
So, we decided it was
more important that
he got to see Pan.
[laughs]
--[CHICHI sighs]
--[GOKU chuckles]
[laughing]
♪ Closing Song ♪
Wow
It's hard to say
Don't wanna stay
I twist and fight,
can't find my way
I must believe, that fear
and trouble can even be fun
if you think the right way
Wow
I don't wanna draw the line
I gotta see it through some way
Fight for what I know is mine
The dream I had of me that day
Wow
Don't care if they
call me greedy
If they hate me, make me blue
Don't care if they laugh at me
'Cause I will make
the dream come true
Wow
[GOTEN]
Hi everybody! It's Goten!
And you won't believe it,
but Trunks and I
are causing some trouble.
We get locked inside
Monaka's delivery truck
and wind up in the middle
of an alien fight.
Something about a special
power inside this planet.
My dad needs to save us, but how
can he without his energy?
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"The Seal of Planet Pot-au-feu.
Secrets of the Unleashed
Superhuman Water!"
Make sure you don't
miss it okay?