♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super.
Despite his extreme exhaustion
from the relentless battle,
Vegeta drew on his passion
and unyielding pride
to fight one-on-one
against Jiren.
You have zero chance of winning.
Even if I'm not
the one who does it...
Even if I'm not the one who
delivers the final blow...
As long as my universe wins,
that's fine by me!
[NARRATOR]
It was a hopeless battle
as the Saiyan prince could
not land a single hit.
But that was never the point.
Through his brave effort,
he had bought Goku
precious time to recover.
And then, when he could
hold out no longer,
he gave Goku all
the energy he had.
[VEGETA]
It's up to you, Kakarot.
Don't you fail, too.
I'm standing here 'cause Vegeta
and the rest of my team
trusted I could find
a way to pull this off.
I'll win.
'Cause I refuse
to let them down!
I won't fail!
[NARRATOR] Taking the hopes
of his allies upon him,
Goku returns to action.
However, faced with
the ferocious attacks
of the overpowering Jiren,
he is once again driven
into a tight corner.
[JIREN]
It's over.
[NARRATOR] As Jiren lunged
forward with his finishing blow,
it seemed the Tournament
had reached its end.
But the Saiyan wasn't done.
Goku's body responded with
that divine speed and power,
and once again he shimmered
with a fearsome, silver glow.
The final showdown takes another
momentous turn... now!
[NARRATOR]
"A Transcendent Limit Break!
Autonomous Ultra
Instinct Mastered!"
Autonomous Ultra Instinct.
This is the third time
in the Tournament
he's managed to achieve it.
[KRILLIN] Let's just hope
third time's the charm.
Yes, it had better be.
He cannot afford
another misstep.
I'm quite sure this will
be his last chance.
Each time he defies
his physical limits
and forces himself
to fight like a god,
the strain on his
mortal body increases.
He has already
pushed himself so far,
reached so deep
into every reserve.
And with no more
allies to aid him,
he cannot hope to recover again.
That moment the glimmer
fades from his eyes,
this Tournament will be done.
The fight's begun!
This is it, huh?
Indeed, sires.
The Tournament of Power's
moment of truth.
Jiren versus Goku.
Both have repeatedly
surprised the gods,
and now they fight
to the finish.
All eyes are transfixed
to what's left of the ring,
with no one daring to blink.
[GOKU yells]
[JIREN grunts]
[GOKU roars]
[SUPREME KAI] This confrontation
is tremendous.
Goku seems to have mastered
his Self Movement.
[ELDER KAI]
Well, yes.
But it seems he still can't
land a decisive blow.
It's the same problem
he had with Kefla.
Goku has been shaped
by a lifetime of fighting
in which he carefully
observes his foes
and probes for weaknesses.
In each moment he
attempts to strike,
his mind is cluttered with
thoughts, strategies,
and analyses that
normally help him.
But in the case of Ultra
Instinct, these are a detriment,
acting as chains that slow
his reflexes and hold back
the full force his
body is capable of.
I can only hope he will learn
to break this habit soon,
before he wastes all
the time and strength
he has left on these
ineffectual and
self-defeating attacks.
[GOKU]
Ka...
A Kamehame-Ha!
That's the tactic he
used to stop Kefla.
With his melee attacks failing,
he may not have another choice.
...me...
...ha...
Ha!
Ka-blewey!
Ultra Instinct's so cool!
[FUTURE ZENO]
Yes! Cool and amazing!
[ZENOS laugh]
[gasps]
[TOP grunts]
[TOP]
Jiren has been watching.
He has studied Goku's power,
and the way the Saiyan fights.
Both during their own battles,
and as a spectator
while Goku fought Kefla.
Jiren has learned.
[JIREN grunts]
Hmph.
Aw, man.
Looks like he took
that blast head-on.
What an explosion!
Yes, it's like fireworks!
In the past that's been most
effective for Goku, but not now.
[ZENO]
Goku may be super-amazing.
[FUTURE ZENO] But Jiren
is super-super-amazing!
A shield?
It looks like he altered
the flow of his Kamehame-Ha
to create a barrier against
Jiren's counterattack.
Smart move. That was close.
He is quite tenacious.
[BELMOD]
Hmph. There's no need to worry.
So he knows how to block.
But a strong defense
will only get him so far.
Without an offense to match,
he has no chance of victory.
I agree, my lord.
And if Jiren continues to attack
that defense will
eventually crumble.
Our win is just
a matter of time.
[KHAI]
Hm. Yes, indeed.
[BELMOD]
Hm... What wasted effort.
With his incomplete
Ultra Instinct,
all he's doing is
delaying the inevitable.
Tch. And all you're doing
is running your mouth!
[KHAI, BELMOD]
Hm?
[VEGETA] Do you even
listen to yourself?
Just now you called
it "incomplete,"
which implies he hasn't
fully mastered it yet.
And if you're stupid enough to
ignore the obvious implications
of that, then I don't
even know where you
get off calling
yourself a "god."
You watch yourself, mortal.
Oh, come on.
Are you suggesting that he
can master Ultra Instinct
in the time he has left?
Please! [laughs]
You're a fool!
That's impossible!
And you'd bet your life on that?
[VEGETA]
Forty-eight minutes.
That's all we were given for
this Tournament of Power.
Yet in that brief time span,
we Saiyans warriors
have shattered our limits,
time after time!
[VEGETA] You've seen it with
your own eyes, Destroyer.
[growls]
[BELMOD]
Jiren! What are you waiting for?
End this! Knock Goku out
of this tournament now!
[JIREN grunts]
Come on, Kakarot!
Find a way! I entrusted
everything to you!
My pride, my promise,
everything!
I won't tolerate failure!
Trespass into the
domain of the gods,
and use that might
to conquer Jiren!
Do it, Kakarot!
[yelling]
[exhales]
[inhales]
[ROSHI] Guess Vegeta's idea
of a pep talk did the trick.
Goku's bounced back.
But now he's just fighting
Jiren to a draw.
The scales aren't
tipping in his favor yet.
And that massive battle cry...
He did that last
time against Jiren,
right before he ran out of gas.
[KRILLIN] Are you in trouble,
buddy? Is this it?
Do you see that, my lord?
Huh?
It would appear that we have new
reason for hope, Lord Beerus.
I can feel it. Not the
chaos of consciousness,
but the elegant
purity of energy
operating on impulse alone.
Goku is focused
only on Jiren now--
or rather, on the battle itself.
He is throwing his whole body
and soul into the fleeting
moment of each strike.
Allowing the flames of
his power to rage freely,
unrestrained by
the walls of thought.
Concerns for his universe,
or the gap in their powers,
his hesitation,
his impatience, his fear--
he has given them all to
the fire and let them burn.
So that now there
is only himself,
his opponent, and the fight.
Soon, he will reach a realm
still faster, keener,
and deeper than instinct,
where even that awareness
will blur and fade.
And beyond that...
I don't understand where he's
getting all of this power.
[TOP] Goku is generating a
heat I've never felt before.
Uh! All I know is that we
can't let this continue.
Jiren! Get him, now!
Hurry and end this!
[JIREN grunting]
[JIREN yells]
[SUPREME KAI] Jiren's attacks
are intensifying as well!
[ELDER KAI]
That's a remarkable technique.
Jiren's using extreme
rapid-fire punches
to generate a barrage
of powerful shockwaves.
He's got Goku pinned down.
And look where Goku is standing.
It's a ring fragment with
nothing else beneath it.
He falls, he's done.
Even with that shield he's
created there's no telling
when that rock will crumble.
And all the other rocks near him
are getting blown apart, too.
If he doesn't make a move soon
he'll have nowhere else to go.
Quick, Goku! Get outta there
while you still can! Hurry up!
He knows.
But he's got his hands full
just blocking those attacks.
He has no time to move, much
less use Instant Transmission.
[KRILLIN gasps]
Then... Then what's the answer?
There's gotta be
something he could do!
No more talk.
[ALL gasp]
Just shut your mouths and watch.
Lord Beerus...
[BELMOD chuckles]
Poor Beerus.
It sounds like he's
accepted the inevitable.
At long lost,
we've come to the end.
Either Goku will drain
the last of his power,
or that rock will crumble
beneath his feet.
Whichever way he loses, all we
have to do is wait, my lord.
Yeah, you got that right.
We should savor this, as the
moment our victory was sealed.
See those sparks?
[BELMOD]
Hm?
[TOP] They look like collisions
from opposing shockwaves.
[TOP] Goku isn't only
shielding himself now,
he's launching a
counteroffensive.
[JIREN grunts]
How dare you?!
There's no way!
Goku broke through!
He sliced through Jiren's
defenses... and connected!
[growls]
[yells]
Oh...
What? Tell us!
What is happening now?
[ZENO]
The ring just got very sparkly!
[FUTURE ZENO]
Sparkly and whooshy!
[ZENO] Do you think all of that
could be Goku's energy?
[FUTURE ZENO] It's so bright and
twinkly, and very, very hot!
[FUTURE ZENO] I think something
amazing's about to happen!
[ZENO]
Yes, I think that, too!
[inhales]
Hmph!
[WHIS]
Mm.
Well done, Goku.
You have successfully
landed a blow.
And you have channeled
this extraordinary energy
to overpower mine.
I'll have to respond in kind.
[JIREN grunts]
[JIREN yelling]
[TOP] Uh! Jiren's unleashing
even more power than I expected.
This pressure is so intense--
if his energy goes any higher
we could all be crushed!
It doesn't matter!
I don't care what happens,
as long as we win!
Just finish him, Jiren!
Use your unstoppable,
inescapable, absolute power!
[grunts]
[JIREN grunting]
Do it, Jiren! Stop Goku,
once and for all!
Farewell, warrior.
It's... over!
[ALL gasp]
[ALL gasping]
[JIREN grunting]
[gasps]
[groans]
[grunting]
Goku seems even more
amazing than Jiren now!
Yes, now he is
super-super-super amazing!
Indeed, sires.
He has arrived at
something truly superb.
[JIREN yelling]
[JIREN grunting]
[BEERUS]
Whis.
Yes?
[BEERUS]
Goku's done it, hasn't he?
He's finally achieved it?
Yes.
[growls]
It's astounding!
This mortal really
is something else.
Look at that brilliant form,
there can be no doubt.
This is the true power,
complete in all its majesty.
This is Autonomous
Ultra Instinct.
Whirling all around
and then back again
The song that connects you
to the heavens
Strength that goes
beyond all measure
Expanding to a beat
that won't end
The meteors fall like rain drops
Astrological tears
from my eyelids
A strong emotion
from deep within
Has been awakened
A spark of possibility
Shines softly like a star
in the night sky
A wish from long
ago now shoots by
And I'm awakened
A never-ending melody,
so enchanting
You're always the one
who makes me tremble
The meteors keep falling down
Surging right into my heart
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Now that I've reached truly
Autonomous Ultra Instinct,
I can't wait to let it rip!
Still, even against my awesome
power, Jiren's not folding easy.
He's raising his own
strength even higher!
But with the lives of
everyone I care about
on the line, I can't fail.
So let's do this,
Jiren. You and me!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"The Greatest Showdown
of All Time!
The Ultimate Survival Battle!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?