♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Hit from the Sixth Universe
and Jiren from the Eleventh
faced off in
a reality-bending clash.
At first, Jiren easily
overwhelmed Hit,
but the cold assassin
had a plan.
[NARRATOR] By steadily
collecting time through
his relentless
"Time Skip" attacks,
Hit trapped Jiren in
a dimensional prison.
[HIT]
One last play.
[NARRATOR]
Then bet it all on one attack.
[JIREN] Do you know what
the pride of an assassin
is good for?
Nothing!
[NARRATOR] But not even
Hit's clever technique
and bold attack could put
the mighty Jiren down.
[JIREN]
This fight is over.
[NARRATOR] His gamble lost,
and Hit was finished.
It can't be!
[NARRATOR] With their most
experienced and cunning warrior
thrown to the bench,
the Sixth Universe
finds themselves
in dire straits.
Meanwhile, Jiren has
boldly begun to meditate,
deciding he no longer
needs to fight.
The Tournament of Power
continues... now!
[NARRATOR] "A Saiyan Oath!
Vegeta's Resolve!"
Jiren. I've still got a
bit of fight left in me.
How much should I be
worried about Goku?
His body is quite clearly
exhausted, my lord.
But his fighting
spirit burns brightly.
Though it may be ill-advised for
him to jump back into battle,
I doubt he can be dissuaded.
Hey. Did you say there
were 50 tacks left?
[GRAND MINISTER]
Yes, sire. One half remains.
And what will happen when
all of the time goes away?
Tell us again, I forgot.
The universe which has
the most remaining warriors
shall be the winner,
and thus be spared.
[BOTH]
Oh, that's right.
The Seventh Universe,
with their seven remaining,
is now alone at the top.
But with Goku tired, this may
be our chance to pounce.
Heh!
[beeping]
Lord Mosco is in agreement.
He says now is the best
time to attack Goku.
[ALL grunting]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU screams]
They're teaming up on Goku!
Three of them attacking together
when he's not yet recovered?
Cowardice!
No offense, Supreme Kai,
but you sound naive.
Believe in him.
It's all we can do.
[screaming]
[PANCEA grunts]
There's trouble.
Hey! Gohan, you need
to help Goku--now!
I'm sure he can
handle it, Piccolo.
We just need to believe
in that and focus on
the fight in front of us!
[yelling]
[GOHAN yelling]
[SAONEL, PICCOLO grunting]
Damn it!
[PICCOLO groans]
[SAONEL]
You're through!
[SAONEL grunts]
[PICCOLO yells]
[SAONEL gasping]
That was close.
You sure you're okay?
I'm okay. Heh. Guess we
shouldn't be surprised
other universes have
strong Namekians, as well.
Pick off a couple more from the
Seventh! Then all we have to do
is keep running and
hiding till it's over!
You want them to run away, sir?
Jiren's unbeatable,
that's obvious now.
The only way we can win is
to have the most survivors
and run down the clock.
I guess that could work,
if you can stomach it.
[CHAMPA] Let the others have
their "honor." I'd rather live.
[CAULIFLA] Hey, enough
with the frowny-face!
[KALE] But Jiren's power is on
a completely different level.
Well losing confidence
won't help.
Think about it. Aren't you
even a little bit scared?
Yeah, I'm majorly scared!
Scared of my own
unlimited potential!
[laughing]
[laughs nervously]
I mean that was my biggest
takeaway from watching
Goku and Jiren duke it out!
You and me are Saiyans
too, right Kale?
If Goku can reach that
crazy level, then so can we!
You're so positive, sis.
Like always.
[gasps]
Whoa, what is that shaking?
[BOTH gasp]
[KALE yelps]
[grunting]
You come to start
somethin', stranger?
I have come to destroy.
Looks like Monna
is about to attack.
She's smart enough
to see the opening.
The Sixth Universe
is one of the teams
that's ahead of us
in the totals.
And with Hit gone, this is
the perfect time to strike.
[CAULIFLA] If you're itchin'
for a fight, that's fine by me.
I'll take her.
You sit this one out.
Yeah, okay.
[MONNA laughs]
Are ya ready?
Come find out.
[whirring]
Huh?
[CABBA grunts]
Hey, Hero Boy!
You're standing in my way.
Let me handle this, please.
You two should go and
hide somewhere safe
until I've finished her.
[KALE]
Cabba...
[CAULIFLA] No way, Tiny!
You're not the boss of me!
Please, trust me,
and do as I ask.
Don't play the savior just
'cause they're girls--
they're welcome to fight me too.
All three of you can
come at me together.
Thanks, but I'm confident my
power is more than enough.
You've got some nerve, boy!
[CABBA yells]
--[MONNA laughs]
--[CABBA grunting]
After all your barking,
I was expecting
just a little more bite!
You've got some real strength,
I'll at least give you that.
Aw come on,
she's overpowering him!
Move it! I'll handle her!
No please, don't!
We need you both to save your
strength for bigger fights!
Don't you worry,
I've got tons to spare!
Fighting her won't tap me out!
There's no room for error--
don't be careless!
Just hold on. I think
we should listen to him.
Huh?!
I'm gonna keep pushing
until you beg me to stop!
Let me do this!
I can defeat her!
[CAULIFLA growls]
He has a point--
there are stronger foes!
You should use your energy
to fight them instead!
[CAULIFLA growls]
All right fine, whatever.
--[MONNA laughing]
--[CABBA grunting]
Just don't get crushed!
C'mon. We need to find
a way out of here.
Yeah.
[CABBA] With Hit gone,
Caulifla and Kale
are the best chances the Sixth
Universe has to survive.
I have to do everything I
can to help them succeed.
Pay attention, I'm a
Saiyan and no pushover.
So I will not let
you look down on me!
[MONNA screams]
[CABBA yelling]
[panting]
Uh?!
I'll be honest short stuff,
that almost kinda hurt.
[growls]
You'll be sorry! Ha!
[CABBA grunts]
[CABBA groaning]
[CABBA screaming]
[gasps]
[CABBA screams]
I'm not done yet!
[CABBA grunts]
[CABBA groaning]
[CABBA panting]
[MONNA]
This is where it ends!
Agreed!
Now, roll right off the edge!
She can turn?!
[CABBA screams]
Cabba!
[CABBA]
Damn it. I failed.
I couldn't even eliminate
one more enemy for them.
But maybe I at least
bought some time
for Caulifla and Kale
to recover their strength.
[CABBA grunts]
[CABBA]
Huh...?
Uh!
[CABBA]
Master?
Master!
Ah!
[CABBA groaning]
Hey, do you mind?!
Don't you steal my victory!
[MONNA yelps]
Heh.
Why would he rescue someone
who's not on our team?
Those two have
forged something of
a "teacher-pupil"
dynamic, sir.
Well that's a complex
thing to navigate
when they're from two
competing universes.
Especially since only one
of our teams can survive.
Vegeta's a stand-up guy,
I've always said that!
Yet again, one of our fighters
has been aided in battle
by someone from your brother's
universe, Lord Champa.
Yeah, yeah, I'll be
sure to pay him back.
You know me, Mr. Magnanimous.
This guy. Just gimme
a freakin' break.
[CABBA]
Thank you for saving me.
I am in your debt.
[CABBA groans]
[coughing]
Don't get the wrong idea.
Yes, Master.
[VEGETA] I didn't pull you
back out of kindness.
I just can't let a Saiyan
embarrass our race
by losing so easily.
[CABBA]
I understand. I'm sorry.
You aren't planning
to get eliminated
and break your old
promise to me,
are you, you punk?
My... promise?
[VEGETA]
You really don't remember?
You said you'd take
me to Planet Sadla.
[CABBA] You know,
the King of Planet Sadla
is a proud, strong man,
much like yourself.
In fact, you remind me of him.
[VEGETA]
That so?
You'll have to introduce
us sometime.
But only one universe
can survive.
That means no matter
how hard I fight,
there's no way to
keep that promise.
I'm going to win this charade.
And when I do, I'll use
the Super Dragon Balls
to bring you and
your universe back.
What? You would do that?
I'm not going to let a
Saiyan break his word.
You're the best! And if by
some chance our universe
ends up winning instead,
I'll make sure we bring back
the Seventh, Master!
Don't be ridiculous!
I'll win this, not you!
Uh! Of course, yeah.
Yeah, sorry sir.
Are those two friends
or not friends?
It is confusing.
It is confusing to me as well!
It appears they have
the relationship
of a teacher and student, sires.
Teacher and student!
How neat!
[VEGETA]
Fight with all you have--
bring honor to yourself
and our kind!
Okay. I will.
A monkey teaching a monkey
with love and adoration.
It really makes the stomach
turn, doesn't it?
Master.
This time I'll remember my
Saiyan pride, I promise!
[MONNA] Ha! You call
that pest your master?
[CABBA groans]
[MONNA]
After I'm done with you,
I'll throw out that
miserable Vegeta, too!
[CABBA]
Master!
[MONNA] And then those Saiyan
women who ran away!
I'm never gonna
let you touch them!
[CABBA groaning]
[CABBA screams]
[CABBA gasping]
[MONNA]
Ha! What a little weakling!
And I thought you Saiyans were
supposed to be great warriors!
You're frauds!
Quitters and cowardly sneaks!
Vegeta is too!
Don't you say that... about him!
But it's true. All he could do
is blindside me and run away!
He's nothing but
a spineless chicken!
[CABBA]
How dare you!
I don't know why I'm wasting so
much time with all you sissies!
I'll finish you, that
sucker-punching twerp
and those Saiyan girls,
then find some worthy foes!
Don't you dare call us unworthy!
[yelling]
Hey, there's something different
about Cabba now, isn't there?
Once again our young
Saiyan fighter is maturing
in the heat of battle, my lord.
Is changing your hair color
supposed to scare me?
[groans]
[MONNA groaning]
[panting]
All right, now I'm angry!
[MONNA]
I'll flatten you, you brat!
[CABBA grunts]
[MONNA]
Here comes the pain, shorty!
[yelling]
[MONNA screams]
[panting]
See, Master? I did it.
Heh. I'm not mad,
I'm just disappointed.
Way to go, Cabba!
As long as you listen
to my coaching,
you can take down anybody!
But Lord Champa,
wasn't it your advice
that he simply go run and hide?
[whistles]
[ZENO]
Boop! Heh!
And with the elimination
of Contestant Monna,
the Fourth Universe has
only three fighters left.
[VEGETA]
Hmph. That's more like it.
Now to the more
important issue.
How long does Jiren plan to sit?
Cocky bastard
gets under my skin.
He assumes we're not
strong enough to matter.
I'm going to show him
how wrong he is.
You'll have to get through me.
I don't pluck second strings.
Yet you're second on your
own team, aren't you?
Oh shut it, moustache!
Why don't you come
find out for yourself!
[yelling]
[TOP yells]
[TOP grunts]
I just hope Kale and
Caulifla are still okay.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[CABBA]
It's you.
Salutations, monkey.
You seem to be a most
stalwart adversary.
I would love the honor of a
duel if you would so oblige.
All right, you got it!
Feel free to attack me
any way you see fit.
[CABBA yelling]
[CABBA grunting]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[CABBA groans]
[coughs]
I have to be honest.
While I do respect
powerful fighters,
there's nothing that I despise
more than a monkey.
After I've rid this ring
of your vile presence,
I'm going to play with
your Saiyan sisters.
That should be a
special kind of fun.
[CABBA]
What?!
I'm not gonna let you
terrorize them.
There's no way!
We're the ones who
are gonna win this!
[panting]
I know that blast connected.
[groans]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Use what little brains
you have and surrender.
I'll never give up again.
I'll keep fighting...
until the end.
Your end is now.
[CABBA screams]
It would have been profligate of
me to waste any more strength
on you. I have
bigger apes to fry.
[CABBA]
I'm so sorry.
He waited until Cabba was
exhausted and cornered him!
Damn it! That craven weasel!
[FRIEZA laughs] The Super Dragon
Balls will be mine alone.
And then I'll wrap the gods
around my finger.
[panting]
Huh? Hey, Vegeta.
Looks like you're having
some trouble with those
recycled waste baskets.
Well, I'm just
stringin' 'em along
until I can get my
strength back.
[VEGETA grunts]
I saw that Cabba got
knocked out of the ring.
Doesn't make any difference--
I just have to win this thing.
Oh, I see.
It's that simple, huh?
The Saiyans will never perish!
You're right about that, Vegeta.
You quitting already?
In your dreams, loser.
[ALL beeping]
[GOKU laughs] I may be drained,
but I'll still fight.
I don't have any choice.
Uh!
[GOKU growls]
[ALL screeching]
[CAULIFLA]
Ha!
[PANCEA groans]
[CAULIFLA yells]
[KOITSUKAI whimpers]
Ha!
Wow. That's amazing!
Thanks a lot! You totally
saved me there!
With the time Cabba bought me,
I'm back to full strength.
So let's go.
You and me, Goku!
Uh?!
[NARRATOR]
First Hit, and now Cabba
have been eliminated from
the Sixth Universe's squad.
But rather than seek
revenge against Frieza
for knocking out her teammate,
Caulifla is choosing to
challenge Goku instead.
What is driving
this fierce Saiyan?
In this battle royale, the
motivations of each fighter
create an ever-more
complicated web.
Twenty-three minutes remain
until the Tournament
of Power ends.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super.
A 70 centimeter squared window
Today the sun broke
through the clouds
The rain is fin'ly gone
Gonna open up
the window for once
No reason, just because
This room has been
stained with the sighs
Of everyday regret
Now it's time to clear the air
Every moment was consumed
with my thoughts of you
Knowing in my heart those dreams
won't be coming true
I've always wanted nothing more
than to see your face
I move on knowing that your
mem'ry can't be erased
[GOKU]
Hey, it's me, Goku!
And it looks like a three-way
Saiyan showdown's
about to begin with
Caulifla, Kale, and me!
I need to find
my strength quick,
because these younger Saiyans
are making bigger
leaps in power,
and launching combo
attacks on me, too!
All right, girls,
let's see if you're ready
for Super Saiyan Three!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"With Great Joy! The Fighting
Freak Saiyans' Battle Rejoined!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?