♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Z,
the inhabitants of Earth
faced the most terrifying foe
they'd ever seen, and it seemed
nothing would remain.
But Goku and Vegeta made
a desperate final stand.
Then, Goku summoned
a massive Spirit Bomb,
drawing on energy from all
the revived people of Earth,
who rallied to help
because of Mr. Satan's plea.
And as more energy flowed in
from across the universe,
this mighty Spirit Bomb
proved too powerful
for even the destructive,
alien magic of Majin Buu.
Six months later, using the
power of the Dragon Balls,
humankind's memories of Buu's
terror and destruction
were erased,
and the planet has enjoyed
several more months of peace.
[NARRATOR]
"A Peacetime Reward:
Who Gets the 100,000,000 Zeni?!"
[birds chirping]
[tractor engine rumbles]
[thud]
Huh? Uh?
[sighs]
[GOKU grunts]
You just won't let go,
will you, stump?
You're about
as stubborn as Vegeta.
[chuckles]
[GOTEN]
Hey Dad!
[GOKU]
Huh?
I brought you lunch!
[GOKU]
Oh hey!
Kinda early for school
to be out, isn't it, Goten?
No, Dad, this is Sunday!
Wow, it is?
[chuckles]
Well, then you wanna drive
the tractor for me while I eat?
Okay, sure!
[GOKU]
I love lunch so much!
[chortles]
Thanks for the grub.
[GOKU grunts lightly]
Ah!
That was awesome.
All right.
[bellows]
[GOTEN]
Huh?
[grunting, yells]
Uh?
[GOKU]
Yaaa!
[chuckles]
Huh?
[yells]
[gasps]
Look Goten. You've gotta
drive a little better than that
or I can't focus on my training.
Do you really think
you have to keep training?
Yeah! Majin Buu
was ridiculously strong.
There's no way I could've
stopped him on my own.
And you never know,
one day someone
even stronger could show up.
So I've gotta keep training,
to keep you guys safe.
Make sense?
[GOTEN]
Uh... Guess so.
[GOKU]
The truth is--
I'd like to go
to King Kai's planet
and do some hard core training.
But your mom's
not quite sold on it.
Not a chance!
You need to work!
You're going to earn this
family some money for once!
Yeah sometimes
I think she must be
the strongest on the planet.
And I guess she has a point,
since all of Grandpa's treasures
burned up in that fire.
There's not much money left.
[OX KING slurps]
Hm?
[GOTEN]
But Mom says there are ways
you could make
decent money, Dad.
You know, like if you did the
kinda stuff Mr. Satan does.
Maybe. But I like
being out here
where I can sneak in
a little training, at least.
[GOTEN] I'm not sure
I'd call it "sneaking in."
This field is kind of a mess.
[GOKU laughs]
Yeah.
What's taking so long?!
Bring it all in, quickly!
[ALL gasp, yell]
Lord Beerus. Please, help
yourself to this royal feast!
Each course has been
meticulously crafted
by our world's finest chefs,
and I can assure you,
their creations are
the definition of exquisite!
[BEERUS] Is that so?
Well. We'll see about that.
[BEERUS] Hmmnngh.
[ALIEN KING 1A whimpers]
[BEERUS]
Hmmuugh.
[sniffs]
Please remember
your manners, Lord Beerus.
[BEERUS]
And what's this?
[shrieks]
It's a, uh, a completely
organically grown,
flash Pasteurized, small batch
serving of à la planètes,
your mighty lordship!
[BEERUS] À la pra...
À--À la pla--?
Are you serious?
What an insufferable name.
[ALIEN CHEFS, STAFF gasp]
[BEERUS]
Hmm. Tastier than I expected.
The use of salt is... divine.
[gasps]
Thank you, my Lord.
So you won't--
[BEERUS]
However...
There's a greasy mouth feel,
which is odd for what
I assume is... dessert?
Tell you what,
I'll only take half.
Half, my lord?
A bit harsh for food you
called "tasty,"
wouldn't you say, my lord?
[BEERUS] Ugh. All that
grease is unhealthy,
makes you sluggish all day.
I've done this galaxy a favor.
[REPORTER 1A] Mr. Satan,
can we get a quote?
[REPORTERS shouting
indisitictivly]
How do you feel about
receiving the Grand Prize
from the World Peace Assembly?
Do you agree they
should have done it sooner?
[REPORTERS shouting
indisitictivly]
[ALL gasp]
I've prepared a statement,
which I'll now state.
I'm proud to say
world peace on Earth
is now officially
permanent-ized!
I say this humbly.
We've had zero
new alien invaders
since I bravely saved us all.
That's clearly because word
of my musclebound heroics
has spread to the stars.
I can see it now!
[ALL gasp in awe]
[MR. SATAN] Villains throughout
the cosmos now quiver in fear,
knees buckling at the
unbridled power of Mr. Satan!
[yelling]
[cameras clicking]
[REPORTERS shouting]
[laughs intensely]
What the deal?! Buu hungry!
[MR. SATAN]
Ooh!
[REPORTERS]
Huh?
[MR. SATAN] Buu!
[BUU'S stomach growls]
[REPORTER 3AA] Some pink
weirdo has entered the room!
Mr. Satan. Buu need food!
Uh, Buu. Can't this wait?
I'm kinda' busy here.
Hungry now!
He yelled at him.
A pretty brazen move,
yelling at our planet's savior.
Maybe he's not afraid of him.
Maybe he's even stronger.
[REPORTERS murmur, gasp]
[MR. SATAN] Eeh!
No, it's not like that.
Everyone stay calm!
There's no need
to be afraid of this guy.
He is an alien
but not an invader.
Truth is he's a galactic
warrior who traveled
from the farthest
reaches of space.
And begged me
to become his sensei.
It was rough at first
but he's now my top pupil!
Oh yeah that make sense.
Don't know why
I didn't guess that.
Of course aliens would want
Mr. Satan to teach 'em, right?
[MR. SATAN sighs]
Now get! Go back to your
training room.
I'll be there soon
to instruct you
in the art of the dynamite kick.
Buu told you Buu hungry!
And your mighty sensei
told you to wait in the back!
[BUU]
Mmmm!
[MR. SATAN snarls]
[grunts]
It's amazing!
He's not just the valiant
protector of Earth!
He's the greatest hero
in the whole universe!
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
Excuse me while I powder
my nose. And go pee.
[MR. SATAN]
I'm sorry, Buu. I'm sorry!
Come on. Don't be mad!
You know I love ya!
I'll make ya lots of tasty
treats later, and then maybe
a nice bubble bath?
Your favorite!
Hungry now!
Okay, okay.
Keep your cape on!
I'm sure there's chocolate
or something in here--huh?
[wails]
Videl! Give your daddy a hand!
I can't find
the chocolate! Videl!
[VIDEL]
I can't believe we found it.
Lucky you. You've wanted
that book for a while.
Oh yeah! This is gonna
make my research
a whole lot easier.
Thanks, Videl. I'm not sure
I deserve this, though.
What's that mean?
You've been studying like crazy!
I know. But you keep
buying me all these
incredible gifts like this.
And I feel bad 'cause
I can't buy you anything.
[VIDEL] There's an easy fix
for that. Just don't feel bad!
Huh?
The best gift you can give me
is to keep on
studying hard, Gohan.
Then I'll have
a scholar as arm candy!
[GOHAN]
Deal!
[chuckles]
Speaking of arm candy,
I want something sweet.
Let's try that bakery.
[huffs]
[TRUNKS]
A present?
Yeah. My brother
and Videl got married
and I haven't
gotten them anything.
I want to find a present
that my new sister-in-law
will love for sure!
Oh. Something
she'll love huh?
For girls, that pretty
much means one thing.
What thing?
[MALE CLERK 1A]
So, what do you think?
[LADY 1A] It's beautiful!
But I can't ask you
to buy me that, baby.
It's too much!
Nonsense, dear, I want to!
Could we, maybe,
have a look at that one?
How about this one?
[BOTH gasp]
[TRUNKS] Are these
gag gifts? They're tiny!
[GOTEN] Maybe they're
rings for babies.
[TRUNKS] No way she'd be happy
with one of these pebbles.
You'll have to go way bigger.
Unless they come with
a magnifying glass.
[GOTEN]
Yeah.
Uh... hello.
Can I help you boys?
Over there, maybe?
[TRUNKS]
Let's see.
[MAN 1A, LADY 1A shriek]
[GOTEN]
Nah, these are tiny, too.
[TRUNKS] You should
get her somethin' else.
[GOTEN]
All right.
You see that?!
They can fly!
[MAN 1B]
Oooh! Wow!
Your skin really does
feel softer now!
I don't know
what to get her.
[TRUNKS] Yeah, if jewels are
out, we've gotta get creative.
Hmm.
How 'bout eau de toilette?
Ooh-duh-what-now?
It's fancy talk
for toilet water,
and ladies like to put it
on their face at night.
At least my mom does.
[BULMA] It smells nice, but
it's wrong for my skin type.
Well maybe I should
give it to Videl.
She might think she's
too young for skin care.
But if she's not on it like me,
one day she'll wake up
lookin' like Master Roshi.
Well if your mom likes it,
then I'm sure
Videl will too, right?
[TRUNKS]
To the girly store!
[GOTEN]
Yeah!
I can't afford this stuff
on my allowance.
[BOTH]
Mmm.
Six thousand Zeni,
that's highway robbery!
Where do you get off
charging that much?!
Well sir, this is
our ultra-advanced
hydrating formula, with rare
skin-nourishing compounds.
You can't find this
anywhere else.
Like hell I can't, missy!
The hot springs back home work
better than this fancy crap,
and they don't cost me
an arm and a leg!
Three days soaking
in there's all you need!
Even turns an old lady's skin
smooth as a baby's butt!
Hey, old dude!
Those hot springs!
How do we get there, man?
'Scuse me?
The hot springs!
The ones you just said
are great for your skin,
even for broke-down
old lady butt!
Wow, you're
a good eavesdropper.
You go a long way
in that direction.
Then at the woods,
take a hard left!
And you'll find the springs
swirling up in the mountains!
[BOTH]
Aaah!
Thank you, old dude!
[TRUNKS] A long way
in this direction.
[GOTEN] And at the woods,
a hard left.
Nothin's here.
Oh! Is that it?
Ah-ah-ah.. choo!
That water looks
kinda dirty, huh?
Prob'ly 'cause all
those nasty people are in it.
Maybe let's go look
higher up the mountain.
Can't we just
get it from a toilet?
[TRUNKS gasps]
Look! Over there!
[GOTEN]
Wow! It's crystal clear!
I bet she'll like that
way better, right?
Yeah!
Perfect gift achieved!
[GOTEN]
All right.
Little more.
Fill up all the way!
[TRUNKS]
Careful, don't fall in!
[GOTEN]
I know, I know.
[hiss]
Nice. Let's head back.
[GOTEN]
Mhmm!
[SNAKE 1A yells]
[GOTEN yells, gasps]
Hold on. I've got it!
[hisses]
Hey watch it, buddy!
If you want toilet water,
get your own!
[yells]
Goten!
Okay, I'm ready!
[yells]
Trunks, here!
Right!
[TRUNKS]
Hey! Knock it off!
He doesn't quit, does he?
[yells]
Hang on, Goten. No!
We're too close to the hot
springs! It's too dangerous!
[SNAKE 1A roars]
[TRUNKS]
Your turn! Catch!
[GOTEN] Aah!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[yells]
Is the jar messed up?
[chuckles]
[TRUNKS]
Yoohoo! Videl!
[VIDEL]
Huh?
[TRUNKS, GOTEN chuckle]
Here! It's my
mega-special wedding gift!
Wow! That's for me?
That's so thoughtful.
Thanks, Goten.
[GOHAN] Goten! Trunks!
When'd you get here?
[GOTEN]
Hey, Gohan!
Hey, what's that?
This is a wedding gift.
From your little brother!
It's toilet water!
[GOHAN]
Uh--what?
It's for her face!
Trunks helped me get it
up on a mountain!
[gasps]
You mean eau de toilette.
Sounds like you went
to a lot of trouble.
[TRUNKS]
Don't you want to try some?
Sure.
[VIDEL gasps]
[VIDEL]
Is this just ordinary water?
[BOTH chuckle]
[VIDEL chuckles softly]
[TRUNKS]
Pretty smooth, huh?
You like it?
Yeah, it's great!
My skin feels incredible!
Thanks, Goten. And thank you,
Trunks. I'm a lucky girl.
[BOTH laugh]
Well just let me know
if you run out!
I'll get you more any time!
[VIDEL chuckles]
[GOKU] You did a really
good thing, Goten.
I'm sure you made Videl's day.
[GOTEN]
Hm!
[GOKU]
So, what's their house like?
It's super big!
Well Mr. Satan had it
built, so I bet it is.
Sure was nice of him.
Now Gohan can study all he wants
and not worry about bills.
[horn honks]
[GOTEN, GOKU]
Huh?
Hey there!
Great to see ya, Goku!
I been lookin' for ya!
Chichi told me you'd be up here.
[GOKU]
Oh hey, Mr. Satan!
Well that's funny. We were
just talking about you.
You're a good man.
I can't thank you enough
for buying that
huge house for Gohan.
It was my pleasure.
I mean what do you expect,
Videl's my baby girl!
But enough about the house.
That's not why I'm here.
Did you happen to see
the news today?
No. I don't watch TV.
All right then, I'll tell ya.
I got an award today.
Grand Prize, in fact,
from the World Peace Assembly,
for saving the earth
from certain doom.
You don't say.
Yeah. You might remember
how it kinda got around
that I saved the world
from Armageddon.
Well that's what it's for.
And the prize money is,
uh, substantial.
A hundred million Zeni.
[GOKU, GOTEN]
A hundred million!
Shh!
[MR. SATAN exhales deeply]
But the point is,
you're the only one
who really deserves this dough.
So I'm handing it over!
[GOKU] Whoa, whoa.
I can't accept that!
[MR. SATAN] Come on, don't be
silly! You earned it, brother!
[GOKU]
No, seriously, I'm fine.
I wasn't the only one
fighting him.
You did your part, too,
in your own way.
[MR. SATAN] But I already
got too much money to count!
B'sides, Vegeta said no too.
Heh. But of course,
that guy's married into
the richest family on Earth.
Hold on. How much
is a hundred million Zeni?
Is that more than
a hundred thousand?
[MR. SATAN]
Huh? Well, yeah, of course!
Let's see, it's uh, a
thousand times more, in fact.
Aah! A thousand times more
than a hundred thousand!
Well now I really don't want it!
Where would I put it!
I don't have a treasure cave!
Uh, I think
you should take it, Dad.
If you come home
with all of that money,
then Mom won't worry
about you having a job.
So you could go train
with King Kai.
You think so? Ah. Mm.
But it's so much.
Come on, Goku. Listen to
your boy and take the cash.
I swear it won't bite.
[GOKU grunts]
Fine. I'll take it.
We could use the money.
So you're sure
you don't want it?
[MR. SATAN]
Hmm!
[GOKU]
Well, okay. Thank you.
Yeah! That's a relief!
Now, uh...
I hate asking for something
in return here, but--
can you keep this
on the low-down?
I got a reputation to protect.
[CHICHI]
A hundred million Zeni!
I don't even know
what to say, Goku!
With this money we can afford
any school we want for Goten!
And lots of private tutors
and anything else he needs!
It's a dream!
I'm glad you like it.
So, uh-- I was wondering
if I could, you know,
train with King Kai now?
[CHICHI] Yeah, sure. Just drop
by from time to time, okay?
Eee! Awesome!
[giggles]
All right, then.
See ya' soon.
[CHICHI] I'm gonna start
looking for tutors right now!
And private schools!
And after-school schools!
Goten, you're gonna
know everything!
[ROSHI]
Yea-ha!
Goku! Is it true, you really
got a hundred million Zeni!
That's a game-changer!
Do you have any idea how many
dirty movie DVDs you can buy
with that kind of load!
You could even go Blu-ray!
[CHICHI snarls]
You think I'd let you
blow our money on filth!
[ROSHI hollers]
Ancestor. Another planet
has been decimated.
Just what could be
happening out there?
[ELDER KAI]
Mmm.
♪ Closing Song ♪
I see all these kids
As I walk to school
Their colorful backpacks
All unique and cool
I can't help but wonder
which color I'd choose
If I were still a kid
Where would I run off to? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
How am I lookin' now that
I've grown into an adult? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
Do I look like I'm proud
of who I've finally become?
Oh, I know I've made mistakes
But I'm tryin' to get it right
And I'm willing just to wait
For the moment I can shine
This anthem
Is a story for all time!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Guess what? Vegeta is
going on family vaction!
I know Bulma
and Trunks are happy,
but can the Saiyan prince
avoid a beach resort meltdown?
And while he's riding
tiny trains,
I'll be busy training!
So watch out, King Kai,
for Instant Transmission
road hazards! Aah!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"To the Promised Resort!
Vegeta Takes a Family Trip?!"
I don't think you'll want to
miss that disaster!