♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the Tournament of Power was
narrowed down to three teams,
and the Seventh Universe
fought against
the four remaining fighters
from the Third Universe,
who had combined
together into Agnilasa--
a towering titan with
astounding techniques.
Goku, Vegeta, Gohan, Frieza, and
the Androids battled together,
yet they still struggled to hang
on against this colossal beast.
[PAPARONI roars]
[A17 grunts]
[A17]
Not good!
[gasps]
Win this for us, all right?
What are you doing?
Come on, I know you like
this warm and fuzzy stuff.
18, no!
[NARRATOR] Sacrificing herself
to keep her twin brother
in the Tournament,
18 was knocked out.
[PAPARONI roars]
Ha!
[VEGETA yells]
[GOHAN]
Ha!
[A17 yelling]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[NARRATOR] As his teammates
fired an immense,
combined blast, 17 struck
a strategic blow
that disabled Agnilasa's
power source,
and the Third Universe
was eliminated.
[MULE] Thanks for everything,
pal. We're outta here.
[NARRATOR] Now only two teams
still stand in the ring:
The Eleventh, and the Seventh.
But only one can
escape destruction.
[JIREN] Try all you want,
you cannot defeat me.
Well that ain't
how I see it, Jiren.
[NARRATOR]
The final showdown begins now!
"With His Pride on the Line!
Vegeta's Challenge to Be
the Strongest!"
There's nine minutes left.
Come on, guys! Win it!
[FUTURE ZENO]
Ooh. It's down to the Seventh
and the Eleventh now. I wonder
which universe will win.
[ZENO]
Yes, I am wondering that, too.
This finale will be
a sight to behold.
Though with so few
spectators left,
the stands do look a bit bare.
[BOTH] Yes, just look
at all the benches!
[GRAND MINISTER]
Hm. I believe this will help.
[ROSHI]
Hm?
Now what?
[gasping]
Hey!
What is going on
with the bleachers?
[SPECTATORS chattering]
Hm?
Hmph.
Uh. Hello.
[KHAI grunts]
[ALL murmur]
[KRILLIN]
Um, crazy fight, huh?
[KRILLIN laughs nervously]
[GRAND MINISTER] Does that
look better, Your Majesties?
Oh yes, I like it!
They aren't sitting
so far apart now!
Look at us all together.
This is downright cozy.
Yes, quite a change.
Though you've been cozying up to
the Seventh for a while, Vados.
Well, now that the Sixth
is erased I'm thinking
I'll impose on this
universe for a while,
like an uninvited houseguest.
[laughing]
[GRAND MINISTER] The time
column is about to drop down
to its final section, sires.
The winners shall
be determined soon.
The two remaining universes
in this Tournament
should be commended, not only
for showing impressive
power in their battles,
but also for showing ingenuity,
and the willingness to adapt
and do whatever it
takes to survive.
Buckle up, boys, this is it.
The battle between the
mightiest in the cosmos.
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU grunting]
[yelling]
[yelling continues]
[JIREN grunts]
Hmph. He always has
to be dramatic.
Hm?
Awesome. You really
are strong, Jiren.
My hands are actually starting
to sting a little bit.
Tell me, Goku. What drives your
endless quest for strength?
Honestly? I can't explain it.
I just want to get stronger--
always have!
As I thought.
You don't even know.
[GOKU] What about you?
Don't you want to get stronger?
[JIREN]
I seek to achieve something
beyond strength, simpleton.
Well, duh, that's
what I've been saying!
I want to get stronger
than strong,
and then stronger than that!
[JIREN grunts]
Contestant Goku versus
Contestant Jiren.
The result of the Tournament
and the fates of their universes
most likely hinge
on this one fight.
I want this fight
to last a long time!
I don't want it to end either!
[BOTH]
It's so fun to watch!
[GOKU grunting]
Okay, are you ready to
start round two? Huh?
All right, Jiren! I demand
you show me your power!
Vegeta, come on!
That's my fight, no fair!
[yelling]
[laughs] You'll never hit me!
It's a simple fact.
I'm the fastest warrior alive
in the entire Multiverse!
[FRIEZA chuckles] A master of
retreat; you must be so proud.
[DYSPO] Sounds like you
want to die twice.
[TOP yells]
[A17, GOHAN grunt]
This Top guy went
toe-to-toe against
my dad in the Expo fights.
Be sure to watch out
for those massive arms--
you don't want to get
caught in his grip.
Yeah. I see 'em.
Come at me. You will only
be fodder for my fists.
[grunts]
[VEGETA yelling]
[VEGETA]
Your energy's like a steel wall.
I've never faced
anything like it.
But... I don't care how
powerful you are--
I will be the one
who defeats you
and claims the
Super Dragon Balls!
[JIREN grunts]
[VEGETA groans]
You're fighting me now, Jiren!
[VEGETA gasping]
[GOKU screams]
[groaning]
[grunts]
Ha!
[GOKU yelps]
[yells]
[GOKU grunting]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA grunting]
You are a stubborn one,
aren't you?
Hmph.
[VEGETA]
Bad news for you, Jiren.
[GOKU gasping]
[VEGETA]
I've got you figured out.
[GOKU]
Vegeta!
[gasping]
Heh.
Whoa, it worked.
He breeched his defenses.
No way!
Vegeta's been watching.
He must have seen something in
that quick flurry of punches
Jiren unleashed on Goku.
Some kind of small opening
or defensive weak point
he could exploit.
Perhaps this fight will be
entertaining, after all.
Stop acting so calm, Eleventh.
Your show isn't fooling me.
[VEGETA yelling]
This is great!
And great is fun!
Vegeta's driving him back!
He's an amazing fighter, too!
[VEGETA yelling]
What's goin' on here?
Could he... be winning?
Do you actually believe
that's possible?
Are you that blind?
[growls]
[VEGETA yelling]
I have to wonder...
--Oh?
--[BEERUS] Hm?
Wonder what, Whis? Do tell.
[WHIS] Could Vegeta have another
motive for challenging Jiren?
Perhaps he seeks a catalyst
for unlocking Ultra Instinct.
[ALL gasp]
[BEERUS]
That would make sense.
And the way he was dodging--
is he knocking on the door?
Hm...
[JIREN groans]
You were faster and stronger
when you were fighting Kakarot.
Don't hold back on me!
[JIREN grunts]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA groaning]
[VEGETA screams]
Vegeta!
[VEGETA grunting]
This isn't looking good.
If he keeps sliding back,
he'll go right off the edge!
Good, Jiren! Finish him now!
[BOTH]
Wow!
Now Vegeta is being overpowered!
He's in real danger!
[VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA groaning]
[yells]
Vegeta, no!
Do you plan to keep running
like this the entire time?
[chuckles] That's the
oldest trick in the book.
Surely you don't believe
you can dethrone an emperor
with such an uninspired cliché.
[DYSPO groaning]
I've always liked having
a tail. So very helpful.
Well, the one that
it's gonna help is me.
[FRIEZA]
Hm?
[FRIEZA gasping]
[groaning]
[FRIEZA groans]
[DYSPO laughing]
[FRIEZA groaning]
[FRIEZA screams]
[GOHAN groans]
[TOP laughs] Is that
the extent of your power?
My fists of justice will
clobber you to pieces!
[yells]
Hm.
Don't interfere! Huh?
Ka... me...
...ha... me...
Ha!
[TOP]
Hmph.
[gasping]
Uh!
I'm far from impressed.
You've tried your attacks
and came up short, warrior.
And now it's my turn.
[GOHAN grunts]
[laughs]
That's what I'm talkin' about!
[BELMOD laughing]
What do you gotta say
to that, Seventh?
Jiren and his squad are
just too much for you!
It's just a matter of time
before you're wiped out!
[growls]
I wouldn't be discouraged
just yet, Lord Beerus.
It's going to take more
than that to stop our team.
If the past is prologue,
then that last attack
should trigger Vegeta to
reach an even greater power.
[VEGETA panting]
Vegeta, are you okay?
[VEGETA laughing]
Even after that whole volley,
you're not even breathing hard.
Defeating you won't be easy.
You can try all you want,
but that will be impossible.
Say what?
[GOKU]
Hm?!
[BELMOD laughs]
Your fighting style
reeks of arrogance.
Ego infects your techniques
and makes them impure.
You think you're
entitled to greatness.
[VEGETA] Hmph. Is that
supposed to be insulting?
You say I'm arrogant--
I say "damn right"!
That's pride.
Pride in the Saiyan I am.
The mighty prince of
the ultimate warrior race!
[yells]
[VEGETA] Impossible to defeat
you? Don't make me laugh!
[JIREN]
Hmph.
I won't surrender control--
that's not the man I am!
Let Kakarot use his thoughtless
Ultra Instinct all he wants,
but I'm the one who's
going to crush you, Jiren.
And I'll do it my way!
Whoa. That's amazing, Vegeta!
You've never powered up
this much before!
[KHAI gasping]
His energy is skyrocketing!
Now he's even stronger than
when he was driving back Jiren
a minute ago. But how?
What is the deal
with these Saiyans and
their bottomless power?
Jiren may have thought
that critique
would embarrass Vegeta,
but all it actually did was
remind him of his pride
and awaken even more power.
That light around him
is very bright!
Vegeta sure is getting
powerful now, isn't he?
[VEGETA]
You claim I'm no threat to you!
I assume that means you
won't act like a coward,
and try to avoid this blast.
Bring it.
[VEGETA chuckles]
Let's go! Give it to 'em!
Pound him with
everything you've got!
Final Flash!
[JIREN grunts]
Bull's eye!
That was a direct hit!
[SPECTATORS gasping]
Jiren...
[A17, GOHAN gasping]
[groaning]
[panting]
[laughs]
Ha! Serves you right!
That's what you get for doubting
the greatest in the cosm--
[gasps]
Vegeta!
[gasping]
I commend you for harnessing so
much power in your last attack.
[gasping]
[screams]
[screaming continues]
[JIREN grunts]
[BEERUS gasping]
[KRILLIN gasping]
Hmph.
It doesn't matter how
high his foe climbs.
He still climbs higher.
[BOTH]
Wow!
Vegeta's attack was so amazing,
but it didn't do anything.
Jiren's incredible!
Vegeta!
[gasping]
[JIREN grunts]
[NARRATOR] Vegeta unloaded his
most ferocious attack yet,
but the mighty Jiren has
still brought him down.
Have we witnessed the final
stand of the Saiyan prince?
And can any combatant
in the Seventh Universe
match the Eleventh's seemingly
invincible champion?
With the clock ticking down,
there is little time to
find a road to victory.
Two universes continue
to fight for survival,
with only eight minutes left
in the Tournament of Power.
Next time, on Dragon Ball Super.
Whirling all around
and then back again
The song that connects you
to the heavens
Strength that goes
beyond all measure
Expanding to a beat
that won't end
The meteors fall like rain drops
Astrological tears
from my eyelids
A strong emotion
from deep within
Has been awakened
A spark of possibility
Shines softly like a star
in the night sky
A wish from long
ago now shoots by
And I'm awakened
A never-ending melody,
so enchanting
You're always the one
who makes me tremble
The meteors keep falling down
Surging right into my heart
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
With Vegeta on the ground,
I've got to try every
trick in my book
to create an opening
in Jiren's defenses,
and let's just say things
could get... explosive.
But no matter how hard I fight,
it still may not be enough
against this incredible warrior,
so you better recover
fast, Vegeta.
Is there anything
else you've got?
Next time, on Dragon Ball Super:
"Body, Soul and Power Unleashed!
Goku and Vegeta!"
Make sure you
don't miss it, okay?