♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[GOKU gasping]
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the newly resurrected Frieza
displayed a frightening mastery
over his golden form,
easily dispatching
an army of assassins
from the Ninth Universe!
Time had not softened
Frieza at all.
He was colder and
meaner than ever.
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA yelling]
[BOTH yell]
[GOKU groans]
[FRIEZA groaning]
[BOTH groan]
[GOKU]
While you were sittin' around
twiddling your thumbs in Hell,
I was busy sparring
with the toughest fighters
from other universes.
So you're not the only one
who's been getting stronger.
[FRIEZA grumbles]
[GOKU] And the next time
you try to kill someone
who's no real threat,
I'm gonna make you regret it!
[NARRATOR]
With his immense power,
Goku fought Frieza to a draw,
and the Seventh Universe
had its final member.
Meanwhile, in the Null Realm,
the arena for the Tournament
of Power was at last complete.
Teams from the across the
multiverse are arriving.
The battle to determine the fate
of the cosmos will begin... now!
[NARRATOR]
"The Time Has Come!
To the Null Realm with the
Universes on the Line!"
So this is where their
fates will be decided.
[sighs] Well,
it's not nearly as grand and
fancy as I'd been expecting.
The clash of mighty
warriors should be
the center of attention, not
the arena in which they fight.
With the existence of countless
trillions on the line,
I expect a battle the likes of
which we can barely imagine.
I wonder if this ring can bear
the pounding it's about to take.
You'll find the arena
more than up to it.
[ALL gasp]
Our humblest greetings,
Grand Minister!
Will we also have
the highest honor
of greeting the Omni-Kings?
Their Majesties wish to
stay in the waiting room.
They will relax there
until everyone arrives.
I look forward to this
tournament very much!
Yeah, me too!
That's quite understandable.
[GRAND MINISTER]
Now, Arak. Let's return
to your question about the
ring's quality of workmanship.
[ARAK]
What?! No, I'm good.
I'm sure he didn't mean
to disparage your work.
Its made of kachi katchintite,
the hardest substance
in the Cosmos,
and even stronger than
regular katchintite.
An element that you may
already know from the Seventh.
That's why the ring
will just do fine.
Yes, that makes sense to me.
[GRAND MINISTER] If you're
still doubting, though,
you may test it.
[ALL gasp]
In fact, such an exhibition
may be just what
the Omni-Kings need, as I'm
sure they're quite bored
waiting for the
tournament to start.
Uh, let's not belabor this.
[IWAN] I think a pre-tournament
fight is a great idea.
I beg your pardon?
[LIQUEER] In fact,
it's an outstanding idea.
I'm not so sure about this!
I'm always happy to show the
Omni-Kings how right they were
to exempt us from
the Tournament,
as our group is far superior
to those universes
forced to fight for
their survival.
Grand Minister, we in the
Fifth Universe don't want--
[GRAND MINISTER] I don't mind
at all! Indulge yourselves.
I'm ready whenever
you are, Arak.
[ARAK growls]
[OGMA]
Uh.
[sighs]
[LIQUEER] We'll use the same
rules as the actual tournament.
Lord Giin, it's unlike you
to skip a fight.
I already know how
it's going to end.
If you're all set,
we'll begin the show!
[ARAK, LIQUEER, IWAN]
I'm ready!
And... fight!
[ARAK, IWAN grunt]
[ARAK, IWAN grunting]
[LIQUEER grunts]
[ARAK grunting]
[IWAN grunts]
[LIQUEER yells]
[ARAK yells]
My goodness.
They've gotten rather
out-of-hand!
All right. Enough fighting
for now, gentlemen.
[ARAK, IWAN, LIQUEER]
Right!
Yes. That exchange
really hit the spot.
[GRAND MINISTER]
More like hit the arena.
Thanks to you three, I see where
we can make some improvements.
What did the Omni-Kings
think of that?
I can't imagine they'd be bored
after watching us fight!
Yes. Let's check in.
Oh, I'm sorry, but it seems
they've fallen asleep.
[ALL gasp]
[GRAND MINISTER]
So it goes.
Anyway, you should get
to work repairing the arena
before the tournament
teams arrive.
I want everything you broke
heavily reinforced.
What?!
[ARAK gasping]
You want us to rebuild that?!
Oh, yes. I'd do it myself,
but I'll be busy helping
to transport the teams.
Hop to it!
[ALL sputtering]
[ALL sigh]
[GIIN]
Hmph.
[FRIEZA]
Well, well, well.
How pleasant to see familiar
faces here to say hello.
[ALL growl]
[BEERUS] I hope you know
I won't be sitting back
and letting you pull
any nefarious stunts.
[FRIEZA] Worry not,
Lord Beerus. I'll behave.
[VEGETA] Hmph. I like the way
that halo looks on you, Frieza.
[FRIEZA stammers]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA]
Thank you, but we both know
it would look even more
fetching on a prince.
Shall I give you one?
[VEGETA]
Go ahead.
Don't even think
about fighting him!
Did you not just hear
me say, "no stunts"?
Hey, Frieza! You can't pick
fights with your new teammates!
Let me make it perfectly clear:
I don't take orders
from a primate!
Goku, are you sure you want
this villain on our team?
Don't worry. I'll keep
him in line, Tien.
Besides, there's no one
else to take Buu's place.
We don't have any other choice!
Poor Yamcha. It's too bad
Goku never asked you
to be their team's
tenth warrior, huh?
Heh! It's probably for the best.
I would have just defeated
everyone too quickly.
[laughs]
[OOLONG sighs]
All right everyone.
Now that we're all
finally in one spot,
let's discuss our strategy
for winning the tournament.
[VEGETA]
There's nothing more to discuss!
[gasps]
We down the strongest
fighters as soon as we can.
That's our strategy.
It's not that simple.
[FRIEZA laughs]
[VEGETA grunts]
Leave it to my former minion to
cut to the heart of the matter.
We're both of the
same opinion on this.
[VEGETA growls]
Vegeta, don't you
realize the stakes?
If we lose, Trunks and Bulla
will be eliminated,
right alongside us and
the rest of the universe!
[VEGETA grunts]
We all have complicated
relationships with each other,
but if we're gonna win
we're gonna have to do it
with good old-fashioned
team work!
[GOKU]
Gohan's right.
We're going against 70 warriors
and they're all bound
to be super strong!
Fine. Since you're all acting
so desperate, I'll listen.
[SUPREME KAI sighs]
As you know,
the Tournament of Power's
a battle royale
between teams from eight
distinct universes.
It's important you
conserve your strength.
So form up in a
group, right away.
When enemies approach,
fight as a team.
Avoid all duels.
If one enemy wants to fight,
two of you should engage.
And if it's two enemies, then
three of you should counter.
Uh!
Uh, avoiding one-on-one
fights is kinda cowardly.
[gasps]
Yeah, you forget that we Saiyans
are a proud, warrior race.
We don't rely on numbers
to win our fights.
[BEERUS growls]
I don't care if it's an
honorable fight or not,
all that matters is that we win!
[PICCOLO grunts]
Your father and Vegeta can't
ignore their Saiyan blood.
In other words, they may
fight based on instinct
rather than logic.
Yeah, I'm assuming
that'll be the case.
But remember,
we're stonger together.
We'll set a good example.
[WHIS] All right,
Team Seventh Universe!
It's time to go to
the Null Realm!
To make a long story short,
you're not allowed
to fight alone!
You jerks got that?
[WHIS] Okay. I'd like everyone
to join hands and form a circle.
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA] Wait, now we're
forming some kind
of friend circle with that punk?
All right! Let's get this
show on the road!
[VEGETA]
Whoa, hold on!
[stammers]
Are you planning on
joining us, Vegeta?
We can't leap away until
we all form a circle.
You're actually making
me hold Frieza's hand?!
[FRIEZA laughs]
You don't have to be scared,
Vegeta! I won't bite!
Scared?!
Did you not just hear
a single word
we said about the importance
of teamwork?!
How's that?
Are you happy now?
[VEGETA grunts]
Yeah, yeah, fine.
Greetings, Grand Minister!
The warriors of the
Seventh Universe
have assembled and are
ready for transit!
[GRAND MINISTER]
Stand by, please.
Good luck, you guys!
We're counting on you!
The fate of the world--
No, the fate of our
entire universe
rests on those ten souls.
You can win this, I know it.
[laughs]
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN]
Wow. So this is the Null Realm?
What's with the flying blocks?
Seems the arena's undergoing
some last-minute construction.
And up there is the crew.
[BEERUS]
Why are Destroyers building it?
Whoa! The teams from the other
universes are coming in!
[BEERUS]
Hm? Hey, wait.
How'd they manage to teleport
without holding hands?
Oh, the hand-holding was just
my way to build team solidarity.
Are you nuts?!
That touchy-feely nonsense
almost tore the team apart!
[A18]
Whoa. You guys need to see this!
[gasps]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[GOKU]
I don't see anything.
[WHIS] Lady and gentlemen,
don't forget--
once the Tournament starts,
anyone who falls
from this ring, loses.
[GOHAN]
That's... a pretty big drop.
Okay, what's to stop us
from flying back up?
[WHIS] The fact that
you won't be able to.
[GOHAN]
Huh?
[GOKU] Is that so?
Let's see if you're right!
[GOKU groaning]
Yeah, I can't fly.
[WHIS] The Grand Zenos
have taken measures
to disable flying techniques
such as yours.
Since pushing your opponents
out of the ring is key
to the competition that...
only makes sense.
How come those guys're flying?
[GROUP]
Uh?
Their flight is an inherent
physical ability
and not an acquired power
using energy manipulation.
And in a similar
matter of fairness,
I should note that
the gravity here
is set to affect each
fighter's body
in the same way it does on
the world of their birth.
[GOKU]
Aw...
Well, then, we must
be going now.
Lord Beerus and I will be
in the spectator seating.
Wait, why do you get to fly?!
It's only the contestants
who are banned
from using that power, my lord.
The moment of truth is here.
Good luck to you all.
Yeah. Just leave it to us!
[FROST]
Well, what have we here?
Huh...?
Hey, it's that Sixth
Universe Frieza!
[FROST]
Hm...
[FRIEZA]
Hmph.
[FROST chuckles]
Now where is he.
Yo, Hit! How's it goin'?
Great. It's him.
[CABBA] Vegeta! It's really
good to see you again!
How are you, Master?
Don't call me that!
Glad ya made it, Cabba! Feeling
good about the Tournament?
[CABBA]
You bet!
Well, introduce the
rest of your team!
Oh, right. This is Caulifla,
she's a fellow Saiyan.
Oh, wow! A female Saiyan?
Nice to meet ya! My name's Go--!
U-Uh...
Caulifla, that's rude!
Oh, please, Cabba.
This is about finding the
strongest fighter in the Cosmos.
I'm not here to
make new friends.
The strongest in
the Cosmos, huh?
That's the same reason I wanted
this tournament, too!
[CAULIFLA grunts]
Um, Caulifla.
[GOKU] Uh? Hey Cabba,
is this one a Saiyan, too?
That's right. Her name's Kale.
Um, hello there.
Master Roshi, you gonna
be okay with this?
You know, going against women?
There's nothin' to
worry about, Krillin.
With some last minute training,
I've banished that
worldly desire!
[KRILLIN]
Yeah!
Not a punch has been thrown
and I'm already sick of
the Seventh Universe.
Leave them be, Sidra.
I can't stand them!
[ROH]
From here on out,
we'll let our own warriors
handle those fiends.
It's like gazing in a mirror.
I'd describe our physical
appearance as almost identical.
But I wonder if our
personalities share
the same belief that
might makes right?
Indeed. I concur.
Then we should get
along quite well.
[FROST chuckles]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
How charming.
Then what would you say
to us teaming up, on the sly?
Oh, yes. By all means.
[MARCARITA]
Greetings, Grand Minister!
The warriors of the Eleventh
Universe are ready for transit!
Splendid.
[GOKU gasps]
Whoa.
That energy...
[CAULIFLA, KALE gasp]
Well, would you look at that.
Ha! You Seventh Universe
Saiyans sure act like
you're all high-and-mighty,
but those guys look like
the real deal to me.
Why you...
All right, calm down.
[GOKU]
Uh?!
I'll be back.
I'm gonna go say hello.
Wait! Dad! Come back!
[TOP]
Hm?
Yo! What's up?
Goku of the Seventh.
I'm looking forward to finishing
what we started back
at the Expo, Top.
Let's be clear. My team
and I are only here
because the fate of the
Eleventh Universe depends on it.
If you believe I care
about some personal duel
you are mistaken!
Fine, but I doubt we'll be able
to avoid each other in the ring.
--[TOP] If it happens, so be it.
--[GOKU] Uhh...
[GOKU]
Heh, heh. And you must be--
Get lost.
[GOKU gasps]
How'd you do that?
[GOKU grunts]
[ARAK]
Looks like teams
from all the competing
universes are arriving.
Then let's pick up the pace
before we're out of time.
[LIQUEER grunts]
What now?!
[ALL grunting]
[gasps]
[GOKU grunts]
[gasping]
That's crazy, he didn't
even flinch at all!
[GOKU yelps]
Look out!
[GOKU] He knew exactly where
those blocks were gonna land.
That's one powerful
warrior, all right.
Okay, here's the final piece!
[GRAND MINISTER]
At last, the arena is finished!
Again... And the teams from all
competing universes are here.
The Second Universe.
Vegeta, that guy on the left
looks like he's from Yardrat!
Instant Transmission.
[GOHAN]
Be careful around that guy.
[GRAND MINISTER]
The Third Universe.
The Fourth Universe.
Maybe I'm wrong,
but I'm counting only eight
warriors on that team.
Hold on... One, two,
three, four, f--
Goku, stop. He's right.
Well, makes it easier for us.
Why would they do that?
Won't they be disqualified
with just eight?
No, wait. It's faint,
but I can sense two more.
[GRAND MINISTER]
The Sixth Universe.
The Seventh Universe.
[GRAND MINISTER]
The Ninth Universe.
The Tenth Universe.
[GRAND MINISTER] And last,
but certainly not least...
...the Eleventh!
Everyone is so strong!
I don't see a weak link
in any of those teams!
Same here.
You better not be
losing your nerve.
Soon as it starts, we'll close
up ranks to beef up our defense.
Then, when the enemy attacks,
we'll work together
and defeat them.
Everyone got that?
Yeah, Shut up!
Your proposal has been duly
noted, that's all I can say.
[GOHAN gasping]
You're wasting your breath
trying to get through
to those two.
[GRAND MINISTER] Ladies and
Gentlemen, quiet, please.
We will now hear some
words of welcome
from the Omni-Kings themselves.
[BOTH] Thank you all!
This will be so fun!
We've been looking forward
to this very much!
So fight well...
[BOTH]
...and give us a good show!
[GRAND MINISTER]
Poetry, thy name is Zeno!
Thank you, Your Majesties.
[NARRATOR] And so, 80 warriors
from across eight universes
have journeyed to
the Null Realm
and assembled on this
most unusual arena!
It will soon be the site of
a tournament like no other,
as teams fight to defend
their universes
and determine which
warrior is the strongest.
Can Goku and his team
from the Seventh
find a way to win against
these imposing odds
and avoid destruction?
Finally, the Tournament
of Power main event.
A fateful 48 minutes that will
drastically reshape the Cosmos
is set to begin.
Next time on Dragon Ball Super!
Boogie Back!
Wish we had better timing
To explore this attraction
Put on a smile, it's showtime
And I'm just playing a part
Let's get lost in the rhythm,
dancing dancing heart
Head over heels
I'm falling falling down
(Boogie Back!)
My heartbeat
keeps growing faster
Every step that I take
brings me back to you
(Boogie Back!)
Give me happy ever after
Let the dream
of our love come true
Boogie Back!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
All right!
The Tournament has started!
Everyone's powered up and
pounding away and it is awesome!
Hey, what do you want?
You think you can
take me out like that?
Well, think again!
There're so many
other guys I wanna fight,
I'm just gettin' started!
Watch out, everyone!
I'm comin' in hot!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Survive! The Tournament
of Power Begins at Last!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?