♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
Okay. Don't be mad,
but I promised Frieza
that if our universe survives
the Tournament of Power,
I'll gather up the Dragon Balls
and wish him back permanently.
What?!
You moron! Are you nuts?!
Yeah! You know he's
just gonna go
right back to his
old, evil ways!
[BULMA]
How are you so stupid?!
[GOKU]
You don't have to get so angry.
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super.
As the Tournament of Power
was rapidly approaching,
Goku recruited Frieza to be
the tenth member of his team.
[QUITELA]
I understand.
Which is why I'd like to help
you eliminate them first.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
spurred on by Quitela,
Sidra, the Ninth
Universe's Destroyer,
sent assassins to attack
Goku and Frieza.
[GOKU]
Who ordered you to come here?
We can't say--
[FRIEZA]
Whoopsie!
Sorry about that.
Hand slipped again.
Crossing worlds
must make me clumsy.
[NARRATOR]
To no one's surprise,
the former emperor
has already proven
to be an untrustworthy ally.
Will Goku and Frieza
be able to make it back
in time for the tournament?
They must battle to
escape this horde now!
[FRIEZA] Don't hold this breach
of etiquette against me.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
"Most Heinous! Most Evil!
Frieza's Wild Rampage!"
[BOTH whimper]
[laughing]
[ASSASSINS growl]
[ASSASSIN BOSS growls]
[laughs]
Remember, you hooded peons
are the ones who ambushed us.
So spare me any feigned outrage
over my blindsiding you.
[ASSASSIN 95A laughs]
Well, don't think you're tough
just 'cause you pulled
off a sucker-punch.
[ASSASSINS laughing]
Where are you guys from? Did
some other universe send you?
[ASSASSIN 95A]
Could be.
Though we have no
obligation to tell you.
But I will say we aren't from
a weak, little nothin'
of a universe
like your precious Seventh.
[ASSASSIN 95B] Yeah! We're from
a "tough-as-nails" universe,
where we don't bat an eye at
low blows and fighting dirty!
Oh?
Well that sounds like a truly
marvelous place to me.
[ASSASSIN 95A]
Doesn't suck.
Now why don't you ditch that
namby-pamby Tournament of Power
and have some fun
with us instead?
[ASSASSIN 95B]
We can have all kinds of fun.
No rules, no refs.
Well, it looks like we've got
no choice but to fight them.
Hey, Frieza, wait a sec!
Yes, monkey?
Are you sure you
should be transforming
into that golden form now?
As soon as we leave here,
we've gotta be ready to
fight in the tournament.
Aw. How thoughtful.
You're worried it'll drain
my energy too fast
like our last tussle, yes?
[FRIEZA]
Put your tiny mind at ease.
Since that sad debacle
I've spent what seemed like
an eternity trapped in Hell.
[FRIEZA] The only way
I was able to endure it
was through acute mental
focus, training myself
to keep my composure through the
torturous, saccharine barrage.
As a result of exercising
these muscles so intensely
and for so very long,
my energy modulation skills
have made great strides.
On the one hand,
even-keeled composure.
On the other,
the ultimate in strength.
It is the true manifestation
of Golden Frieza!
This is who I truly am
in my purest form.
[GOKU gasping]
[GOKU growls]
[FRIEZA laughing]
[ASSASSINS gasp]
[ASSASSINS scream]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[ASSASSIN 95E gasping]
[ASSASSIN 95F whimpers]
[ASSASSIN 95G screaming]
[ASSASSIN 95H gasping]
[ASSASSINS groaning]
[laughing]
That's but a taste!
So tell me, how do you like
this newly polished Gold?!
Frieza, no!
[ASSASSINS groaning]
Surprise surprise,
the monkey cries.
Hey, that's enough.
There's no need for you
to pile up more bodies!
Whether these unimpressive
cretins are killed by me here,
or we eviscerate
their universe's team
at the Tournament and they're
obliterated along with
the rest of their peers,
is the end not the same?
[GOKU grunts]
Why not make it fun?
[ASSASSIN 95A whimpers] You sure
talk a big game, dontcha?
Get him!
[ASSASSINS yell]
[ASSASSIN 95T]
Ow, my face!
[ASSASSINS whimper]
[ASSASSINS yelp]
Hey!
[ASSASSINS hooting]
[ASSASSIN 95A]
Go for the old hag!
If we take her hostage,
they can't lay a finger on us!
[ASSASSINS laugh]
--[GHOST USHER whimpers]
--[BABA screams]
[GOKU grunting]
Quick, Baba, get inside!
It's too dangerous for you here!
[BABA]
Ahh! Coming through!
[ASSASSINS groan]
[ASSASSIN 95CC groaning]
[ASSASSINS gasp]
[GOKU]
You done, Frieza?
Oh, why did you have to
interrupt my flow?
I was just starting to warm up
so I could show you
my true power.
[GOKU]
Come on, haven't you had enough?
[ASSASSIN BOSS growls]
[ROH] Now, you aren't being
ordered by anyone to do this.
No, on the contrary, you're
going to ambush Goku and Frieza
wholly of your own accord.
You understand
my meaning, right?
There's no confusion?
[ASSASSIN BOSS laughs]
Oh, I hear you loud and clear.
Ah, very good. Now take this.
I'm sharing with you some
Energy of Destruction.
[SIDRA] Nobody who's been hit
with this energy can escape
its devastating toll,
no matter who they are.
They won't even pass
to Other World.
Their very essence
will be eliminated.
[whimpering]
[ASSASSIN BOSS laughs]
[FRIEZA] Do be sure to aim
carefully, little lapdog.
Despite being so
woefully outmatched,
there was a reason why
your poor comrades' eyes
were not completely glazed
over with despair.
It was because of the energy
you hold in your paw, yes?
[ASSASSIN BOSS growls]
By all means, please
proceed at your leisure.
[growls]
Well, here goes!
[grunts]
[laughing]
I've still got the real one...
...right here!
[FRIEZA] Heh! That was
a halfway decent plan.
For a simpleton
like you, that is.
Ha!
[gasps]
[grunting]
[screaming]
What's going on?
[ASSASSIN BOSS]
Now, perish into nothingness!
[screaming]
And that... is acting.
Wha...?
And now it's my turn to
unveil a grand surprise...
The true extent of my strength.
[gasps]
Wha...?!
[FRIEZA grunting]
[yelling]
[yelling continues]
[FRIEZA panting]
What? No, impossible!
That's Lord Sidra's Energy
of Destruction! You can't--
[panting]
Whoa. Awesome.
[GOKU] Man, I'm surprised you
made it outta that thing.
Impressive.
[FRIEZA] Oh, that was merely
a warmup exercise.
For someone who's been
bound up in a cocoon,
your power level sure has risen.
[FRIEZA]
Hm...
So what is that thing anyway?
Yes, that's a very
good question.
I'm sensing some major
power coming off of it.
Indeed, and for energy
to be as pure
as this particular
little bundle here,
I believe it's most likely
of divine origin.
But that would mean...
This anemic battalion's
pathetic attempt at an ambush
must've been orchestrated
from on high
by either the Supreme Kai
or Destroyer of one of
the other universes.
Then I guess their mission
was to assassinate
the both of us, huh, Frieza?
I've got no clue which
universe did this,
but whoever it was must
be awfully desperate.
[GOKU]
Listen up, guys!
We here in the Seventh
Universe don't run or hide,
and we don't back
down from a fight!
So go tell the gods back in your
universe that we'll settle this,
fair and square, in the
Tournament of Power!
[ASSASSINS]
Uhh...
[GOKU]
Hm? That's an odd reaction.
Okay, Friez--
[screaming]
Carelessness is still
your greatest foe.
[GRAND MINISTER] I appreciate
your patience, Grand Zenos.
The ring for the Tournament
of Power is at last complete.
[ZENOS]
Oooh!
What do you think
of it, my lords?
It's very fancy.
[FUTURE ZENO laughing]
[ZENOS]
I like it, I like it!
I do aim to please.
[ZENO]
Here, this is for you.
You spoil me.
I can't wait for it to begin.
Yes, I can't wait, either.
[GOKU screaming]
[GOKU]
Argh, Frieza.
What is wrong with you?!
[laughs]
You do realize I have a
strong desire to kill you.
I always have and always will.
For you to so incautiously turn
your back on me like that
proves what you really are.
A poor fool who
will never learn.
Though, for the moment,
perhaps you ought to concentrate
on escaping from
that crushing energy
and as swiftly as your crude
little body will allow.
Remember, I had no
trouble doing so.
[GOKU grunting]
[yelling]
Oh?
[GOKU grunting]
[yells]
[laughing]
How pathetic.
This is too much for you.
[GOKU grunting]
[chuckles]
Either I've become even
stronger than I thought
or you've become
much weaker.
Now then...
[ASSASSINS gasping]
[ASSASSIN 95DD whimpers]
[ASSASSIN 95DD yelps]
I'd like a word with the
gods of your universe,
and I would appreciate it
if you would facilitate
that meeting for me.
[ASSASSIN 95DD] And what
exactly do you plan to say to--
[ASSASSIN 95DD groaning]
[ASSASSIN 95DD]
Uh... All right. I'll do it.
You can say whatever you want!
[ASSASSIN 95DD groans]
No, on second thought,
why don't you hold off
on making contact
for a bit. After all,
it's been a very long time
since I've had this much fun.
And I think I'm going to savor
it just a little while longer.
[ASSASSINS gasping]
[ASSASSINS yell]
[ASSASSINS groaning]
[BABA screams]
[SIDRA] Damn it,
what's taking them so long?
We have to leave for the
tournament any moment now!
Yeah, I know, I know!
Ooh, finally, they must be done!
[BOTH gasp]
Greetings, deities of
the Ninth Universe.
I am Lord Frieza.
You insolent... How do you
know who we are?
A reasonable query.
I got that from one
of your minions,
just like this nifty
communicator.
He says you're the ones who
commissioned this attack on me.
I suppose I should be flattered.
That's a fanciful story,
but what proof do you have?
Oh, I think your
"Energy of Destruction"
will be evidence
enough, don't you?
[ROH growls]
That was given to them for
an entirely unrelated matter.
If they abused it,
that's not my fault!
Do you honestly believe
Grand Zeno will take the word
of an unscrupulous
miscreant like you?
Yeah, trying to turn
us in won't work!
Hm... It would seem
your impression of me
is grossly ill-informed.
In what way?
I harbor no intention
of tattling to Zeno
about what you've done.
I merely wish to propose a deal.
It's nothing too difficult,
I assure you.
All I want is for
you to appoint me
as one of the warriors
for Universe Nine.
Wha...?!
[FRIEZA]
You see, I've ensnared Goku
in your Energy of Destruction.
And as much as it pains me
to give the simple simian
any bit of credit,
the Seventh Universe
will never win the Tournament of
Power without his assistance.
This universe will
be eradicated.
And I find that outcome
less than ideal.
[RO, SIDRA grunt]
Surely by now you appreciate
the magnitude of my strength
and the talents I have to offer.
If you'd be so kind as
to put me on your team
and fully restore my life,
I will vow to give you
everything I have
in pursuit of achieving victory
for you in the Tournament.
So, what do you say?
It's not an egregious
proposal, is it?
Yeah, but, be honest.
Are you sure about this?
And why wouldn't I be sure?
Because if you do this, your own
universe will be annihilated!
I'm aware.
I don't care how callous
and evil you are,
there still has to be something
there that you wish to preserve.
Loved ones, memories.
Every creature has to
care about something!
You confound me.
I have no desire at all
to preserve anything.
Ha! Other than myself,
of course.
[BOTH gasping]
Hang on, are we even allowed
to recruit someone
from another universe
to be one of our fighters?
Well, I don't see anything
in the rulebook
specifically prohibiting it.
All right, then let's
just do it already!
Wait, no! Our universe may
have a well-earned reputation
for depravity, but that lunatic
is too much, even for us!
He's a psychopath who thinks
nothing of his universe
being annihilated!
You heard him!
Sidra, he's even more of
a Destroyer than you!
Then we'll be the strongest
team there, right?!
[ROH] A double-crosser will
always double-cross again!
[SIDRA]
Duh, I know that!
But when he does,
I'll just destroy him!
That's kind of my
thing, you know!
[ROH] Oh, please. There's no
way it'll go that smoothly!
Oh, drat, out of time.
Well, so much for that idea.
[BOTH gasp]
[GOKU groaning]
Oh for goodness' sake...
How did this happen?
[inhales]
[panting]
Ah. Thanks, you saved me.
I was starting to
wonder what nonsense
you'd gotten yourself into,
so I came to check.
As for you, that was
Energy of Destruction.
You'd better have
a good explanation.
Who me? I was attacked
with it, as well.
Though I didn't struggle
with it nearly as clumsily.
Don't try to play me.
You were just in contact with
one of the other universes,
weren't you? If you're
plotting something...
Hold on, we need Frieza!
It was my fault for
letting my guard down!
It's hard to know, my lord.
Perhaps he called up their
assailants to acquire some
information that could
assist us in some way.
[FRIEZA]
Yes. Perhaps so.
What's wrong with you, Goku?
Doesn't this infuriate
you even a little?
Well of course it does!
It's just, I feel I'm
at least partly to blame
for forgetting Frieza's
such a terrible, sneaky,
rotten, no-good, evil bastard.
I'd say that's putting
it mildly at this point.
[FRIEZA]
This fiasco confirms it.
This upcoming tournament,
with the fate of
the universe at stake
is the perfect opportunity
for me to manipulate
even the all-powerful gods.
In the end, I'll be
the one who laughs last.
You don't get to have everything
go your way forever...
...Beerus.
I know!
Hey, listen, Whis.
What is it?
Can you give me and Frieza
just one minute for something?
Huh?!
[WHIS] When I give the signal,
the skirmish may begin.
However, as soon as either
of you lands the first blow
the match will immediately
come to an end--
with no hard feelings.
Are these terms
agreeable to you both?
Hurry up and get it
over with already!
All right, Frieza, if I win
this, you've gotta forget about
whatever beef there
is between us
and promise to stay
loyal to our universe
throughout the Tournament
of Power, okay?
That's cute, but when I win,
you will agree to leave me
alone to do as I please.
[FRIEZA]
The mental control I honed
whilst imprisoned
took great effort.
And you didn't ask how I did it.
It wasn't as simple as
casting out bad thoughts
and clearing the mind.
I focused on nothing
but an endless series
of combat simulations in which I
killed you over and over again.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
I can visualize it all!
Your every move!
My inevitable victory!
I see the whole fight play out
with perfect clarity
and precision!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[whistle blows]
Will we ever really be able to
trust him, even if Goku wins?
I would say that's highly
doubtful, my lord.
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA yelling]
[GOKU yelling]
[FRIEZA yells]
[WHIS]
Ooh!
[GOKU groaning]
[FRIEZA groans]
[BOTH groan]
[GOKU]
While you were sittin' around,
twiddling your thumbs in Hell,
I was busy sparring with
the toughest fighters
from other universes.
So you're not the only one
who's been getting stronger.
[FRIEZA grunting]
[GOKU] And the next time
you try to kill someone
who's no real threat,
I'm gonna make you regret it!
[FRIEZA] I refuse to take orders
from a primate like you.
This isn't over between us.
Not by a long shot.
[GOKU]
Oh yeah. I know.
The two of them appear
to be evenly matched now.
Yes, I must say that Lord Frieza
is rather impressive, isn't he?
[NARRATOR]
With the treacherous Frieza
filling the missing position,
the Seventh Universe team
is now complete,
and not a moment too soon.
As the eight competing
universes finalize
their strategies
and preparations,
the Tournament of Power,
which will determine
each of their fates,
is set to begin at last.
Do Goku and the rest of
the Seventh Universe fighters
have what it takes to evade
the threat of annihilation?
Find out next time on
Dragon Ball Super.
Boogie Back!
Wish we had better timing
To explore this attraction
Put on a smile, it's showtime
And I'm just playing a part
Let's get lost in the rhythm,
dancing dancing heart
Head over heels
I'm falling falling down
(Boogie Back!)
My heartbeat
keeps growing faster
Every step that I take
brings me back to you
(Boogie Back!)
Give me happy ever after
Let the dream
of our love come true
Boogie Back!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Finally, after all that buildup,
the tournament's about to start!
What incredible energy!
Is that Top's friend Jiren?
Huh, everybody here seems
to have brought their A-game,
so I'm gonna have to bust out
my full power to show 'em
what's up! Took a
while to get here,
but now it's the Seventh
Universe's time to shine!
Next time, on Dragon Ball Super:
"The Time Has Come!
To the Null Realm with the
Universes on the Line!"
Make sure you
don't miss it, okay?