♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
over half the contestants
had been eliminated,
and two universes were erased.
As fighting raged on,
Frost was biding his time,
waiting for the right moment to
exact revenge against Vegeta.
[ROSHI] I don't care about my
old shell of a life any more.
At least I'll make it count!
Here goes my last shot!
Evil Containment!
[FROST]
Just what I was waiting for!
[yelling]
[VEGETA]
No you don't!
Ha! Heads up, dear Saiyan!
Here it comes!
[VEGETA]
What?!
[screams]
[NARRATOR] By reversing
the Evil Containment Wave,
Frost managed to seal up Vegeta.
But Master Roshi was determined
to undo that mistake.
[FROST laughs]
[ROSHI grunts]
[FROST yelps]
[VEGETA]
Damn you!
[NARRATOR]
And with that,
Frost's attempt at revenge
went up in smoke.
Elsewhere in the ring,
Goku is all set to
battle Ribrianne... now!
[NARRATOR] "Frieza and Frost!
A Mutual Malevolence?"
[GOKU yells]
[BRIANNE yelling]
[GOKU, BRIANNE grunting]
Wow, you've sure got some fight
in ya, huh, Universe Two?
Not fight. This is 100% love!
That's how I will defeat you,
Universe Seven.
With pure heart!
[GOKU growls]
[BOTH grunting]
[HELES]
Is there anything more beautiful
than a shining maiden's passion?
It truly is magnificent how
she lights up our world.
Let's go!
C'mon Ribrianne, win
this one for Lord Heles!
Show her your love!
[BRIANNE] Of course!
I promise with all of my heart,
I will not let you down,
Lord Heles!
With beauty and grace,
I send you my love!
Pretty Cannon!
[GOKU yelps]
Pretty Love Machinegun!
Ai love!
[GOKU yelps]
[BRIANNE]
Amore !
[GOKU]
Whoa!
Man, Goku's getting
thrown off his game
by that lady's weird
lovey-dovey attacks.
Huh, that kinda tickles.
Amore mia !
That warrior's love attacks
are rather intense.
I've never seen
anything quite like it.
Yes. Based on the numbers
remaining, I figured
either the Sixth or Seventh
Universe would be the victor.
Heh. But her passion is
indeed a powerful force.
Against all odds,
the Second Universe may
actually last until the end.
Come now, don't tell me
you're developing a soft spot
for that Ribrianne woman.
Maybe I am.
Meanwhile, the Eleventh Universe
may only have three
fighters left in the ring,
but each of them is
an absolute powerhouse.
[TOP]
Justice Punch!
[CABBA screams]
[TOP]
That is Justice!
At this point,
it's all so unpredictable.
There's no telling which team
is going to win the tournament.
The simple fact remains,
this is a fight among
the universes with
lower-level mortals.
It doesn't matter which
of them comes out on top.
Nothing is going
to change for us.
[OGMA]
Lord Arak! How can you sit there
watching this without
having a nervous breakdown?!
Just imagining what it would be
like if the Fifth Universe was
thrown into the middle of that
is giving me heart palpitations!
This is all far too much
for my delicate constitution!
Everyone else here
seems to be thoroughly
enjoying themselves.
I think it's high time
I found my next playmate
and had some fun of my own.
[BORARETA]
Beam bora!
[GOHAN grunts]
[BORARETA]
Beam bora!
[GOHAN]
Ha!
[GOHAN grunts]
[BORARETA]
Execute punch bora!
[GOHAN grunting]
[BORARETA]
You are doomed, bora!
Bora?
[BORARETA]
Enemy not found, bora.
[GOHAN] All the fighters who
are still left are top-notch.
This is hardly gonna
be easy to pull off.
[sighs, gasps]
I need to find Piccolo
and the others to regroup.
[JIMIZU yells]
[GOHAN gasps]
[JIMIZU]
Not bad, Universe Seven.
I am Jimizu, defender
of the Second Universe!
[JIMIZU] In the name
of protecting my home,
the beautiful Lord Heles,
and the maidens,
it is my duty to defeat you!
[JIMIZU grunts]
[GOHAN] Yardratians like him are
masters of Instant Transmission.
I can't let my guard down
for even a second.
[gasps]
[JIMIZU yells]
[GOHAN groans]
--[JIMIZU grunts]
--[GOHAN groans]
[GOHAN groans]
That little guy's
transporting himself
into Gohan's blind spots!
Imagine being able to perform
Instant Transmission
with such skill!
This Jimizu fella's one
to watch, if you can.
Hey, Goku Junior!
Is that really
the best you've got?!
[GOHAN grunts]
Man, he's so hard to track.
And I thought Dad was
good at that move. Huh?
On your feet, boy!
If I could only find
a way to stop him
from hopping around like that...
Come on!
The poor kid's in trouble.
He's all turned around
and discombobulated now.
He's just too much.
You clearly possess great
potential as a warrior,
but you are up against
the wrong opponent.
If the conditions
were different,
I would teach you
this technique.
Farewell now.
[FRIEZA laughs]
[GOHAN gasps]
[FRIEZA laughs] You seem
to be having difficulties.
[GOHAN growls]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
A friend of yours?
Good, perfect timing!
Save Junior's rear and
show him how it's done!
[FRIEZA laughs] How are you
struggling against this runt?
It would seem you failed
to inherit any of your
Daddy's skills. Is he
as disappointed as I am?
What'd you say?
[FRIEZA]
Well, so much for the great
and powerful Saiyan
warrior race.
But perhaps this
is the opportunity
I've been waiting for.
Oh, knock off the pontificating
and get to it already!
Hey, Frieza?!
Why isn't he attacking
the other fighter?
I don't like this.
You don't think Frieza's
planning to turn on Gohan
to get him out of the
competition, do you?
Why would he take out
his own teammate?
Frieza knows it's
a numbers game, right?
If the Seventh Universe loses,
he'll be erased along with us!
Yeah, well.
You don't know Frieza.
He really is a rotten bastard.
[BEERUS]
Hm?
There's no doubt in my mind
that creep's working some angle,
plotting to use this opportunity
for some nefarious purpose.
What do you mean,
"nefarious" purpose?
I thought his reason for being
here was to obtain resurrection.
Yes, but even so...
He could have an
ulterior motive. Mm...
If he makes it to the end of the
tournament and proves himself
the strongest fighter, he'll be
awarded the Super Dragon Balls.
And then, he could
make a wish far greater
than anything that Earth's
orbs could possibly fulfill.
Such as erasing a deity,
for example.
[ALL gasp]
If that's true, he must
see Gohan as an obstacle
to winning this thing
and getting his wish.
[KRILLIN growls]
I really hate that guy!
So long as the possibility
remains for Frieza
to be granted a wish,
given that we don't know
what that wish might entail,
you won't be able to feel safe,
my lord, even if
the Seventh does prevail.
[BEERUS growls]
Hey! Frieza! If you lay
a finger on that kid,
I will strike you down
where you stand!
[JIMIZU laughs]
[JIMIZU] I can see that your
soul is a truly ugly one.
For the love and peace
of the Second Universe,
I shall defeat you
both together!
[laughs]
Amusing as it would be to
see you make the attempt...
[FRIEZA] ...I prefer to do
my fighting one on one.
I'll just sit back and observe
until you're done with him.
So please, put on
a good show for me.
Abandoning your own
ally in battle?
My goodness, what an
unbecoming universe.
[GOHAN yelps]
[yells]
[JIMIZU grunts]
Gohan!
[GOHAN gasps]
[JIMIZU]
It's over.
It has been my honor
to defeat you.
[JIMIZU chuckles]
[GOHAN]
Uh?
[FRIEZA laughs]
Pardon me. My hand
must've slipped just now.
What's your problem?
Wait, I thought you had said
you weren't going to interfere.
[FRIEZA] Yes, but then I got
bored and had a change of heart.
[FRIEZA laughs]
[JIMIZU] Ugh. Fine! I will
dispense with you first!
[JIMIZU yelps]
[groaning]
But how did you...?
Since I know about
your proclivity for,
and overreliance on
Instant Transmission,
there's really nothing to it.
--[JIMIZU gasps]
--[FRIEZA chuckles]
As I previously stated,
there's nothing to it!
[JIMIZU screams]
[JIMIZU groaning]
[JIMIZU gasping]
[FRIEZA laughing]
[groans]
[laughing]
Thank you for the entertainment.
No, Frieza, don't!
[JIMIZU screaming]
[BOTH gasp]
[PELL] He killed him!
He's disqualified!
What? Kill him?
Do you honestly believe I could
make such a foolish mistake?
[JIMIZU groans]
I avoided anything
that's immediately vital.
Though of course...
I cannot be held accountable
for what happens once
he's out of the... ring!
[JIMIZU screams]
Jimizu of the Second Universe
has been eliminated, sires.
[JIMIZU]
Uhh... Supreme Kai.
I... am so sorry.
I know, Jimizu, I know.
Don't say another word.
[HELES] Such ugliness.
I would have never believed
that anyone in the cosmos
could fight so dirty!
[HELES growls]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[GOHAN]
Hey, Frieza!
[FRIEZA] Hm? Oh, dear.
Why the sour look on your face?
This is what happens
when you hold back--
declining to use
your full strength.
Hmph. You could've
turned Super Saiyan
and actually put up
something of a fight,
but no, no, no.
You waste your time
sizing up opponents.
It is one of the many
annoying flaws
of your despicable simian race.
I cannot understand
your miniscule minds.
[FROST]
Bravo! Well done!
[FRIEZA]
Hm?
[FROST] Magnificent, sir. It's
a privilege to watch you work.
[GOHAN gasps]
[FROST chuckles]
Well, look who's back!
Oh come on, what is
Frost up to now?
Perhaps, sir, he wants to
challenge Frieza himself.
Uh...? Hey, are you
outta your mind?!
Don't try to be a hero!
You can't take him!
You have nothing to
worry about, Lord Champa.
Our intended foe...
...is this half-Saiyan who
doesn't know when to quit.
Did he just say "our"?
As in, he and Frieza are working
together to take out Gohan?!
[ALL grunt]
Heh, I suppose the cat
is out of the bag now.
Heh, I was hoping to keep it
a secret a wee bit longer.
Frost and myself share
a common loathing
of the Saiyan race.
As such, we've agreed
to join forces.
How charming.
Then what would you say to
us teaming up, on the sly?
Oh, yes, by all means.
[FROST, FRIEZA laugh]
[ROSHI]
So that's what his angle was!
He didn't save Gohan
right away in that fight
with Jimizu because he wanted
Gohan to waste his energy,
making it easier for Frieza and
his new best friend to win!
[SUPREME KAI]
Then Frieza's goal really is
to be the last man standing.
So he can get a wish from
those Super Dragon Balls.
And then erase anyone
who stands in his way.
You mean me?!
Please, be my guest and
take the first crack at him.
And by all means,
use as much force as you
deem pleasurable.
You're kind, but after you.
[laughs]
Well, all right, if you insist.
[CHAMPA]
Well, how about that?
I don't really know
what's happening,
but if they're
fighting each other
that's good news for our team!
Forgive my caution,
but I must make certain that
you're truly committed
to this alliance of ours.
Because if you intend
to double-cross me...
I see your trust in me
is less than complete.
Take whatever measures you must.
[gasps]
Heh.
[FRIEZA laughing]
They're on the same team
but fighting. Wow!
Yes, what a twist!
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOHAN groans]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[BOTH]
Wow!
[GOHAN groans]
Way to go, Frieza!
Frieza, Frieza, he's our man!
If he can't do it, no one can!
You're the best, Frieza! Ha, ha!
You jerk, you're enjoying
this way too much!
[FRIEZA]
Ready to call it quits?
Uh?
Even if you are,
I'm not ready to let you!
[GOHAN groans]
[yelling]
Goku's son is pushing
back hard now.
Push, Goku's son, push!
[GOHAN yells]
[FRIEZA groans]
[FRIEZA] Ah, so now you decide
to show your true power?
[laughing] In that case,
I suppose I ought to start
getting serious, as well.
[FRIEZA yells]
Unbelievable.
He's gone Golden Frieza.
That bastard really is planning
on killing the boy, isn't he?
[GOHAN, FRIEZA grunting]
[groans]
[groaning]
[chuckles]
[ALL gasp]
Monster!
[CHAMPA]
He did it! He actually did it!
Attaboy, Frieza!
With him on our side, the
Sixth Universe is unstoppable!
We're guaranteed victory!
[FROST]
That was outstanding.
[FRIEZA]
Hm?
I didn't know you possessed
such incredible power.
[FRIEZA] With a little effort,
you too can reach this level.
[FROST]
You really think so?
[FRIEZA]
Well, maybe not Golden.
[FRIEZA grunting]
But you should at least
be able to do this.
[FROST]
Undoubtedly.
[FROST grunting]
[FRIEZA] Very good.
You know, there's a secret
to fighting more
efficiently in this form.
Would you like me to teach you?
[FROST]
Yes, please do!
In combat, it's best to
hit your stride early on,
maximizing your
full potential up front.
Because this
enhanced mode we're in
consumes energy rather
swiftly, I'm afraid.
I understand.
[FRIEZA] Oh, and though you
probably already know this,
there is one more bit of
wisdom I'd like to impart.
And that is...
...you should never
trust anyone. Ever.
[FROST]
Uh?
[FROST screams]
What the...?
Come on! What's wrong with you?!
Frost of the Sixth Universe
has been eliminated.
[GOHAN grunting]
Look, he got back up!
Gohan. Are you gonna be okay?
So, does this mean
what I think it does?
Those two were only
pretending to brawl.
When I took that
first attack from you,
I knew right away.
You held back as if
it were all for show.
So then I chose
to play along
with whatever you had planned.
Well, if you had been
too dense to figure it out,
then I would have had
no choice but to kill you.
[FROST]
You tricked me!
[FRIEZA]
Hm?
[FROST growling]
You honestly think that
I would join forces
with a second-rate
dilettante like you?
A what?!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Me? A second-rate dilettante?
How dare you!
Hey, get back here!
Treat me like I'm some sort of
pathetic neophyte, will you?
I'll show you!
[ZENO, FUTURE ZENO]
Bye-bye!
[CHAMPA screams]
No attacks from outside!
Do it again and the entire Sixth
Universe will be eliminated.
[CHAMPA whimpers]
I am so profoundly sorry, sires!
At least now we know
for certain that Frieza
is truly on our side.
I don't think I would
go that far.
Yeah, if Gohan hadn't caught
on to what he was up to,
Frieza would've betrayed us all
in a heartbeat, that's for sure.
Wha--?!
[FRIEZA]
My dear Gohan.
That was fun.
We should try to continue
working together
as we move toward victory.
[NARRATOR]
With a mischievous grin,
Frieza heads off on his own.
Can this duplicitous villain
ever really be trusted?
Meanwhile, the battle
between Goku and
Ribrianne rages on.
Uh?!
Oh, you!
That sort of malicious attack
will never work on me!
Love is everlasting!
Love always wins in the end!
True love!
[GOKU grunts]
[NARRATOR] Ribrianne seems
impervious to Goku's attacks.
Can he find her weakness?
Just 29 minutes are left
in the Tournament of Power.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super.
When the time has come
to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever in my mind
as I look up to the sky
I was watching you
from your left side
Was trying to get
a good look at your face
The tears in your eyes;
were you laughing or crying?
Your long hair in the way
Blocking the thoughts inside
When the time has
come to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever I will wait,
for the light to show the way
For us to meet again
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Finally, I get to take on Jiren!
I've been looking forward
to this for a long time,
and his strength
doesn't disappoint!
Heh, heh. I'm thrilled
to be fighting someone
as powerful as him!
There's a special technique
I've been saving for
just such an occasion,
but I'll need everyone to share
their spirit energy with me!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"The Mightiest Enemy
Zeroes In on Goku!
Launch the Knockout
Spirit Bomb Now!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?