♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the second match got underway,
with Gohan facing Lavender
of the Ninth Universe!
Despite being
blinding by a toxin,
Gohan went Super Saiyan and
creatively used his energy
to sense his opponent
and knock him out,
but then succumbed to
Lavender's poison.
The Grand Minister
declared a draw,
and then made an
alarming announcement!
Those universes defeated
in the Tournament of Power
are to be eliminated
by Grand Zeno himself.
[NARRATOR]
With the deities of the Cosmos
still reeling over the
Tournament's cataclysmic stakes,
Goku stepped forward to face
a new and dangerous opponent.
The final match of the
Zeno Expo begins now!
[NARRATOR]
"Bergamo the Crusher vs. Goku!
Whose Strength Reaches
the Wild Blue Yonder?"
[DEITIES chattering]
[EA]
If we lose, we're dead,
along with the entire
Third Universe.
This Tournament of Power is
going to be an all-out war.
Vados, if we just go home,
we can't lose, right?
Bad idea, sir.
If we defy the Grand Zenos,
our destruction is 100% assured.
[knuckles cracking]
[chuckles]
So you're Bergamo,
is that right?
This match may not decide if
our universes get destroyed,
but I still say we
should go all out!
[grumbles]
[BERGAMO] I won't take
orders from some low-life.
All you floatin' around
up there, listen up good!
Eh?
What now?
Yes, what is it now?
I am the eldest brother of the
unstoppable Trio of Danger!
I'm Bergamo the Crusher!
The Grand Minister has just
told me our Ninth Universe
is home to the lowest-ranked
mortals in the entire Cosmos!
That's wrong!
How can it be true
when this man's level
is far below any of my brothers?
He doesn't deserve to fight me!
Wait, ya mean me?
We wouldn't be facing
universal destruction
if he hadn't requested this
tournament in the first place!
So not only is he unimpressively
weak, he's a selfish moron!
All right, bucko, you're
takin' this way too far!
You've said enough
for one day, fool!
Your ignorance makes you a
threat to the entire Cosmos!
On behalf of all them,
I'm going to crush you!
Great Omni-Kings.
After I defeat this joke,
I beg you to rescind your order
to destroy the losing
universes in the Tournament.
[DEITIES chattering]
[BOTH]
Hmm...
Well said, my boy!
[BASIL, LAVENDER]
Thank you, brother!
[SIDRA chuckles]
That Bergamo really knows
how to win hearts and minds.
[BEERUS]
Dammit!
He's convincing everyone here
that Goku is the main
villain of the tournament!
You're right, my lord.
The anti-Goku sentiment will
clearly be on the rise now.
It seems Bergamo has
effortlessly convinced
the other universes to
support him over us.
Underhanded, but quite
effective, I must say.
That mortal should have
left well enough alone.
[DEITIES chattering]
Huh?
[GRAND MINISTER] Do you have
an answer for Bergamo,
your majesties?
[FUTURE ZENO]
Mm...
[ZENO]
Tell me, Goku,
how's it feel to have the whole
Cosmos rooting against you?
It doesn't bother me at all!
If everybody's against me, that
makes it more of a challenge,
and that'll just force me
to try even harder to win!
You keep deluding yourself.
Okay, Bergamo. Let's talk.
[BERGAMO]
Uh, yes, sire?
We have an answer
to your request.
That's right, we have
thought very hard.
We like what you said.
We agree to your
request. Don't we?
Yes, we do!
[gasps]
[BASIL, LAVENDER]
Brother!
[BERGAMO]
Thank you, Grand Zenos.
His majesties the Omni-Kings
have accepted
Bergamo's proposal!
If he wins this match, no
universe will be destroyed
for losing the
Tournament of Power.
Wait, what?
But be advised, Goku.
If we get the sense you're
intentionally throwing the match
to get this rule revoked,
the Omni-Kings will feel
compelled to obliterate
all twelve universes
without hesitation.
Oh, yeah!
That works for me
'cause I hate to lose.
I'll give this
fight all I've got.
What's wrong with him?
Does he even know
what's happening?
It seems that no matter
how dire the situation,
Goku finds a way to enjoy
himself in a fight.
It's kind of impressive
in its own way.
Tell me, Top.
[TOP]
Yes?
[CAE]
He's an interesting mortal.
What is your opinion
of this Goku?
Why do you even bother
askin' that, kai?
I can't imagine
it's anything good.
[TOP] I first need to see
him fighting all-out.
Only then can I give
you my appraisal
of this most unusual man.
Boo! Boo!
[EA] Excuse me!
Destroyer of the Sixth?
You seem to be
somewhat acquainted
with this mortal
from the Seventh.
Can you shed some light
on his peculiar approach?
Especially to the Grand Zenos?
Please do!
I want to know what in the
Cosmos he could have done
that allows him to speak
to the Omni-Kings
and Grand Minister that way,
without fear of punishment!
We've just been told he
hails from the universe
with the second-lowest rank.
It's bizarre!
Don't go lookin'
to me for answers!
Goku's just a weird guy
who does weird things.
I don't get him, either!
How's it goin', First Universe?
You must be eating this up!
[ANAT chuckles]
Why yes, we are. It's
rather nice being exempted.
We can just relax
and enjoy the show.
Like us, their mortal levels
are too high to be at risk.
That's one of the many
benefits of a universe
having excellent
divine guidance.
Yes, naturally it
reflects well on us.
I mean, how could a universe
have a higher mortal level
unless its gods were
a higher level too?
We didn't even know that
mortal levels were a thing.
But I do have to say, we're
just delighted to be exempt!
[growls]
Stupid, spoiled exempt universes
really like to rub
it in, don't they?
[chuckles]
[growls]
The third match of
the Zeno Expo. Begin!
[BERGAMO yells]
Well, that was close.
[BERGAMO]
Heh.
You're pretty good.
[GOKU]
So are you.
It's too bad I have
to destroy you.
Hit me!
As soon as you do,
you'll understand
why in the Ninth Universe I'm
called, "Bergamo the Crusher."
[BERGAMO laughs]
He wants to get hit?
That's a bad plan when
you're up against Goku.
[chuckles]
Well, what are you
waiting for? Punch me!
Fine!
[yells]
[chuckles]
Whoa. No way!
[ALL gasp]
[SUPREME KAI]
He grew bigger!
[yells]
Take that!
Oh, don't stop. I know
you wanna hit me more!
[groans]
No, Dad, stop attacking him!
He's obviously absorbing your
punches to get stronger!
Yeah. I see that now.
You don't stand a chance,
Seventh Universe!
Bergamo the Crusher can
absorb and convert any attack
into raw energy to grow in size,
then hit back twice
as strong as before!
He'll grow and grow
till his power is literally
through the roof!
[BERGAMO chuckles]
Your power can grow
through the roof, huh?
[chuckles]
You're just the kinda guy
I've been waiting to fight!
[yells]
[BERGAMO]
You gave me a mighty blow,
now I'll give it right back!
Wow, he's strong.
Yes, really strong.
[chuckling]
[GOKU]
I've been in a lotta battles,
and using your opponent's
power isn't that rare!
That's enough outta you!
[screams]
Keep attacking, you're only
making things harder!
The more you hit Bergamo,
the stronger he gets! Ha!
Yes, that's it, run away!
There's no shame in it
when all you've done so far
is hasten your own death!
He's so big now!
Looks like Goku is
having to run away!
[chuckles]
Wait, is he laughing?
C'mon, Dad.
[chuckles]
It's the end of the line, Goku!
[yells]
Where'd he fly off to now?
[BERGAMO yells]
The bigger you get,
the more blind spots you
have for me to exploit!
Ya better watch out!
I don't need advice from you!
I wanna see how big you can get!
I don't think it's smart for
your pop to hit that wolf guy
if it's just gonna
raise his power!
You know Dad.
The reason he asked
for this tournament
is to fight the strongest
guys in the cosmos.
That means getting
Bergamo as big as he can.
I'm so tired of these Saiyans
making every battle they're in
harder than it needs to be.
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU]
Is this as big as you can get?
Why you!
[chuckles]
[yelling]
Could this really be possible?
His power is equal
to that of a god!
What an impressive warrior!
Did we take him too lightly?
[GOKU yelling]
[gasps]
Oh, wow, Goku is amazing!
He calls this level
"Super Saiyan Blue"!
I'm not done!
I can take this power
level and multiply it!
Kaio Ken!
Your light show
doesn't scare me!
[roars]
Kamehame...
...ha!
[BERGAMO]
Wolfgang Penetrator!
[GOKU yelling]
[BERGAMO groans]
What's wrong?
Let's fight some more!
[gasps]
How could the Seventh
Universe achieve this?
What... are you?
That settles that.
The Zeno Expo is
hereby concluded!
The Seventh Universe
is the winner!
[gasps]
Oh, no, Bergamo!
[BASIL, LAVENDER]
Our brother!
Your friend Goku is very strong!
Yes, my friend Goku
is super-duper strong!
[GOKU]
Hey, Zennies!
[BOTH]
Huh?
I didn't hold anything
back, like I promised.
You were awesome!
You made the Expo so much fun!
[giggles]
[BEERUS sighs]
Goku intentionally made
Bergamo as strong as possible,
and then used that
challenge as motivation
to reach his own
highest level of power.
The Saiyan truly
loves nothing more
than to back himself
into a corner.
All right! Universe
Seven is number one!
I think your celebration
is a little premature.
We haven't started the actual
Tournament of Power yet.
[BASIL, LAVENDER]
Brother! We're coming!
I wanted to see your
true power out there,
but in a way, I was just
fighting against myself.
You'd just absorb my power,
and then fight me
with only that.
If we square off
in the tournament,
you gotta show me
what you can do, okay?
Everyone here thinks of
you as a villain now.
You just can't wait to see
whole universes
destroyed, can you?
Well, since that's the case,
I'll do everything to make
sure your vile universe
is the first to go!
Every fighter here will
be coming for you!
You're gettin' obliterated,
Seventh Universe!
The Ninth isn't goin' anywhere!
We'll win this
thing, you'll see!
[GOKU]
All right!
Then bring it on, guys!
I'll face all of you!
I love a good challenge!
Send all your strongest
warriors against me at once!
I'll clobber every single
one of 'em! Woo!
[DEITIES chattering]
[GOHAN]
Heh.
Did the Expo excite you for the
tournament proper, Grand Zenos?
Shall I tell our visitors that
we'll be proceeding as planned?
Oh, yes! That was
super in every way!
Super is the word
I was thinking, too!
[BOTH] We super-can't wait
for the Tournament of Power!
Assembled deities from
across the great Cosmos,
the three matches between the
Seventh and Ninth Universes
has brought much pleasure
to the Omni-Kings.
The Zeno Expo is an
unmitigated success!
Since that means we'll be moving
on to the Tournament of Power,
allow me to explain its rules.
[GRAND MINISTER] The Null Realm
will be home to this ring,
specially built for
the tournament.
If you knock an opponent out
of the ring, they lose.
Rather simple, is it not?
[GOKU] What if you knock out
your opponent in the ring?
[GRAND MINISTER] Then push them
out to complete the elimination.
Furthermore, now
that the Zeno Expo
has given us more
time to consider,
we have decided to add
a few other prohibitions.
Number One:
The use of any outside
weapons is strictly forbidden.
Number Two: You are not
allowed to kill any opponents!
Number Three: Any advanced
techniques that enable flight
will not work in the Null Realm.
Taking away flight
definitely changes things.
It means winning is going
to take a lot more strategy.
Finally, there'll be a
time limit of 100 tacks.
[WHIS] Translated to Earth time,
that comes out to 48 minutes.
That seems like a rather
long time for each match.
With so many strong fighters,
isn't there a risk the
tournament goes on for too long?
The tournament will
not be one-one-one.
Every fighter will compete
against every one else
at the exact same time.
In other words, the tournament
is just one match.
That's not a tournament,
that's an eight universe,
80-fighter battle royal!
All those guys fighting in
one place, at one time?
Don't worry, you'll
have plenty of space.
The ring we're constructing
is quite large.
Everyone will fight until
the clock hits zero,
whereupon the universe
with the most fighters left
will be declared winner.
Of course, in the event one
team defeats all others
before time runs out, that
universe will be victorious.
If we want our universe to live,
they have to fight as a team.
[WHIS chuckles]
Teamwork does not strike
me as Goku's strength.
[BEERUS]
This thing gets worse and worse.
What? I can do teamwork!
Plus, Gohan's all
about that kinda stuff.
As long as we've got
you, we'll be fine!
Right, son? Team-buildin'?
You know.
Gee, thanks, Dad.
No pressure, huh.
[GRAND MINISTER] The Omni-Kings
look forward to a valiant fight
from each competing universe.
[EA]
A battle royal?
The fate of our entire universe
rests on the outcome
of a glorified riot?
[BOTH]
Hm.
This situation is
far from ideal.
[TOP]
Hm.
Excuse me.
Goku!
[GOKU]
Uh?
[chuckles]
[FUTURE ZENO]
Wha--?
[ZENO]
What?
Fighter, state your name!
[TOP] Grand Minister, forgive me
for barging forward like this.
Greetings, Goku!
I'd like to have a word
with you, if I may.
I can't see anything.
Yes, you're in the way!
[TOP]
Know this, sir!
I'm the leader of the Eleventh's
most elite combat unit!
The gallant, and handsome,
Pride Troopers!
I am the warrior of
freedom. I am Top!
Fight me, Goku!
Right now. In single-combat!
And I warn you: If you
fight without honor,
then my righteous fists
will be your ruin.
You're on!
You don't look like any more of
a challenge than the last guy!
I've made many-a-solemn-vow
in my day
to fight evil-doers,
wherever they are!
So I'm the bad guy here,
huh? Well, this'll be fun!
[NARRATOR] And just like that,
Goku faces a new challenge!
A warrior from the Eleventh
Universe named Top!
How will Goku fare against a
man who thinks he's a villain?
Find out next time on
Dragon Ball Super.
An angel and a demon sit
One to my right,
one to my left
In between I'm tryin'
to figure out the right way
Is one way good?
Is one way bad?
Too much confusion in my head
I can't think with all
this noise, I'm goin' crazy
Is there any way to know
what's right or wrong?
Demons in an angel mask
Hopin' that I'll do
just what they ask
Telling me
they know what's right
Lead me to the light
"For the sake of everyone
You have to destroy
the evil ones
That's the only path, you see"
So they said to me
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
My new opponent is Top,
a by-the-books warrior
from the Eleventh Universe,
loaded with power!
And get this, he says
I'm a bad guy! Me!
That's okay, though.
I've been waiting for an
opponent who pushes my buttons.
I can't wait for us
to throw down.
It's gonna be
next-level bonkers!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Goku Must Pay! The Warrior
of Justice Top Barges In!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?