♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the attack-absorbing
Botamo was outfoxed
and outmaneuvered by Gohan.
[OBNI]
You're keeping pace.
I knew I was right about you.
I've been waiting to face
such a worthy foe.
[NARRATOR] Obni was the
last combatant remaining
from the Tenth Universe,
and his masterful techniques
put Gohan to the test.
[OBNI] Refusing to give up
to the bitter end.
You are a true warrior.
[GOHAN]
Ka...
...me...
...ha...
Ha!
[OBNI groans, screams]
All warriors of the Tenth
Universe have been
thrown from the ring.
Their team has been defeated.
By the rules laid forth,
Universe Ten of the cosmos
will be obliterated at once.
[NARRATOR] Though he knew
it had to be done,
the kind-hearted Gohan
couldn't help but feel haunted
by the Tenth Universe's
elimination,
and the part that he played
in making it happen.
As one fight ends, a new
showdown between gladiators
is set to begin... now!
[NARRATOR] "A Transcendent
Light-Speed Battle Erupts!
Goku and Hit's United Front!"
You're Hit from
Universe Six, right?
That's right.
[DYSPO] Well, I'm Dyspo
from the Eleventh Universe's
Pride Troopers, and I'm
the guy who's gonna overcome
that Time Skip of yours.
So you know about
my favorite move?
For my proud universe,
and my fellow troopers,
I will set the hammer
of justice upon you!
Will you?
[DYSPO chuckles]
Come on...
So what do you think?
Should we try to help him?
Relax, Kale. We don't
need to worry about Hit.
You'll see. He can handle
this all by himself.
[DYSPO]
Hmph.
[yelling]
[DYSPO gasps]
[DYSPO grunts]
[HIT groans]
[HIT grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
Ah! What's happening?!
[VADOS] Well, this is an
unexpected development.
How strange.
Yes, what just happened?
[HIT gasping]
[DYSPO laughing]
[HIT] It appears your confidence
isn't just for show, now is it?
Ha! Of course it's not.
Getting in one good
shot is just a fluke.
Nothing more!
Gah! What a pain!
Careful, my lord.
Getting upset will raise
your blood pressure.
What's worse, that clod
looks like Beerus!
You think so? Seeing as
Lord Beerus is your brother,
then he must resemble
you, too, my lord.
[CHAMPA gasping]
They look nothing like me!
I have a robust,
classically handsome face!
Not like those ninnies
with their high cheekbones
and chiseled jawlines!
I never thought I'd see Hit
under this kind of pressure.
His opponent's one of those
Eleventh Universe fighters.
They really are a formidable
bunch, aren't they?
[DYSPO] That's what I'd expect
from Hit the assassin.
You don't get rattled after
one punch, do you?
Still stoic as ever.
But you know,
that whole arrogant vibe
you got goin' on?
It really pisses me off!
[DYSPO]
Heh!
[HIT groaning]
[laughing]
Ah! He landed another blow?!
Vados! It all happened so fast!
Could you even see it?
Yes. I had no problem following.
Poor Hit can't use
his lethal techniques.
What now? This is bad!
[BELMOD laughs] Looks like
Champa's losin' his mind.
It makes sense, my lord.
Hit appears to be their
most valuable fighter.
And with his composure,
he serves as their
emotional pillar, too.
If he is defeated,
there's a strong chance
the entire Sixth Universe
team will fall apart.
You mean when he's
defeated, not if.
They move too fast!
Yes, we can't see!
[GRAND MINISTER] I've added a
new feature to your godPads.
You can now enjoy
slow-motion instant replay.
Wow, that's awesome!
Yes, super-awesome!
I can't see him coming.
It's almost as though he's using
a Time Skip of his own on me.
[TOP]
Ah, Dyspo.
Our great captain of quickness.
First, he transcended the
speed of sound, and then,
the speed of light! Truly,
he is justice in the flesh!
[DYSPO]
Quittin' already?
[HIT growls]
[DYSPO laughs]
So that's it.
Right before I employ my Time
Skip, for just a fraction
of a second, you move at
supersonic pace, don't you?
Aren't you clever.
Yes, I can do it briefly.
Ramp up my own speed several
thousand times over.
[HIT]
No wonder I couldn't see you.
[DYSPO] Ha, ha! Now you're
probably asking yourself,
"How does that dashing and
gifted warrior time his attack
to the exact moment
I use my Time Skip?"
[HIT]
I'll find out soon enough.
[DYSPO]
Oh, yeah?
Lowerin' your guard?
You are a cocky man.
[DYSPO grunts]
No matter how many
times you try,
the outcome will be the same.
[laughing]
It's the sound.
Whenever I engage my Time Skip,
for a split second,
I flex my entire body.
And you're able to hear the
sound of my muscles contracting.
That's very good.
But still, you'll lose.
There's just no way
to get around it.
Every time somebody moves, their
muscles make a sound I can hear.
It's completely unavoidable.
And it's even more pronounced
when using a special technique.
[CHAMPA]
All righty, then.
We just need to create a loud
ruckus to drown out the sound!
Oh, my vuvuzela!
Bring me my vuvuzela!
I doubt that will work, sir.
He can probably pick out
individual frequencies as well.
Background noise aside,
I would imagine he can focus
on any sound of his choosing.
Uh. Eh... Well, duh,
of course I knew that.
He can't use his power
without tipping Dyspo off,
and yet he can't defeat
him without it.
Now that is the perfect bind.
Indeed, sir.
[HIT] You may have
defeated my Time Skip,
but you won't defeat me.
Tough talk,
but can you back it up?
You'll see.
[DYSPO yells]
[BOTH grunting]
[K'NSI]
It's a blowout.
[TOP]
No, it's not.
It seems that Hit fellow
is beginning to adapt
to Dyspo's speed now.
Are you sure?
[TOP]
Although he's taking some blows,
he's avoiding any
critical attacks.
In fact, this may even
be part of his strategy.
[K'NSI grunts]
[TOP]
Ah, it's a trap! K'nsi!
I read ya loud and clear,
big guy. I'm on it.
[DYSPO yells]
[HIT gasps]
[DYSPO]
Nowhere left to run!
You're through!
[DYSPO yells]
[HIT grunts]
[DYSPO gasping]
Impossible!
Woo-hoo!
He got him!
[TOP]
No!
He fell!
He's out of the ring!
[DYSPO screaming]
Looks like you're the one
with nowhere to run!
[DYSPO screaming]
Yeah that's it!
Just keep falling!
[K'NSI grunts]
[gasping]
What now?
Are you one of his teammates?
[K'NSI grunting]
I am K'nsi, member of
the Pride Troopers.
And I'm not about to stand by
and let you eliminate
one of my loyal
comrades like that!
[DYSPO gasping]
[chuckles]
Ow. Oh. Ow...
Hey, thanks for the lifeline.
No problem.
[TOP] I see. He shifted his
body to another dimension
to avoid Dyspo's attack.
This Hit really is a force
to be reckoned with.
Hey! C'mon, those
rope-like thingies
have gotta be a violation
of the rules...
[VADOS] Perhaps if they
were external weapons,
but they are not.
It's energy emanating
from his body, that's all.
[CHAMPA growls]
Well, that's not fair!
[DYSPO] Can't believe he
deliberately let himself
be driven to the edge,
just to force me over.
As of right now,
I'm tagging in, too.
We'd be up a creek if anything
bad happened to you.
Sure, fine.
[K'NSI]
You hear that?
Eh, suit yourselves.
[K'NSI, DYSPO grunt]
[DYSPO growls]
[rustling]
[K'NSI, DYSPO grunt]
Not so fast!
Eat this!
[DYSPO grunting]
Hey, you're fighting dirty!
That's not fair,
Universe Eleven!
[vuvuzela blares]
[DYSPO, HIT grunting]
Just wait here for me,
you got that?
Wait, no, you can't go, not yet!
We should still be laying low!
I don't care! You really
expect me to just
sit back and watch them
do this to Hit?
I've gotta help him!
Oh, this time you're
finished for good!
[DYSPO gasping]
What the hell is that?
Ah! No way!
Wait a minute.
What are you doing, Goku?
[CAULIFLA, KALE gasp]
[GOKU yells]
[DYSPO groans]
I don't need your help.
That's good, because I
didn't come here for that.
[HIT]
Tch.
[GOKU] I saw those guys had you
backed into a corner.
And, you know, it made me
itch for a fight too.
I say we fight them together.
[DYSPO, K'NSI growl]
What is that?
That is his Super
Saiyan God form.
It allows him to move
faster than Super Saiyan,
while still expending far
less energy than he would
have to with Super Saiyan Blue.
[BEERUS] Looks like Hit's
been granted a reprieve.
How 'bout a little
gratitude, Champa?
Oh, spare me, Beerus,
we don't need your charity!
[exhales]
Fighters from twin universes
teamin' up, huh?
This is a chance to defeat the
best of two universes at once.
Let's not pass it up.
[HIT]
Listen, Goku.
The one with the ears is mine.
Don't get in my way.
You're free to try and stop me.
[DYSPO yells]
[GOKU]
Huh?
[GOKU groans]
Bet you can't do that
again right away!
[K'NSI grunts]
--[HIT gasps]
--[K'NSI laughing]
You're gonna have to
get through me first!
You're pretty fast, aren't you?
But I've got my own tricks,
silly rabbit.
[gasps]
[groans]
Damn it! He won't let me
use Instant Transmission!
There you are!
[yells]
Man, how did he already
know what I was gonna do?
Sure, you've got speed on your
side, I'll give you that.
But your moves are
simple and predictable.
Once I get the timing down,
fighting you should
be a piece a cake.
Goku's using his
brain for a change.
Impressive.
He turned Blue for just a second
at the moment when he attacked.
Thereby giving him the
speed and power he needs
without draining his energy.
Gotta say, I'm amazed
you were able
to deflect my energy blasts.
Looks like you left your
trash lyin' around.
If you think it's just trash,
go ahead and touch it.
[HIT]
Let me guess. They'll explode?
[K'NSI] Like you wouldn't
believe. Heh, heh, heh.
[HIT]
So it's an impenetrable defense?
[K'NSI]
You can use your fancy tricks
and stop time all you want,
but a lot of good that'll do
if you still can't get
anywhere near me.
I don't need to get near you.
Say what?
Why don't you take a load off.
[groaning, coughing]
What was that?
Some kind of shockwave?
How did he slip right
through the minefield
and then land a blow on K'nsi?
It seems to be a
transparent energy blast
that only impacts
physical bodies, my lord.
That's the same technique
that Hit used
to stop Goku's heart
when they fought.
Take that you Universe
Eleven cheaters!
Hit's got all kinds of
tricks up his sleeve!
[GOKU yelps]
Those Eleventh Universe
guys are pretty tricky.
And they're not gonna get
pushed out so easily.
I think it's time
we traded opponents.
[gasps]
[DYSPO groaning]
What just happened?
I flexed my muscles
the same way that I do
before I Time Skip just
so I could lure you in.
[DYSPO]
So, you faked me out,
pretending you were
about to Time Skip,
and then countered
my Light Bullet attack?
You figured it out.
Way to go!
Those were some
slick moves, Hit.
[K'NSI] Oh yeah?
You think that's something.
Wait till you see what I can do!
I'm not gonna
make it easy on ya!
[yells]
Careful, Goku, he's
surrounded by traps--
Doesn't matter!
[GOKU yells]
Big mistake. Uh?
What?! Are you kidding me?!
[GOKU yelling]
[groans]
[yells]
[screams]
Wait, that time you did
use the Time Skip!
I did.
So, which do you think
it'll be next time?
Perk up those ears and listen.
Carefully.
[gasping]
Ha! Hit's thrown that Dyspo guy
completely off his game now!
In a contest of extraordinary
speed such as this one,
a moment's indecision
can spell certain defeat.
[DYSPO gasps]
[groans]
This fight is effectively over.
Out of respect, I'll let you
walk yourself off the edge.
If you can't stand,
I'll help you up.
We Pride Troopers don't know
the meanin' of
the word "surrender"!
Quitting goes against
our code! Hear me?
Then I'll put an end
to this for you.
[DYSPO groaning]
[K'NSI grunts]
What the...?
What do we do?
Fall back for now and wait
for the right time to strike.
I'll take that Hit guy
down with me.
[gasps]
[K'NSI]
We're all counting on you.
Uh!
The only thing you'll be
taking with you is pain.
Ah!
[K'NSI screams]
K'nsi!
Why you...!
Aw man, now there's
only three left.
But two of those
are Jiren and Top.
So there's no cause
for panic yet.
Contestant K'nsi of
the Eleventh Universe
has been eliminated.
[FUTURE ZENO]
Tap, tap.
Let's see, K'nsi...
Huh, where'd he go?
Oh! Bye!
I wonder who'll be out next!
Yes, so do I!
[DYSPO groaning] We'll get
our revenge immediately.
Justice waits for no--
[TOP]
Enough! Quit playing the hero.
[DYSPO]
Uh...
[TOP]
This isn't about justice.
This is about survival
versus extermination.
Which one will we claim?
[GOKU] Well, well, you've
improved yet again.
But just so you know,
when that Dyspo guy's had a
chance to get his strength back,
then he's all mine, Hit.
Ya got that?
As you wish.
So now what?
Is this the part where
you and I start fighting?
I'll let you go for now.
As thanks for your help.
If you make it all
the way through,
we're gonna settle this
once and for all.
That's how this is gonna end.
Heh. Fine by me.
[NARRATOR] By forming what
could be the greatest tag team
in the history of the
cosmos--Goku and Hit
prevailed over the
formidable Pride Troopers
of Universe Eleven.
But what will happen
when the two warriors
face off against each other?
Only 35 minutes remain until the
fateful tournament concludes.
The action continues,
next time on Dragon Ball Super.
When the time has come
to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever in my mind
as I look up to the sky
I was watching you
from your left side
Was trying to get
a good look at your face
The tears in your eyes;
were you laughing or crying?
Your long hair in the way
Blocking the thoughts inside
When the time has
come to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever I will wait,
for the light to show the way
For us to meet again
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Master Roshi is showing off
the results of his training,
and the old guy
is tearin' it up!
The Fourth Universe
won't know what hit 'em!
But wait, is he about
to give it all up
in exchange for that
monster technique?
Don't do it, old man!
It's not worth it! Seriously!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"A Valiant Fight!
Master Roshi's Blaze of Glory!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?