♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Beerus the Destroyer
awoke from his slumber,
in search of a new archrival.
And the Kais feared that if Lord
Beerus were excited in battle,
it could lead to
a destructive frenzy
that would spell
the end of the universe.
While back on Earth,
Bulma kicked off
her birthday party on a
massive cruise ship,
and old friends
were reunited once more.
But not everyone
accepted her invitation.
Vegeta told you to tell me
he's too busy training?
And Goku's not coming either?
[NARRATOR] Though that was
hardly the most pressing matter,
as Beerus located Goku
and set off to confront him
on King Kai's world.
He hopes the Saiyan will lead
him to the mysterious warrior
prophesized to match him,
fist to fist. Now.
[BEERUS] Whatever it takes,
I will find him.
This Super Saiyan God.
[NARRATOR]
"Bid for the Dragon Balls!
Pilaf and Crew's
Impossible Mission!"
[BEERUS]
Mmm?
[chuckles]
Mmm.
Eh!
[sighs]
For the love of--
Listen up, Whis! Is this
all you brought us for lunch,
'cause I'm not really
feeling it.
I guess I wasn't paying
attention when you told me,
since all that's here
is grilled river fish
from Planet Wartrin
and cluckbird nanban.
And I just remembered
that I'm sick of them both.
I don't see how
you could possibly
be sick of that dish, my lord,
since I've only
made it once for you
and that was over a hundred
and sixty years ago.
When you annihilated
Planet Monsa, remember?
If I say I'm sick of it, I am!
Well I'm afraid
that's your only option.
And if you do choose
to stomach a meal you had
a mere century and a half prior,
then you should hurry.
We'll be at North Kai's
planet in ten minutes.
Oh, well in that case.
[GOKU panting]
[KING KAI]
Eeeh!
This is a total disaster!
Why is Lord Beerus' energy
moving this way?
Oh no! He's already
in the same galaxy cluster!
That's way too close
for comfort!
Oooh nooo!
We're through!
Uh, what's going on
with you, King Kai?
Are you sure okay?
Get out of here, quick!
Didn't you say something about
your friend's birthday party?
Use Instant Transmission
and go there right now!
Don't worry about a gift.
You can just say
it's in the mail!
I don't think so.
I'm not really good at parties.
I always get
kinda bored and stuff.
You have to go!
I'm worried about
your social life, Goku.
I can't let you
lose your friends!
[GOKU]
Hm?
I think I'm the one
who should be
worried about you, King Kai.
You're acting
really strange today.
Ah! Ahhh. No no,
nothing's happening,
I'm just a strange guy!
[KING KAI chuckles nervously]
[KING KAI]
♪ I'm strange! I'm strange! ♪
♪ I'm so strange,
I'm deranged. ♪
♪ I'm strange! I'm strange!
I'm strange and deranged. ♪
I mean he is weird, but not
usually as weird as this?
[fog horn blows]
♪
[inaudible]
Do they think
doing jumping jacks
is more important
than my birthday?
It's not personal,
you know that.
It is to me! You know how long
I've known your father?
Aw come on, Bulma,
let's talk about
something more pleasant--
like uh, how old
are you now, anyway?
[BULMA grunts]
Like I'd tell you! You should
never ask a woman that!
Want some more punch?
[CHICHI sighs]
This is amazing.
I've never been
on a cruise before!
Knowing the richest woman on
Earth certainly has its perks.
Gotta hand it to Goku,
he knows how to make friends.
[A18] Bulma, I've been dying to
ask about these bingo prizes.
Is it true you're giving away
a castle and an airplane?
Yup! I sure am!
But that's not the best part.
Wait 'til you see
the grand prize!
You hear that, Krillin?
We've got three of us here,
including Marron,
and that means three chances!
We've gotta
make sure we take home
the second prize castle, okay?
Really? Don't you
want the top prize?
[A18 grunts]
Something wrong
with finishing second?
[KRILLIN]
Okay, I was not going there.
[yells]
I didn't think about
the number of bingo players!
How can Goku be missing this?
[GOTEN, TRUNKS laughing]
Hey, are you really
gonna show me
all of the bingo prizes, Trunks?
[TRUNKS]
Yup! It's the VIP tour!
[GOTEN]
Whoa! Awesome!
[TRUNKS]
This way!
[GOTEN]
Sorry, Mr. Chef!
You damn kids!
[CHEF MAN 4C]
They sure run fast.
[GOTEN stutters]
[TRUNKS] All right, Goten.
Ready to have your mind blown?
[GOTEN]
Yeah!
No flippin' way!
These are bingo prizes?
My mind is so blown!
[TRUNKS]
Nuh-uh-uuuh!
Hold on! I haven't shown
you the craziest part yet!
Watch this!
What the--
Goten, wait!
[GOTEN yells]
[sighs]
When something's glowing,
you probably shouldn't touch it.
[GOTEN laughs]
Awesome! That's some pretty
high-level security, isn't it?
Yeah, it's
my mom's invention.
She says with
this baby in place,
no one can find out what
the grand prize is for bingo
till she lifts the curtain!
[GOTEN]
Whoa!
So, I guess that means
we have to wait, too.
[TRUNKS]
Oh no it doesn't!
As awesome
as that fence is,
my mom didn't exactly
think of everything.
[chuckles]
You see? That's called
a "security gap."
[GOTEN]
Cool! Way to go, Trunks!
Next flaw? Leaving
your secret password
out on the kitchen table.
[beeping]
[sirens wail]
[BOTH]
Whoa!
[BOTH laugh]
[birds cawing]
[PILAF'S stomach grumbles]
[PILAF whimpers]
I'm so hungry.
You don't get to complain
when it's your fault, sir.
I haven't eaten anything but
grass for three whole days!
And that is pretty brutal,
even for a dog.
When are you going
to admit there's no
buried treasure on this
silly island, Emperor?
[PILAF] Listen,
you insolent servants.
If the map says treasure,
there's treasure, okay?
It can't be wrong!
It cost me fifty Zeni!
Well maybe next time
you shouldn't believe
a cheap little map!
Just like you shouldn't
believe that a cheap
motor boat
would work, either!
Now the engine's totally
shot and it's leaking
from at least thirteen places!
How are we supposed to
get back to civilization
in that piece of junk?
On the bright side, at least
I've already dug a grave.
[PILAF grunts]
Enough talking back!
We won't stop until we find it,
even if it takes us
the rest of our lives!
[MAI grunts]
[PILAF snarls]
[MAI mummbles]
[PILAF'S stomach grumbles]
[PILAF] My stomach sounds
like some jungle beast!
All I want
is some food. But no!
I can't even
catch a measly guppy!
Aaah! Even the fishies in
the ocean are disrespecting
the glorious Emperor Pilaf!
[BOTH gasp in awe]
[Dragon Radar beeps]
Oh.
[PILAF]
Huh. Uuh!
Yeee-ha-haaa!
[GOTEN laughs]
[TRUNKS]
Amazing, right?
My mom tracked 'em
all down, just for today!
[PILAF] All seven Dragon Balls,
all in one place!
And that place
is moving this way!
[fog horn blows]
But what are the chances
of that? Can this be?
Can this be?!
Daaah!
[chuckles]
Finally, the great wheel of
fortune is turning our way!
Sire, look!
Your line is moving--
you caught something!
What?
Gotcha! Ah, ahh-uh.
The Dragon Radar!
No, we need that! Come back!
[SHOU, MAI] We need
that food a whole lot more!
[PILAF grunts]
Oh, that's it. We're dead.
Oh well! We don't need
some rinky-dink fish now anyway!
The real feast is coming!
Because your genius
Emperor just found
all seven Dragon Balls!
[BOTH scream]
[Dragon Radar beeps]
[laughs]
[TRUNKS] Better put 'em back
before my mom catches us.
[PILAF laughs intensely]
Bet you won't doubt me now!
[SHOU, MAI]
Hmm!
You do realize there's
nothing on the screen, right?
You haven't eaten
for so long, sire.
I think your head might be
workin' a little bit funny.
Hm?
[yells]
Lose your mind
all you want,
but did you have to
lose the fish, too?
I saw it! I'm not delusional,
it was there!
Well sire, if you're
sure about your sanity,
then maybe the radar broke
when it went underwater.
[PILAF]
This is waterproof!
I know I saw 'em!
Who's messing with me?!
[SHOU, MAI]
This is how we row the boat!
This is...
Sir, I'm too hungry to row!
Yeah, I'm starving!
Buck up, soldiers!
We're almost there.
The Dragon Balls
are on that ship!
[fog horn blows]
[MAI] Emperor Pilaf!
The boat's filling up!
Just keep rowing!
Go, go, go!
[MAI, SHOU]
This is how we row the boat!
This is--
[MAI, SHOU]
This is how we row the boat!
[MAI sobbing]
Seriously, sire. I'm sorry,
but we're all rowed out!
Aw, come on, guys.
We're almost there.
But my arms
feel like noodles!
Don't cry, it's okay.
What about
any of this is okay?
Not you too, Shou!
Once we get the Dragon Balls
we can do and eat
whatever we want, you just
gotta think big picture!
Picture? You're the
only one who saw anything!
Are you sure it was
all seven Dragon Balls
and we won't just row around for
no reason until we're fish food?
[PILAF]
Mai, I'm telling you!
They're all together
inside that ship!
[ALL yell]
[MAI]
Cold! It's so cold!
[gasps]
Emperor Pilaf, behind you!
I'm pretty sure
that guy isn't friendly!
Holy schnikes! Go!
[SHOU, PILAF, MAI yell]
Oh man. That was close.
Dumb shark.
But you'll have to
do better than that!
[ALL yell]
[ALL panting]
Did we make it
or am I dreaming this?
Wow, I thought we were all
goners for sure!
You've really hung in there--
and now that's literal.
[TRUNKS]
Hey! What are you doing?
[ALL]
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
Hey, silly-heads! It's way
easier if you use this!
[PILAF sighs]
Thank you children,
you have served us well.
So just what were you
doing down there?
[laughs] We were hunting
for Dragon--uh.
Uh, hunting Dragon Fish--
you know, the fish?
But don't you need
nets or fishing poles?
Oh we're purists,
we fish by hand!
[ALL sniff]
[ALL stomachs grumble]
Hey, are you guys hungry?
Why don't you grab some food
from my mom's party?
There's all kinds of booths.
You can take your pick!
[SHOU, MAI]
You really mean it?
Not so fast, you two!
You're not some
charity-taking beggars!
You're the great Emperor
Pilaf's royal guard!
Aw, come on.
All right, sir. After all,
you are the boss, I guess.
Well, whatever.
Well I'm gonna eat.
[TRUNKS] Yeah, me too.
I'm gonna eat till I'm sick!
[GOTEN]
Oh, me first!
[MAI, SHOU whimper]
[ALL gasp lightly]
Hey! You idiots! This is your
fault for being so obedient!
Can't you goody two-shoes
defy me once in a while
and get what we need?
Like, have some initiative!
[MAI, SHOU gasp]
You sure you don't want any?
What's the use?
If you're gonna keep asking me,
I'll eat some to shut you up.
It's heavenly!
You guys eat some too.
We can't be rude!
[MAI, SHOU]
Thank you, Emperor sir!
[BOTH chuckle]
[phone rings]
[laughs]
That was a hundred
and fifty times gravity.
Not even that
can slow me down now.
[buzzer buzzes]
Excuse me. Mr. Vegeta, sir?
[VEGETA] Get out, woman! You're
interrupting my training!
[WOMAN 4A] But sir,
it's Miss Bulma calling.
She wants you to come
to her birthday party.
[VEGETA]
I said get out!
Tell her I have no time for
cake and meaningless chatter!
[BULMA ON PHONE]
Listen Vegeta!
Your adorable wife will
put up with a lot of crap,
but you missing her birthday
is not on the list!
Get your Saiyan butt
over here now!
Uh.
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU grunting]
[KING KAI]
Bubbles, I'm not built for
this kind of stress,
honestly. I mean--
Oh, I mean why would Beerus
want to come to my world anyway?
I don't have
a single restaurant.
Ka...me...ha...me...
Ha!
[ALL yell]
[GOKU grunting]
Yaa!
[panting]
Wow, that kinda stung!
[KING KAI]
You Grade A idiot!
If you're gonna
launch a blast like that,
a little warning would be nice!
[BUBBLES, GREGORY holler]
[KING KAI]
Aah! Uh!
Bubbles!
[GOKU]
Eeh.
Oh, that's bad!
You do realize I still have to
live on this planet,
don't you, Goku?
I'm sorry, King Kai.
Getting stronger is
really important to me
and I guess I just
got carried away.
That's how you roll.
I get that.
And that's why we can't let
you and Beerus meet,
because neither one of you
can control yourselves.
Wait what? What's a Beerus,
is that a person?
[gasps]
Aw jeez, that was dumb!
Stupid, stupid, stupid,
stupid, stupid, stupid!
Oh I see. You've been trying
to hide something from me.
That explains why you've been
acting so weird all day.
[KING KAI]
Mn-mmm!
So who is this guy?
[KING KAI]
Mmm...
[GOKU]
Ah!
[KING KAI]
Mmm...
Okay, I'll tell you,
but just try to listen
like a grown-up.
It's Lord Beerus
and he's not a human
or anything close
to that, he's a deity.
On the same level as
Supreme Kai, roughly speaking,
and he's actually
heading here now.
Okay, cool. But deities
are good, right?
Why are you worried?
Because Lord Beerus is a
very different sort of deity.
He's moody, unpredictable,
and very scary.
Well what does he do
that's so scary?
He's called a Destroyer
because his role is to
destroy stuff, which he does
on the slightest of whims.
If you do anything
he doesn't like,
he'll explode your planet
without a second thought.
Like if you
just didn't clean up
after your dog on a walk?
[KING KAI]
Mmm.
I guess that would
be enough, sure.
Or if you didn't
eat all your broccoli?
[sighs] Yup, that could
probably do it.
Or if you go to a hot spring
and pee pee in it?
[growls]
Yeah of course, Goku!
Because that's totally
disgusting, but the point is
is that Beerus is dangerous
and any planet or galaxy's
at risk whenever he's awake,
so we have to be careful!
Oh I see.
So he's a bad guy, huh?
[KING KAI]
Mmm.
It's not as simple as that.
[KING KAI] The universe must
always be balanced.
If deities like Kais exist
to create life and worlds,
and encourage order, then other
deities must also exist
to destroy life,
and spread chaos.
Then I take it
he's a strong one, huh?
The word "strong"
does not begin to cut it.
His power's on a level
beyond anything you've seen
or can even imagine,
and he could destroy the whole
universe if he felt like it!
No one can match him!
Wow, can't wait
to meet this guy!
[KING KAI]
That is not going to happen
unless absolutely necessary!
And if you do meet,
I'm warning you,
don't do anything stupid!
You hear me?
Okay, I get it!
You don't want me
to challenge this Beerus
unless he does something
really wrong, right?
[KING KAI]
Hmm. Hm?
Get inside!
Don't talk, don't move,
and don't come out!
[panting]
Okay, keep it together,
King Kai. No problem.
Ouch, King Kai. Take it easy!
What was that for?
[panting]
I never should've
gotten out of bed.
[BEERUS]
Something the matter, Kai?
[gasps]
[GOKU]
Hmm.
[screams]
L--Lo-Lord Beerus, sir!
Wha-What brings you
to my planet?
Oh, wow! So that's what a
Destroyer God looks like, huh?
[wails quaveringly]
[BEERUS]
Mm.
♪ Closing Song ♪
I see all these kids
As I walk to school
Their colorful backpacks
All unique and cool
I can't help but wonder
which color I'd choose
If I were still a kid
Where would I run off to? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
How am I lookin' now that
I've grown into an adult? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
Do I look like I'm proud
of who I've finally become?
Oh, I know I've made mistakes
But I'm tryin' to get it right
And I'm willing just to wait
For the moment I can shine
This anthem
Is a story for all time!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And if King Kai is so worried
about this Destroyer guy,
he must be really strong!
Which is exactly why I've got to
give him everything I've got!
How else am I supposed to know
how much I need to train?
But don't worry,
it's a friendly fight.
What's the worst
that could happen?
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Showdown on King Kai's World!
Goku vs. Beerus the Destroyer"!
You definitely
don't want to miss it,
because somebody's going
Super Saiyan Three!