Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me go back to the start
Wishing on the starlight
In the sky, let's paint a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of God
Kyo-Let's☆Mo-Let's☆Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic
I don't care 'bout limits, no regret
Make me tougher even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo' try me
So-Zets☆Cho-Zets☆Dynamic!
Let's Go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going power pumpin' up
something greater waiting not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the 6th Universe
had been whittled down
to its last,
most fearsome warrior:
the legendary assassin, Hit.
Vegeta powered up
to Super Saiyan Blue,
but not even that could
stop Hit's astonishing
special attack.
[NARRATOR] With Hit's ability
to jump a fraction of a second
into the future, it seemed
his time-defying advantage
was too much to overcome.
Until Goku stepped
into the ring.
Still lucky?
[HIT]
What?
[GOKU chuckles]
Your whole advantage
is moving a tenth
of a second forward in
time for a surprise shot.
So then I just anticipated--
guessing where your
moves will take you
after you start your attack.
Based on watching
your fighting style.
A new phase of
the fight begins.
You're finally taking this
thing seriously, aren't ya?
Then I'll be doing
the same, Hit!
Now I'm going all out!
[GOKU]
Okay, here goes.
Thanks for waiting, Hit.
He defended himself
from that Time Skip
by predicting how
Hit would attack.
Damn! Kakarot makes it
sound like it's child's play!
But why would he tell Hit
what he was doing?
He had a critical advantage
and he may have just blown it!
[HIT]
You show poor judgment, Goku.
Now that I know
what you're doing,
I can outwit you by
being harder to predict.
You can try. But these
are split-second reactions.
Going against your instincts
is harder than you think.
And my speed's gonna make it
even more of a challenge.
I gotta give Hit credit.
He's hanging in there
against Goku even though
he's in his
Super Saiyan Blue form.
What's the matter?
Aren't you gonna
use that Time Skip?
[GOKU yells]
I'll admit it. Without that
technique, I won't last long.
Okay, so what are
you waiting for?
Try it out now.
[HIT]
Very well.
[HIT grunts]
[GOKU chuckles]
Yeah! Nice one!
Damn it! No one's ever
stopped his Time Skip!
Yes, it seems Goku
has found its flaw.
Now they see what
my Saiyan can do.
Your Saiyan? And here I thought
I was the one training him.
[VEGETA growls]
Of course, it's
easier to go second.
He used my fight
to study Hit's moves!
You ready to surrender?
Huh?
Hey, you feeling okay?
[HIT yelling]
I don't like this.
Why not? What's he doing?
[HIT yelling]
[PICCOLO] It's hard to
tell what he's up to.
All right.
[GOKU] You kinda caught
me off guard there.
Guess you're the sort of guy who
yells when he powers up, too.
[GOKU] That's weird; he's not
fighting any differently.
[CHAMPA]
Hey!
My lord?
[CHAMPA] I thought the
point of that screaming fit
was to boost his power!
How am I supposed
to know why he screamed?
[CHAMPA] Oh, don't play coy.
You know everything!
Does this mean he can't win this
and we'll lose to my brother?
Not sure. But I wouldn't
abandon all hope just yet.
That's it, Goku! You've
got him up against the ropes!
[GOKU yelling]
You're mine!
[GOKU grunting]
Interesting. I wasn't
sure that would work.
That was a brutal blow!
I need to know, Contestant,
can you still compete?
C'mon, buddy.
Well... Looks like
this fight is--
[GOKU]
Wait!
I am not finished yet!
So, it was a power-up, then.
He can ascend to new
levels just like a Saiyan!
I don't think so.
It seems that was
merely dramatic flair.
You mean all that screaming?
[VADOS] Perhaps he wanted
to start his attack
with some showmanship,
like Goku does.
I can't increase my ability
through some kind of
noisy transformation the way
Frost and you Saiyans do.
If I wanna become more
lethal, I don't have the luxury
of cutting corners; I just have
to do it the old-fashioned way.
Anybody know what
he's talking about?
He's talking about
his pure technique.
And what does that mean?
Somehow, he's figured
out how to improve
his fighting move in
the middle of this match,
without any boost to his power!
Combat is craft. What matters
most is not raw power,
but the skill by
which you hone it.
I'd never even thought
of improving my Time Skip.
Up to now there was no reason,
since I could defeat
anyone I faced.
And then came you.
So I thought,
maybe I can push it farther.
And as you can see,
my experiment paid off.
By refining my technique,
I've managed
to jump twice as far
into the future.
He improved his Time Skip?
Man, what's gonna happen next?
[CHAMPA laughing]
If his move is twice as good,
he must be the best now!
Looks like it.
All right, Hit,
finish him quickly!
I want to wrap this thing up
and get my hands on that Earth!
Damn it!
[grunting]
What are you waiting for?!
Attack!
[GOKU grunting]
Get on your feet.
That could cost ya.
It's because of you that
I've improved my technique.
That mercy was payment.
It's all you'll get.
He deliberately ignored me!
How dare he defy his Destroyer!
[HIT] Based on the results
of my last attempt,
this stance should
maximize the effectiveness
of the Time Skip.
Let us find out.
[GOKU] He's impressive--
there's no denying that.
His improved attack cut
right through my defenses.
[GOKU] If he's serious about
doubling his Time Skip,
he can jump ahead about two
tenths of a second now.
I can only take a few
more shots like that,
but a few more should be enough.
Two tenths isn't
that far out of reach.
What could that
Saiyan be smiling about?
[ELDER KAI chuckles]
[VEGETA] The ability to improve
during battle is in our blood.
It's what makes Saiyans
the ultimate warrior race.
I refuse to believe this
"Hit" can do it better.
[HIT] You're badly misreading
the situation you're in, Goku.
[GOKU]
How's that?
Right now, you're trying
to calculate how many
of my blows you'll
be able to absorb
while you try to
predict my attacks.
You believe two tenths
of a second won't make
enough difference,
and you'll still be able
to take the damage and
make a counter-strike,
but that's where you're wrong.
[HIT] Because I'm not
done improving yet.
[HIT] That time I skipped
forward half a second,
which is five times better
than my initial technique
and obviously more
than you can handle.
He's joking!
Usually Goku's the one who
gets better as a fight goes.
That's how he managed
to save us so many times!
If this guy can step it up
faster than Goku can,
we really are in trouble!
[HIT]
Referee.
[TD REF]
Yes, contestant?
[HIT] We've established that
killing will disqualify me.
[TD REF]
That's right.
[HIT] Then as with Vegeta, it's
up to you to end this fight.
A while back, you nearly
called this match.
What are you waiting for now?
Goku, get up!
[TD REF]
Uh...
[HIT]
Make a decision!
[TD REF] Contestant Goku is
somehow back on his feet!
[GOKU]
I'm not giving up.
[HIT] It seems you're too proud
to admit when you've failed.
That's not it!
What?
[GOKU] Stopping now
wouldn't be fair to you.
It'd give you the wrong idea.
[HIT]
What does that mean?
[GOKU] Look, it's not 'cause
I've been trying to trick you,
or make you think you're
stronger than you are, okay?
I'm just still working
on something
and I didn't want to use it
in battle till I was sure
it was time.
Honestly, I didn't think I'd try
it till after this tournament,
when I was ready to
challenge Lord Beerus again.
Say what? Do you know what
he's talking about, Whis?
[GOKU] Since I am
still figuring it out,
at this point I only have about
a one-in-ten chance
of pulling it off.
And if I mess this move up,
it's gonna do a lot more
than just knock me out
of this tournament.
But here goes!
[GOKU yelling]
Is he actually
trying what I think?
Surely he hasn't
discovered a transformation
beyond "Super Saiyan Blue."
But if not that, what
could he be trying to do?
Defeat him, Hit,
while you still can!
I don't know what he's up to
and I don't wanna find out!
Don't just stand there! Attack!
Come on!
[HIT] Your greatness has
fueled my own, Goku.
As you rise even higher,
by necessity, so will I.
I wanna see where
this competition goes,
for my own sake.
Let's take this to its peak.
The assassin's sounding
more and more
like a martial artist.
He's certainly
acting differently.
I've never heard him
talk so much before.
He has an effect
on his opponents.
That's what's unique about Goku.
[GOKU chuckles]
Now, I'll show you
the Kaio-ken!
I pulled it off!
All the power of
Super Saiyan Blue
intensified with the
Kaio-ken technique!
If I'd messed this up
even a little,
my energy would've
run out of control,
and with this much of it,
I woulda been toast.
But it looks like
I've got it in check.
Good old Kaio-ken.
I guess it was worth
the risk after all.
And what exactly
does this technique do?
[GOKU] It's basically
an energy multiplier.
I learned it a long time
ago from King Kai.
This version doubles my
strength, speed, and senses,
and all the other traits
I use in a fight.
Here it comes!
[HIT]
Impossible!
[GOKU]
Over here!
I couldn't follow
his movements at all!
That uppity, disrespectful
Saiyan was planning
to use this move against me?
I'm detecting a hint of concern
in your voice, my lord.
Do you think that would
be a problem for you?
Don't be ridiculous!
Why would I even care?
If you're not at all worried,
then why are you sweating?
I'm sweating because
I hate losing to my brother
and Goku holding back
could've cost us.
Now leave me alone!
[VEGETA] Beerus doesn't
understand what sort of
technique that is.
[VEGETA yelling]
[GOKU yelling]
[GOKU]
Kaio-ken! Times four!
[VEGETA yelling]
[VEGETA] The Kaio-ken
does amplify his attacks,
at least for a while,
but it takes a huge toll on him.
Going Super Saiyan
strains his body, too,
and I'm sure that so-called
Super Saiyan Blue's
exponentially worse.
Adding Kaio-ken on top of that?
It's hard to imagine the
damage he's doing to himself.
No wonder he didn't
use it earlier.
He was saving it
as a last resort.
I know it's risky,
but there's a big payoff, too.
Super Saiyan Blue's all about
power through extreme control.
Combining that with the
calming focus of the Kaio-ken,
and now there's no
telling how high I can go!
[VEGETA]
Damn it! No!
He's leapt past me once again!
His energy keeps shooting
higher; it's extraordinary!
[GOKU yelling]
It's triple. Quadruple.
No, it's...
[GOKU]
Times ten!
Kaio-ken times ten!
No way!
He's so fast!
Let’s start the continuation of our dream
That was once interrupted
Just draw a door in the sky
Connecting the stars
A new stage
Is the place we’ll challenge the gods
Intense ☆ Violent ☆ Dynamic!
kku!
a
Let’s Go! Go! A huge panic
n
i
k
Let's!
Losing makes us stronger
Not knowing our place
Means we have no regrets or boundaries
Grand ☆ Transcendent ☆ Dynamic!
Chou
kku!
Let’s Go! Yes! Let a barrage of kicks
d
a
k
i
Let's!
k
u
Go!
Yes!
Rain down, and tremble with adrenaline
An amazing story is waiting for us
What the--?
It won't work.
I don't care how far
you push your Time Skip;
it won't stand a chance
against what I am now.
Even with the energy
control of Blue,
I can't keep this up for long.
I gotta end this with one shot!
[GOKU]
Kame...
...hame...
Ha!
[GOKU]
You're mine!
[NARRATOR] Is that the shot to
end this war between universes?
The Tournament of
Destroyers concludes,
next time on Dragon Ball Super!
Whoa–oa
It's hard to say - don't wanna stay
I twist and fight, can't find my way
I must believe, that fear and trouble
can even be fun if you think the right way
Whoa–oa
Whoa
I don't wanna draw the line, I gotta see it through some way
Fight for what I know is mine, the dream I had of me that day
Whoa–o-oa
Whoa–oa–oa
Don't care if they call me greedy,
If they ever make it make it through,
Don't care if they laugh at me,
cus' I will make the dream come true
Whoa–oa
Whoa–oa–oa
Hey, it's me, Goku!
I hope you like encores,
'cause this battle isn't over just yet!
Ha! I may have unleashed
a whole new level of power
but there's a reason Hit was chosen
as the strongest fighter from the 6th Universe.
And if I'm gonna win, I'll have to
find the strength for one last shot.
Next time on Dragon Ball Super:
Make sure you don't miss it, okay?