♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Goku claimed someone
wanted to kill him.
And sure enough, the mighty
assassin, Hit, arrived!
The two staked
their lives on the battle!
But no sooner
than it had started,
the bout was over!
[GOHAN]
He's not moving. He must be...
[gasps]
[GOTEN whimpering]
Dad, no!
[sobbing]
[NARRATOR]
"Will He Strike Back?
The Unseen Killing Technique!"
Come on, get up!
No!
Goten! Stand back!
Goku! Stay with me!
♪
[GOHAN]
Huh?
Oh, it's no use. Come on!
What is that?
Look!
[gasps]
Oh, I see.
Both of you, get back!
And what? Leave our dad!
Just do it!
[gasps]
[panting]
Aw, Dad! You're okay!
Wait, what? What are you guys
doing all the way out here?
[GOTEN] Dad, we all
thought you were dead!
Easy there, buddy.
You're tickling Daddy.
[sighs]
What a relief.
You know, you're a
hard man to keep down.
You must've launched that
before you collapsed.
An insurance policy
in case he struck you down
and you needed the jolt
to revive your heart.
You're the most brilliant
idiot I know, Goku.
Where'd he go?
Why would he leave
in the middle
of a fight like that!
Well, he did kill me.
That makes sense.
Man. Hit really nailed me good.
For a second there,
I thought I was gonna
meet King Yemma again.
[chuckles]
For a guy who died,
you're sure in a good mood.
[PICCOLO]
I don't know why we even bother.
Listen, Dad. If Hit's gone,
then Gohan and I will find him.
I swear, we'll get back
at that bum for what he did!
You can't. This is between
me and Hit and no one else.
Okay, Goten?
But think about how sad
Mom will be if
he beats you again
and we can't bring you back.
Listen. I'll be fine, buddy!
I don't know, Dad.
Hey, trust me on this one.
Goku. How exactly
did he defeat you?
I thought you'd figured out
a way to stay ahead
of his Time Skip technique.
That's not what
he used against me.
This move was
even cooler than that!
Up to now, I'd only heard
stories about this guy.
If he could defeat you that fast
then he really is impressive.
When Hit means business,
you won't find
a tougher fighter.
Yeah, he pushes me.
I love having the chance
to face him at his best--
Gohan. Piccolo.
Please don't try to
talk me out of this, okay?
[GOHAN]
Mmm.
Suit yourself. You've risked
your life time and time again
for the survival
of this whole planet.
So fight who you want.
You've earned that privilege,
no matter how stupid
it might be.
No use arguing.
Go fight him, Dad!
Heh! Now we're talkin'!
But, this time, you better win!
Right.
Come on, gimme the fist bump!
I promise I'm not gonna die!
Go get 'em, Dad!
Show that guy who's the best!
I won't let you down, Goten!
Ha-ha!
All right, Hit!
Round two, let's get it on!
Your heart strike
didn't kill me!
[HIT] It doesn't matter
if you're back. I killed you.
I've fulfilled my contract.
[grunts]
I can hear his voice, but can't
sense his energy at all.
Uh oh, Dad. He's even
trickier than I thought he was.
He's an assassin, all right.
For those guys, hiding energy
is as easy as breathing.
Come on, Hit!
This isn't fair at all!
I was barely out!
Isn't there like, a three second
rule or something? Like food?
I hate to be rude, but I
don't like how this is going.
You're pissing me off!
And guess what?
Your move? I figured it out.
How do you like that, Hit?
Oh?
[ALL gasp]
I know you can't
stand that. C'mon.
[GOKU]
All this cover.
He'll love fighting
in a spot like this.
Until I met you, I didn't
know assassins were so shy!
Hm?
If I can feel his energy
coming from behind those trees,
then I bet he's hiding
in the other direction!
You have the ability
to create dummy copies
of your energy, don't ya?
Your copy lures me in, then the
real you attacks me from behind!
Now where's the real Hit?
Focus.
Over there?!
Damn it, I almost had him.
[GOKU] I'm sensing your
energy all over the place.
[GOKU]
Hm?
You just keep making
more copies.
You've got skills.
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU]
Huh!
[yells]
[groaning]
Ow, now that's smarts.
[laughing]
Guess I wrecked your
little plan to finish me off
with one strike. What a shame.
[HIT]
Hmm.
But I admit, I sure
wasn't expecting you
to attack me
through a solid tree!
Though on the bright side,
I'm learning more
about your attack.
I can't see it because
it's not normal energy.
[HIT] Understanding it
won't be enough.
Then face me in the open!
Why don't you stop
hiding in the woods?!
[HIT] You know, when you emit
your energy like that at night,
there might as well
be a lighthouse
guiding me right to you.
That's the reason I'm doing it!
[grunts]
[HIT chuckles]
In all my years, I've never
allowed a mark to escape.
I believe it.
That's right.
Every job I take, I finish.
And your best efforts won't
stop me from finishing you.
Gotcha!
[GOKU grunting]
[yells]
You're not hitting me
with that move again!
Impressive evasion. The third
time's the charm for you.
Now let's see
if you can dodge me!
--[GOKU] Hm!
--Uh?
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU]
Aw, damn it. I totally missed.
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU]
An afterimage?
No, it's different!
[screams]
[GOKU groaning]
I gotta hand it to you, Hit.
You're way stronger now
than you were at the tournament.
And you know what?
If you pushed yourself,
you could get even stronger.
I'm trembling. That's strange!
That tremor isn't
excitement, Goku.
You are afraid
I will kill you again.
Let's find out. Hmph!
[VEGETA grunts]
That's 97!
[panting]
That leaves three more drills.
I hope you have it in you.
How 'bout a steak instead?
I'll serve you the best steak
dinner in the universe!
Go on.
Instead of finishing
three more sparring drills,
I can have you eat like a king!
[WHIS] Is that what this
has come to, Vegeta? Bribery?
You know, I've already had
several cuts of steak
from your Earth bovines,
so it would have to be
quite the extraordinary
preparation
to make me agree to that.
[VEGETA]
Oh, come on! Wait, wait!
I'll drizzle it in my
grandmother's secret sauce!
[GRANDMA 72A]
Everyone loves Granny's special!
[BOY 72A, GIRL 72A]
Yay!
Did you say a secret
sauce from Granny?
That's what I said!
A prime cut that's topped with
the Vegeta family recipe!
It's a deal! Give me this steak
and I'll declare
your sparring complete!
Yes. Yes. Yes!
I figured out how to
dodge his attacks,
but I can't land my own.
This is tough.
I've just gotta keep trying!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU]
He doesn't even flinch!
My attacks just go
right through him!
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU]
First he copied his energy.
Now it's like
his body's copied, too!
[GOKU groans]
This fight's gone on
for a while, hasn't it?
Hit's going all out and
still hasn't finished Goku!
In a way, both men are having
a difficult time of it.
You understand Hit's
techniques don't you?
So why isn't Goku
able to make contact?
My Lord Champa.
Don't you remember his
Time Skipping move
from their first battle?
Oh yes, where he can stop time.
You're in the right ballpark,
but he's doesn't
actually "stop" it.
To be exact,
he can skip ahead in time.
And why's that mean
he can't be touched?
It's complicated, sir.
But basically, Hit can store up
all the time he skips over.
Hold on. Store it how?
In a temporary
space-time parallel to ours.
You might think of it
as a pocket dimension.
A place he can
move through without
matter here
interacting with him.
It's because Hit's
using this ability
that Goku can see him,
but can't touch him.
[CHAMPA]
Hmmm.
I'm a god and I don't
understand anything you say!
[GOKU panting]
All right, I'm pretty sure
I just figured out
how to handle you.
[HIT chuckles]
Handle me, if you can.
[yells]
What the hell?
[GOKU groaning]
[GOKU chuckles]
Looks like I grazed ya!
I'm not the least bit surprised.
You're quite impressive.
It feels like we're right back
at the tournament again,
doesn't it, my lord?
[CHAMPA] Whenever Grand Zeno
decides to hold his,
Hit should be
the odds-on-favorite.
And you made his path to
victory that much smoother
by having him take out Goku now.
What's that? I didn't
hire him to eliminate Goku.
I merely acted
as the intermediary
--for the actual client.
--Who? Tell me!
Sorry.
[GOKU]
So every time I attack,
you jump to
some other place, right?
That is correct.
But while you're
wherever it is you go,
you can't attack me, huh?
That's why the physical you
only blinks back
into this world the second
before you strike.
But I can attack in another way.
[GOKU]
Huh?
[GOKU groans]
Hit's introducing Goku
to every one of his powers.
This battle with
the Saiyan must've really
scratched an itch for him.
And here I thought
assassins were all business.
That is true. But now he's
not fighting as an assassin,
but as a martial artist.
My energy attacks
can jump as well.
I admit, you have
the upper hand.
In fact, you're always
one step ahead of me.
[grunts]
Is that smart!
But guess what, Hit.
If I'm going down,
I'm going down fighting!
When we fought, you went
down with nary a whimper!
[GOKU]
Huh?!
Lord Beerus? Whis? Vegeta?
What in the world
are you guys doing here?
We came to observe you.
[GOKU]
You mean, watch our fight?
And it seems we aren't
the only audience, either.
[GOKU]
Uh?
--[CHAMPA] Meh!
--[VADOS giggles]
[GOKU] Lord Champa and Vados?
When did you get here?
[BEERUS]
Hurry up and finish your fight.
[GOKU]
Hey! With all due respect,
it's you guys
who interrupted us!
All right. Now where
did we leave off?
[yelling]
There's no way!
He's shattering
the pocket thingy!
Oh.
Ka... me...
...ha... me...
Ha!
[HIT grunting]
[CHAMPA gasps]
[chuckles]
[HIT chuckles]
[laughing]
--[VEGETA] Ugh!
--Huh?
All right Kakarot, I can't
help but get the feeling
you enjoy fighting
this Hit bastard even more
than you enjoy fighting me!
[GOKU] Hey, that's not true!
Hit's trying to kill me!
I had no choice but to go at
him with him everything I got!
He wants to kill you?
Yeah, totally!
And who hired you?
If someone put a mark on him
you should at least tell us who!
I would never reveal a client.
No, of course not.
Maybe because the one
you're working for is Vegeta.
Are you crazy?!
You dare to insult me?
I'll end you.
[VEGETA] No-no-no-no-no!
I didn't mean that!
Uh, forgive me, Lord Beerus!
Think, Vegeta. Who else
would be behind this ploy?
[VEGETA gasps]
[GOKU chuckles]
[VEGETA]
Kakarot?
You were so desperate
for a good challenge
you put a bounty on
your own head just so
Hit would come and fight you!
[GOKU]
Ya got me! Heh.
I thought Vados hired me.
Yeah, sorry for the big secret.
I just figured
if I hired you directly,
you wouldn't have been
nearly as motivated
to fight as hard as you did.
You are one strange man.
Your obsession with battle
is quite profound.
That's a compliment, right?
[chuckles]
Hold on, Whis.
My lord? Is something wrong?
Fess up! Are you a player
in this farce, as well?
Yes, but only a small one.
Goku came to me first
but was so insistent,
I asked my sister for her help.
She was the one who went ahead
and hired Hit for him.
I don't like you running these
crazy schemes behind my back.
But, Lord Beerus, you were
the one who requested
that Goku be trained in case
there's another tournament.
Well, I didn't expect you
to help him call an assassin!
So, Goku. Is there
a deadline for this job?
[GOKU]
Nah, it's pretty loose.
[HIT] Good. I don't
like having onlookers.
Wait, are you leaving?
I'll kill you on my own time.
Always watch your back, Goku.
Crazy. Goku put
a hit on himself!
Lord Champa. It's time
for us to go, as well.
All right, fine.
Later!
Goku, its me!
Oh, Goku! I was so worried
about you, honey!
[GOKU]
Hey, it's okay. I'm okay!
But Piccolo told me
there was an assassin
coming after you!
What's that about?
Uh. My bad.
We gotta find the creep
paying to take out Goku
and put the screws to him! Goku!
--[GOKU] Uh.
--Any idea who it could be?
[GOKU]
Lemme think.
Well... I don't know...
Well, then! If I had to guess,
it's probably
that evil Frost guy!
[VEGETA grunts]
Promise me you'll never tell her
I put the hit on myself!
[VEGETA]
Hmph!
What is it?
Don't forget. You made
a promise to us!
We're still waiting for you
to get us that dinner
of prime cut steak!
And don't skimp on the sauce!
[VEGETA]
Nnngh!
[GRANDMA 72A]
Granny's special!
[VEGETA]
Crap! I don't have a steak,
let alone secret sauce!
Heck, I'm not even sure
I have a grandmother!
[VEGETA] Uh, it's coming!
I'm working on it!
The recipe's very involved!
[GOKU]
Until next time, Hit!
I'll be ready!
♪ Closing Song ♪
1, 2, 3, I'm hungry
Nothin' but fried rice fantasies
I got a passion for the dish
Nothin' compares to what it is
I don't get my fill
I'm like a monster
Those ingredients
No one could possibly resist
They got me so bewitched
Make it spicy and I can't say no
Seasoning is everything,
I think so
Bon Appetit
I'll burn the world
straight to the ground
If I can't have
that greasy mound
My hanger's not to be ignored!
1, 2, 3, I'm hungry
Nothin' but fried rice fantasies
I want fried rice,
I'm so hungryyyyyy-yeah!
[GOHAN]
Hey, folks! Gohan here!
I've got huge news!
They're making a
Great Saiyaman movie!
And guess what?
They hired me to be
my superhero alter-ego's
big screen stunt double!
Oh, no. Trouble on the set?
[SAIYAMAN laughs]
Evildoers everywhere
will know my justice!
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Gohan's Plight!
The Preposterous Great Saiyaman
Film Adaptation?!"
Say that three times fast.
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?