♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Goku ran out of
the massive, divine energy
his fellow Saiyans
had bestowed on him,
but incredibly,
the fight wasn't done.
Even though the Super
Saiyan God power expired,
your body has learned
from the experience
of fighting in god form.
Merely feeling that level
of power was enough
to push you to new heights.
In a sense, the god power
is part of you now.
The red glow of Saiyan
divinity may have left you,
but the strength now burns
within you like a flame.
Am I wrong?
Well, honestly I don't know.
And it doesn't matter, right?
All that matters is that
I can still win this thing.
[BEERUS]
Heh.
[GOKU chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
The battle's final round. Now!
[NARRATOR] "This Is
All the Power I've Got!
A Settlement between Gods."
[GOKU yells]
[chuckles]
[BEERUS]
Not good enough!
[GOKU]
How's this?
[GOKU yells]
[yells]
[BEERUS chuckles]
[GOKU]
Gotta move. I need air!
[yells]
[groans, growls]
Your turn!
[GOKU groans]
[BEERUS] What happened to
that supposed god-like power
we thought burned
inside you like a flame?
Is it so easy to blow out?
[groans]
Damn you!
[bellows]
Yes, that's better.
[yells]
[BEERUS] But you'll
still have to try harder
if you want that to reach me!
[BEERUS]
Have you forgotten?
I've mastered a technique
that neutralizes energy.
You simply can't compete.
[groans]
[GOKU]
Aw, crap!
[laughs]
Victory at last!
[GOKU]
Think again!
[GOKU bellows]
Give it up!
[yells]
Still more?
[GOKU yells]
Now I see. That ceremony was
only the start of the power.
Aah.
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU breathes heavily]
[BEERUS] The god you summoned
was a patchwork thing,
stitched together from the
strength of five other Saiyans.
And what you've created from its
template is perhaps even better.
Not a divine, but a level.
And it took a stunning
amount of my own power
to stop it. So I'll
be honest with you, Saiyan.
[quietly]
Just between the two of us,
for a moment there
you actually made me regret
getting obsessed with
that little dream of mine.
Heh. That's nice
of you to say, Beerus.
But it's not gonna
make me feel any better.
I know what this means.
I've let everyone down.
I really wanted to win this,
but I'm not going to get
another chance will I?
You'll destroy my planet.
It's all gonna be gone.
[BEERUS] This is how
I first attacked you.
Clearly it left you
with a hunger for vengeance.
So to make it poetic,
it will be my last shot too,
fueled by the passions this
battle has stirred within me.
You're done, Goku.
I've won at last.
No! It's not... over!
[screams]
You've ruined
my perfect ending,
you stubborn freak of nature!
Will you just stay down already?
My world's at stake.
I can't give up.
I don't really know
where my power ends now.
But as long as I have
the energy to move my body,
then that means I still haven't
hit you with everything yet.
[BEERUS] Is that right?
Then what are you waiting for?
Go on. Put it all
in one attack.
Then I can finally
be done with you.
We'll see.
[inhales]
[GOKU grunts]
That's quite the display.
Seems I'll need more than my
fists to take care of this one.
[GOKU bellows]
[GOKU]
Ka...me...
...ha...me...
Ha!
[yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[GOKU] What-- What the hell
is that thing?
Ah. Come on. I've never
seen anything like this.
Their blasts merged
into another energy orb.
But this one's even bigger!
I'm done making guesses.
We both know
what that's capable of.
I'll leave it at that.
[BEERUS]
Hm.
[GOKU]
No! Damn it.
[GOKU grunts]
[yells]
I won't let you!
Come now.
Stop fighting it. You know
you've reached your limit.
[GOKU]
Shut up!
[yells]
[GOKU] Hey Beerus,
I did it, didn't I?
In a way.
[GOKU]
You're a god. I get that.
Maybe the strongest
of them all.
[chuckles]
[groans]
But I don't care.
Not even you get to
tell me what my limits are.
[sighs]
Saiyan pride: it's boundless.
[VEGETA]
Boys! Out of the way!
[panting]
Hey. Nice catch, buddy.
Shut up! I can't believe
I lent you my power
just so you could
waste it all in defeat!
I'm sorry.
[PICCOLO]
Don't let your guard down yet!
Anyone who can still fight,
stand behind me and get ready!
[MR. SATAN]
Awww...
[phone rings]
[MR. SATAN]
Sorry, my bad! One second!
Hello? Look this is not
a good time, okay?
[PIIZA] What? But what about
the press conference?
Do I sound to you
like a man who's got time
for a press conference, Piiza?
[PIIZA]
'Kay, I'm confused.
And the reporters are
getting tired of waiting.
There's at least one of 'em
heading your way right now!
Huh?
[helicopter blades whirl]
[REPORTER 12A] There he is!
We've tracked down our hero!
With this exclusive
ambush interview,
we're going to find out
what's going on!
[MR. SATAN] I don't know
what to tell 'em!
This really is
the end of the world!
Let's try to keep
perspective. Okay, big guy?
[WHIS]
Nice fighting up there.
[BEERUS grunts]
You know, we could leave
things just as they are.
And we can get you straight home
into a warm, relaxing bath.
[BEERUS]
Huh?
But I suppose that's
too much to ask of you,
isn't it, my lord?
It is. A Destroyer must
keep his word, after all.
I agreed to spare this planet
if Goku could defeat me.
But if I won
I would show no mercy.
You stay out of it,
I'll handle him.
This is no time for an ego trip!
We all need to fight together
using whatever power we've got.
Shut your mouth!
This can't be it.
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU]
Beerus, please.
I'm asking you
one last time, Lord Beerus.
Please don't destroy my planet.
There's gotta be another way.
Can't you make an exception?
I'm beggin' you.
No. I cannot.
[ALL]
Huh?
[BEERUS snoring]
Hmm. It seems my lord
has fallen asleep.
[snoring]
[WHIS]
Not surprising, honestly.
He spends most of his time
sleeping and eating
and watching what you
would call "TV anime."
So to go from that
to a protracted battle
at maximum power
must take an exhausting toll.
[chuckles]
[WHIS] Just look at him.
He's out cold.
It appears that he won't
wake up for quite a long time.
And when he finally does
he will have forgotten
all about his threats
to destroy your world,
or at least that's
the most likely scenario.
You're only guessing?
[WHIS]
There can be no guarantees.
Oh great!
[BEERUS]
Pudding...
[snoring]
Though it's far less likely
he'll forget about the pudding.
If you could have some ready
the next time we come,
that could help
your cause immensely.
Well in that case I'll have a
whole swimming pool full of it.
But then I don't
want to hear him complain
if it's not the
wonder-food he's imagining.
Oh if he dislikes it
I doubt you'll hear anything
as he'd almost certainly
destroy the earth for that.
All right, aren't you
supposed to be leaving?
[WHIS]
Heh. Goku.
Uh, yeah?
Thank you very much
for playing with Lord Beerus.
It has helped more
than you can know.
Someday I'll repay you.
Awesome!
Take care of yourselves,
everyone. Bye!
[WHIS] Convincing
performance, my lord,
even if the snot bubble
is a bit over the top.
But you know, you can
stop pretending now.
I wasn't pretending, Whis.
I did fall asleep!
My mistake.
Earth is a curious
place, isn't it?
Has strange power
over Saiyans,
dampening their violent
instincts and honing
something the Kais call "noble."
It could be argued
that it's changed you
a little as well, my lord.
Care to repeat that?
[WHIS]
No, just mumbling nonsense.
Telling Goku that you were
using one hundred percent
of your power
was a very clever tactic
to draw out his full strength.
Yes, very effective.
Even though it wasn't true.
[BEERUS]
You could tell that? Hm-hm!
[KING KAI]
Bubbles, Gregory.
It all worked out
exactly like I thought.
I don't want to take
too much credit,
but Goku's an amazing guy.
He's even gained respect
from a Destroyer.
You might not expect it
from a guy who'd rather
train alone than go
to a birthday party,
but he sure has a knack
for making friends.
Ah!
Aw man. This has been
the worst birthday ever.
Can't we just act like
it never happened?
I mean it's bad enough I have
to be a year older, now this?
You must be completely
worn out, Dad.
--Yeah!
--Hey, uh.
[GOKU]
Uh...
[clears throat]
Look, Dad.
I know we all found out
in kind of a weird way,
so I want to
retry that announcement.
We're havin' a baby!
[GOHAN]
Uh...
[GOKU]
Gohan!
This food is great,
so make sure you guys
--eat plenty of it!
--Yeah. Okay!
--Hey, Dad?
--What, son?
What's it like being a god?
Was it awesome?
In a way I guess, but it
was just borrowed power.
And then at the end
I'm not sure what happened.
All I can say is that I still
wasn't strong enough to win.
Beerus was better
than I was, hands down.
But that Beerus guy
is the strongest fighter
in the whole universe, right?
It's so cool you're second best!
[chuckles]
[VEGETA]
Hmph!
It's your turn
next time, Vegeta.
What are you talking about?
The next time we
do that ceremony thing.
We'll make sure
you'll be the one who gets
the Super Saiyan God
power, just like you said!
[VEGETA]
I don't want it.
Only a fool would be happy
with second best.
[GOTEN growls]
[VEGETA] I'll improve
the only respectable way:
with my own power.
I'll become stronger than that
Super Saiyan God puppet show.
Stronger than Beerus.
And stronger than you!
Well if anyone can
do it, it's you, Vegeta.
[VEGETA] You think empty
compliments from a loser
mean anything to me?
[GOKU] But I'm serious.
You showed crazy power today.
Like when you
got all mad and yelled
"What did you do to my Bulma?"
[VEGETA] I did not--
I mean--How did you--?
Just as I thought.
Goku, you used your
Instant Transmission
to get back.
You were here for a while just
watching the fight, weren't you?
[GOHAN, MR. SATAN,
GOTEN, TRUNKS] Whaaa?
Yeah, you got me.
Sorry about that.
I wanted to watch
Lord Beerus in battle
so I could figure out
a good strategy against him.
But that was a waste of time,
since I never really
came up with anything.
[chuckles]
[MAI, SHOU]
This is how we row the boat.
[sigh]
[MAI] I like that breeze.
It feels nice.
[SHOU]
And that food was delicious.
All in all, a pretty great day.
Can't remember
the last time we said that.
Would you put a sock in it?!
It's not a good day
'til I get my wish!
You hear me, Dragon Balls?
You haven't seen
the last of me yet!
I look back
to when I was young
Reminisce on all that I've done
In my hands, I held
The dreams of my childhood,
that now've come to pass
So let's ride upon
the wind and journey to
A world we've never known
(It's a brand new story)
Now, a new chapter starts
Shining Star
In the night be
my compass and guide
Take me to where I belong
The warmth we once shared
Will always be there
Its magic lives on in our hearts
Shining Star
Give me strength
from your light up above
Show me the way to be brave
My hands still hold onto hope
that together we'll manifest
All that we dreamed of
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And after losing to Beerus
my training matters
more than ever!
But Chichi says I have to stay
home and do granddad stuff!
Whoa, what's going on
with Mr. Satan?
We've barely had
any time to rest
and there's already a new
alien species making threats?
I think there's a lot more
to this than meets the eye!
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Valiant Mr. Satan,
Work a Miracle!
A Challenge from Outer Space!"
Trust me, this one's
too weird to miss!