Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me go back to the start
Wishing on the starlight
In the sky, let's paint a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of God
Kyo-Let's☆Mo-Let's☆Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic
I don't care 'bout limits, no regret
Make me tougher even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo' try me
So-Zets☆Cho-Zets☆Dynamic!
Let's Go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going power pumpin' up
something greater waiting not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super!
Cabba the Saiyan contestant
from the Sixth Universe
challenged Vegeta!
But unlike Vegeta and Goku,
he lacked the ability to
transform into a Super Saiyan!
Teach me.
Teach me how to
transform like you do.
[VEGETA]
It's shameful.
Yet you dare...
...call yourself a Saiyan!
[NARRATOR] Cabba's weakness
infuriated Vegeta,
and the Saiyan prince
viciously attacked him,
until it awoke the
rage within him.
[CABBA]
I will... make you pay!
The best trigger for the Super
Saiyan transformation is anger.
So hold on to that
feeling you just had.
Right.
[NARRATOR] Vegeta's rage
was merely tough-love
in order to train
his fellow Saiyan.
[CABBA groans]
Making Vegeta the winner!
[NARRATOR] Frost, Magetta,
Cabba, all defeated!
Vegeta fights his
next opponent now!
[VEGETA]
So he's my next opponent.
[VEGETA] This guy seems
so calm, it's eerie.
I know hidden deep behind
that face is pure aggression.
He's strong. I can
sense his energy.
It's honed as sharp as a knife.
[chuckles]
[VEGETA] But no matter
how prepared he is,
it won't be enough to beat me.
[BEERUS]
Hm...
So his name is "Hit."
Is that right, Whis?
I know he's from
another universe,
but he seems familiar.
What's his deal?
From what I've been
able to glean,
he's a professional assassin.
In fact, he's the
most talented one
in the entire Sixth Universe.
Stories of his exploits claim
that not a single target
has ever escaped his reach.
They call him, "Never Miss Hit."
[GOKU]
Whoa!
If he's even half that good,
I'm impressed!
Well.
For the sake of winning my bet,
I need Vegeta to
come out on top.
But speaking purely as
a fan of a good fight,
I'm excited to see
these two in action.
Hm.
Wait, what? What's happening?
And begin!
[yells]
[whimpers]
Ha!
Wouldn't use that narrow
stance if I were you.
[growls]
See that?
Oh, yeah. His guard's perfect.
[chuckles]
This guy knows how to
handle himself in a fight.
[growls]
[VEGETA] That guard doesn't make
it easy for me to attack.
But I'm not going to stand
here all day, either.
He's fast! But it's nothing
I haven't seen before!
[yells]
[groaning]
What the--?
Holy crap!
That speed.
Uh-oh.
I second that, my lord.
[CHAMPA chuckles]
So far, so good.
Hit is quite impressive.
[growls]
[VEGETA]
I didn't even see him hit me.
Just like that,
I was on the ground.
Give up, now.
[VEGETA]
Yeah, right.
You're pretty cocky for someone
who's landed a single blow.
Agh! I'm gonna end
this fight now!
[yelling]
[gasps]
[VEGETA]
How'd he do that?!
He keeps blinking out of sight
right before he strikes.
Hey, Piccolo. Are you
seeing Hit's attacks?
No. Nothing.
[VEGETA]
What the hell is going on?
Is he cheating too?
[VEGETA] All I have to do is
strike just before he moves
and then his speed won't matter.
This fight is mine.
[VEGETA] I can't believe how
many hits he got on me!
[VEGETA groaning]
[VEGETA] Damn. I'm no match
for him if he keeps this pace!
[yells]
[gasps]
[growls]
You dare mock me?!
[VEGETA]
He struck from way over there?
And without preparation?
--[GOTEN] Whoa!!
--C'mon, Dad!
Vegeta, what's going on?
I don't see him moving;
you're just flying around!
[VEGETA groaning]
You only have one option left.
Surrender.
No! I will not!
[GOKU] Jaco, are you able
to see any of Hit's attacks?
Not a one.
I thought you had really good
eyes for this kinda thing.
Well, not here.
Look at that.
He's hitting his vital spots
with pin-point strikes.
He's certainly living up to
his "Never Miss Hit" nickname
and being the Sixth Universe's
top competitor.
[BEERUS] Once again,
they take the advantage
with a secret skill.
[CHAMPA]
Heh?
[chuckles]
[growls]
[VEGETA coughing]
[VEGETA]
I can't believe it.
How could I,
at Super Saiyan Blue,
not even lay a finger on him!
[VEGETA] Not being able
to see his attacks coming
has got me off balance.
But even after all
the blows he's landed,
the fact is, I'm still standing.
That tells me that while Hit's
got speed, he lacks strength.
Have you formulated
your strategy yet?
[chuckles]
My plan's to charge you head
on till you cry for mercy!
[VEGETA yelling]
[yells]
[VEGETA chuckling]
Just like that,
I neutralized your advantage.
[VEGETA yells]
How do you do this?
[ALL gasping]
[gasping]
Woo! Yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes!
[TD REF]
Uh!
It's against the rules for
me to kill him, correct?
[TD REF]
Uh, yeah.
Well then, what do we do now?
He can't very well announce
his surrender to me
if he's knocked out.
[TD REF]
Uh... Mm...
Okay.
The winner, by knockout,
Contestant Hit!
Of all the people I've fought
who've taken that
many of my attacks,
you are the only one to live.
[CHAMPA laughing]
[growls]
No. Vegeta lost.
Oh no!
[TRUNKS]
Dad!
Uh. Wait, Trunks!
I'm coming to help, too!
Krillin, hurry.
Go down there and give
Vegeta a Senzu Bean.
Yeah. On it.
After watching that,
I can tell you Hit's
moving at super speed,
and that's what's making
him so hard to beat.
Well, yeah, we've all noticed
that so far. C'mon, Jaco.
Yes, but have you noticed
what happens when he attacks?
It's more than just speed.
What? I'm not exactly sure
what you're telling me.
[JACO] In the middle of his
attack, he disappears.
Completely.
A fast, invisible man?
No, if that were it,
we'd see his clothes!
Oh. That's right.
So then maybe it's more like
when I use my Instant
Transmission?
Although doing it with
that kind of precision
is on a whole other level.
[JACO]
Hmm...
--[thud]
--[VEGETA] Damn it!
What a waste of time!
Here's an idea.
What if he's actually
time skipping?
What does that mean?
Yes! That is it!
Huh? I'm with Bulma.
What is that?
Granted, I've only heard rumors
of the ability to
manipulate time,
but apparently,
there are a few beings
out in the various universes
who can perform this "skip."
And I'm not talking about
much time, mind you,
only around a tenth of a second.
I don't understand anything
of what you're saying at all!
What he's saying is that there
are some people out there
who can jump ahead
in time just a tiny bit
and get the drop
on someone else.
Yeah, but how's
that enough time
to gain the advantage
in a fight?
True, a tenth of a second
doesn't sound like much,
but when combined with
superhuman speed,
like the kind Hit has,
that's plenty long enough for
him to surprise his opponent.
Hold on, Jaco!
Didn't you make a big stink
during the last Frieza thing
about how messing with time
is against Galactic Law?
Wait, is that true, Jaco?
I know what you're getting at,
and I don't like it!
Well good. Then go over
there and arrest him!
No way. We're out
of my jurisdiction.
And you call yourself
an elite patrolman?!
Yes, and since I'm super-elite,
my life is super important.
I'm also gonna sit out
this time travel issue.
[BULMA] Come on!
What is wrong with you guys?!
Yeah, I actually don't
want Hit arrested, either.
How'm I gonna fight him
if he's being booked
for some sort of time crime?
Argh! You are all so worthless!
[WHIS] Hit is even more
impressive than his reputation.
And I didn't expect
this tournament
to feature someone else who
is able to manipulate time.
[BEERUS grumbles]
Hit's gonna be a big
problem for us.
[laughing]
[growling]
Although, it seems like
Goku's plotting something.
[GOKU]
Hmm...
[TD REF]
All right, fans!
For our next match,
Contestant Hit will face off
against an old favorite
from the Seventh Universe:
Goku!
He's back in the tournament!
Well, how do you guys
think I should handle this?
By praying.
Oh, and to make it a good one.
That doesn't exactly help.
Oh, wait!
Got any tips for fighting
this guy, Vegeta?
How's this? Don't lose.
[GOKU]
What?
Vegeta, c'mon!
That's not good advice!
Yeah, you're on your own.
[GOKU] That's pretty cold, dude!
We are on the same team, y'know!
[VEGETA]
Hmph. As if I care about that.
[GOKU]
Uh. Ha.
I got myself into a real
pickle with this match.
You're the time expert.
If you have ideas for
how Goku can win this,
now would be the time
to go down and tell him.
An essential part of any
great fighter's training
is that he finds the
solution for himself.
But this isn't training,
this is a tournament!
Why don't we just
trust that Goku
will figure this out on his own?
How can you be so casual
after that Vegeta loss?
If Goku loses, too, then--
Well, we still have
the strongest man
in the Seventh Universe.
I know he's small,
but I hope you haven't
forgotten about Monaka.
All right.
You're only acting this way
to spite me, aren't you?
Oh-ho, I can't deny it, my lord!
I am still a little miffed
that you told a lie
to motivate Vegeta and Goku,
and that you filled out
our tournament roster
by bringing in such an
egregiously unhelpful amateur.
[WHIS laughing]
[BEERUS groans]
[PICCOLO]
So that's the explanation.
It's up to you, Goku.
[GOKU]
Hm.
[HIT]
Huh?
Begin!
All right, Hit. Let's get
started! Best of luck!
So you're not going to
start already transformed?
[GOKU]
Huh?
Oh, doing that uses
a lot of power,
so I always keep it in my back
pocket for later in the fight.
Besides, I still
haven't figured out
a winning strategy
against you yet,
so don't get mad if all I do
right now is stall for time.
You showing your cards
tells me... that you're young.
[GOKU chuckles]
Well, I appreciate
the compliment,
because I'm actually
a grandfather!
That's young to a man
who's a thousand years old.
[yelps]
A thousand years old?
Whoa, for real?
You really are my senior,
and then some!
Here. Let's start this over.
I look forward to
our fight, sir.
[chuckles]
Now it's time to fight!
[yells]
[yelping]
[groaning]
I definitely didn't
see that one coming,
and your attacks are really
hard for an old guy.
All right. Attack Plan B!
[GOKU yelling]
[yelling]
[GOKU panting]
Ow! That really hurt!
Try all you like, it won't work.
And it doesn't matter how
tough you are, either.
If I keep striking
your critical points,
you will eventually die.
I recommend you surrender.
[chuckles]
Now why would I
surrender, old man?
After all, I just got my
first hint of the secret
to beating you!
Oh? A hint?
Yeah. A hint.
I think you're bluffing.
All right.
Then why don't you
call me on it?
Try.
[yelling]
[HIT]
Hm?
[GOKU chuckles]
Well, well. How 'bout that?
I just beat your
time-skipping attack.
[GOKU]
Try to dodge me now!
[BOTH gasp]
[GOKU yelping]
I did it! I just hit
you in the face!
Lucky shot.
[GOKU]
Maybe, maybe not.
[HIT]
Hm?
[chuckles]
So... let's see if you're right.
[yelling]
Still lucky?
What?
[chuckles]
That was amazing!
How did Goku do that?
Oh, wow.
Now it looks like Hit's the one
who can't keep up with Goku!
Yeah, I know!
Oh no! C'mon, Hit!
[BEERUS gasps]
[gasping]
[growls]
Your whole advantage
is moving a tenth of a
second forward in time
for a surprise shot.
So then I just anticipated,
guessing where your
moves will take you
after you start
your attack,
based on watching
your fighting style.
A new phase of the fight begins.
[GOKU chuckles]
You're finally taking this
thing seriously, aren't ya?
Then, I'll be doing
the same, Hit!
Now I'm going all out!
Whoa–oa
It's hard to say - don't wanna stay
I twist and fight, can't find my way
I must believe, that fear and trouble
can even be fun if you think the right way
Whoa–oa
Whoa
I don't wanna draw the line, I gotta see it through some way
Fight for what I know is mine, the dream I had of me that day
Whoa–o-oa
Whoa–oa–oa
Don't care if they call me greedy,
If they ever make it make it through,
Don't care if they laugh at me,
cus' I will make the dream come true
Whoa–oa
Whoa–oa–oa
Hey, it's me, Goku!
Well, I may have cracked Hit's Time-Skipping
but the strongest warrior in the 6th Universe
won't go down without a fight.
When this guy cranks it to 11,
he's even better than I imagined!
So, once again, I'm gonna have to scramble.
Thankfully, I've got a secret move
that I've been hiding from everyone!
Next time on Dragon Ball Super:
Trust me, you don't want to...skip...this one.