♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Trunks and Goten got stuck
on Monaka's space truck,
ending up on planet Pot-au-feu!
[yells]
It's been way too long
since I've seen you!
So how have you been?
[NARRATOR] Knowing where
Monaka was headed,
Bulma sent Vegeta and Jaco
to pick up the boys.
But when they got there,
they found Goten, Trunks,
and their new friend, Potage,
under attack by
strange, purple men!
Vegeta rescued them
all in the nick of time,
but ended up covered in
purple alien goo!
[VEGETA coughs]
[VEGETA DUPLICATE]
This is why you're weak!
[NARRATOR] Vegeta's run-in
with this strange liquid
resulted in the creation
of some kind of duplicate!
What the hell?
[NARRATOR]
The story continues, now!
"Vegeta Disappears?!
Menace of the Duplicate Vegeta!"
[VEGETA DUPLICATE chuckles]
All right. Just who
the hell are you?
And why do you
look exactly like me?
It's more than just looks.
I possess all of your energy
and fighting skills.
I am now the only Vegeta
in the universe.
You're nothing but
an old shell I left behind.
"A shell you left behind"?
I don't have time for this
disrespectful nonsense!
You're nothing but
a pathetic imposter!
And now you're going to hell!
[yells]
[laughs]
Damn it. I can't.
Is this what you'd like
to do to me? Too bad.
[gasps]
Oh, no!
Gallick Gun!
[yells]
What is going on here?
Keep denying it all you want,
I am the real Vegeta
while you are nothing!
That's right! Who would
have ever thought
a mortal creature
that walks on two legs
could possess such great power!
This is the strongest
duplicate I have ever seen!
Go on. Absorb the energy of the
other four humanoids as well!
And make you
first target that boy.
What?
That's Trunks.
Hurry! Absorb their power
before they have
the chance to run away!
[VEGETA DUPLICATE grunts]
[VEGETA]
No, stop!
He-he. It's super elite
galactic patrolman time!
Don't worry about
these monsters, guys.
I got this one.
Trunks, go!
--[TRUNKS] Goten!
--[GOTEN] Right.
[JACO] As the galaxy's
best and brightest,
I'll finish them off
with a special move!
[GRYLL DUPLICATE growls]
[JACO]
Wait. Where'd they go?
[yells]
You're going to pay for that!
[GRYLL DUPLICATE]
Aah! I can't see!
Whew! That was a close one!
Hm?! I forgot my suit
only has enough energy
to do the rocket escape
move once a day.
But if I hadn't used it,
I'd be toast, so no regrets.
[yells]
That's it.
Before this day is done,
we will absorb all their powers!
Uuugh! I save their bacon
and those ungrateful people
just leave me behind!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Now, we need to get
to the bottom of this imposter!
His ability to use
the Gallick Gun makes him
far more than
just a look-a-like.
Ahem.
Allow me to fill in
some of the blanks.
What's been attacking us
is Superhuman Water.
Hold on. Superhuman Water?
Yes.
How've you heard of it?
[JACO] I'll answer that,
but first I need to
get something off my chest.
[ALL coughing]
As you know, I'm a super
elite galactic patrolman!
How dare you abandon me
to those monsters
after I save your skins!
I asked you a question,
now answer it!
Aah! Right!
[POTAGE chuckles]
[JACO] Um, from what I remember,
it's a miracle water
that makes you hundreds
of times stronger.
[chuckles]
Most people think it's a legend!
Hm! You only know
a fraction of the story!
Wait, wha...?
Don't waste our time,
old man--tell us!
The Superhuman Water.
That's one of many names
given to it by off-worlders.
Its real name is Comméson.
[GOTEN, TRUNKS, JACO]
Comméson?
[POTAGE]
It was developed right here
on Pot-au-feu for self-defense.
So, it's a weapon then.
Yes. Biological warfare.
Long ago,
we Pot-au-feuans were weak.
That is, until we discovered
a liquid that could
stop our enemies
by absorbing their powers.
Soon, we were able
to protect our planet
from whole armies of invaders.
The scale of
Comméson's effectiveness
appeared to have no end.
Over the years, it absorbed
the power of countless enemies,
turning each one
into a duplicate
who would fight on our side.
But absorbing that much evil
corrupted the Comméson.
And what began as
a tool for self-defense
developed its own
aggressive personality.
[roars]
[POTAGE]
The duplicates it created
were no longer ours to control,
but rather soldiers
for the Comméson itself.
It had become
an independent life-force,
an army, wholly consumed by
the need to absorb power
wherever it could be
found on this planet.
But since these duplicates
looked like powered up
versions of the people
who were absorbed, word spread.
"Pot-au-feu is home to
a 'miracle water!'" they said!
And these rumors drew
even more invaders,
feeding a vicious cycle.
[MONAKA, GOTEN]
Uh...
I kinda knew what
I was talking about.
[POTAGE] But here's where the
story gets really interesting.
If the Comméson's power
had been allowed
to keep multiplying
at that rate,
it would have
decimated Pot-au-Feu.
And then spread like a plague
across the entire universe!
With the fate of
all creation in the balance,
we Pot-au-feuans developed
a sealing antidote,
then tricked the Comméson
into ingesting it
by treating ourselves
with the seal
and allowing the Comméson
to absorb us all.
I, Potage,
am the last of my race.
And for one hundred years,
I have nobly guarded the prison
protecting this universe from
the dreaded Comméson.
Victory! All thanks to me!
♪ I am a legend! A living
legend! Legendary Potage! ♪
And that's the full story
of Superhuman Water
and how I saved the universe.
[MONAKA, GOTEN, TRUNKS, JACO]
Uuuh...
You've guarded it
for a hundred years?
Um, Mr. Potage.
How old are you?
I may look old, but I feel
a hundred years younger
than I actually am!
[MONAKA, GOTEN, TRUNKS, JACO]
Aah!
And then those robbers appeared
and screwed it all up, huh?
Right. Gryll and his men,
like so many others before them,
had been seduced
by false tales
of the water powering them up.
Those vandals broke the seal
on the Comméson!
[yells, groans]
Oh, no! What's happening?!
[GRYLL gasps]
[GRYLL DUPLICATE]
And now the rest.
[GRYLL GOONS groan]
--Goten!
--Uh?
[TRUNKS, GOTEN]
Hyaa!
[GRYLL GOONS groan]
--[POTAGE sighs]
--[TRUNKS] C'mon, move!
[yells]
We must stop the spread,
and once again
seal away the Superhuman Water.
The fate of the universe
is at stake!
Those stakes aren't new to us,
but if we're gonna help,
there's something
I need to know.
What's wrong, Dad?
That imposter
not only looks like me,
he has all my powers, too.
So for all intents and purposes,
this universe is now
also home to an evil Vegeta!
Correct, you are.
However, he hesitated.
When Gryll told him
to absorb Trunk's powers.
Why is that?
He's supposed to be
all evil water, right?
[POTAGE]
Hm-hm-hmm!
For this, you can thank
we Pot-au-feuans'
technical skill. Your duplicate
hesitated because
your personality is now
part of his character, too.
My personality, huh? I see.
Since I'd never take
a shortcut to power
by absorbing someone else's,
let alone my own son's.
Aside from
his emotions, though,
his mind is still
under complete control.
That weak-willed fool.
I'm ashamed to even think
about my duplicate
being the puppet
of some other master!
Tch! One more question.
What happens to people after
the Superhuman Water
takes their powers?
Well, it's complicated.
C'mon, tell us!
They die, don't they?
How much time do I have?
[POTAGE] When your body
starts disappearing,
you'll have five minutes left.
Maybe less.
It's probably happening to
those robbers right about now.
What? What's going on?
Why're we disappearing?
Somebody save us!
[JACO] This is bad!
Who cares about Gryll?
But if Vegeta goes,
Bulma will hold it over me
for the rest of my life!
We have to find a way
to keep her from blaming me!
[GOTEN, MONAKA, POTAGE groan]
[clears throat]
To reverse the effect,
we have to destroy the copy.
Oh, boy.
You mean
Vegeta's duplicate, right?
[VEGETA] And defeating him will
be just as hard as defeating me.
[GRYLL DUPLICATE]
Where did those humanoids go?
We'll find them eventually!
Huh?
[BOTH]
What took ya so long?
We've been waiting for you!
Look, there they are!
Stepping forward to fight us,
even though it's certain
he'll be defeated.
I've raised
one brave little boy.
Trunks! You really think
you can stop me?
Uh.
Don't let him get to ya!
We're gonna take down
that imposter!
You're right. Let's do this!
Ready when you are, Trunks!
[BOTH]
Fu... sion! Ha!
Dun-da-da-dun!
Say hi to
all-powerful Gotenks!
They became one?
[VEGETA DUPLICATE]
Hm!
I'll let you take it from here.
Liquid phony!
You won't be absorbing
any more power now that
Gotenks is here to stop you!
[VEGETA DUPLICATE]
Heh.
[GOTENKS grunts]
Say your prayers, imposter!
You're going down!
Oh, really?
Attack any way you want!
All right!
How about a Miracle Punch!
Miracle Kick!
Let me show you what
a real attack looks like!
[groans]
[GOTENKS]
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
If that attack didn't work
too well, how about now?
[GOTENKS yells]
[hollers]
[bellows]
Aw yeah!
Let's see him fight
Super Saiyan Three Gotenks!
Uh-oh.
Hey, you okay? Monaka?!
[VEGETA grunts]
Not only can they fuse,
they have the ability
to transform to a new
power level? I want that!
Quit stalling! Go smack
that jerk while he's off-guard!
[GOTENKS]
All right, all right. Round two!
You're no match
for my fast attacks!
Great Special Rolling Kick!
--[JACO] Wow, awesome!
--[POTAGE] Extraordinary!
Ha! Not so special.
I got more! Here's my
Super Special Crusher Hammer!
Please.
[yells]
Headache much?
You know that had to hurt.
Did a mosquito land on me?
Well, in that case...
Finish Special!
Say hello to my Flash Strong...
...Big Bomber!
Direct hit!
[POTAGE, JACO whimper]
Ha. That's nothing
to be scared of.
You thought that would stop me?
Uuuh! That didn't
even leave a mark!
It's no use! That duplicate
is far too strong!
I'd love to help,
but what I love even more
is not putting my self at risk.
Ah! Vegeta, your body
is starting to disappear!
I'm afraid that means
you haven't got much time left!
That's bad.
Ha! My old shell.
I like your disappearing act!
Hey! Now that Gotenks is
distracted, go absorb his power.
All right! Bring it on! Aaah!
[groans]
[yells]
[ALL yell]
[GOKU] All right, I think
I'm back to normal!
Now I gotta
get something to eat.
Uh. I hope you plan on
doing the dishes later on.
It's been too long since
I've had your cooking, King Kai.
Oh, yeah?
[chuckles]
I forgot how plain it is.
Hey, now! Haven't you heard
not to bite the hand
that feeds you?!
Because I'm actually feeding
you, so don't complain!
Huh?
Gotenks is there?
[GOKU]
Gotenks?
Hold on. I sense
Vegeta with him, too.
It feels like--wait,
are they fighting each other?
[yells]
[groaning]
[grunts]
Uh, oh no!
He's vanishing!
[GOTENKS groaning]
[GOTENKS groans]
Ha. Of course the son
can't defeat his father.
And while I'm proud
of your courage,
this is where your fight ends.
[GOKU]
That's enough, Vegeta!
Were you seriously
gonna kill our sons?
Is that Kakarot?
Kakarot?
[VEGETA]
That purple guy is not me.
Aah! Uh. But... Uh...
I count two Vegetas here.
Uh, okay.
But who's the real one, though?
You're purple, which is weird.
But he's see-through,
which is also weird!
Can somebody tell me
what's going on?
Dad, all you need
to know is he's bad
and you need to stop him!
If you don't, the real
Vegeta's gonna disappear!
[GOKU] Uuum! Oh, boy. Can you
start over, from the top?
[VEGETA] We don't have time to
draw you a picture, you fool!
--Huh?
--Just do as the boys said,
and defeat the slimeball in the
next three minutes, or I die!
But know that he's
my exact duplicate,
which means he'll give you
as much trouble in a fight
as I do. And there's
a pretty good chance
that he'll defeat you.
Oh, man! I don't understand
what's going on here,
but I just gotta defeat
this purple guy, right?
[VEGETA DUPLICATE]
Kakarot, I never thought
when I woke up this morning
the day would end
with the two of us
dueling like old times.
[GOKU] I know! I'm kinda
excited about it, too!
[VEGETA DUPLICATE laughs]
All right! That guy's
power level is amazing.
I can't wait to absorb him!
Wait, Dad! Be careful!
These purple guys have the
ability to steal your energy!
I'm not gonna fight dirty!
I want this duel to be a
one-on-one, stand up fight.
Kakarot! Prepare to
taste defeat at my hands!
Forget your own grudge!
Just use our powers
to make him part of us!
You just stay out of it!
If you interfere in this fight,
I'll destroy you.
Ah! It is you who will pay
for disobeying us.
Watch!
[VEGETA DUPLICATE groans]
What's wrong?
The Comméson wants to
destroy whatever freewill
the duplicate has left!
How rude.
Only a fool tries to control me!
I don't take orders
from man or water!
Uuh!
No! You can't!
You answer to me!
[groans]
How could this have happened?
Whoa.
I can't believe it;
the individual duplicate
broke free of its control!
[VEGETA]
Hmph!
[VEGETA DUPLICATE]
There's no one to stop us now.
Let's get this fight started.
I'm ready when you are,
fake Vegeta.
Fake? Bring it on, Kakarot!
Ha! All right,
I'm not gonna hold back.
The strongest guy in
the universe is watching.
I wanna show him my best!
[VEGETA grunts]
--[POTAGE, JACO, TRUNKS] Whoa.
--[GOTEN chuckles]
[GOKU]
Yeaaah! Huh?
Don't you hold
anything back now!
C'mon, get up!
Ow! Purple Vegeta really
does fight like real Vegeta.
Why're you surprised?
He literally
drained all the power
and fighting skills
right out of me!
Wow! Wish I saw that.
But if that's true,
that means I just have to
approach fighting him
like I'm fighting you
at your usual strength.
Okay, real Vegeta.
Do I officially
have your permission
to beat up fake Vegeta?
Of course you do!
But whether you actually
can defeat me
is something
I'm much less sure of.
An all-out fight with Vegeta
with both our lives at stake?
Now that I'm healthy again,
this sounds like a ton of fun!
Oh, yes; I couldn't agree more.
[GOKU chuckles]
[VEGETA DUPLICATE chuckles]
♪ Closing Song ♪
Wow
It's hard to say
Don't wanna stay
I twist and fight,
can't find my way
I must believe, that fear
and trouble can even be fun
if you think the right way
Wow
I don't wanna draw the line
I gotta see it through some way
Fight for what I know is mine
The dream I had of me that day
Wow
Don't care if they
call me greedy
If they hate me, make me blue
Don't care if they laugh at me
'Cause I will make
the dream come true
Wow
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
I can't believe
this Vegeta faker
actually has the same powers
as the real one!
Leave it to me, Vegeta.
I'll make that
evil imposter pay the price
of stealing your identity!
Wait, what?
Even though he's
making you disappear,
you won't let him lose to me?
Whose side are you on?
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Goku vs. The Duplicate Vegeta!
Which One Is Going to Win?!"
You don't wanna miss this one!