♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the Seventh Universe
battled hard against
the two remaining warriors
from the Eleventh.
The Pride Trooper Top achieved
an entirely new level of power
as he took on the mantle
of a Destroyer.
With his Energy of Destruction
shielding him,
it appeared the Seventh
had no way to win.
But the Saiyan Prince
refused to quit.
[VEGETA] Unlike you, I won't
abandon all that to play god!
[TOP gasps]
[VEGETA yells]
Our universe will remain,
no matter the price.
Hakai!
[yelling]
[NARRATOR] After Vegeta resorted
to the explosive technique
that had once
cost him his life,
Top's defenses were
finally breached,
and the new Destroyer
was knocked out.
[gasping]
It's stunning you could
find so much power
without sacrificing your ideals.
You've fought hard to
defeat Top. Well done.
[VEGETA growls]
Heh.
[GOKU grunting]
[yells]
[NARRATOR]
Only one opponent is left,
and Jiren seems to be
unleashing his true power...
Now!
[NARRATOR]
"The Approaching Wall!
A Hopeful Final Barrier!"
[yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[A17 grunting]
[VEGETA growls]
[JIREN yelling]
[JIREN yells]
[GOKU grunting]
Uh?!
Whoa! Look, look,
Jiren's on fire!
Like actual fire!
That is so cool!
But not actually cool!
His energy's outta this world!
What is this guy?
Some kind of monster?
Ha!
[GOKU, A17 grunting]
I never would've guessed he
was holding back this much!
Man! If the force of his energy
is reaching us up here,
how does it feel to them?
[ROSHI]
Jiren's power is unbelievable!
He's in a league of his own!
[TIEN] How are Goku and the
others supposed to compete?
[VEGETA] So, now that your
little friends are gone,
you're finally getting serious.
[A17]
Uh.
Vegeta?
[VEGETA] It's about time.
Though it won't change much.
I'll crush you, too,
and claim my prize.
Come now. Don't be foolish.
You have no chance against me,
especially in your current form.
[VEGETA]
Don't you shrug me off!
That idiot!
[VEGETA, GOKU yell]
[JIREN growls]
[A17 gasping]
[A17 screams]
[A17 yells]
[VEGETA, GOKU, A17 grunting]
[JIREN]
That's... enough.
[VEGETA yells]
You'll pay for your impudence.
[VEGETA groans]
[A17, GOKU groan]
[grunting]
See how you like this!
[A17 yells]
[VEGETA yelling]
[panting]
[gasps]
What the--?
[A17 groans]
You stay in your lane, Android.
I didn't ask you for your help.
Jiren, I'll defeat you myself!
[yelling]
[VEGETA yells]
What the hell are
you looking at?
[yelling]
[GOKU grunting]
[JIREN]
Hm?
[VEGETA]
We're not done!
[VEGETA yells]
An impressive strike.
With attacks like this, I can
see how you outmaneuvered Top.
[groaning]
But that won't get you close
to winning against me.
[screams]
[GOKU]
Vegeta!
[GOKU groaning]
[yells]
[JIREN yelling]
[GOKU groans]
[growls]
[groaning]
He cut through Goku's
Kamehame-Ha Wave
like it was butter!
How can he exert that much
force with just an uppercut?
He's a beast. This is crazy!
[TOP]
Hmm...
Uh?
[A17]
Hold on. I got something for ya.
[yells]
17!
[VEGETA gasps]
[A17 groaning]
In retrospect, maybe blasting
myself wasn't such a great idea.
[gasps]
Look at his back--
it broke through!
How dare you!
Heh. Though seeing that rip
in your snazzy outfit
makes it all worthwhile.
You will suffer!
Ha!
[yelling]
[gasps]
Hey, that looked pretty insane.
Are you okay, 17?
Yeah, all things considered.
I gotta hand it to you,
you really know how to fight.
And thanks to that big shot
you landed against him,
I'd say we've got ourselves
a new strategy.
[GOKU]
If we launch attacks that big,
and his defenses are down,
we can actually do some damage.
[A17]
Right.
Maybe if we use combo attacks
to create an opening,
then unload with techniques even
higher-powered than that...
Yeah. It might be just what
we need to knock him out.
I'll play along, if it means
finishing this punk!
[GOKU]
I'll charge in with Vegeta,
and we'll find some way
to knock him off guard.
Once we do...
[A17]
Say no more.
You done concocting your
little plan of attack?
We're going to pay you
back for all the trouble
you've caused us, and
with compound interest!
[A17 grunts]
That's right, Jiren--it's
our turn to take control.
[A17]
Hm.
[A17 yells]
[JIREN yells]
[VEGETA, GOKU yell]
[VEGETA, GOKU groan]
[VEGETA, GOKU grunting]
Here goes! Ha!
Huh. You really thought
you would fool me twice?
The hell--?
Damn that guy!
Ha!
[JIREN grunts]
[A17 grunting]
[A17 groans]
It isn't working!
Vegeta, maybe if all three of us
attack him at once. Let's go!
[GOKU]
Ha!
[A17 yelling]
[VEGETA yelling]
[GOKU yells]
[yells]
[yelling]
[JIREN growls]
[A17 groaning]
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU groaning]
[panting]
I can't believe he fought
off our combined attack.
How can Jiren really
be that strong?
[A17 grunting]
The time has come.
[FRIEZA grunting]
[FRIEZA] Your team pushed me
around, made me play the fool!
Did you think I'd
let that stand?
[FRIEZA groans]
[groaning]
There's no need to follow
the rules any more.
You're the only one left!
Take what you deserve.
Death at the golden
hands of Lord Frieza!
[gasping]
[screams]
[JIREN]
Hm?
So you actually think
you can face me alone.
What I think doesn't matter--
it's the only choice I've got.
The Seventh has to survive.
[groaning]
Wait, can he...?
I guess we'll find out.
What if you did somehow prevail?
Uh?
What do you expect to
get out all of this?
Tell me, what great wish would
you ask of the divine dragon?
When I get the
Super Dragon Balls
I'm gonna keep it real simple.
I just want to take my family
on a nice little cruise.
[BELMOD]
Is that supposed to be a joke?
[A17]
You see me laughing?
How 'bout you, Jiren,
what would you choose?
It seems to me all you want is
to be known as the strongest.
Or is there more?
I too have a wish
to ask of the dragon.
Do you know his wish?
For years his heart
has clung to one thing.
And that must be it.
Tell us, Belmod.
Perhaps it's time
that all of you know
the true reason behind Jiren's
obsession with strength.
[birds chirping]
[footsteps]
[JIREN laughing]
[gasping]
[gasps]
[BELMOD] Jiren's parents were
slaughtered by a powerful foe.
[JIREN gasps]
No!
[BELMOD]
But the boy was spared.
Rescued by a man who would
go on to become his master.
From that day on,
Jiren devoted himself to
the path of righteous power,
determined to forge
himself into a steel wall
no marauder could break.
In time he made friends,
a new community,
and he followed
his master's way.
Then, that same
villain returned.
Jiren and his new brothers
in arms stood against him.
The boy was sure this
time they would win.
But the foe was too strong,
and Jiren watched as his
friends were slain, one by one.
Even Jiren's master lost his
life in the merciless battle.
[JIREN]
No!
[BELMOD] Jiren tried to
regroup and keep fighting,
but none of the other remaining
students would join him.
With no hope of rescue,
the people in his land
were forced to submit
to this cruel conqueror,
and Jiren was left all alone.
[JIREN wails]
Jiren suffered untold grief
when those he trusted
walked away, betraying their
principles for the easier path.
After that, his view
of the world changed.
He gave up trusting anyone.
[TOP exhales]
As he saw it, there was
only one great truth.
That might makes right.
And that sheer strength
determines all.
Only victories
ensure allegiance.
Subdue and others will follow.
Having feelings just
gets in the way.
I have become enamored
with his singular resolve.
This colossal yearning
for strength,
built on a bedrock of
suffering and desolation.
Fascinating.
So that's what you'll wish for.
Here I was wondering
what a heartless machine
could ever want.
But as it turns out, you're a
lot more human than I assumed.
Heh. Belmod may like to talk.
I do not.
[A17]
Trouble trusting people?
Because it seems like
your teammates
have been trusting you,
but you've just been using
them to get what you want.
Quiet! You don't know
anything about it, okay?
[A17] You're stuck in the past.
That's all you care about.
--[A17 gasps]
--[JIREN grunts]
Oh, I'm sorry, did I just strike
a nerve and make you angry?
[groans, screams]
[yelling]
Let me guess...
You think if you win, everything
can go back to the way it was!
You'll have the dragon
undo what happened.
[JIREN]
Nonsense.
[A17 yelps]
[GOKU groaning]
Oh, damn it all!
I trust no one, even dragons.
I want the power to
bend all to my will.
Even bend time itself.
Now the burden of weakness
falls upon you!
[JIREN grunting, yells]
Goku, no! Come on, buddy!
17!
Come on. Get up!
[VEGETA, GOKU grunting]
[yelling]
What's he doing?
Has he gone mad?
[GOKU] At least get yourself
out of the way!
17, no! That's crazy!
[yells]
You don't have the power
to hold back his attack!
You have to get
out of there now!
[A18]
Now! 17!
[A17]
Hey, Goku... Vegeta...
[GOKU grunts]
Uh?
[A17] I'm giving up my dream
of that cruise. You owe me.
There. I bought you some time.
Sacrificing myself
to help other people.
Look at me, being all "human."
[screams]
[yelling]
[A17]
Hmph.
[yelling]
[KRILLIN gasping]
[ALL gasping]
I can't believe it.
That attack could've blasted
Goku and Vegeta away.
Yes, and then all three of them
would have been
out of the fight!
You have escaped elimination.
You should be grateful
to your ally.
He has sacrificed himself for
your weak and miserable hides.
[GOKU grunting]
[VEGETA grunts]
17. You paid that price
just so we'd have a few
more moments to recover.
Bastard Android. Must've been
planning that from the start.
[GOKU]
Thanks, 17. We owe you.
[GOKU groans]
Why did you go and do that?
You just had to play the hero.
Impressive.
He made those barriers
to shield Goku and Vegeta,
but he knew that alone
wouldn't be enough.
So he blew himself up
to counter Jiren's attack
and disperse the
destructive energy.
[ALL grunt]
But then that would mean that...
Yes, that's right.
Even though Jiren
initiated the attack,
17 made the choice
to self-detonate,
which means that he
actually eliminated himself.
Therefore Contestant
Jiren of the Eleventh
will not be incurring a penalty.
17...
You still want more?
[panting]
Jiren, I hope you're ready.
'Cause I'm going to knock
the hell out of you.
[NARRATOR] Shielded by
17's explosive final effort,
the Saiyans have managed
to hang on for another round.
Now, Vegeta is summoning
all the power he can
to face Jiren once more.
But how can he hold up against
this seemingly unbeatable foe?
[VEGETA] Don't you dare
look down on me!
[NARRATOR] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super!
Whirling all around
and then back again
The song that connects you
to the heavens
Strength that goes
beyond all measure
Expanding to a beat
that won't end
The meteors fall like rain drops
Astrological tears
from my eyelids
A strong emotion
from deep within
Has been awakened
A spark of possibility
Shines softly like a star
in the night sky
A wish from long
ago now shoots by
And I'm awakened
A never-ending melody,
so enchanting
You're always the one
who makes me tremble
The meteors keep falling down
Surging right into my heart
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Number 17 gave everything he had
to keep me and Vegeta
in the Tournament,
which means it's up
to us to keep fighting
and save our universe
from getting erased!
I don't care how
strong Jiren is,
we've gotta use whatever
motivation we can,
dig deep and figure
out how to win!
Let's do this, Vegeta!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super,
"To the Noble, Proud End!
Vegeta Falls!"
Make sure you
don't miss it, okay?