♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the Tournament of Power
moved into its final stretch,
with only the Seventh and
Eleventh Universes remaining.
As the two powerful teams
clashed for the right
to survive, Frieza
struggled against Dyspo.
Gohan jumped in to
help his teammate,
and the odd pair
worked together.
But even with their combined
assaults, Gohan and Frieza
still couldn't counteract
their opponent's hyper speed,
until Gohan came up
with a daring trap.
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOHAN]
Go!
[GOHAN, DYSPO grunting]
[GOHAN yells]
[DYSPO groans]
What the--?!
Frieza!
Your strategy worked.
Well done, team leader.
And now we get to the fun part.
[NARRATOR] To ensure that
Dyspo would be eliminated,
Gohan sacrificed himself,
and now only six fighters
remain in the ring.
With the clock winding down,
the Tournament of Power
continues... now!
[NARRATOR]
"A Commanding Presence!
The Advent of Top
the Destroyer!"
[GOKU, VEGETA grunting]
[GOKU]
Get ready, Vegeta!
[VEGETA]
Don't give me orders!
[GOKU grunting]
[VEGETA]
Final Flash!
[grunts]
[GOKU, VEGETA grunt]
[JIREN yells]
[VEGETA groans]
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU grunts]
[BOTH panting]
This is absurd!
We hit him with all that,
and the bastard still isn't
even breaking a sweat!
[GOKU]
Yeah.
That's what makes him
so awesome.
You're kidding me.
Goku and Vegeta's combined
attacks aren't working either.
[GOHAN]
It's okay.
We've seen them get out of
plenty of tough spots before.
As strong as Jiren is,
I know they can get
through this, too.
Yeah, you're right.
If anyone deserves our
trust, it's those two.
Hey there, son of Goku.
Huh?
Sorry. Gohan.
You fought well down there.
[gasps]
[GOHAN]
Thank you, Lord Beerus.
Hmph.
You must be sure of yourself,
Kakarot, to look away mid-fight.
[laughs] You're funny.
I could say the same about you.
[VEGETA] I'll pretend
you didn't say that.
I'll take him myself
if you need a rest.
[GOKU]
No. I can keep up just fine.
Let's go, Vegeta!
[yells]
[VEGETA]
Don't tell me what to do!
[TOP]
Justice Flash!
[TOP growls]
That cursed barrier.
We only have six more
minutes to settle this, huh?
[A17 yells]
[TOP] Ha! I hope you don't
actually think you can stop me
with a few pinpricks, warrior.
--[A17] No.
--[TOP] Huh?
But wait.
This is just the start.
[yells]
[TOP grunting]
Nice! 17's driving him back!
Well. It's pinned Top down
for the moment,
but it won't finish him.
That may not be the point.
We both have an endless supply
of energy, remember?
He can keep firing those
blasts and hold Top down
until the time runs out.
Oh, yeah, right.
Our team's ahead. 17 can
just run down the clock.
[TOP]
Why, you...!
Now!
[TOP]
This is the moment I defeat you
and keep my universe intact!
Funny. I was thinking that, too.
[TOP]
His power is inexhaustible.
I have to give it my all.
[A17 grunts]
I will summon all the powers
of justice I have left.
[TOP] And hit you with one,
decisive blow!
[yelling]
[TOP]
Retreat will not save you!
[TOP yells]
[yells]
[TOP grunting]
Impressive energy.
[TOP]
This is your undoing!
Ha!
[A17 grunting]
[TOP]
Your battle is over.
[TOP yells]
[gasps]
[A17 grunts]
[yells]
[TOP]
You demon.
[FRIEZA laughs]
Android, it seems to me you lack
the appropriate
degree of urgency.
There's no time left
to toy with your prey.
I hope you'll forgive me
for doing this while
your hands are tied.
[TOP grunts]
Oh? I should have
expected this
from a self-proclaimed
"Pride Trooper."
Hubris can do wonders
for one's constitution.
Consider these stronger attacks
a tribute to your valor.
[TOP grunting]
[FRIEZA] Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Come now, muscles.
Won't you direct your so-called
"powers of justice" at me?
That is,
if there's anything left!
[laughing]
[TOP grunts]
[FRIEZA laughing]
Honestly.
This isn't much fun
if you don't fight back.
[TOP panting]
[FRIEZA] Perhaps the moment's
come to put you down--
without killing you,
as regrettable as that is.
Huh?!
Farewell, Trooper.
I'm more for poetic justice.
Ha!
[TOP screams]
[TOP groaning]
[gasping]
Frieza's always been tough, but
now he's a full-on nightmare.
What a shot!
Let's just hope he's
not disqualified
for using excessive force.
Yeah, good point, Tien.
We're gonna want all of
the help we can get
to take care of Jiren.
[WHIS]
Hmm...
Hold on. It would appear
that Top is not yet finished.
[ALL]
Hm?
[TOP panting]
Why... you... Uh...
Well, well, well.
I should call you a "warrior
of just-won't-leave-the-ring."
Though it's not exactly
a dignified stand
since you're no longer standing.
Look at you there, crumpled,
singed, and tattered.
Like litter left on the road.
And trash should be tossed,
as should fragile justice.
Guess I should do my civic
duty and pick you up
and drop you into
the proper receptacle.
Hold on...
I will concede your toughness
is truly remarkable, Trooper.
But it's sad to see you
like this--how well can you
symbolize justice now that
your nifty uniform's all torn?
[TOP]
That's... irrelevant.
Huh?
[TOP] I won't be fighting
for justice any longer.
That side of me is through.
Oh, my.
[GOKU, VEGETA grunting]
[JIREN grunts]
[VEGETA, GOKU]
Huh?
What's that gigantic energy
that just showed up?
It seems Top has
made his decision.
Well done.
This can't be. He's been
hiding this the whole time?
His power...
It's starting to feel
like divine energy.
[ALL gasp]
[BELMOD] Hmph. I can't
think of a better time.
Go on and give 'em a show.
[BELMOD chuckles]
[TOP yelling]
[FRIEZA grunts]
Oh, very well.
I don't know what you're doing
but I do love a
good show-and-tell.
[TOP yelling]
[TOP yells]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA]
Hmph.
I'm sensing something
strange here.
[BELMOD]
Yeah. Yeah, that's it.
The next moments will decide
whether or not our universe
will vanish,
and these desperate times...
...call for the most desperate
of survival measures.
[laughing]
And here I thought you
were going to show off
some grand transformation!
All you've done is put an even
grumpier scowl on your face.
Let's hope you're right.
I suppose the only way to find
out is to put him to the test.
Okay.
That power...
So he's a...
Destroyer.
[ALL gasping]
So you're saying he's
got power like you?
Oh, you got that right.
It's a form of energy only
Destroyer Gods can wield.
Which bring us to Top.
He's currently being groomed
to be the next great Destroyer
of the Eleventh Universe.
[ALL gasp]
[MARCARITA]
An exciting moment, my lord.
We shall finally see the results
of his training with me.
All that remained was for
him to make the decision
and accept the mantle.
Yes! We have now witnessed
the birth of Top the Destroyer!
Heh!
[laughing]
[FRIEZA]
Am I meant to bow?
Even Destroyers pale against
the glow of Golden Frieza!
[FRIEZA cackles]
Oh, right.
I do believe I've seen
this technique before.
[TOP]
Hakai.
This is bad.
Yes, the "Energy
of Destruction."
Just like the sphere
from that band of rogues.
I think this time
one hand will do.
[laughing]
Most may fear this power,
but not me--
it's merely a trifle!
Hm?
[FRIEZA] Fine, two hands it is!
But it's still of no import!
No, these cheap
theatrics are futile!
They don't frighten me!
[FRIEZA growls]
They don't... frighten...
...me!
[ALL grunting]
[KRILLIN grunting]
What the--?
Look at the sky!
[rumbling]
Uh!
The whole ring has
been split in two!
[BOTH]
Wow!
Amazing!
It went crack, boom!
Step forward.
You cannot hide from me.
I was hoping to ambush you.
Let me guess--
does that make me unjust?
Justice and evil.
I have moved beyond
that binary now.
There is only being
and the absence of being.
Yeah, I agree.
What?
Sorry, I was thinking out loud.
You can ignore me.
[TOP grunts]
[grunts]
Impressive. Even his normal
energy blasts are stronger now.
You won't escape.
[yells]
[grunts]
Did you see that?!
Why aren't 17's attacks
working on him anymore?
It's hakai.
He can summon the Energy
of Destruction at will
and wrap it around himself
like a suit of armor.
Oh, man. So he can cut through
the ring like butter
and make himself
freaking invincible?
Well, that's great.
I guess this is payback for me
using my barrier earlier--
now I can't even slow you down
with my energy attacks.
But still, even fortresses
have a weak point somewhere.
[A17 yells]
[yelling]
[TOP]
This will do you no good.
[TOP yelling]
Get out of there, 17!
More destruction's on the way!
[A17 grunts]
[TOP] Distance will not
save you, either.
Hakai!
Ha!
[KRILLIN]
It's headed this way!
[TIEN]
No!
[ROSHI]
I don't want to be destroyed!
Calm down, mortals.
I'm getting sick of
these close calls!
[sighs] The upshot is I've had
a chance to observe him.
It still takes him
time to charge up
his Energy of Destruction
before he's able to release it.
So they could strike him
while he's charging.
No, I doubt that.
While he's waiting,
he can shield himself with
that energy, remember?
If they try to punch him,
they'll probably end
up like that rock.
I'll never win this way.
But what other choice do I have?
You'll find no sanctuary.
It is time for this to end.
[TOP growls]
[TOP]
Hakai.
There you are.
I see. You've endured.
That's impressive.
[FRIEZA panting]
Do you actually believe
you're fit to play god?
Well I'll destroy the Destroyer!
You'll make a fine
trophy for my case.
You think you can
stand against me
when you're barely on your feet?
Very well, give me
everything you've got.
[FRIEZA laughing]
Oh, my gift won't disappoint!
You're not the only one with
the power to destroy worlds!
[FRIEZA] Now it's the would-be
god who has no sanctuary!
[TOP]
Nonsense.
[FRIEZA laughs]
I'll blow you away!
Die!
[gasps]
[FRIEZA whimpers]
[groans]
It would be so easy for me
to expunge your helpless soul
from existence, but that
would only disqualify me.
[FRIEZA groans]
[screams]
Trash deserves to be
tossed, correct?
[thud]
[FRIEZA gasping]
[FRIEZA groans]
[A17] Sorry, my hand
must have slipped.
It wasn't my intention
to pummel you that hard.
[TOP]
You.
I have to give you credit for
surviving this long against me.
Well fought.
But there is no way you can win.
You so sure?
'Cause I say as long
as I'm still on my feet,
I've always got a chance.
[yells]
So you're refusing to submit.
Then you leave me
no choice, fighter.
[TOP growls]
[NARRATOR] In the midst
of this climactic battle,
the terrible power
of a Destroyer God
has awoken within Top.
And neither Frieza or Android 17
has found an answer.
[A17 yells]
[TOP]
Perish!
[NARRATOR]
Even with his unlimited energy,
does this android have
any chance of beating
such a fearsome foe?
Only five minutes remain
in the Tournament of Power.
Next time, on Dragon Ball Super!
Whirling all around
and then back again
The song that connects you
to the heavens
Strength that goes
beyond all measure
Expanding to a beat
that won't end
The meteors fall like rain drops
Astrological tears
from my eyelids
A strong emotion
from deep within
Has been awakened
A spark of possibility
Shines softly like a star
in the night sky
A wish from long
ago now shoots by
And I'm awakened
A never-ending melody,
so enchanting
You're always the one
who makes me tremble
The meteors keep falling down
Surging right into my heart
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Now that Top's unleashed
his intense new power,
it seems like 17 and Frieza
don't stand a chance.
And I guess the challenge
of fighting a new Destroyer
is too tempting for my
fellow Saiyan to pass up.
But you gotta
be careful, Vegeta!
I know we've got
everything on the line,
but are you really planning
to pay the ultimate price?
Next time, on Dragon Ball Super:
"Surpass Even a God!
Vegeta's Sacrifice Strike!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?