♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Goku Black continued
his merciless assault
on the earth of Trunks' future
with Zamasu at his side.
Convinced the present-day
Zamasu would soon
initiate a plan that would lead
to this future's devastation,
Whis, Beerus, and Goku
traveled to the world of
the Kais in the Tenth Universe,
then watched
as Zamasu did indeed
try to overthrow his master.
Sorry Kai,
but your luck has run out.
[BEERUS]
Hakai.
[NARRATOR] In one swift move,
Beerus destroyed Zamasu.
But how would this
affect Trunks' future?
Divine action is not so sloppy,
and when I kill a god it will
affect all flows of time.
I hope so. But I
need to see for myself.
[NARRATOR]
A jump through time. Now!
"Into the Future Again.
Goku Black's
True Identity Revealed!"
What's wrong? You say that as if
you refuse to believe
the word of a god.
I should trust you.
I know that,
but just can't do it.
You're a hard-headed one.
Aren't you?
What is wrong with you people?!
I am the great Destroyer
of this whole universe!
I will not tolerate disrespect!
You hear me?
[WHIS]
Let's go.
[BEERUS] You should be
clinging to my every word--
[WHIS]
I know, my lord, I know.
I'm sure they're
cowering on the inside.
[BEERUS]
...when I show kindness?
I should destroy them all!
Sorry. But I have to go.
You need to know
for certain, huh?
I do.
[BULMA] Maybe it's changed,
and maybe it hasn't.
But look on the bright side.
Either way you can find out fast
'cause you're fueled up
and ready to go!
But first, let's have a meal.
It's time travel so there's
no rush, after all.
And you need your strength.
Just in case, right?
Good point.
Thanks, Mom, but I'm
really not that hungry.
[BOTH]
Hm?
Listen to her, Trunks.
Its really good
for your tum tum!
--Okay.
--Dinner, my lord.
Well, I'm still angry
but it would be gauche
to refuse such an offer.
[GOKU]
Wow! Great spread, Bulma!
[BULMA]
You know me, always prepared!
[WHIS]
Mm!
Lord Beerus. Have you
tried this soup yet?
[BEERUS]
Mm?
Well, you should.
The flavor's astonishing!
Is that so?
I'd been holding off
since it looks like something
the dragons of Planet Gaspa
would puke up.
[BEERUS]
Mmmm!
You're right, it's delicious!
You should've told me!
What if I'd skipped
the soup completely?
Do you mind?
You're spraying me with it!
[BEERUS]
Silence! Is there more of this?
[BULMA]
Yeah, relax! There's plenty!
Oh hey, Trunks!
[BOTH]
Yeah, what?
[GOKU] Oh, sorry.
I meant the older one.
Feed that tum tum!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Uuuh...
All right!
Now that's the spirit!
By the way, I'm going
to the future, too!
Didn't you tell me
the time machine
gives you motion sickness?
[GOKU]
Well, I can get used to it.
[BEERUS] And why would you
want to join him?
Are you implying
that you suddenly
doubt my divine wisdom, too?
I believe you. But even if
there's a tiny chance
things didn't change,
I should be there to help.
I mean, I'm not saying
I'm rooting for it,
but I'd love the chance
to fight Zamasu one more time.
We can't just fight them
again without a plan.
That's mindless.
You're voting for caution?
That's hardly
your style, Vegeta.
The fact is we can't
afford to lose again.
If the future's unchanged
and we don't play this right,
it's over!
[BOTH]
Scary!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Father's right.
Hey, there's nothing to
worry about. We've got this.
I promise you, Trunks.
I won't forget the beans.
That's hardly the only
thing we're worried about.
You really insist on going,
just to see that I'm right?
Imbeciles.
You really can't let that go,
huh, Lord Beerus?
Then you could come with us,
too, to say "I told you so."
Don't be ridiculous. A Destroyer
traveling through time?
There's no telling what kind
of chaos that would wreak.
You may be willing
to commit taboos,
but this god
is staying out of it.
I guess this is it, Mom.
It's time to head out.
Hold on!
There's a god right here telling
us he's taken care of this!
Now that Zamasu is finished,
he'll never ask
that dragon to create Black!
So the future Earth is okay!
Black isn't gonna kill our mom!
Or hurt Mai or anyone else,
so what are you doing?
[panting]
If Lord Beerus is right
and Black never comes,
then the second doomsday
never even happened.
The peace won
after stopping Cell held.
If so, then what
am I doing here now?
[PILAF]
Yeah, that's true!
If none of this apocalyptic
junk is gonna happen,
then big-boy Trunks would have
no reason to travel back here!
Are you saying he should've
vanished the moment
things changed,
like some sort of ghost?
But then how would you
know about Black?
[BEERUS growls]
Patience, my lord.
We'll let him explain
his point of view.
This'll be confusing,
time travel always is.
Sure you want to hear?
Yeah.
It's both true that
I came from the future...
...and false.
That's how it works.
Time has been split into
more than one reality,
or timeline.
[gasps]
[FUTURE TRUNKS] It's a
distinction I've tried to make
since I got here.
That's why I say "my future"
and not yours.
Biologically we're
the same, both Trunks.
But we're not the same person.
There's no way we could be.
What do you mean--how are
we the same and different?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Come on.
When I was a child
looking at the horizon,
I never saw anything
as beautiful as this.
Our experiences, the ones that
shaped us, they're diverged.
Take our father.
You've grown up with him,
but in my world he was
killed by the Androids,
about six months
after I was born.
[VEGETA scoffs]
Wait, what do you
mean by "Androids"?
You mean like 18?
That's right. In your
reality, she changed.
She married Krillin--
they even had a kid together.
But in my world
she was never redeemed.
She and 17 were pure evil
and tried to wipe out
the human race.
Father, Piccolo, Krillin,
countless others.
The Androids
murdered all of them.
They were heartless monsters
bent on destruction,
and they would've kept
going if I hadn't returned
from your timeline
and destroyed them instead.
Think how profoundly
she's changed here.
From annihilating human life
to creating one of her own!
Circumstances made
the 18s different,
and they make us different, too.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Until I came to your timeline,
I'd only seen
Father's face in pictures,
heard about him in stories.
The same's true for Goku.
By the time I was born,
Goku was already dead
in my reality, struck down
by a heart disease.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
That's why I traveled here
in the first place--to give him
a drug to treat that disease
and stop him from dying,
so he could fight the Androids.
And I'm grateful, by the way.
You're the best, man!
Hold on. You did it
so he could fight?!
So when you
went back to your time
he was alive again, wasn't he?
He wasn't. And that's when I
learned how time travel works.
But that's not right! I've seen
stuff like this in movies!
If you change the past, it
should change the future, too!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Mm-mmm.
You're not listening.
It only affects the future of
the timeline you've traveled to.
Your future. Not mine.
[gasps]
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
You're describing dynamic
time travel theories.
But from what I've seen,
that's not how it works.
Those movies got it wrong.
There's the world, the reality--
the timeline where I live,
then there's the one
where you're from.
They're similar,
but different. Separate.
Saving one won't save them both.
This is wacko!
How many different
timelines are there?
So there's a me with Trunks,
but that doesn't mean
that my future is with him, too?
Okay, can we stop please?
Does this mean there could
still be a future
where someone actually
mentions me?
I get it now. That's why
you can't believe
Lord Beerus changed your
future even if you want to.
'Cause that's not
how you've seen it go.
That's right.
Eliminating a Kai is a massive
change in this reality.
But I'm still worried not even
that could fix my timeline.
Understand?
If you're so sure, mortal,
jump in your little
tin can and go see.
[blows]
--Lord Beerus.
--Now what?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Doubting you is disrespectful.
I see that, and I'm sorry.
But still, even though
I need to see for myself,
I'm holding out hope
that you're right.
[BEERUS]
Mm.
My fears are based on how I've
seen Earthlings affect time.
I take your point that a diety's
actions might be different.
Maybe gods affect time
in miraculous ways
I can't comprehend.
If you're trying to apologize,
then you can save your breath
because I don't care.
Whether your world's peaceful
or a smoldering wreck
makes no difference.
Now get lost, you bore me.
I mean it, though.
You've given me hope.
So thank you for that.
Huh.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Father. Would you mind
coming with me, too? Please?
I'd like you there.
All right, fine. I'll go.
But swear to me,
if this miracle's happened
and your future has been saved,
you'll never come
bother us again, okay?
Okay.
Good luck.
I'll root for that miracle.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Me too.
And I'll tell the Mai
I know you said hi.
So, I won't see you again?
Well, maybe not.
But you've got
the little me, right?
Take care of him for me, okay?
Hey, Vegeta. Make sure you
don't forget the senzu beans!
You're the one
who has them, you clown!
Oh, yeah. Uh. Where'd they go?
[BULMA]
You're hopeless.
Haha! Ah, there they are!
I'll just put them
right back here.
Oh and by the way,
I'm coming too.
--[VEGETA, GOKU] What?
--But why?
What if Trunks stays in his time
and there's something wrong
with the autopilot, huh?
--[VEGETA growls]
--[GOKU] Eeh!
Lucky for you, I know
that machine inside and out!
Besides, I've always
wanted to see the future,
or his future--whatever.
And one more thing.
I ordered a new one for you,
custom made!
[TRUNKS, MAI]
Here.
Nice! Very sharp!
Just like the
first day I saw you.
I gotta say, that is definitely
my favorite look for you.
Thanks for everything, Mom.
You're the best.
Hey. Don't make me cry.
[PILAF] They look
they're sardines in there.
You okay, Bulma?
Don't get smushed!
Too late, Mai. Looks like
she's smushed already!
[TRUNKS] Hey, can you
guys breath in there?
We'll be fine, let's just go!
Do you really
have to come too, Bulma?
Do you?
Don't bother, Kakarot.
You won't win.
--[ALL yell]
--Brace yourselves, here we go.
[TRUNKS grunts]
[BEERUS] It's blasphemy.
Come on, Whis. Let's go.
Are you certain, Lord Beerus?
Don't you want to see
how it turns out?
[BEERUS]
Oh, good grief.
[TRUNKS panting]
[TRUNKS]
Good luck, me!
Good luck!
[GOKU groans]
[VEGETA scoffs]
Wow! So this is what it's like!
One more minute, guys--
we're almost there.
[FUTURE TRUNKS gasps]
My god. It's awful.
My world didn't change.
I knew it.
Beerus couldn't fix this.
Not even the act of a god
made a difference.
I hope Mai is okay.
--[BULMA groans, chuckles]
--[GOKU hollers]
[GOKU hollers, groans]
[ZAMASU]
Hm?
They are here.
Man! That hurt!
Come on.
You didn't fall that far.
And I'm still
feeling all dizzy, too.
[FUTURE TRUNKS] Mom, can you
be in charge of this?
You bet. Do you know
where they'll be?
Mai and the others?
Commander Trunks! It's you!
You really did come back!
Yeah. Tell me.
Is everyone okay?
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER A]
Mai's not.
[gasps]
She was trying
to help some people
fleeing from Black,
and took a bad hit.
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER A]
They're here.
[REFUGEES murmur]
Has Trunks come back?
Mai!
[gasps]
You're here!
Help her, Trunks.
We don't know what to do!
She's dying!
Goku, quick. Senzu bean!
Oh, yeah.
Here you go.
[HARU, MAKI gasp]
[FUTURE MAI inhales, exhales]
[BOTH gasp]
Whoa! What was that, Trunks?
You put your mouth
on hers--that's so weird!
Kakarot. You've never
kissed someone?
No, of course not, why?
You're married
and have children!
Yeah, duh, but what's
that have to do with kissing?
You-- Oh, no way.
No, tell me! Is that like,
something people do?
--[BULMA sighs]
--[HARU, MAKI giggle]
[FUTURE YAJIROBE chuckles]
Wow, Yajirobe?
Yeah, so what?
[chuckles]
You're looking good!
That soldier said
you're the one who saved Mai.
Yeah. You know me,
I've always been a hero.
--Wake up.
--Come on, Mai.
[REFUGEES gasp]
I told them you'd come back.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
You're okay. Thank god.
--[MAKI] Hooray!
--[HARU] That was awesome!
[MAKI]
Here, Mai. So you can clean up.
--Yes! She's all better!
--[REFUGEES cheering]
That was good timing. Nice work.
I'm sorry, Goku.
That means we only have
four senzu beans left.
[GOKU] It's fine.
We'll make 'em count.
Whoa. Bulma, you're so young!
And you're so grown up!
It's great to meet you, Mai.
--You're pretty!
--Oh, stop.
I brought you guys
more food and water,
and other essentials
no one should live without.
They should help you get by.
[VEGETA]
Hm?
That energy. Do you sense it?
They're on their way now.
--Is it Zamasu?
--[REFUGEES gasp]
And Black, too.
--It's okay!
--[REFUGEES scream]
Everyone else stay here!
Don't worry, Mai.
Trunks is gonna be just fine.
[FUTURE MAI]
Right.
I told you we needed a plan,
yet here we are.
Oh, relax, I'm sure we'll
find a way. We always do.
Sure. Except for all
the times that we've died.
[GOKU]
Hm?
I see you have
returned, dear Saiyans.
Zamasu.
Welcome back. I do
appreciate you returning
so I can become even stronger.
This will be no repeat
of our last fight!
Vegeta, what about the plan?
All I know is that
I'm taking Black!
Oh! Okay, that works for me!
You'd love nothing more
than to defeat me.
You crave it. Since you lost
so easily last time.
Shut up! I didn't come
to this wasteland
you created for myself!
It's for my son!
So this Earth can have a future!
Well, that's not
very Saiyan of you.
[GOKU]
We know the truth!
All the terrible
things you've done!
We know you used the Super
Dragon Balls to get your power!
And we know about Gowasu!
Oh. You're quite the detective.
You made yourself invincible.
And made this fake copy!
You think I'm a copy?
You're wrong, Goku.
--[FUTURE TRUNKS gasps]
--What?
Then what are you?
This is Goku's actual body,
down to the last battle-scar.
The perfect war machine, once I
learned how to control it.
But the mind that's inside
belongs to me.
The Supreme Kai Zamasu.
[gasps]
After I dispensed with
my tragically useless master,
I took the Time Ring and
found the Super Dragon Balls.
Then with my first
wish to the Dragon
I switched bodies
with you, Goku.
[ALL gasp]
[ZAMASU]
Hm.
They traded bodies?
[gasps] So that means
you took over my body?
And then what?
Can't you guess?
Then I killed you.
[gasps]
Death by your own fist.
♪ Closing Song ♪
1, 2, 3, I'm hungry
Nothin' but
fried rice fantasies
I want fried rice,
I'm so hungryyyyyy-yeah!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
We've just heard
a real shocker from Black,
but that's not the whole story.
We're about to learn
all the details
of how he carried out
his wicked plan.
Then it's time to stop him,
but with the two
powered up Zamasus
tag-teaming us,
it's gonna take
everything Trunks,
Vegeta, and I have
just to hang on!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Zamasu's Ambition.
The Storied 'Project
0 Mortals' of Terror."
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?