♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the resurrected Frieza arrived
on Earth to take revenge.
But Goku and Vegeta were
training on the other side
of the universe and unaware
of the invasion back home.
And the chances
of contacting them
became even more daunting
when Whis transported them
to a different dimension.
All right, soldiers!
Show no mercy!
[NARRATOR]
Without Goku and Vegeta,
Earth's remaining warriors
were left to fight
Frieza's army on their own.
And despite being
vastly outnumbered,
it seemed Gohan and
the others could prevail.
But there was one more
soldier in the Frieza Force
who had yet to show his power.
A formidable one who had spent
the last several months
training with
the evil emperor himself.
[KRILLIN] Gohan,
here's a senzu bean. Eat it.
Who is that bastard?
[TAGOMA]
If I kill them all myself,
will you make me
your commander--
your right hand man?
[NARRATOR]
Tagoma attacks. Now!
"Change! An Unexpected Return!
His Name Is Ginyu!!"
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[SORBET growls]
[TAGOMA chuckles]
[GOHAN panting]
Ya feel that?
He's a strong one.
Compared to
the rest of these guys,
he's a monster.
[GOHAN]
Yeah. I'd say his energy's
on the same level as mine.
Back when I was
at the top of my game.
--[KRILLIN] What?
--[PICCOLO] Dammit.
Jaco. You're sure we
can stop this guy, right?
I don't see why not. I mean,
he's not the kind of guy
you want to meet
in a dark space port.
But it's five against one,
so the odds
are still on our side.
Hold on. There's one,
two, three, four, five.
I notice you're not
including yourself!
Hey, I specifically
told you I'd help
take on the weaker ones, Bulma,
and that guy is not weak.
So, fighting him now
would make me a liar.
Oh, come on!
You can't duck out
'cause he's tough!
You think that's any way for a
Super Elite Galactic
Patrolman to act?
[JACO]
Yes, I do!
Ugh!
Well then,
guess I should get on
with the carnage already.
Relax, Sorbet. Once Lord
Frieza makes me commander,
I won't kick you off the Force.
You can have guard duty on some
remote backwoods planet.
He stabs me in the back
and twists the blade.
After all that I've done
to bring him up in the ranks?
Arrogant traitor!
[croaks]
You should feel honored
to be crushed by the hands
of a future legend.
Who's going first?
Or if you want to die quick,
I can take you all at once.
I'll fight you.
You're a lightweight.
I can kill you
in under three minutes.
Don't be so sure.
[growls]
[bellows]
What?
Yeah... That's about
what I thought.
[PICCOLO groans]
[laughs intensely]
Leave him alone!
[TAGOMA yells]
[PICCOLO groans]
Piccolo, take a senzu bean.
[chuckles]
That didn't phase him at all.
[laughs intensely]
Serving as Lord Frieza's
training partner
meant I was basically
a punching bag
for one of the most powerful
warriors in the universe.
I was beaten to a pulp
for four months straight.
And each time the machine
put me back together,
I got stronger!
Now it's like my skin's
made out of steel
and your dainty attacks
won't even scratch me.
[laughs intensely]
Dun-dun-dun-dun!
Enemies beware!
Super Gotenks is here!
[TAGOMA screams]
I bet he won't call
that attack "dainty."
Oh, yeah!
--The boys are here.
--I noticed.
You boys aren't
supposed to be here.
What are you doing?
Did you really think
we wouldn't find out?
We came as soon as we
sensed that dweeb's power.
You can't leave us out of all
the fun; it's super unfair!
It's not unfair!
It's being a good mom!
You're too young to
fight aliens! Now go home!
Sorry, no can do.
Who cares how old we are?
Our strength
is all that matters,
and Super Gotenks is invincible!
You're the boss
of these dudes,
right, Flying-Chair-Boy?
Well then get ready!
'Cause we're taking you on
and we won't go easy--
--[BOTH] Eeh!
--[TRUNKS] Okay this is bad.
Oh. So, you younglings
learned Fusion? Huh?
[FRIEZA]
That face.
He's a spitting image
of Goku, poor thing.
He's clearly
that monkey's offspring.
And that one looks
familiar too, somehow.
I've seen him before, but where?
[gasps]
[FRIEZA] The other!
He looks like the other!
That second, cursed Super
Saiyan who cut me in half!
Hey! Frieza!
[yells]
[FRIEZA groans]
[FRIEZA] If he's the son
of that swordsman,
that would mean he's
at least part Saiyan, too.
I leave this world for a while,
and those filthy creatures
start procreating
left and right!
It's a damned
spring time for monkeys!
It looks like we
made him really angry.
I'm not scared,
but I think we should run.
[BOTH]
Eeh!
I assume you're
still on the ground
for dramatic purposes.
But let's go, Tagoma!
Exterminate those children
before they escape!
--[TAGOMA whimpers]
--[FRIEZA] Hello?
[FRIEZA] Are you
listening, you imbecile?
Get up, or I'll have
to kill you myself!
[groans]
[GINYU FROG grumbles]
[TAGOMA] What?
Does that say "change now"?
[TAGOMA FROG croaks]
[GINYU laughs intensely]
At last. Back on two legs,
after all this time.
[laughs]
And it feels unbelievable!
It's been entirely
too long, Lord Frieza.
Your voice. It's different.
You're not Tagoma, are you?
Have you forgotten me?
I'm captain of the High-Level
Executive Class Ginyu Force!
Ginyu!
Yes! That playful pose
is unmistakable!
It is you, captain!
[TRUNKS]
What's a Ginyu Force?
They used to be
a part of Frieza's army.
A mercenary team hand-picked
by Frieza himself,
composed of the most elite
and gifted warriors.
And Captain Ginyu
was their leader.
Okay, that sounds
pretty impressive,
but Goten and I can do
way cooler action poses!
--Right?
--[JACO] I can't even.
Captain Ginyu. It's been
a long time indeed
since I've seen you.
Between your battle
with the Saiyans
and the explosion of Namek,
I thought you'd
perished for sure.
Would you like to hear the
tale of my survival, my lord?
I hope you won't
think less of me,
but it brings me to tears
just thinking about it!
The whole ordeal
began when I was
fighting that traitor Vegeta.
I was trying to use my
body-swapping power against him!
I thought it would
serve him right if he had
to watch his
own body be defeated!
[laughs]
[GINYU]
I've got you now!
Change now!
[VEGETA grunts]
[FROG groans]
[GINYU] The other Saiyan
interfered with my battle,
and I was trapped in the body
of that Namekian frog!
[GINYU FROG croaks]
I hate that frog.
I forgot all about that.
[FEMALE NAMEK FROG]
Mwah! Mwah! Mwah!
[GINYU] I thought
my fate was sealed!
I was trapped in that
Namekian wasteland!
[GINYU FROG]
Huh?
[GINYU] Then suddenly,
I was on this planet,
for reasons
I couldn't understand!
It was the Dragon Balls.
What do you mean? When?
On Namek.
When Frieza's attack
was about to rip
the planet apart.
Dende asked their Dragon
to transport everyone
except Goku and Frieza to
Earth to avoid casualties.
Ginyu came, too?
So, you mean he's
been here this whole time?
I hate that frog!
So, I'm guessing
you two have some history?
I don't wanna talk about it.
[ALL gasp]
[GINYU] But my hardships
didn't end there!
I endured years
of humiliating struggle!
But I persevered no matter
how awful it got!
Because I always believed
in my heart that one day
I'd be able to fight
for you again, Lord Frieza!
And now that time has come.
Let me show you something
I've been working on, sir!
A special fighting pose
to mark this day!
[FRIEZA]
Mm.
If you really want
to show me something,
then why don't you show me
a few heads on a platter.
Yes, sir!
I haven't gotten
used to this body yet
but I'm sure it'll be enough
to handle these maggots.
Sorry, but you're facing
the great Captain Ginyu now!
[yells]
So? Shall we get started?
[laughs]
Who would've
guessed that exuberant
old captain was still alive?
I normally hate being wrong,
but this is delightful.
[laughs]
I know you.
You were that child
who was with Vegeta
back on Namek, correct?
And you were there too, baldy.
I'm going to enjoy
settling these scores.
[yells]
[groans]
[ROSHI, PICCOLO,
GOHAN, KRILLIN groan]
[laughs]
Marvelous, captain,
this body fits you well!
He's so strong.
His energy is
even greater than before.
Tagoma's body was strong
but he had nothing
close to Ginyu's
experience in battle.
The captain must know
how to maximize his power.
[laughs]
I was due some good luck!
Inhabiting a body
with this level
of battle power is
almost indescribable!
All those years hopping
in the dirt were worth it!
I feel so good!
I'm never going to let this
vessel go, I swear it!
It's the best body
I've ever worn!
Just a shame
we can't do anything
to swap out that
farcical personality.
A body built like a tank,
with all that speed
and fighting skill.
It's not going to be easy
to beat this guy.
--Mm?
--[panting]
--Let me take him.
--[PICCOLO] Gohan.
Master Roshi, Tien,
you can't help in this fight.
Take some senzu beans
and go find some cover.
Yes, let's see how far he's
come in his battle training,
now that the child
is all grown up.
[ALL]
Huh?
All right, kiddos,
you want to chip in?
Then you're gonna
help me make a call.
We've gotta contact Whis.
So he can tell your dads to
come join the fight, okay?
[BULMA]
Oh, Whis!
I've still got this
super-deluxe sundae for you!
Come on, Whis! Hurry!
Or I'm gonna eat it myself!
I'm gonna
stick my face in it!
Well, it looks like
the crazy is spreading.
It's a little greasy,
but I could see it
on the regular menu.
Now, what it's called again?
That's "pizza," my lord.
Pizza, yes.
Ridiculous name for
a food, don't you think?
Now that you've been fed,
do you still think
it was wise to send them
to that realm, my lord?
Relax, Whis, they're fine.
They're the type
of fighters who can only
reach their full potential if
they're pushed to their limits.
Besides, if we're doing this,
I want it done quickly.
So I can have someone
to play with.
[WHIS]
Mmm.
[GOKU grunts]
[VEGETA]
Ah! Damn it!
I can't move!
Come on!
So, that's the trick.
If I raise my energy
but control it
so it doesn't
leak out, I can move.
Nice, Vegeta! Shoulda
known you'd figure it out!
Yeah, it's working
for me, too.
That's way better.
Pretty demanding to
keep it all inside, though.
So is this the secret
to divine energy?
The pressure
inside's so intense.
Kakarot. Doesn't this place
remind you of somewhere?
Yeah! The way the air
feels is definitely
ringing a bell.
All weird and humid.
It feels exactly like the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber!
[VEGETA]
Hmph!
Eeeh! This is the
ultimate training space!
This must be where Lord Beerus
goes to get stronger, too!
Wait, I just realized!
What Kakarot? Spit it out!
If it's like the Chamber
then it's
a different dimension,
so there may not be an exit.
We've got to find
the supply building
or wherever Beerus
keeps his food in here
before we're
too drained to move.
Or we could starve to death,
which is kind of a problem.
Of course it's
a problem, you moron.
It might be another way
he's testing us!
And the only thing that might
help us is that staff.
[yells]
You definitely don't live up
to my expectations, boy.
Why'd you jump at
the chance to fight me
if this is all you can do?
[GOHAN] I'm not tapping
into my full strength!
Is that 'cause
I haven't been training?
--[GINYU yells]
--[GOHAN groans]
I got you now, boy!
[laughs]
Gohan, no!
[GOHAN] No choice.
I have to do it now.
[bellows]
He's a Super Saiyan, too?
Huh?!
It seems Goku shared
his technique with
both his sons, like some
twisted monkey virus.
Evidently,
you've been hiding
a massive amount
of power from me.
Like you didn't think you needed
it to battle Captain Ginyu.
And that's an insult
I do not take lightly.
[GOHAN] If I am out of shape,
it's time to find out
how much I can take.
A real Super Saiyan.
This should be far
more interesting now.
[yells]
Way to go!
Man, my brother's awesome!
We both know
this battle's over.
I won't keep hurting you
just to feed my own ego.
[gasps]
[snarls]
Now get off my planet
before I change my--
[groans]
Miserable Saiyan.
Thank you, Lord Frieza,
he merely
caught me by surprise.
I can handle
the fight from here.
[FRIEZA]
Stand down, Captain!
Yes, sir!
I appreciate your
overflowing enthusiasm,
but I've decided
to kill this one myself.
After inflicting
a great deal of pain.
Gohan!
Stay back, Goten!
But why?
[GOHAN] You're no match for him.
I don't want you hurt.
[GOTEN grumbles]
What brotherly love;
I can barely stomach it.
I would be
an unforgivable villain
if I separated
the two of you boys.
When I'm done with Gohan
I'll kill you, too,
so you can hold hands in Hell.
It shames me to admit,
but did you know
that I was once
spared by your father?
The same way you just
spared Captain Colorful?
There. I've given you
some of my energy.
With any luck,
it should be just enough
to get you off this planet
before it blows.
But that's all you get.
I was a filthy
simian's charity case.
Do you realize how
I've suffered from that,
reliving the humiliation
every day since?
And now you have the gall
to remind me of it again!
You'll pay dearly for that.
Yes, you'll pay
with your suffering
and the pleasure
it will afford me.
For the sight of Goku's face
when he finds
what is left of you.
When he imagines the agony
I put you through,
now that is a fair recompense!
Gohan!
I will not allow you
to interfere with this fight!
[yells, groans]
Well? What are you waiting for?
If you're entertaining
any hope of survival,
then you had better run.
[yells]
[BULMA]
Gohan!
Sorry, I can't watch this.
I'm a very easy fainter.
Does that hurt, child?
Are you suffering now?
It hardly compares
to what Goku did to me
so we're not remotely
close to being done.
And not because I'm a sadist,
it's simply tit for tat.
[yells, groans]
Go on. Try to escape;
I enjoy a moving target!
[yells, groans
[FRIEZA] Oh, drat,
now I've done it.
You can't even stand.
[groans]
I see you haven't inherited
all of daddy's traits.
You give up much faster.
[screams]
[FRIEZA] If you think I'll stop
once when you're on the ground,
well, you're not
thinking at all.
[screams]
You don't know how this works.
Once you can't move anymore,
you're supposed
to beg for mercy.
Say you'll do anything
if I spare your life.
Let's hear it, boy!
Cry for me! Scream!
Soak your face in tears
and rend your clothes!
[laughs]
Not that I would
let you go,
but it's all part of
the experience for me.
No, mercy would be impossible.
I've waited for this too long.
Your death will
balance the scales.
It's what you get
for being a Saiyan.
And it's what you deserve
for being Goku's son.
[FRIEZA]
Now die!
Gohan!
Brother!
[gasps]
[GOHAN]
Piccolo, why?
Why would you do that? Piccolo!
[NARRATOR] Piccolo has
paid the ultimate price.
How will Gohan respond?
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super.
I look back
to when I was young
Reminisce on all that I've done
In my hands, I held
The dreams of my childhood,
that now've come to pass
So let's ride upon
the wind and journey to
A world we've never known
(It's a brand new story)
Now, a new chapter starts
Shining Star
In the night be
my compass and guide
Take me to where I belong
The warmth we once shared
Will always be there
Its magic lives on in our hearts
Shining Star
Give me strength
from your light up above
Show me the way to be brave
My hands still hold onto hope
that together we'll manifest
All that we dreamed of
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Vegeta and I have
to help our friends,
but first I need find
a way to get us back!
And once we do get there,
the action is going
to heat up fast!
Frieza says
he's gotten stronger,
but could he really
be on our level?
I guess we're
about to find out!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Earth! Gohan!
Both on the Ropes!
Hurry and Get Here, Goku!!"
Wait, that's me!
I'll do what I can, okay?