♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Grand Zeno, inspired by Goku,
called for The
Tournament of Power,
bringing together
the entire cosmos.
As a prelude to the main event,
the Zeno Expo commenced.
The exhibition fight pits Goku
and the Seventh Universe
against the Ninth Universe.
In the first match,
the Seventh Universe was
represented by Majin Buu.
He's strong, too.
Way stronger than you are!
[yelling]
[BUU]
Buu!
[screaming]
That was fun!
Yeah, that was really fun!
The Omni-Kings Grand Zeno
have expressed satisfaction
with the match at hand.
By their orders,
the first fight of the Expo
is hereby concluded!
[NARRATOR]
With Majin Buu securing victory,
it was time for the
second round to begin.
Fighting on behalf of
the Seventh Universe...
Looks like it's my
turn in the ring.
Good luck, son!
Now get down there!
I'm on it.
[laughing]
[NARRATOR]
Gohan enters the ring. Now!
[NARRATOR] "Awaken Your
Dormant Fighting Spirit!
Gohan's Fight!"
[laughing]
It's been a long time since
I fought in a tournament.
I'd better ease
myself into this,
at least until I get
the feel for it again.
[laughing]
Since I can't sense
this guy's energy,
I'll just have to see what
his first move's gonna be.
[GOKU]
Gohan!
Don't play "wait-and-see"
with an opponent
whose energy you can't read.
Are you sure?
Yes, you're strong,
don't hold back.
Just go ahead and hit him
with everything you've got!
Thanks for the advice, Dad.
I'll go at him with full force.
I'll admit, he does
have a good point.
Just forget about my opponent.
The first thing that I need to
do is gauge my own power now.
[chuckles]
Let the second
match... begin now!
[GOHAN yells]
[LAVENDER laughing]
[yells]
I caught you!
All right!
What's that?
I do not know!
[laughing]
[LAVENDER laughing]
So he just starts out
by blinding him, huh?
[WHIS chuckles]
Indeed, that does appear to
be a rather potent toxin.
[GOKU]
Hmm...
[RO]
How do you like that?
Behold, the Trio of Danger's
middle brother Lavender
and his Poison Blow!
Breathe it in, then fall to your
hands and knees in surrender!
So he can't see
anything anymore?
And the poison did that to him?
That was a low-down,
dirty trick!
I hate to say it,
but there's no such
thing as a dirty trick
when you're in the ring.
Well, how does my
poison taste, boy?
You know, if you take
in too much of it,
your body will start to rot now.
[laughing]
Hey, Seventh Universe! Why don't
you just concede already?
Before your body
begins to decay!
[SUPREME KAI]
Here, Gohan, take a senzu!
Their last fighter
used a power-up.
We should, as well.
[GOHAN]
No, Supreme Kai!
I don't need a senzu!
You guys...
Please, just stay outta this.
I need to fight this battle
alone, using my own power.
[chuckles]
I'd like to see how long he can
hold out against that poison.
Poison! Poison!
Hey, Supreme Kai, I'll hold
on to that senzu bean for ya.
[SUPREME KAI]
As you wish.
Cool, thanks.
[MR. SATAN]
Are you sure about this?
Your boy is gettin' absolutely
destroyed out there.
It's for the best.
He can't see the guy
or read his energy.
Since Gohan hadn't fought
in such a long time,
it's the perfect
training for him.
[MR. SATAN gasps]
[LAVENDER laughs]
Now, as my poison slowly
works its way inside of you,
it'll start breakin'
down your body.
[LAVENDER laughing]
[GOHAN]
Don't be misled by his voice.
His movements. His presence.
I have to feel
them with my body.
What the--?!
[yells]
Damn it!
Yeah!
Wowie!
Double-wowie!
But how?!
[LAVENDER growling]
There's no way I'm gonna
let you show me up.
That was a lucky shot!
How are you blocking me?
Impossible!
'Fraid not, sir.
I think what's going on,
at least from my perspective,
after being blinded,
he heightened his other senses
and became even more
aware of his surroundings.
That's the spirit of an
opponent truly worth fighting.
I know what you'll do,
before you do it.
[yells]
[LAVENDER laughing]
[GOHAN yells]
I'll get you!
That's it. That's how
you do it, Gohan.
[LAVENDER laughs]
Let's try this.
[laughing]
He's flying.
Yes, he's flying.
[GOHAN]
Hm?
That's odd, I can't sense
his footwork anymore.
Where is he?
[laughs]
I must say, quite
the clever gambit.
It will be difficult to detect
his presence from that distance.
[LAVENDER chuckles]
[yells]
[gasps]
[laughing]
Uh! Whoa, this is bad!
Yeah, it could be bad.
[MR. SATAN]
Huh?
Although, the more Gohan
gets backed into a corner,
the better he learns to cope
with what he's up against.
[snickers]
That was incredible, Lavender!
Now finish him off!
Oh, I'm on it!
I'm going to enjoy this!
[GOHAN]
I'm not done yet.
My power goes beyond
what you've seen so far.
[yelling]
What the hell did he just do?
Ha! Big deal! Who cares
if he's glowing a little?
Whoa! What is that?
That is what they
call a Super Saiyan.
It's so pretty. He's shiny now.
Not to mention much stronger.
Super Saiyan, was it?
[TOP]
Hm. He appears to be a lifeform
capable of altering
his battle power.
[yells]
Even if you are lit up and
a teensy bit stronger,
you still don't know how
I'm going to attack you next.
Yeah? Go ahead and try me.
[growls]
How'd he do that?
[ZENO]
He blocked it!
Yeah, that was neat!
You got lucky, kid! That's all!
[screams]
[GOHAN yells]
I don't get it!
How can you see me?
I don't need to see.
My energy tells me where you
are and what you're gonna do.
Not bad, Gohan. Not bad at all.
By bouncing his own
energy off of his opponent,
Gohan is able to
detect his every move.
One might call this technique
a form of active radar.
Though it is a novel
and resourceful use
of his Super Saiyan abilities,
it may prove to be something of
a double-edged sword in the end.
In that case, he's gotta
wrap this up quick!
[yells]
It's all over for you now!
[gasps]
[groaning]
[laughs]
He was trying to push
his enemy to the limit,
but he ended up pushing
himself beyond it first.
Yes.
And in so doing, he hastened
the spread of the poison.
Is that the double-edged sword
you were referring to before?
[WHIS] Well, it is conceivable
that by turning Super Saiyan,
he fueled the poison,
allowing it to circulate
throughout his entire body
at a much more rapid pace.
You won't get away!
[yelling]
Oh, no! Using his power will
just spread the toxin faster!
[BOTH]
Whoa!
Getting desperate, huh?
Ha! This fight ain't gonna
be that easy for you!
Oh, don't you worry.
I'm well aware of that!
[GOHAN yells]
[BOTH]
Wow!
[yells]
[LAVENDER yells]
[screams]
Oh, no! He's flyin'
into the poison!
What?!
You were baiting me
into dropping my guard!
As long as I've got you, it
doesn't matter if I can't see!
[GOHAN yells]
--[GOHAN yelling]
--[LAVENDER screaming]
I won.
Well, what's gonna happen now?
As neither contestant
remains standing,
the second match is
officially a draw.
[BOTH laugh]
It's a draw?
It would appear that
the poison really has
taken its toll on young Gohan.
[GOKU] Gohan, here's a
Senzu. Open up, buddy.
Dad, I-I'm sorry.
Don't be. Ya did
great out there.
I can take him. I kept
telling myself that.
And yet, still, I wasn't
good enough to win.
That fight was amazing.
I got so excited watching it.
Listen, you're stronger
than you think.
No, got a long way to go.
Ladies and gentlemen,
assembled deities.
I have a message for you
from the Omni-King.
Grand Zeno is deeply
moved that those
of the lowest-ranking
mortal levels
would treat us to battles
as extraordinary
as the ones we've
just witnessed,
and would like to
extend his gratitude
to all the fighters
for their efforts.
Wait, mortal?
What levels?
You see, Grand Zeno
has carefully
evaluated all twelve universes,
and assigned each one a ranking.
So, um, how did the Seventh
Universe fare in his estimation?
Among all worlds
populated by mortals
within the Seventh Universe,
the average level is 3.18.
Which is rather poor.
That's second from
the bottom, in fact.
[yelps]
Pardon me, but if we're
the second from the bottom,
then which universe would
be ranked lower than us?
I'm sure you already know.
[RO gasps]
You can't mean--!
That's correct.
The Ninth Universe's average
level is the lowest.
A meager 1.86.
[gasps]
Now, as for this
Tournament of Power,
the Omni-King has long said that
there are far too many universes
in the cosmos.
Which is why the proposal
offered by Goku of
the Seventh Universe
presented the
perfect opportunity.
[GOKU]
Uh.
Those universes defeated in
the Tournament of Power,
are to be eliminated
by Grand Zeno himself.
Say what?!
[DEITIES chattering]
So if we lose
these Expo matches,
does that mean our universe
will be annihilated, too?
[GRAND MINISTER]
No, that won't be happening.
[sighs]
Uh, hold on. Did he
just say eliminated?
Sorry, I'm just havin'
a little bit a trouble
following all of this stuff!
Grand Minister, there is one
detail I wish to clarify.
By all means, please
tell me what it is.
When you say the defeated
universes will be eliminated,
does that apply to
all of the universes
that are defeated
in the Tournament?
[GRAND MINISTER]
Yes.
Although, I should point out
that the First and
Twelfth Universes,
as well as the Fifth
and the Eighth,
are exempt from participating
in this particular tournament.
Those four universes have
average mortal levels
of seven or higher,
so they will be spared that
particular consequence.
Interesting.
So what you're saying
is, essentially,
the true purpose of
this tournament
is to take a
lower-level universe,
one which was already on the
Omni-King's chopping block,
and if it should
prove victorious,
granting it a reprieve?
[GRAND MINISTER] Yes, that's
pretty much the gist of it.
I see.
I can't wait for the actual
Tournament of Power to begin!
Oh yeah, I'm excited
for it, too!
Yeah, sorry, but I'm
still not gettin' it.
What's this guy yammerin'
on about here?
[SUPREME KAI]
If we lose,
our entire universe
will be wiped out.
Huh? So wait, what
you're sayin' is...?
All of us, along with our
universe, will cease to exist.
[yelps]
What's wrong, Mr Satan?
This is all your fault!
You're the one who foolishly
believed that if a mortal world
didn't reach a higher
level all on their own,
it wouldn't mean anything,
so you refused to lift a single
finger to help them!
What about you?
What have you done besides spend
most of your time sleeping?
If that's all, we should move
on to the third match now.
[ELDER KAI] Uh, just a minute
there, Grand Minister.
In the event of a defeat for
our universe in the tournament,
what happens to us deities?
[GRAND MINISTER] Why,
you'll all be done away with
at the same time.
Except for the
Angels, naturally.
Whis? Now what the hell
makes you so special?
[WHIS chuckles]
Well, Lord Beerus, my position
is different from yours.
Vados! You're safe, too?
And that concludes our
information session.
Moving on, the
Expo's third match
will sadly be its final one.
All right! It's my turn now!
[GOHAN]
Hey, Dad.
Good luck out there, okay?
Thanks!
[NARRATOR]
What sort of powers
does the Ninth Universe's
fighter Bergamo possess?
And what does he have
in store for Goku?
With the threat of universal
destruction looming over them,
the final match of the Zeno
Expo is about to get underway.
An angel and a demon sit
One to my right,
one to my left
In between I'm tryin'
to figure out the right way
Is one way good?
Is one way bad?
Too much confusion in my head
I can't think with all
this noise, I'm goin' crazy
Is there any way to know
what's right or wrong?
Demons in an angel mask
Hopin' that I'll do
just what they ask
Telling me
they know what's right
Lead me to the light
"For the sake of everyone
You have to destroy
the evil ones
That's the only path, you see"
So they said to me
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
We're entering the last
round of the Zeno Expo,
and finally it's my turn!
My opponent is the Ninth
Universe's strongest warrior,
Bergamo the Crusher.
Hey, man, let's enjoy
ourselves here,
pushing past our limits
and making this
a battle to remember!
Next time, on Dragon Ball Super:
"Bergamo the Crusher vs. Goku!
Whose Strength Reaches
the Wild Blue Yonder?"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?