♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
with the fate of eight
universes on the line
in the Tournament of Power,
participants from all over the
Cosmos assembled at the ring,
located in the Null Realm,
accompanied by their deities.
[GRAND MINISTER]
It's made of kachi katchintite,
the hardest substance
in the Cosmos,
and even stronger than
regular katchintite.
An element you may already
know from the Seventh.
That's why the ring
will do just fine.
Yeah, that makes sense to me.
[GRAND MINISTER] If you're
still doubting, though,
you may test it.
[ALL gasping]
In fact, such an exhibition
may be just what
the Omni-Kings need, as I'm
sure they're quite bored
waiting for the
tournament to start.
And fight!
All right. Enough fighting
for now, gentlemen.
[NARRATOR]
And so, 80 warriors representing
each of the universes
gathered atop
the completed ring, ready to
put forth their best efforts.
When the dust settles,
will Goku and the rest
of his Seventh Universe
allies emerge victorious?
The curtain is about to rise on
an unprecedented battle royale!
[GRAND MINISTER] Ladies and
Gentlemen, quiet, please.
We will now hear some
words of welcome
from the Omni-Kings themselves.
[BOTH]
Thank you all!
This will be so fun!
We've been looking
forward to this very much!
So fight well...
[BOTH]
...and give us a good show!
[NARRATOR]
The battles commence... now!
"Survive!
The Tournament of Power
Begins at Last!"
Wow!
For those who neglected
to pore through
the rulebook assiduously,
I'll lay out the basic
guidelines for the battles.
The competition
will last 100 tacks.
The column in the center
will descend as time elapses,
and once it reaches the ground,
all fighting will
officially conclude.
Uh, what's a hundred tacks?
I think it's roughly equivalent
to 48 Earth-minutes.
Really?! Isn't that
kinda short though?
Special techniques are allowed,
but the use of weapons
is prohibited--
as are any lethal
attacks or maneuvers.
However, you may force your
opponents off the ring,
and must do so to win.
For even if someone is
rendered unable to fight,
they will not be eliminated
unless they're out of bounds.
Well, that oughta give us
a little creative latitude
in how we approach these fights.
[GRAND MINISTER]
Energy-based flight techniques
that would prevent
you from falling
will not be accessible
to you here.
However, those of you who
possess wing-like appendages
will still be able to fly.
Lastly, regardless of how
wounded you may be,
the use of restorative
implements
is expressly forbidden.
And that concludes our
review of the rules.
[QUITELA chuckles]
[FIGHTERS chattering]
Okay, enough talking.
Let's get this show on the road!
[GOHAN]
Listen up, guys!
Uh?!
[GOHAN] We're gonna follow
the Supreme Kai's advice.
We'll stick together and work
as one unified team, got it?
We should start out forming
a circle with our backs
to each other,
and no matter what,
we'll take 'em on in
groups of two or more.
Nobody fights alone.
Hmph. A cowardly strategy.
Well, I shall take it under
advisement, for now...
Oh, that's just perfect.
These two are never
gonna be team players.
[KALE whimpers]
[CAULIFLA]
Hey, Kale!
What're you actin'
all jittery for?
You're gonna make
the Sixth look bad
in front of all the
other universes.
It's just that...
everyone's so big and strong.
It's kinda scary.
What do you have to
be scared about?
You've just gotta tap into
that rage you're hidin'
and go all glow-y on 'em.
[CAULIFLA] And you'll win
this thing, hands down!
[gasps]
[GOKU chuckles]
All this palpable bloodlust I
sense in the air is refreshing.
Truly a salve for the soul
after all those wretched
fairies and teddy bears.
Okay, I'll handle all
the female warriors.
Master Roshi,
are you sure that's wise?
What if you're not ready yet?
[ROSHI]
Oh, don't worry. I'm ready.
[SUPREME KAI]
Do you think that our universe
actually stands a
chance of winning?
All we can do now is
hope that's the case.
You are correct to
recognize your impotence
in this situation,
as all three of your fates
rest solely in the hands
of those mortals now.
Stop talking like that, Whis!
Just 'cause you're not
at risk of disappearing.
[laughs] Yeah, I'll
be fine either way.
[BEERUS] Hmph. I'm counting
on you guys to win this!
Go Universe Seven!
You can do it!
I wanna see teamwork!
[QUITELA laughs]
Come on!
I don't believe my ears.
How pathetic to hear you
spouting off about
"teamwork," Beerus.
[BEERUS growls]
Just ignore him.
Oh? Are you not going to
come back at him, My Lord?
How unlike you!
Forget it. That guy's not
worth it! He's a joke!
[laughing]
Hey, let's just try to stay
close together, babe.
You read my mind.
[GRAND MINISTER] At last Grand
Zenos, it is time to begin.
Are we ready?
Yes, hurry!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Very well, then.
Now, if all competitors from
each of the eight universes
could assume their
starting positions.
[SUPREME KAI grunts]
[ELDER KAI whimpers]
[BEERUS growls]
[GOKU]
Heh, heh!
Let the Tournament
of Power begin!
[LAVENDER, BASIL, BERGAMO growl]
[FIGHTERS yell]
[TOP yells]
[SHOSA, KETTLE grunting]
[FIGHTERS grunting]
[FROST yells]
[FIGHTERS grunting, yelling]
[ZENO, FUTURE ZENO gasping]
[ALL gasp]
[ALL gasping]
Oh, boy!
Looks like all hell's
breakin' loose, huh?
Ah, found ya!
There you are!
Wait, Dad, come back!
[TOP, MAGETTA grunt]
Hey, c'mon, Top!
Let's go, you and me, right now!
[TOP]
Huh?!
[yelling]
[GANOS grunts]
[GOKU grunting]
What happened to
teamwork, Dad?!
Did you completely forget
about our strategy?
Huh?!
[KRILLIN gasps]
Aw, come on now, you, too?
If everyone else is having fun,
I might as well partake.
What the...?
We had a plan.
Don't worry about it, Gohan.
It's not like we didn't see it
coming with so many egos.
Why did we even bother
devising a strategy?
Oh, good grief, what a mess.
These mortals will be the
death of me. Literally.
[NARIRAMA grunts]
[CAULIFLA]
Ha!
[NIGRISSI yells]
[NARIRAMA]
Na... ri... rama...!
Nari... rama!
[NARIRAMA yells]
[ALL gasp, yelp]
Appalling! That brute attacked
Brianne and the others
before they even had
a chance to transform.
Which is not beautiful at all!
[CABBA grunts]
[BOTH scream]
That spinning move's
a dirty trick,
and why the heck
didn't we think of that?!
[EYRE laughs]
Super survival mode!
What a truly marvelous
survival tactic!
[ALL groaning]
[MOSCO beeping]
Lord Mosco says,
"Show no mercy.
Take the other warriors out
by any means necessary.
Mow them down, sweep them off
the edge of the platform.
Now."
With dynamos like
Narirama on our side,
I'm confident that
the Third Universe
will be the ones to survive!
[MOSCO beeping]
Wow, nice hit, Hit!
That's how you do it!
[NARIRAMA groans]
[laughing]
Ha, ha! Bravo!
Excellent work, Basil!
[NARIRAMA groans]
[NIGRISSI]
Narirama!
What the...?
Our best laid plans have gone
awry! How could this be?!
[MOSCO beeping]
[CHAMPA laughs]
I guess that's what they mean by
"Pride goeth before the fall."
Ya got that, Universe Three?!
Looks like their
secret plan failed!
We have our first
failed strategy!
It would appear the
Third Universe's plan
to clear the field
has been met with
inglorious defeat.
[RYLIBEU]
Ha!
[BASIL grunting]
[BASIL]
Come on!
You sure are pretty slippery,
you mangy mutt!
Don't get too cocky!
Just 'cause you can fly,
don't mean nothin'!
Shining Blaster!
[RYLIBEU screaming]
[BASIL]
Here, have another! Plus One!
[RYLIBEU groaning]
[RYLIBEU screams]
[BOTH gasp]
Yeah, that's our Kicking Basil!
Way to go!
[RYLIBEU screaming]
[screaming]
Uh?
Uh-- Uh?
So that's what happens.
When you fall outta the ring,
you get transported back over
to the spectator seats.
Ah, Contestant Rylibeu
of the Tenth Universe
has been swiftly eliminated.
Omni-Kings, it is now time
to turn to your godPads.
[BOTH]
Yay!
[FUTURE ZENO]
Tap, tap.
Now, let's see...
Rylibeu, Rylibeu...
Boop!
Bye-bye, Rylibeu!
[ZENO]
She's gone, huh?
Hey, let me do the next one.
Okie dokie!
I'm so ashamed of myself.
As well you should be!
Dummy, what do you
think your wings are for
if not to stop you from falling?
I'm really sorry!
It just happened so fast,
my mind went blank and I
totally forgot I could fly!
[RUMSSHI] Imagine, the
tournament's first casualty
coming from my team.
You've brought great shame upon
the entire Tenth Universe!
Only nine more of
these losers to go
until I'm obliterated forever!
Well, there isn't
anything we can do
about her falling out, is there?
So let's just focus on the
warriors we still have left.
And Rylibeu, you can help by
cheering the others on with us.
You've got it.
Come on, Universe Ten, let's go!
Congratulations, you're gonna
be the second one to fall!
[BOTH grunting]
That's it, Basil! Go for glory!
Push him over the edge!
Hey! Listen!
Nobody from Universe Seven
drops out! Got it?!
[CHAMPA]
Yo, Sixth Universe!
Hurry up and knock
the Seventh out!
Every last one of 'em!
[laughing]
[FIGHTERS grunting, yelling]
[A18 grunts]
[yells]
[A18, COCOTTE grunting]
[HYSSOP screams]
[HARMIRA screams]
--[CATOPESRA groans]
--[FRIEZA chuckles]
[GOKU grunts]
[chuckles]
What are you waiting for?
Why don't you entertain us,
Universe Seven.
[ROSHI]
Hmm...
[FIGHTERS laughing]
[GOHAN grunts]
We meet again, Saiyan.
Only this time, it isn't
gonna end in a draw!
[ROSHI]
Settle down, Gohan.
You came up with a
solid strategy here.
Don't second-guess it now.
Well, that's just brilliant.
They're surrounded!
No, it'll be all right.
They have each other's backs
and are facing their
rivals collectively.
Just as we planned.
[laughing]
[yells]
Solar Flare!
[ALL groaning]
Special Beam Cannon!
Destructo Disk!
[yells]
[grunts, yells]
[FIGHTERS laughing]
These guys are the real deal.
I can definitely see why they
were chosen to be here.
Stay on your toes.
We have to be ready for them.
You got it!
Basil, look! Right behind you!
Huh?!
[BASIL]
Chew on this, fat boy!
[NAPAPA grunts]
Come on!
Dosukoi!
This is the end of
the line for you!
Down you go!
[NAPAPA gasping]
Enjoy the view...
from the sidelines!
[NAPAPA grunting]
[NAPAPA]
Dosukoi!
[GOWASU]
All right, Napapa!
Way to hang in there!
[ALL laughing]
Well, of course he
hung in there!
Napapa is a renowned Dohyodor
Yokozuna, with a reputation
for being an absolute wiz
at the edge of the ring.
Unlike some fighters.
[NAPAPA grunts]
Ah, much respect.
[BOTH]
Dohyodor, wha...?
A martial art indigenous
to the Tenth Universe.
And a Yokozuna is the most
powerful of the Rikishi,
possessing great skills,
as we've just witnessed.
[FUTURE ZENO]
Wow! That's really neat!
[ZENO]
So interesting!
[DYSPO, KAHSERAL yell]
[A18, COCOTTE grunting]
[VEGETA grunting]
[GOKU grunting]
[GANOS growls]
Huh?!
[TOP]
Justice Flash!
Yo, Top!
[TOP]
Huh? Ugh, Goku again.
--[whirring]
--Huh?
[MURICHIM grunts]
[GOKU]
Hm? Hmm...
Hey, I think that's
that Jiren guy.
[ZENO]
Whoa, you see that one?
Looky, looky!
Ooh, that's something different.
It is, it is!
The Tournament of Power...
[ZENOS]
...is so much fun!
[RABANRA yells]
[RABANRA grunts, gasps]
Jiren hasn't moved
a muscle yet.
Yeah, nor would I expect him to.
That's kind of his shtick,
the whole stoic thing.
[GOKU grunts]
[BEERUS]
Ah!
Oh no, Goku!
For goodness' sake,
he dropped his guard again.
That boy'll never learn.
[laughing] Get a load of how
ridiculously strong Nink is.
I mean, look at those biceps!
--[NINK chuckles]
--[GOKU choking]
Ironic, the mastermind behind
this entire tournament
will be one of the first
ones eliminated.
Goku! Are you just gonna let him
handle you like a
sack of potatoes?!
You've got more power than that!
Unleash the fury!
[NINK grunting]
[GOKU grunts]
[NINK laughs]
I love strong you
more than weak you!
Ha, ha. The more you fight,
the more I love you!
[QUITELA laughs]
[NINK laughing]
[GOKU]
Hey, wait, are you crazy?
You're gonna fall off,
too, you know!
Oh, that's okay.
As long as I got my
strong little buddy with me!
Oh, great! He's diving over
the edge and taking Goku!
Not a bad way to take out
another team's best fighter.
Wish we had thought of it.
--[GOKU groaning]
--[NINK laughing]
Come on, friend, let's go
to Other World together!
Next stop, Other World!
You can go there... all by...
...yourself!
[NINK screams]
[screams]
Huh?
Goku?!
Did Goku fall out?
[GOKU grunting]
Whew, that was a close one, huh!
What is wrong with you, Goku?!
If you could overpower
him with Blue,
then why didn't
you do it sooner?!
[GOKU] Sorry for giving you
a scare, Lord Beerus!
I was just trying
to save my energy.
That's all well and good,
but if you lose because
you're holding back,
then what's the
point of saving it?
That didn't go the way
I saw it goin'.
[QUITELA]
Ya think?!
All you did was cost
our team a man, you clod!
Contestant Nink of
the Fourth Universe
has officially been eliminated.
[ZENO]
Tap, tap.
Where's Nink, where's Nink?
Oh! Boop!
Nink goes bye-bye.
I wonder who will
go bye-bye next.
Yeah, me, too, me, too!
[BERGAMO chuckles]
[BASIL, LAVENDER laughing]
[GOKU]
Hm?
[FIGHTERS laughing]
[GOKU]
There sure are a lot of you here
just to take on
little old me, huh?
That's okay, it'll make
it more interesting.
Didn't think it was
going be this much fun.
[NARRATOR]
With the fate of eight universes
hanging in the balance,
the Tournament of Power
is at last underway.
Which contestant will
be the next to fall,
putting their universe one
step closer to elimination?
And, in the end, who will be
the last warrior standing?
The Tournament of Power
has only just begun.
Forty-seven Earth-minutes
remain until time is up!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super!
When the time has come
to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever in my mind
as I look up to the sky
I was watching you
from your left side
Was trying to get
a good look at your face
The tears in your eyes;
were you laughing or crying?
Your long hair in the way
Blocking the thoughts inside
When the time has
come to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever I will wait,
for the light to show the way
For us to meet again
[GOKU]
Hey, it's me, Goku!
The Tournament of Power's
turned into a real melee,
right from the start,
and lucky me,
I'm getting a personal visit
from the Ninth Universe's
welcoming committee!
Boy, these guys are
tougher than they look,
and they really wanna
take me out, bad!
Still, me and Vegeta have
a few tricks up our sleeves.
Oh, wait, I don't
have any sleeves!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Ah, the Uncertainty!
A Universe Despairs!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?