♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Grand Zeno made everyone
nervous when he summoned Goku,
but it turned out he just
wanted a new friend.
Meanwhile, Zamasu,
and his master, Gowasu,
observed the future
of an alien race,
but were disappointed the beings
had wasted their intelligence
in favor of barbarism.
How can we call ourselves gods
if we watch this blight
and do nothing to stop it?
[NARRATOR]
And at last,
Trunks returned to his
apocalyptic future.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
This is Mai's.
She was lying right
here when I left.
[NARRATOR] Can Goku and the
others save Trunks' future?
The next battle with
Goku Black starts now!
[GOKU gasps]
[NARRATOR]
"Rematch with Goku Black!
Enter Super Saiyan Rosé."
[yelps]
Incoming!
[yells]
All right!
[chuckles]
Great. Plan B!
[clicking]
This is for everyone
you've killed!
Eat lead, murderer!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Hold your fire!
This man isn't Black!
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER A]
What?
It's Commander Trunks!
Don't you remember the
battle on Mango Hill?
He fought Black to a standstill!
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER B yelps]
It won't happen again,
Commander Trunks!
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER A] It's an
honor to be in your presence.
If it wasn't for you
reinforcing us on Mango Hill,
the Resistance would have--
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER B panting]
Can I get your autograph?
What are you doing
asking for that
in the middle of a warzone?
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER B]
But I just thought...
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER A]
Well, you thought wrong!
I'd love his autograph,
too, y'know,
but you don't see me
bugging him, do ya?
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER B]
If you want it, too,
then let's ask together.
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER A]
We can't do that now,
it's too embarrassing.
[sighs]
[BOTH]
Hmm...
[GOKU chuckles nervously]
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER A]
Sorry about that.
We almost blasted ya good.
You really do look almost
exactly like Black.
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER B]
And your friend havin' that
mean-lookin' face didn't
help matters, either.
See, Vegeta? They say
its your face's fault!
It's your face
that's the problem!
[GOKU] No, it's not! I don't
have a villainous-looking face.
I mean, you might.
And Black certainly does--
Hey, that's enough fighting.
We still owe these soldiers
a proper introduction.
Allow me to introduce
Goku and Vegeta.
Explaining any more
could take a while.
Well, now that we know
they're with you, Commander,
we can only assume they're
reinforcements from the past
here to defeat Black.
Uh?
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER B]
It's still really weird, though.
Of all the possible
reinforcements,
this Goku looks like the guy
he's supposed to fight.
And the other back-up looks
even scarier than Black!
You better shut up
about my face now!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
What's going on?
The only other people
who knew about the plan
to use the time machine
were Mom and Mai.
And they're both gone.
[gasps]
It couldn't be.
Who told you about
the time travel plan?
Uh, well, it was Mai.
Who else would tell us that?
[gasps]
[RESISTANCE SOLDIERS groaning]
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Mai.
Is that you?
Mai!
I thought you were dead.
I could say the same of you.
I didn't know what to do.
Again, I could say
the same thing.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
This is too much.
[gasps]
Uh, hey.
[FUTURE TRUNKS] It's like
waking up from a nightmare.
I... I thought for sure
that I lost you, Mai.
[FUTURE MAI]
Dummy.
You should know I'm
harder to kill than that.
Now stop crying, soldier!
That's an order!
But I'm glad that you're back.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Yeah.
[GOKU giggling]
[VEGETA]
Hmph.
[FUTURE MAI gasps]
You found a nice
location for the new base.
Thank you.
After I came to,
I linked up with Resistance
soldiers mounting a defense.
And our previous base had
already come under attack.
[REFUGEES screaming]
Hurry! This way!
Fire!
[ALL scream]
Fight back!
Trunks will be back.
Back from the past
with reinforcements
so we can destroy Black.
Are you with me?
Are you with me?!
Then let's show him
we're not giving up!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
So, you bought time
for all the refugees
to get here.
[FUTURE MAI]
Some.
[FUTURE MAI] These are
the only ones who made it.
[VEGETA]
This is all that's left?
[FUTURE MAI]
Yes.
I should've saved more.
I think you did the best you
could with what you had, Mai,
and there's no shame in that.
Right.
[footsteps]
Thank you.
[MAKI giggles]
Yo!
[whimpering]
[GOKU]
Uh.
[HARU growls]
[laughs]
[laughing]
[MAKI, HARU laughing]
Thank you for saving
smiles like these.
Oh, Trunks.
Oh, wow.
You know how to lift our spirits
with your words and your looks.
Whoa, slow down.
We'd be honored if the great
Trunks stayed here, right?
[REFUGEES chattering]
[REFUGEE A]
Sit with us, Commander Trunks!
[VEGETA]
Hmph.
--[GOKU chuckles]
--[VEGETA] Tch.
[GOKU]
Uh. Uhh...
[VEGETA] All right,
make room! Outta my way!
Let's go! Move it!
Do you know what
he's trying to do?
No.
[REFUGEES gasping]
Thank you!
It's not from me.
Your mother put this
together for them.
She says there's more
where that came from.
Do whatever you want with them.
[gasps]
Thanks!
[GOKU] Wow! Bulma really
came through, huh?
[VEGETA] Hmph. Of course she
did! She is my wife, after all.
Well, what do you say
we chow down like a Saiyan?
[REFUGEES cheering]
Ahh...
[grunting]
[GOKU]
Huh?
Hey, pal, you look familiar.
[FUTURE YAJIROBE]
Hm?
Wait, Yajirobe?!
Goku?
How in the world have you
survived all this time?
What about you?
Ain't'cha supposed to be dead?
I don't understand, Yajirobe.
I always thought the
Androids got you.
[FUTURE YAJIROBE]
They almost did.
But when they
attacked the tower,
Korin said, "Save yourself."
And then he... he gave me
the last Senzu Bean!
Just thinking about what
he did makes me all weepy.
Well, for someone who
hates getting involved
as much as you do,
I'm surprised to see you
here with the Resistance.
Sounds like Korin saving him
must've motivated Yajirobe
to take a stand and
fight for a change.
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER A] Actually,
every time there's a fight,
he disappears.
He only pops his head up
when someone puts out food.
Aw, come on!
You can't talk about a man in
front of his friends that way!
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER A]
I'm not lying! It's the truth.
[FUTURE YAJIROBE]
All right, ha-ha-ha.
You can stop kiddin' around now!
[FUTURE MAI]
It's been a long time
since I've seen them so happy.
Thank you for
everything you've done.
I wouldn't be thanking
us just yet, Mai.
Our mission here isn't complete
until we defeat Black
and restore peace
to your timeline.
So are you going
to fight him, too?
Yeah.
[VEGETA]
No, you're coming to observe.
I can defeat Black by myself.
What? I wanna
crack at him again!
It's my turn and I won't
let you take it from me.
Wait. Let's rock-paper-scissors!
I said no!
[GOKU]
One, two, throw!
[VEGETA]
I'm not playing!
[GOKU]
Aw, c'mon, Vegeta! It's fun!
Well, they don't seem very
worried at all, now do they?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Uh...
[GOKU, VEGETA]
Throw!
What?! I lost?!
Oh, Kakarot,
you're so predictable.
--[FUTURE TRUNKS] Father.
--[VEGETA] Hm?
Please, let me fight
Black with you.
It's our world, after all.
And since we have to live here,
I should be the one to save it.
[VEGETA]
Of course not.
Father, c'mon!
It's possible this is
a fight we cannot win.
If we fall against Black,
at least you can survive
and build your own future
with your girlfriend.
[BOTH gasp]
[GOKU]
I'm kinda shocked that Vegeta
would be the one to
say it, but he's right.
Plus, she is pretty cute!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Yeah, but we're not--
We're just friends!
Comrades-in-arms, really!
[FUTURE MAI]
Uh, yeah.
[GOKU]
Mh-hm.
All right. Let's throw down!
[FUTURE MAI]
Be safe, and you better win!
It's heartbreaking to
see a world so scarred.
But the purge is necessary.
I can see a bright,
shining future here
once it's finally free of
the mortals who defile it,
like the barbarous
vermin they are.
It won't be long until this
planet's reborn as a utopia.
[laughs]
You mortal menace. My final
judgement is now upon you.
[GOKU] Well, if that
doesn't get his attention,
I don't know what will.
[thunder rumbles]
[GOKU]
Hm?
He's here!
Damn you!
I could've sworn I destroyed
your time machine.
Ha! There's something
I'd like you to see.
This is Super Saiyan Blue.
And it's going to
bury you in the ground.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Dad's Super Saiyan Blue form
doesn't even faze Black.
It's like... like somehow
he knew it was coming.
[GOKU BLACK clapping]
A most brilliant display.
A Saiyan body enveloped in
divine energy is beautiful,
even if it's wrong.
[growls]
[GOKU BLACK] But while you've
trained to an incredible degree,
you remain nothing more
than a mortal being.
[VEGETA] How did he get
through my guard like that?
He must've already powered up
since Kakarot
fought him in our time.
[VEGETA]
Oh, well.
That means nothing when faced
with Super Saiyan Blue!
Whoa.
It's pretty spooky
to watch somebody
who looks exactly like you get
his face pounded in like that.
Now I know how
Vegeta must've felt
when we were back
on Planet Pot-au-feu.
--Hey, Goku.
--[GOKU] Hm?
Did you hear what he said?
A "mortal being."
Doesn't that imply that
Black's a god? Is he Zamasu?
I don't know. I still can't
wrap my head around it all.
[yells]
[VEGETA yelling]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[VEGETA]
What the--? I sense something.
[groans]
You okay?
For a lowly animal,
you've come quite far.
As a reward, I'll show
you how far I've come.
Say what?
[yelling]
What's going on over there now?
[REFUGEES gasping]
[yells]
What is this?
He's changing.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
A new form?
What do think of it?
Quite the color, huh?
In keeping with how you like
to label your power levels,
the name of this one is "Rosé."
That's right. I have now
reached Super Saiyan Rosé.
Hold on, Super Saiyan Rosé?
[GOKU BLACK laughing]
[GOKU BLACK] At last, I have not
only mastered Goku's powers,
I have made them my own.
[GOKU BLACK laughs]
[GOKU BLACK]
Go on, Goku! Rejoice!
Only through me will you finally
reach the pinnacle of beauty
you have sought
for so very long.
I don't know what
you're rambling on about,
but just get on with the fight.
Of course you don't.
Your mind is too small.
Your kind is incapable
of understanding
the grandeur of my success
and the glory of my cause.
It's like staring into the sun.
You cannot see.
The vast beauty of
my being overwhelms you.
For I am a breed apart.
And Divine.
[GOKU] He's startin'
to rub me the wrong way.
--[VEGETA] Black!
--[GOKU BLACK] Hm?
[VEGETA] What are you doing
talking to Kakarot?!
You're supposed
to be fighting me!
[GOKU BLACK] Aw, you don't
you understand, Saiyan.
Your time is already at an end.
[VEGETA]
Like hell it is!
[GOKU BLACK]
You were the opening act.
Now leave the stage.
[yells]
You don't know your place!
Get outta there!
[yells]
[VEGETA]
I'm not the opening act.
I'm the star of this damn show!
[chuckles]
--[thud]
--[VEGETA groans]
[BOTH gasp]
You... How'd you do that?
Calling you the opening
act is a weak metaphor.
It's much more like...
...you're just the appetizer.
That's right,
a light introduction
before I commence
with the main course.
Why... you vile bastard!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Father!
[GOKU BLACK laughing]
You've helped refine my palette
and made me that much stronger.
Now watch as I consume
the main dish
and rise to an even greater
level of power still!
I can hardly wait.
I'm going in.
Stay back!
Goku, wait!
[yells]
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Super Saiyan Blue.
He's going into the fight
already at full power.
[GOKU]
Trunks, go check on Vegeta.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Uh. Right!
I take it this is what
you meant when you said
that any pain I inflict
will only make you stronger?
[GOKU BLACK] I am already
at a level no mortal
can even dream of reaching.
I see it in your face.
You crave a taste of
this power, don't you?
Yeah. You may be right!
[GOKU yells]
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Father!
Father.
They're equal.
[VEGETA]
No, they're not.
He's strong!
A Kamehame-Ha?
[VOICE]
That's enough!
[gasps]
[GOKU]
Hm?
[VOICE] I will not allow you
to act on your own any further.
Is that Zamasu?
No way. It can't be.
[gasps]
Looks like I was
wrong about them.
Black and Zamasu
aren't the same guy.
[FUTURE ZAMASU]
I thought we had an agreement.
Wasn't I supposed
to be the one...
...who gets the honor
of destroying him?
[gasps]
Get ready!
Instant Transmission!
Two fingers placed
right between the eyes
Get ready!
My hair will stand up!
'Cause I got
all the power of a Saiyan!
Ohhhh HEY!
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! (KAMEHAMEHA!)
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! It's what you need
Feel the magic of the beat
(Woo-hoo)
DANCE! It makes you smile
Nothing else can
quite compete (yoka yoka)
So when the world is lame
Don't play that game
You know that every problem
can be answered the same
Just let go and feel the rhythm
Everybody dance
with all your might!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And talk about a
time-twisting surprise!
Zamasu isn't Black,
but he's working with him ?
I better keep my head on
straight against this pair,
or I'm gonna be in trouble.
And Trunks has gotta help, too!
But it looks like our attacks
don't work on Zamasu at all,
so what do we do now?
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"A God with an Invincible Body.
The Advent of Zamasu."
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?