♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR]
"Goku Enkindled!
The Awakened One's
New Ultra Instinct!"
[ALL gasping]
[GOKU grunting]
[yells]
[ZENOS]
Whoa!
He stopped it!
That was very close!
[BEERUS]
Hmph.
Yes! Don't give up
Saiyan, finish this!
[JIREN grunts]
[ZENOS gasping]
He's still pushing!
I am amazed!
[GOKU grunting]
It's a considerable
amount of energy, indeed.
Most effective.
Yes, it's a great achievement.
Such might cannot be gained
through any normal discipline.
Jiren is especially astonishing.
The way he can exert and
command such incredible force
with merely a glare. It is a
wondrous strength to behold.
[GOKU grunting]
[ROASIE yelps]
Huh?
[GOKU grunting]
[WHIS] It seems Goku has reached
the very limit of his power.
While Jiren remains
calm and collected
and is a far cry from
going all out, my lord.
[BEERUS growls]
Astounding.
I've never felt such force.
Not in all my life.
His strength...
is beyond words.
Indeed, and if I
were to measure,
I would have to say,
his power is at the level
of a Destroyer God.
And perhaps it is even higher.
I have heard a rumor
that one of the universes
has produced a mortal who has
surpassed his own Destroyer.
A wild notion, but... now I
see that it may be true.
That's right, Jiren.
Show the cosmos the full extent
of your remarkable power.
Do your duty and destroy Goku!
Am I the only one concerned
about that giant ball of energy?
[VADOS] The pressure of
their colliding powers
is causing the energy
ball to expand,
and it cannot remain
stable for much longer.
[ZENOS]
Whoa! Wow!
[GOKU grunting]
[yelling]
[inaudible]
[TOP]
It's over, Jiren.
Victory is yours.
[ZENOS]
Huh...?
It would seem the
standoff has ended.
[ZENOS]
Whoa! Ha, ha!
I thought that was
amazing, did you?
Oh yes, I thought that too!
I must admit I feel relieved
the ring was able to withstand
that blast. However, sires...
[ZENOS]
Huh?
[gasping]
[ZENO] You don't think
he is finished, do you?
[FUTURE ZENO]
Oh, my. Could he have lost?
[BEERUS gasping]
[SUPREME KAI]
No, it can't be.
[KRILLIN]
He hasn't warped to the bench.
That means he's
down there, right?
[TIEN]
I don't know.
I don't sense his energy
anywhere in the ring.
[ELDER KAI]
Goku was in the middle of that
massive explosion. I'm afraid
he may have been obliterated.
[KRILLIN, TIEN, ROSHI gasp]
[ROSHI]
Obliterated?
Hold up. That would mean
he's dead, right?
That's perfect!
Then that means Jiren
will be disqualified!
--I don't think so, my lord.
--Huh?
Goku's the one who launched
the initial energy blast
that swelled and ultimately
destroyed him.
In that case...
[GRAND MINISTER]
You are correct.
While Jiren did play a role
in expanding its power,
it was Goku's attack and he
therefore eliminated himself.
I hereby rule that contestant
Jiren of the Eleventh
Universe receives no penalty.
Superb. Without Goku, the
Seventh won't stand a chance.
I say we have Jiren keep going
and end this tournament.
It is time.
Agreed. The Eleventh
shall win the day.
And survive this
dreaded gathering.
[CHAMPA]
Hm?
It seems even after
witnessing Jiren's power,
several of the other universes
have still not lost the
will to fight, my lord.
Such courage.
[CHAMPA growls]
Hey! Let's go, Sixth!
Keep on attacking,
don't just stand there!
Chase them down! Push them out!
Find a way to win!
Do whatever it takes!
Sound advice.
Let me remind you, contestants.
Not even half the allotted time
for the Tournament of Power
has elapsed.
Until this column has
completely descended,
all survivors have a chance.
No matter which
fighters or universes
have been eliminated,
the battle will go on.
So I encourage you
to make the most of it.
[BEERUS] Is it true? Is this
really the end for you, Saiyan?
And for us?
[growling]
Goku! Are you finished?!
[rumbling]
[VEGETA grunts]
Feel that?
Yeah.
[TOP, DYSPO]
Hm?
[TOP]
What are those tremors?
[ELDER KAI] The ring--no,
the entire Null Realm--
is being shaken by some
sort of influx of power!
[SUPREME KAI] But what could
it mean? What's causing it?
If you ask me, there's
only one good answer!
Yes, I agree. Heh, heh, heh.
Time for the real fun to begin.
Beerus, my lord. Is there
something you wish to say?
[BEERUS]
Here it comes.
[ZENO]
Ooh! Goku's okay after all!
[FUTURE ZENO] Yes!
He is okay and very sparkly!
[BOTH laughing]
[ZENO]
I am thrilled!
[FUTURE ZENO]
Thrilled and excited!
Goku endures. What has he done?
I don't know how
to explain this,
but based on what I'm sensing,
it's safe to say he didn't
survive on dumb luck.
Something's different
about him, that's for sure.
Yes.
I'm sensing an incredible
strength from him, and yet...
His energy is so calm,
it's giving me the creeps.
[WHIS] Let us watch
and see what happens.
After all, this
is the first time
even I have seen Goku
in this curious state.
[DYSPO, TOP grunt]
♪♪
Go go go go go the distance
No no no no way we'll give in
Fight fight in the ultimate
battle just for fun
Nothing to prove
So let's brawl til
the battle's won
[PICCOLO] Goku may only
have grazed Jiren,
but he did connect.
Considering he couldn't touch
this guy in his Blue form,
that's saying something.
He's amazing.
I've never seen my dad move like
this before, not in any form.
It's not just that he's a lot
faster, it's more than that...
I can't sense him transitioning
to his attacks at all.
Yeah. His dodges are
like that as well.
What the hell is going on?
I'm watching this
with my own eyes
but I still can't believe what
he's doing is actually possible!
Kakarot, what have you become?
[TOP] You don't know
when to surrender, Goku.
You've already lost this fight!
[TOP, DYSPO grunting]
[ALL gasping]
This is no everyday
power up, boys.
That reaction speed...
And such precision...
[KRILLIN] It's crazy!
How is Goku doing this?
[WHIS]
Hmm...
[TOP grunts]
Take this, scoundrel!
Justice Flash!
Huh? You want me to stand down?
[sighs] You wish to
face Goku alone.
So, who would you say
has the upper hand now?
I think it's too early to tell.
That said...
There used to be a massive
power gap between them,
but Goku has clearly closed it.
And that's not all.
As strong as he's become,
seems Goku's not done improving.
Every time Jiren fends
him off, Goku responds
with an even faster,
sharper, and harder strike.
I'm speechless.
I never imagined any mortal
could push Jiren this far.
What the--?! How can
this be happening?!
[ZENO] Ooh! Goku has become
so much stronger now!
[FUTURE ZENO] Yes! Much stronger
and much more amazing, too!
Tell me why!
Tell me how!
[GRAND MINISTER]
Hm... Could it really be?
It's so wonderful!
I hoped for this.
But I have to admit,
I wasn't sure if the Saiyan
would ever be able
to achieve it!
[SUPREME KAI] Then you know
what's happened to him?
[WHIS]
Yes, I believe so!
Oh, I have tried to steer
him towards this forever!
Ha ha ha some say it's foolish
We don't care 'cause
we were born to fight
That's all we want
Give it your all
Go until you become undone
Autonomous Ultra Instinct.
[gasps]
[sputtering]
[ALL whimper]
So that's how he's
reacting so quickly.
I see. But Goku
is a mortal being,
and that is an extremely
elite level of power,
difficult for even the
highest Gods to reach.
[BELMOD]
It can't be! It can't!
It's impossible!
[ROSHI] I'm not sure what
you're talking about,
but the other deities
certainly seem to be
pretty concerned about it.
Hm?
Mm...
[FRIEZA chuckles]
All the others are
surprised, too!
It must be something
super-spectacular!
Well... At this
point it would be
premature for me to verify
it as true. However,
it is certainly a development
that demands attention.
[ZENO]
I am excited!
[FUTURE ZENO]
Excited and thrilled!
In this marvelous cosmos
wonders really do happen,
don't they, my lord?
[BEERUS growls]
The deities from other Universes
seem to know what
this is, Great Ancestor.
Wait. Are you telling me
you don't know about this level,
you wet-eared rookie?
[SUPREME KAI]
Mm!
But why now?
And why is it Goku?
Well my lord, the
Saiyan's Spirit Bomb
most likely served
as the catalyst.
Uh. You mean Goku absorbed
the Spirit Bomb's energy
and he's using it to fight?
I doubt that.
The Spirit Bomb was strong
but Jiren pushed it back.
Even if Goku added all of its
energy to his own power,
it still wouldn't be enough.
You are correct, Tien.
Most likely, Goku has used
the Spirit Bomb's energy
to replenish his exhausted
body. But as you said,
that alone would not be
sufficient to explain
what we're seeing now.
It was the start.
A match that lit a much
greater power within.
My theory is when the
Spirit Bomb exploded
so close to him, its tempestuous
power coursed into Goku
and smashed into
his own energy,
which he was already
pushing to its max.
This was the collision he
needed to shatter the ceiling
of his power, and reach
an even greater potential
that has always been
locked within him,
but he could never fully reach.
He broke through his ceiling?
Yes. He's now in
uncharted territory.
And it remains to be seen
what will happen to him
as he tries to
sustain this fervor.
[yelling]
[growls]
[yells]
Well, Saiyan.
You are a truly
fascinating creature.
However...
[GOKU grunting]
[JIREN]
...your passion is expended.
You have nothing more to offer.
[GOKU screams]
[ALL gasping]
That power up. It looks
like it was only temporary.
Of course it was.
You really think he could master
such a divine level
on his first try?
Ah! Hit's sneak
attack didn't work!
[VADOS] A fighter is at his
most vulnerable the moment
he delivers a finishing blow.
Yet Jiren was still
able to counter.
The infamous assassin
of the Sixth Universe.
Just why are you here?
To do my job.
What was all that?
You will tell me everything now!
[GOKU groaning]
Looks like I used up all
my power. That's too bad.
[VEGETA]
Answer me!
[laughs]
Truth is, I'm not
even sure myself.
Of course you're not.
We'll talk later.
You'd best recover fast--
--[instant transmission]
--Huh?!
Kakarot?
[NARRATOR] Goku reached
an astounding new level,
an achievement that alarmed even
the highest ranks of the gods.
Only to see it
quickly fade away.
With only 25 minutes remaining
until the fateful end
of the Tournament,
can Goku grasp that power again?
My, my, doesn't this
feel familiar?
It's like Namek all over again.
A 70 centimeter squared window
Today the sun broke
through the clouds
The rain is fin'ly gone
Gonna open up
the window for once
No reason, just because
This room has been
stained with the sighs
Of everyday regret
Now it's time to clear the air
Every moment was consumed
with my thoughts of you
Knowing in my heart those dreams
won't be coming true
I've always wanted nothing more
than to see your face
I move on knowing that your
mem'ry can't be erased
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Jiren, the best of the
Eleventh Universe,
and Hit, the best of the Sixth,
are going toe-to-toe
in a battle of titans.
Hit's got a secret strategy
that uses Time-Skips
in a whole new way,
but will his clever trap
be enough against
Jiren's sheer power?
Just watching this fight
is getting me pumped!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"An Extra-Dimensional
Ultimate Battle!
Hit vs. Jiren!"
Be sure you don't miss it, okay?