♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Goku managed to outmaneuver
Hit's Time Skip
by predicting his attacks.
However, that wasn't enough
to stop the deadly assassin.
[HIT] Because I'm not
done improving yet.
[GOKU grunts]
[HIT] That time I skipped
forward half a second,
which is five times better
than my initial technique
and obviously more
than you can handle.
[NARRATOR] As Hit continued
to enhance his own powers
throughout the battle,
Goku finally revealed
a new spin on an old technique.
Now I'll show you the Kaio-ken!
Times ten!
[GOKU yells]
[HIT grunting]
[GOKU]
You're mine!
[yelling]
[NARRATOR]
"A Decision at Last!
Is the Winner Beerus?
Or Is It Champa?"
[TD REF yelling]
[coughing, groaning]
Ugh!
What happened with the match?
[coughs]
I can't see anythin--
[yelling]
Uh...
Just where did they go?
Wow, you're really
something, you know that?
What now? Both fighters
are out of bounds.
You're wrong.
Where they're now standing...
[CHAMPA]
...is still part of the ring.
[TD REF]
The match continues!
[HIT]
A worthy rival.
That's what inspires evolution
in a warrior's talents.
[GOKU grunts]
Right in that moment,
I increased my
Time Skip even farther.
That's how I dodged your attack.
And I'm going to
keep on improving.
Oh, is that so?
[GOKU chuckles]
I don't believe it!
Hit just smiled back at him!
[ELDER KAI laughing]
That's--
That's just the awesome
effect Goku can have.
Hey, I was just about to say
the exact same thing!
Don't steal my lines!
Huh...
I guess his stance
is evolving, too,
in correlation with
his growing powers.
Well, yes, I suppose
that would make sense.
These two are so evenly
matched, it's scary.
[GOKU] This guy is
off-the-charts powerful.
[grunting]
That ain't good.
Hey, Hit!
He can't keep this
Kaio-ken thing up for long!
There's no need
to mix it up with him!
If you just move around and
stay out of reach for a bit,
you're sure to win!
Honorable advice,
Lord Champa.
Is that sarcasm?
My, my, what
a keen observation.
Please, Lord Champa, reconsider!
Hit won't wanna win like that.
He's a very proud man, sir.
I don't care!
This contest is between
me and Beerus!
[MAGETTA]
Pow. Whiz.
[CHAMPA]
You keep your ego in check.
Listen up! Okay?
You worthless people are
nothing more than pawns
in our little game!
[gasps]
[yelling]
It doesn't really
matter, does it?
[CHAMPA]
What are you trying to say?
What I mean is you're
able to punish them
at any time if you so choose.
But for the moment,
I personally am much more
interested in seeing
how this contest here plays out.
Aren't you?
[GOKU] Thanks for not
backing down, Hit.
[GOKU] Now let's show them
we're more than just pawns.
We still have a say!
[GOKU] The 6th Universe's
team has been amazing.
I'd say they were all
pretty tough opponents.
[GOKU] I'm just glad
I finally got the chance
to fight the best of 'em all.
This is it!
[GOKU yelling]
[HIT yelling]
I wouldn't be surprised
if the dome shattered again
just from the sheer
force of their intensity.
[BOTH yelling]
My Time Skip has advanced
so much you can't keep up
with me anymore!
[GOKU choking]
[HIT]
Huh?
Impossible!
[GOKU yelling]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU]
Whew!
Yo, Lord Beerus!
Would you mind doing
me a small favor?
[BEERUS]
Huh?
If you don't have
a problem with it,
then I'd like you to lift all
the rules for the tournament.
[GOKU] If you don't
have a problem with it,
then I'd like you to lift all
of rules for the tournament.
[VEGETA]
Hey, Kakarot!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
You want a no-holds-barred
fight with that guy?
Of course not.
I mean, it's not the
ideal setup for me,
but I really want to
fight Hit at his full power,
and this is the only way
he's gonna be able to do that.
[HIT]
Huh?
Ah!
Yes, because Hit is an assassin!
[HIT] It's against the rules
for me to kill him, correct?
Due to the tournament's rules,
he's not allowed to use the
full range of his techniques.
So that's it.
As long as Hit's
forced to hold back
his most severe attacks,
he can't possibly show
off his full potential.
[GOKU] If you coulda used
some of your assassin tricks,
then who knows?
There's a pretty good chance
you would've killed me
after that last attack.
Right?
Anyway, sorry it took me
so long to realize all of that.
Though in my defense,
I did kinda have my
hands full back there.
But are you not afraid
that you might die?
Oh, you're not gonna
get me like that again.
I see.
Have to say, I never imagined
there were people
like you out there.
[CHAMPA]
Bravo!
[clapping]
This is the true spirit
of sportsmanship in action!
I'm so touched!
The rules are hereby revoked.
Extreme force is now legal.
Hold it!
This is unacceptable!
You can't just unilaterally
make rule changes!
But it was your own contestant
who made the request.
Just let him have it.
Oh, you are shameless!
The only reason that you
wanna change the rules
is to give yourself
an advantage!
Well now, that's pretty
rich coming from you
since the only reason you want
to leave the rules in place
is that it's to your advantage!
You make me so sick!
You already agreed to the rules!
You can't just undo that!
Yes, but it was your
contestant who asked me
to make this change!
[BEERUS] That may be, but you
can't go changing the rules..
[GOKU]
Oh, man.
Sounds like this won't
be over anytime soon.
[BEERUS]
You always do this!
[CHAMPA]
Yeah, well...
I'm afraid the two
of us may just be pawns
in their game after all.
For now, anyway.
What do you mean, "for now"?
Just for now. You know?
[BEERUS] There's enthusiasm
and then there's gluttony!
[CHAMPA]
You take that back!
[BEERUS]
Why should I?
[CHAMPA]
Oh, real mature of you!
[BEERUS]
You're one to talk!
[CHAMPA]
Get your hands off of me...
[GOKU]
Wow, they're really going at it.
They're totally hopeless,
aren't they?
[BEERUS]
Then let go!
[CHAMPA] Fine, on the count
of three, we both let go!
[BEERUS]
All right, I'll count!
[GOKU] Well, let's do
this again sometime,
when there's no rules
to get in our way
and we can give
it all we've got!
[CHAMPA]
Oh, yes I can! One, two--
[BEERUS]
I was being facetious!
[CHAMPA] I don't even
know what that means!
[TD REF]
Hey!
Look! I fell outta the ring!
See?
Yes, well, uh... Let's see.
As far as I could follow,
the rules are still
in effect, and they say...
...Contestant Hit is the winner!
[HIT]
Huh?
[BEERUS, CHAMPA]
Huh?!
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOKU grunting]
Are you all right?
I think... I might be done now.
How can you be so reckless?
[GOKU]
Sorry.
Every move you make
is a surprise to me.
Thank you for your patience!
The next fighter from
the 7th Universe
to face Contestant Hit is...
...Contestant Monaka!
Which makes this the final
match of the tournament.
The winner's team
will claim victory!
[GOKU grunting]
You idiot.
Well, I guess after that,
Kaio-ken might need
to go back on the shelf
for a little while.
Do you have the slightest
idea how much damage
that stunt of yours
has just caused me?
Yeah, yeah, I know,
but at the rate we were going,
my Kaio-ken was gonna run
out in the middle of the fight,
and I woulda lost to him anyway.
And you know,
it's kinda your own fault
for wasting so much time
arguing with your brother.
[BEERUS]
Shut up!
If you hadn't requested
that we throw the rules out,
then we wouldn't
have been arguing!
All right, all right,
just calm down, okay?
Don't forget, we still have
Monaka waiting in the wings,
and he's supposed to be
even stronger than I am.
See? We'll be fine.
[BEERUS growls]
[PICCOLO grunts]
What's wrong?
You'll see.
[TD REF] Is there a
problem, Contestant?
Make your way to
the ring, please.
[GOKU]
Go get 'im, Monaka!
You've got this!
Well, that's the best fighter
in the 7th Universe for ya!
He's so unpredictable,
he always keeps you guessing!
Wow, I cannot wait, man!
[bones crack]
I must have pulled
something really bad.
[BEERUS groaning]
It's hopeless.
I'm utterly finished!
It's all over!
[HIT]
So that's how it is...
Come on, let him have it, Hit!
[gong rings]
[TD REF]
Begin!
[MONAKA yells]
[HIT yells]
[ALL gasp]
[TD REF]
Uh...
That's a ring out!
Contestant Monaka wins!
Whoa, then that means...
The winner of the tournament
is the 7th Universe!
[ALL]
Hooray!
[ALL cheering]
Hold on, what just happened?
Did... Did he win?
Oh, wow!
That guy's awesome!
[KRILLIN]
Way to go!
[BULMA]
You're the best!
All of them are just so strong!
I really do wish that
I could recruit them
into the Galactic Patrol.
Bad idea, sir!
All Galactic Patrol uniforms
are on perpetual back order
for the foreseeable future.
--[KRILLIN] Goku!
--[GOTEN] Dad!
Thanks for cheering me on, guys!
--[bones crack]
--Ow!
Oh, my, are you all right?
You sure put up quite
a fight back there.
It was all thanks to you,
Galactic King, sir.
I mean, if you hadn't told me
that stuff about time skipping,
then I would have
been totally up a creek.
So, thank you!
That's a highly sensitive organ.
[GOKU yelling]
[ALL laughing]
And now our score
is settled, Goku.
[CHAMPA growls]
I don't need the
transport vessel.
So just let me go home now.
Oh, I see you're quite
the jokester, aren't you?
So that's how you
want to play this?
[MAGETTA]
Ker-plop.
Over and over again, you
ignored my direct orders.
And as if that
weren't bad enough,
you lost in the final round.
There's no way I'm letting
you leave this place alive.
[CABBA]
Lord Champa!
Please, I'm begging you--
[CHAMPA]
That goes for you, too!
Each and every one of
you so-called fighters
has failed and humiliated me.
[CHAMPA] And for that,
I'm going to destroy all of you!
--You can't!
--[BEERUS] Now, Goku...
Don't go stepping out of line,
forgetting your place.
Yeah, but Lord Beerus,
we can't just stand by.
[BEERUS] Look, you all did well
enough, in your own way.
And for that,
you have my praise.
But the competition's over now.
Which means your time in the
spotlight has come to an end.
That's right!
So, from here on out,
we gods are back in charge
and running the show again!
You got that?
We make the rules around here!
While you stupid puppets just
shut up and do as you're told!
[laughing]
[BEERUS]
That being said,
if you wanted to challenge
a Destroyer to a duel
in order to change the rules,
then I feel certain we
could arrange something.
[GOKU growls]
Lord Champa...
I'm ready if you are!
[chuckling]
I'll even let you use your
Time Skip, or go Super Saiyan,
or whatever other
gimmicks you want.
Lord Champa, look.
It doesn't matter.
I'll destroy everything!
I'll show you first-hand
the magnitude of terror
a Destroyer can rain down!
Lord Champa!
[CHAMPA]
Sheesh, what is it?
Wha--?
[yells]
Lord Beerus...
Huh?
[yells]
[GOKU]
Huh? Who's that?
No, it can't be!
You're kidding me, right?
That looks like--
But it couldn't--
Though maybe it could.
Is that...?
I-I-It really is...!
[BEERUS, CHAMPA]
Grand Zeno!
♪ Closing Song ♪
Wow
It's hard to say
Don't wanna stay
I twist and fight,
can't find my way
I must believe, that fear
and trouble can even be fun
if you think the right way
Wow
I don't wanna draw the line
I gotta see it through some way
Fight for what I know is mine
The dream I had of me that day
Wow
Don't care if they
call me greedy
If they hate me, make me blue
Don't care if they laugh at me
'Cause I will make
the dream come true
Wow
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Who is that teeny
little striped guy?
Whoever he is, seems like he's
making Beerus and Champa
awfully nervous.
Though I don't see why.
He doesn't look
that strong to me.
Oh well, we've got bigger
things to worry about.
Like what we're gonna wish for
with those Super
Dragon Balls we won!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Come Forth, Divine Dragon!
And Grant My Wish,
Peas and Carrots!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?