♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the Tournament of Power began,
and with universal
destruction on the line,
it was a contest like no other.
Lord Beerus told me to use
whatever tricks it
takes just to survive,
but I've gotta at least try
to take a few of 'em out!
Destructo Disk!
[NARRATOR] Using supercharged
techniques and combos
with Android 18, Krillin gave
a fantastic performance.
[KRILLIN]
Ha!
[MAJORA groaning]
[MAJORA screams]
[BEERUS] You're exceeding
my extremely low
expectations for you!
Oh, yeah! Hear that?
I am absolutely
Krillin' it today!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[FROST]
How quickly the tide can change.
[KRILLIN]
Eh?
[NARRATOR] But when he
briefly dropped his guard,
Krillin was knocked
from the ring.
His team must fight
with only nine.
Now!
[NARRATOR]
"Rampage!
A Crazed Warrior's
Savagery Awakens!"
Damn. Krillin's
taken out already?
Just stay calm.
We can either look at this
as being down a man
or as having nine strong,
expertly trained,
battle-tested warriors left.
[TIEN] Hmph. That's some
good advice, Master Roshi.
[ROSHI] It's not just
a turtle shell I carry.
I got the wisdom of age
on my back, boys.
[GOHAN]
He's right.
We can do this with nine.
We've all just
gotta stay focused.
Spin it all you want,
but it's still pathetic to get
knocked out just because
you were careless.
I can't say I'm proud to
call you my husband right now.
You wasted all that money
on your home gym,
just to leave our team short.
C'mon, Honey, I said
I'm sorry, okay!
[CHAMPA laughs]
How sad for your team, Brother!
I don't have time to
trade insults, Champa!
[CHAMPA] Hey that's an excellent
point, you don't have time!
Now that the Seventh Universe
is counting down
to its certain extinction,
I guess you don't have much
more time for anything! Ha, ha.
[BEERUS growls]
Oh looky, Beerus!
It seems your Saiyan Vegeta
is about to be the next victim!
Huh?
You gutless little bastards!
I'm sure if Magetta
could hear you right now
he'd be terribly insulted!
Damn these two!
[VEGETA grunts]
[CABBA]
Master!
Uh.
[MURISAM, NIGRISSI grunting]
[MURISAM, NIGRISSI groan]
[yells]
Unless you bow out now, we'll
have no choice but to fight!
[VEGETA grunts]
[HIT]
This battle is as good as over,
so I'm going to
give you a choice.
You can either leap
from the ring right now
or I can force you out.
[NARIRAMA]
Narirama...
[EYRE] Hm. While it's true
he's lost both his arms,
that core unit in his torso
is what really matters.
He can still fire
his main cannon.
[NARIRAMA]
Cannon charging complete.
Nari...
[HIT]
Hmph.
[NARIRAMA
...rama!
What-- But that's impossible!
[exhales]
How could Narirama be defeated
this early in the contest?
I'm sensing a strange presence
here, and it's not pleasant.
[METHIOP grunting]
[METHIOP groans]
I got him!
[METHIOP]
And now I've got you!
[METHIOP laughing]
[KALE groans]
[gasps]
That's my toe you're
squashin', lady.
[KALE whimpers]
No!
Let me go!
[laughing] Hey check it out,
partner, we've got ourselves
a living punching bag!
[METHIOP grunts]
I hope you're ready for this!
[gasping]
[METHIOP grunting]
Gut punch!
Gut punch! Gut punch!
Gut, gut, gut, gut,
gut, gut, gut, gut!
I love to hear you shriek!
[METHIOP laughing]
Wake up! Who said you
could pass out on us?
That's no fun.
How did such a light weight
get picked for this match?
Dosukoi!
I got ya, Kale. Are you okay?
[KALE]
Huh...
Caulifla, I failed you.
[CAULIFLA grunts]
[KALE] I should've been
stronger. I'm sorry.
[CAULIFLA]
Don't be.
Just take a little breather.
[CAULIFLA growls]
[METHIOP, NAPAPA laughing]
You made a big mistake
messing with her.
Ooh, I bet ya she's
a good crier, too!
[CAULIFLA]
What?!
Oh, there's gonna be
some cryin', all right.
But it won't be from me.
My first course
will be the seafood!
[CAULIFLA yells]
[groaning]
--[CAULIFLA yelling]
--[METHIOP groaning]
[grunting]
[METHIOP groaning]
[METHIOP screams]
[NAPAPA]
Dosukoi!
[NAPAPA yelling]
This freight train is goin'
straight outta the ring!
[CAULIFLA yells]
[NAPAPA]
Huh?
[NAPAPA grunting]
[yelling]
[NAPAPA groaning]
[BOTH grunt]
[NAPAPA]
No!
[CAULIFLA sighs]
At least one of 'em's
gone for good!
Kale!
Huh?
[KALE]
Caulifla?
Careful, or someone's
gonna throw you over.
I'm really sorry.
Why don't you go all out,
like when we were training?
[KALE whimpers]
Hey! Look at me, Kale.
What is it, are you mad?
You can handle these
fighters if you dig deep.
I believe in you.
So just believe in yourself.
Got it?
Okay, I'll try.
[CAULIFLA]
Now let's have some fun!
What do you say we
take care of that guy?
Huh?
[JIMIZU laughing]
You can't pin me down.
No one can.
[JIMIZU groaning]
Uh? Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
It's Goku, right? I've been
wanting to talk to you.
I saw you across the ring,
and you powered up
into a kinda Super Saiyan
I've never seen before.
[GOKU]
It's Super Saiyan Blue.
I don't care what you call it,
I just want you to show
me how I can do it too.
Show us how, and we'll
thank you by using
your "Blue-whatever" to
defeat everyone here.
Starting with you!
[KALE] Hey, be careful!
That's no way to say thanks!
[GOKU sighs]
What to do?
Aw, why the hesitation?
You're not scared, are ya?
Not at all. I'm not entirely
sure either of you rookies
are ready to handle
that kind of power yet.
Rookies?! If that's
what you think of us,
then you've got
another thing comin'.
--Let's show him, Kale.
--Huh?
What are you waiting
for... transform!
We'll clobber that dope
for looking down on us.
Right, I'll try.
[grunting]
Make your back tingle and push!
Oh, man. This isn't
starting well.
[GOKU]
No offense, but can I go now?
[CAULIFLA]
No, wait a second!
I'll show you an awesome
transformation!
Try not to freak out!
[CAULIFLA yells]
[panting]
You're not so confident
now, are ya?
Well, you're entertaining,
I'll give ya that much.
Kale, remember.
[gasps] Remember what?
That I believe in you.
Let's do this! One-on-on,
Saiyan versus Saiyan!
[GOKU]
Sure, bring it on.
[CAULIFLA yells]
[grunting]
[yelps]
[CAULIFLA]
Hey!
Why can't I land a punch?!
You pumped up your
muscles for strength,
but in exchange you
killed your speed.
Don't think this is
over, damn it!
[grunting, sighs]
On top of that, that bulk
drains your stamina--
so it's not suited for
a drawn-out fight.
[CAULIFLA grunts]
[GOKU]
For those reasons,
I don't think that's
the best form.
At this point in your training,
the Saiyan transformation
you should be aiming
for... is this!
Whoa, and what form is that?
I call this form
Super Saiyan Two.
What do you think?
[CAULIFLA panting]
Yes! That's the one
I got to before!
I haven't been able
to repeat it since
and it's been driving me crazy,
but I know I did it once!
[GOKU]
Really? You did?
Does the trick have to do
with the feeling in your back?
With the tingling?!
Kinda. Hadn't thought
about it that way before!
[BEERUS]
Hey, Goku!
Stop wasting so much time
with that little novice,
and flatten her already!
[GOKU] Aw come on, Lord Beerus,
give me a break!
This is just starting
to get interesting!
[CAULIFLA] Let's see, if I
use your form as a guide...
[yelling]
All right! It worked!
Oh wow, you're a quick
study, aren't ya?
Guess I'll have to remember to
stay on my toes around you.
Before this fight is over, you
could be at Super Saiyan Three.
[CAULIFLA]
Wait, there's a Three?!
That's right.
But before you mess with that,
you should master Two.
Come on, let's go.
That's fine with me!
[yelling]
[CAULIFLA yells]
[GOKU]
Hmph.
[CAULIFLA grunting]
[CAULIFLA]
This rocks!
Super Saiyan Two is awesome!
[CAULIFLA yells]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[CAULIFLA groans]
Heh, heh.
[GOKU]
Hmph.
Are you all right?
I'll transform now, you
shouldn't have to do this alone!
[CAULIFLA]
Let's keep going.
[GOKU]
Sure.
[CAULIFLA grunts]
[BOTH grunt]
[CAULIFLA, GOKU grunting]
Don't worry! I'll back you up!
[yells]
[GOKU grunts]
Hey! What was that?
[KALE gasps]
I hate to ask, but this is
our fight--can you stay out?
[gasps] I'm sorry, sir.
I just...
Caulifla's my...
[KALE]
We face everything together.
Caulifla, you don't think
I'm interfering,
do you?
[KALE gasping]
Now you're making it seem like
I'm not good enough for her
again, like I'll
always let her down!
[KALE sobs]
This is your fault.
Yours, Goku!
[wails]
[screaming]
You're taking my one
and only away from me!
And you're going to
regret that, Goku!
I'll make you pay!
[yelling]
[CAULIFLA, GOKU gasp]
You did this, Goku!
Her power's incredible.
What in the hell was that?
[CABBA]
Kale! She must've transformed!
[CAULIFLA]
You finally powered up!
Amazing, Kale!
[KALE growling]
[CAULIFLA screams]
Oh come on!
What happened?
[HIT]
Unbelievable.
It seems that your
antics have awakened
an outrageously powerful beast.
[CAULIFLA]
You saved me with a Time Skip?
[KALE yelling]
[ZENOS]
Whoa! Incredible!
Look at that brute form
she's taken--it's grotesque!
Is that her idea of
going Super Saiyan?
That's incredible.
I'm glad you're showing us
what you're really made of.
[KALE growls]
Goku.
[VEGETA] Careful, Kakarot!
Don't get sloppy!
[GOKU]
Relax, I won't!
We don't know what
we're dealing with!
That could be the Legendary
Super Saiyan form
our ancestors spoke of!
[GOKU]
Huh?
[KALE]
You are Goku.
Goku the destroyer of lives.
Goku the ruiner!
I'll kill you!
[GOKU groaning]
[GOKU grunting]
[KALE yelling]
[KALE screams]
[GOKU muffled grunting]
Goku the arrogant.
Goku the parasite!
[KALE growls]
Goku!
[GOKU yells]
I'm gonna have to put a
little power behind this.
Well? Come on!
Goku the undeserving.
Ka...
...me...
...ha...
Ha!
[GOKU yelling]
[KALE growling]
[GOKU muffled grunting]
Goku the vulnerable.
Let's help him!
Hold on!
Something's not right.
[panting]
[GOKU groaning]
[KALE screams]
She doesn't know how
to control her power.
[yelling]
[KALE yells]
[GOKU gasps]
[KALE screaming]
[GOKU grunts]
[CABBA, VEGETA grunt]
[BOTAMO]
Get us out of here, Magetta!
[MAGETTA]
Clang! Sputter!
[BOTAMO screams]
[METHIOP]
Please, no! Ahh!
[GOKU groans]
Ouch!
Uh? Where'd she go?
Goku the stubborn!
She's a monster.
Goku the spineless!
[VEWON]
Halt, crude behemoth!
The Pride Troopers
shall not allow this
indiscriminate rampage!
My Justice Whip renders any
violent offender powerless
to continue their wicked crimes!
[KALE grunting, yells]
But that can't be!
[KALE yells]
[VEWON grunts]
Boop!
And Vewon is knocked out too!
[KALE roars]
[TOP] That much force
from her voice alone?
Jiren!
I'll handle this.
[HIT]
This is dangerous.
[CAULIFLA]
Uh, yeah, obviously!
[HIT]
I mean for Kale.
[CAULIFLA]
What? Why?
If she kills someone
she'll be disqualified.
Oh yeah, I forgot!
Hey! Kale!
Bring it down a notch!
No dropping bodies!
Do ya hear me?!
Kale?!
[KALE yelling]
[CAULIFLA]
Huh?
[JIREN grunts]
[JIREN]
It's over.
Kale!
A poor choice.
Yo!
Let's go while we can.
Agreed.
[NARRATOR] Jiren, Pride
Trooper of the Eleventh,
has defeated the mega-charged
Kale in the blink of an eye.
[NARRATOR] The Tournament
of Power is clearly stacked
with contenders of
unimaginable strength.
Will Goku and his team be
able to endure this gauntlet,
and save the Seventh Universe
from destruction?
The brutal contest continues,
next time on Dragon Ball Super!
When the time has come
to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever in my mind
as I look up to the sky
I was watching you
from your left side
Was trying to get
a good look at your face
The tears in your eyes;
were you laughing or crying?
Your long hair in the way
Blocking the thoughts inside
When the time has
come to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever I will wait,
for the light to show the way
For us to meet again
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And it looks like Jiren's
teammates from the Eleventh
all want to come at me at once.
Which sure sounds fun to me!
17 and 18 are mixed
up in it too,
and these Troopers have some
impressive combos for sure.
I just hope they'll drop their
poses and hero routines
and show how deep
their powers really go!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Warriors of Justice Close In!
The Pride Troopers!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?