♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Goku visited the nature
preserve where Android 17
works and tried to recruit him
for the Tournament of Power.
[A17]
Look, it's not about the job.
It's about the island.
I can't afford to leave it.
[NARRATOR]
But just as 17 refused,
alien poachers arrived and
stole the island's animals!
[GOKU yells]
I have a highly powerful
self-destruct device
implanted inside my body.
[gasps]
[POACHER BOSS] Do you really
want me to turn all of us,
including your precious animals,
into space debris?
[A17]
Okay, Goku.
I'll let you take it from here.
[POACHER BOSS screams]
[NARRATOR]
With the poachers defeated,
and the animals returned
to the island,
17 made a surprising decision.
[A17]
All right, fine.
I'm in.
[GOKU]
Hm?
I'll join your team
for the tournament.
I don't like being
in debt to anybody.
I'll leave Trunks and Goten
in charge of the island
and just hope they're up to it.
[NARRATOR]
17 is ready to fight
on the biggest
stage of them all!
But what about his teammates?
Find out now!
[NARRATOR]
"Gohan and Piccolo.
Master and Pupil Clash
in Max Training!"
[GOHAN grunting]
[GOHAN panting]
So, that's where your skills
are at these days, huh?
[GOHAN grunts]
[PICCOLO]
I'll be honest.
After you guys won the Zeno
Expo, Goku paid me a visit.
Uh? Wait.
So then my Dad already
told you everything?
Yeah. He told me about
your performance--
how well you did there, and how
if we lose the Tournament,
our universe gets destroyed.
Fine. You just found yourself
another teammate, Goku.
Yeah?
[PICCOLO] The best fighters
in the Cosmos,
fighting for their
very existence?
You won't find a tournament
with stakes higher than that!
I knew that once I explained it,
you'd be excited
to join the team!
[PICCOLO chuckles]
Speaking of team, how's Gohan?
Think he can do this?
[GOKU] Well, considering how
little he fights these days,
I think he handled himself
pretty well at the Expo.
On the other hand,
we both know how much power
he's got locked deep down.
He could do way more.
[PICCOLO] Hmm... Do you
have any senzu beans?
[GOKU]
Hm? No, not on me. Why?
[PICCOLO]
Go get me two.
I'm going to whip Gohan
back into shape
for the Tournament of Power.
[GOKU]
No argument here.
Whatever helps the team!
Be glad that I got these
senzu beans, Gohan.
'Cause from here on out,
things get tough.
Oh, I'm ready, Piccolo.
If we're gonna win this thing,
I need to be stronger than
I've ever been before!
[yells]
Huh?
[yelling continues]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN grunting]
[groans]
[GOHAN grunts]
That all you got?
[BULLA cries]
Wait, is this side the front?
Or... is it this?
The problem isn't
that it's upside down,
it's that you're holding
it inside out.
[TRUNKS]
Inside out...?
Oh. That explains why these
thingies weren't sticking.
Yeah, a healthy baby
girl, named Bulla.
No, Bull-uh, with
an "A" at the end.
Oh, I'm glad you like it.
I think it's cute, too!
I'll text you some pics.
She totally looks like me.
--[BULLA cries]
--[TRUNKS, GOTEN gasping]
Human babies are hard.
[BEERUS growls]
[TRUNKS]
Dad, help!
[VEGETA]
Hmph. Watch and learn!
[VEGETA grunting]
[BULLA coos]
Whoa, that was awesome!
Diaper master!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[TRUNKS] You're way more fun
when you're not crying!
Oh, yeah. She got all her
cute-ness from my side!
[BULMA laughs]
Our universe could be a day
away from total annihilation,
and they're lounging around,
yucking it up!
The old saying, "ignorance is
bliss," feels appropriate, sir.
[BEERUS] We should tell them
the truth, for their own good.
My Lord, with everything
we know of this group,
I would recommend
we avoid doing that.
[BEERUS]
Huh?
I'd like you to think for a
moment how Bulma would react.
What?
If we lose they'll
wipe out our universe?!
And I'm assuming that
this is all your fault!
What? I had nothing
to do with this!
Your problem's
with Goku, not me!
He's the one who put this
thing in Grand Zeno's head!
If Goku did this by himself,
why didn't you stop him!
Well. Of course,
I tried to, but it
just didn't work out.
How could you not know
by now that when you
leave Goku alone like that, it
always ends in major trouble!
How can you call yourself
a god with a straight face?!
You dumbbell!
[BULMA, WHIS]
You bone-headed, stupid,
moronic, dope of a deity!
Nobody likes you!
Stop that!
Oh, my. So, then, what'll it be?
Are you ready to take
on "Hurricane Bulma"?
Don't worry about a gift.
Bulla's already got more stuff
than she knows what to do with!
[BEERUS growls]
No thanks. I'm good.
[MARRON laughs]
[signing]
Hey, kids, your Daddy's home!
[yells]
[MARRON]
How was work, honey?
You hit lots of buttons
on your computer?
Whoa.
I know bickering is a
part of any marriage,
but this is a bit much.
[laughing]
[WOMEN laugh]
Yeah! Kick each other's butts!
[WOMEN gasp]
[A18]
Hi-yah!
Mama, you won again!
You're running out
of time to improve.
[groans] That really hurt.
You're supposed to
pull your punches!
When we win, I'm taking
your ten million zeni
and there's nothing
you can do about it.
Sweetie, I'll buy you
any toy you want
with your father's
prize cut, okay?
[sighs]
So much for my dream
of upgrading the home gym
with a steam room.
[GOHAN, PICCOLO grunting]
[GOHAN groaning]
[GOHAN panting]
I'm not... down yet...
I will protect...
my friends and my family.
You're just psyching
yourself up.
[gasps]
[PICCOLO]
Telling yourself you have to win
isn't training, Gohan.
It's pointless.
You need to face reality,
and do the real work.
If you can't tap
into your true power,
all the motivation
in the world
won't be enough to
protect Videl and Pan.
[GOHAN gasps]
[PICCOLO]
Sure, having something
to defend or fight for
can drive you.
But when feelings dominate,
they can just as quickly
drag you down.
You want your emotions to
complement your strength,
not shackle it!
[GOHAN grunting]
[PICCOLO] If you're too
desperate to win--
if love makes you afraid--
you won't be able to assess
the fight logically.
You'll misjudge your opponent's
abilities and lose.
[GOHAN]
So that's it.
That's what I've
been doing wrong.
[GOHAN screams]
There's no such thing as
a fight that can't be lost!
If we lose, our entire universe
will be destroyed.
You must accept that fact,
and come to terms with it.
Only then can you prevail.
All right.
[PICCOLO]
Hmph. You can do this, Gohan.
You can win.
Huh?
[PICCOLO]
I believe in you.
Now believe in yourself.
Piccolo.
I won't let you down.
[CABBA]
Unbelievable.
We're in a fight with our
universe's existence at stake.
I don't care how strong Hit is,
there are no sure things
when you're fighting
70 warriors from
across the Cosmos.
Building the right
team is critical.
Which means I have no
choice but to ask him.
[whirring]
[RENSO]
Hm?
[RENSO spits]
[knocking]
[CABBA]
Renso, sir? It's Cabba!
Huh? Cabba?
[RENSO yelps]
[crash]
[CABBA]
Huh? Uh!
Renso!
Hey, easy, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just got a little too excited.
Heard your voice and
forgot about my bum leg!
[CABBA]
Hm?
[RENSO]
Well.
What can I say, Cabba,
it's been too long.
I've tried to keep up
with your career, though.
I was so proud to hear
you're now an ace
in the Sadala Defense Force's
Saiyan Elite Corps.
I couldn't have done it if not
for your training, Captain.
[laughs] I'm retired now.
Oh. I see.
Anyway. I hear you've mastered
a new fighting move.
You wanna show off
for your old mentor?
[CABBA]
Heh. Sure!
[yells]
Whoa! That's more impressive
than I was expecting!
With you out there, our
universe is in good hands.
[gasps]
Well, sir, now that
you mention it...
[RENSO]
Uh?
What? Wiped out?
[CABBA]
Please.
I'm here to ask you
to join our team!
We need all the help we can
get if we're gonna survive!
I can't.
I retired from
the Defense Force.
And besides, with my bum leg...
But you wouldn't be fighting
like you did in the old days.
Grand Zeno has decreed that it
be an 80-man battle royale.
So just having your combat
experience on hand
will be a huge help
for the team.
[RENSO]
You give me too much credit.
You have to!
We're talking about the
existence of our whole universe!
[RENSO grunts]
[CABBA]
Renso!
[RENSO] You need the best team
of fighters possible.
If I'm there,
I'll just be a burden.
There is one way I can
help you, though.
The fighter you should
be recruiting is Caulifla.
Uh. Wait.
Caulifla, as in... your sister?
[RENSO]
Think she can't do it?
No, I think she's
an amazing fighter,
it's just that I sometimes...
Well, we sometimes don't
see eye-to-eye, is all.
[RENSO laughs]
I know, she's a rebel.
A punk, if I'm being blunt.
But still, Caulifla's latent
abilities far outclass my own.
[CABBA]
What? They do?
[panting]
I think we've both
warmed up enough.
From here on out,
the gloves are off.
Come at me as hard as you can!
[GOHAN]
Right!
[yells]
You're strong,
that much I'm aware of.
But you have another weakness.
And unless you can overcome it,
you won't last long
in the Tournament.
And if you lose, our universe
won't be far behind.
I'm gonna show you
your weakness.
[GOHAN, PICCOLO grunting]
[PICCOLO groans]
[gasps]
Ha!
[GOHAN gasping]
Told ya I was takin'
the gloves off!
[PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO]
What's the matter, Gohan?
Is that all you've got?
Don't blame me
when you black out!
I'm... not giving up yet!
Piccolo, when did you
get so powerful?
Did you really think I was
sittin' on my hands
all this time,
while you had your head
buried in some textbook?
[groaning]
[GOHAN screams]
[GOHAN coughs]
[PICCOLO]
Gohan, it's over.
You're strong, but you lack--
Well...
You just might not have
the heart of a true warrior.
If there's a chance to win,
you have to close the deal.
[gasps]
It's an old problem.
Remember when you
fought Majin Buu,
after the Elder Kai
drew out your power?
You were overcome by a
different feeling: arrogance.
You had struggled for so long
to unlock your potential
that when you did,
you enjoyed it too much.
Instead of using your
strength to win,
your arrogance left
you open to attack.
Succumb to that again,
and you'll lose no matter
how powerful you are.
Be a warrior!
No matter the opponent,
you fight with
everything you've got!
All right, Piccolo.
This time, I won't let you down.
[yelling]
Ha. I want to see something
even more powerful than
just Super Saiyan!
[GOHAN grunting]
[PICCOLO] Show me the power you
had when you fought against Buu!
Re-awaken the fighter
you truly are!
[gasping]
How's that?
So is this what you
wanted to see?
That's perfect, Gohan.
[yells]
Cloning, huh?
[PICCOLO CLONES yell]
[GOHAN grunts]
[gasps]
[GOHAN]
Piccolo!
[PICCOLO]
Yes, that's it. That's good.
Huh?!
If you can fight like
this in the Tournament,
then those other universes don't
stand a chance against our team.
Thank you, Piccolo.
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[screams]
[GOHAN groans]
But you didn't close the deal.
It's the same thing
that happened
when you fought against Buu.
You thought you defeated him,
and dropped your guard.
Which allowed him to sneak up
from behind and absorb you!
[GOHAN gasps]
It's not entirely your fault.
Your father often makes
the same mistake.
Don't you forget this.
Stay focused.
Drop your arrogance
and keep your guard up
until the tournament's over.
Right.
[PICCOLO]
Good! Let's go again!
[GOHAN]
Ready when you are!
[DINOSAUR screams]
[DINOSAUR cries]
[GOHAN]
All right, Piccolo.
Thanks again for the training.
Oh, no.
Your training is
only getting started.
[GOHAN]
What?
Listen, I believe that
what you tapped into today
was actually a fraction
of your latent power.
We pushed through one wall and
now I wanna find the next.
[PICCOLO]
Aren't you curious?
Don't you wanna know
how strong you truly are?
Don't settle for being better,
when you could be the best.
Tournament doesn't
start till tomorrow.
We still have a little time.
Let's put it to good use.
You wanna be stronger than
you've ever been, right?
Stronger than I've ever been.
Yeah.
Let's do it!
Oh, and since we'll be
hangin' out together,
maybe we can come up with
some combos moves, too?
[PICCOLO]
Combo moves, huh?
[GOHAN] Yeah! We'll need
every advantage we can get.
[PICCOLO]
Interesting...
[PICCOLO chuckles]
All right, why not!
[NARRATOR] Thanks to Piccolo's
intensive training,
Gohan's preparations
for the tournament
are proceeding quickly.
We are now just 9 hours
and 30 minutes away
from the start of the
Tournament of Power!
What is the depth
of Gohan's abilities?
What combo moves
can he and Piccolo
master in the remaining time?
How well can they
fight as a team?
And most importantly:
who will take the final slots
for the Seventh Universe?
[YAMCHA]
All right, he'll ask me,
but first I'm gonna
play hard-to-get.
"The 'Tournament of Power?,' eh?
I'd love to, but I've
already got plans
to wash my hair that night."
Or, wait. Maybe I should
go for false modesty.
"But I'm not on
your level, Goku.
I'd only hold the
rest of you back."
Nah, that doesn't
sound believable.
--[YAMCHA] Uh. What should I do?
--Oh...
My poor Yamcha.
[YAMCHA] And what's with him
taking so long to ask?
I mean, really, Puar.
Don't you think he should
have been here by now!
Wait! Knowing Goku, he'll just
use Instant Transmission!
Goku, are you here yet?!
No? Okay, what about here?
Ah, you can zap yourself
in anytime now!
I'm waiting!
Anytime, Goku!
Ha, ha, ha...
Boogie Back!
Wish we had better timing
To explore this attraction
Put on a smile, it's showtime
And I'm just playing a part
Let's get lost in the rhythm,
dancing dancing heart
Head over heels
I'm falling falling down
(Boogie Back!)
My heartbeat
keeps growing faster
Every step that I take
brings me back to you
(Boogie Back!)
Give me happy ever after
Let the dream
of our love come true
Boogie Back!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
All I need to do now is
get Tien and Master Roshi,
and our team will be set!
Wow. This is a pretty impressive
dojo Tien's runnin'.
Ooh. I'm gettin' some
bad vibes about this!
Looks like Master Roshi's
going on a rampage!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"A Mysterious Beauty Appears!
The Enigma of the
Tien Shin-Style Dojo?"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?