♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Vegeta saw Goku reach
a stunning new level
in his fight with Beerus,
and the proud Saiyan prince
was desperate to acquire
this divine power
for himself, at any cost.
Sorry. Yes, I am Lord Beerus'
teacher as well.
[NARRATOR] Vegeta begged
Whis to teach him,
and finally convinced
the strange alien
by cooking what he claimed
was the best food on Earth:
a cup of instant ramen.
Since Vegeta's training began,
over half a year has passed.
The adventure continues, now!
[NARRATOR]
"Pan is Born!
And Goku Goes on
a Training Journey?!"
[door knob clicks]
[door thuds]
[PAN laughs]
[MR. SATAN]
Oh, look at you!
You're a happy
wittle baby, aren't ya?
[PAN laughs]
Can you give a big smile
for your fave-wit gwampa?
[chuckles]
Peek-a-Boo!
[laughs]
Sorry to interrupt,
but it's time for Pan's nap.
[MR. SATAN]
Peek-a-Boo!
Did you hear me?
--[MR. SATAN] Who's a cutie?
--Dad, I'm talking!
Huh?
Eh.
--[MR. SATAN chuckles]
--[VIDEL sighs]
[GOHAN panting]
Hey, I'm here!
Welcome home, hon.
How was the conference?
Everything go well?
Uh. I think so, yeah. Huh?
Upsie-daisie!
Sounds like playtime!
Well, so much for the nap.
[PAN laughs]
At times, he's a
scholarly egghead,
giving lectures.
Other times,
a mild-mannered daddy,
going on walks!
But, behold a third identity!
He is the brave warrior
preserving peace on Earth!
The Great Saiyaman!
--[MR. SATAN gasps]
--[PAN laughs]
Fiendish Mr. Satan, I've
caught you stealing Pan's heart!
And now the Great Saiyaman
will make you pay!
Oh, I've been
waiting for you.
Now we can
settle this at last!
Prepare for justice! Ah!
It's not so easy fightin'
against you one-handed, hero!
Looks like I'm gonna
have to use my Baby Juggle!
Wook at you. Wittle baby
Pan just wuvs her
awesome gwampa so much,
doesn't she?
[chuckles]
Not too bad.
[laughs]
Oh no!
Ha-haa! Not even Grandpa is
a match for the mighty power
of Saiyaman's
Super Mega Daddy Love!
I'm not done yet!
[yells]
They play this
game every day.
How do they
not get tired of it?
Hi Videl. I brought
Pan a few more things.
Is she up?
Huh?
[growls]
[laughs]
[CHICHI] What do you think
you're doing?!
[BOTH]
Aah!
[BOTH sigh]
[CHICHI grunts]
Mom, you can't
scream like that.
You totally broke
our concentration.
That could be dangerous,
you know.
You think
I'm being dangerous?
You're tossing around
a baby who can't even
hold her own head up yet!
There, there, Pan,
don't be scared.
Your grandmother will
keep you safe, won't she?
For your information,
she can hold up
her head just fine.
And she's got
Saiyan genes, remember,
so this kind of
roughhousing is no problem.
We do it all the time.
[MR. SATAN]
Mhm!
Well you're not doing it
anymore, do you hear me?
Don't you realize
what'll happen
if she watches you
fight all the time?
She'll turn out to be
a battle-obsessed maniac
like your dad,
and we can't have that!
Pan is going to be
a graceful, modern woman
with several prestigious
degrees and a corner office.
Sorry to throw a wrench
in your plan there, Chichi.
But I've already
decided Pan's gonna be
a great martial artist.
She's gonna follow
in my footsteps
and become the
next famous World Champ!
Just imagine the headlines
when I hand over the belt.
The press'll have a field day!
This is a joke, isn't it?
She's got the blood
of Gohan and yours truly
flowing through her baby veins.
Her fightin' power
and talent are gonna be
off the charts! She'll be
the greatest on Earth
and hundreds of fighters
will want to train at her dojo
that she'll probably
name after me.
Well I have no intention
of letting my Pan
do anything of the sort!
Yeah? Who made you queen?
[MR, SATAN, CHICHI grunt]
[GOHAN] Guys, come on, we've got
a few years to discuss this.
No, we're talking
about this now!
Do you know how many
years it took me
to get Goku straight?
But I finally have,
and I'll get Pan
on the right path too!
I don't care what you
or anybody else says,
there's no way I'll let her
step foot in a ring!
Whew!
Grow up strong now, okay?
[SALON STAFF 17A]
So, only a cut today, ma'am.
No shampoo?
[BULMA] Yeah, I really just
need to even out my bangs.
[BOTH laugh]
All right, I'll be there
at one o'clock, see you soon.
--[beeps]
--[MAN 17A, 17B yell]
[BULMA]
What's going on around here?
Are you kidding me?
[screams]
[MAN 17C]
You okay in there?
[BULMA] How dare you
do that to my car!
This is a custom build!
Man! He keeps dodging me!
I'm about to show you
what happens
when someone
puts a dent in my car!
You're gonna be sorry!
[BOTH yell]
What are they doing?
I'm not through yet!
[THIEF A, B yell]
[THIEF B]
Tree! Tree! Tree!
[THIEF A, B groan]
[BULMA]
Hm!
[KRILLIN] You know our
position on vigilantes, right?
Krillin?
They generally mean
more stuff blowing up.
[chuckles]
[BULMA]
You're a cop now?
Wow, so you really passed
the police academy
exam and everything?
Well it did
take me a few tries,
but eventually, yeah.
Congratulations, Krillin.
I think that's great!
Hey, thanks, Bulma. I do, t--
Wait, don't distract me!
I'm on official
business right now
and I'm officially mad
at you for taking the law
into your own hands.
That was dangerous!
Please. Those jerks
interrupted a young lady's
trip to the beauty salon.
There's not a jury in the whole
world who would convict me.
Trying to argue with you
is like trying to
fight a dragon with a yo-yo.
You haven't changed
one bit. Here.
And what the hell is this?
[KRILLIN] Ticket for speeding
and reckless driving.
I'll overlook
the unlicensed jet.
Huh?!
--[phone ringing]
--Hey wait a second,
--you can't give me a ticket.
I'm the victim here.
I'm telling you,
I was supposed to
get my bangs cut.
Gohan's calling.
Hello? What?
Yeah, okay.
I'll be right there.
[GOHAN]
What do you think?
[MR. SATAN]
Hmmm.
[knock on window]
Let us in, Gohan.
Dad's here too.
[BULMA, GOKU, KRILLIN]
She locked you out?
Yeah. She says it's not
safe to leave Pan with us
until we clean up our act.
Sorry, Gohan.
This is kinda my fault.
I got carried away with the
future plans thing, too.
Look. We just have to
hold our ground
until they see things
our way, okay?
[VIDEL]
Uh-huh.
Though maybe I'm
speaking out of turn here.
I haven't asked how you
want to raise Pan, have I?
I mean, what kind of future
do you want for her?
Just take your time,
and think about it.
Whatever you choose,
I'll be on your side.
O-kay.
I beg ya, Goku!
Ask Chichi to let us in.
I can't take another
minute without Pan!
Sorry I'm no good talking to
Chichi when she's like this.
I'll just make it worse.
Can you talk to her?
You're a cop. You're
trained for this right?
Ahhh...
Hostage situations
aren't exactly my specialty.
Leave it to me you guys.
I'll convince her for you.
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH] Oh, thank you,
Bulma. You mean it?
And in return, Krillin's
gonna make that ticket
he gave me
magically disappear.
No can do.
I'm dealing with
a crisis you just said
you can't handle,
Mr. Policeman.
So dropping a ticket
is the least you can do!
I said I can't!
Fine, be that way! You jerk!
[knock, knock]
Hey, Chichi. It's Bulma.
Can you open the door for me?
[rattling]
[rattling, clanging]
[ALL]
Uhhh...
[BULMA] I know, right?
The guys don't get it!
They think they can do
whatever they want.
It drives me up the wall!
[CHICHI] I hear you, sister!
You and me both!
I don't know if it's
the way Saiyans did it
back on their planet or what,
but when I
gave birth to Trunks,
Vegeta didn't even
bother to show up!
Saiyans are clueless.
They have no idea
how much trouble we go through!
[BULMA]
What do you think, Videl?
I know your daughter's
part Saiyan,
but how do you feel
about her fighting?
It's got to worry you, right?
It's hard to say. I grew up
studying martial arts,
and that's partly
what drew me to Gohan.
[BOTH]
Mhm, mhmmm.
It was fun for me,
but I also liked books
and dolls and all sorts
of things, too.
When it comes down to it,
I guess I just want her
to have all the options
and grow up to be
whatever she wants.
That sounds
pretty good to me.
Chichi, I think Pan
is gonna be just fine.
Think of everything Gohan did as
a boy and now he's a scholar!
Even Goku's got a regular job.
It all works out.
I think when you
marry a Saiyan,
you have to let life unfold
in a little different way.
Take my husband for instance.
He's across the universe
training with that Whis guy
and I haven't seen him
in six whole months!
[GOKU]
Vegeta's doing whaaat?!
What do you mean
he's off training with Whis?
How did that happen,
and why didn't anybody
tell me, Bulma?
I don't know.
'Cause you never asked,
and it's not a big deal.
Whis is just helping him reach
a new level like you did.
[screams]
He's been off training
this whole time
while I've been out farming?
[KRILLIN]
Wow, this is nuts-o.
I seriously can't believe
Whis was actually
Beerus's teacher all along.
I'm guessing he likes
to keep his cards
close to his chest.
It's a common practice
of great martial artists.
And naturally
I had my suspicions.
[KRILLIN]
Uh-huh.
What's the plan, Bulma?
You're friends with Whis,
so when's he coming
back to Earth?
I gotta make sure I talk to him
the next time he's here
so I can convince him
to train me too.
He was here pretty recently
so I think it'll be a while.
Based on his usual pattern,
I would say it's gonna be
about a month, or maybe two.
Are you kidding me?
I can't wait that long!
Isn't there some way
you can call him
and tell him to come?!
Stop it, Goku! You're
acting like a crazy person!
Busting through walls
at your son's house
where your
granddaughter's sleeping
'cause somebody
mentions training?
No! I won't allow it!
[whimpers]
[grunts] Oh, why am I even
trying? You're hopeless!
[whispers]
Goku. Wait.
If Vegeta's on Beerus's world,
then can't you just
search for his energy?
Once you lock onto his power,
you can use your Instant
Transmission, right?
[whispers] Oh yeah,
I didn't think of that!
[whispers] It's no use.
I can't sense his energy.
I think he's too far away.
Guess all I can
do now is wait.
Is Whis here?
[BULMA]
No! Not yet!
[keyboard keys clicking]
--Is he here now?
--[gasps]
Don't scare me like that!
So how 'bout now?
[BULMA grunts]
Seriously?
[GOKU hollers]
[BULMA]
Here, take this.
When Whis shows up,
I'll call you, got it?
I came all the way here
to give you that,
so thank me and promise
you'll stop bugging me!
Are you sure you won't
forget to call me?
[BULMA]
Yes, I'm sure!
[CHICHI] Why are you
giving Goku a phone?
--[GOKU shrieks]
--[CHICHI] Hmm!
Don't worry,
I can explain!
Uh, it's for Pan, actually.
Bulma wants to throw a giant
surprise party for her
without Gohan
or Videl finding out.
Yeah. And this is
to help us plan it!
[CHICHI]
Hmmm...
Oh, that's great!
So you're finally taking
your grandpa job seriously!
[GOKU]
Uh, yes, exactly!
That's right,
he's a changed man!
[chuckles]
[whispers]
You've had all this time
and you still
haven't talked to her
about training there yet?
I tried.
[chuckles nervously]
Still no call.
Is this thing broken?
--[door knob clicks]
--[GOHAN] I'm back!
Here you go, Mom. I got
everything on your list.
[CHICHI]
Wonderful, thank you!
Hey, Goku!
Look who stopped by!
Uh, Dad?
[gasps]
Is something wrong with Dad?
He's sure acting funny.
[laughs]
Nice try, but you won't
get me to talk!
Let's just say
fun is on the horizon!
Goku's being
such a great grandpa.
[GOHAN] Now I'm
definitely suspicious.
Still no call. Huh.
[GOHAN]
Hm?
[phone rings]
[GOKU]
It's her! Bulma?
[gasps]
[GOKU] Yeah! Of course!
I'll be there!
Finally!
Don't tell me--
You're definitely
gonna love today's menu!
[GOKU]
Hey, Whis! Whis!
Whis!
Hi there!
Greetings, Goku.
What a surprise.
Long time no see.
Oh man, I knew it!
I heard a rumor
that Vegeta's been
training on your world,
is that true?
--[WHIS] Hm?
--[BULMA] Mm-mmm!
That's correct. The Saiyan
prince introduced me
to an unbelievably
delicious cuisine,
so I practically had no choice.
That's great!
While you're at it,
would you mind training me too?
[sighs]
I want to become as
powerful as Lord Beerus.
It's all I can think about!
I beg you,
I'll do whatever it takes!
Please be my teacher!
Sorry.
I don't see why not.
--[GOKU exclaims]
--[GOHAN gasps]
--Wow, you mean it?
--Of course.
I have been thinking
this was about
the right time to do it, anyway.
Hold on, what was that?
So this isn't a joke,
you'll train me?
I will.
All right, let's go.
I don't want to waste
any more time!
Sorry, Goku, I'm afraid
you have to wait.
You don't expect me
to cancel my lunch plans
with Bulma, do you?
That is the whole reason
I made this journey
to Earth, after all.
Oh yeah, sorry.
I just got excited.
You guys have a great lunch
and enjoy yourselves,
and I'll wait right here
'til you get back.
Take all the time you need!
How generous of him.
Yeah. Let's go eat!
What did you mean
when you said
it's about the right time?
I don't know, Bulma.
Did I say that?
I can't remember.
I can't believe
this is happening.
I get to train on his world!
This is gonna be so awesome!
[sighs]
This is gonna be so awful!
When Mom hears, she's
gonna totally flip out!
Ooooh!
What a wondrous custom!
So you dip the meat in the
water and cook it yourself?
An interactive
dining experience!
I can't wait to hear sizzles!
Are you guys done yet?
Eh, no, Goku.
We haven't started yet.
Oh, right. Sorry,
just take your time.
He is quite the
impatient one, isn't he?
Anyway, back to the fun!
Look, Bulma! Here I go!
So... now are you done?
Eh. No, as I said,
we're only starting.
Oh, right. Heh. Sorry!
You know, if you wanna save
time you can eat it raw!
[chuckles nervously]
[WHIS] Look, it's changing
color! How delightful!
Now are you done yet?
Goku, please.
If you continue with
these interruptions,
I won't actually
have a chance to eat,
and you'll have
to wait even longer!
[GOKU] Sorry,
I just want to start!
Can you get it to go?
Goku, he offered to help
and all you're doing now
is pestering him!
Be careful or he might decide
not to train you after all!
[gasps]
[laughs nervously]
My mistake.
Just take your time!
I'll be over there,
waiting patiently.
[GOKU chuckles]
[WHIS exhales]
He's like a gnat.
It's absolutely fantastic!
Elegant in its
simple preparation,
allowing the quality of the
ingredients to truly shine.
Okay, you're done,
so we can go, right?
Goku. Your complete
inability to sit still
is a most troubling sign.
If this is how you'll
be training, I don't
believe I can teach you.
Aw come on,
that's not fair!
You said you'd teach me!
You can't take it back now!
I can do as I please, Goku.
[CHICHI]
Nobody move!
[GOKU]
Huh?!
It's Chichi! Oh crap!
[CHICHI]
Goku!
Sorry, Dad,
but I had to tell her.
For my own safety.
What is this
about training?
You know how I feel
about this. You can't go!
Tell him, Bulma. He's
too busy being a grandpa!
--[BULMA chuckles nervously]
--[CHICHI] Hey!
Look, Chichi.
It's not a big deal,
I'm not talking about
a long time.
Just a little training.
That's all I need,
a little eency bit!
Do you think
I was born yesterday?
That's what you always tell me
but I'm not falling
for it this time!
Come on, Mom, it's okay.
Why don't you let him go?
It's gotta be important
if Dad wants it this bad.
Hush, Goten,
Mom and Dad are talking!
[GOTEN]
Okay.
Don't get angry, Mom,
but I think you should
let him go, too. We saw
how strong Beerus is
and how close he came
to blowing up the earth,
and we couldn't
do anything to stop him.
If there's ever trouble,
I'll always try to help.
But we know Dad's our
best shot at keeping us safe,
and if he can get stronger,
that's better for all of us!
I said no and I
meant no, Gohan!
I want Pan to have a granddad
who sets a good example
so she can have
a nice, normal life
and not run around
battling monsters!
Just a bit of training!
Just a teeny tiny little bit!
It appears this dispute
could take a while.
I think I should go, Bulma.
Thank you for
the meal as always.
Uh, you're leaving now?
Look Chichi, I'm sorry!
I tried to do it your way,
but I just can't manage it.
I need to train
and get stronger.
It's too important
to pass up! Bye!
Wait!
Oh my!
Hey, it's Goku!
Goku! Goku!
[CHICHI sighs]
I almost thought
he'd changed this time.
But that's Goku for you.
I guess I can't really
be surprised.
He'll come back eventually,
when he's hungry,
then we'll start it all again!
[GOHAN]
Huh?
[CHICHI] So Bulma,
on to important things--
when are you having
that big party?
Huh? Who me?
Might as well, I guess.
Yeah! We'll make it
even bigger than the last!
That was a rash move.
[chuckles]
Are you sure you want
to leave like that?
I would hate to be
called a home-wrecker.
Nah. Chichi may get mad,
but she understands me
more than anybody.
And do we get to have
a bingo tournament, too?
Oh, you know it!
I won't have time
to get the Dragon Balls,
but I'll make sure to load up
with really cool prizes!
[GOHAN] Well, Dad,
looks like you don't have to
worry about Mom after all.
You're free to
train your heart out.
[CHICHI] I've got to go
shopping right now!
I've always wanted
to put a baby girl
in a cute little party dress!
Mom, you really are amazing.
I look back
to when I was young
Reminisce on all that I've done
In my hands, I held
The dreams of my childhood,
that now've come to pass
So let's ride upon
the wind and journey to
A world we've never known
(It's a brand new story)
Now, a new chapter starts
Shining Star
In the night be
my compass and guide
Take me to where I belong
The warmth we once shared
Will always be there
Its magic lives on in our hearts
Shining Star
Give me strength
from your light up above
Show me the way to be brave
My hands still hold onto hope
that together we'll manifest
All that we dreamed of
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Vegeta's definitely stronger
from his time with Whis.
I barely recognize the guy!
And here's a challenge
I've never faced:
making a deity's bed!
Trouble is brewing
in space, but for now,
Vegeta and I are focused on
some pretty strange training.
But hey, I'm willing
to do anything
if it gets me to a new level.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"I'm Here, Too!
Training Commences
on Beerus' World!"
And we've got new characters
you won't want to miss!