♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Trunks told of a
shocking new calamity
in his alternate future.
An enemy, clad in black
and looking just like Goku,
has launched a cruel attack
against all of mankind,
plunging the world
into darkness once again.
Yeah, don't worry, Trunks.
We've got this.
We'll go with you to the future!
Sure, but the job of
defeating Kakarot will be mine,
are we clear?
It's time to go back
to the future and avenge me!
[NARRATOR]
But just as Goku and the others
were making plans to help,
a figure emerged
through a rip in the sky.
[GOKU BLACK]
Hm?
[chuckles]
Well, you must be Goku.
So you're Goku Black!
[NARRATOR]
A new rivalry, now!
"Goku vs. Black! A Closed-Off
Road to the Future!"
[GOKU BLACK] That's bizarre.
I've been pulled through time.
[MAI, SHOU, PILAF gasp]
Wow, they do look alike.
I'm stumped; any theories?
No.
[grunts]
Look closely, my lord.
The index finger of our
new visitor's right hand.
[BEERUS]
Hmm?
--Whis, is that--?
--[WHIS] It is.
Huh?
[GOKU BLACK]
Vegeta.
And the Destroyer, Beerus.
It would seem
something ominous
and rather mystifying
has taken place.
Yes, I'm dying
to know his story.
[FUTURE TRUNKS] What is this?
How did you get here?
I don't know what caused this
warping of space-time
that brought you here,
but that warping
has brought me here, too.
Or perhaps I'm here because
your soul cried out to me.
Begging me to help set it free.
Come try.
[VEGETA] Don't! You're not
strong enough to beat him.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
But Father.
--[VEGETA] Kakarot.
--[GOKU laughs]
You snooze you lose, pal!
[laughs]
Man, this is freaky. It's like
I'm looking in a mirror.
How are you, Goku?
You're looking quite well.
[chuckles]
I can't begin to guess
who or what you actually are,
but oh well. Trunks down there
tells me you're strong.
Why don't you show me?
[chuckles]
That would be an honor.
Truth be know, Goku,
I've often wondered
what it would be like to fight
against you in this body.
Huh? What are you talkin' about?
The answer to that is not
something you need to know.
[GOKU yelling, groaning]
What do you know about him?
All I know is he's from
the future and he killed me.
[KRILLIN]
Huh?
You don't say.
So we're about
to watch Goku vs. Goku?
And I thought
fish sausage was a treat.
[chuckles]
Not bad. But you're a whole lot
stronger than that, right?
[GOKU BLACK laughs]
This really is a pleasure, Goku.
Having you of all people
seeing and rating my power.
[GOKU chuckles, grunts]
Jumping to Super Saiyan, are we?
It's my turn to show off.
[yells]
[GOKU BLACK grunts]
[KRILLIN, FUTURE TRUNKS gasp]
[GOKU]
Hm!
[laughing]
Yes, outstanding!
So, this is the power of
legendary Super Saiyan Goku.
Now I understand.
We're not just alike
on the outside, huh?
Fighting someone strong
gets you amped up, too.
[GOKU BLACK]
Yes.
[yells]
Nice! You can power up, too!
[BULMA]
What is that?
Your power is the only
good thing your warrior race
ever produced. I want
to feel that close up.
[laughing]
Seems like the guy in black
just keeps getting
stronger and stronger!
What's wrong with Goku?
Is he low on energy?
Why isn't he using
the power he showed
when he was fighting me?
Blame Kakarot's ridiculous habit
of not going all-out
from the start.
What?
[laughing]
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL gasp]
[laughing]
[chuckles]
What are you trying to find out?
I could ask you the same.
I'm just killing time...
...until you show
what you've really got.
But I'm getting too much
out of this to rush.
That will come in time.
Let's enjoy ourselves.
The power emanating
from this so-called "Black"
is considerable, sir.
Yes. And it's interesting, too.
It feels like Goku
yet not Goku. I'm not sure
if I've ever sensed an energy
quite like this before.
Curious, don't you think?
So what you're saying is
if I don't want to wait around
for your actual power
then I'll have to
bring it out by force. Ha!
Fine with me.
I was hoping you'd say that.
[GOKU]
Aaah!
[groans]
[laughing]
Uh! Huh?!
[yells]
[groaning]
[chuckles]
Excellent, Goku.
Yes. You can hurt me
as much as you want;
the pain will only
make me stronger.
Uh, okay, that's a pretty
creepy thing to say.
[GOKU BLACK laughs]
[grunts]
[KRILLIN]
Oh joy! He's getting stronger.
[yells]
[laughing]
[GOKU groans]
[BOTH holler]
Careful! Not the time machine!
[GOKU BLACK]
Huh? Hmmm.
Did he just call that
a time machine? Now I see.
So that's the way
he travelled through time;
with a heap of metal?
[GOKU]
Keep your eyes on the ball!
[groans]
[gasps]
[GOKU BLACK groaning]
[BOTH gasp]
Whoa, what's happening to him?
That pull. The distortion
in space-time
must be dissipating.
It's going back to normal.
[GOKU BLACK grunting]
How could you?
[laughing]
Aaah!
[GOKU]
Hey!
[KRILLIN]
Okay. That's a new one.
I'm not sensing his energy.
It's almost as if
he completely vanished.
Our invader didn't disappear
by his own choice, did he?
Hard to know for sure, my lord.
But it's most likely that
machine created a considerable
warp in the space-time
as it passed through it.
And that Time Ring
reacted to the warp,
pulling Black to
this time somewhat like
a planet spiraling down
into a gravity well.
As the disturbance subsided
and space-time returned
to its former state,
the pull ceased, too.
So, like a marble
in a drawn slingshot,
when the pulling force let go,
Black was launched back
into the time
from which he came.
No more pull, so no more Black.
You might say he
ran out of time.
[gasps]
So I'm back to the future?
[grunts]
[groaning]
[chuckles, groaning]
So, Goku. That's what
the power of your exalted
Super Saiyan
transformation feels like.
It's quite a different thing
to experience how you fight
firsthand now that I can
apply it so directly to myself.
All those battles
with Trunks were instructive,
but this will help me hone
my strength so much further.
[breathes heavily]
No. Looks like I won't be
able to go back there again.
But, that's okay,
because I've destroyed
their time machine.
Which means Trunks can never
come back to this time, either.
[laughing]
At last! There is no one left
in this world who can resist me.
Uh--
So, what do you think
happened to him?
[FUTURE TRUNKS] I'm sure
he returned to my future.
[grunts]
But now I can't get back there.
And I was so close! I failed.
Father said he'd go.
And Goku, too!
Working together,
I know we could have won!
I was the only one who could
stand up to him in my time.
Now he has no one.
He's going to exterminate
all of mankind!
Just like he always
said he would.
Tell me.
Compared to all the
other times you went up
against Black in your future,
just how strong did he seem
during our fight?
He's shown me more power.
But I wouldn't say
it's much more.
So he was only holding back
a little against me?
Yeah. I think.
--Awesome!
--[VEGETA] Good,
then you can relax!
Kakarot's true battle power is
a great deal higher than that.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
What?
And let me state for the record,
the same goes for mine as well.
[FUTURE TRUNKS] How? What have
you guys been through?
Hah. Quite a bit.
Black might be
weaker than you now,
but I felt his energy
growing rapidly
when he was fighting you.
Yeah. There's no telling
how deep it goes.
[PILAF, MAI, SHOU
imitating siren ringing]
Ha-ha! Let's count off!
Two! Uh, sorry, I mean one.
Two!
Three! The Imperial Fire Brigade
heroically reporting for duty!
--What?
--Since when?
Stand back you hopelessly
unprepared citizens,
and let the mighty
Imperial Fire Brigade
handle this towering blaze!
Fire hose ready!
[SHOU, MAI]
Ready, sir!
Commence spray!
Spraying, sir!
We've got this.
Take a deep breath.
Oh, wait, don't do that.
There's smoke.
[BULMA chuckles]
Right.
Can you fix that
time machine, Mom?
[BULMA] I'm afraid
there's too much damage.
I'll have to start from scratch.
But can't you build
a new one using those notes?
Well...
[BULMA]
Hmmm.
Augh! This might be
too much for the current me.
Aw, really?
[sighs]
[gasping]
Oh, yes, of course!
Uh, Mom? Hey!
[BULMA] Come on, I know
I put it here somewhere.
Honestly! It's like
my whole lab's a junk drawer!
I can't believe it's gone.
That was my world's final hope.
[BEERUS] Yes, I'm sure
that's upsetting for you,
but at least that means mankind
can no longer tamper with time.
[WHIS] These events raise other
vexing questions, though.
Did any of you notice
the ring Black was wearing?
On his right hand?
Yeah, so?
Well, it happens
to have been a Time Ring,
which only Supreme Kai
are allowed to use.
Most puzzling, wouldn't you say?
--[GOKU] Whoa!
--What's a Time Ring?
Are you saying that means
Goku Black is a Supreme Kai?
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
Supreme Kai are divine beings,
and they certainly do not
look like Saiyans.
If Black's not a Supreme Kai,
then who is he?
You got me. Maybe Whis
knows something.
Time Rings are only designed
to take you into the future.
They only move back
when returning travelers
to the time
from which they came.
It is normally impossible
to travel any farther back
than your own relative present.
Again, traveling to the past
is strictly forbidden,
even for deities,
due to the grievous
complexities it creates.
[GOKU]
Hmm.
So you can't go to the past to
get a present for your relative?
I get confused just
talking about this stuff.
Something's happened
that shouldn't have, Goku.
That's all that
you need to worry about.
[FUTURE TRUNKS] If Black has
a Time Ring and isn't a Kai,
maybe I could use one, too!
May I borrow your ring, great
deity, to reach the future?
Are you trying to anger me
on purpose, mortal?
Keep it up and I'll do as my
title suggests, and destroy you.
[gasps]
Like my attendant told you,
I'm a Destroyer god
and only Supreme Kai
are allowed Time Rings,
so there's nothing to lend.
Oh. I'm sorry.
But I have to get back
to my time somehow.
Or it's all over.
What did we say?
Fiddling with time
is a serious transgression,
you've no doubt caused
enough complication already!
It's become painfully clear
you and Black
are nothing but trouble.
You think Black could
get back here again?
Good question.
If my theory's right, then no.
His traveling here was a freak
occurrence, not intentional.
Aw, man. But, if he can't
come back to this time
and we can't go there either,
how am I gonna fight him again?
Wait! Can't you do it, Whis?!
Excuse me?
Your power! You know!
That do-over thing
you did against Frieza
to roll back time!
Can't you just rewind everything
to before Black blew up
the time machine?
[WHIS]
Clever! But no.
--[KRILLIN, FUTURE TRUNKS gasp]
--[GOKU] What?
I'm only capable of
turning back by three minutes,
and it's been
much longer than that.
Sorry, you've missed the boat.
Oh, what a shame.
[GOKU] Come on, Lord Beerus.
Can't you do something?
--[BEERUS] No!
--[GOKU groans]
And that's how you
put out a fire!
I forgot how it felt to succeed!
Yes, well, now that
we're living in this
gazillionaire's paradise
it's only right
that we make ourselves useful
and earn our keep!
You're right we should
earn our keep,
but I'd say we've earned
a little extra.
Don't you agree?
Of course, which is why
I'll be demanding
a generous cash donation,
extra dessert with
all our meals from now on,
and steak and loaded pancakes
every other day!
[PILAF laughing]
[ALL laughing]
We must see this through,
even if we have
to sacrifice everything.
You're the last hope we've got,
son; it's all up to you.
I'm sorry mom, but I can't
keep that promise now.
You're the best chance
that we've got;
you have to survive!
I can't.
You don't give up.
You find a way.
Right.
So, Whis. Should we guess what
our troublemakers will do next?
Well, I just heard Vegeta
tell his future son
not to give up.
Mortals are always
so quick to say that.
But sometimes there are
forces beyond your control.
Knowing when to give up's
an important skill, too.
Speaking of
uncontrollable forces,
where are the
other fish sausages?
They're in my belly.
That's what I was
afraid of, my lord.
I guess that means
this fine specimen
I've been holding
is the last one.
I bet you'd love to eat this.
But as you said, we all
have to know when to give up.
Oh! So delicious!
[BEERUS growls]
[BULMA] I found it, I found it,
I found it! I found it!
[panting]
[KRILLIN]
You found what?
I'm just gonna guess
you didn't mean a hair brush.
I had to tear
my lab apart to find it,
but I knew it was
in there somewhere.
What are you talking about, Mom?
[BULMA giggles]
Guys, look! There's still hope
after all! Check it out!
[ALL gasp]
Whaaaa...?
Ta-da! A time machine!
Wait, what?
[BULMA giggles]
There was still
one more, remember?
[thunder rumbles]
Get ready!
Instant Transmission!
Two fingers placed
right between the eyes
Get ready!
My hair will stand up!
'Cause I got
all the power of a Saiyan!
Inside we all have
a shining heart!
(Whoa, look out!)
Time warp to the future,
say konnichiwa
See the world in ways
that you thought impossible
Open open up to your intuition
No you can't give up
When your heart is still beating
Pounding out a rhythm
that'll make you wanna dance!
Ohhhh HEY!
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! (KAMEHAMEHA!)
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! It's what you need
Feel the magic of the beat
(Woo-hoo)
DANCE! It makes you smile
Nothing else can
quite compete (yoka yoka)
So when the world is lame
Don't play that game
You know that every problem
can be answered the same
Just let go and feel the rhythm
Everybody dance
with all your might!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And I can never get used to
how crazy time travel is!
So Trunks was fighting
in the future
with a grown-up version
of that little girl?
And she wasn't
the only one helping him
fight my look-alike; there's a
whole resistance army, too?
Now we've really got
to get back to the future,
and put a stop to Black!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Feelings That Transcend Time.
Trunks and Mai."
Be sure you don't
miss it, okay?