♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
as his battle
with Goku ramped up,
the resurrected Frieza
unveiled the results
of his intensive training,
and transformed into something
far beyond his previous form.
I know the gold's
a bit gauche but I wanted
to ensure you
grasped my new position.
At the very top of the
universe's pecking order.
And now for the sake
of your feeble little mind,
we can keep the name
simple as well.
We'll call this Golden Frieza.
[NARRATOR] With Goku
powered up to his own,
self-made version
of Super Saiyan God,
the two titans appeared
at first to be evenly matched.
But as the fight raged on,
Golden Frieza's power
proved to be
even greater than Goku thought,
and gradually the
Evil Emperor wore Goku down.
If Frieza can't be overpowered,
is there another way?
The battle continues. Now!
[NARRATOR] "A Chance
Appears in a Tight Spot!
Launch a
Counteroffensive, Goku!"
[GOKU breathes heavily]
On your back gasping for air.
Quite undignified for the God
of Monkeys, don't you think?
[chuckles]
Just a little breather
before I fight you for real.
[FRIEZA snarls]
[GOKU groans]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[gasps]
Heh.
That's it! Yes,
that's the look I'm after.
Now go ahead
and cry for me! Scream!
Let me savor
every anguished wail!
Tch. What an idiot.
[GOHAN]
This is awful.
[KRILLIN] It looks like
your dad's underestimated
this Golden Frieza power.
He's losing! Come on, Jaco,
we've got to do something, now!
You've been all over the galaxy,
you've got to know
someone or something
that can help us!
Knock it off, Bulma.
You're giving me
motion sickness!
--Well I've seen enough.
--Uh. Yeah.
I suggest you stay there.
--[BOTH] Hm?
--[GOHAN] But why?
'Cause all you're going
to do is get in the way.
Goku may need help against
this stronger Frieza,
but not from you.
If he and Vegeta
simply work together,
the Saiyans should have
no problem achieving victory.
Yeah, that's right!
I knew that but I get
so stressed out I forget!
Go, Vegeta! Fight next to Goku.
If you work together
you can win this!
Well, sadly, Bulma,
that is not a possibility.
--[BEERUS] Hm?
--[BULMA] Huh?
We discussed this subject
during their training.
Though the Saiyans
have teamed up in the past,
neither showed any interest
in doing it again.
It seems they would rather
lose than agree to that.
As far as I can tell,
they're both too proud
to work together in combat.
But that makes no sense!
Your wife is here too, you know!
[BEERUS] Battle obsessed
to a fault, huh?
[WHIS] Indeed, my lord. They're
not unlike you in that regard.
What's that? Did you
just say something?
Just eating.
[screams]
You bastard!
[FRIEZA snarls]
What?
[groans]
[FRIEZA] You're pressing
your luck, God Monkey.
[yells]
--Goku!
--That's bad.
[SORBET] I knew Lord Frieza
would deliver for us!
Despite a few hitches, my
gambit is working after all!
The Emperor
is back because of me.
And soon we'll
rebuild our forces
and have the universe
in shackles once again!
[JACO] Bulma, you're the one
who needs to act!
You've got to
control your husband!
--[BULMA] What?
--[JACO] Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Don't you realize
if the Saiyans lose
I'll be in danger too?
If they lose, that would be
the only silver lining!
Staying close to Bulma
was definitely a bad idea.
[panting]
[breathes heavily]
--[chuckles]
--[VEGETA] Hm?
--That's interesting.
--[exhales]
Perhaps now you're
beginning to understand
a tiny sliver of
the humiliation you made me
suffer through on Planet Namek.
[chuckles]
That was ages ago.
You really know how to
hold on to a grudge, huh?
[FRIEZA]
A grudge?
Don't trivialize me with
such a paltry, piddling word.
I was on the very cusp
of immortality.
I would have ruled the universe
till the end of time.
You talk of god-like power.
I would have been the god.
The ultimate usurper!
And you ripped that all away
with your filthy simian paws!
[gasps]
Die. In disgrace.
At the hands of your Master!
[GOKU]
You fool!
[yells]
Ever since you fired
that fateful blast,
not one hour has gone by
when I wasn't consumed
by my righteous fury
and the fantasy
of this vengeful day.
[GOKU yells, groans]
Damn it! Let go of me!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[ALL gasp]
He's in for it now.
Yep.
[FRIEZA] But at long last those
wrongs can be right, Goku.
Let's try this.
[FRIEZA laughs]
I want to see
what your body can endure.
No, Goku!
Oh, no, Dad!
[panting]
[chuckles]
Gohan. Will he be okay?
I don't know. I can't
sense his power either.
Come on, Goku.
Please don't be dead.
[JACO]
Save your tears, Bulma.
He's okay.
[BULMA]
Huh?
[JACO] I don't know how he
does it, or how much more
he can handle...
but for now, at least,
he's still up there.
How could anyone survive that?
[GOKU] In case it makes you
feel any better, Frieza,
that one really hurt like hell.
Honestly, when I saw
the blast I didn't think
I would pull through,
but I guess you're still
stuck with me after all.
My goodness. I must've
held back my full power.
Seems I wasn't ready
to say goodbye yet.
[gasps]
[wheezes]
[VEGETA]
Kakarot!
I can only wait for so long!
If you're really too dense
to figure out what's happening,
I'll be more than happy
to take over
and kill this bastard for you!
Are you piping up again?
What's he talking about?
[gasps]
[laughs]
As if you'd
stand a chance, Vegeta!
The only way you could kill me
is if I died from laughter.
You've had your shot.
It's my turn now.
Ah, come on, Vegeta.
That isn't fair!
You and I both know
it's just about to get fun!
Hm?
I'm not gonna
let you take over
right at the best part!
I'm done watching!
You're hogging him!
Just a little more time.
Just a teensy,
weensy bit, all right?
Do you honestly
expect me to believe you?
I'm serious, okay. I promise!
Just the tiniest
little teeny bit.
[grunts]
Stop this ridiculous chatter.
You won't make a mockery of me!
All right, Frieza.
You want serious?
Then that's what you'll get.
[GOKU]
I'll tell you right now,
you'd be a whole lot
better off leaving this planet
on a high note, while you're
still winning the battle.
After all you did just
get a new chance at life
and I'd hate to
see you to waste it.
[laughs]
Retreat with victory
so close at hand?
That's a strategy only
a Saiyan could devise.
What sort of fool
do you think I am?
[chuckles]
It's up to you.
But if you stick around
it's gonna get harder,
because I'm about to
turn the tables on you.
The flailing of cornered prey
always fascinates me.
Since you're
ignoring my warning,
I assume that means you haven't
realized the problem yet.
Your Golden Frieza form
is awesome,
but it has a big weakness, too.
[laughs]
Don't try to manipulate me
with mind games, Goku,
I'm the master of the art.
You can't chip away
at my confidence
with some vague
and ludicrous claim.
Then I guess we'll see.
Since powering up
I've been using you
as a wrecking ball
to reshape this landscape.
Yet you say I'm the one
with the weakness?
Don't you know
for a lie to work
there has to be
a kernel of truth?
It's not effecting you yet,
Frieza, but it's about to.
And all I have to do
is wait for it.
Is that so? Then all
I would have to do
is kill you now, since you've
so stupidly given me warning.
[chuckles]
That is your best chance,
but I'm not gonna make it easy.
Oh?
[GOKU bellows]
[chuckles]
You're always more fun
when you're desperate, Goku.
You should have been using
that reserve from the start.
Well, now I'm gonna hit you
with everything I've got.
Glad to hear it.
Yes, let's make this
final act a strong one
with all the grandeur
it deserves.
I'm going to unleash everything
I have left as well.
You're going to see
what true power looks like.
[bellows]
[gasps]
There's no getting around it,
your strength
really is incredible.
Isn't this what you wanted?
The chance to fight me
in my full glory?
Yeah. It's only right.
From here on out
we both play for keeps.
I can't believe they
were still holding back.
Their power's so high I can't
make sense of it anymore.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
They're in totally
different territory now.
Please, Dad. Just win.
[GOKU yells]
[BOTH yell]
[GOKU]
Not there yet.
[yells]
[GOKU]
Just a little longer.
[groans]
[yells]
[FRIEZA]
Damn!
[yells]
You're not getting away now!
[GOKU]
Crap!
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[GOKU groans]
That filthy Saiyan.
Making some bluff
about Frieza's weakness.
Obviously my lord still has
the upper hand in this fight!
[VEGETA]
Hmph!
I can't see what's going on
but it's bad, right? Is it bad?
I just wish
we could help somehow.
Come on, Dad.
Now do you realize...
the truth?
You're nothing compared to me!
[GOKU] Damn it! He'll really
have an advantage in the water.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Drowning would be
far too merciful!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[laughs]
[GOKU grunts]
[chuckles]
[FRIEZA] I'm ready
to claim my victory.
Die!
[ALL gasp]
--[SORBET] Ooh.
--[VEGETA] Hmph!
What in the--?
Your candle may have
been brighter, Frieza,
but it was burning
a lot faster, too.
[FRIEZA]
Eeeh!
It's over now. And I've won.
--[GOKU grunts]
--[FRIEZA groans]
[gasps]
It can't be!
He outlasted Frieza.
I knew Goku could
turn the tables on him!
All right, Dad!
I knew you could do it, Goku!
Now hurry up
and finish him for good
so we can go home and celebrate!
[panting]
This isn't over.
[whispers]
Lord Frieza!
You know what to do, Sorbet.
[chuckles]
Huh? Yes, sir.
[GOKU]
You understand now, don't you?
[FRIEZA]
Huh?
[panting]
Your weakness. That's what
I was talking about.
Spare me your monkey wisdom.
You rushed here
as soon as you achieved
this new form, didn't you?
You were so desperate
to get revenge.
Yes, that's right. Is there
a point to this babble?
[GOKU]
Your "Golden Frieza" state.
It's burning through more power
than your body can supply.
And now you don't even
have enough gas left
in the tank to defend yourself,
let alone win this fight.
[exhales]
And it's a good thing
for me because I was
pretty close to
biting it back there.
Well, I guess
he does have a brain.
He could afford to use it
about ten times more often
but yes, it's a start.
[GOKU] You should've waited
until you were used to
this form and knew how
to regulate its power
before you started
picking fights.
If you had, I'd be
the one on the ground.
[FRIEZA growls]
I do not accept this. I can't!
You will not defeat me again!
Face it, Frieza.
It doesn't matter how much
you want to win, it's over.
[FRIEZA growls]
[whispers]
All set, my lord.
Denying it won't
make it any less true.
No!
There's no point in
dragging this out any longer.
This can't be true!
I'm supposed to kill you!
I'm supposed to conquer all!
I'm the Evil Emperor
Lord Frieza!
You should leave this planet
while you still you can.
[FRIEZA growls]
I'll be here for a rematch
when you're ready, I promise.
[echoes]
I promise...
[gasps]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[GOKU groans]
[laughs]
A perfect shot!
[grunts]
That imbecile!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Excellent
marksmanship, Sorbet.
Your timing
was flawless as well.
Looks like you're
not useless after all.
Thank you, sir,
I live to serve!
Good thing for
contingency plans, right Goku?
As if I'd allow the slightest
chance of losing to you again.
Clearly a dirty move
but effective--
you have to give him that.
Yes. I specifically warned
Goku this could happen.
It doesn't matter
how strong he is
if he completely
drops his guard like that.
That's not good.
What? That's how
you want to win?
[groans]
You're too strong
for your own good;
it's made you overconfident.
A fearless fool who
insists on second chances
and habitually
lowers his guard.
When powered up you're
one of the strongest mortals
in the cosmos,
yet you've allowed yourself
to be felled
by a common ray gun.
How pitiful does that
make you feel, Goku?
[chuckles]
[screams]
Feel that?
That's the whole universe
watching with bated breath,
because they've just seen
the shocking climax
in my theater of revenge!
[wails]
[laughs]
And with a final bang,
the drama ends.
Down comes the curtain.
[ALL gasp]
[FRIEZA grunts]
Wait.
You forgot I'm
in this show, too.
♪ Closing Song ♪
Goodbye to our adventure
In twilight we must
go our separate ways
And try to discover
The path to our own destiny
I can't find the words
To tell you how much
our parting hurts
I hope you know
I'll always love you
And all that we shared
will be remembered
How could I forget your face?
All my memories erased
I can still hear the
melody of your voice
Petals falling from above
Fade away all that we loved
In the twilight,
fade away, fade away!
Sayonara!
Fade away, fade away!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
I can't believe I dropped
my guard like that.
And now Vegeta
gets to unleash the power
he's gotten from training,
and it's out of this world.
But Frieza's so crazy for
revenge, what's he gonna do
if he sees he can't win?
The earth is gonna what?
Next time
on Dragon Ball Super:
"The Earth Explodes?!
A Decisive Kamehameha!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?