♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super.
With the remaining teams
fighting for the survival
of their universes,
the Tournament of Power
continued to intensify,
and the Seventh Universe
faced off against opponents
they couldn't see.
But still, they found a way.
Invisibility's a neat trick,
but without it you're kinda
pathetic, aren't you?
[yells]
[NARRATOR]
Despite successfully defeating
the invisible man Gamisalas,
Piccolo was forced out of
the ring by another combatant
from the Fourth Universe
who was even more elusive.
[GOKU grunting]
Something's wrong.
I know he's there,
I can sense him,
but none of my attacks
are connecting.
Now I see. Of course.
[A17] The reason you're not
hitting him is far more simple.
[GAMISALAS grunts]
[growls]
[A17]
We're fighting an insect.
[NARRATOR] Thanks to the
clever actions of Android 17,
the insect warrior
was eliminated,
and the Omni-Kings erased the
Fourth Universe from existence.
[BOTH]
Bye-bye! Ha, ha!
[screaming]
[NARRATOR] Only three universes
are left in the tournament.
Which one will win, and keep
their reality intact?
The battle continues... now!
[NARRATOR]
"A Perfect Survival Strategy!
The 3rd Universe's
Menacing Assassin!"
[ZENO]
Wow, so many fighters are gone.
[FUTURE ZENO]
Yes, only a few are not gone.
So, will it be over soon?
Yes, very soon.
[GRAND MINISTER]
There is still so much
to look forward to, sires.
With the numbers down, the real
excitement is about to begin.
The champions of the three
remaining universes will soon
have no choice but to face
each other, head to head.
That is a very good point!
I can't wait to see!
[ZENO] I think this
will be very exciting!
[FUTURE ZENO]
Yes, and thrilling, too!
The good news is we've still got
six fighters left on our team.
But now that we're
in the final stretch,
we'll have to work
even harder to survive.
Just take a look at
who we're up against.
[VEGETA] Tch. Those circus
performers from the Eleventh.
We knew we'd have
to deal with Jiren
and his teammates eventually,
and I guess that time is now.
Not necessarily, Dad.
We could choose to
fight the Eleventh,
but there's another
team to worry about.
Universe Three, right?
[VEGETA, GOKU]
Hm?
Yeah.
[PICCOLO] The Third Universe
still has five in the ring.
Only one less than us.
Yeah, so we can't
exactly count 'em out.
[EYRE laughs]
We've managed to hang on
while so many have fallen.
It would seem the survival
strategy of the Third Universe
has been executed almost as
brilliantly as it was devised.
[MOSCO beeping]
Lord Mosco says, "The most
crucial phase of the plan
has yet to begin.
This is not the time
for foolish celebrations"
[gasps]
[MOSCO beeping]
Lord Mosco is wise.
He says, "with fewer combatants,
this is our best chance."
Yes, I could not agree more.
[alarm blares]
I've just received
the order from Lord Mosco!
It's time! Third Universe
team, fall in!
I want you all to
remember with every strike
that the fate of our
universe depends on you.
The Seventh Universe has
the most fighters remaining
in this Tournament, so we
will eliminate them first.
Attack!
[KOITSUKAI]
Beam Kai!
[VEGETA]
That bastard!
[GOKU grunting]
[PANCÉA]
Pancéa!
[GOKU groaning]
You okay?
[BORARETA]
Bora!
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOHAN groans]
Damn, these fighters are
coming at us like crazy!
You guys all right?
Right now, I think we need to
make sure we're all right.
[BIARRA]
Ha!
[BIARRA screams]
[gasps]
[BIARRA]
That won't work on me.
I guess not.
This one's built tough.
We'll have to fight like
we actually mean it.
[EYRE laughing]
Biarra's capabilities
make him one of the two
greatest defensive specialists
in our universe. He will
patiently wear down
their stamina and then
turn the tables on them.
Just as we predicted!
[yelling]
What?!
[BORARETA]
Bora!
[VEGETA grunts]
I'm getting worried.
Seems like these bucket-heads
are beginning to read our moves.
Considering they've
lasted for this long,
it's entirely possible.
I do not expect they will
be defeated easily, my lord.
What the...?
[PANCÉA]
Pancéa!
Uh!
Come on!
[GOKU grunting]
[PANCÉA]
'Cea!
[KOITSUKAI]
Analyzing enemy combat strength.
Target approaching.
Ha!
[gasps]
[VEGETA, GOKU grunting]
[KOITSUKAI] Koitsukai to
Pancéa and Borareta.
Combine attacks to
wipe them out. Over.
--Borareta acknowledges.
--Pancéa acknowledges.
[GOKU grunts]
Bring it, you junkyard scraps!
I'll knock the bolts
right out of you!
--[BORARETA] Bora!
--[PANCÉA] 'Cea!
[GOKU growls]
[PANCÉA]
'Cea!
[GOHAN growling]
Gohan!
Please, Dad. Trust me.
I can fight these
guys on my own.
[yells]
--[BORARETA] Bora!
--[PANCÉA] Cea!
[GOHAN yelling]
[BORARETA]
Bora!
[PANCÉA]
'Cea!
Come on! I'll take on
your whole team myself!
[GOKU laughing]
[VEGETA] Tch. If you lose,
it'll be on you, boy.
Is he really trying to
defeat them singlehandedly?
If the Third's knocked out,
it'll be a showdown
with Jiren's squad.
Gohan must be trying
to save Goku and Vegeta's
strength for that final battle.
That's a smart play.
Yeah, that's one of
Gohan's best traits.
Thinking several moves ahead.
All right, Gohan!
You can do it!
[GOHAN]
I've got to give everything--
right here, right now.
We can't afford to let Dad and
Vegeta waste any more strength.
I can do this.
[GOHAN grunts]
[beeping]
[PANCÉA]
'Cea!
[GOHAN yells]
[yelling]
[PANCÉA]
'Cea!
Uh!
[PANCÉA]
Pancéa!
[GOHAN grunts]
[KOITSUKAI]
Beam Kai!
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN yelling]
[BORARETA]
Bora!
[GOHAN]
Perfect!
Now that I've got a good grip
on you, you're finished!
[yells]
[BORARETA screams]
[GOHAN grunting]
Those guys are pretty strong,
and Gohan's giving them
a real challenge.
That's my son for ya.
[VEGETA]
Hmph.
He fended off an impressive
combination move,
all by himself!
That's right, kid, run circles
around those punks!
Uh! I wasn't expecting them
to get a handle on
our moves, as well.
[BIARRA]
Give up.
You're a lot tougher
than I thought.
And all this time,
I thought you would be a bore.
How do you like this?
[BIARRA]
You waste your time.
[BIARRA grunts]
[A18 grunts]
[BIARRA]
These blasts accomplish nothing.
Remarkable. You must
feel so proud.
In that case, you won't mind if
we go even harder, will you?
[BIARRA grunting]
What's wrong? I thought
our attacks did nothing.
Watch out, cause we're
still ramping up.
[BIARRA grunting]
[A17 yells]
[A18 yelling]
[BIARRA groaning]
I'm sorry, did we actually
hurt Mr. Invincible?
Heh. No offense, but just
standing there taking
our attacks is about the dumbest
strategy I've ever seen.
Buckle up, 'cause you're
going for a ride!
[BIARRA screams]
Contestant Biarra of the
Third Universe is eliminated.
[ZENO]
Biarra... boop! Heh!
No, no, not Biarra!
How could they defeat him?
[growls] Why didn't
his approach work?
Don't those two ever get tired?
[BEERUS laughs]
If you're trying to exhaust
your opponents, you shouldn't
be fighting Androids
who have infinite energy.
Excellent work, you guys!
Gohan seems to be
easily handling
the other combatants
from the Third.
This does bode well.
--[BORARETA] Borareta!
--[PANCÉA] Pancéa!
[GOHAN grunts]
[MOSCO beeping]
Lord Mosco says, "There is
only one way to prevail.
The time has come for
them to execute Plan X."
Oh, right. Plan X, I forgot!
We've delayed it long enough.
This is the end of the line.
I'll finish this!
[GOHAN growls]
[PAPARONI laughs]
You've got it backwards.
It's not the end,
it's only the beginning!
The real fight starts now!
[PAPARONI laughing]
For your sake,
I hope you're ready.
For what?
For Plan X.
Programming Phase.
Engage!
[KOITSUKAI]
Plan X. Order received.
Koitsukai!
[PANCÉA]
Pancéa!
[BORARETA]
Borareta!
[gasps]
[KOITSUKAI]
Koitsukai!
[PANCÉA]
Pancéa!
[BORARETA]
Borareta!
[KOITSUKAI, PANCÉA, BORARETA]
Combined!
[GOHAN growls]
[gasping]
[BEERUS growls]
[EYRE chuckles]
[MOSCO beeping]
Wow! They're all together now!
Combined they are very big!
Yes, they are not small at all!
Set functionality to
maximum level, 1,256%!
Show them the true power
of the Third Universe's
collective warrior!
Koicéareta!
Do you feel that? Their energy
just shot up like a rocket!
Tch. Well, that's annoying.
Even if their clumsy-looking
combination is more powerful,
Gohan should still be able
to handle it, right?
[TOP]
It seems the Third
still had one more pesky
trick up its sleeve.
[JIREN]
Mm...
Just when their little fight
was beginning to bore me,
things take another
fascinating turn.
I think I'll stay up here
and enjoy the carnage.
[EYRE laughs] As instructed,
Dr. Paparoni altered
all three of their bodies to
maximize their strongest traits,
then combined them to
form the ultimate warrior
with superior speed,
power, and defense.
[MOSCO beeping]
Lord Mosco says, "Plan X
is a complete success,
and our victory
is now assured."
Teach them raw muscles
can't compare
with the might of technology!
It's time to demonstrate
your true power
and the superiority
of the Third!
[GOHAN growls]
[PAPARONI]
Attack!
[KOICÉARETA roars]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN yelling]
'Attaboy, Gohan!
[gasps]
That didn't even phase him!
[PAPARONI] Excellent.
You've got him doubting himself.
Now's the time to attack!
[KOICÉARETA grunts]
[yelling]
Wha--?
[KOICÉARETA grunts]
[PAPARONI laughs]
Fool.
You thought you could
outmaneuver him
because of his size, but his
speed is enhanced, as well.
Then I'll just lose the gimmicks
and fight him head on!
[GOHAN, KOICÉARETA grunting]
Aw, man!
[KOICÉARETA yells]
[GOHAN grunting]
[gasps]
Oh, great!
[PAPARONI laughs] How long
can those organic muscles
hold him off,
warrior of the Seventh?
[GOHAN grunting]
He's slipping!
You have to dig deeper, boy!
[PAPARONI]
Go on, Koicéareta! Smash him!
[yells]
[VEGETA, GOKU yell]
[KOICÉARETA groaning]
[ALL gasp]
Seriously?!
I'm sorry I barged in
on you like that
while you're takin'
out the trash, Gohan.
But thanks to the
rest you bought me
I've got some strength back,
and there's no way we can just
stand around on the sidelines
without getting
our licks in, too.
I've got it.
Then let's fight together.
If they love trios so much
then we'll give them our own.
Those scrap-metal jokers
won't last a minute
against three Saiyan warriors!
Ha!
All right, Gohan, let's go!
Right!
[KOICÉARETA roars]
[VEGETA, GOHAN, GOKU grunt]
[ALL yelling]
[KOICÉARETA grunting]
[VEGETA yells]
[GOKU]
Ha!
[VEGETA, GOKU]
[KOICÉARETA groaning]
[PAPARONI] What?
They're driving him back?
There's no way my greatest
masterpiece can be outdone!
Koicéareta! Never give up!
Never surrender!
[KOICÉARETA grunts]
[ALL gasp]
He's unbelievable! He managed
to block their blasts!
[KOICÉARETA growls]
[PAPARONI laughing]
Imbeciles!
Perhaps now even your
organic minds understand
the power of the Third's
combined warrior!
And that there's no way you can
stop him from crushing you!
[laughing]
I wouldn't be so
sure about that.
You're the real imbecile here.
[PAPARONI]
And why's that?
[gasps]
I never would have gotten
this chance without Dad
and Vegeta's help, and there's
no way I'm gonna waste it!
[PAPARONI whimpering]
I see, they were
just buying time
for Gohan to charge his energy.
Those guys know how to win,
that's for sure.
Here's my full power!
[yells]
[KOICÉARETA grunts]
[PAPARONI laughing]
You see?
That's the brilliance
of his design!
Even when you're giving
everything you have,
you're still not strong
enough to overcome
his magnificent defenses!
[GOHAN grunting]
[KOICÉARETA grunting]
[ALL gasp]
My universe is gonna win,
no matter what it takes!
[KOICÉARETA groaning]
[PAPARONI]
What? But how?
That's it! Get him, Gohan!
[GOHAN]
Ha!
[KOICÉARETA groaning]
It can't be!
[KOICÉARETA groans]
[PAPARONI screams]
[GOKU]
Gohan!
You did it, son.
We did.
He had a small opening,
and he made the most of it
with a well-executed attack.
Even as a giant,
combined warrior,
they were still no match
for three Saiyans.
You've made your
Destroyer proud, boy.
Well done, Gohan.
[PAPARONI grunting]
[growls]
[VEGETA] I figured you went over
the side, and yet here you are.
You're one stubborn bastard.
[GOHAN] Sorry, but you need to
leave the ring. Last warning.
[laughing]
What the hell are you
laughing about?
[PAPARONI]
I was hoping I could avoid this
but you leave me no choice.
I'm going to knock
every last one of you
out of the Tournament,
even if it costs me my life!
You're about to face the
ultimate, secret technique
of the Third Universe,
from which there is no escape!
[ALL gasp]
[NARRATOR]
After Gohan's powerful attack,
it seemed the Third Universe
was heading for certain defeat.
But now the sneering
Dr. Paparoni claims
they have another play.
What is this "ultimate,
secret technique,"
and can it keep them alive?
The fates of the last
three competing universes
will soon be decided,
as only ten minutes remain
in the Tournament of Power.
Next time, on Dragon Ball Super.
A 70 centimeter squared window
Today the sun broke
through the clouds
The rain is fin'ly gone
Gonna open up
the window for once
No reason, just because
This room has been
stained with the sighs
Of everyday regret
Now it's time to clear the air
Every moment was consumed
with my thoughts of you
Knowing in my heart those dreams
won't be coming true
I've always wanted nothing more
than to see your face
I move on knowing that your
mem'ry can't be erased
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
After Dr. Paparoni reveals
his secret technique,
we've got to fight
an even bigger warrior
with massive strength!
This giant could destroy us all,
not to the mention the ring!
If we're gonna get through this,
our entire team will
have to fight together.
Vegeta, Frieza--
that means you, too!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"All-Out War!
The Ultimate Four-Fold Union vs.
the 7th Universe's
Total Offensive!"
Make sure you
don't miss it, okay?