♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Goku wanted Frieza as
the team's tenth warrior!
[GOKU]
Don't worry, guys.
I'll just ask Fortuneteller Baba
to bring him back for 24 hours.
[NARRATOR] And so, Goku
visited Hell to convince
his old arch-enemy to enter
the Tournament of Power.
[FRIEZA]
All right. But on one condition.
If in the end we
prove victorious,
and our Universe remains intact,
you will use the Dragon Balls
to truly bring me back.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
in the Fourth Universe,
Quitela schemed about
Frieza's return.
[QUITELA]
Relax, Kur. I thought of
an absolutely brilliant way
to stop the Seventh!
And what would that be?
[QUITELA laughs]
[NARRATOR] Frieza's safe return
is anything but assured!
Goku's effort to get the Evil
Emperor on his team continues...
...now!
[NARRATOR]
"The Evil Emperor Returns!
A Reception from
Mysterious Assassins?"
[GOKU]
I'm starvin'!
Well, don't keep us in suspense.
How'd things go with Frieza?
Oh yeah! He's on board.
I'm surprised that
power-mad villain
actually agreed to your
24-hour-parole idea.
Uh. Yeah, me, too.
Well I figure even Frieza
wants a change of pace.
Better to get one day off than
be stuck there forever, right?
You're hiding something.
I just know it!
Goku. We always know
when you're lying.
Out with it.
Give us the truth, right now!
[GOKU chuckles nervously]
Okay. Don't be mad,
but I promised Frieza
that if our universe survives
the Tournament of Power
I'll gather up the Dragon Balls
and wish him back permanently.
What?!
You moron! Are you nuts?!
Yeah!
You know he's just gonna go
right back to his old evil ways!
How are you so stupid?!
You don't have to get so angry.
It's the best move
he could make.
[GOKU]
Um, thank you!
[WHIS] So what if Frieza
returns to your realm?
Compared to Grand Zeno
destroying our entire universe,
I'd say one more villain on the
loose is a small price to pay.
Yeah. I guess he's got a point.
Look, if Frieza does
anything bad... he'll pay.
We'll take him down
like we always do.
[VEGETA grunts]
[sighs] Well, if you're certain
he's our best option.
Frieza it is.
[SIDRA]
You know this for a fact?
[QUITELA]
Yes.
I have no doubt about it.
I've sent spies into
each of the universes
and their reports are
always accurate.
Sidra, I'm afraid that as soon
as the tournament begins,
the Seventh Universe plans to
crush everyone from your Ninth.
[SIDRA growls]
That miserable Seventh!
They'll pay for their insolence!
[QUITELA]
I understand your rage, Sidra.
Which is why I'd like to help
you eliminate them first.
[SIDRA]
Eliminate them how?
Just what are you
getting at, Quitela?
[QUITELA] My spies inform me
that the Seventh Universe
has drafted the tenth
member of their team.
This Frieza is a former emperor
and a powerful warrior.
He's on his way to joining
them as we speak.
[SIDRA]
Frieza?
[QUITELA]
Yes, and apparently
the Seventh Universe considers
him to be quite the villain,
equally feared and loathed.
Which is why I
believe if he were
eliminated before
reaching his new team...
...finding out who
did the dirty deed
would be all but impossible,
thanks to his many enemies.
We only have about
an hour and a half
before the Tournament starts.
If the Seventh Universe
doesn't show up
with the required
amount of warriors,
the Grand Zenos will likely
disqualify and destroy them
before the Tournament
even begins!
[SIDRA]
But wait,
if the Omni-Kings find out
about this plot,
won't it be our universes that
ultimately pay the price?
[QUITELA] We'll be fine, as long
as we don't get our hands dirty.
Perhaps you know some "hitmen"
who can do the job without
it leading back to us.
[SIDRA]
Hm...
[QUITELA] Good! Then the
next time we see each other
will be at the Tournament.
A Tournament
without the Seventh.
[QUITELA] You see, Kuru,
isn't my plan brilliant?
[KUR]
I never doubted you.
And by eliminating their
team before we even start
our own chances of winning
the Tournament of Power
will take a sharp upward turn.
But do you actually trust
Sidra to take out Frieza?
Yes. He's desperate.
[laughing]
[TRUNKS]
Mm... Frieza?
Hey. What exactly do
all these pictures mean?
[BULMA]
Honey, you're still awake?
Bulma, wait.
You haven't spilled
the senzu beans about
the tournament to Trunks
and Goten, have you?
Are you telling me the boys are
totally in the dark on all this?
Yes.
Oh, jeez. Well,
they can't find out now.
It would only complicate things.
Get him away from that.
[TRUNKS]
Huh...
Hey, Trunks, so, this board is
a, uh, a list of family friends
who want to congratulate us
on your sister's birth.
As you can see, many are
already here, just hangin' out.
But hold on a second.
Isn't Frieza that super bad guy
who invaded a while back?
[BULMA laughs nervously]
[TRUNKS] Seems kinda dangerous
to invite him over now.
[BULMA]
U-Uh...
[VEGETA clears throat]
True. But, Frieza's had...
Well, he's turned over
a new leaf, Son.
Ugh! He's one of
the good guys now!
[TRUNKS]
Really? Well, that's good.
[VEGETA]
Yep.
[VEGETA] Of all the rotten
villains in the cosmos,
why do I have to pretend
to like Frieza?!
Damn it all!
[TRUNKS sighs]
Hey Trunks, I got
something for ya!
So there's this island
with monsters.
Do you wanna come see it?
Wait, are you serious?
[GOKU]
Yep! See this guy here named 17?
He works on the monster island
and protects them from poachers.
And what's a "poacher"?
[GOKU] Bad guys who
illegally hunt animals.
Or in this case, monsters.
Y'know, because guarding
them is such a big job,
17 hasn't been able
to come congratulate
your mom like he wants.
How about this?
You and Goten can
trade places with him.
While he's here
you can guard the island!
And play with all the monsters!
Wait! That's not a--
I'm ready!
Yeah! Let's go right now!
Great! Go and tell
Goten what's up.
Then next stop, Monster Island!
[TRUNKS]
Thanks, Goku! This rules!
And that takes care of that.
Hey, hold on.
Why do I get the feeling
you already promised 17
the boys would guard his island?
Sneaky bastard.
[laughs nervously] Ya got me.
Of course.
It's not dangerous, is it?
[GOKU] It'll be a piece
a cake for those two.
You have my word!
[VEGETA]
Tch! Whatever that's worth.
[GOKU laughs]
[sighs]
--[GOKU] Hey, Krillin.
--[KRILLIN] Uh. What's that?
I hate to spring this
on you last minute,
but do you mind taking
Trunks and Goten
down to 17's island?
I could really use
the help here, man.
[KRILLIN]
Uh...?
[GOKU]
Baba's bringing back Frieza,
so I gotta be at her place
to deal with that.
Um... I don't think
17... likes me much.
[GOKU]
You have nothin' to worry about!
He's not a bad guy anymore!
Look, if it'll make ya feel
better you can take 18.
[KRILLIN grumbles]
[KRILLIN]
Well...
18 is a completely different
person than she used to be.
And if she can change,
I suppose her brother can, too.
[KRILLIN]
Fine. I'll take 'em.
[GOKU]
I owe ya!
Which reminds me--
I owe Baba a gift, too!
Bulma, ya got anything
nice I can give her?
[BULMA]
That greedy old bat.
Come on, I'll find something.
[GOKU]
Ah. Thank you!
[ROSHI grunting]
[yells]
[ROSHI]
Lightning... Flash...
...Surprise Attack!
[YAJIROBE groaning]
[screaming]
[ROSHI] Considering the
tournament's ring-out rule,
immobilizing techniques
like this
or the Evil Containment Wave
should really come in handy.
[KORIN]
All right, that's enough!
[YAJIROBE groans]
[ROSHI]
Sorry, Yajirobe.
I might've put a little
too much "oomph" into that.
You geezer! That hurt!
Isn't it about time
for you to go?
Right.
So tell me, Roshi.
Why'd you want to do your last
bit of training in my tower?
[ROSHI] I suppose it's
just for old time's sake.
A way to reconnect with my
youth and all those days
I spent here learning
from you, Master Korin.
I was a sponge,
soaking up every bit
of martial arts
knowledge I could.
But then, you knew that's why
I came back, didn't you?
Oh, I did.
I just wanted to hear the words
come out of your own mouth.
Now go out there and fight
as hard as you possibly can.
And if you lose, you'll have to
come back and answer to me!
All right. I'll be off then.
[ROSHI]
Wait.
Come to think of it, I actually
don't know how to fly.
--[KORIN] Wha--?!
--[YAJIROBE] Huh?!
[ROSHI laughs]
[ROH] Hm... This Frieza
is something else.
From what we're seeing on
GodTube, he's as cold and cruel
as any villain from
across the multiverse.
He'll wipe out an entire planet
without batting an eye!
[SIDRA] Then what of
this grand proposal?
What do you think, Roh?
Would you like to
debate its merits?
Sidra, there's
no need to debate.
We will enact this
plan immediately!
And eliminate
the villain Frieza!
[SIDRA]
I'm glad we agree!
[ROH]
Indeed! Now enough back-patting.
Let's find some assassins and
get them over to the Seventh!
We'll win this tournament
before it even begins!
[GOKU laughs]
Here's the gift I promised.
So... You like it?
It's from Bulma's.
[BABA grunts]
Oh, it's a re-gift.
Well, maybe there's
a receipt in the box.
Stay here, I'll be right back.
[GOKU]
Great! Make it fast, please!
I wonder how things are going
for Krillin and
the boys on the island?
Long time no see.
Of all the people,
I didn't expect you to come.
At least try to pretend that
you're happy to see me.
I did try.
[KRILLIN]
Okay...
Ha, ha! What a nice reunion!
You look well!
[laughs nervously]
[TRUNKS]
Ha, ha! C'mon!
Let's go take a tour
around the island!
[GOTEN]
Yeah!
So, uh. Yeah.
You uh, look good.
You said that.
Ah. Right.
Ha, ha, ha! This island's great.
You have to live here
when you work, right?
You should come to our place
for dinner sometime!
Yeah, no thanks.
That's cool, dude.
You don't have to force the
small talk, Krillin. Huh?
[MARRON giggles]
Hello, Uncle!
Oh, wow. I can't believe
how big you've gotten!
Mm.
Marone?
That's Marron !
If you get it wrong again...
you're dead.
[gasps]
You got a scary Mommy.
Sorry I said it wrong, Marron.
Do you like animals?
Yeah, do you like 'em?
[A17]
Yes.
Except for the humans.
[A18] Is it going to be this
awkward the whole time?
[A17]
Prob'ly.
[KRILLIN grunts,
laughs nervously]
Hilarious, 17! You said you
like all animals but humans!
It's a joke! Sorta...
[A18] Krillin, honey,
you're forcing things again.
[KRILLIN]
I'm done.
[TRUNKS]
And... we're back!
[BOYS laugh]
This island is even
bigger than I thought!
You sure they can handle
this job while I'm gone?
Yeah. You're in good hands.
Don't forget 17, they're
the sons of Goku and Vegeta!
Hm. A fair point.
So it's not the island's health
I should worry about
while I'm gone,
but that of the poachers.
[KRILLIN] Yeah. I told the
boys if they encounter any
they're not allowed
to hit 'em too hard.
[A17]
How thoughtful of you.
[TRUNKS, GOTEN laughing]
[KRILLIN]
'Kay. We're gonna go now, boys.
You take good care of
this place while we're gone.
[TRUNKS, GOTEN]
You bet!
I'll stay to watch
the island, too!
You what?
Don't you want to go
and stay with Aunt Bulma?
Nope!
She wants to be
a guard like us!
That's right!
She'll be fine.
If you give her the space,
you'll learn Marron's a lot
tougher than you think.
Yeah, but 18...
[sighs] All right, fine.
Honey, we should only be gone
for a couple of hours.
'Kay!
[MARRON]
Come back safe!
I hope you have fun
at work, Mom and Dad!
Huh? "Have fun at work"?
[BOSS POACHER 86A laughing]
It's our big break!
That meddling ranger
is going on vacation
and trusting the island
to three useless children!
But, Boss. We just saw
them literally flying!
I think it's safe to say
they're not normal kids.
[GOHAN]
Everyone.
I know some here haven't
always been allies.
But to win this Tournament,
we'll have to fight as a team!
So let's rally,
and do this thing!
[VEGETA] Would you give up
on this teamwork garbage.
I'd rather crush the other
universes by myself!
[BULMA]
Oh, please.
I hope you've spent these years
getting stronger, Android.
I was going to say
the same thing.
[KRILLIN]
U-Uh...
[GOHAN gasping]
The truth is, I'm glad
you agreed to join our team.
We need you.
I look forward to this.
Good. And so do I.
[GOHAN] Thanks for the warm
welcome, Piccolo.
[ROSHI grunts]
[GOHAN] Master Roshi,
we've been waiting for you.
Sorry I'm a little
late getting here.
Uh? [chuckles]
You sound ready to lead, Gohan.
So now we're just waiting
on You-Know-Who.
[GOKU grunts]
[grunting]
[GOKU]
Hm?
[sighs]
Haloed like a cherub,
when it should be a crown.
My humiliation has no end.
He's all yours,
now get him outta here!
Right! Thanks, Baba--
[groans]
How rude of me.
My fist slipped
right into your chest.
[chuckles] Yeah, I hate it
when that happens.
[FRIEZA groans]
[GOKU]
Heh. Oh, sorry.
Mine just slipped, too.
[GOKU laughs]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Enough! Get going!
[GOKU] She's right--
the clock's ticking.
All right, Frieza.
Here, take my hand.
[FRIEZA]
Hm?
[GOKU] Instant Transmission.
You've seen it before, right?
Oh...
[GOKU] And no more
"fists slipping," okay?
[FRIEZA]
Very well.
Though sometimes my tail
has a mind of its own.
Can you please stop bantering
long enough to leave?
[GHOST USHER]
'Scuse me.
Sorry to interrupt,
but there are some gentlemen
gathered outside
who wish to meet you.
Uh, do you know who they are?
Uh. No idea.
But they all look like
they're in a bad mood.
And by "all," I mean
"several hundred"!
Who are you
and what do you want?
Hmph. We can't say.
I'm guessing you're here
to stop me and Frieza
from entering the Tournament.
Can't say.
Who ordered you to come here?
We can't say--
[FRIEZA]
Whoopsie!
Sorry about that.
Hand slipped again.
Crossing worlds
must make me clumsy.
I must say, as impromptu
as my return is,
the high turn-out for my
"welcome home" reception
is quite impressive. [chuckles]
[BEERUS grumbles]
Where is he?!
Doesn't that idiot know
we're on the clock?!
So, uh.
What happens if we're late
getting to the tournament?
[WHIS]
Hm... We might be disqualified.
Which means we'd know the
humiliation of destruction
before the tournament
even starts!
[KRILLIN gasping]
You better get here fast Goku!
Sorry, but we don't have time
to stay and fight them.
Let's go!
Oh, Goku.
I can't believe you want to run.
Look, I love to stay and fight,
but we simply don't
have the time!
In that case...
This won't be about sport
but rather destroying them
as quickly as possible.
[FRIEZA] All that time
in Hell made my body soft.
You don't want me going
into the tournament rusty
and out of practice, do you?
Come join me.
If the two of us must be
combatants together
then let's at least warm-up!
[GHOST USHER whimpers]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Gentlemen.
We don't have as much time for
this fight as I would prefer.
So I must forgo
the niceties of battle.
Don't hold this breach
of etiquette against me.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Boogie Back!
Wish we had better timing
To explore this attraction
Put on a smile, it's showtime
And I'm just playing a part
Let's get lost in the rhythm,
dancing dancing heart
Head over heels
I'm falling falling down
(Boogie Back!)
My heartbeat
keeps growing faster
Every step that I take
brings me back to you
(Boogie Back!)
Give me happy ever after
Let the dream
of our love come true
Boogie Back!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Assassins are
after me and Frieza!
Where are they from?
Who sent them?
[FRIEZA laughs]
I don't care who they work for!
All I ask is that you join me
in disposing of this threat!
It's been too long since
I've stretched my legs.
Allow me to savor this
return to glorious combat!
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super,
"Most Heinous! Most Evil!
Frieza's Wild Rampage!"
Make sure you
don't miss it, okay?