♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Here we go, everyone!
We'll defeat Zamasu!
[NARRATOR] After a hard-fought
battle pushed the Saiyans
to the very brink, Trunks
harnessed the life energy
of every mortal
in his future world,
and finally overwhelmed Zamasu.
It's not about
gods and mortals!
You don't believe
in anything but yourself,
and we won't let you win!
[ZAMASU screams]
I don't give a damn about you
or your so-called justice!
But how? It can't be!
[screams]
[NARRATOR] The long,
desperate struggle against
a rogue god concludes. Now!
[NARRATOR]
"With New Hope in His Heart--
Farewell, Trunks."
[FUTURE TRUNKS panting]
[ZAMASU] A righteous god,
defeated by a mortal.
It's sacrilege! It cannot be!
[ZAMASU laughing intensely]
[screaming]
[exhales]
Nice work.
[chuckles]
You got him.
Yeah.
We all did.
Thanks, everyone.
[GOKU]
Hm?
--[FUTURE MAI] Trunks!
--[FUTURE TRUNKS] Mai!
You really won?
It's really over?
Yeah.
[sniffing]
[crying]
[BULMA]
That was amazing, kiddo.
I wish this world's me
were here.
She would've been proud of you.
Thanks.
I gotta say, I've never
seen a Spirit Bomb
in a sword before.
It was the power we needed.
All of us, together.
Standing, and fighting, as one.
--[BOTH gasp]
--What's that?
[GOKU gasps]
[GOWASU gasps]
No. That darkness! It's him!
Are you sure?
[ZAMASU CHORUS laughing]
[ALL gasp]
Zamasu!
[GOKU]
This guy never quits!
[grunts]
What?
[VEGETA]
Don't lose focus, Kakarot!
[yells]
It's from launching that
Kamehama-Ha from earlier.
They don't have
enough power left
to go Super Saiyan,
let alone Blue.
Well, I'm not done yet.
[yells]
We have to do something;
let's go.
[FUTURE MAI gasps]
Here goes!
Kamehame...
Ha!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Galick Gun!
Final Flash!
[ZAMASU CHORUS laughing]
That didn't even affect him!
Bastard freak!
[FUTURE TRUNKS grunting]
What's happening?
He was cut down.
But thanks to the dragon's
power, his being remains.
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[GOWASU] It seems he's embraced
this new, ethereal state.
No longer confined
by his divine vessel,
he may be trying
to become part of
the very fabric of the cosmos.
His own twisted idea of justice
and order made manifest.
[ZAMASU CHORUS laughing]
That's insane!
[gasps]
[ALL yelling]
[ALL groaning]
[ZAMASU CHORUS laughing]
What is that thing?
I'm scared!
It's not like the time
Goku Black came through
that portal, is it?
Yup. That's definitely
a monster comin' to eat us.
[ALL THREE shriek]
[WHIS]
Hmmm. That's troubling.
It's faint but I'm picking up
the most unpleasant vibe,
my lord.
It's making my skin crawl.
[BEERUS] It's Zamasu. Something
momentous is happening
in that sword-swinger's future.
It's rippling across
the timelines,
even affecting us here.
[GOKU groaning]
He really is rotten.
[VEGETA]
That's an understatement.
[FUTURE TRUNKS groans]
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
What's going on?
[ZAMASU CHORUS
continues laughing]
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
You guys all right?
I think so.
What is this?
It looks like
some kind-a nightmare.
[BOTH groan, gasp]
[ZAMASU CHORUS
continues laughing]
--[FUTURE TRUNKS gasps]
--What is it now?
[FUTURE TRUNKS] I'm not
sensing anyone else out there.
The life energy
from all those survivors
I felt flowing through me when
I sliced through Zamasu...
--It's all gone.
--[FUTURE MAI gasps]
What's that mean?
Do you think they're dead?
He killed them all?
[ZAMASU CHORUS
continues laughing]
[FUTURE MAI]
It can't be.
It can't be! No! No! No!
What have you done to them?
You son of a bitch!
They were innocent people
just trying to hang on!
After all that,
they can't be dead!
Mai!
[FUTURE MAI sniffing]
[sobbing]
What a blackened soul.
[SUPREME KAI]
How are we supposed to
fight against him now?
[GOKU] If I had one more senzu
bean I could at least try.
Yeah, well, we don't!
We won't get anywhere
with "ifs"!
Hey, wait!
[gasps]
Sorry, never mind--
I thought I found one.
Hm! Supreme Kai, tell me.
Do you think the Zeno of this
timeline is still around?
What? Uh, the Omni-King? Well...
Yes, there's no question,
of course he would be.
No one can defeat Grand Zeno;
it's impossible!
Oh, really. You don't say.
What's your plan? Spit it out!
[GOKU chuckles]
Now we just have to see
if this thing will work
in this universe.
[GOKU]
Woo-hoo! Zeno, you're here!
I wasn't sure it would work!
Aw, what a relief!
Uh, what?
[SUPREME KAI]
Grand Zeno!
[SUPREME KAI, GOWASU]
We are humbled, sire!
Can someone explain?
That's Grand Zeno.
The supreme ruler
of this whole Multiverse.
[FUTURE MAI, FUTURE TRUNKS]
Ah!
Who are you? That's odd.
Did you summon me?
Yup. I sure did. I'm Goku!
[FUTURE ZENO]
Mmmm... Mm...
[ZAMASU CHORUS laughing]
Ew. What's this?
There's nothing here, you see.
That's very bad.
Did you do this?
[GOKU]
Hm? No, no, wasn't me.
That guy up there did it.
[ZENO]
Huh.
[ZAMASU CHORUS
growling, laughing]
He is very nasty.
Yup!
So, what's he going to do?
I would not even
deign to guess.
Something this nasty
should be cleaned up, right?
[FUTURE ZENO]
Yes, it should.
I'll destroy it.
[GOKU]
Nnnnh!
Hurry! Get in the time machine
before its too late!
Supreme Kais, you should
get out of here, too!
--Gowasu?
--Yes. Right.
Guys, what're you waiting for?
Launch it now!
I have no idea
how long we've got!
[BULMA grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
[VEGETA grunts]
All of existence, go away!
--[ZAMASU CHORUS screams]
--[ALL gasp]
[ZAMASU CHORUS screaming]
[ALL gasp]
[ALL]
They made it through!
Nngh! Ow! I am
really tired of that!
--[TRUNKS] Dad!
--[GOTEN] You're here!
--Did you win?
--[GOKU screams]
Oh, I'm sorry, Dad.
Did they hurt you again, Goku?
--[TRUNKS] Mom!
--[BULMA giggles]
[TRUNKS]
I was worried about you!
Yeah, me too!
[MAI]
Trunks!
I didn't think
I'd see you again!
This is so great!
[FUTURE MAI]
Huh?
[FUTURE MAI, MAI]
Are you me?
Holy smokes, two different
Mais? What now?
Our group balance
is completely shot, sire!
--[FUTURE MAI] Uh.
--[TRUNKS] Eeh!
Up!
[FUTURE TRUNKS] Goku.
What happened to our timeline?
Whoa, Lord Beerus!
Looks like you got roughed up
pretty good, Saiyan.
Yeah, you know.
[chuckles]
Thank goodness. I feared
you wouldn't get away.
--[BEERUS] Hmm?
--[GOWASU] Lord Beerus.
I'm sorry for causing you
all this trouble.
Next time I'd suggest you choose
your apprentice more
carefully, Kai.
Yes.
Bulma, get the time machine
ready to go again.
Already? Where are you going?
I'll take the helm
this time, Goku.
Mom's earned herself
some downtime.
Ah, thanks, Trunks!
That works for me!
Same coordinates.
You see anything?
[GOKU]
Hmm.
There! Look!
Yo, Zeno!
[FUTURE ZENO]
Hm?
I'm gonna take you somewhere
super fun, okay?
--[FUTURE ZENO] Really?
--You betchya! He-heh!
[MAI]
They're already back!
[PILAF] You realize
it's time travel, right?
[BEERUS] Huuuuh?!
You brought Grand Zeno?
Great Omni-King!
You grace us with
your presence as always!
I hope this day
finds you well, sire.
[GOKU laughs]
You busy, Supreme Kai?
We need a ride.
Uh?
[FUTURE ZENO giggles]
[GOKU chuckles]
Goku!
[giggles]
[BOTH]
Huuuh?
[BOTH ZENOS] Hey Goku,
he looks just like me!
Look, Zenny. Like I promised!
I brought you a new friend
even funner than me!
[chuckles]
Another you!
[laughing]
[BOTH ZENOS]
Uuuh...
--Hi!
--Hello!
[BOTH ZENOS]
You seem fun!
Clever. Was this
your idea, Whis?
Not at all.
This was Goku's brainchild.
Mm. I must admit, I'm envious
of your Universe Seven.
Well, you're more than welcome
to pay us a visit sometime,
my dear father.
Yes. Perhaps I shall.
[ZENOS laughing]
[GOKU chuckles]
[WHIS]
I've been thinking, Trunks,
and I do believe
it's possible to return you
to your timeline
before the obliteration,
and make,
shall we say... corrections.
Seriously?
Absolutely not, Whis,
you stay out of this!
You know as well as I do--
That would create
another Time Ring!
These Earthlings have
caused enough messes.
How would you
explain that to Zeno?
That is an interesting position
for you to take, my lord.
Considering that when
you chose to destroy Zamasu,
you produced an alternate
reality and Time Ring yourself.
[BEERUS]
Eh! Wait, I did what?
You mean you didn't know?
Zamasu's Time Ring travels
had made a rare "causal loop,"
and when you destroyed him
you broke that loop,
necessitating yet another
temporal divergence:
One where he was destroyed.
And one where he was not.
After all your scolding of the
Earthlings for splitting time,
you went and did it, too.
What? No I--!
Uh... okay, maybe I did.
Wait a minute! If you're
planning to take Trunks and Mai
back to their future
before Zeno destroys it,
doesn't that mean Zamasu
will still be there
waiting to attack?
Yeah, Mom's right!
And then the whole thing
will just repeat itself!
[WHIS]
You needn't worry about that.
I'll speak to the Lord Beerus
in your timeline.
Before he vanishes as a result
of your Supreme Kai's death
and explain the situation.
I will ask him to eliminate
your Zamasu and
I'm certain he will oblige.
I don't know, Whis.
It could work,
but we're not sure when
he made himself invincible.
What if that's already happened?
That's right,
and even if Lord Beerus
can vaporize his body like
Trunks did with that sword,
he'll turn into that ether
and they're still screwed!
[WHIS laughs]
I have something even better
than your Containment Wave
and that adorable
little jar with the seal.
[GOKU gasps]
And you're just telling
all of us now?
[BEERUS]
Don't be pathetic!
You Saiyans are
getting hooked on divine help.
Come on, please.
[WHIS] But there's
one problem I can't solve.
Naturally,
if I take Trunks and Mai
to an earlier point
in their timeline,
they will already be there.
Two versions of each of you,
forced to coexist.
Can you do that?
You mean...
[FUTURE MAI]
It's fine with me.
[ALL gasp]
You sure?
If that's the price
to enter a world where
everyone we fought with
is alive,
well then, if you ask me
that's a pretty good bargain.
[gasps]
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
You're right. Of course you are.
Aw. A quiet gaze as they
face their future together.
Dreamy!
[TRUNKS]
Hm?
[MAI]
Mmm.
Uuuh!
[BEERUS]
Time to go, Whis.
[WHIS]
As you wish, my lord.
--Hey, future boy.
--Yes?
[BEERUS] Since Whis likes you,
I'll absolve you, this time.
Now have a good life.
[GOWASU] It was my sin, too,
that forged this ring.
I failed you, Zamasu.
We both did.
Hey, are you leaving already?
Yeah. Take care.
Love the new coat, kid.
That color looks great on you.
Oh, thank you.
Be proud.
You've taken huge leaps
in a short time, Trunks.
It doesn't matter what enemy
comes at you down the line,
you'll always find a way.
Thanks, Goku,
I hope you're right.
[BULMA]
Here. Take these with you.
Lots of food and other goodies
to get you started.
Call it a housewarming gift.
Still taking care of me.
[BULMA]
Just hang in there,
and find what makes
you happy, okay?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Mom, come on.
[BULMA] You know what?
I like this future son thing.
Means way less time
until grandkids!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Mom!
Please, tell the future me
she's done great work!
[BOTH]
Right.
You showed up.
[yells]
[TRUNKS]
Bye, big me! Keep training!
And I'll get stronger too, okay!
[sobbing]
I think her heart
just broke in two, sire.
Hey, no need to cry.
You're just trading in the
old Trunks for a newer model!
Don't ruin this for me!
[FUTURE MAI chuckles]
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Piccolo.
And Gohan, too.
[panting]
[gasps]
I failed, Gohan.
I failed you.
I couldn't save them.
[GOHAN]
You've got this, Trunks!
Never doubt that,
you hear me?
Right!
You ready now, softy?
[FUTURE TRUNKS sniffs]
Let's go.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Thanks so much, everyone.
For everything.
Hope was the right choice,
and it always will be.
♪ Closing Song ♪
1, 2, 3, I'm hungry
Nothin' but fried rice fantasies
I got a passion for the dish
Nothin' compares to what it is
I don't get my fill
I'm like a monster
Those ingredients
No one could possibly resist
They got me so bewitched
Make it spicy and I can't say no
Seasoning is everything,
I think so
Bon Appetit
I'll burn the world
straight to the ground
If I can't have
that greasy mound
My hanger's not to be ignored!
1, 2, 3, I'm hungry
Nothin' but fried rice fantasies
I want fried rice,
I'm so hungryyyyyy-yeah!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And I'm thinking
it's time I finally
get rid of King Kai's halo,
so I'm collecting Dragon Balls
like the old days,
and summoning
the Eternal Shenron!
But what's this? Everybody
else is showing up too,
with wishes they want
to make instead!
Come on guys, if I don't
fix up King Kai now,
he's gonna be furious,
and I don't what he'll do!
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Come Forth, Shenron!
Whose Wish Will Be Granted?"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?