♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[rumbling]
[MAN panting]
[NARRATOR]
"SOS From the Future!
A Dark New Enemy Appears!!"
[thunder rumbles]
[MAN panting]
Hm!
[bubbling]
[beeping]
[keyboard clicking]
[MAN]
Mom!
Oh! What a surprise!
Great to see you.
You're looking well, kiddo.
I guess.
And you're looking
as beautiful as always.
Uh--
That should be enough
to make a one-way trip.
[FUTURE TRUNKS] That's it?
After a whole year of work?
Come on, let's stay positive.
We just have to get you there.
It's the best we can do.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
But only one-way?
I can't just leave you here!
There is a way to get back,
but it's a gamble.
You just have to trust me, okay?
Right. Hey. You've been
working yourself to the bone
this whole time, haven't you?
Why don't you
take a little break?
Don't worry about me,
I'll be fine.
We don't have a second to waste.
[FUTURE BULMA] We've got
to get this to Capsule Corp.
as soon as we can.
I'm not taking any chances.
I can take it from here.
You should stay behind and
get some rest, Mom; seriously.
When's the last time
you got real sleep?
Nice try, but I'm
coming with you.
What if something happens
on the way there?
If he attacks,
we can't run the risk
of you being on your own.
Two of us going
means two chances
to keep this safe.
If it gets destroyed,
this entire year will have
been a waste of time.
You've made your point.
[chuckles]
[FUTURE BULMA] I need to make
sure you understand this, son.
We can't forget how many
people gave their lives
to make sure we had the chance
to create this energy.
We have to honor that debt.
That means seeing this through,
no matter what happens.
Even if we have to sacrifice
everything to succeed.
You're the last hope we've got,
son. It's all up to you.
I know.
Good. Then we should get moving.
Mai is waiting for us.
[FUTURE TRUNKS grunts]
--[FUTURE BULMA gasps]
--[FUTURE TRUNKS] Get down!
[gasps]
Your laboratory!
[FUTURE BULMA gasps]
Get out of here!
Do you hear me?
Where did she go? Aaah!
Get off her!
[FUTURE BULMA]
Trunks, don't!
Be strong! You have to go!
You have to!
[FUTURE TRUNKS gasping]
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Mom. I swear, I'll make it back.
I'll save this world,
no matter what!
[birds chirping]
Wow. It looks like
I can farm after all!
Great work, Dad.
This is amazing!
I agree! I told you you could
do it if you tried, dear.
I guess so. I know I was
trying to get out of it
for a while, but I wanted
you guys to have good food
so I decided to give it my all!
[PICCOLO]
Great. Now why did you call me?
So we could train
together, why else?
And what sort of training
did you have in mind, exactly?
[GOKU] We're gonna harvest all
this in one day! Fun, right?
[PICCOLO] That's not training,
Goku! That's just work!
What? It totally counts!
Back when Krillin and I
trained with Master Roshi,
we did stuff like this
all the time with him.
He had us deliver milk for him,
to all kinds of far-off places.
We plowed fields with our hands,
and other chores, too.
That's how we got strong!
It was all just
training in disguise!
Ha! Or a way to get free labor.
I don't care what you call it!
Without your help
it won't get done!
Trust me, we'll make it fun!
Goten. You can train, too.
We'll see which one of us
can pick the most!
--Now wait.
--Yeah! Let's do it!
I'm gonna win!
Not so fast, Goten--
you have to study!
Why?
What do you mean "why," mister?
You have to study
so you can learn
and get a real job
like your brother!
[GOTEN]
Come on, Mom. Please?
You have a test
next week, remember?
[GOTEN]
Mmm.
[chuckles]
Well, I guess
it's just you and me!
Hold on! I never
agreed to anything;
you can't just assume tha--
Ready...!
[GOTEN, CHICHI]
Go!
[PICCOLO] Damn it!
How did I get roped into this?
[BOTH grunting]
[PICCOLO] Though I have
to admit, it is effective.
My legs, back,
shoulders, and arms--
they're all getting
a good workout.
Not bad, Piccolo. Looks like
it's gonna be a close contest.
Yeah and it seems the old hermit
might've been onto
something after all.
[GOKU chuckles]
That's for sure!
Wow! They're so fast!
Hey! That's enough stalling!
I told you to study!
[KRILLIN]
Well, that's one way to train.
What's up, Krillin?
Oh, I just came by
to say hi. Harvest, huh?
I'm surprised Goku
is cool with all of this.
With what?
Well, I dropped by Bulma's
place earlier this morning.
And she said Vegeta had gone
to Lord Beerus' world again.
[GOKU]
Huh?
As crazy-competitive
as those Saiyans are,
I figured Goku would want
to be training there, too.
[GOKU]
Mmmm...
[VEGETA grunting]
Are you feeling well?
If you keep
performing like that,
you're going to go another full
day without striking me once.
[VEGETA grunts]
[yells]
Yeah, I got him!
[PICCOLO]
Huh?
I spoke too soon.
[CHICHI] You shouldn't
have spoken at all!
Now get in there
and take his place!
Eeh!
Piccolo didn't want
to do it either, but look,
he's having fun!
Uuuuh...
[bellows]
[GOKU]
Ooow!
[groans]
[VEGETA]
Kakarot?
You're not playing fair, Vegeta!
You keep running off and
training here without me!
Please! It's not my fault
you can't keep up!
[BEERUS]
Mm?
Oh! Hey, Lord Beerus.
What's up?!
I hope you didn't
come here empty-handed.
Uuuh... Here!
That better be edible.
It's called lettuce!
And it's from my own field.
I just picked it fresh
a minute ago!
Huh?
I believe that's what they call
"farm to table," my lord.
You really can't get
any fresher than that.
Ah! What an elegantly
subtle sweetness! Uh--
Though. As an offering
from a mortal
visiting the great Destroyer
of his universe,
I'd say it falls
a good deal short.
[GOKU chuckles]
[FUTURE TRUNKS panting]
[footsteps]
[knocking]
[FUTURE MAI]
Looking for me?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Mai!
[FUTURE MAI]
Welcome back.
[gasps]
But where's Bulma?
Mom's gone. She bought me time.
[FUTURE MAI]
Oh, no.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
That bastard Black.
He must know my energy now.
He can track me.
I led him right to her,
and now she's gone
and her equipment is gone, too.
But at least there's this.
[FUTURE TRUNKS] This is the
energy Mom gave her life for.
This means we can
go back... to the past.
[WHIS sighs]
All righty. It's almost done.
Three more seconds,
and... there!
Five minutes of torture
have passed!
We can now enjoy
our sweet reward!
[ALL]
Aah! Thanks for the grub!
[BEERUS sniffs]
Oh, that smells good.
I don't believe
I've had this type before!
So, what do you think,
Lord Beerus?
I love it;
the richness is divine!
And just what flavor
did you say this was again?
Miso and butter, my lord.
You could at least
have brought some more
ramen with you, Kakarot.
Sorry, it was
spur-of-the-moment,
--but there's plenty of lettuce!
--Idiot.
[GOKU]
Fine, if you don't want it,
I'll just give it to that
Zeno dude next time I see him.
All you did was say his name.
Yeah, you're really jumpy
about that guy, Lord Beerus.
You get the face-sweats
and everything.
[BEERUS growls]
Something would be wrong
if he didn't fear Grand Zeno.
The Omni-King is the most
supreme of all deities,
ruling over
our entire multiverse.
In the hierarchy of the gods,
there is no one above him.
Does that mean he's
the strongest fighter
out of anyone anywhere?
You know, you Saiyans
have a terrible habit
of judging a being's power by
his physical capabilities alone.
Grand Zeno
is not a fighter, Goku.
But without a doubt
he is the mightiest.
You simply couldn't
fathom his power.
What does that mean?
Are you telling me
that you've already
forgotten about
my lord's warning?
Grand Zeno can annihilate
anything he wishes
in the blink of an eye,
regardless of scale
or complexity.
Be it a single life form.
Or a world. Or a galaxy.
Or an entire universe.
If it ever struck his fancy,
he could eliminate everything.
All of reality as we know it.
--[GOKU] Whaaa...!
--[VEGETA] What?
Has he ever done that?
I mean, instantly destroy
an entire universe?
Oh, yes. The fact is
we used to have
18 universes
instead of only 12.
That's completely insane!
So he just wiped out
the other six?
It doesn't take much
to provoke him, either.
Any perceived insult
and next thing you know...
Pow! Bye, bye!
Hopefully now your tiny
little brain can understand
why we were so nervous when
you were talking to him, Goku.
[VEGETA] That settles it.
You are an idiot.
Wow, that is nuts.
But I still think you guys
are worrying way too much.
If he destroyed us,
how could he have
the tournament
he's so pumped up about?
Your ignorance
is almost enough
to make me lose my appetite.
By the way,
what is this thing?
A fish cake.
Oh my, what a
fascinating flavor!
Ah, man, I just hope we don't
have to wait much longer!
[chuckles]
The strongest fighters
from all twelve universes
meeting in the ring?
Can you imagine?
It could be giants,
or super-blobs,
or dinosaur people, or anything!
And techniques
I never dreamed of!
Just thinking
of the possibilities
gets me totally amped!
--[BEERUS slurps]
--[VEGETA] Hm!
[FUTURE MAI]
Want to get some rest?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Mn-mmm.
What's in there?
Look, it's something
I've been saving for us.
For when we really needed it.
Isn't it amazing?
It's not even dog food.
[meows]
Don't worry, you stinker.
I've got a little
something for you, too.
[FUTURE MAI]
Dig in.
Oh, wait. Is he gonna be okay
when we're both gone?
Oh, yeah; he'll be fine.
Cats are totally self-reliant.
I've heard they'll forget their
masters' faces after three days.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Well, I'll remember you.
That's okay, Trunks.
You can eat it all.
I saved it for you.
Oh, come on.
I know you're hungry.
[FUTURE MAI'S stomach growls]
[FUTURE MAI] So how many
trips will that give us?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Only one.
[FUTURE MAI]
What? So... we can't come back?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Right now, all that matters
is surviving long enough
to get there.
But that's not absolute.
My mom did tell me
there should be a way
to get back if we're lucky.
And what way is that?
I don't know. Least not yet.
But we will. Mom said
to trust her, and I do.
So first, we have to
get to Metro West.
And then it's a
17 year jump from there?
Yeah.
I know I have friends
back in that timeline.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
They can help me stop Black.
[meows]
[BOTH]
Hm!
[thunder rumbles]
What do you think?
Can you sense Black's energy?
No, nothing. Let's move.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Go! Now!
[FUTURE MAI gasps]
[FUTURE TRUNKS bellows]
[FUTURE TRUNKS groans]
[FUTURE MAI]
Trunks!
What are you doing?
I told you to go!
Stop trying
to save me and think!
I have to stay here, not you!
You're the best chance
that we've got.
You have to survive!
Mai! Wait!
Aah!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Mai!
♪
[grunting]
You killed her!
[GOKU BLACK]
It's about time, Saiyan.
You've been running around
making messes for too long
and now I'm going
to choke the life from you.
I can't wait to watch you die.
♪ Closing Song ♪
Wow
It's hard to say
Don't wanna stay
I twist and fight,
can't find my way
I must believe, that fear
and trouble can even be fun
if you think the right way
Wow
I don't wanna draw the line
I gotta see it through some way
Fight for what I know is mine
The dream I had of me that day
Wow
Don't care if they
call me greedy
If they hate me, make me blue
Don't care if they laugh at me
'Cause I will make
the dream come true
Wow
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And what in the universe
is going on?
Future Trunks is under attack
from a guy named Black,
who looks exactly
like me! But how?
I mean if I had an evil twin,
I figured I'd know!
Trunks is coming back to
see us in his time machine,
and he's in pretty bad shape.
I'll just cross my fingers
he can give us some answers!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Hope!! Redux.
Awaken in the Present, Trunks!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?