♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super.
Piccolo and his teammates
struggled mightily against a foe
who concealed his position
and attacked from long-range.
[TIEN COPIES]
Let's go!
[NARRATOR] Tien stepped
boldly into the fray
with his Multi-Form Technique.
[TIEN COPY screams]
There goes my last copy.
All right. Let's see if
they got me close enough.
[HARMIRA growling]
There! Neo Tri-Beam!
Ha!
[HARMIRA grunting]
[panting]
You fought capably to
the end. I commend you.
[NARRATOR] It appeared
Harmira was on his way out,
but he wasn't finished yet--
and forced Tien
into a sacrifice move.
Where'd you come from?
I won't be leaving
this ring alone.
[HARMIRA]
It's not fair!
Well, I say all we can
do is keep fighting.
After all, now we're fighting
for Krillin and Tien.
[NARRATOR] With cosmic
survival on the line,
the Seventh Universe's team
is down to eight... now!
[NARRATOR] "Revenge 'F'!
A Cunning Trap is Set?"
[CHAMPA]
So if the Sixth Universe wins,
you want all your crimes
to be pardoned?
Ah... You have no right to
be asking for such a prize,
especially considering
how badly you embarrassed me
during our contest
with the Seventh!
[FROST]
You are absolutely correct.
Glad you agree.
Now go do some stretches!
And if you're caught cheating
again, you'll answer to me!
[FROST]
What if I can accomplish more?
If I can throw that despicable
Seventh's team off balance,
humiliate them, and
steer them toward defeat--
would you pardon me then?
[CHAMPA] Hm... Your own
brand of vengeance, huh?
And how exactly do you
plan to do this?
I believe at last
the moment is right.
I will prove myself most
useful to the Sixth.
For the sake of
my own endeavors.
[FROST chuckles]
[FUTURE ZENO]
Wow, so many are gone!
[ZENO]
Yes! So, so many!
How many do you think
are not gone yet?
[FUTURE ZENO]
Hm... Uh...
[BOTH]
How many fighters are left?
Currently there are a
total of 36 contestants
remaining, Your Majesties.
Thirty-six?!
Oh my!
It is a lot to keep track of.
Perhaps you would like me to
break it down by universe?
Oh yes, tell me!
I would like to hear it, too!
Of course, sires.
I'll start with Universe Two.
[GRAND MINISTER]
At this moment,
they have six contestants
remaining in the ring.
While there are seven survivors
from Universe Three.
I would like to study
our enemies a little more
while we have the benefit
of a wider field.
In particular, that Jiren
from the Eleventh.
His abilities are far too
unknown for comfort.
I believe it's time to have
our gifted Maji-kayo jump
into the action, and use his
unique body to find out more.
[MOSCO beeping]
[GRAND MINISTER]
Moving on.
The Fourth Universe has
four fighters remaining.
[BEERUS]
Hm?
[GRAND MINISTER]
With eight remaining fighters,
the Sixth Universe is
currently tied for the lead.
Sharing that honor
with Universe Seven.
[ZENO, FUTURE ZENO]
Goku's team is doing well!
Our defensive battle formation
may not have lasted for long,
but they've still employed
enough teamwork
to be tied for first place.
I'm starting to see
a path to victory!
We could actually win this!
Uh. Lord Beerus?
[BEERUS] Did you hear the count
for the Fourth Universe?
What? Yes.
The Grand Minister said
they had four fighters
remaining in the ring.
I count six on their bench,
which does add up to ten.
What's your point?
[gasps] Ever since
the Tournament started
we've only spotted
eight of 'em, right?
No one's seen the last two.
Indeed. I sensed them--
the faint energy of
two more fighters.
But we have no idea
what they're actually like.
[WHIS] That certainly
could be a problem.
I have heard it said that
the Fourth Universe is home
to many warriors with
most unusual abilities.
At a critical moment
they may very well try
to spring something on us.
[SUPREME KAI whimpers]
Blast it! Where are
the other two fighters?
This is just like that
devious Quitela--
always plotting something!
[QUITELA chuckles]
[GRAND MINISTER]
Last of the competing universes
still in contention,
we have the Eleventh,
with three remaining fighters.
By the numbers, the Sixth
and Seventh with their
eight fighters would seem
to have an advantage.
But one never knows,
Your Majesties.
[BOTH]
Oh, wow!
I can't say I
enjoyed that tally.
Numerically speaking, we're
in the worst position, my lord.
Our universe has the three
strongest fighters in
the Tournament, led by Jiren
who's in a class all his own.
Being outnumbered
doesn't matter.
It's quality that's key.
And Jiren and Top have taken
virtually no damage yet.
We are the ones with
the true advantage here.
[MAJI-KAYO chuckles]
[DYSPO]
Hm?
What's wrong, Dyspo?
Not sure. I just
heard something.
[MAJI-KAYO]
Ha!
[TOP]
Huh?!
[MAJI-KAYO]
You're mine!
[DYSPO]
Think again!
[MAJI-KAYO groaning]
[DYSPO]
Justice... Crush! Ha!
[screams]
That's what he gets
for his cowardly ambush!
That is justice!
[MAJI-KAYO gasping]
No, please have mercy!
His body is unusual, Dyspo.
Be sure to stay on your toes.
Yeah, I got it.
I'll knock him out before
he tries somethin'!
Justice Kick!
[groans]
[DYSPO chuckles]
Gotcha!
[DYSPO groaning]
What the--?
[DYSPO gasping]
[DYSPO]
You're a-a monster!
Yes I am.
[laughing] And that's
our Maji-kayo for ya!
His freakish body
always prevails!
[MOSCO beeping]
Dyspo tore him into pieces,
and yet he regenerated
in no time!
And now his body is 100% healed.
You're a fraud! You pretended
to be helpless!
[MAJI-KAYO laughs]
Those ears are huge, Dyspo--
like parachutes on your head.
I bet if I snip them off you'll
be able to run even faster!
I don't know what's more
twisted, your body or your mind!
Dyspo's clearly having
trouble with that one.
[JIREN]
Step aside.
I'll handle it.
[laughing]
Uh?
At last, the big boss steps in!
Let's go!
[DYSPO]
Don't take your eyes off me!
What in the...?
I'm sorry, Jiren. I'm out!
Good. You're the one
I came for anyway.
Let's have some fun!
Show me what you've got!
Excellent, Maji-kayo!
Unveil the mystery
of Jiren's power!
[MAJI-KAYO grunting, yells]
[MAJI-KAYO screams]
Ahh! All that, from
a mere shockwave?!
[gasping]
As we said.
Numbers will not be an issue.
[sighs] Aw, for real?
That's what I was going to say!
How am I supposed to
conduct my research
if you get tossed out
from a single attack?
[ZENO]
Boop! Heh.
One more is gone!
That means there are 35!
Fuwa. What to do, what to do?
Calm down! Man up, already!
[FUWA] But that Jiren
fellow is so strong!
How are we going to stop him?
Whoever has the most fighters
in the ring when time
runs out wins, so we should
focus on weakening the Seventh,
not worry about one guy
on a losing team!
--[VADOS] Lord Champa?
--Eh?
Pay attention, sir.
Our man is making his move.
[ROSHI sighs] That's what
stinks about being old.
I just don't have the stamina.
[FROST] Yes, you do look
dreadfully weary.
[FROST chuckles]
Are you looking for someone?
[ROSHI gasping]
[GOKU gasping]
Master Roshi!
Hold on!
[BRIANNE]
I'm back, foe from the Seventh!
Time to settle the score!
Outta my way!
[ROSHI groaning]
You're barely resisting
at all, old man.
Where is the fun in that?
[ROSHI]
I know what you're doing.
You start by
picking off the weak,
then you'll try to snake your
way up to the strongest
on our team, with
some ambush or trick.
You're as sneaky and as
spineless as ever-- Ah!
What is it about the feeble
elderly that makes them
rattle on so incessantly?
I'll toss you from the ring
just to stop the chatter!
[ROSHI grunting]
[ROSHI groans]
[chuckles] What a shame!
[ROSHI yelps]
This pesky rule about not
killing our foes. It's hard
to hold back my strength against
such delicate flowers.
[FROST chuckles]
[gasps] What's this?
Evil Containment!
[screaming]
What's this... attack?!
He's trying that again?
[FROST screaming]
[ROSHI grunting]
[yells]
[FROST]
Let go of me!
No!
[yells]
[FROST]
Stop!
[panting]
[ROSHI gasps]
[FROST panting]
[BOTH gasp]
No! He missed it!
Aw, damn it!
So...
All this time the old geezer
had this trick up his sleeve.
How naughty.
[FROST]
Hold on.
[FROST chuckles]
[ROSHI groans]
[FROST]
I admit you almost got me.
But who would've guessed
you still posed such a threat?
[FROST chuckles]
[ROSHI grunts]
[VEGETA growls]
[laughs]
[ROSHI panting]
[FROST laughs] A technique for
sealing away problematic foes.
That could prove rather useful.
Have one of those
senzus on standby.
That old man has
reached his limit.
Once he's knocked out, be sure
to feed him one before he dies.
[FROST laughing]
Now then, it's time to make
your defeat official.
[FROST] Fair warning, this
ejection is going to sting.
Just please be sure not to die.
[ROSHI grunts]
[VEGETA growls]
[FROST screams]
Vegeta... Why'd you--?
Don't get the wrong idea.
I came to crush that repulsive
bastard, not to save you.
[ROSHI]
Hm?
[sighs]
It's been far too long, Vegeta.
[VEGETA] Hmph! And too long
into this tournament for you
to still be in the ring.
[FROST] I'm not the same
as when we fought last.
It would behoove you
to realize that.
[VEGETA laughs]
Please.
Even if you've gotten stronger,
you're still no match for me.
[FROST] Oh no, you've
misunderstood completely.
I mean I've gotten weaker.
[VEGETA]
Hm?
[FROST]
As a result of my misdeeds
in the Sixth Universe being
revealed, I've become a fugitive
criminal, and all that running
has sapped my vigor. [laughs]
I mean, just look at me.
After that opening
salvo of yours,
I can barely stand on my feet.
One more of your mighty punches
before I've recovered
could kill me.
[VEGETA]
Stop trying to buy time, coward.
[FROST]
Mm? [chuckles]
Was it that obvious?
I guess there's no fooling you.
Never underestimate
the wits of a Saiyan.
[VEGETA grunts]
I confess,
ever since our first tournament
when you shamed me in battle,
I've been thinking about
something obsessively.
What would be the best
way to defeat you?
[MAGETTA]
Toot, toot!
[VEGETA gasps]
[MAGETTA]
Bang!
You're really back for more?!
Gimme a break!
[MAGETTA]
Clickety-clang! Thunk!
Thunk, thunk, thunk, thunk,
thunk, thunk, thunk!
Smash!
[VEGETA yelling]
[MAGETTA]
Clack clang?
You junk heap!
Big Bang Attack!
[MAGETTA]
Ka-boom!
[VEGETA gasps]
[FROST chuckles]
Don't expect your name-calling
to work just because
Botamo's not here.
[VEGETA grunts]
The tin can and the coward.
Could there ever be a
more pathetic tag team?
You certainly enjoy your
insults, don't you, Vegeta?
Meanwhile, I will enjoy
beating you within
an inch of your life!
Good idea. I may
have to steal it!
[VEGETA, FROST yell]
[gasps]
[MAGETTA]
Chugga-chugga-chugga-bang!
[FROST yells]
As a Metalman, Magetta
is nearly impervious.
Normal attacks will never
force him from the ring.
That would take something
far more spectacular.
[VEGETA]
Damn you!
[VEGETA grunting]
I've got your "spectacular"
right here.
The old guy.
He just won't quit.
It's his best chance.
That's crazy, it would be
his third time to try it!
Master Roshi, no!
Please, it's too draining!
One more time could kill you!
[ROSHI] I don't care about my
old shell of a life any more.
At least I'll make it count!
Old man, don't!
I've got this--
I don't need your help!
[FROST]
Heh.
[ROSHI]
Here goes my last shot!
Evil Containment!
[MAGETTA]
Kerplunk!
[FROST]
Just what I was waiting for!
[yelling]
--What the--?
--He's... reversing it.
[KRILLIN] Master Roshi could
get sealed up instead!
[VEGETA]
No you... don't!
Stay back, Vegeta!
It's a trap!
Ha! Heads up, dear Saiyan!
Here it comes!
What?!
[VEGETA groans]
[ROSHI gasping]
[ROSHI grunts]
Nice try, wrinkles,
but I still have this one
from when you tried to trap me!
[FROST chuckles]
[FROST grunts]
[VEGETA groans]
[VEGETA]
Frost, you bastard!
[FROST laughs]
I cannot thank you enough.
Your "Evil Containment"
technique is truly outstanding.
Because of your help, I've
realized my revenge against
Vegeta, and that detestable
monkey is off of my back.
I won't let one of our strongest
warriors be forced out
because of my own mistake!
Too bad for you,
you're expendable now.
[ROSHI groaning]
[laughing]
[ROSHI yelps]
[FROST chuckles]
Was that the last bit
of power you could
scrape from the barrel?
What a disgrace.
[ROSHI grunting]
[FROST grunts]
[gasps]
[screams]
[FROST screams]
[MAGETTA]
Clankety-Clack!
[VEGETA]
Damn you!
Don't just stand there,
Magetta, go and stop him!
I'm sick of you, Metalman!
Give up like the worthless
junk you are!
[MAGETTA]
Huh. Boing.
Ratchet. Kerplunk. Whir. Thud.
[FROST]
No!
Get ready!
'Cause you're next, Frosty.
[FROST]
You may have won this round,
but I swear, with every
fiber of my being...
...I'll destroy you!
[VEGETA]
Of course he runs.
Gutless wimp.
[MAGETTA]
Toot, toot...
[VEGETA]
Good riddance.
Your mental weakness
is an embarrassment!
And then there is you.
You're tapped out,
aren't you, old man.
I messed up. And I'm sorry.
[VEGETA] Hmph. Go get
a senzu before you croak.
You can leave
the rest of this to me.
[ROSHI exhales]
[FUTURE ZENO]
Bye, Magetta!
[ZENO]
Bye, Roshi!
[KRILLIN]
Here, Master.
It's okay, Roshi.
You're in the stands now.
Right.
You losers make quite
the spectacle, you know.
You're the Three Baldies
of the Bench!
[TIEN, KRILLIN, ROSHI]
Uh....
Still. You fought
well for an old guy.
Not bad, Roshi.
I'm almost impressed.
[NARRATOR] Thanks to the
tenacious efforts of Vegeta
and Master Roshi, the Seventh
Universe has escaped a trap
that could have spelled
the end for their team.
But of course, in the Tournament
of Power there is no time
for relishing victories,
as each triumph
quickly gives way to
the next powerful threat.
Thirty minutes remain in
the great battle for survival.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super.
When the time has come
to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever in my mind
as I look up to the sky
I was watching you
from your left side
Was trying to get
a good look at your face
The tears in your eyes;
were you laughing or crying?
Your long hair in the way
Blocking the thoughts inside
When the time has
come to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever I will wait,
for the light to show the way
For us to meet again
[GOHAN] Dad, we need to
face the truth about Frieza.
He's too sadistic
to call an ally.
And it looks like he's been
secretly teaming up with
the Sixth Universe's Frost!
We can't let this pair
of self-serving traitors
get away with their scheme!
If I have to stop 'em
myself, then so be it!
I'm not afraid!
I'm gonna take out the trash!
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Frieza and Frost!
A Mutual Malevolence?"
Be sure you don't miss it, okay?