♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the Tournament of Destroyers,
which would decide
if Earth would stay put or
be sent to a different universe,
had reached its final
and decisive blow.
[TD REF] That's a ring out!
Contestant Monaka wins!
[CHAMPA] Each and every one
of you so-called fighters
has failed and humiliated me.
And for that, I'm going
to destroy all of you!
[NARRATOR]
Lord Champa the Destroyer,
was moments away from
eradicating his own team,
and Goku would not
be allowed to intervene.
Now Goku, don't go stepping out
of line forgetting your place.
[grunts]
[NARRATOR]
But in the nick of time,
a mysterious visitor
appeared in the ring.
[BEERUS, CHAMPA]
Grand Zeno!
[NARRATOR]
"Come Forth, Divine Dragon!
And Grant My Wish,
Peas and Carrots!"
Who is that guy?
[ALL gasp quaveringly]
Great Ancestor, should I know
who that childlike creature is?
Don't you know anything?
[TD REF]
Our ring has been invaded!
Who could these mysterious,
purple-clad intruders be? Aah!
Looks like some
sort of alien child.
Who knows.
You think he's lost?
[BEERUS] Silence, mortals!
Grand Zeno is no child!
That's the Omni-King;
supreme ruler of
all twelve universes!
[BOTH]
Hm? Aaah...!
Do you really think it's proper
to remain up here, my lord,
causing us to look down
on the Omni-King?
Of course I don't--come on!
What could Grand Zeno
be doing here?
That sure was nice timing.
Does this mean we're spared?
[HIT]
Good question.
[CHAMPA, BEERUS]
Welcome, Grand Zeno!
You grace us with your presence!
[ZENO]
Mhm.
We apologize
for not staying in touch.
[ZENO]
Mhm.
Has anything
interesting happened?
[ZENO]
Mhm.
[BOTH]
Nnnnnnh!
[ALL gasp quaveringly]
Your visit humbles us, sire!
Uh. May we ask what brings you
here today, Grand Leader?
Yes, you may!
You had a big fight.
And you didn't tell me.
So, I came to warn you.
Yes, sire!
Destroyers are
supposed to destroy!
Not doing your job is very bad!
Please forgive us, Omni-King!
You show great wisdom
in scolding them, sire.
Recently, Lord Beerus
has become more interested
in napping and eating than
in destruction, I'm afraid.
Lord Champa hasn't behaved
any better, Grand Leader;
just look at the shape he's in!
I tell him it's affecting
his performance
and I work so hard to give him
nutritionally balanced meals,
but he throws
the plates on the ground
and tells me
I'm a terrible cook!
Oh! It breaks my heart, sire!
Mmm. These Destroyers are bad.
We need new ones.
[BOTH scream]
--Just kidding!
--[CHAMPA, BEERUS sigh]
--[ZENO] But anyway...
--[CHAMPA, BEERUS] Yes, sir?
Like I said, I was
coming here to warn you!
But then I was watching.
And it was so fun!
And fun's good, right?
[CHAMPA, BEERUS]
Yes, sire!
And then I got an idea
that was very good!
A tournament with
all the universes together!
I think we should try it
sometime; wouldn't that be fun?
[GOKU]
Oh, hell yeah!
That would be
totally awesome, little dude!
[BOTH scream]
[GOKU]
Can we really do it, really?
Stop! What are you doing?
--Uh!
--[CHAMPA, BEERUS] Aah!
[GOKU]
Hey, I just wanna talk!
Please! Just a
quick little chat?
You are an
insignificant mortal!
You shouldn't even
be gazing upon Grand Zeno,
let alone speaking to him!
We can talk; it's okay!
[CHAMPA, BEERUS scream]
Grand Zeno, are you sure?
You had some good matches, huh?
[laughs]
You hear that? Good matches.
Ah!
--[ZENO] Okey-dokey!
--[BEERUS, CHAMPA] Ah?
We can have a tournament
real soon, all right?
Sounds like a plan, buddy!
[BOTH holler]
[ZENO]
Mmm...
[CHAMPA hollers]
[BEERUS hollers]
[GOKU chuckles]
[laughs]
[GOKU] Come on,
little buddy. I won't bite!
[hollers]
[DESTROYERS, KAIS sigh]
[GOKU laughs]
[ZENO]
Uuh.
[BOTH]
Hey!
It's okay, everybody!
You're funny and I like funny!
I'm leaving now. Bye-bye!
Great meeting you--
I'll see you soon!
[ZENO]
Mhm.
[BOTH]
Thank you for coming, sire!
[ZENO]
Mhm.
[ZENO GUARD 1, 2]
Later gators.
[CHAMPA, BEERUS sigh]
[BEERUS]
Listen, you fool.
If the Omni-King ever felt
like it, he could easily
annihilate all twelve universes
in the blink of an eye!
Wow, that's impressive.
But why would he ever do that?
He seems like a nice guy
to me! Plus, you can't
have a tournament
without fighters, right?!
[chuckles]
Uuugh. That was
so stressful I'm not even
excited about winning anymore.
[chuckles]
I don't blame you, brother.
If Grand Zeno's
holding a tournament,
then this one means nothing!
It was just practice
for the real event!
So, don't try to
brag about it; I don't care!
Ha! Care or not, you can't
weasel out of our bet.
[CHAMPA]
I know that!
The six Super
Dragon Balls are yours,
but good luck
finding the last one!
I scoured both our universes
and never caught a whiff of it!
Ha! Let's go!
[CHAMPA]
Come on, losers!
If Grand Zeno
likes watching you,
I'll have to bring you
to the next one
and just hope you won't suck!
--[CABBA sighs]
--[MAGETTA] Ka-chunk.
Come to Planet Sadla
whenever you want, master.
I can show you around.
I never told you that I would
be your master, pip-squeak.
Right, sorry, master!
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU]
Hey, Hit.
Since we're not sure
when this new tournament
of Zeno's is gonna be,
what do you say we have
our own little rematch
while we're waiting?
We could do it
anywhere you like:
your universe or mine.
How about three days from now--
does that work
with your schedule?
[HIT grunts]
What? You don't feel
like waiting that long?
Then how 'bout tomorrow?
Just let me know!
[BUU] Aah! Buu have
a long and wonderful nap,
but sorry no get you
special super wish.
Don't worry about it, buddy.
I had a blast
just watching the show!
Plus, I got to meet
this amazing fella.
You shoulda seen him fight!
What do you say we
go into business together
and I make you the mascot
of my training dojo?
Your face would
look great on a hat!
[MONAKA]
Uuuh...
[BULMA] Look, if I'm gonna
help you, you've got to promise
you won't wish for
something terrible, okay?
I don't take orders
from humans.
Want to find this
Super Dragon Ball or not?
[BEERUS] Okay, fine.
Just get on with it!
Uh... I'm still not
getting a reading.
If Whis can take us to
the center of the universe,
we can try my original plan
and use the Radar there.
And if it doesn't pick up
anything at that vantage point,
I guess we'll look for it
in the Sixth Universe instead.
That sounds like an awful lot
of traveling, Bulma.
I'm not sure my captain's
gonna be too cool with me
missing that much work.
Wait, Bulma.
We need a total of seven.
I think I see them
all on the screen.
Huh? Uh--
Whoa, I was just assuming.
You're right,
there are seven readings!
[ALL]
Huh?
But there's only six up there;
that makes no sense!
Yes, it is quite
the perplexing riddle.
Oh, hi.
In my line of work,
I spend a lot of time
looking at cosmic maps.
Usually when there's confusion,
it's 'cause you're not thinking
three-dimensionally.
Uh-- Are you
implying what I think?
Yes, Monaka, of course
that's the answer!
I honestly can't believe
I didn't think of that myself!
All aboard
the hexahedron everyone.
We need to make a trip.
What do you think
Whis is planning to do?
Here goes.
[VEGETA]
What's happening down there?
Be patient, you'll see.
[A18, KRILLIN,
JACO, GALACTIC KING gasp]
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL gasp]
Huh?
[BULMA]
Wait, what?
So, all that time
we wondered where the last
Super Dragon Ball was,
we were on it?
Who knows how many
centuries have passed
since the last time
they were scattered.
I'm guessing that one collided
with an asteroid here,
and over the years
the scattered debris
was pulled in
by the orb's gravity,
creating its rocky surface.
Well done, Monaka.
Your deduction was right.
So, do we know
what we're supposed to say
to summon the Dragon, now that
we've got all seven together?
[BULMA] If I tell you, promise
you won't make evil wishes!
Ugh! You've made
your point; stop nagging!
That's the best you're
going to get from him.
[sighs] Okay fine,
here's what you do.
In the divine language,
you have to say,
"Come forth, divine dragon
and grant my wish,
peas and carrots."
You ready, Whis?
I'm going to tell you
the special phrase
and you shout it toward
the Super Dragon Balls, okay?
Understood, my lord; I'm ready.
Uh, let's see.
Emoc htrof, enivid nogard,
dna tnarg ym shiw.
Now that end part.
What does
"peas and carrots" mean?
I have no idea
why it's in there,
but I think it's
another way to say "please."
Well, there's no way to
say that in the divine tongue.
Well then,
leave it untranslated.
Why do I feel like
I'm being pranked right now?
Oh well, I can't think
of a better idea.
You hear that?
[WHIS]
A-hem.
Emoc htrof, enivid nogard,
dna tnarg ym shiw.
♪ Peas and carrots. ♪
That's odd.
It doesn't seem like
that worked, you guys.
Must be that
"peas and carrots" nonsense.
Are you sure
you heard that right?
Ah?!
[ALL gasp]
♪
[WHIS]
Mmm.
What is that?
Don't you think we should go?
Not to worry. I'm pretty
sure you'll be fine.
[GOKU] You're pretty sure?
What does that mean?
[WHIS laughs]
[BULMA groans]
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU groans]
What's that?
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
[roars]
[SUPER DRAGON roars]
[ALL gasp]
[roars]
[chorale music plays]
[GOKU]
Whoa!
[chorale music plays]
[music continues]
[SUPER DRAGON roars]
[SUPER DRAGON growls]
[gasps]
What the--?
Wow. What is this?
Are those planets?
And galaxies?
Whoa. Is everybody seeing this?
Why can't I dream about flying,
like a normal pig? Uuuh.
What do you think? Where are we?
If I had to guess,
I'd say we're inside
this Super Shenron's body.
What?!
Wait. Does that mean
the dragon ate us?
We're not all gonna turn into
dragon poop, are we?
This is serious, Goku!
Will you grow up?
[WHIS] There's no need
to worry, Earthlings.
This is necessary
to interact with the dragon,
that's all you need to know.
[GOKU]
Ooh.
Uuh.
[gulps]
[ALL gasp]
[BULMA] So, are we seeing
his actual body now?
I don't understand.
[BEERUS] It's hard
to explain to a mortal.
It's more the nucleus
of his being.
His core, if you like.
--You follow that?
--Unh-uh.
[SUPER DRAGON]
Won kaeps yht shiw.
I llahs tnarg eeht
yna eno shiw.
The divine language, huh?
I'm sure he's just telling us
to make a wish, right?
No offense, but we'll let
the gods handle this, okay?
Anything I want.
What should I ask him for?
Are you telling me
you haven't even
thought of a wish yet?
Shut up, human,
I'm thinking now!
[SUPER DRAGON growls]
All right!
Gnirb kcab eht htxis s'esrevinu
htraE dna ecar namuh.
Are you sure
that's what you want, sir?
--I'm sure.
--An interesting choice.
I'll convey it now, my lord.
Gnirb kcab eht htxis s'esrevinu
htraE dna ecar namuh.
Yht hsiw si detnarg. Lleweraf!
[roars]
--[VEGETA] Is it over?
--[PICCOLO] Seems like it.
Okay, spill it.
What'd you wish for?
You have no need to know.
Come on, that's not fair.
We just fought a whole
tournament to get that wish!
Oh, very well--
if you must know
I asked the dragon to give me
a more comfortable bed.
You what? Are you stupid?
You blew the ultimate wish
to save a trip
to the mattress store?
You dare insult a Destroyer?
You do remember
we destroy things, right?
Can it be?
[CHAMPA]
Oof!
Come on! I nearly broke my face!
There's something
I need to show you.
Yeah, yeah, Beerus' Earth!
Why would I want to see that?
[VADOS]
Trust me. You do.
Okay, what is it?
You're looking at Earth
in the Sixth Universe, my lord.
[CHAMPA]
Eh?
[VADOS]
And this is a live view.
The planet has been
brought back to good health,
along with its people.
Is this some kind of joke?
Hardly, sir.
And now it seems
their civilization is very
similar to the Seventh's.
If that's really true...
They should be producing
culinary delights
which we can now enjoy
as much as we like.
[CHAMPA]
How is this possible?
It's only logical.
Your brother has decided
to use his
Super Dragon Balls wish
for your benefit, Lord Champa.
[CHAMPA]
Wh-What?
Yes. What a tricky move.
He wants to lord it over me.
That smug little devil.
That was very kind of you, sir.
Kindness has
nothing to do with it.
I just want him to owe me.
No! And stop asking!
Come on, the tournament's over.
What's the big deal?
I only want to spar
with him for a little bit,
just to get
a sense of his power!
If you want
to know his strength
there's no point fighting him
while he's exhausted.
Go home and I'll let you
fight before long.
Fine. I'm gonna
hold you to that.
Exemplary work, Monaka.
You can go back to work now.
Yes, sir.
I put something inside
for your trouble.
Holy freaking crap!
Thank you, Lord Beerus.
You're awesome!
You motivated Goku so well
I may have to ask you
to do it again.
[MONAKA]
Eeeh-he-heh.
[PICCOLO] A tournament
between all universes.
Sounds like
a dangerous mess to me.
[GOKU]
Yeah! I can't wait for it!
I'll start saving
my vacation days now!
Guys, look! We're home!
[NARRATOR] And so
the Tournament of Destroyers
has come to an end,
with Goku, Vegeta,
and the rest of the Seventh
Universe team as the champions.
What adventures
await our heroes now?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball Super!
♪ Closing Song ♪
Wow
It's hard to say
Don't wanna stay
I twist and fight,
can't find my way
I must believe, that fear
and trouble can even be fun
if you think the right way
Wow
I don't wanna draw the line
I gotta see it through some way
Fight for what I know is mine
The dream I had of me that day
Wow
Don't care if they
call me greedy
If they hate me, make me blue
Don't care if they laugh at me
'Cause I will make
the dream come true
Wow
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And it looks like I'm finally
getting what I wanted all along.
The chance to fight Monaka!
I didn't think he was gonna
make this little party,
but you definitely
won't hear me complain!
Why's everybody else
acting so weird, though?
I mean Vegeta's sweating,
Piccolo seems nervous.
Is there something
I should know?
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"A Chaotic Victory Party!
Showdown at Last?
Monaka vs Goku!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?