♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Super,
the Zeno Expo was winding down,
the Eleventh Universe's
fighter Top appeared
out of nowhere to challenge
Goku to an extra battle.
[TOP]
Justice Flash!
[GOKU]
Ha!
[NARRATOR] And Goku savored
the opportunity to once again
test the limits of his power.
I'll administer
the harshest judgment
the cosmos has ever seen!
Yeah, that's it. I want you
to use everything you've got.
And I'm gonna show you what
it's like when I hit my ceiling.
And break through it!
[NARRATOR]
Neither fighter showed any sign
of slowing down, until...
And, that's enough!
[NARRATOR] The Grand Minister
abruptly cancelled the fight,
choosing to save the drama
for the upcoming
Tournament of Power.
And with all the universes
turned against Goku,
his chances were looking dim.
Only 39 hours are left
before the start
of the massive battle royale.
In order to assemble
the remaining members
of the Seventh Universe's
team for the tournament,
Goku and the others
return to Earth. Now!
[NARRATOR] "Field the
All-Seventh-Universe Team!
Who Are the Mighty Ten?"
[CHICHI] ♪ Oh!
Little baby, come on out, ♪
♪ and show your bum-bum. ♪
♪ Oh! Little baby, come
on out, and rub-a-tum-tum. ♪
Huh?
[ALL]
Ooh.
Oh. How's it going, Chichi!
What's with all the food?
[CHICHI]
Oh, Goku, yay!
You and your friends
showed up just in time.
Now come and eat
before it gets too cold!
Uh. Whoa, you mean it?
When I heard Bulma was
about to have her baby,
I just panicked and started
making a whole bunch of food.
But now it sounds like it might
be a while before she's ready.
[PILAF, SHU, MAI, BULMA]
♪ ...your bum-bum. ♪
♪ Oh! Little baby, ♪
♪ come on out,
and show your bum-bum. ♪
♪ Oh! Little baby, ♪
♪ come on out,
and rub-a-tum-tum. ♪
[BULMA] Hey, Vegeta,
sorry we're taking up
your training room like this.
Yeah, you should be!
Thanks to you I'm getting
downright flabby here!
Sheesh, should she really
be moving around
so much right now?
[TRUNKS] You're pretty
worried about Mom, huh?
Yeah.
Mm!
[GOTEN] But Mai said these
exercises would help her
have an easier time
delivering the baby.
You're getting
pretty antsy, aren't you?
Ah!
It's not like I'm
hanging around here
'cause I'm eager
for the baby to come.
I'm just here because
she told me to stay.
[TRUNKS]
Dad, where you goin'?
[VEGETA]
To train. Somewhere nearby.
I wanna come train!
Yeah, me, too!
--[VEGETA] Well, too bad.
--[BOTH] Awe!
You heard me, boys.
And weren't you
supposed to be getting
the baby's crib ready, Trunks?
[TRUNKS] Oh, right!
Hey, Goten, come gimme a hand.
M'kay!
[VEGETA] Hm. Suppose I should
start thinking of a name.
Something befitting
the Saiyan royal family.
[CHICHI]
Hey, what are you wearing?
Oh, well, Videl said
that I should spend some time
with Dad for a change,
so you know.
[CHICHI grunts]
Oh man, that's delicious!
I really needed this.
I haven't eaten anything
since the fight ended.
Just keep bringing those
plates over, chop-chop!
Sorry to interrupt,
but perhaps we should
select our team first?
[BEERUS] If you're gonna rush
me, then pick them yourself!
Although, you'd better
make sure they can win.
Of course.
How can they just sit there
and eat at a time like this?
[sighs] Well, shall we
get started then?
Uh, sure, Supreme Kai,
but before we do,
I was wondering,
can you tell us how many
inhabited worlds there are
in the Seventh Universe?
[SUPREME KAI]
Let's see.
Since Planet Sadla, Vegeta,
and Namek are no longer with us,
that brings the total
to 28, I believe.
Do you think anyone on
those worlds is strong enough
to compete in
the Tournament of Power?
That's difficult to say.
I've never observed them all
from the perspective
of their combat abilities.
And that negligence is
precisely why we're now ranked
as a low-level universe, Kai!
Still can't believe
out of 12 universes
our average mortal level
is only second from the bottom.
It's pitiful.
There's gonna be eight teams
competing in this, right?
Which means our odds
of winning would only be
around 12.5%-- if all the
universes were on equal footing.
Kinda makes me wish I could
get re-sealed in a Z Sword.
[ELDER KAI laughing]
Hey, this is no time
to be laughing, old man!
If we lose,
you'll be vaporized, too!
That may be, Destroyer,
but there's no point
in pitching a fit about it now.
There's nothing to worry
about, Lord Beerus.
All we gotta do
is win this thing, right?
Though I can't wait
to see what kinda
heavy-hitters'll be there!
Your confidence is only
outpaced by your naivety.
Considering the short window,
I doubt we have the time
to go world-hopping,
so perhaps we should
limit our recruitment
efforts to Earth for now?
[GOHAN] Good thinking. We can
start with the three of us
who competed in the Zeno Expo,
plus Vegeta and--
And Monaka!
Mona--er, Monaka
can't come, sorry.
He's not feeling well.
And he's busy too.
Oh no, are you sure?
But he doesn't even know about
the tournament yet, right?
I called him up
when you weren't looking.
Monaka can't come, okay!
[GOHAN]
Let's just drop it, Dad.
If he's not up to it right now,
there's nothing we can do.
Aw, but what a shame--
the strongest fighter
in the universe can't make it.
[sighs]
Lord Beerus, don't you
think it's about time
you told him the truth?
[BEERUS]
Absolutely not.
Well, we could get Piccolo
and Krillin--that's two more.
Um, wait, Gohan--
are you sure about Krillin?
It's been a while
since he was in the ring.
Gohan.
Right.
[KRILLIN, BASIL grunting]
What is this?
It's an Image Battle.
They're fighting
inside their minds.
[yells]
--[BASIL growls]
--Destructo Disc!
[BASIL yells]
Afterimage Strike!
[BASIL]
He-heh.
[BASIL yelling]
Solar Flare!
[BASIL groans]
[KRILLIN yelling]
[KRILLIN]
He-heh.
[laughing]
Uh-uuh!
This will finish you off
once and for all!
Uh...
[KRILLIN yells]
You know, maybe this fight
is too much for Krillin.
No way. Krillin'll do
just fine there.
He's started training again.
Huh? Really? He has? Since when?
He's even got this awesome
technique you've never
heard of before, so he'll be
more than all right, son.
So that makes six.
What do you think about adding
Goten and Trunks to the team?
They seem to have
extensive latent abilities.
Nah, that's not gonna work.
Those boys are still too green.
This tournament is more than
just a raw test of strength.
You win by pushing others
out of the ring,
which requires strategy.
They don't have
enough experience.
Okay, in that case,
what about Master Roshi?
I mean, he's got
centuries of experience,
and knows all kinds
of tricky maneuvers.
[GOKU] Oh, yeah. I guess the
old-timer can fight well enough.
All right, that makes seven.
--[MR. SATAN] 'Scuse me.
--Huh?
Might I suggest
you ask Number 18?
Aah! That's a great idea!
Yeah, and there's
Number 17, too.
We should ask 18
where to find him.
[SUPREME KAI]
Are you sure that's allowed?
Those two are technically
robots, aren't they?
Well, they're human-based.
Just upgraded
to superhuman strength
at the cellular level,
that's all.
[SUPREME KAI]
But still...
I'm going to have to pretend
I didn't hear any of that!
[SUPREME KAI]
Lord Beerus.
If they can win, then I
don't care what they are!
That makes nine. One more to go.
[GOKU]
Hmm. Who else is there?
Well, we still have
some time to figure it out,
so I see no need to force
a decision right away.
Indeed--that's a good point.
And there still could be
people on other worlds
with high combat abilities.
We should explore that.
Then I'll leave you to it.
I'm gonna stick around
a little longer and
finish things up here.
[SUPREME KAI]
Don't overdo it, Great Ancestor.
Yeah, yeah, I know!
Man, this Tournament
of Power is shaping up to be
tons of fun already!
Oh, before it starts,
we'd better go get
some senzu from Korin.
Actually, I believe those
are against the rules.
--[GOKU] Uh?
--[WHIS] If I'm not mistaken,
[WHIS] "senzu" are
those beans that recover
your physical strength?
That technically makes
them an "outside weapon,"
which is clearly not allowed.
Wait, so no senzu?
I don't like the sound of that.
[whispering]
Just pop a few on the sly.
--Really, Lord Beerus!
--[BEERUS] Ngh!
If they're caught cheating,
they'll be eliminated, sir.
[BEERUS]
Ugh.
[VEGETA]
Hmmm.
How 'bout "Échalote."
Yeah, that's not too bad.
Hey, Vegeta!
[VEGETA]
Ugh! And now he's back.
Hey, I've got some awesome news!
We're gonna get to fight some
super strong warriors soon!
It turns out the cosmos
is like, really huge!
There's this one guy, Top,
from the Eleventh Universe,
and even after
turning Blue, I'm not sure
I coulda beaten him,
he was so strong!
You're serious?
Even after turning Blue?
Yup! And the best part is,
80 of us get to fight
--at the same time!
--[gasps]
Yeah, that's right.
Ten contestants from
eight different universes
will enter the ring at once,
and whoever's left
at the end is the winner.
Eighty combatants
fighting all at once?
You're talking about
a battle royal.
We're leaving the day
after tomorrow.
[GOKU chuckles]
In that case, you'll just
have to count me out.
[GOKU, GOHAN]
Huh?
I don't know if my child
is going to be born by then.
[GOKU]
Didn't you hear me?
We get to fight all the best
fighters from across the cosmos!
[GOHAN]
Yeah, you've gotta come, Vegeta!
Something's fishy here.
Uuh...
Why are you so eager
for me to join your little team?
That isn't like you, Kakarrot.
Ordinarily,
you'd be much happier
hogging an opportunity
like this all to yourself.
That way, you'd be able
to fight 80--well, 70--
other opponents
without me showing you up.
Yeah, well,
see the thing is we--
Hey, quit flapping
your gums, Saiyans!
You're going to compete
and that's an order!
If you really want me to fight,
then you'll have to
persuade Bulma.
Because I'm not going
anywhere unless you do!
[BEERUS]
Eh! Uh.
[sighs]
All right, I'll do it.
[CHICHI] Now, now, Bulma,
you need to rest.
I mean, just look how big
your belly's getting.
Gee, thanks,
you're so thoughtful.
[door knob clicks]
Hello, everyone.
[BULMA, CHICHI]
Whis?
Listen, you can't just
come barging in like this!
Bulma's in a very
delicate state!
[WHIS]
Hmm.
What is it?
[WHIS] Eepans ti ekam stel dana
eebab eltil , hatarof emoc .
Eepah amam raed ruoy ekam ,
yoj fo eldnub .
[ALL]
Uuh!
[BABY crying]
Whis, is this really my baby?
[BULMA]
There, there, little one.
[PILAF, MAI, SHU, CHICHI]
Awe!
Well, Vegeta, you should
be available to compete now,
if I'm not mistaken?
[VEGETA, MR. SATAN]
Uuh...
Wow, thanks. That couldn't
have gone any easier.
I'll have to call you the next
time I'm pregnant, too.
Yeah, if the earth's
still here, that is.
--[GOKU, GOHAN] Eeh!
--[GOHAN] Don't say that!
Anyway, congratulations, Vegeta!
[PILAF, MAI, SHU,
CHICHI, BULMA laughing]
I'm gonna go and give Trunks
the good news, okay?
Yeah.
[BULMA giggles]
[BABY snoring]
[GOKU]
So, that's Vegeta's baby, huh?
It doesn't look
anything like him.
[GOHAN]
That's not true.
See here, that looks
just like Vegeta.
[BULMA'S MOM] Well, I'll be,
their foreheads do
look sorta similar, don't they?
[BRIEFS]
Lemme hold my grandchild.
Oh, now look at you--
aren't you precious?
I'm your granddaddy.
Coochie-coochie-coo!
[BABY laughing]
[BULMA'S MOM]
All right, it's my turn.
Ooh, you're just
the cutest ever!
Hi there, I'm your grandma!
Goochie-goochie-goo!
[laughing]
[MR. SATAN]
M-Mind if I cut in?
[laughing]
How adorable!
I'm your Uncle Champ!
Blah-la-la-la!
[crying]
--[VEGETA grunts]
--[ALL] What the--?
Are we under attack?
Hey! You keep that food
coming, or else!
Okay, okay, okay!
It's coming right up, sir!
Hup-two, three, four.
[PILAF]
Aah. Here you go, sir!
[BEERUS] For all we know,
this could be our last supper.
So I say let's make it count.
[YAMCHA panting]
[GOKU]
Come on, it's my turn now.
[YAMCHA]
Whoa, the baby's here?
[ALL]
Uh?
Long time no see, guys.
Oh, Yamcha,
nice of you to drop by.
Well, I figured it was about
time for the baby to arrive.
Oh, whoa! Look at that
little cutie pie!
Can I hold it?
I promise I'll be careful!
[VEGETA grunts]
Well, hello there, baby,
it's your Uncle Yamcha!
Has your mommy told you
all about me?
--[crying]
--[YAMCHA] Huh? Uh-oh, uh, whoa.
[VEGETA grunting]
[YAMCHA]
Are we under attack?
[TRUNKS]
Hmm. A little more to the right.
No, more to the left.
Hmm.
That's a good place to start.
Huh?
It's a crib, does it really
matter where it goes?
[TRUNKS] You know it has
wheels on it, right?
[GOHAN]
Hey, Trunks.
Oh. Hey Gohan!
Ooh, good timing. Now you
can help us figure out
the best place to put the crib.
[GOHAN] Never mind that,
the baby's here.
[TRUNKS]
Uh.
It just happened.
Didja hear me?
You're a big brother now!
Wow! Congrats, Trunks,
that's awesome!
[TRUNKS] Hmm. So I'm
a big brother now, huh?
I can't tell if I like that.
So, Gohan. What is it?
A boy or a girl?
Aw, man. I forgot to ask
the most important question.
Ah, you're completely hopeless.
[GOHAN chuckles]
A younger brother
would be fun, right?
Yeah, just think. Then you
guys could train together.
Whoa, really?
Yeah, definitely. You know,
my big brother trained me
when I was little.
That's right.
When Goten was born,
our dad wasn't around,
so I helped out.
'Specially 'cause we had the
World Martial Arts
Tournament coming up.
I get to train
my younger brother?
Hee! Haa! Hoo!
Of course, having a sister
can be cool, too.
[TRUNKS]
Huh? Mmm.
[GOTEN] Might be nice to have
a little sister like Pan.
She's really cute, right?
Yeah, she's cute I guess. Mmm.
Still, I think I'd rather
have someone to train.
Ooh, how adorable!
My little Goten was
just as cute as that,
with those little
chipmunk cheeks.
Uh, hey, Mom.
Oh, there you are, sweetie.
Why don't you come over here?
Trunks, I want you to meet
your little baby sister.
Huh? A sister? Uuh.
Aw man, having someone to
train with sounded like fun.
Ooh, ooh, can I see her, too?
Why, of course.
[GOTEN] Wow, she's so
tiny and squishy!
Hey, y'know, you were
just as tiny as that
when you were born, Goten.
How would you know, Goku?
You weren't there, you were
too busy being dead!
Oops, I just had to go and
open my big mouth, didn't I?
[ALL laughing]
[VEGETA grunts]
Kakarrot.
[BULMA] So, Trunks,
would you like to hold her?
Uh! No, that's okay.
[BULMA]
Just for a sec.
Aah!
She's a lot heavier
than she looks.
[BULMA]
Now, as her big brother,
it's your job to always
keep your sister safe.
--[BABY laughing]
--[TRUNKS] Uuh...
[laughing]
I'll be counting
on you, all right?
Uh-huh.
[VEGETA coughs]
[TRUNKS]
Tickle, tickle, tickle!
--Tell you what, sweetie.
--[TRUNKS] Blaah... Mm?
[TRUNKS]
Dad!
Yeah, what do you want, Trunks?
Mom says that
you should hold her now.
[TRUNKS]
Hm.
That's not the way
you hold her! Give her to me!
Wow, you're good at this, huh?
[VEGETA]
Hmph!
[BRIEFS]
By the way, Bulma,
you settled on
a name for her yet?
If you'd like, I can
offer some suggestions.
[VEGETA grunts]
As a matter of fact,
I've already picked out a name,
one worthy of a Saiyan w--
Oh, I've got the perfect
name for her!
We're calling her... Bulla!
Nh! What? But I had a...
--[laughing]
--[GOTEN] Baby Bulla, huh?
[TRUNKS]
That's all right.
[BRIEFS] Ah, Bulla.
What a wonderful choice, dear!
A lovely name
for a lovely girl.
It's perfect! Bully for Bulla!
--[ALL laughing]
--[VEGETA] Hey, just hold on
[VEGETA] a minute there!
This is ridiculous.
I wanted to give my daughter
a traditional Saiyan name!
[laughing]
Well I'd say,
now there's one more thing
we need to fight to protect.
Yeah.
Mark my words, Gohan,
we're gonna win
that Tournament of Power!
You know it.
[GOKU]
Well, so long.
I'm heading over
to Krillin's place now.
[GOHAN] I'll catch up
to you later, Dad!
[YAMCHA] So, uh, what's this
Tournament of Power?
Ah, jeez! So you uh,
heard that part, did ya?
--Duh.
--Well, you see, it's uh...
[YAMCHA] What? So he's going
off to recruit Krillin now?
And you're saying that
there's ten fighters per team,
and if you guys win this
Tournament of Power,
then you get to have
any wish you want granted,
just like last time?
Using the Super Dragon
Balls again, yeah.
[YAMCHA]
Hmm. Ten fighters, eh?
With ten spots to fill, I'll be
getting an invitation for sure.
But wait.
When they ask me,
I should turn 'em down,
and then make
a dramatic entrance
right before
the tournament starts.
[YAMCHA]
Hey, fellas!
[GOKU]
Hm?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[GOKU]
Whoa, Yamcha!
We'll win for sure
now that you're here.
Stand back, I got this.
[YAMCHA laughing]
Then I get to play the hero!
Now to head home and just wait
for them to come beggin'!
[YAMCHA]
All right, check this out.
Excuse me there, Bulma!
I just remembered there's
something I need to do.
Guess I'll see ya later, then!
Goodbye for now!
That Yamcha sure is
a popular guy, isn't he?
Bulla, hmm?
[laughing]
[VEGETA]
Well, it's not the worst name.
[BULMA giggles]
[NARRATOR] Unbeknownst
to his friends and family,
Goku races around the globe
gathering a team of warriors
to keep them safe
and protect the universe
from potential doom.
Thirty-nine hours
remain until the start
of the Tournament of Power,
which will determine
the fate of
the Seventh Universe.
Will Goku be able to assemble
his ten champions by then?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball Super.
An angel and a demon sit
One to my right,
one to my left
In between I'm tryin'
to figure out the right way
Is one way good?
Is one way bad?
Too much confusion in my head
I can't think with all
this noise, I'm goin' crazy
Is there any way to know
what's right or wrong?
Demons in an angel mask
Hopin' that I'll do
just what they ask
Telling me
they know what's right
Lead me to the light
"For the sake of everyone
You have to destroy
the evil ones
That's the only path, you see"
So they said to me
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
I stopped by Krillin's place,
but it looks like
he's been off
training in secret.
[GOHAN] Krillin's just
full of surprises,
including some
awesome new moves.
[GOKU] In that case,
let's mix it up a little bit
before the tournament and
see how strong he really is.
Time for a full-power
contest, Krillin!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Goku the Talent Scout.
Recruit Krillin and Android 18."
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?