♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Lord Beerus and Whis
suspected the true identity
of Goku Black was a Supreme Kai
in training named Zamasu.
Goku sparred with the Kai,
but the connection to
Goku Black remained uncertain.
I'm not so sure about that.
Seems like a pretty big leap
from him to Black.
Zamasu didn't strike me
as that bad of a guy.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
Vegeta offered to train his son
from the future
and showed Trunks
the power of Super Saiyan Blue.
If Saiyan blood
flows in your veins,
if you're my son as you claim,
then I won't tolerate you
losing to anyone!
You'll be the best,
or you'll be nothing!
[NARRATOR]
And across the universe,
Beerus answered
an alarming call.
Well, I'd like
to see Goku, you see!
[BOTH shriek]
[NARRATOR]
"I'd Like to See Goku, You See.
A Summons From Grand Zeno!"
[BEERUS grunting]
Yo, Lord Beerus!
Whis said to come see you.
Things are about
to get pretty hectic,
so whatever you want,
can you make it quick?
[hollering]
That's my face!
The Omni-King has informed us
he wants to see you.
Owww! You mean
that Grand Zeno guy?
The ruler of us all--
yes, he wishes you
to come to his palace.
Is this about his tournament?
I would not deign to guess.
Sounds fun, but can I
take a rain-check?
Bulma's almost done
fixing the time machine,
so I'm gonna have to leave soon.
Don't be stupid!
When Grand Zeno calls for you,
you don't check your
damn calendar! You just go!
Well where does he live?
How long does the trip take?
Even for me, it takes
two days each way.
Two days? That's crazy,
I can't be gone that long
in the middle of
this thing with Black!
Are you honestly that dense?
[BEERUS] Ridiculous! What could
Grand Zeno possibly want
with this brainless meatbag?
Wait, I just remembered.
You're friends with
the Supreme Kai of this
universe, aren't you, Goku?
Yeah, why?
Among the many
privileges of Supreme Kais
is the power to leap to Grand
Zeno's palace instantaneously.
Instantaneously? For real?
Clever idea.
With the Supreme Kai there,
we just might survive.
You should go too, Whis,
to keep Goku in line.
[WHIS] Then you aren't coming
as well, my lord?
Bah! No, of course not.
I'm extremely busy!
[WHIS]
Mmhmmm.
[GOKU]
Busy sitting on a stump?
You just focus on yourself,
and don't do anything dumb
while you're there!
[muffled]
What are you so worried about?
Do you not comprehend
that the fate of our universe
hinges on you
having good manners?
Listen! If you do anything
that Grand Zeno finds insulting,
he could easily erase you, me,
this entire reality
from existence!
Don't you forget that!
[GOKU laughing]
Sorry, but you look
funny when you're mad--
it's like your eyes
are gonna pop out!
[BEERUS growling]
I give up, we're all doomed.
Hey, just relax. I've got this.
Zeno likes me, remember?
I'll get this taken care of
and be back in no time.
Don't worry so much!
[birds chirping]
[buttons clicking]
[BULMA]
A-ha!
All done!
[DR. BRIEFS, MAI, SHOU gasp]
All right, then what do you say
we give this baby some juice!
[SHOU, MAI laugh]
I'll go tell Trunks
the good news!
[BULMA]
Hold on.
Not yet. He just finished
some intense training
with his dad, and I want him
to get some rest while he can.
So let's wait until we're sure
this thing is ready to fly.
--'Kay?
--You got it.
[BEERUS] And another thing.
You're not actually going to
the Omni-King's palace
dressed like that, are you?
Yeah! Of course. Why?
You should wear something
formal, you dolt.
[GOKU]
What, like a suit or something?
If I have to do that,
I ain't goin'!
Well, I could offer
an apology, saying we were
in such a rush we didn't
have time for proper attire.
Fine, but make sure
you don't even hint about
Goku Black or the
time machine, is that clear?
What? Why not?
If Grand Zeno learns
of the time tampering
and alternate realities,
he'll be all kinds of angry.
And you know what
he'd do then, don't you?
Ooooh...
One more thing.
If Grand Zeno does lash out,
make sure it's not
at Supreme Kai.
I need him protected
at all costs.
I'm quite aware, my lord.
Wow, that's a shocker.
Never heard you worry about
someone besides yourself before.
Ha! Right! Though he is
worried about himself,
since they are a set.
A set?
When a Supreme Kai dies,
the Destroyer of that
universe dies with him.
No way! Is that true?
So if I wanted to
defeat you, Lord Beerus,
I'd just have to get rid of
Supreme Kai and that's it?
That's crazy!
I mean, not that I ever would,
where's the challenge in that?
Whis, how could you blurt out
my greatest vulnerability
like some casual
piece of gossip?
Forgive me, my lord.
But knowing Goku
as well as we do,
there's no reason
for alarm. C'mon.
Yeah, like I said,
there's no fun in that,
and I'm super good
at keeping secrets, too!
[BEERUS growls]
Okay then.
Shall we get moving, Goku?
Yep! I'll see you
next time, Lord B!
[BEERUS sighs]
[BABARI roaring]
[roars]
[ZAMASU] They take what
they want by savage force.
Their so-called society
is based on nothing else.
They possess neither
justice nor order.
[GOWASU]
Mmm.
[ZAMASU]
They were gifted with life.
Brains capable of wisdom.
Yet they waste it completely.
Should these gifts
not be taken back?
Zamasu!
[ZAMASU]
Huh?
[roars]
[MALE BABARI 55C groaning]
[GOWASU]
Zamasu!
[roars]
You must not strike!
[GOWASU]
What have you done?
How could you?
Zamasu. Answer me!
[ZAMASU gasping]
[GOWASU]
The Potara. Now.
Why did you take his life?
We could have easily returned
without interference.
For all we know,
that individual could have had
a major impact on
the future of the Babari.
A warrior who saw the light,
and led his people
to true reformation.
You may have
robbed them of that.
[ZAMASU grunts]
[SUPREME KAI] What?! Wait?
The Palace of Grand Zeno?
Yup, that's what I said!
Can you take me, pretty please?
Would you be so kind?
You mean he invited you there?
Why in the worlds
would he do that?
You're not even divine!
Beats me, he didn't say.
To think! Goku laying
eyes on the palace!
But I haven't even been there!
Of course not, you toddler!
I've only been
three times myself!
Right, sir.
[ELDER KAI]
Hmmm... Hmmm...
Uh, you okay?
I'm begging you, please don't
make a fool of yourself
while you're there.
Why's everyone keep saying that?
Do I really seem like
the rude type of guy
who can't behave himself?
[KIBITO, ELDER KAI, SUPREME KAI]
Yes, you do.
[laughs]
You guys are funny.
We don't seem to be
getting through.
I suppose we shouldn't
keep him waiting.
Great!
We do appreciate the ride, sir.
Kai-kai!
Oh wow! So that's it, huh?
This is Zeno's house!
Huh?
Welcome, my friends,
and thank you for coming.
[SUPREME KAI, WHIS]
It has been too long.
[GRAND MINISTER chuckles]
[GOKU]
Uuh!
You must be the Saiyan Goku--
how nice to meet you.
Yo! Uugh!
Uh, yes sir! Hi sir!
[WHIS] We wanted to arrive
as soon as possible,
so please forgive
this mortal's informal attire.
[GOKU laughs]
Don't be trifled
for a moment, my friend.
After all, for you
that is the most important
and meaningful outfit
you have, is it not?
You betcha! I mean, yes, my sir!
Sounds like you're
a pretty smart dude!
--[SUPREME KAI grunts]
--[GOKU] Nngh! Uh!
[SUPREME KAI sighs]
Let me show you
the way, gentlemen.
That guy may not look like much,
but I get the feeling
he'd be tough in the ring.
Most keenly recognized, Goku.
Many would be deceived
by his appearance,
but when it comes
to fighting prowess,
the Grand Minister is considered
to be in the top five.
Among all the universes.
Yeah? That's awesome!
Shh! I know your tendencies
quite well, Goku.
But you must not
under any circumstances
ask him to fight,
do you understand?
Aw man, but now I'm all curious!
You'll just have to
take my word for it.
Suffice it to say not even I
can hold a candle to him.
Whoa! So he's that good, huh?
Guess this trip
was worth it, after all!
--[GOKU chuckles]
--[SUPREME KAI sighs]
[GRAND MINISTER] The Saiyan
Goku of Universe Seven,
as requested, sire.
Oh yippee yippee!
I am very happy now!
Welcome, funny Goku!
--What's up?!
--A-hem!
Uuuh! I mean,
good day and greetings!
So what's going on with you?
I'm not asking much.
I just want a friend, you see!
--[ZENO chuckles]
--[GOKU] Uh?
--[SUPREME KAI gasps]
--[WHIS] Oh.
You're not like
most people--you're fun!
I want you to be
my friend, okey-dokey?
And?
And what?
And now that we're friends,
just what are we gonna do?
--[GUARDS grunt]
--We can play!
We could do that I guess,
but is that the only
reason you called?
Is that bad?
Of course not, Grand Zeno!
Goku would feel privileged
to play with you
as many hours, days,
or years as you wish,
and provide you unsurpassed joy!
You be quiet.
[SUPREME KAI]
Yes, sire!
Are you trying to tell me
something? Saiyan Goku?
You know, you can
just call me Goku.
Just Goku? Yes, that's fun.
Then what should you
"just call" me?
Uh... Like a nickname? Hmmm.
How 'bout Zenny?
--[GUARDS grunt]
--[GRAND MINISTER chuckles]
--[WHIS] Oooh!
--[SUPREME KAI sighs]
Oh yes, Zenny is
a very fun name!
What should Zenny and Goku play?
I'm sorry. I'd love to play,
but now's a bad time.
There's something
I've got to take care of,
but when it's done
we can play, I swear!
[GUARDS]
You dare defy the Omni-King?
You will go back. Or bye-bye!
[GUARDS]
Aaah! Uh! We're sorry, sire!
So once you're done
with your busy thing,
you'll play with me?
Sure! And if you want,
I can bring somebody else
who'd be even more fun
to play with too.
So the next time you
won't have to wait on me!
--Really?
--Yeah, no problem!
Okay, it's a date! Oh, hey,
we can do that silly thing
we did last time, Goku,
to show we agreed on something!
What thing?
[ZENO giggles]
Oh! Right!
[BOTH laughing]
You fling me around, it's funny!
No one else will try!
You can do what
no one else can do!
Yeah? It's just
a handshake, it's easy!
[ZENO] Can you show me
some other fun things, too?
If this is your idea of fun,
it must be boring here.
You should come
to Earth sometime--
there's lots of cool stuff!
Hooray, let's do it!
I'll give you this!
Whoa, what is that?
[ZENO] This is a button. If you
push it, then I will appear!
[GOKU]
Uh...
It doesn't make sense
to push now.
Because I'm already here,
you see?
Oh right, sorry.
Then I'll save it for later.
[chuckles]
Remember the friend
you promised me, okay?
Yeah, will do.
Bye-bye, just Goku!
Bye! Come on,
Supreme Kai. Let's go.
Please tell me its over.
You bet, and we're all good!
[sighs]
[GOKU]
I told ya not to worry.
All right, Zenny, I'll see ya!
Okay!
You okay, Supreme Kai?
You totally fainted.
[SUPREME KAI]
Yes. I'm fine.
[GRAND MINISTER] You have quite
an interesting friend there.
[WHIS]
Indubitably.
I would enjoy seeing him
again myself, if possible.
I know he would be
delighted as well.
Until next time.
[SUPREME KAI]
Kai-kai.
Whew! That's done.
Thank goodness you're all right.
Oh by the way, Goku,
what was that business
about you promising
to bring Grand Zeno an even
better companion next time?
Who do you have
in mind for that?
Wait, you promised what?
Oh. Right,
the whole friend thing.
I just said that on the fly.
Do you guys know
anyone he'd like?
Are you telling us
you made that promise
with no idea how to fulfill it?
Well duh,
I had to say something.
I thought if I didn't,
he wouldn't let me go home.
[SUPREME KAI]
This is a disaster!
You've raised the hopes
of the Omni-King,
and now if you can't deliver
he'll retaliate
by destroying us all!
[laughs]
It's fine! I'll think of
something later, okay?
What? You're back already?
Like I said,
you didn't have to worry.
Zenny's a totally awesome dude!
[BEERUS yells]
Did you just say "Zenny"?
Uuuaah!
[GOKU]
Lord Beerus?
You'd better let me
handle this from here.
You go on home and tend to that,
uh, "important business."
[GOKU laughs]
He said Zenny. He said Zenny.
[GOWASU] You lack faith
in mortals. Tell me why.
This tea is a mirror,
pointed inward.
If the soul of
its maker is clouded,
the tea will be as well.
So is it fear
that clouds this cup?
Or bewilderment?
Speak.
[ZAMASU] Master Gowasu,
you have said something often.
To make mistakes
but learn from them,
thus forging a better world.
That is the essence
of a mortal spirit.
[GOWASU]
Mmm.
But as far as I can see,
mortals do not
learn this way at all.
Planet Babari
is no outlier, Master.
You've seen this
countless times before.
Patience, Zamasu.
Every seed needs time to grow.
Gardens are tended.
Not just watched.
Should a gardener
not pluck the weeds?
When I was invited here,
I thought you would
teach me divine justice.
But all you seem to do is watch
while these monsters
stain existence
with each other's blood!
[GOWASU]
Hmm.
[GOWASU] Zamasu, do you ever
ponder the relationship
between good, evil, and justice?
[ZAMASU]
Yes. All the time.
Evil is the
great obstacle to good.
And justice,
the sword by which good
can overcome
this obstacle and flourish.
[GOWASU]
That is one perspective.
But I have come
to view it this way:
Justice is not a sword
eradicating evil,
but a scale keeping good
and evil in balance.
Balance, master?
[GOWASU]
One can succumb to evil,
but reject that darkness
and rediscover the light
with new understanding.
Justice makes
that journey possible.
Evil informs good.
And that is why we give
the mortals their minds.
[ZAMASU] You give corruption
far too much credit.
Evil does not inform good.
It sullies it.
Like the Babari sullied
their world with violence.
And that arrogant Goku
sullied this sacred ground
by swinging his fists at a god.
Mortals received
the divine gift of intellect--
the potential for wisdom--
but they misuse it to destroy
the beauty of creation.
Mortals do not succumb to evil,
they are the evil.
They create it and spread it
with minds they
shouldn't possess.
How can we call ourselves
gods if we watch this blight
and do nothing to stop it?
[GOWASU] Zamasu. You have
a strong hunger for justice
and that can be a great thing.
But we must put temperance
over righteousness.
And guide lost children
to the good path
at a pace that seems slow
even for us.
Do not forget the true
reason you have honed
your fighting ability
is to strengthen your mind
for your journey
toward enlightenment.
Being gods does not
make us perfect.
We too must learn
and mature over time.
Reflect on our discussion
as you make more tea.
Merely watching.
That's a sin, too.
Don't you see?
[BULMA] Okay guys,
get ready to be impressed!
[laughing]
Duh, duh duh duh!
Wow, it looks brand new!
Of course, we're the ones
who polished it!
[MAI, SHOU]
I can't feel my hands!
Yeah and I helped some too!
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Mom, I can't thank you enough.
[VEGETA]
C'mon, Trunks.
Let's go.
Right!
[BULMA] Vegeta, Goku.
Look after my boy, okay?
[GOKU groans]
My head!
I was staring out the window
and it made me dizzy.
Moron.
[GOKU]
So this is your future, huh?
Wow. Looks way worse
than I thought.
[FUTURE TRUNKS gasps]
Hey, Trunks!
[GOKU]
Uh! Uh? Huh...
Hmm.
[VEGETA]
What's wrong?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
This is Mai's.
She was lying
right here when I left.
[GOKU]
Hm?
Aah!
Get ready!
Instant Transmission!
Two fingers placed
right between the eyes
Get ready!
My hair will stand up!
'Cause I got
all the power of a Saiyan!
Ohhhh HEY!
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! (KAMEHAMEHA!)
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! It's what you need
Feel the magic of the beat
(Woo-hoo)
DANCE! It makes you smile
Nothing else can
quite compete (yoka yoka)
So when the world is lame
Don't play that game
You know that every problem
can be answered the same
Just let go and feel the rhythm
Everybody dance
with all your might!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
After all these years
hearing about Trunks' future,
I finally get to see it myself!
Black continues to terrorize
Earth's survivors,
but they've held on this long
'cause they believe in Trunks,
and now Vegeta and I are here
to give them the help they need.
But with Black's new power up,
it won't be an easy fight.
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Rematch with Goku Black!
Enter Super Saiyan Rosé."
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?