♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[footsteps]
[keypad beeping]
[keyboard keys clicking]
[gasps]
[BULMA] It's gonna work
this time. I'm positive!
[grunts]
[BULMA] I know time travel
is against the laws
of the universe
or whatever, but still!
Trying something everyone
says can't or shouldn't
be done is the whole point
of being a scientist.
Heck, I already built one.
Well, future me did.
Point is, there's no reason
I shouldn't be able to do this.
[BULMA] Please work,
please work, please work.
What? Another failure?
Ugh! Why is it
so hard to start up?
It must have something
to do with this part.
It's the only piece made of
a material from the future.
[BULMA grunts]
No way. I can't give up now!
There has to be a present-day
substitute I can use.
[NARRATOR]
"Come Forth, Shenron!
Whose Wish Will Be Granted?"
Say, what? Are you really gonna
use a wish to resurrect us all?
[GOKU]
That's right, King Kai!
I realized I've put it off
for way too long.
Besides, the last time
we called Shenron,
we only used one wish
to ask him where
the Super Dragon Balls were.
So I'll just summon him up
again and use another wish
to bring you guys back to life!
[KING KAI]
Uh... Oh, Goku!
I'd resigned myself
to being stuck in this form
for the rest of eternity!
[sobbing]
It's nice to know
you were thinking about me--
I'm so touched!
[BUBBLES hollers]
I can't breathe. King Kai.
Will you please let go of me.
[KING KAI]
Sorry, I got carried away.
[GOKU]
Water. Water. I need water.
You say you'll bring us back.
But how can we trust you on that
when something always seems
to come up at the last second?
[KING KAI, BUBBLES]
Uuuuh...
[GOKU]
Ah!
Look, don't worry,
it's gonna happen this time.
What could possibly go wrong?
[chuckles]
[keyboard keys clicking]
Hey, a perfect match!
All I have to do
is find the element
and I can finish
the time machine!
All right, let me find
the nearest supply.
What? Under the surface?
Near the core?
--Yo!
--Oh hey. What's up, Goku.
[screams]
Uh, hold on!
Uh. Nothing to see here!
[chuckles]
[GOKU]
Uh?
[BULMA]
What is wrong with you?!
How is it possible you've
been alive for this long
and you still don't know
you have to knock first!
Sorry, but how am I
supposed to knock
when I'm using
Instant Transmission?
Fine. In the future,
just call ahead, okay?
So why'd you come to see me?
Mind if I borrow your
Dragon Radar for a bit?
Uh. Uh, yeah, I guess so.
Here ya go.
[GOKU]
Thanks a lot, Bulma.
[BULMA]
So once the dragon gets here,
what are you gonna wish for?
[GOKU chuckles]
Funny you should ask.
Making good on my promise
to bring back King Kai.
I'll return this
in one piece! Bye!
[exhales]
Well, that was a close one.
If Goku finds out
I'm building a time machine,
it'll get back to Beerus.
Then I'll have
a Destroyer mad at me!
Hey, wait a minute.
If Goku summons Shenron,
I can just go to him and
wish for that crystal instead!
[radar beeping]
[GOKU]
One must be down there!
[ROSHI exhales] Things've gotten
too boring around here.
If this chair wasn't
so comfortable,
I'd say we should
find some girls.
[MARRON]
Yay! I love my new dress!
Don't dance around too much,
the floors are slippery.
'Kay!
I never realized how
much more fun it is
shopping with a little girl.
You get to dress them up in
all sorts of adorable outfits.
Isn't it great, 18?
Huh? Hey, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
[A18] I'm fine. It's just all
this shopping's made me think
how Krillin never
wants anything for himself.
[MARRON giggles]
He's always doing something
nice for me and Marron
or giving us presents.
I say it's time we get
something for your daddy.
I just don't know what.
Shopping for others
isn't my strong suit.
[CHICHI] Well, no matter what
you get, I'm sure he'll love it.
[BULMA slurps]
[BULMA]
What's taking him so long?
Hello, Bulma.
You're looking well.
[gasps]
Whis and Lord Beerus?
Don't be mad, I can explain.
Explain what?
[BOTH]
Mmm.
We're rather hungry and
were wondering if you could
serve us one of
your delicious meals.
You're here for food?
Yeah. Okay, sure.
[laughs]
Right. I just meant
don't be mad 'cause
the food's not ready yet!
Of course you came to eat,
'cause there's nothing else
to see down here!
[BULMA] Gotta play it cool.
I can't have Beerus
get suspicious and
start looking around in my lab.
And what is with these two
always showing up
at the worst possible times?
Great. Now I gotta
find them a big spread,
make sure they eat fast,
and then get them to leave.
And all before Goku returns
with the Dragon Balls.
Okay! I know just the place!
[WHIS gasps]
[giggles]
This might just be the most
tender crustacean meat
in the entire
Seventh Universe, my lord!
And look at this one, Whis.
I can still make the claw move!
[BULMA] Just eat your damn food
and get outta here! Sheesh!
[GOKU grunts]
Great. I got all seven.
Time to get back.
[GOKU]
Bulma! I'm done!
Yo, Bulma!
Where are you?
Guess she's not here.
Well, too bad!
All right, let's do this guys!
Eternal Shenron!
By your name,
I summon you forth!
[thunder rumbling]
[SHENRON roaring]
Aaaah! This is it!
[BOTH gasp]
[BULMA]
Shenron?
[ALL gasp]
[TURTLE, ROSHI]
Oooh.
[PUAR, OOLONG]
[BULMA]
Um, sorry Lord Beerus, I, uh,
have an important thing
to do now. But, take your time!
[BULMA]
Keep the change.
From all this cash?!
Wow. This meat does not
want to come out.
Try this, sir. The Earthlings
have invented a tool
for just such a problem,
which I call
"The Crustacean Thigh
and Leg Extraction Fork".
--Catchy, right?
--Wait, what was that?
Like I said, sir,
The Crustacean Thigh
and Leg Extraction Fork.
All right now. Speak your wish
and I shall grant it.
The last time you
summoned me, I granted one.
That means two wishes remain.
Now, speak your next wish.
Yes! He'll bring us back
any second now!
Okay, my wish is for
everyone on King Kai's world--
[A18]
Hold on a second!
[ALL]
Uuh!
[GOKU]
What?
O great, Shenron-- Nggh!
[ROSHI]
Oh no you don't, piggie!
You haven't even
heard my wish yet!
We'd be fools
to let you wish again.
Don't think we've forgotten
your Shenron history.
The world's most comfortable
pair of ultra soft underwear!
[SHENRON]
Your wish is granted.
[BOTH grunting]
So, Goku.Why did you
summon Shenron?
What do you need
to wish for now?
[GOKU] I'm gonna bring King Kai
and his pals back to life!
Do it! Do it!
[A18]
Wait, that's it?
Then that still leaves
one wish, doesn't it?
That's right.
Then I want that
last wish for myself!
[ROSHI]
No, I wanna take it!
We can't waste a wish on you!
You'll use it to surround
yourself with
a bunch of party girls!
You don't know that!
[A18]
My wish is for Krillin.
You understand wanting
to do something nice
for your spouse, right Goku?
[GOKU]
Uh, I guess.
[ROSHI] Hey, what's
so wrong about an old man
finally getting what
he's always wanted?
[OOLONG]
This is pig-scrimination!
They are all so embarrassing.
Ugh! What is your next wish!
--[A18, OOLONG, ROSHI chatting]
--[GOKU chuckles nervously]
[PILAF chuckles]
My dream of world domination
is one wish away
from coming true!
All the time we've spent
at Capsule Corp.
as virtual prisoners,
forced to be good citizens,
has led to this
one moment of redemption!
Considering we eat free
gourmet meals every day
and don't pay rent, I don't
think it's been all that bad.
Eh! Yes, Shu, that is
a fair point. But that's done!
I want you both
to remember this moment
as the rebirth of Emperor Pilaf.
Pilaf's back! Oh, Shenron!
A word, please!
[TRUNKS]
Coming in hot!
[PILAF groaning]
[BOTH]
Emperor Pilaf!
Trunks and Goten, too?
[TRUNKS] We saw the sky
go dark, so we had to come!
[GOTEN]
Did you make a wish yet, Dad?
[GOKU]
I haven't had a chance.
Well, good. We've got a big one
we want Shenron to grant!
Why should your wish
go to the front of the line?
Because we're sick and
tired of having to watch
you grown-ups always
get your wishes granted!
It's about time us kids
finally get some face time
with Shenron, right Goten?
[GOTEN]
Uh-huh.
[A18]
Sorry, you're not allowed.
It's bad for a child
to think he can get
anything he wants in life
simply by wishing for it,
rather than putting in
actual hard work.
[ROSHI]
Mm-Hm. 18's right, boys.
When you're young,
you work hard.
When you're old, you par-tay.
That doesn't sound fair!
Aw, c'mon, 18!
[A18]
I said, "no," and I mean it!
[OOLONG]
He-heh. Now's my chance--
I told you, you're wishin'
days are over, pig!
Roshi! You're choking me,
you crazy old bastard!
[SHENRON] I don't care who,
but one of you should hurry
and make a wish!
[ALL chatting]
N-No. Y-You're just
talking over one--
[SHENRON growls]
[MAI, SHU]
Pull, two three!
[BOTH]
Come on already!
[PILAF yells]
[PILAF groaning]
Emperor Pilaf!
[MAI]
Your Majesty, are you okay?
Leave me alone, I'm fine!
No one expects
to be blind-sided,
but this time
I'll be ready for it.
[PILAF panting]
Shenron! Wait!
[GOHAN]
Hold on! It's an emergency!
[hollering]
Emperor Pilaf!
Gohan?
[GOHAN]
Hey. Are there any wishes left?
Yeah.
[GOHAN] Oh, good.
Pan's had a fever all day
and it's getting worse.
Oh, no!
--[PAN panting]
--[GOKU] Poor little thing!
I took her to the doctor,
but nothing they did worked.
I think her being
part Saiyan makes it
hard to find
an effective medicine.
Do you mind if I use
a wish to ask Shenron
to make her all better?
[A18] Gohan, of course not.
Go right up there!
We would never say no to Pan!
[TRUNKS, GOTEN, ROSHI]
Uh-huh!
You guys are the best!
[GOKU]
Well, go!
[GOHAN]
Right!
Shenron! I wish for you
to restore Pan's health!
[panting]
That is a simple wish to grant.
[giggles]
You okay?
[PAN giggling]
[GOTEN]
Good job, bro!
[TRUNKS]
All right, Pan!
Your wish has been granted.
[PAN giggles]
[A18]
You're a good dad, Gohan.
Thanks. And you guys
are good friends.
Well, better get back.
Videl's waiting for us!
[chuckles]
What a nice moment.
Now, speak your final wish!
[A18]
Great, there's only one left!
[ALL groan]
[ROSHI] If you had any
respect for your elders...
[OOLONG] Please don't tell me
we have to fight for it now!
I'm sorry about that, guys.
But this last one is for me.
All your wishes will have
to wait for the next time
we summon Shenron, and you
can decide who has dibs then!
[ALL groan]
I hope you're listening
up there, King Kai,
'cause I'm finally
gonna fix you!
Ready when you are, Goku!
[GOKU]
Yo, Shenron!
Here's my wish: I want the three
people on King Kai's world to--
[A18]
Wait, wait, wait, wait, stop!
[KING KAI]
Mm?
[A18] If you're waiting this
long to bring back King Kai,
can't we wait a little longer?
[ROSHI] Yeah! 18's gotta
good point, Goku!
--[KING KAI groans]
--Put that wish back in play.
[OOLONG]
He's not going anywhere.
Bring him back next time.
Guys, c'mon, this isn't fair!
[GOKU] No way! I made
a promise to King Kai!
[OOLONG] If it's not on paper,
it doesn't count.
[ROSHI] Yeah, no judge
would enforce that.
[A18] I don't even know why
he'd want to be revived.
I'm sure the halo
looks great on him.
Anyway, can we
talk about my wish--
[TRUNKS] Pan got a wish
and she's younger than us.
What gives?!
All of you, shut up!
--[ALL gasp]
--[GOKU] King Kai?
[KING KAI]
How are all of you this selfish?
Goku got the Dragon Balls
to fulfill his promise
and fix what he did to me. Me !
Who is your King Kai by the way!
[GREGORY]
Do it, Goku! Make your wish!
[A18] But why do you guys even
need to be brought back to life?
Does it really
make any difference
whether you're alive or dead?
[KING KAI]
It feels different!
What, "It feels different"?
Well, my reason is
way better than that!
And my wish for party girls
is better than her wish!
And mine's better than his!
--[ROSHI, OOLONG, A18 chatter]
--[ALL] Uuuuh...
We're going to be here
all day, aren't we?
[PILAF groaning]
Unbelievable.
I can understand once,
but getting blindsided twice?
Um, sir, maybe you
should take all this
as a sign to sit this one out?
It just doesn't feel
like it's your day.
Hey, cram it! I'm not giving up
over a couple speed bumps!
Okay! Third time's
the charm, kids.
Shenron! I'm coming!
[BULMA] Hey, wait!
Don't wish for anything yet!
[PILAF groans]
[PILAF] You guys're right.
I will let this one go.
[GOKU]
Whoa, Bulma?
So, if Shenron is here,
I'm assuming there's
at least one wish left, right?
Well, sorry, guys,
I'm taking it!
[ALL]
Huh?
[BULMA]
Don't act all surprised!
If it wasn't for my Radar,
Goku wouldn't've
found the Dragon Balls to summon
Shenron in the first place!
Whoa! No fair, Mom!
We got here first!
Yeah, Trunks is right!
That's why I'm asking Shenron
to help me find out
what Krillin wants!
[BULMA]
Why go through all that trouble?
If you forgot this wishing
business and just asked him,
do you know what he'd say?
[A18]
Uh?
[imitating KRILLING]
So long as I have my perfect 18
and Marron in my life,
I have everything
a man could ask for!
[BULMA] If there's one thing I
know, it's men. Oh, and science.
Are-Are you sure?
Yeah, of course!
I guess that does sound
like something he'd say.
Oh, I know.
Forget talking to Shenron
and hurry home to Krillin.
Being with him is the
best present you can give.
You're right, Bulma.
Next! What do you want?
A pink car full of hotties!
Not once have you
ever surprised me.
For ten million zeni,
can you send over a pink car
filled with girls in bikinis?
[ROSHI]
Eeeh?
[GIRLS chatting, giggling]
[ROSHI]
Ah-haaaa!
Not bad, Bulma.
You've become an even better
wish-granter than Shenron!
[SHENRON scoffs]
[OOLONG]
Bulma, do me next!
It's new undies, right?
[OOLONG]
No! This time's different!
18, if you get rid of this
weirdo, all this is yours.
Done and done!
[OOLONG] But I never told you
what my wish was!
[BULMA] What about you two?
What'd you come for?
We came to ask Shenron for--
Uh... What?
Yeah, what do we want?
If you want a wish granted,
you need a wish.
[TRUNKS] I know! We just never
figured out that part.
Well, then good luck.
When you finally have something,
come back to me,
and maybe I can help.
In the meantime, I think
I'll take your spot for myself.
[BOTH]
Uuh!
And with that, I can get
my wish granted.
I still haven't had
[BULMA] What? I thought
you already went?
[laughing]
Nope. It's a long story.
[BULMA grunts]
[BULMA]
Okay, how 'bout this?
Go deep under
the earth's surface
and find this rare crystal.
If you can bring it back to me,
I'll let you have
the the last wish.
Whoa, the center of the earth?
It seems like it could be
dangerous down there,
even for me.
You should be okay,
as long as you wear
one of our newly developed
pressure suits.
[GOKU] Hmm. All right,
you got a deal.
[SHENRON] Unfortunately,
there is no time for that.
I must go now.
Are you serious?! You can't
wait just a little longer?
No. Time's up.
Okay. But I'm warning you,
if you go, I'll have
no choice but to tell
Lord Beerus that
you were rude to us.
[SHENRON]
He's here? Mmmm.
[BEERUS laughing]
[SHENRON]
Lord Beerus!
Fine, I-I'll stay!
But only for a little bit, okay!
[BULMA]
Aw, thank you!
Suit up, Goku! You're goin' in!
[SHENRON] Make it snappy!
I've been here too long!
Right. I'll try.
[WHIS]
Uh! Wow. Yummy.
Well, Lord Beerus, if you're
full, we should be going.
Oh, Chef! Your seafood
was scrumptious!
Took a little work to get it
out of the shell, though.
[CHEF 68A]
Thank you! Enjoy the night!
My only disappointment
was that Bulma could not
stay and eat with us.
I'm curious as to
where she ran off to.
[BEERUS] Maybe it had
something to do with Shenron.
[WHIS] I sense Goku's
up to something, as well.
[GOKU] Hm. Looks pretty
close to the picture.
[gasps]
Lord Beerus?
Goku. What exactly
are you doing here
at the center of the earth?
--[TRUNKS gasps, grunting]
--[GOTEN laughing]
--[ROSHI groaning]
--[GIRLS giggling]
So, um, do you think
Goku will be much longer?
[BULMA]
Just be patient!
You don't understand.
My body's about to disappear.
Hey, nice timing, Dad!
Yeah, and he brought
Lord Beerus and Whis!
This is bad.
Oh, uh, uh, hey, Lord Beerus.
Hello. What a pleasant surprise.
[BEERUS] Why are you
acting all nervous?
Nervous? Oh. I-I'm not nervous.
[BEERUS]
Okay.
[BULMA whispering]
Hey, Goku! Over here!
Well, come on. Did you
get the crystal or not?
Yeah, there was a small hiccup.
Bulma, this is the element
you wanted, is it not?
You sent Goku on a very
dangerous journey for this,
so it must be critical
to whatever it is
you're working on.
Very suspicious.
I hope this doesn't mean
you've secretly been
building a time machine.
Is it possible you still
don't understand the severity
of altering the flow of time?
Well, there are so many rules--
who can keep track of them all?!
[BEERUS grunts]
[BULMA shrieks]
Forgive me! I won't time
travel anymore! I promise!
[BEERUS] Good to hear! And just
so you're not tempted...
[ALL gasp]
[BULMA]
Uuuuuh! My time machine!
[KING KAI]
Goku! Make the wish!
Oh, right! King Kai!
I almost forgot!
Hey, Shenron! I wish for
everyone on King Kai's world--
[SHENRON]
No. I can't take it anymore!
--[GOKU] What?
--[ALL gasp]
[yawns]
Sorry about that, King Kai!
He left before I could finish.
I'll get ya next time, buddy.
Goku, you moron!
How many times did I tell you
to make the damn wish?!
♪ Closing Song ♪
1, 2, 3, I'm hungry
Nothin' but fried rice fantasies
I got a passion for the dish
Nothin' compares to what it is
I don't get my fill
I'm like a monster
Those ingredients
No one could possibly resist
They got me so bewitched
Make it spicy and I can't say no
Seasoning is everything,
I think so
Bon Appetit
I'll burn the world
straight to the ground
If I can't have
that greasy mound
My hanger's not to be ignored!
1, 2, 3, I'm hungry
Nothin' but fried rice fantasies
I want fried rice,
I'm so hungryyyyyy-yeah!
[ARALE]
Hi-hi-hi! It's Arale!
If you folks enjoyed
today's episode,
you're gonna love the next one.
Why? Because I'm
a special guest!
And get this: I have a showdown
with a crazy-powerful person!
Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy!
[GOKU] Hey, is the
"crazy-powerful person" me?
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Goku vs. Arale!
An Off-the-Wall Battle
Spells the End of the Earth?"
[ARALE]
Be sure to watch, m'kay?
Bye-bye-bye!