♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Super,
Goku and Vegeta
joined Trunks in his future,
and encountered
Goku Black and Zamasu.
[GOKU]
I thought you were decent,
but you're scheming with Black!
We are more like comrades
on a righteous crusade.
[NARRATOR] Goku and Trunks
challenged Zamasu
and Goku Black,
unleashing incredible attacks.
But the Kai from
the Tenth Universe
revealed a daunting defense.
I've taken godhood
to a new level.
Divinity made perfect.
--This is your end!
--Die, Saiyans!
[NARRATOR]
Overwhelmed and defeated,
Goku, Trunks, and Vegeta were
rescued by Mai and Yajirobe,
and returned to
the present timeline,
where more danger was brewing.
Zamasu in the present
had begun an ominous quest.
What I want
is for you to tell me
about the Super Dragon Balls.
[NARRATOR] "Zamasu and Black.
The Duo's Mystery Deepens."
[ZUNO] Very well. I shall give
you a comprehensive answer
on these cosmic artifacts.
Super Dragon Balls
are called "wish orbs."
They were created in the year
41 of the Divine Calendar
by the dragon god, Zalama.
And they are
perfectly spherical,
planet-sized celestial objects,
measuring exactly
37,196.2204 kilometers
in diameter.
Super Dragon Balls are rare
and only number seven.
They are divided between the
Sixth and Seventh Universes.
A-hem!
In the center of
each pale yellow sphere
is a unique arrangement
of red star-shaped markings,
numbering them
one through seven--
[hollers]
I am a Supreme Kai in training.
And I can easily
eliminate you if I choose,
so I suggest
you don't waste my time.
But you requested that
I tell you everything I know
about the Super Dragon Balls,
which is precisely
what I'm doing!
Just skip the trivia
and tell me how to use them!
Oh! Yes of course, I'm sorry!
[gulps]
Using them is quite easy.
But first you must locate them,
spread across the vast expanse
of the Sixth and
Seventh Universes,
and gather them all together
in preparation of the summoning.
Then once they've
been collected,
you must speak
in the divine tongue.
You must recite the phrase,
"Come forth, divine dragon
and grant my wish,
peas and carrots."
Peas and carrots? Really?
That's the grand phrase. Yes.
[ZAMASU grunts]
Once you say that,
the Divine Dragon
will be summoned forth
and grant you any single wish
that you desire
without limitation.
After that wish is fulfilled,
the Super Dragon Balls
will be dispersed again across
universes Six and Seven,
and wait in silence
for another seeker
with an unfulfilled wish
to gather them again.
Where exactly are they
waiting in silence now, sage?
I'm afraid I can say no more.
[hollers]
[ZAMASU]
You will if you wish to live.
Uh. But even if
you can locate them now
they won't help you, for a
summoning occurred too recently.
The brilliant celestial glow
of their power has faded
and their efficacy is gone.
So how much time before
they can be used again?
The span between the birth
and death of a cockroach.
[ZAMASU]
What?
That means nearly
one year from now.
Almost a year? You sure?
You will have to wait, Kai.
Have patience.
[ZAMASU]
You will tell me precisely
where the orbs have gone.
I what?
[ZAMASU] That's not all. I want
to hear everything you know
about the mortal named Goku.
[gasps]
The Saiyan Goku?
[BULMA sighs]
Feeling any better?
It's good to be back.
[GOKU groaning]
How could we
have lost so badly?
All right!
Now I'm ready for the rematch!
[growls]
[BULMA]
You idiot!
I put all that work into getting
the time machine and fuel ready,
then you ran into battle without
even taking the senzu beans?
Hey, easy, Mom.
Oh, yeah, I guess
we did screw that up.
So where'd you find that bag?
Are you sure you want me
to answer that, Goku?
[TRUNKS]
Up on the toilet.
Oh! Yeah, that makes sense.
I think I had to use the
bathroom right before we left.
You are unbelievable.
Sorry, you guys,
that was my fault.
The understatement of the year!
So Black still won?
Even when it was all three
of you guys against him?
Well, we weren't
just fighting Black.
What?
Are you telling us
he's got an ally now?
[MAI, PILAF, SHOU gasp]
--But who?
--Zamasu was there.
We had to fight both of them.
Okay, wait a second? Zamasu?
He's the Supreme Kai
in training from Universe Ten
with the energy that felt
kind-a like Black's, isn't he?
[GOKU]
That's him all right.
I thought he was good,
like the other Kais.
But he's an enemy,
and a strong one.
That's weird. You guys
thought he was Black,
but he's working
with him instead?
What's more, he's invincible.
[gasps]
[ALL]
Invincible?
So you mean he can't be hurt?
Why, because he's a god?
Not even deities are
supposed to be invincible.
Yeah and that's not
the only problem, either.
Black already figured out
a ridiculous new level
of Super Saiyan.
What? He's a Super Saiyan?
So what level did he reach?
He's calling it Super Saiyan--
Uh! What was it called again?
--Rosé, fool.
--Ooh!
That's right, Rosé.
Rosé? So of all the names
for what you're implying
is the fiercest level
ever reached, he went with
Super Saiyan Rosé,
like, on purpose?
[TRUNKS]
Uh...
Let's go. We've gotta
get back there!
[BULMA] Hold on!
Do you even have a plan?
How do you intend
to defeat an enemy
whose body does not
sustain damage?
C'mon, we'll think of something.
Think of what, you imbecile?
There's no way!
Maybe we'll all
become invincible, too.
Wait a sec.
What do you mean by that?
You really think
that's possible?
Yeah, you betcha.
We just need to bring
an all-you-can-eat buffet
of senzu beans!
[ALL groan]
[VEGETA] Where the hell
are you gonna find
that many senzu beans?
[BULMA] Oh and this
coming from the guy
who forgot all of them
on the toilet!
[GOKU] Well, obviously
I won't forget 'em this time!
[BULMA] In no way
is that obvious with you!
[footsteps]
Mai, can we talk?
There's something I have to tell
you before I lose the chance.
Go, go!
Yeah, sure, what's up?
The you in my future,
turns out she survived.
--[TRUNKS, MAI, SHOU gasp]
--Seriously?
[SHOU]
Here come the happy tears!
--[FUTURE TRUNKS sniffles]
--[PILAF, SHOU] Uh?
So then what?
What happened to her?
I'm sorry. We only
barely made it back,
and I couldn't
convince her to join us.
Does that mean--?
You've got nothing
to worry about, Mai.
Your future self isn't
gonna give up that easily.
Yeah, the kid's right!
Your future self
is super strong!
'Course we've never
actually met her.
Yeah. I know she'll make it--
she's proven that much.
She's helped me escape
to this time twice now.
And I'm gonna stop those
monsters and return the favor.
Sounds good.
But if Zamasu's invincible,
how can you win?
[WHIS]
Good evening.
Whoa, you're back!
And this time you've got
Supreme Kai with you, too?
[WHIS]
Please forgive the intrusion.
But do you know
if Goku is nearby?
Our most honorable Supreme Kai
tells us there's something
he needs to say to him.
It's most important.
[WHIS]
Mm!
Aaah!
What is this?
[MAI, PILAF, SHOU chuckle]
[GOKU] Yo, Supreme Kai. Did you
need to tell me somethin'?
If the Kai charged with
overseeing our whole universe
has come all the way
here to talk,
I'm pretty sure
it won't be good.
As it so happens,
I received a message
from an expert collector
of information named Zuno.
You mean Master Zuno?
How's he doing these days?
He's doing fine now, I suppose.
But according to his message,
someone travelled
an incredibly long distance
to ask him about
the Super Dragon Balls.
And about Goku.
Somebody asked about me?
Do you know who it is?
Your old pal Zamasu.
Zamasu, really?
Why would he be asking
about the Super Dragon Balls?
Sounds like we have
something we need
to share with you, too, then.
And just what
would that be, Saiyan?
My goodness,
is it empty already?
Zamasu, I'm in need
of another pot of tea!
Zamasu?
Where in the world did he go?
Zamasu assaulted you?
And he's literally invincible?
A transformation called
Super Saiyan Rosé?
That sounds like a tasty
flavor of ice cream.
--[BEERUS chuckles]
--[SUPREME KAI gasps]
Considering what
we're dealing with,
we could really use your advice.
How do you get rid of a deity?
Goodness. That's a
rather casual request
for something so dreadful.
I could take that as a threat
against me, too, Bulma.
Come on, you know
this is an emergency!
[BULMA, BEERUS growling]
Well, this is perplexing.
If Zamasu and Black aren't
the same being after all...
...then why are their
energies so much alike?
Two individuals could have
similar energies by coincidence.
Indeed, but the odds
would be most extraordinary.
There are two stories here.
Zuno's and Goku's
from the future.
Put together, they suggest
some intriguing possibilities.
[BULMA]
Huh?
Sounds like you've got a theory.
What are you
waiting for? Tell us!
She's right, Whis. Stop milking
the drama and speak.
Of course.
Consider what we know
has transpired
in the two timelines.
Zamasu, a Kai heralded for
his gifts as a fighter,
was defeated by Goku
in a sparring match
and has since gone out of
his way to question Zuno
about the Saiyan,
suggesting a strong fixation.
Why research an opponent
who bested him?
Could he want
that power for himself?
Perhaps he imagines
he could accomplish
his own ambitions
with such might.
His own brand of justice.
I believe Zamasu
seeks a collaborator
with the offensive power
he's realized he lacks.
He also would like to make
himself harder to defeat.
His intention
is to achieve both.
[gasps]
Oh, yeah and I know how.
--You do?
--[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[ALL gasp]
He'll use the Super
Dragon Balls, won't he?
Yes. That's correct, Goku.
He'll need the great power
of those orbs
to get what he desires.
[ALL cheering]
Wow, it's rare for you
to use your cranium
for something other
than a head-butt.
Think! That dragon can grant
any wish Zamasu makes,
which explains
the mystery we haven't
been able to crack
since this started.
He's going to wish
for Goku Black.
[ALL gasp]
Are you sure?
Well, no. It's just a guess.
[BULMA groans]
A good guess.
I think you're right, Goku--
well, more or less.
[ALL shriek]
--[BEERUS] Hm!
--Oh yeah!
You guys hear that? I am right!
Am I awesome or what?
[BULMA] This is no time
for a victory lap!
There's a bad guy out there
with the same strength as you,
and we don't know
how to stop him!
Of course at this point, this is
nothing more than a theory.
But it fits what we know so far.
Black could be
a magical copy of Goku,
created with the limitless power
of the Super Dragon Balls.
Give me a servant
who possesses the same body
and fighting power
as the Saiyan Goku!
It explains things well,
for the most part.
You're saying Black
is Kakarot's doppleganger?
Yeah, but why would this
Zamasu-guy pick Goku?
Like I said,
Goku defeated Zamasu
in battle when we visited.
The Kai must have taken
special interest in him then.
So this is your fault
for picking another fight?
Aw come on, I wouldn't
exactly put it like that.
And then
after Black is created,
Zamasu will wait
for another year.
Until the Super Dragon Balls
become active once again.
Emoc hitirof, enivid nogarid,
dina tinarig yim sihiwi.
Peas and carrots.
[ZAMASU] Give unto me
the power of invincibility!
[chuckles]
Now I'm ready.
[ZAMASU]
I have an invincible body
and the offensive power of Goku
to eliminate all mortals!
At last I have the means
to carry out divine justice.
Once empowered,
Zamasu and Black will launch
their attack on the earth
in Trunks' future.
Waiting a year between wishes
would take some real patience.
Yeah, as angry
as he must be,
it's hard to believe
he'd wait that long.
Plus all the time tracking down
the Super Dragon Balls,
not once but twice?
It's hard enough
to search a planet,
let alone across two universes!
That's some major perseverance.
I'd get way too bored.
But wait, of course!
He has that Time Ring!
If he uses that handy thing,
then he wouldn't have to wait
a year between wishes!
That's correct, my lord.
He could simply travel
a year into
the future instantly.
But Black's the one
wearing it, right?
How'd he get to use it?
[BEERUS groans]
I hate riddles.
Why can't you ask him yourself?
Well, I guess if Zamasu gets it,
then he could let Black
borrow it, couldn't he?
[BEERUS grunts]
We've already covered this--
Time Rings can only
be used by Supreme Kais.
It's not like checking
things out from a library.
Plus, the Zamasu in our time
is only a Supreme Kai
in training--
he couldn't use it either.
So this neat little theory
still doesn't explain the Ring.
We don't know
how Black wears it,
but we can explain
how Zamasu does.
He's either named Supreme Kai
between now and then,
or he takes the title.
[GOKU, BULMA, VEGETA]
Hm?
--Uh, takes it how?
--By being a very wicked Kai.
--You don't mean...
--[GOKU] Uh.
You believe Gowasu, Supreme Kai
of the Tenth Universe,
is in imminent danger, is that
what you're suggesting?
Okay, I missed that.
Why would he be in danger?
Why don't you use
that brilliance you showed us
a minute ago and think!
[GOKU]
Hmmm...
Oh, come on! It's obvious!
Zamasu is prob'ly
gonna kill his master
to become the new Supreme Kai!
He'll take the Time Ring
right off Gowasu's finger,
then be able to use it
however he wants!
Is that clear enough for ya?
[GOKU]
Hmm. Wow, that's messed up.
So you really think
Zamasu's turning into
that bad of a guy, huh?
He sure fooled me.
If we're right,
Zamasu ruins my future.
And he claims it's all
in the name of justice.
Nobody who trumpets justice
ever turns out to be rightous.
--[GOKU] That's it!
--[ALL gasp]
[BULMA]
Uuh...
I'm gonna look Zamasu in
the eyes and find out for sure.
It's hardly settled.
We still haven't explained
Black wearing the Ring or why
their energies feel so alike.
True, my lord. If Black's
a copy of Goku as we suspect,
why is his energy
so akin to Zamasu's?
I trust these questions will
all be answered in due time.
But at the moment,
I'm more concerned
about ensuring Gowasu's safety.
[SUPREME KAI]
I will take you to their world.
On one condition.
I must insist
you keep this amicable.
After all, the present
Zamasu has done
nothing explicitly wrong.
Not yet.
Don't worry, Trunks.
We're gonna figure this out.
[VEGETA]
Hmph!
You'll go with them, won't you?
[VEGETA] I have no interest
in the present Zamasu.
From what I've heard,
he's just a bitter zealot
with a overblown ego.
[FUTURE MAI]
Hurry up!
[grunts]
Hop on!
[FUTURE YAJIROBE]
No way! I can't ride caboose
on a lady's bike!
I'd never live it down!
[FUTURE MAI] If they find us,
you won't live at all.
Come on!
[FUTURE YAJIROBE]
I did not okay this!
[hollers]
[FUTURE MAI]
Let's go!
[FUTURE YAJIROBE]
This is straight up abuse!
--[MAKI, HARU] Mai!
--[FUTURE MAI] Maki, Haru!
But where is Trunks?
And why isn't he with you?
[FUTURE MAI]
Don't worry, guys, he's safe.
And far away from here.
Lucky.
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER A]
Commander.
Is it really true
Vegeta and Goku
were no match for the enemy?
If they lost,
what chance do we have?
It's not over. It was one fight.
Yeah! Haven't you guys
heard of a strategic retreat?
There's no hope left--
they're just too strong.
[MALE REFUGEE A] I can't
believe there's two of them now.
--What do we do?
--How can we stop them?
It's just a matter of time.
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER B]
You actually think Trunks
and the others
will come back?
Why would they?
Don't say that!
Of course they will!
[RESISTANCE SOLDIER A]
Sorry, we're just-- just scared.
They've killed so many
of our friends so easily.
Maybe if we surrender...
[FUTURE MAI]
We can't give up, not ever!
There are still
other survivors out there
doing their best to hold on.
We just have to band together!
We will have faith and
wait for Trunks to get back!
We will survive!
Is that understood?
[FUTURE YAJIROBE]
So, uh, do these pep rallies
come with dinner?
[GOWASU]
Huh?
What's up?!
[GOWASU]
My, another surprise visit.
Has something happened
to bring you here?
Well first of all, I'm relieved
to see you're all right.
What does that mean?
Why wouldn't I be?
Is Zamasu here?
We would like
to see him most urgently.
I'm so sorry to disappoint you,
but I'm afraid
he's been an absentee
since early this morning.
Absentee?
And where might he be?
[GOWASU]
That's just it. I have no idea.
Tell me, has my apprentice
done something wrong?
he fact is, he's making
a big mess in the future.
[GOWASU]
Huh?
[GOKU]
Oww-ow-ow-ow!
What was that for?
I just answered him!
[BEERUS growls]
We'll do the talking, Goku!
[GOWASU]
Did he say the future?
Is there anything
about Zamasu that's been
bothering you lately, Kai?
[GOWASU]
Bothering me? How do you mean?
Talk of "divine justice,"
for example?
Ahh, divine justice.
He's still a young Kai.
I have already
put those doubts to rest.
Doubts, you say?
Zamasu is in the process
of learning his divine duties.
And in due time, he will
oversee the Tenth Universe
as its Supreme Kai,
as I have for eons.
What is the meaning
of mortality?
Of wisdom? What is
the essence of godhood?
We watch the ups and downs
of countless worlds,
and questions arise.
He and I maintain
a healthy dialogue.
[BEERUS] Questions.
That's a gentle way to put it.
And you're saying
those "questions"
have been put to rest?
[GOWASU] Yes. Right now,
his soul is perfectly clear.
For a time he was apprehensive--
about a Kai's role,
about the interplay
between good and evil,
and his own desire for justice.
But I have helped him
understand the perspective
necessary for a Supreme Kai,
and he has opened the door
that leads to enlightenment.
Huh?
Zamasu!
Gowasu, I have
brought your tea, master.
Get ready!
Instant Transmission!
Two fingers placed
right between the eyes
Get ready!
My hair will stand up!
'Cause I got
all the power of a Saiyan!
Ohhhh HEY!
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! (KAMEHAMEHA!)
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! It's what you need
Feel the magic of the beat
(Woo-hoo)
DANCE! It makes you smile
Nothing else can
quite compete (yoka yoka)
So when the world is lame
Don't play that game
You know that every problem
can be answered the same
Just let go and feel the rhythm
Everybody dance
with all your might!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And this drama in the Tenth
Universe feels pretty intense.
Does Zamasu really plan
to overthrow his own master?
Because if so, we can't just
stand here and let it happen!
We've gotta stop this guy,
but our Supreme Kai
says we need proof!
If we wait any longer, though,
it could be too late!
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Protect the Supreme Kai Gowasu.
Destroy Zamasu!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?