♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Super,
Goku went to Krillin in search
of a sparring partner.
Uh, oh! Mama's saying
Dada's a wimp!
[KRILLIN gasps]
[MARRON]
I wanna strong Daddy!
[gasps]
[chuckles]
Okay! One strong
Daddy coming up!
Train with me, Goku!
[NARRATOR] However, the gap
between Krillin and Goku's
abilities was soon
made abundantly clear.
As part of a training exercise,
Master Roshi sent
the two fighters off
to retrieve a medicinal herb,
but what Goku and Krillin
found when they arrived...
...were all the foes
that they had once faced!
The nightmarish training
ordeal continues. Now!
[NARRATOR]
"Conquer the Terrifying Foes!
Krillin's Fighting
Spirit Rebounds!"
[ALL chuckling]
[KRILLIN hollering]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[ALL chuckle]
[GOKU] Hey, what're
these guys doin' here?
What is this place?
Aw, come on,
take it easy, Krillin.
These guys are obviously
just illusions, see.
--[KRILLIN gasps]
--[GOKU] Aah!
[GOKU groans]
Are you all right?
[GOKU] Aaah! He got me
pretty good with that one.
Yeah, but there's no chance
it could be the real him, right?
Unh-unh. There's no way
Vegeta would be here.
[KRILLIN, GOKU gasp]
Come on Krillin,
let's take these guys out,
and get outta here!
[yells]
If we don't, we're never
gonna find that herb!
Yeah. I can try!
[gasps]
[KRILLIN hollering]
[KRILLIN]
Uuuh...
[KRILLIN grunts]
Uh?
[KRILLIN]
Uuuh...
Uh-uh-uh!
[KRILLIN gasping]
[hollers]
[GOKU grunts]
Krillin, I can't do this alone.
You gotta fight, too!
Yeah, but these guys are...
Uuh!
Whoa, that looks
just like Bulma.
[KRILLIN gasping]
[ROSHI]
Mmm.
[TURTLE]
Hm?
[ROSHI] Ah, sis.
I appreciate you doing this.
It ain't charity. My fee's
ten million zeni.
I see you're just as
money-grubbing as ever.
Fine, I'll just
put it on your tab.
[screaming]
What's the matter, Krillin?
This is a pretty
bold move on your part,
taking drastic
measures like this.
[A18] What do you mean,
"drastic measures"?
[BABA, ROSHI]
Uh...
Oh, uh, hey there, 18.
What's up?
Ah, it's you, the wife.
Worried about your
little hubby, eh, dearie?
Uh?
[MARRON]
Oh no, Dada's in trouble!
Hey, Dad, why aren't
you fighting back?
Knock their blocks off!
What are we watching here?
That there is
the Forest of Terror.
Well, that sounds ominous.
[BABA] It's a place nestled
somewhere between our world
and Other World, which gives
form to the memories
that haunt the deepest
recesses of our hearts.
The former rivals you see
gathered together here
are the memories of Goku and
Krillin's past battles embodied.
[A18]
They're what?
Jeez, these guys
just don't give up.
Hey, Krillin!
Let's take 'em all out
with a Kamehame-Ha from above!
Whoa, wait,
you mean even Bulma?
[GOKU] I'm tellin' you,
that's not really her!
[KRILLIN hollers]
Ya ready to do this, Krillin?
Uh, yeah.
Oh, please forgive me, Bulma!
For the last time,
that isn't Bulma!
[GOKU, KRILLIN]
Ha!
[ALL chuckle]
[panting]
You okay, Krillin?
C'mon, pull yourself together.
Okay.
All right, let's get back
to looking for that herb.
It's supposed to be a race,
after all, remember?
I just hope those guys
don't come back.
[GOKU] Man, that was
so much fun, wasn't it?
Never thought we'd get to
fight any of them again!
[KRILLIN]
Y'know, I really thought I had
a handle on your personality.
[GOKU]
Mm?
But how can you be in
such a good mood right now?
Time and time again, those
monsters all terrorized us!
Frieza, and Tambourine,
Majin Buu. They all killed me!
[panting]
Hey, buddy, are you
sure you're all right?
I'm kinda worried.
[panting]
[KRILLIN]
I'm leaving.
[GOKU] What about the herb?
The old timer's waiting for it!
[KRILLIN] This kinda
thing isn't fun for me
the way it is for you.
Yeah, but I thought you wanted
to get stronger, like me?
If it means having
to go through all this,
well, then I don't care
about that anymore!
What're you gonna do
when some bigger,
badder guys show up?
You won't be able to fight!
Then I guess
I won't be fighting.
Aw, Krillin.
[KRILLIN]
I'm scared. I...
I'm not like you, okay!
I'm just not like you!
[GOKU gasps]
Uh.
Wait, come back here!
Yo, hey, Krillin,
can't you hear me?
I said wait! Dude!
--[gasps]
--Great, now what?
Um, what's happening?
[GOKU]
Uh...
[BOTH]
Uh?
Oh, no! They're back!
Yeah, and this time
they're giant-sized.
[KRILLIN]
Uh?
--[GOKU] Aah!
--[KRILLIN] Goku!
Oh no, Krillin!
[yells]
Outta my way!
Krillin!
[groaning]
So, Master Roshi,
are you seriously not gonna
let us out of here until we
finish this so-called errand?
[KRILLIN hollering]
Man, I just can't
get away from these guys!
--[TAMBOURINE] Ah!
--[yelling]
Dada!
This is turning into
quite a show.
This is in poor taste.
Are you saying you
don't think he can take it?
[A18]
Hm.
[ROSHI]
Eh?
What is Dada doing?
Well, right now, Dada is
fighting a battle with himself.
[MARRON]
Mmm.
[inhales]
Ah!
[panting]
[KRILLIN]
I am such a dumbass.
[yelling]
[GOKU]
Jeez, there's no end to this.
All right, no more
playing around!
Uh.
[GOKU]
Wait, I think I figured it out.
[inhales]
[exhales]
Ha-ha. That's it!
Just like I thought!
All the bad guys disappeared.
Well, well. Looks like
Goku finally figured it out.
Wait, he figured what out?
Keep watching.
Let's see how long
it takes Krillin to catch on.
[KRILLIN groans]
[yells]
How many times are they
gonna keep reappearing?
[KRILLIN screams]
[GOKU]
Krillin?!
Aw! If only I could
fly to him right now.
But if I try to fly, all those
guys'll show up again.
Ooh, I know!
Hey, Flying Nimbus!
Whoa.
[chuckles]
Man, I'm surpirsed
that still works.
Whoa. Now that's usin'
the ol' noggin.
♪ Cha-la, head cha-la! ♪
All right, Nimbus, let's jet!
Hey, Krillin! Where are you?
[FRIEZAS chuckle]
[TAMBOURINES laugh]
[CELLS laugh]
[NAPPAS laugh]
I don't get it, Master Roshi.
Why are you making me fight
all these villains again?
[NAPPAS laughing]
You want me to face my past.
All of those losses
and the humiliation?
[KRILLIN]
Fine.
I will face them down!
And I will win!
[NAPPAS yell]
Solar Flare!
[KRILLIN]
What's with these guys?
Destructo Disk!
--[NAPPA yells]
--[KRILLIN yells]
Wait. That energy?
Hang on, don't tell me.
They're feeding off my power?
[birds chirping]
[KRILLIN]
It worked.
Once I cleared my head
and calmed down,
the big Nappas
stopped moving altogether.
Makes sense, 'cause
the more afraid I became,
the bigger they kept getting,
and the more there were.
I get it now, Master Roshi.
If I don't overcome
my fear of the past,
I'll just keep running from it.
I've gotta control my energy.
If I can do that, then they
won't be able to move!
All right,
time to meet the new me!
Yay, he did it!
[gasps]
Ah, good, he figured it out.
Now for one last push.
[A18]
What are you gonna do?
[BABA chuckles]
Just keep watching.
Krillin! Where are you?
What the heck was that?
[yells]
[groaning]
[SUPER DRAGON growls]
Oh, great, now Super
Shenron's here, too?
Hey, hang in there,
Nimbus buddy!
[roars]
Ugh! Oh wow, your breath
really stinks, pal!
Uh! Hey, Goku!
[GOKU]
What's up, Krillin?!
[SUPER DRAGON growls]
Super Shenron's here, too?
[GOKU]
He's fake like all the others!
This one's too small,
and his breath reeks!
What's the hold up?
You could take out
this imposter in
one shot, couldn't you?
[GOKU] Yeah prob'ly,
but a blast like that
would take out Nimbus, too!
Wait, Nimbus?
Well, don't worry,
I'm coming to save you both!
[inhales, exhales]
Whoa, are you sure?
[SUPER DRAGON roars]
Oh no, Krillin, look out!
He'll be fine down there.
No need to worry.
Krillin is just trying to rise
above himself, that's all.
What do you mean?
[KRILLIN exhales]
Here goes!
[SUPER DRAGON growls]
[yells]
[SUPER DRAGON roars]
[GOKU]
That was awesome, Krillin!
Nice catch, Nimbus!
Thanks for rescuing me!
[roars]
All right, let's do this!
Sure thing!
[SUPER DRAGON roars]
[GOKU, KRILLIN]
Ka... me... ha... me...
Ha!
[SUPER DRAGON roars]
It's the paradise herb!
Check it out, Krillin!
They're sprouting up like weeds!
Didja see how strong he was?
Yeah.
[BABA, ROSHI chuckling]
The old man's gonna be floored
when he sees how many we got.
--Hey.
--[GOKU] Hm?
So that ability you
have to stay positive
and keep smiling,
no matter what comes your way
or how bad things get.
Well, that's the real strength
I want for myself.
Oh, really?
Which is why I've decided
to become a fighter again.
For my own sake. Heh.
Okay, and I want my daughter
to be proud of me.
[GOKU]
Uh... Yeah, Krillin, uh.
[KRILLIN]
Hm?
I don't have the
slightest idea what you're
tryin' to tell me, buddy.
--[KRILLIN groans] Seriously?
--[GOKU] Sorry.
[KRILLIN] I put a lotta
thought in that hero speech!
[chuckles]
[gasps]
What are you doing here?
18.
[MARRON]
Daddy! I saw you!
And you were
so strong and brave!
[BABA, ROSHI chuckle]
You watched me the whole time?
We did.
Hot damn! You boys
really outdid yourselves.
Yeah, we really didn't compete
against each other, though.
You don't say. In that case,
guess I won't be teaching
either of you the secret
to super-charging your energy.
You're just gonna
keep it to yourself?
Heck, if something
like that actually exists,
I sure do hope someone
tells me about it.
What? There's no secret?
So what you're saying is,
you were just wasting
their time with this?
No. I mean, it's--
[KRILLIN]
It's not like that, 18.
[GOKU, ROSHI, A18]
Huh?
It's about
controlling our energy.
Isn't that right, Goku?
Yeah, that's right.
Once we calmed down
and reigned in our energy,
Frieza and the rest
just disappeared.
That's what Master Roshi
wanted me to get
outta this all along.
Somehow, you knew
everything that I needed.
[laughing]
Why, of course I did!
I wouldn't go so far
as to say he knew everything .
So you don't even
need these herbs, do you?
[ROSHI]
Well, I wouldn't say that!
Jeez, you look
like a cow, old man!
Ya-haaa!
Wow, talk about an energy boost!
I feel younger already!
I could live
for a thousand years!
[BABA] Well, you'd better.
It might just take you
that long to pay off
my assistance fee in full.
Aw, why couldn't I have a sister
who likes to help me for free?
[GOKU chuckles]
--[KRILLIN] Hey, Goku!
--[GOKU] Huh?
Looking forward
to continuing our training.
[GOKU]
Hm. Good.
--[buzzing]
--[giggling]
There, all done.
Wow! It's so smooth!
You think your old man
looks cool, Marron?
[MARRON]
Super cool!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[GOKU]
Heya, Krillin!
Hey, what's up?
I gotta do some training
and I'm gonna need a partner.
How'd you like to
spar with me again?
Count me in.
There's just one thing.
Oh yeah, what is it?
No turning Super Saiyan on me.
[laughs]
An angel and a demon sit
One to my right,
one to my left
In between I'm tryin'
to figure out the right way
Is one way good?
Is one way bad?
Too much confusion in my head
I can't think with all
this noise, I'm goin' crazy
Is there any way to know
what's right or wrong?
Demons in an angel mask
Hopin' that I'll do
just what they ask
Telling me
they know what's right
Lead me to the light
"For the sake of everyone
You have to destroy
the evil ones
That's the only path, you see"
So they said to me
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Yo, Vegeta, let's go do some
more training with Whis.
Huh, whaddaya mean,
you're not coming?
What's gotten into you?
Does this have
something to do with
Bulma's tummy getting bigger?
All right, I can't
take it anymore!
I'm just gonna
go ahead and ask Zenny
to hold another tournament.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Let's Do It, Grand Zeno!
The Universes' Best Tournament!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?