Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me go back to the start
Wishing on the starlight
In the sky, let's paint a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of God
Kyo-Let's☆Mo-Let's☆Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic
I don't care 'bout limits, no regret
Make me tougher even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo' try me
So-Zets☆Cho-Zets☆Dynamic!
Let's Go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going power pumpin' up
something greater waiting not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the Tournament of Destroyers
was about to begin!
And as Goku and friends arrived
at the Planet With No Name,
they all saw the majesty
of the gigantic
Super Dragon Balls
floating in space.
So, those are
the Super Dragon Balls?
Man, they're huge!
They really are
the Super Dragon Balls!
[NARRATOR] But, already
waiting on the planet below
were our heroes' counterparts,
and their tournament opponents,
from the Sixth Universe!
That looks like a robot--
isn't that cheating?
But I don't know, maybe he's
some kind of robot-like person?
Goku, look!
Ah! Whoa,
that looks like Frieza!
I guess their universe
has one, too!
And that bear guy
looks pretty tough.
[BOTAMO]
Heh.
[NARRATOR]
If Lord Beerus' team loses,
Earth will be transferred
to the Sixth Universe,
and subject to
Lord Champa's whims.
The fate of Earth once again
hangs in the balance
as the Tournament of
Destroyers begins. Now!
♪
You got some pretty
nimble footwork there
for such a big guy!
[TD REF]
The tournament is underway!
Contestant Goku
versus Contestant Botamo!
Here in the early going,
these two titans
are taking a methodical
approach, sizing each other up.
[TD REF shrieks]
[yells]
[hollers]
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa!
Whew!
Turn around, Goku!
He's right behind you!
--[GOKU] Huh?
--[BOTAMO chuckles]
Hey, why didn't you
attack me? I was wide open!
And, Botamo is
just egging him on!
A cocky start
from the Sixth Universe!
Meanwhile, Goku's style can
best be compared to
a scared little child!
Why is the Seventh Universe
so slow out of the gates?
Quite the start.
Goku's still got the same,
sluggish reflexes
he showed on Beerus' world!
[CABBA] We may all be Saiyans,
but it seems our universe
has produced a version
that is much stronger.
[BOTAMO] Man, oh man,
Lord Champa told me
you were weak, but you're
even worse than I imagined.
If you're not going
to try to give me a fight,
you might as well
just tap out now
so I can get started on my nap.
Hey! Don't embarrass me!
I ate way too much
barbecue at lunch.
--[BEERUS] Huh?
--[BULMA] Huh?
[GOKU]
One, two, three, four.
Hold on, pal. Just trying
to digest lunch here
so I can get
in the swing of things.
[BOTAMO]
Uh.
The slow-moving Goku
has admitted
he over ate before the match!
We gotta remember not to serve
free food when Goku's around!
[ALL laugh]
[chuckles]
I don't got all day,
so here's a little something
to soothe your tum-tum.
Hey, dodging that
actually loosened things up!
Keep those power loogies
coming, pal. They really help!
[BOTAMO grunts]
[GOKU yelps]
Aah!
He's back!
Oh, brother. Now he's
giving  me indigestion.
[CABBA grunts]
He should have
finished him off by now!
Botamo is simply
getting warmed up, my lord.
Victory will soon be in hand.
All right!
[yells]
Yeah! That's it!
[BOTAMO]
Heh.
Hm. Hmm. Mhmm.
[yells]
[chuckles]
[GOKU grunts]
[ALL gasp]
Wow. I can't believe
that golden space bear's
able to withstand every one of
Goku's attacks and
still be on his feet.
He's absorbing it somehow!
Despite all that force,
his feet haven't moved an inch!
He's not absorbing
the blows with his fat,
he's dispersing their energy
to an alternate dimension.
Is that really true?
Uh. Yeah. Sure.
Uh. Do you know or not?
It's not often you see
Goku forced back like that.
How do you like this?!
[BOTAMO]
Ah-heh.
[yells]
Safe to say, this match
is not playing out
in the fashion we desired.
Hey! Stay on the attack
and don't let up!
I'm doing what I can!
But nothing's working so far.
How am I supposed to
beat this guy?!
Well, figure something out.
Kakarot! Stop punching him
and use your darn head!
What? Oh, okay!
Heh. I'm pretty sure that's
not what your teammate
wanted when he told you
to "use your head."
Where'd he go?
[GOKU]
I'll try this. Up you go!
Since my punches don't
hurt you, maybe this'll work.
You got too much
on your body protecting you,
but I think I got a better idea.
[BOTAMO] Not fair;
you're fighting dirty!
Hey, let go of me!
--[GOKU hollers]
--[BOTAMO grunts]
[yells]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[BOTAMO groans]
[yells]
[hollers]
[CHAMPA screams]
--[WHIS] Hah!
--[BEERUS] Ah!
Ladies and gentlemen,
that's a ring-out victory!
Contestant Goku of the
Seventh Universe is moving on!
[GOKU chuckles]
All right, Dad!
Nice job winning
with that ring-out, honey!
I almost forgot.
It's been a long time
since we've
had fights with rules.
Yeah.
Who cares if it's cheap--
we'll take the win!
Way to go!
Whew! I'm sure glad
this is just a tournament.
If that was a real fight
I could've been toast.
--[CHAMPA] Cheater!
--[GOKU] Huh?
This just proves that
back on Beerus's world,
you were pretending to be
weaker than you really are!
What are you talking about?
I wasn't pretending.
When you saw me I was wearing
a heavy training suit
Whis gave me and
that slowed me down,
but that wasn't a trick.
And then today you can do that
energy blast from your hand?
I didn't agree to using
projectile attacks!
Range attacks aren't weapons
if they come from
the fighter's' body;
they're technically
a physical ability.
Your man Botamo
used one as well.
Well, I say
his win doesn't count!
The only fair thing to do now
is to re-fight this match!
You're a sore loser!
Lord Beerus is right!
Yeah, he won. Get over it!
You sound like a toddler
who lost a game of marbles
on the playground.
Didn't know little crybabies
could be Destroyers!
[whispers]
Try not to make him any angrier.
[Z FAMILY, FRIENDS booing]
I hate losing!
I hate it! I hate it!
Please calm yourself,
Lord Champa.
We don't need to win every
match to defeat your brother.
Our team still has
four strong contestants
who have yet to fight.
And this next one up
is extremely promising.
[BOTAMO sobbing]
[TD REF] With Botamo
eliminated, Goku's moves on
to his next opponent:
Contestant Frost!
So over in the Sixth Universe
this guy must be their Frieza!
♪
Man, we just finished
getting rid of our own Frieza!
Just looking at him
makes me sick.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Whoa. You sound
almost exactly like Frieza!
Your performance was exemplary.
Before we commence,
I want you to know
I consider it
an honor to match up
with a warrior
with such aptitude.
Let's have a good, fair fight.
Huh? Nice to meet you, too.
[FROST] Ladies and gentlemen
of the Seventh Universe!
It is a shame we must
gather here today, divided,
with an "us" versus
"them" mentality.
But thankfully,
this is but a tournament.
I believe that no matter
who wins, at day's end,
we'll all be able
to shake hands and say,
"That, sir, was a fair game,
well fought."
So, sit back
and enjoy the contest
between me and
your champion, Goku.
I thank you for
lending me your ears.
[ALL]
Huh?
How come their universe
got a polite Frieza
and we got a murderous jerk?
Eeh...
Man, I never imagined a good-guy
Frieza was even possible.
This is definitely
throwing me for a loop.
[rings]
[TD REF]
Match two! You may begin!
[GOKU] All right.
How's he gonna start?
[neck cracks]
Hm.
[GOKU yells]
[hollers]
Whoa, what technique was that?
Caught me way off guard.
[chuckles]
Excuse me, Goku.
I would love to stand
toe-to-toe and trade blows,
but considering our
differences in stature,
I must fight with a style
emphasizing speed and agility.
--Huh?
--Uh...
My dear rival what's wrong?
[GOKU] You're stalling
to size me up, aren't you?
You can just
cut to the chase and
change into your final form.
My what?
Ha! We've dealt
with your kind before.
Goku knows all
your stupid tricks.
[GOKU] You're planning to
gradually transform in stages
while you test
my weaknesses, right?
And, why would you think that?
Because there's someone
like you in  my universe
who I've fought
a couple times already.
[FROST] I see. That saps
some wind from the sails.
If you stand there
twiddling your thumbs,
I'll knock you out before
you ever get to full strength.
I do appreciate
your honesty.
Then I shall go right
to full strength so we can
have the battle
we both came here for!
[bellows]
If you want a challenge,
how about my final form?
[CABBA, CHAMPA gasp]
I didn't know he could
transform like that!
[VEGETA] Goku's a fool,
but I bet even he
can tell this is a lie.
Final form my ass!
[FROST]
Will this do?
Yeah, I think
it'll be enough.
Though it's a little bit
different from the other Frieza.
Before we start,
I'd like to know
who won the fight between
us in your universe?
Let's just say...
...you might get mad
when you hear the answer.
I was that bad, huh?
Well, I hope things go
differently for me this time!
Yeah, it's no fun
to go out how he did.
Now, back to the fight!
[yells]
[groans]
[ELDER KAI chuckles]
[gasps]
[GOKU yells]
[screams]
Wow! This fight
could go either way!
A quick bit of trivia for
all you fans of the sport.
I'm told the official name
of Frost's altered state
is known as
"the Charging Form."
And now a little backstory
on Contestant Frost.
To end the constant warfare that
once plagued the Sixth Universe,
Frost led a peacekeeping
army, and used this
Charging Form to
pacify countless worlds.
He now devotes
his time to reconstruction,
finding homes for
the billions of children
orphaned in the wars he ended.
These humanitarian efforts
have earned him the coveted
Universal Peace Prize
a record three times in a row.
I had no idea
Frost was such a good guy.
To recruit him, my lord,
I had to tell him
you would support his
peace campaigns if he won,
in addition to your own promise.
But, if he loses,
he gets nothing, right?
That is correct, sir.
Seems a bit cruel, doesn't it?
My lord, a God of Destruction
should not worry about
whether or not
something is "cruel."
Wow... Their Frieza may
have similar looks and powers
to the one we know,
but he thinks so differently.
He's such a good guy, I'm not
even sure who to root for now!
Root for our universe,
you traitor!
Goku! C'mon, bro!
Yeah, Dad! You got him
right where you want him!
[yells]
Well, look at that,
ancestral Kai of the Seventh;
it appears that
Frost has taken
the upper hand
against your Goku.
[chuckles]
I wouldn't be so sure
of that, big boy.
[yells]
Oh, bother.
Was that too much?
[GOKU panting]
Thanks for the dodging
exercises; that was fun.
You've finally got me all
warmed up. I'm feeling great!
You mean I still haven't
seen all your moves yet?
I have to give you credit
for that gamesmanship.
[chuckles]
Come on! Stop being
such a jerk by holding back!
And what do you mean by that?
I told you to
skip to your final form
and I know for a fact
that's not it!
You're trying to
save your real power
for your next match, aren't you?
[FROST] Why would you
suggest such a strategy?
[GOKU] 'Cause I've been
doing the same thing!
[FROST]
Huh?
[GOKU bellows]
What's he doing?
Since when can you Saiyans
transform like that, Cabba?
Since never! I haven't
seen or even heard of
anything remotely like this.
Are you ready, Sixth Universe?
You're about to meet
a Super Saiyan!
[GOKU] From here on out,
neither of us holds back, Frost!
Let's both agree
that from now on
we will use our full power.
Now, you give me your final
form like I asked you to!
Very well, but then
you'll see the true reason
I've concealed my final form.
And that reason has
nothing to do with keeping
something in reserve for matches
later in this tournament.
[FROST bellows]
Ha!
All right, all right! Enough!
[FROST] Controlling my power
in this final form
is exceedingly difficult. It is
best used only to destroy.
As such, there has been
but one time I have been
forced to use it
against an adversary.
After what happened
in that fateful duel,
I've kept it locked away
ever since. But you, Goku...
I believe that in you
I have met someone
able to match its full
destructive fury.
Good! Don't hold back;
I can take it!
Hm. I have truly enjoyed
meeting you, warrior. All right!
[yells]
Behold, Goku.
This is my full power!
[yells]
[BOTH yell]
[6TH SUPREME KAI gasps]
See. I told you
you shouldn't feel
too confident, young fella.
It can't be.
How are you so strong?
[yells]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[FROST groans]
I take it that's the limit
of your final form's power.
Since you seem like
an honorable guy, Frost,
I don't want to hurt you
any more than I have to.
Tap out and let your teammates
take it from here.
I appreciate your
concern for my health,
but I'll never give in
to you or anyone else
from your universe's team.
I'm fighting for a cause.
It's imperative I win this
match, and then the tournament.
So I can continue to forge peace
by securing
Lord Champa's support!
Baah!
[yells]
I can't watch this anymore!
C'mon! It's not over yet, Frost!
Okay, now what?
He seems so nice.
[FROST] "No matter
what happens, never give up.
Get back on your feet."
That's right. The same
encouragement I give
my liberated orphans is
the encouragement I'll use now!
[grunts]
[yells]
[chuckles]
[GOKU moans]
[GOKU mumbles]
What's happening? Why?
Why am I...?
This match is over.
[BOTH gasp]
What the--?!
[NARRATOR]
In a stunning turn,
Goku has fallen
outside the ring.
Can the Seventh Universe prevail
without the powerful Saiyan?
The battles continue, next time
on Dragon Ball Super.
Goodbye to our adventure
In twilight we must go our separate ways
And try to discover the path to our own destiny
I can't find the words
to tell you how much our parting hurts
I hope you know I'll always love you
And all that we shared will be remembered
How could I forget your face?
All my memories erased
I can still hear the melody of your voice
Petals fall in from above
Fade away, all that we love
In the twilight,
fade away,
fade away
Sayonara,
fade away,
fade away
Hey, it's me, Goku!
I have no idea what kind of
super-punch Frost used on me
but now it's up to Piccolo
to find a way to win
'cause if we lose another match,
I don't even wanna know what Beerus will do.
Piccolo might not be on the same level
as us anymore when it comes to power
but with the right technique
he just might even the score.
Next time on Dragon Ball Super:
Make sure you don't miss it, okay?