♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Goku reminded everyone
of an ultimate tournament
between universes, which Grand
Zeno had proposed some time ago.
Let's make it
the best one ever!
[BOTH]
It's settled!
[giggles]
--[ZENO] Let's do it!
--[FUTURE ZENO] Yeah!
Oh man,
this is gonna be great!
Thank you Zenny's,
you guys are the best.
I can guarantee,
it's gonna be super exciting.
[NARRATOR] And so, the epic
contest was put into motion,
and the Omni-King's
Grand Minister was sent
to announce the details.
[GRAND MINISTER]
On day 3,135,500,603
of the Royal Calendar,
at precisely 1:57 o'clock,
the Tournament of Power
shall commence in all its glory.
Ten warriors from each universe
shall engage in epic combat!
So now we have to look for ten?
The Tournament of Power, huh?
Aw, yes! My heart's
really pumpin' now!
[NARRATOR] "Even the Universes'
Gods are Appalled?!
The Lose-and-Perish
'Tournament of Power.'"
So. Where's it gonna be?
Somewhere awesome, right?
It is a special place, indeed.
The Null Realm.
The Null Realm?
[BEERUS] It's a world
of infinite emptiness,
where not even
time or space exist.
[GRAND MINISTER] Since literally
nothing's in the Null Realm
there's nothing to break,
thus you'll be free
to fight as
vigorously as you like.
Also. As with
the tournament you held
between the Sixth
and the Seventh,
the ultimate champion
of our competition
will be awarded
the Super Dragon Balls,
which will grant
whatever wish is desired.
They have already been gathered
in preparation
of this grand event.
Yes, that's right.
And in case you're wondering,
he got three of them from me!
Damn you, Champa!
Do you mean you've been
collecting them once again?!
E-Excuse me.
And what prize does
the champion's
home universe receive?
They go on.
Uh, what? Like, go on stage?
No, no. They get to
go on as before.
Wait, how's that
a prize? I'm confused.
You're jumping the gun.
Grand Zeno intended for this
announcement to come later,
but due to your friendship
with the Omni-King, Goku,
I guess I'll make an exception.
--[GOKU] Hm?
--[BEERUS grunts]
It is a prize by its contrast.
For the universes that
don't win shall be eliminated.
Uh, could you repeat that?
It's simple. All of
the defeated universes
will be promptly
wiped from existence.
Grand Zeno will
see to it personally.
The whole universe? Wiped out?!
[ALL gasping]
Goku. There's one more thing.
Huh?
[GRAND MINISTER]
The Omni-King has a favor
to ask of you in the meantime.
--[BEERUS swallows]
--What's the favor?
A show. He'd like
to have some fighters
from the Seventh,
yourself included,
going up against
champions from the Ninth.
Think of it as a warm-up act
before the main show begins.
[GOKU]
Uh?
You see, the Grand Zeno from
the alternate future timeline
did not have the
opportunity to witness
your matches
against Universe Six.
Thus, he's a bit behind.
--[FUTURE ZENO] Hey, me?
--[ZENO] Yes, me.
[FUTURE ZENO]
What kind of power will be
in a Tournament of Power?
The power will be
fighting power.
Is it fun?
Want to see?
Oh yes, very much!
[GRAND MINISTER] What's needed
is a demonstration.
Our Omni-King wants to bring
his counterpart up to speed,
and build excitement
in them both
for the upcoming
tournament proper.
To that end,
we'd like you to take part
in these run-up matches, which
we are calling the Zeno Expo.
A fight before
the fights? Really?
[GOKU]
Sounds great!
So, who am I
gonna get to take on?
Well, that remains to be seen,
but as I said, it will be
someone from the Ninth.
You have exactly
one hour from now
to gather two other
worthy participants,
then present yourselves
at Grand Zeno's palace.
See you then.
[groans]
That's odd. Why'd they
choose Universe Nine?
I agree, that's an
intriguing question, sir.
But I would say that's the least
of our concerns at the moment.
Three of us get to fight
in this one, huh?
I wonder who I should
pick for this.
[BEERUS growls]
How can you be so
glib about this, Saiyan?
You're hopeless! Do you
have any comprehension
of what this stunt you've pulled
is going to do to the cosmos?
Just because
you wanted a workout?
Huh?
He's right.
Imagine for a moment
if the whole Seventh Universe
is plucked from existence.
I could never forgive myself.
And now all the universes
face the same threat.
Wait, so, should I
go ask Zenny not to pluck
the Seventh Universe and
obliterate it from existence?
Though your intentions are good
I must advise against that.
The Omni-Kings and
Grand Minister may seem amiable,
but they don't like dissent.
If you criticize their plan,
they might destroy
our universe to prove a point.
Aaah!
That's terrible, what do we do?
[BEERUS] Hm! You're a bit
late realizing that now.
And don't think your
so-called friendship
with the Grand Zenos
will save you, Goku.
You are a temporary plaything,
a bauble to be cast aside.
If you lose, they won't
hesitate to obliterate you,
along with the rest
of the Seventh.
[GOKU]
I know, I know!
But I didn't expect it
to turn out like this!
This is insane!
That's irrelevant!
You'll still pay the price!
Pay what price?!
Fine. I don't care who I fight.
All I know is I have to
win this tournament.
No matter what!
Indeed. As awful as this is
we have no choice
but to play along.
First, we need to build
the team for this Expo.
Then we can worry
about finding all ten
for the tournament after that.
Right. Well I'll take one spot!
Yes, we know! Moron!
Now find two more.
It's your mess to fix, so go!
[VEGETA ]
We've been over this already!
I am waiting for my child!
Okay, Vegeta, chill out.
You don't have to
yell my ear off.
--[GOTEN] Here I come!
--[TRUNKS] Bring it on!
[TRUNKS, GOTEN yell]
[yells]
[GOTEN]
Ooo, ow!
Yo!
--Hey, Dad, what's up!
--[TRUNKS] Gotcha!
[GOTEN groans]
No fair, that was a cheap shot!
So what! You were
wide open, dude!
[GOTEN]
All right, take this!
I don't know what this
"Zeno Expo" is, Kakarot.
But if you need help,
then why not ask your son?
Yeah, I could. But I have
no idea who we're gonna fight.
Goten may not be
up to the challenge yet.
--[GOTEN yells]
--[TRUNKS grunts]
[GOKU]
Wait. My other son!
Now I get it!
Thanks, Vegeta!
That's a great idea!
[VEGETA]
Hmph!
[GOHAN]
Hm?
A Zeno Expo and
a Tournament of Power?
Inter-universe match-ups
sound pretty intense, Dad.
Yeah, exactly, that's why
we need your help to win!
You want me? But why?
You'll be fine, son.
Sure, you haven't kept up
with your training,
but it'll come back!
You've got great instincts
and incredible power
locked up in there--
we've all seen it!
I don't know.
[GOKU]
Hm?
Look, the truth
is this tournament
could be kind of a problem.
Wait, what do you mean?
[whispers] I'll tell you,
but you have to promise
you won't tell Videl,
or anyone else, okay?
Okay.
Supposedly every universe
that loses this
will be completely
wiped out by Grand Zeno.
Uuh! Huh...?
Wiped out? Like, seriously?
Seriously.
How could you?
Uh?
Dad. How could you let
something like this happen?
If word spreads,
riots will break out everywhere.
And if he actually
goes through with it.
I know it sounds bad, okay?
Supreme Kai and Lord Beerus
already laid into me,
but maybe it's all just a bluff.
[GOHAN]
And if it's not, what then?
Can you stop it? Can you
do anything about it, Dad?
Well, I'm not sure yet;
we'll have to play this out
and deal with it if it happens.
But that's insane!
[gasps]
Wait. Does anyone else
know about this?
Not here on Earth.
Just you and me so far.
[GOHAN] Well, we need
to keep it that way.
You can't tell anybody else!
And I won't tell either--
we can't cause a panic!
[VIDEL]
What's up, you guys?
If you want to visit,
you should come inside!
Yo!
Nothing! Nothing to worry about!
[GOKU] Yeah, I was just
inviting Gohan to enter
a martial arts tournament
with me, that's all.
But apparently he's
too busy to help his old man
and join the fight.
Yeah, you know,
kinda gave up all that!
Aw, come on, it's just
a tournament, right?
[GOHAN]
Huh?
Why don't you help him?
I think you'd have fun!
[PAN]
Mama!
Welcome home, little nugget!
--[PAN giggling]
--Was Grandpa nice?
Did you play any fun games?
--[PAN] Yeah!
--Yeah.
He's good for that.
[VIDEL chuckles]
Aw, sweetie.
[GOHAN] All right, Dad.
I'll join the fight.
That's the spirit, son!
[PAN giggling]
Gotta protect
my family, don't I?
[GOKU chuckles]
[MR. SATAN] Wow. Each time
I see Pan she's bigger
and stronger than before!
She must take after her grandpa!
Oh! Hey there, Goku!
[GOKU chuckles]
Uh?
--Buu!
--Long time no see, Goku!
[GOKU] This is perfect timing!
I need a favor!
Huh?
Say no more!
Whatever you need,
I'm here to help, Goku!
One manly world-saving
hero to another!
Uuh... Thanks, man,
but actually I'm gonna
need Buu for this one. Cool?
Really? You need Buu?
[BUU munching]
[MR. SATAN]
Wha-- Okay, uh!
[BUU chuckles]
[BEERUS]
This is the best you could do?
[BEERUS groans]
Uh, hi, Lord Beerus.
And what is that one doing here?
Oh well, uh, uh.
We're kind of a package deal.
I'm the only one
he'll listen to, ya see.
[chuckling]
[whispering]
So Goku, do these Earthlings
know what will happen if
we lose the main tournament?
[whispering] Only Gohan does.
He said we shouldn't
tell anyone else since
it would cause a big panic
and make things worse.
Is that right?
[BEERUS] Hmm. He's got a brain,
at least I can say that.
Well. Let's not keep
the Omni-King waiting.
Kai kai!
What's that?
[SUPREME KAI]
The palace of Grand Zeno,
ruler of the Multiverse.
How'd they make it float?
We cannot afford
any slip-ups, human.
[MR. SATAN]
Huh?
Do not speak or move
unless prompted.
You hear me?
Or you will regret it.
Yes, sir. Sorry.
[footsteps]
[GOKU]
Huh?
Ah, noble gentlemen
of the Ninth.
It's been too long.
[RO]
Hm.
[GOKU]
Hm?
I take it those are the guys
we're gonna be fighting.
Yeah.
[ALL chuckle]
[GRAND MINISTER]
Glad you could make it.
[MR. SATAN]
Uh! Down, Buu!
Oh!
[giggles]
Now then, taking a
page from Earth's
martial arts tournaments,
I will prepare the ring and
seating for the spectators.
[GOKU, GOHAN, MR. SATAN gasp]
[GOKU hollers]
--[MR. SATAN hollering]
--[BUU laughing]
[BUU]
Mm!
Gathered deities,
please come down.
Join us.
[BOTH gasp]
[BEERUS growls]
All twelve universes'
Supreme Kais and Destroyers.
Angels, too.
What a truly rare assembly.
[ELDER KAI]
Eh...
These are all gods, huh?
--[BUU yawns]
--Kinda freaky.
[GOKU]
Yo!
Hey Champa!
How's it goin', man?
Whoa! That's a god, buddy!
Shouldn't you use some "thees"
and "thous" or somethin'?
Aw, relax it's okay.
I've known Champa
for a while now.
[GRAND MINISTER]
Excuse me, Goku.
I'm afraid I must
insist on silence.
Aw, great! You ticked off
the little blue angel guy!
[GOKU chuckles]
Loyal Supreme Kais and
Destroyers of the Twelve,
thank you for joining us today.
As I informed you earlier,
we gather here to prepare
for the upcoming
martial arts competition,
which Grand Zeno has named
the Tournament of Power.
For those who don't know,
our great Omni-King
has a new companion.
It's his own counterpart
from an alternate future.
Due to timeline discrepancies,
that Grand Zeno has never seen
a martial arts tournament.
So we will remedy that
with this: our Zeno Expo.
Hail the Omni-Kings!
You humble us
with your presence.
[GOKU]
Hey! Zennys, it's me!
[shouting]
Over here! Hi!
[GOHAN]
Dad!
Did-did he say "Zenny"?
What's up, you guys?!
Thanks for giving us these
awesome pre-fight fights!
--Get down, idiot!
--[GOKU hollering]
[ALL gasp]
[BEERUS] Please forgive
the disturbance, sire!
[MR. SATAN] I told you, you
can't talk to a god like that!
That's Deity 101!
He'll wipe us out! I told you!
--Say what now?
--Uh!
[BEERUS whisling]
--[BASIL] What's wrong with him?
--[DEITIES murmuring]
[SIDRA] Do they teach them
nothing in the Seventh?
[CHAMPA]
Control your Saiyan, brother!
I'd hate for it
to get ugly for you!
[DEITIES murmuring]
Great deities. Before we start,
we should acknowledge
a mortal from the Seventh
who's enthusiasm helped
set this all in motion.
Without him we wouldn't
have gathered here today.
Would you care
to speak, Saiyan?
Sure.
I'm Goku. And I heard
the other universes
had strong fighters
I didn't know about!
So I said to Zenny,
it would be great
to fight all those guys.
And he was nice enough
to set it all up!
Thank you, Goku.
Yes, thank you!
I want to see fights!
Yes, please hurry!
You got it, dudes.
I guarantee you
it's gonna be amazing!
[GRAND MINISTER]
Thank you, Goku.
Now then, let's get
to the particulars.
In keeping with
our Omni-King's wishes,
this Zeno Expo will be
comprised of successive
one-on-one matches
between three martial artists
from the Seventh Universe
and three from the Ninth.
These contests will
have no time limits.
Each match will go on
until one opponent
declares defeat or is rendered
incapable of continuing.
Combatants are allowed
and expected to use
all powers they have
in pursuit of victory.
[RO]
A question, Grand Minister!
What will the winning universe
receive as their reward,
for being superior?
The only point
of this Expo is to show
the appeal of martial arts
to His Majesty's
esteemed counterpart
from the future.
It's not intended
to judge these universes,
so there is no reward.
Though that is not to suggest
these are matches
without consequence.
If he feels that your fighters
don't live up to the task,
he may take drastic measures.
[RO]
Ngh!
Grand Minister, are you
implying if he gets bored
and doesn't think
they're impressive enough,
he might exterminate
the fighters,
or the whole universe?
All I can say with accuracy
is those possibilities do exist.
It all depends on the whims
of the Omni-Kings.
Now, let's get on with the Expo!
Our first two contestants.
Please enter the ring.
Yeah! The first one's
all mine, brothers.
[grunts]
[chuckles]
Go on, Basil! Show them!
I'm counting on you to deliver
for the Ninth Universe!
Yeah, make it look easy.
Don't worry,
I won't let you down!
Oh, please. He doesn't
look like much to me.
All right, you guys,
let's just stick to the plan.
You're fighting first, Buu.
[BUU snoring]
[GOKU]
Aah!
[ALL]
He fell asleep?
Knucklehead! Isn't this
the whole reason you're here?
Deal with this!
Yes, sir!
Hey, Buu. Come on, buddy!
This ain't your nappin' time!
Hey, look! I been
savin' this one for ya!
It's a chocoholic special!
[sniffing]
Okay, that's the spirit.
Now, remember
what you promised me?
How you'd play over there?
[BUU]
Hm?
Buu think he funny!
He look like dog!
[MR. SATAN]
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Go get 'em, Buu!
That doggy-man says
he wants to play with you
really, really bad!
[BASIL]
Uh?
Play?
He especially likes
getting tackled.
So be a good Buu
and play with him
and I'll give you
tons more chocolate, okay?
Okay, Buu will play!
Be sure to play
super-extra hard!
[yawns]
So you wanna challenge me ?
Let the opening match begin!
[BUU chuckles]
[BASIL chuckles]
Buu, no!
[laughing]
Whoa! They are fast!
Oh yes! Yes, they are!
[BUU groans]
A rough start. Those kick
techniques are hard to block.
Yeah. He's looking
pretty tough to beat.
[BUU]
Uh!
[laughing]
They chose this blob
as their leadoff fighter?
Embarrasing!
He's an absolute joke!
[BASIL laughs]
[RO chuckles]
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[BEERUS growls]
[BOTH gasp]
[BUU giggles]
An angel and a demon sit
One to my right,
one to my left
In between I'm tryin'
to figure out the right way
Is one way good?
Is one way bad?
Too much confusion in my head
I can't think with all
this noise, I'm goin' crazy
Is there any way to know
what's right or wrong?
Demons in an angel mask
Hopin' that I'll do
just what they ask
Telling me
they know what's right
Lead me to the light
"For the sake of everyone
You have to destroy
the evil ones
That's the only path, you see"
So they said to me
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And things aren't
looking good for Buu.
This Basil guy's kicks
have some incredible force,
and they may too much to handle.
[GOHAN]
Please, Buu, this isn't a game!
You've got to get serious!
Our whole universe
may be on the line!
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"The 9th Universe's
Kicking Basil vs.
the 7th Universe's Majin Buu!!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?