♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the Tournament
of Power raged on,
and with the teams
whittled down,
each new battle
was proving to be
even more intense than the last.
[CABBA] With Hit gone, Caulifla
and Kale are the best chances
the Sixth Universe
has to survive.
I have to do everything
I can to help them succeed.
Pay attention. I'm a Saiyan
and no push over.
So I will not let you
look down on me.
[NARRATOR] Cabba fought
the Fourth Universe's Monna,
hoping to save the energy
of his remaining teammates
for the greater struggles ahead.
[MONNA]
This is where it ends!
[screaming]
[NARRATOR] Just when he
thought he was he done,
he was saved by
a surprise assist.
[VEGETA]
Don't get the wrong idea.
I didn't pull you back
out of kindness.
I just can't let a Saiyan
embarrass our race
by losing so easily.
You really don't remember?
You said you'd take me
to Planet Sadla.
[NARRATOR] Inspired to
keep his word to Vegeta,
Cabba ascended to
Super Saiyan Two,
and decisively won
victory over Monna.
But there was no time to rest.
[FRIEZA]
I have to be honest.
While I do respect
powerful fighters...
...there's nothing that I
despise more than a monkey.
[CABBA]
What?!
[NARRATOR] Frieza took advantage
of Cabba's exhaustion,
and knocked him from the ring.
The tournament continues... now!
[NARRATOR]
"With Great Joy!
The Fighting Freak
Saiyans' Battle Rejoined!"
[ALL beeping]
[GOKU laughs] I may be drained,
but I'll still fight.
I don't have any choice.
[GOKU gasps]
[ALL screeching]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU growling]
[CAULIFLA yells]
[PANCEA groans]
[KOITSUKAI groans]
Ha!
Wow, that's amazing.
[GOKU]
Thanks a lot!
You totally saved me there!
With the time Cabba bought me,
I'm back to full strength.
So let's go. You and me, Goku.
[GOKU grunts]
[KALE gasping]
First Hit was knocked out of the
ring, and now Cabba's gone too.
I never should've
have let that happen.
I have to get stronger so I can
keep fighting in their place,
and give our universe a chance.
So show me how to get
to the next level.
I don't have time to wait!
I need to get to
Super Saiyan Three.
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU]
Fine, I'll do it.
[CAULIFLA]
You serious?
[GOKU]
Yeah sure, why not.
But I can only show you
if you try to defeat me
with everything you've got.
Aren't you gonna
transform, too?
[GOKU] I just fought Jiren,
so I'm a bit tapped out.
Don't worry, though.
I'll work up to it slowly.
Trust me, I'll get there.
[CAULIFLA]
Oh, is that right?
[GOKU]
Come see for yourself.
You shouldn't doubt me.
Is Goku really gonna fight her
in the shape he's in?
Ah? This could be the big
break our team needed!
Normally Goku would defeat her
easily, but since he's still
weakened from facing Jiren,
she'll have the advantage.
Get him, Caulifla!
This is our chance to get rid
of their strongest fighter!
Toss Goku out like a rag doll!
Try thinking for once,
you numbskull!
If she knocks out Goku, then
who's gonna deal with Jiren?!
It should be obvious to anyone
with eyes and a brain--
Goku's the only one who can
even come close to that guy.
Yeah, and so what
if he is, Brother?
Considering the rules
of the Tournament,
we don't actually have
to fight him to win.
If we want to survive, we just
have to be the universe with
the most fighters left
when time runs out.
[growls] So how many
minutes are left now?
[SUPREME KAI]
Looks like about 23.
Ugh. Then he might have a point.
Maybe they could
run out the clock.
Even if Jiren is the best,
his Eleventh Universe
is down to three fighters.
Since this is about numbers,
we're actually ahead of
them in the scoring.
It's your team with seven left--
that's where we need to focus.
Our best hope is picking off
your fighters whenever we can!
Then if we play this right,
we'll win with our four!
That's just simple
arithmetic, Beerus!
You can't argue with that!
That was an impressively
level-headed assessment,
Lord Champa, I admit
you've surprised me.
What can I say, I'm a
natural-born strategist.
Get him! Now, Caulifla!
All right, get ready!
I hope they've saved you
a spot in the bleachers!
[CAULIFLA yells]
[GOKU, CAULIFLA grunting]
[CAULIFLA growling, grunting]
[CAULIFLA]
Get back here!
Goku is too weak
to hold his ground!
She is attacking non-stop!
Yes, I am very amazed!
That's the way, Caulifla, yes!
Drive him back all
the way out of the ring!
[CAULIFLA]
Take this!
[GOKU grunts]
What?!
Impossible!
Don't stop now.
If you let up that easy, you're
never gonna win this fight.
[CAULIFLA growls]
Bastard!
[CAULIFLA yells]
[GOKU, CAULIFLA grunting]
[CAULIFLA]
Come on. Why can't I connect?
[GOKU grunting]
[yells]
Uh.
[CAULIFLA gasping]
Just hang in there!
Oh give me a break,
what's the problem now--
how are you letting him
get the best of you?
You're at Super Saiyan
and he's not--
you should overpower him easily!
Martial artistry
and street brawling
are entirely different things.
One cannot throw sloppy
punches at random
and expect mere strength
to ensure victory.
One must constantly measure
one's reach against opponents,
judge their breathing and
how they move in battle,
always probing for an opening
in their defenses,
a weakness to exploit.
That is what makes one
a martial artist,
rather than a scrappy punk
who likes to tussle.
Aw, sorry, Champa,
too bad for you!
This was your best
chance to stay alive,
but your Saiyan just
can't compete with mine!
[CHAMPA growls]
All righty, change of plans!
Don't worry about Goku,
we'll defeat the others,
just get out of there, now!
Shut up!
[CAULIFLA yells]
[groaning]
[CAULIFLA grunts]
[FUWA, CHAMPA gasp]
Ha! I'm not fallin' for
the same trick twice!
No. I guess not.
Then let's see if you'll
fall for this one!
Huh? What? What is this?
[gasps]
Over here!
[CAULIFLA yelps]
[CAULIFLA] Damn it...
Hey! That's a cheap move!
Using fancy tricks
to sneak up on me?
Fight me face-to-face!
Look if you can't see through
a simple After-Image,
Super Saiyan Three is gonna
be a big problem for you.
Say what?
Enough with that trick!
I told you so! You should
have run away when I said!
[GOKU yelling]
Huh?
[laughs]
You like that?
Oh man, that time she
saw his attack coming!
[BOTH grunt]
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH grunting]
[CAULIFLA, GOKU yell]
[yelling]
[yells]
Incredible--she's adapting
in front of our eyes,
learning to react faster
and counter Goku's moves.
Her responsiveness as
a fighter is astounding.
I know she's a Super Saiyan,
but it's Goku.
He should still have the edge!
The fact that she's doing
this splendidly shows
the vast amount
of inner potential,
which up to now she's
not known how to tap.
Fighting against Goku is rapidly
releasing that buried power,
and allowing her to improve
at an exponential rate.
Don't act like a know-it-all!
A minute ago you called that
girl a sloppy street brawler!
Huh, I said that? Are you sure?
I don't recall.
[CAULIFLA yelling]
[GOKU grunting]
[CAULIFLA, GOKU grunting]
That's the spirit,
Caulifla, get him!
Yes, make him pay, just like I
said, don't stop until he's out!
I'm confused, my lord,
I thought you said
you had a change of strategy.
Well, I changed it again.
It's called flexibility, Vados!
It's also called "flying by
the seat of one's pants."
Uh!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU groans]
[CAULIFLA yells]
I hope for your sake you're
ready to transform, Goku.
I'd hate for you to drop out
before you fight for real.
Yeah you're right,
I would hate that, too.
[yelling]
[laughs]
[yells]
Nice, but are you sure
you don't want to go
Super Saiyan Three?
Fun as that would be,
I don't have enough strength
for that yet.
Well, that's too bad for you.
[yells]
Is that really the same
Super Saiyan Two level
that I'm at now? [grunting]
Careful!
[CAULIFLA growls]
I won't let you win!
Crush Cannon!
[GOKU gasps]
Goku!
[ALL gasp]
I'll be honest, you took me
by surprise with that attack.
I never would've imagined
you had a special move
like that up your sleeve.
I guess you're not the only one
with secret weapons, huh Goku?
Okay, but do you think you can
keep up with me
in round two?
[CAULIFLA] Bring it, hot-shot!
I'm not scared of you!
Good, glad to hear it. Because
I'm getting worked up, too.
[yells]
[yelling]
[BOTH grunting]
Wow! They are getting
much faster!
Yes! And faster is better!
[KALE whimpers]
[GOKU grunting]
[groans]
[yelling]
Oh, my! They are both fantastic!
Double fantastic!
[GOKU] Hmph. Back when I
showed you Super Saiyan Two,
I said you'd need
to stay at that level
for a while so you
could master it.
But you're a quick
learner, Caulifla.
I gotta say, I'm impressed.
[laughs] It's just how I am.
The harder the battle, the more
the power inside me grows.
I'm gonna defeat you right now
and then go straight
on to Three!
[GOKU]
Heh.
[CAULIFLA, GOKU grunting]
I don't think so--there's a lot
more to my power than just this!
[yells]
You won't outdo me!
[yelling]
They keep pushing each other
further and further!
The question is:
which one of them will
reach their limit first?
Astounding! I didn't know
Caulifla had this much power!
[CAULIFLA yells]
[GOKU grunting]
[CATOPRESA screaming]
[CAULIFLA, GOKU grunting]
[yells]
[yelling]
[CATOPRESA, ZARBUTO yelp]
Take this!
[GOKU grunts]
[yelling]
[CAULIFLA]
Ha!
[ALL gasp]
That's sure one heck of a fight.
They're both taking
Super Saiyan Two
as far as that form
will take them.
[BOTH grunting]
I can really tell.
She loves this.
What?
Gotcha!
[GOKU groans]
[yelps, groans]
Aw, yeah! Ya like that?
When I first met you,
I never expected your power
would climb this high, Caulifla.
I'm starting to think
you can reach Three now.
Maybe even beyond.
So, how 'bout you, Kale?
Are you game?
Uh! Honestly?
Yeah, let's go!
We can get to Three together!
Right!
[BEERUS]
That brainless fool!
Now he's inviting her
to fight against him too?
All right! This is perfect!
They'll be an unstoppable force!
Together they'll win for sure!
Do it Kale and Caulifla,
knock him into next week!
All right, you can come
at me any way you want.
[CAULIFLA] Heh. You don't need
to hold back your power
for my sake. Give him
everything you've got!
You bet!
[KALE] Finally, we get
to fight together.
Caulifla and me,
standing as a team.
[KALE laughs]
Let's do this, Kale!
You got it!
[yells]
[BOTH grunt]
[GOKU grunts]
[yells]
Good shot!
Thank you.
[CAULIFLA grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[KALE, CAULIFLA yelling]
[GOKU yelps]
It's what I've always wanted.
It's how it's meant to be!
[KALE grunting]
Crush Cannon!
[KALE grunts]
Goku!
All right, now we're talkin'--
that one kinda stung.
[CAULIFLA]
Heh.
[KALE]
Hmph.
[CAULIFLA] I've always
liked fighting alone,
but I gotta say, this teamwork
thing ain't half bad, either.
Heh.
I fear Goku is overwhelmed.
Fending off two Saiyans
at once is too much,
especially without
all of his power.
Maybe. But you should
know by now, sir,
Goku's always made himself
stronger by pushing himself
right to the limit. That's
just the kinda guy he is.
[gulps]
[CHAMPA] Keep going, ladies!
Just a little bit more!
Eliminate him and the
Seventh will be doomed!
Hey, now!
Come on, you've got this!
Just make him pay!
Let's bring him down, Kale!
Coming!
[CAULIFLA, KALE]
Ha!
[CHAMPA growls]
It's two against one!
They'll win this for sure!
[SAIYANS grunting]
Looks like Goku's
actually holding his own!
There's no way!
How can he possibly fight
off two Super Saiyans?!
[SAIYANS grunting]
Is he doing it again?
What do you mean?
"Is he doing" what?
You know. That thing he
was doing against Jiren.
[BEERUS]
Which thing, Roshi?
Autonomous Ultra Instinct?
I can assure you it is not.
[BEERUS]
Huh?
Autonomous Ultra Instinct
is a martial mastery
that's hard for even Destroyers
to reliably achieve.
As adept as Goku is in battle,
it would be impossible for him
to accomplish it again with
such quickness and ease.
[exhales]
[WHIS] Goku is improving his
defenses a more traditional way:
by studying and learning the
way Kale and Caulifla fight.
[SAIYANS grunting]
[CAULIFLA]
Kale, now!
[BOTH yell]
[GOKU grunts]
[growls]
[BOTH yell]
[yelling]
[BOTH gasp]
[GOKU]
This is all thanks to you.
Fighting you both at once,
I discovered I had
power inside of me
that I didn't realize was there.
Whoa. Your energy is incredible!
So that's it. The next level!
Super Saiyan Three!
[KALE gasping]
[BOTH gasp]
[GOKU]
Heh, heh. I couldn't resist
jumping to Super Saiyan Three.
But it takes a huge amount of
power to stay in that form.
I'm not ready for that.
[CAULIFLA] What? Are you
kidding? That's a total tease!
[GOKU]
I know, I know. I'm sorry.
[CAULIFLA] Whatever. We got
to see it--that's enough.
Now we know what it
looks and feels like
to transform from
Super Saiyan Two to Three.
We're gonna defeat you, then I
swear we'll get there ourselves.
We'll get there together!
Let's do this.
I'm not going to let her down.
I have to keep
getting stronger too!
[yelling]
Well this could get ugly.
Don't push it too far!
You know what could happen!
[KALE yelling]
Whoa, Kale!
[KALE yells]
[CAULIFLA yelps]
[KALE growls]
Oh, not again!
That's the form she took before!
So already she's back
to going berserk?
[GOKU]
Hmph.
[NARRATOR]
As the battle between three
mighty Saiyans intensifies,
it appears Kale's desire
to prove herself
worthy to Caulifla
has once again pushed her
to a level she cannot control.
With Goku still recovering,
will he be able to stop her
next ferocious rampage?
Only 22 minutes remain
in the Tournament of Power.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super!
A 70 centimeter squared window
Today the sun broke
through the clouds
The rain is fin'ly gone
Gonna open up
the window for once
No reason, just because
This room has been
stained with the sighs
Of everyday regret
Now it's time to clear the air
Every moment was consumed
with my thoughts of you
Knowing in my heart those dreams
won't be coming true
I've always wanted nothing more
than to see your face
I move on knowing that your
mem'ry can't be erased
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And Kale's really bringin' it!
Looks like this time she's
figured out how to reach
that incredible level
without losing control,
making her a true
Legendary Super Saiyan!
And that's not all.
By teaming up with Caulifla,
the two Saiyans
are unleashing the ultimate
combo technique.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Bloodcurdling! The Explosive
Birth of a New Super Warrior!"
Make sure you
don't miss it, okay?