♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Beerus the Destroyer
arrived on Earth.
Having already interrogated
and defeated Goku
on King Kai's planet,
Beerus targeted Vegeta
for information.
[VEGETA]
Of course!
That's who
Beerus the Destroyer is!
No wonder he could
beat Kakarot in two blows!
[BEERUS]
Now then...
Why don't you prove
I'm wrong and tell me
something useful about
this Super Saiyan God.
A Super Saiyan God?
Seems letting me down
is your kind's specialty.
Wait, let me think.
Sorry for the wait!
A pyramid of takoyaki,
Your Grace!
[NARRATOR] Knowing full well
what Beerus could do to Earth,
Vegeta tried desperately
to keep the Destroyer happy,
but not everyone cooperated.
[WHIS] Would you mind
sharing a pudding with us
from your... ample collection?
[BUU]
Blalalalala.
[screams]
[NARRATOR] Majin Buu's lack of
respect greatly insulted Beerus.
And it seemed
the world would end
over the most
trivial of causes:
an unshared plate of pudding.
[VEGETA] It's all over.
Our lives. This planet!
We don't stand a chance!
[NARRATOR] If the Saiyan Prince
hopes to save Earth,
he must channel a power unlike
any we've seen before. Now!
[NARRATOR] "How Dare You
Do That to My Bulma!
Vegeta's Metamorphosis
of Fury?!"
[PICCOLO growls]
Vegeta? You okay?
I thought that guy
was your friend?
[panting]
[BEERUS growls lowly]
It's all right, Dad.
We're here.
You okay?
I'm seein' so many stars
it's like a galaxy!
What's going on?
That guy's a major buzzkill!
Vegeta?
Honey?
Well normally,
I'd say let it go!
But that jerk-wad
is ruining my birthday!
Teach him a lesson!
[VEGETA]
Bulma.
[grunts]
Please. Lord Beerus.
Let me handle this for you!
There's no need
to lose your temper.
Just enjoy the party!
I'll make that pink fool
sorry, believe me!
Step aside.
[VEGETA]
But Your Grace.
Right now.
If you want pudding,
I'll have them make some more,
the best on the planet!
I told you to move! Now!
[PICCOLO] Vegeta's scared.
Cowering like a servant.
Who is this guy?
And Dende's trembling, too.
Dende. You're obviously
afraid of him, tell me why.
Dende!
If you're sensing something,
I need to know!
I'm not sure
what I've been sensing,
but I've never felt
anything like it.
You mean his energy
is unique somehow?
Yes.
[panting]
Nobody does that to Buu.
Buu will make you pay!
[WHIS]
Is my food almost ready?
What? Oh yes, sir.
Almost. Sorry!
Splendid--
I'm looking forward to it.
You seem to be
an excellent craftsman.
Oh. Thanks,
you're too kind, sir.
I haven't learned
a single thing about
the Super Saiyan God here.
And I didn't even
get to taste the pudding!
Let's wrap it up, Whis!
I'm gonna wreck this world
and get on with
the rest of my day!
[WHIS]
A few minutes, my lord!
I'm right in the middle
of an order!
I'm not waiting! So you
either get up here now
or explode with
the rest of this planet!
[TRUNKS]
You ready, Goten?
[GOTEN]
I was born ready, Trunks!
[BOTH]
Fu...sion. Ha!
Somebody need a suphero?
'Cause Gotenks
just answered the call!
Boys, no! Stay away!
Bad news, kitty cat.
You shouldn't poop on a party
when I'm on the guest list!
You've got about five
seconds to start behavin',
or the great Gotenks
is takin' you to school!
Funny, kid. Now move.
Well, I warned you.
But it looks like
school it will be! Heh!
Ultra-Awesome Megaton-Powered
Propeller Punch Attack! Ha!
What? No way!
Just curious,
was that supposed to hurt?
I know the real reason you
came here and it won't work!
'Cause I'll do
whatever it takes
to keep the
Dragon Balls from you!
Dragon Balls you say?
Sounds like quite the delicacy.
Let go of me, you bully!
Are your hands made of steel?
Is it made of pastry
or actual dragon parts?
It's not food at all,
you dumbass. Let me go!
You don't play
very nice, you know!
I'm not your playmate,
little one,
and I don't have time
for your childish games.
You're calling me childish?
Look in the mirror, pal!
You're the one
who's throwing a silly fit
over some lousy pudding!
What? Downplaying
my dessert tragedy?
It might seem like
nothing to you,
you pudding-spoiled brat!
But I've never
tasted it before!
I have no idea what it's like!
Is it more creamy?
Or gelatinous?
Is it savory or sweet?
Lumpy or smooth?
Is it a rustic flavor?
Or experimental?
Rich or tart? Or spicy?
It could be a brand new flavor!
Refined on your planet
for thousands of years!
And I would never know!
It could have shattered my whole
understanding of what food is!
I'll spend eons
wondering "what if"!
Do you still think
that's trivial, boy? Do you?
Say it don't spray it, dude!
I don't feel sorry
for you one bit!
If it was up to me, all you'd
get to eat is cat food!
Your mouth is smarter
than your brain is.
You need to be disciplined! Bad!
That hurt!
Bad bad bad bad bad
bad bad bad bad bad bad!
Not even the boys'
Fusion is doing anything
against this guy.
Okay, that is a serious lump!
Sorry to bother you, sir.
Run on home, kid!
Though actually, I'm about to
destroy your whole planet.
So I guess there's
really no point.
We may not stand
a chance against you,
but I won't go down
without a fight.
You've taken this far enough!
We've got children
to protect here.
Just who or what are you?
That's not something
you need to know.
You'll be wiped out soon anyway.
We'll see about that!
[A18, TIEN yell]
[yells]
[BOTH groan]
[groans]
[yells]
You okay, hun?
Stay there, I'll restore you.
Thanks. How is it
possible he inflicted
that much damage
without even touching us?
Those stupid kids!
Come on, Whis. Let's go!
[SUSHI CHEF 7A]
Here you are.
[WHIS]
Thank you!
My word! Oh-ho-ho-ho!
So this is
what you call sushi?
Yes, sir. Don't forget
to dip it in this first.
That's called soy sauce.
[WHIS] Now what's
this orange one here
with the spongy texture?
That one's our special
sea urchin battleship roll.
Oh, my!
And what about that one?
It's practically sparkling
like a diamond.
That's our premium
tuna-belly nigiri.
Tuna belly!
--And that?
--That's an egg.
--Salmon roe.
--And that?
--Abalone!
They all look
supremely delicious.
I'm not sure where to begin!
Let's see. Guess there's
no time to dither!
[squeals]
It's perfection!
Thanks, sir.
I'm glad you like it.
[BEERUS]
Whis!
Did your ears fall off? Whis!
Okay, be right there!
Hello, Lord Beerus.
You called?
I've been calling you
for quite some time.
Like I said before, I'm ready to
destroy this planet and go home.
Does that mean
you're over your little
Super Saiyan God
obsession already?
The Oracle Fish
and I must have had
our psychic wires crossed.
[WHIS]
This sushi is wondrous!
[chuckles]
And you're keeping it all
for yourself, I see.
No need for
hurt feelings, my lord.
I'm having a special sampler
platter made for you
that we can take on the road.
How unusually
thoughtful of you.
Of course that means
you'll have to be patient
a little bit longer.
Okay, okay. I suppose
I can hold off on
global annihilation long enough
for a sampler platter.
You feeling better now, Dad?
Yeah, it was just a scratch.
[laughs]
I can't believe even Piccolo
didn't stand a chance.
Do you think everybody's holding
back their real strength
'cause that guy's
friends with Vegeta?
I wish that were true,
but nobody's
holding back at all.
It's bad, Videl.
I've got a feeling
we've just picked a fight
with a power that
we can't even comprehend.
[distant rumble]
[COOKS yell]
[grunts]
Now Buu extra mad!
[yells]
[panting]
Jeez, man.
They've gone nuts!
Of all the times, why now?
[CHICHI]
Krillin!
Your brave wife's
put her neck on the line
to protect us,
so what's your excuse, huh?
I hung up my fighting shoes
a while ago, Chichi.
You can't be retired
when there's danger!
But then who's gonna
look after Marron?
I will, man!
You have my word, old buddy.
I'll guard your
little girl with my life!
So you're free
to fight all you want!
Don't bother. You'd just
be wasting your life.
I know what he is!
[DENDE] It's the only way
to explain his strange energy.
[DENDE]
He's a deity!
Say what?
[BUU]
Huah!
[PICCOLO]
Are you serious?
You think he's
some kind of... god?
[grunts]
[bellows]
Gohan! Stay back!
Enough, already!
[yells]
Gohan!
Are you okay?
He took Gohan down
in a single blow, too.
Maybe a deity is the only
possible explanation.
Oh, Whis! Is that
sampler platter ready yet?
Ooh, that's delicious!
These are the "shrimp," correct?
I've always enjoyed the flavor
of decapod crustaceans,
but the way you
use them is inspired,
especially in
what you call sushi!
Would you mind including them
in the sample platter, as well?
[SUSHI CHEF 7A]
Sure, no problem.
[WHIS]
Uh! You are truly a peach.
[groans]
[breathes heavily]
Do you think anything's
broken, sweetie?
No, but it hurts,
like a lot!
That's what you get
for trying to fight, Goten.
--You're just kids!
--C'mon, Mom!
[VEGETA] What the hell
have I been doing?
What was the point?
The prince of all Saiyans,
reduced to a butler?
Well no more!
From now on
I kneel to no one!
Guess you can't
face the truth, either.
[yells]
[VEGETA]
He's doing it again!
I can't even find
the strength to move!
My, my-- Is that
your idea of power?
[BEERUS]
Absolutely pathetic.
And you have the gall to call
yourselves a "warrior race."
That's what disgusts me
about Saiyans.
So much bravado
but you always let me down.
[VEGETA groans]
[panting]
Vegeta!
Your father used to buckle
under my foot like this.
Despite all his muscle-flexing
and fist-waving,
he couldn't even
scratch my heel.
You and your father
are exactly the same.
Weaklings pretending to rule
from imaginary thrones.
[gasps]
[BEERUS] What a day
of disappointments!
No pudding,
no Super Saiyan God!
This world is
nothing but a tease!
So needless to say...
There's no reason for me
to keep the earth intact.
This world and its creatures
will serve this galaxy
equally well as dust.
Ha! Of all the ways that
a man can die in the universe,
killed by a Destroyer
deity in battle
might be as noble as it gets.
Thank you.
You'd be shocked how
few people understand that.
Uuh!
That's it! I'm trying to be
a gracious host and all
but I'm getting really tired
of you ruining my party
when you weren't
even invited, okay!
I want you off
this boat right now!
No! Bulma, no!
[BEERUS]
Mmm.
Don't grumble! If you've
got somethin' to say
then just say it!
[chuckles]
Beerus, please have mercy!
Whatever you plan to do,
do it to me!
Don't hurt her!
[smack]
[VEGETA yells]
We got you!
Mom, say something.
Are you okay?
[BULMA moans]
[VEGETA yells]
What have you done?
How could you?
What did you do...
to my Bulma?
[WHIS]
Hmm. Hmph.
[BEERUS]
Hm.
Mark my words, Beerus.
Mark them well.
You're going to suffer
for what you've done.
[chuckles intensely]
♪ Closing Song ♪
I see all these kids
As I walk to school
Their colorful backpacks
All unique and cool
I can't help but wonder
which color I'd choose
If I were still a kid
Where would I run off to? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
How am I lookin' now that
I've grown into an adult? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
Do I look like I'm proud
of who I've finally become?
Oh, I know I've made mistakes
But I'm tryin' to get it right
And I'm willing just to wait
For the moment I can shine
This anthem
Is a story for all time!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Looks like Vegeta's training
has really paid off,
especially now that he's mad!
I've never seen him so strong!
Still, this is a Destroyer
we're talking about,
so Vegeta's rage
might not be enough,
and we need someone else
to step up, too.
But wait, Beerus is
challenging who next?
Oolong? What can he do?
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Goku Makes an Entrace!
A Last Chance
from Lord Beerus?!"
Good luck, Oolong!