♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the battle continued
between Goku
and the merged
Saiyan warrior, Kefla,
with both fighters doing
all they could to stay
in the Tournament of Power
and save their universes
from instant annihilation.
Even with Goku elevated
to Super Saiyan Blue,
the combined power of Caulifla
and Kale seemed to be too much.
But Goku refused to quit.
[GOKU]
No. This isn't over yet, Kefla.
Well that's okay with me!
Just remember, you asked...
...when you're choking
on my power!
[NARRATOR]
Once before in this Tournament,
Goku had achieved an immense
new height of power difficult
for even Destroyer
gods to master.
And somehow, he has reached
that pinnacle again... Now!
[NARRATOR]
"Signs of a Turnabout!
The Autonomous Ultra
Instinct Erupts!"
[KEFLA growls]
Damn you. What is that power?
[GOKU roars]
[KEFLA gasping]
You need to face the facts,
Kefla. You cannot stop me now.
I'll be the judge of that.
[VEGETA, TOP]
Huh?
Damnit, Kakarot.
[laughs]
That's right, Goku,
keep getting stronger.
Be your best ape.
Is that it? Oh, my. Has Goku
really found it again?
His energy's feeling like
"Boom-Boom-Whoosh-
Bang-Bang-Pow"!
Yes, like, "Boom-Boom-Whoosh-
Bang-Bang-Pow" indeed,
Your Majesty.
This is quite a sight.
Once more,
that Saiyan is venturing
into the domain of the gods.
I wonder, how will the
mighty Jiren respond?
Goku's giving off some
incredible heat!
And look at his eyes.
It's that same focused glimmer
he had against Jiren.
It's Ultra Instinct, all right.
He couldn't have achieved
this without another catalyst.
This time it must
have been Kefla.
You mean it was her
enormous energy?
Yes, sir.
The first time that Goku
reached Ultra Instinct it was
the sheer force of his Spirit
Bomb that triggered him,
and Kefla's energy is roughly
equivalent to that blast.
Spurred by her great power,
Goku has defied the odds, and
his own limits, once again.
It's magnificent!
If he's truly done it,
and rekindled his
Autonomous Ultra Instinct,
he'll stop her, for sure!
The tide of this battle
is turning yet again sir.
[growls] Hurry, Kefla!
You've got to smack him
out of the ring now,
before he fully masters
Ultra Instinct!
Hell, yeah!
You really are
cookin' now, Goku!
I can feel the heat
your body's churning out
all the way from down here!
Is that your "Automatic Ultra
Reflex" thing or whatever?
It's Autonomous Ultra Instinct.
Yeah, yeah. Well,
I gotta give you props.
It sure is one hell of a look,
but on the other hand...
...I won't be
outdone by anybody.
I'll just have to up
my own game, too!
[KEFLA yelling]
[yelling]
[BOTH grunt]
Now they're making an
actual tempest in the ring.
Those Saiyans have never
been much for subtlety.
They're made for each other,
there's no mistake.
They've figured out how to reach
Super Saiyan Two as Kefla!
Yeah, that's what
I'm talkin' about!
My power just keeps rising.
It's incredible!
I gotta say, it's a real
privilege to be born a Saiyan!
Go on, power up more,
I dare ya!
No matter how high you climb,
I'll follow and leave
you in the dust!
Uh! Well, there goes
more of the ring!
[ROSHI] And think of the damage
if those two collide head-on.
There probably won't
be a ring left!
[ALL gasp]
What's happening up there?
Is that... Dad and Kefla?
We're looking at two titans now.
When one of them transcends
to a new level,
it prompts the other to
do the same. On and on!
You're saying that
because of Dad,
the power of their fusion is
even greater than it was before?
That's right.
I can feel her energy getting
bigger with every minute.
She's in a completely
different league now.
[GOHAN]
Come on, Dad...
[KEFLA yelling]
[KEFLA laughs] I can't get over
how awesome this feels!
I've got so much power
flowing through me,
I bet if I really wanted I could
rip your whole universe apart
with a single blast!
[GOHAN gasping]
Just feel her energy.
She may have even surpassed
Goku's strength
when he first got to this form.
Stronger than Dad, you sure?
Who knows, she's been
amping him up, too.
He's still reaching deeper
into this form's potential.
[KEFLA]
Done already?
Sure you don't wanna
try charging up more?
I'm good.
I think this is all
the power I need.
Heh, heh. You think so?
All right. You're gonna be
sorry when I blow you away!
[yelling]
[grunting]
Hey! Dodging like
that is for sissies!
[KEFLA growling]
He's dodging everything!
Yet Goku's barely
moving from his spot--
his precision's unbelievable.
If he can anticipate Kefla's
every attack like this,
her enormous power-up
won't matter!
This is bad! She can't even
lay a finger on him!
[growling]
Kefla! Step it up!
I didn't give you
those earrings to miss!
She has attained a level
of strength and speed
few in the Multiverse
have ever known.
But against Goku's reactions,
it seems she will
still fall short.
[CHAMPA growling]
Bwah! Kefla! Smash that
stinkin' punk to pieces!
Uh, Champa? Is something
wrong with your Kai?
That's just his angry side. He
usually represses it in public.
[FUWA]
Bwah!
[yelling]
You tryin' to make
a fool out of me?!
[VEGETA] Kakarot's movements--
He's reading her like a book.
It's almost like his body
is reacting on its own.
[gasps]
[VEGETA]
No. Don't tell me...
Neither of you yet possess
the necessary speed.
You two are both still
thinking before you move,
rather than just moving.
And I'm afraid this habit
is especially strong
with you, Vegeta.
All this overthinking's
limiting your fighting speed.
Listen. Messages
only travel through
your nervous system so
fast, relying on thoughts
for physical action costs you
precious fighting time.
The end goal for you both should
be to master the ability
to have each part
of your body think
and move independently
of all other parts.
I admit, this is
exceedingly difficult.
In fact, not even Lord
Beerus has mastered
this completely yet,
and he's a god.
But if you overcome
the learning curve,
you'll be able to avoid
any danger, however severe.
[VEGETA] You've figured
out that technique
Whis told us about, didn't you?
So that's what this is, Kakarot.
You just had to
show me up again...
[KEFLA yelling]
[KEFLA yells]
Ha!
[gasps]
[GOKU yells]
[KEFLA screaming]
[KRILLIN, TIEN]
He got her!
It's over now!
[BOTH gasping]
[BOTH]
Whoa!
[GOKU growling]
[BEERUS]
Hm...
[KEFLA grunts]
[laughing]
You didn't really think that
punch would hurt me, did ya?
You may have awesome reflexes,
but your attacks when you're
like this are just pathetic!
Come on, Goku.
Don't disappoint me!
You can do better, can't ya?
Yeah. I'm starting to
get a handle on it.
I can do much better.
Behold the power
of Ultra Instinct.
[JIREN grunts]
Something the matter, Jiren?
[DYSPO]
You concerned about this guy?
Look there. Jiren's back
on his feet again.
I suppose Goku
has enticed him.
He's become far too
mighty to ignore.
And his contest with the merged
one is certainly fascinating.
All eyes are on them now.
Ha! Well it does look like
you've turned it
up another notch,
but you still haven't shown me
you can use this upgrade
to pack a decent punch.
[KEFLA] Ooh, is your silence
supposed to scare me?
All it really does is make
me wanna kick your ass!
So get ready!
Okay. Here I go!
[KEFLA gasping]
[KEFLA screams]
[groaning]
There's no way.
What's the matter, Kefla?
Is that all you've got for me?
[KEFLA growls]
[KEFLA screams]
[grunts]
[KEFLA groaning]
[GOKU growls]
Is she okay?!
[KEFLA screams]
[panting]
How is she still on her feet
after taking all those attacks?
Is she invincible? Or what?
Hardly.
There's no doubt
Kefla's fortitude
and fighting spirit
are commendable.
However, Goku's strikes are
not nearly as potent as they
should be, considering
the extent of his power.
Perhaps he has still not
adjusted to the new way
his muscles work through
Autonomous Ultra Instinct,
and how to command
them for attacks.
This wasted effort is costly.
If he cannot defeat her
with his next volley,
I fear his strength
may give out.
I'm gonna finish this right now.
♪♪
[KEFLA growls]
Damn you.
No you won't!
I'm nowhere close to done!
[KEFLA yelling]
Go go go go go the distance...
You feel their energy?
It's surging even higher now!
If that's what you want
then I'm gonna throw everything
I've got into this next attack!
[yelling]
Wanna test my limits,
so let's go
Show me how hard you hit
[BOTH]
Wow!
It looks so beautiful!
She's shiny like a star!
Aw, yeah! What kind
of move is that?
Kefla's energy is radiating
outward in every direction
as highly concentrated
rays--like laser beams.
Most uncanny.
One might say she's literally
become the ultimate weapon.
I may not know what's going on,
but I do know I like it!
Go, Kefla!
With Goku's threat making her
think she either had to win
now risk losing the Tournament,
she found an even greater
extreme of power.
"There is no such
conquering weapon
as the necessity of conquering."
[KEFLA yelling]
I'll see you in Hell!
Looks bad. If one of those
rays hits Goku head-on,
it could be the end for him!
That's so much energy! Is she
planning to burn through
all she's got left
to knock him out?
[yells]
[GOKU]
Ka...
[KEFLA grunts]
...me...
[KEFLA growls]
[yells]
Waking senses,
strength that's endless
Passed the point of all we knew
[GOKU]
...ha...
So the battle must continue
Go go go go go the distance
[KEFLA yelling]
Fight fight in the ultimate
battle just for fun
So so so so so preposterous
Ha ha ha some say it's foolish
We don't care 'cause
we were born to fight
That's all we want
...me...
[yelling]
Give it your all
Go until you become undone
Not bad, but you can't
dodge in midair!
Game over, Goku!
Now you're through!
[gasps]
[GOKU]
Ha!
Ha!!
[KEFLA screaming]
[GOKU yells]
[KEFLA screams]
[KALE, CAULIFLA scream]
[KALE, CAULIFLA groan]
[CABBA]
Caulifla! Kale!
[CAULIFLA]
Ow...
[BOTH] Wowie! That was
such an amazing fight!
Contestants Kale and Caulifla
of the Sixth Universe,
known collectively as Kefla, are
eliminated from the Tournament.
Bye now, Kale and Caulifla.
Supreme Kai Fuwa...
Lord Champa...
I'm sorry. We've failed you.
Hey, Goku! You bastard!
Next time I'll kick
your ass, I swear it!
Hey, now! Take it easy!
Fuwa, what to do, what to do?
They couldn't even stop
him with the Potaras!
How could you both lose
to that numbskull?!
That means it's down
to the Namekians, sir.
If they're knocked out,
too, then we're done.
[CHAMPA growls]
Crap!
Only two more fighters left?
This is really bad!
How can the fate of my whole
Universe rest on Namekians?
Hey! Saonel! Pilina!
You know what you
have to do, right?
Yes, Lord Champa,
just leave it to us.
We won't let you down.
No matter what!
We will take out the Seventh
and then win this whole thing!
[sighs] He won. Oh man,
that was close.
In view of the circumstances,
Goku made an excellent choice.
With limited stamina,
he needed to win quickly.
And a close-range Kamehameha had
the power his punches lacked.
With the superior reflexes
of Ultra Instinct,
he knew he could avoid her
onslaught while he charged up,
then unleash everything in one
attack to knock Kefla out.
It may have worked
this time but I doubt
he'll be able to
use that trick again.
He'll have to face Jiren
and whoever else attacks.
You're right, Master Roshi.
If only he could punch
without thinking, too.
[WHIS] That is the hardest
aspect of Ultra Instinct.
Skilled martial artists
think constantly in battle,
probing for weaknesses and
devising the best assault.
Goku's melee attacks
were underwhelming
because he was still trying to
command his body consciously,
thus sending contradictory
signals to his muscles
that were moving independently
through Ultra Instinct.
To succeed, he must
learn to let go,
separating his conscious mind
from his body so the subliminal
can take over. The question
is whether he can do this
in the short time
remaining in this contest.
It's a most fascinating
development to watch.
You agree don't you,
Lord Beerus?
Don't try to rope me
into your prattling, Whis.
[DYSPO] Looks like Goku's
attacks are improving.
He's getting even more
polished in that new form.
[TOP] The longer we wait, the
stronger he's going to become.
[JIREN]
Mm.
[GOKU grunting]
[panting]
I can't hold that form anymore.
Looks like I'm out of energy.
The glories of this "Ultra
Instinct" do not come cheap.
It seems to dance through battle
like an untouchable god
one's body must pay a toll
so severe it's
essentially paralyzing.
Heal quickly, Goku.
As distasteful as it may be
to associate with you,
I'm afraid I need you to
keep working on my behalf.
[chuckles]
This Ultra Instinct.
If you can do it,
then obviously I can, too.
Damn you, Kakarot.
You may have gotten there first,
but I will master it.
[NARRATOR]
Goku has prevailed over Kefla.
But with only 17 minutes left
in the desperate Tournament of
Power, there's no time to rest.
Can Goku find a way
to fully embrace
Autonomous Ultra Instinct,
and keep his universe intact?
The clock keeps ticking,
next time on Dragon Ball Super!
A 70 centimeter squared window
Today the sun broke
through the clouds
The rain is fin'ly gone
Gonna open up
the window for once
No reason, just because
This room has been
stained with the sighs
Of everyday regret
Now it's time to clear the air
Every moment was consumed
with my thoughts of you
Knowing in my heart those dreams
won't be coming true
I've always wanted nothing more
than to see your face
I move on knowing that your
mem'ry can't be erased
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Now the Second Universe
is coming at us
in a full-on group attack!
After Ribrianne uses her
love-power to make
a crazy transformation, the
battle gets unexpectedly tough.
And since I can barely
stay on my feet,
I'll have to depend
on the Androids
to get me out in one piece.
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Showdown of Love!
The Androids vs.
the 2nd Universe!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?