♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super.
[BRIANNE]
Happiness to one and all!
I send you my love!
Ribrianne!
The thunder of the wild!
And the roar of love!
Kakunsa!
The strike of love,
with dreams and magic!
Roasie!
[ALL]
Transformation complete!
[NARRATOR] With the fates
of entire universes on the line
in the chaotic
Tournament of Power,
a peculiar group of
battle maidens transformed,
and then confounded
their opponents
with energy attacks
fueled by love.
I'll teach you to mess
with our transformation!
I will make you pay!
[NARRATOR]
Android 17 faced an onslaught
of unrestrained,
impassioned attacks
from the beastly maiden Kakunsa,
but with his trademark style,
the artificial human
managed to keep his cool.
[A17]
This fight has been instructive.
I do appreciate the lesson.
[NARRATOR]
17 prevailed in the struggle,
but that only put a bigger
target on his back.
[BRIANNE] It wasn't enough to
interrupt our transformation.
You had to knock out Bikal
and Kakunsa, too.
I swear, you will pay for that!
Maidenly anger!
[NARRATOR]
The showdown continues... now!
"Gohan, Get Ruthless!
Showdown with
the 10th Universe!"
Ribrianne! I failed!
I tried to be strong
but it was all in vain!
[cries]
[BRIANNE]
How dare you knock her out!
Kakunsa is a noble fighter!
But thanks to you
she's finished!
Only a truly heinous,
cold-blooded man
could target such
a delicate maiden!
Listen to me, cruel
villain of darkness,
you enemy of the Second! Say
your name so I can know my foe!
Heh, I dared fight back,
so now I'm a villain?
Very well!
I am your worst nightmare,
Android Number 17!
Laying it on a bit
thick now, isn't he?
Yeah, I'm surprised--
it kinda seems like he's
having fun messing with her.
[A17]
Warrior of Love! Face your doom!
And never mind that I have
my own universe to protect!
That's right, I am only
here to defeat you!
Well that defeat
will never happen.
Because I fight with
the great power of love!
No one will ever harm
the Second Universe!
I'll make sure of it!
[A17]
I see.
Then we'll have to find out
which force is stronger.
Your own desire to protect,
or mine to destroy.
My thoughts exactly!
Let me show you the real
power of Ribrianne!
[BRIANNE yells]
[A17 growls]
[BRIANNE grunting]
[A17 grunting]
[BRIANNE grunts]
You're not half bad, are you?
I don't want your
compliments, villain!
I just want to defeat you!
Yatcha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha!
Yatcha-cha-cha-cha-cha!
[GOKU groaning]
You shouldn't have
knocked out Kakunsa!
The Seventh Universe
will pay for that!
[GOKU grunting]
What's the matter
with you, Goku?!
Some of her energy blasts
have trick movements
that are confusing him.
The vengeance of
a maiden warrior.
There can be beauty
in that, as well.
[SOUS ROAS, BRIANNE grunting]
[BRIANNE yelling]
[GOKU gasping]
Yatcha! Yatchaina-ken style!
Yatcha-cha-cha-cha-cha...!
Yatcha-cha-cha...!
[GOKU gasping]
[SOUS ROAS]
Yatcha-cha-cha-cha-cha...!
Ya... cha!
[GOKU grunts]
Huh?
[SOUS ROAS] You've let me
surround you completely!
Big mistake!
This is where I get my
payback for Kakunsa!
[BRIANNE, A17 grunting]
Atcho...
Hai!
That Saiyan fool was careless
again and now he's trapped!
Now he's going to witness the
true fury of a scorned maiden.
Uh?
[ALL gasping]
Huh?!
17 took them all instead!
A perfect attack!
What?!
Seems you're having trouble.
Need a hand?
No thanks. I'm doin' just fine.
How cruel to ignore
your adversary
in the middle of a fight!
Well then, I guess I
really am a villain.
Bad news for you. I'm starting
to see how you fight.
[GOKU grunts, yells]
[SOUS ROAS]
Ya! Yatcha-cha-cha...!
[SOUS ROAS gasps]
Heads up!
[SOUS ROAS]
Wha--?
[GOKU grunting]
That's more like it, buddy!
Yes, it looks like she's the
one pinned in by energy now.
[gasping]
This fight has been
very instructive.
I appreciate the lesson.
[SOUS ROAS gasping]
Atcha!
Oh, no!
[SOUS ROAS screams]
[SOUS ROAS grunting]
Uh!
Goku of the Seventh Universe.
I have to admit...
...you sure are strong.
Roasie. You sure you're okay?
I'm all right now,
thanks to you.
[BRIANNE] I won't let
you attack her again!
You can make this
easier on us all...
...if you go over
the edge on your own.
[BRIANNE grunts]
[SOUS ROAS gasping]
Uh! Oh, no! My maidens!
No need for you
to worry just yet.
[HELES]
Hm?
[PER] These maidens are still
protected by a knight.
Take my hand, my ladies.
Let me to steal you away.
[GOKU]
Uh!
Instant Transmission, huh?
That's right, that guy's from
the Second Universe's
planet Yardrat.
If they want to run, so be it.
On to the next.
Yeah. It wouldn't be smart
to chase 'em too far.
Just try not to drop your
guard from now on.
[GOKU]
Heh. Yeah. I hear ya.
[BEERUS grumbles]
Watching that sloppy,
impulsive mortal fight
is going to drive me mad!
[CHAMPA] Which fighter
do you mean, Beerus?
Because I wouldn't
just worry about Goku!
Say what?!
[laughs]
If I were you, I would
feel even more anxious
about two of his
weaker teammates.
Ha!
Go get 'em, Botamo!
Ha, ha. It's my pleasure.
I wasn't planning to face Botamo
this early--he could be trouble.
If you don't mind, Piccolo,
I'd like to take him myself.
Huh?
[PICCOLO chuckles] All right,
he's all yours, kid.
[GOHAN]
How 'bout it?
You game for a one-on-one?
[BOTAMO] Sure! Please,
attack me any way you like--
I can spare a few
minutes to play around!
[yells]
Huh?
[BOTAMO laughs]
I hope you didn't think
that would hurt me.
[PICCOLO]
Hm... Botamo can absorb attacks
all day without taking damage.
What's Gohan planning?
[GOHAN yells, grunting]
[BOTAMO laughs]
What do you think
you're doin', boy?!
If you just keep railin' on him
you're the one who's
gonna collapse!
Excellent work, Botamo!
You must be feeling
frantic now, brother.
Here you are about
to lose another one.
[GOHAN grunting]
[BOTAMO laughs]
[GOKU]
Yo, Piccolo.
What's up?
You curious about your
son's fighting skills, too?
[GOKU]
Yeah, of course.
[PICCOLO]
So, how do you think this'll go?
[GOKU]
I'm optimistic.
I told him all about
my fight with Botamo
in the last tournament.
So I'm not too worried.
I'm confident Gohan's thought
up a decent enough strategy.
Guess we'll see.
[GOHAN grunting]
[BOTAMO laughs]
[BOTAMO] Enough playing.
It's my turn now.
Uh?
That's it!
He's starting to lift him up!
[BOTAMO gasps]
No! My feet!
I can't touch the ground!
[GOHAN grunting]
Do something,
you gigantic fool!
You got to find some way
to fight back quickly
or he's going to push
you out of the ring!
I can't reach him!
Then retreat! Jump away!
[BOTAMO]
I can't jump!
He's got me!
[GOHAN growling]
[BOTAMO groans]
This should finish the job!
[yells]
[BOTAMO screams]
Anybody who thinks they
can get by on raw power
is no match for me.
If I'm done, so are you!
Oh no, the boy's dropped
his guard again!
[BOTAMO]
Come on!
Botamo of the Sixth Universe
has been knocked out
of the ring as well.
[FUTURE ZENO]
Hmm, let's see, where are you.
Botamo... Botamo...
And boop!
Bye-bye, silly-billy!
[CHAMPA growls]
You useless waste of space!
How could you get
knocked out that fast?!
I'm sorry, sir.
Heh, heh. I knew
that would happen--
I was just building suspense.
Looks like Gohan pulled it off.
Well, I'm out. I'm gonna
go get back in the action.
Remember, don't get
careless, Goku.
Yeah, I know!
A strong fight, warrior.
You serve the Seventh admirably.
[GOHAN]
Hm?
Believe me, I am one
who would know.
My name is Obni, of the Tenth.
And I'm his teammate, Rubalt.
[OBNI] I have judged you
to be a worthy adversary
in this tournament.
Now fight me!
[GOHAN exhales]
[RUBALT chuckles] Well then,
I guess I'm dancin' with you.
That works for me.
[OBNI chuckles]
[ZIRCOR]
What the hell?!
You'll never lay a hand
on the great defenders
of the Second again.
Take heart, Maidens.
I won't let the flames
of your love fade away.
[BOTH]
Ooh, Thank you.
You're our hero!
[GRAND MINISTER]
Zircor of the Tenth Universe
has been eliminated.
[ZENO]
Bye!
Oh dear, they've taken
out another one.
Seems we must brace
ourselves for the end.
No, not yet! We still
have two more chances.
Obni and Rubalt are down there!
Find a way, warriors!
You are our last hope!
Aw man, this is bad.
Eight of us are already
out of the ring.
You have no need to be
alarmed, Lord Rumsshi,
we will save the Tenth
Universe from destruction
no matter what it takes.
It's all up to you!
So do you think he'll
be able to handle this?
Are you ready?
[GOHAN]
His defenses are flawless.
I'll have to stay on my toes.
[RUBALT chuckles]
[OBNI grunts]
[GOHAN grunts]
[PICCOLO]
Hmph.
[RUBALT yells]
[PICCOLO groans]
[GOHAN grunting]
You're keeping pace.
I knew I was right about you.
I've been waiting to
face such a worthy foe.
[grunts, screams]
[GOHAN gasps]
Impressive.
I can't tell which
one's the real him!
[yells]
[OBNI yells]
Gohan!
[GOHAN groaning]
He's putting on a rather
promising show.
We know that you
can do it, Obni!
Win this for all of us!
Funny. I thought you
had given up hope.
That was before.
Now that one of our own is
actually performing well,
I'm eager to stick around.
This technique will be most
difficult for Gohan to overcome.
The half-Saiyan not
only uses his eyes,
but unconsciously
reads the energy
of his opponents to
follow their movements.
Obni has learned to divorce
his energy from his actions,
redirecting it at will to
prevent his physical body
from being tracked.
[GOHAN grunts]
In other words, the guy's
manipulating his energy
as a fake-out, to make Gohan
think he's somewhere he's not.
I know it seems rudimentary,
but it's actually quite
a rather sophisticated and
nearly unbeatable technique.
I don't like the sound of that.
They're down to two. But that
doesn't mean they're done.
[RUBALT, PICCOLO grunting]
[PICCOLO yelling]
You must be feelin'
pretty desperate!
Your blind attacks are
missin' me completely!
Oh am I missing, or just cutting
off all your escape routes?
Uh--?! What?!
[PICCOLO]
That's right. You're through!
[RUBALT gasping]
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[RUBALT groaning]
And now to make this official...
get out of my ring.
Rubalt from the Tenth Universe
has been knocked out,
Your Majesties.
[FUTURE ZENO]
Tapping screens is very fun!
Let's see... Rubalt is... here.
Boop!
I'm sorry, Gowasu. I failed.
Come on, no need to worry.
Obni's still out there, with
that incredible technique.
He can win, I'm quite sure.
[OBNI yells]
Goku's son is in
a lot of trouble!
Oh yes, he may lose now!
--[OBNI yelling]
--[GOHAN groans]
[yelling]
Let's go!
Refusing to give up
to the bitter end.
You are a true warrior.
Get ready!
[OBNI yells]
[GOHAN groans]
I just figured out
how to find you.
[OBNI]
What?
[GOHAN yelling]
Huh?
[yells]
Huh?!
Since he can't read
that fighter's moves,
he's letting himself get hit,
then counter-attacking.
[WHIS] It works in a way, though
with an obvious downside.
It means Gohan
can't attack without
sustaining damage himself.
[BEERUS] And his opponent keeps
pressing, even though he knows
he'll be countered.
They're both giving their all.
I hate this! Goku's son had
better not lose this one!
[GOHAN, OBNI grunting]
[panting]
[panting] I'm impressed you've
lasted this long against me.
What is your name, boy?
My name is Gohan.
Of planet Earth.
[OBNI]
Well met, Gohan of Earth.
I am pleased we
have crossed paths.
But with all my
comrades defeated,
the fate of the Tenth
rests with me.
There are lives I must protect.
[yelling]
[OBNI groans]
Hey, look! Gohan's attacks
are starting to land
like normal now!
[OBNI grunting]
Yes. Obni can no longer expend
energy on his deception.
[GOHAN yells]
[OBNI growls]
[GOHAN]
Ka...
...me...
...ha...
Ha!
[OBNI screaming]
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, dear. Obni's fallen too.
Obni of the Tenth Universe
is eliminated, sires.
[ZENO]
Time to tap again!
Goodbye Obni, you are done!
Boop!
[FUTURE ZENO] The Tenth
Universe has no one left!
All warriors of
the Tenth Universe
have been thrown from the ring.
Their team has been defeated.
By the rules laid forth,
Universe Ten of the Cosmos
will be obliterated at once.
Thank you, Obni.
You fought with great valor.
[BOTH]
Universe Ten.
Bye-bye!
Heh, heh!
Farewell, Lord Rumsshi.
[exhales]
It's time to go.
I know.
[NARRATOR] Sharing the same
fate as the Ninth,
the entire Tenth
Universe has now been
expunged from existence.
Another chilling reminder
of the Tournament of Power's
cataclysmic stakes.
With this steady
culling of the field,
the battles between the
truly strongest fighters
in the Cosmos are
about to begin.
What fate is in store for Goku,
and the rest of the Seventh?
Only 37 minutes remain
until the end of the match.
The struggle continues,
next time on Dragon Ball Super!
When the time has come
to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever in my mind
as I look up to the sky
I was watching you
from your left side
Was trying to get
a good look at your face
The tears in your eyes;
were you laughing or crying?
Your long hair in the way
Blocking the thoughts inside
When the time has
come to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever I will wait,
for the light to show the way
For us to meet again
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And those fighters from
the Eleventh are ready
to attack again, but with
even more intensity!
There's a wild
match between Hit
and the hyper-fast
warrior Dyspo,
then another Pride
Trooper jumps in!
And man, are they a strong pair!
But here's the good news:
looks like I might finally form
that dream team with Hit!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"A Transcendent Light-Speed
Battle Erupts!
Goku and Hit's United Front!"
Make sure you
don't miss it, okay?