♪ Opening Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Through the
power of the Dragon Balls,
mankind no longer remembers
the destruction
caused by Majin Buu.
Instead, they believe
their beloved hero
prevented it
from ever happening.
Yeah. You might remember
how it kind of got around
that I saved the world
from Armageddon.
Well that's what it's for.
And the prize money is,
uh, substantial.
A hundred million Zeni.
[GOKU, GOTEN]
A hundred million?
I'm glad you like it.
So, uh, I was wondering
if I could, you know,
train with King Kai now?
[CHICHI]
Yeah, sure.
Just drop by
from time to time, okay?
Awesome!
[giggles]
All right, then.
See ya' soon.
[NARRATOR] Goku has left
to train on King Kai's planet.
While across the far
expanse of the universe,
something very strange,
and very troubling,
appears to be
sharpening its claws.
[BEERUS] Tell you what.
I'll only take half.
[NARRATOR]
"To the Promised Resort!
Vegeta Takes a Family Trip?!"
[KING KAI humming]
Doesn't get better than this!
Perfect weather
for a little drive!
You know, when evil monsters
aren't bent on destruction,
life's as easy as pie!
A great big easy pie
and you can cut me
a world peace!
[laughing]
Why aren't you guys
laughing at that?
It's funny because
I took "piece of pie"
and combined it with
"world peace"
even though they're
spelled differently.
See, we comedians
call that a pun.
It's the highest form
of comedy, which you'd know
if you'd paid attention
in your Pun Theory class!
Oh! Let's change the subject
and put the pedal to the metal!
[screaming]
[BOTH screaming]
[KING KAI, GREGORY,
BUBBLES screaming]
[crashing]
Aah! Uh. Whoops.
[laughs]
[KING KAI]
What were you thinking?
Who jumps in front of a Kai
on a joy ride? Seriously!
[GOKU]
Yeah, my bad, I'm sorry.
But hey. It's not that big
of a problem, right?
Can't you just
use your powers
to fix your car
and house faster?
[KING KAI] Of course! But fixing
them by hand kills time
and gives me something
to gripe about--I mean--
is something I enjoy because
I believe in hard work. Yeah.
But I digress--
why are you here, Goku?
[GOKU]
What? Why do you think?
Don't talk
with your mouth full!
It's rude and
it's a choking hazard!
Aah!
[chuckles]
I'm stuffed!
Don't worry,
there's no trouble.
I came here to train
a bit, that's all.
Your world's gravity
is ten times stronger
than Earth's, remember?
I can't think of a better
place in the universe
to build some serious muscle!
[KING KAI sighs deeply]
[GOKU] Hm?
You don't sound happy.
Of course I'm not.
Why would I be happy
that a Saiyan
is using my sacred world
as his own workout gym?
And let me guess, you'll want
room and board with that, too?
Yeah, sure. That sounds great!
Come on King Kai, you act like
we're not pals or somethin'!
Hey! Maybe you forgot
because of my disarming
sense of humor,
but I'm a pretty major deal!
I'm way higher than a Guardian
and you wouldn't have
talked to Kami like this!
[GOKU chuckles] I'm gonna
jump to it, all right?
[KING KAI]
Hey!
[GOKU]
Man, this feels great!
Nothing better than training
on a full stomach!
Well change
your clothes at least!
You look like you're
on safari or something!
Yeah now we're talkin'.
Man, it's been way too long.
[BULMA]
We'll be there soon, Trunks.
You better wake up!
[yawns]
Flying like this takes
too much time, Mom.
If you could just learn
to fly like me and Dad do,
we could get places
a whole lot faster, you know.
[BULMA grunts]
Well excuse me, young man,
but my human body is not
built for mach speeds.
[TRUNKS]
So... Dad still up top?
He sure is. He still
refuses to come inside--
you Saiyans are all off
your rockers if you ask me.
This isn't anywhere
close to proper training.
I'm sorry. If you wanted me
to make it a challenge.
You should have
just said so, dear.
[yells]
Can you handle this?
[BULMA grunts]
[VEGETA]
Hm! What a joke.
[car horn honks]
[indistinctive chatter]
[BULMA] This is nice,
don't you think?
[VEGETA] Don't even
think of buying me that.
[BULMA] Ooh, these
sunglasses are a must!
[TRUNKS] Can I get this? The
lady says it's an "accessory"!
[BULMA] Trunks? You okay
in there by yourself?
[TRUNKS]
I'm fine, Mom.
I can put on my own pants.
So why?
Why what?
Normally when
I suggest a family trip
I get the trademark
Vegeta scoff.
So why'd you agree to
come along with us this time?
Tch.
And if you can land
even one punch on my face,
I'll take you
to that amusement park
you're always going on about.
[TRUNKS yells]
[VEGETA yells]
[groans]
Stop that whining!
I'll take you
to the stupid park!
I'm just keeping a promise,
it's nothing more than that.
How cute! So you made
a promise to Trunks?
[TRUNKS]
Thanks, Dad!
This is way better
than an amusement park!
Awwwe!
You big old softy!
Hey! I'm not soft!
[BULMA laughs]
Calm down, I'm kidding.
There is something
different, though.
I'm not sure how to describe it,
but ever since you fought Buu--
I don't know, you've changed.
Ta-da! They fit!
Check it, Dad!
Is this cool or what?
Don't ask me! Though I'd
hardly call someone "cool"
when they can't even
button a shirt.
Huh? Aah! Oopsie.
[TRUNKS laughs]
[BULMA chuckles]
Well anyway.
Come on!
[TRUNKS]
Wha--Wh-Whoa!
[BULMA shrieks]
[TRUNKS laughs]
[TRUNKS]
Yeah! Faster! Faster!
[VEGETA grunts]
[BULMA]
Jeez, this is heavy.
Uh, you guys know I can't
see anything, right?
Just because you won't shop
doesn't mean you can't
carry some stuff!
[TRUNKS]
Uh-ha!
I'd say I deserve a meal.
Fine then! Let's eat!
[BULMA] Excuse me! Can we
get more food over here?
[TRUNKS, VEGETA]
Aah!
This beast is delicious!
[BULMA] I should've known this
would help with his bad mood.
We still need more!
[TRUNKS, VEGETA gasp]
This is so awesome!
[BULMA]
You got anything bigger?
[ALL gasp]
[chuckles]
Pretty great octopus,
right, dear?
I'll eat your whole race!
[VACATIONERS gasp]
[VEGETA yowls]
[VEGETA]
Ah-ha, no! No!
Dad? Are you okay?
This is bad.
[VEGETA growls]
You impudent,
tentacled bastard!
[VEGETA growls]
[BULMA] Calm down, honey.
Just remember to breathe.
[TRUNKS] Yeah Dad,
it's okay. Don't flip out.
Let's just go!
Sorry about that everyone.
Hope you're having
a good vacation!
Don't get the octopus!
[BULMA]
Mm-mmm!
That breeze is nice.
[fog horn blares]
No way!
It's a cruise liner!
You know, my birthday
is coming up.
Maybe we should
charter a big ship like that
and celebrate in style
on the high seas!
What do you say, Trunks?
[TRUNKS]
Yeah! That'd be sweet!
[fast paced drumming]
[VACATIONERS cheering, laughing]
[BULMA] I can't
believe we lost him.
And he hates crowds.
[TRUNKS]
Dad! Dad!
Dad! Where are you?
[BULMA]
Hey! No flying!
Great. Where did Bulma
wander off to now?
Why am I wasting time at this
farce while Kakarot is out--
[MAN 2A]
Yeah!
All right, party people,
it's time for
our local specialty.
So grab a cold drink and
watch 'em dance... with fire!
[VACATIONERS]
Fire!
[PARTY MC 2A]
What do they dance with?
[VACATIONERS]
Fire!
[VEGETA]
I defeated Majin Buu!
I should be hailed
as number one
by every creature
on this planet,
not lost in a crowd
like some commoner.
--[MAN 2A] Party!
--[VEGETA snarls]
[VEGETA] Even so.
I have to keep training.
Every second. I waste here.
I could be losing ground.
To that clown!
Now hold on, everyone!
That guy's not smiling!
I think he needs to come
and have a dance off
with our fire dancers
to get in the mood!
Come on, folks! Chant with me!
All together now!
[ALL] Dance off! Dance off!
Dance off! Dance off!
Hey! Look, it's Dad!
Where? I don't see him!
[VACATIONERS]
Dance off! Dance off!
[VEGETA grunting]
[VACATIONERS continue chanting]
Dance off! Dance off!
That's enough. Enough!
[groans]
[VACATIONERS gasp, murmur]
[VEGETA grunts]
He's flying!
No way! This place rules!
If he's part of the show,
they coulda' told me.
[TRUNKS]
Aw, shoot.
Looks like Dad's checkin' out.
I guess we should be grateful
he lasted this long.
Thanks, Dad!
I had an awesome time!
See you back at home!
[BULMA chuckles]
[BEERUS] Mmmm.
What was I just dreaming?
I can almost remember.
But then it slips away.
[BEERUS]
Hmmm.
Oh, Whis? Are you done? Whis?
[WHIS] I still have
two more minutes,
Lord Beerus.
[birds chirping]
[DINOSAUR 2A growls lowly]
[ALIEN BLOBS cheep]
[roars]
[ALIEN BLOBS shriek]
[DINOSAUR 2A growls lowly]
Mm?
[ALIEN CHIEF 2A]
Ho!
[DINOSAUR 2A roars]
[ALIEN BLOBS cheer]
[ALIEN BLOBS chatter cheerfully]
[ALIEN CHIEF 2A]
He-he-heh.
[WHIS]
I'm terribly sorry
to interrupt your
big moment, Chief.
Huh? Huh?!
But you see,
it's this dinosaur meat.
Word is that
it's most delicious.
We've heard tales of it all
across the Seventh Universe.
I'm sure it was
a most difficult hunt
so I hate to take it from you.
Nevertheless. I am taking it.
Ho ho ho ho!
[WHIS]
Oh, not this tongue.
[ALIEN CHIEF 2A]
Ho ho ho, ho ho ho, ho ho!
Ho ho ho, ho ho ho ho, ho!
[clears throat]
Ho ho ho, ho ho ho ho.
Ho ho, ho ho ho!
[WHIS] Ho ho ho,
ho ho ho ho ho ho.
[ALIEN CHIEF 2A]
Ho ho, ho ho ho.
[WHIS] Ho, ho ho ho ho,
ho ho ho ho ho.
[ALIEN CHIEF 2A]
Ho ho ho, ho ho ho ho.
[sighs] Lord Beerus
only gave me three minutes
to acquire this my own way.
If you could just
hand it over nicely
it will give me
something to brag about.
And you and your world
can escape unharmed.
I'd call that
a win-win situation.
Ho ho ho.
[bellows]
[ALIEN BLOBS]
Eh? Eh?!
[WHIS]
Oh, my.
Your kind can achieve
a combat transformation?
Seems my research
was woefully incomplete.
But I still have forty seconds.
[BEERUS]
Nope! Sorry, time's up.
It's only been two minutes
and twenty seconds,
and you know it!
You sure? Because it
feels more like
two centuries and
twenty years to me, Whis.
Oh pish posh.
I still don't get
why you're so irritable
the first few years
after waking up.
You know all the talk about this
dinosaur meat are just rumors.
And they may not be true.
I'm well aware of that,
but I still think
it's worth a try.
If the stories are true,
then it packs a flavor
unrivaled in the cosmos. Mmm.
I'm hoping it gives a jolt
to my senses and helps me
remember the figure
from my dream.
A dream?
A premonition.
Forgive me, but your
premonitions don't have
much history
of coming to fruition.
You once dreamt
a galactic pop star
was moving into
our solar system.
And that didn't pan out,
now did it?
You're mocking me,
aren't you?
[yells]
[grunts]
Huh?
I find you dreadfully boring.
[growls, yells]
Impressive.
[ALIEN CHIEF 2A laughs]
Huh?!
[bellows]
Is this yours?
[groans]
Are you done now?
It really irks me when a
creature lacks basic manners.
Now then. What was
I talking about?
You had a premonition
about some mysterious figure
you can't recall.
Oh, right. I'm this close
to remembering but I can't.
Oh, and it's such
an annoying feeling,
like having something
caught in your back teeth
that you just can't fish out.
Or a dried up bit
of earwax you can't reach
but you feel it rattling
in your head all day.
You know what I mean, right?
It's the worst!
So, my lord.
What about the meat?
Shall we try some?
Forget it. It doesn't look
that tasty, after all.
[ELDER KAI gasps]
[KIBITO KAI] Ancestor, is there
something the matter?
[ELDER KAI gasps]
[KIBITO KAI] Is there a problem
with the tea? Too bitter?
[ELDER KAI] Are you serious?
You didn't feel that?
[KIBITO KAI]
Feel what, exactly?
Were you born yesterday?
This is bad.
Horribly, horribly bad!
[ELDER KAI] It's only been
thirty-nine years!
Lord Beerus
the Destroyer has awoken!
Mm.
[BEERUS]
Huh?
Training levels.
One. Two. Three. Four!
Engage now!
[groans]
[VEGETA]
Ah!
[groans]
[VEGETA]
Fine, Kakarot.
You are the mightiest Saiyan.
I've admitted that much.
At least for now.
You're ruining my lawn, Goku!
[GOKU] It'll grow back!
Don't make me stop,
I'm just starting to sweat!
[VEGETA] But don't you dare
think this is over.
I won't let you keep me
in second place forever,
feeding on the scraps
of your glory.
I will surpass you.
And even then,
I'll keep pushing.
I'll surpass every single
warrior in the universe!
I won't stop until
I'm the ultimate Number One!
[chuckles intensely]
[BEERUS exhales deeply]
Others might see this
explosion as something foul.
But in my eyes, there is
nothing more beautiful
than a shattering planet.
Are you sure that was wise?
What if that meat
could have helped you?
[BEERUS]
Hm. It's no longer required.
Oh? Is that so?
[BEERUS] Yes. I planned
for the punch of flavor
to jog my sleepy mind, but it's
this full-bodied explosion
that's done the trick.
Now I see him clearly--
the ultimate fighter,
waiting to be awoken.
His power will keep me
suitably entertained.
Now the image has a name.
Then by all means,
let's hear it.
What was it?
[WHIS]
Mm.
It starts with an "s"
I know that much--
a "super" something I think?
Yes. A Super Saiyan God.
A Super Saiyan God?
Are you sure?
I think.
Or is that wrong and
now I'm forgetting again.
That's the trouble with visions.
They're too slippery.
Apparently so. Well I
wouldn't strain your mind
too much about it. Why don't we
go back and get you fed?
You don't have to ask me twice!
[WHIS]
All right then. Hold on.
♪ Closing Song ♪
I see all these kids
As I walk to school
Their colorful backpacks
All unique and cool
I can't help but wonder
which color I'd choose
If I were still a kid
Where would I run off to? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
How am I lookin' now that
I've grown into an adult? Oh!
Hello Hello Hello
Do I look like I'm proud
of who I've finally become?
Oh, I know I've made mistakes
But I'm tryin' to get it right
And I'm willing just to wait
For the moment I can shine
This anthem
Is a story for all time!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
And I forgot Bulma's birthday!
She's having a huge party
while I'm off training,
which isn't good, 'cause she's
scary when she's mad.
Speaking of scary,
there's some sort of
crazy-strong fighter out there,
but King Kai's trying
to keep him from me!
Why would he want to do that?
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Where Does the Dream Pick Up?!
Find the Super Saiyan God!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?