♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the relentless battles
in the Tournament of Power
had two more teams on
the brink of elimination.
The Second and Sixth Universes
did all they could to survive,
but ultimately fell short.
[RABANRA, ZIRLOIN, ZARBUTO]
Pretty Black Hole!
[GOKU]
Ha!
Sorry to make you wait.
Hope you're at peace.
Special Beam Cannon!
[SAONEL gasping]
So this is the true power
of the Seventh Universe's
Namekian warrior?
Impressive.
[ROASIE]
Ready, set...
[ALL]
Love!
Bye-bye!
You taught me much, master.
Good luck to you, Vegeta.
[NARRATOR] The Second and Sixth
Universes have been annihilated,
which means only four more teams
remain in the Tournament.
[VEGETA] I think it's time
for you to say your prayers.
This isn't personal.
I'm just in one hell
of a bad mood.
[NARRATOR]
The fight continues, now!
"Unavoidable?
The Ferocity of
a Stealth Attack!"
[VEGETA yells]
[CATOPESRA yelling]
[CATOPESRA, VEGETA grunting]
[CATOPESRA]
Not bad, ne'er-do-well!
You are a worthy foe!
[VEGETA grunts]
[CATOPESRA] It seems the time
has come for me to unleash my
even-more-unbeatable power!
Mode Change!
'Whirlwind Raging
Ultimate' Mode!
[CATOPESRA]
Now that I'm in Ultimate Mode,
I'm 300 times faster
and more powerful!
[CATOPESRA grunts]
Indecent fiend!
How dare you attack
me mid-speech?!
No more games!
[CATOPESRA]
Whoa!
[VEGETA] I don't have time to
listen to you pump yourself up!
[CATOPESRA] So eager for battle?
Then how do you like this?
[CATOPESRA, VEGETA grunting]
[CATOPESRA yelling]
[VEGETA yells]
[CATOPESRA]
Steel yourself, evil-doer!
And behold, my decisive
secret technique!
Catopesra: The Final Mission!
Final Flash!
[CATOPESRA gasping]
[VEGETA grunting]
[yells]
[CATOPESRA screams]
You see now? That's what a real
finishing move looks like!
[CATOPESRA groaning]
[CATOPESRA screams]
[MOSCO beeping]
Lord Mosco demands answers.
He's asking, "How did you
fall out of the ring?"
[sighs] I'm not sure.
I was on my feet, but then...
It felt like someone had swept
my legs out from under me,
but nobody was there.
[VEGETA]
Heh.
In the end, he took himself out.
Washed-up loser.
[VEGETA grunting]
What was that? Who's there?
What in the world just happened?
They were both moving strangely
at the edge of the ring.
Perhaps another fighter
ambushed them
with some kind of
stealth technique.
Like Instant Transmission,
or maybe an After-Image.
But even then, we should have
at least seen them for a second.
[GOHAN yelps]
Thanks, Piccolo.
You really saved my neck.
How'd you fall?
I don't know. It felt like
somebody kicked me from behind.
I see.
Let's hope we're
not dealing with
another Time-Skipper, like Hit.
You sense that?
There's someone here.
Yeah.
[VEGETA grunts]
[ZENOS]
Uh...
Huh?
I wonder why they
stopped moving?
Yeah.
It's no use. I can't find them.
Yeah, they must be
suppressing their energy.
I really hate it
when things get weird.
[A18 yelps]
Uh! 18, are you okay?!
[A18 grunts]
I don't understand.
She's fighting, but it's
like no one's there!
[laughing]
Hey! What's so funny, rodent?
[gasps] Don't tell me...
The Fourth Universe
must be behind it.
I know Quitela. This has
his foul stench all over it.
What kind of dirty
trick is he up to now?
Any thoughts, Master Roshi?
What could it be?
Can't see his body,
can't see his attacks,
we can't see anything.
I would say it's
an invisible man.
[KRILLIN gasps]
Aw, great, really?
Don't be silly. I haven't
seen that trick in ages.
Heh! Good guess, Wrinkles.
[BEERUS gasps] You actually
have an invisible man?
[laughs]
[A18 groaning]
Listen up, 18! You're fighting
someone that's invisible!
Yeah, I noticed, Krillin.
Not seeing him kind
of gave it all away.
What can she do? How can
she defend or attack?
An invisible man? Well,
this is just what we need!
[A18 groaning]
18, Stay down!
[A18 gasps]
[PICCOLO grunting]
Ha!
[PICCOLO gasping]
Damn. He managed to escape.
Clever try.
By launching an explosive
and wide-ranging attack,
he could strike
without seeing them.
Perhaps, but if he keeps using
that technique
it will exhaust him.
Yes, and once he's tired, then
he'll be at the enemy's mercy.
So if that's not the answer,
then what should they do?
[ROSHI]
Yamcha dealt with this once.
Oh! Hey, Gohan, you can see him
if you spray something
on him, like a nosebleed!
I don't get bloody noses.
Oh. Wait a second.
I think I have an idea.
What is it?
Try all you like!
Nothing you do will stop us!
Good grief, you actually
thought that could work?
Gamisalas is a pro! You won't
hit him with blind attacks! Heh.
You won't catch him and
you won't avoid him either.
Here's what you will do.
You'll sap your precious energy
till there's nothing left!
You heard me!
And once you're drained, he'll
knock you out of the ring!
Wait, look!
What the...?
[PICCOLO grunts]
[GAMISALAS screams]
[GAMISALAS]
Why, you...! Ahh!
Invisibility's a neat trick,
but without it, you're kind
of pathetic aren't you?
[yells]
[GAMISALAS screams]
[GRAND MINISTER] Contestant
Gamisalas of the Fourth Universe
has been knocked out.
[GANOS, MONNA gasp]
[GAMISALAS] Sorry, you guys.
He saw right through me.
You see that, Quitela?
Your dirty tricks won't work.
Not against the might of
the Seventh! It's all over!
[QUITELA growling]
Heh.
[QUITELA] Not over.
Just time for the main event.
Well, that worked out.
Sure did.
[GOKU]
Those two are really doing
a great job down there, huh?
Great work, Gohan and Piccolo!
You can do this!
Calm down. It's a little
early to celebrate.
You're up. Do it, Xiangca!
[XIANGCA]
Mm!
[grunts]
[GOHAN, PICCOLO]
Uh?
[BERGAMO]
Brace yourselves.
[GOHAN, PICCOLO grunt]
[BERGAMO] We've been
summoned from an alternate
reality, and we're going
to take our revenge on you.
I'm going to enjoy
cutting you into ribbons.
No way. I thought the Ninth
Universe was destroyed.
Don't get spooked.
[yells]
Ha. Nice try, big guy.
Uh.
[SORREL grunts]
Hey, what the--?
[GOHAN] What do you think?
Is this a trick?
Some kind of optical illusion?
It doesn't matter.
Ha! Can't touch us!
We won't lose to
smoke and mirrors!
[BASIL]
You sure about that?
Huh?
[BASIL yelling]
What?
[BASIL laughing]
[PICCOLO groans]
What are they?
Not sure.
It's like they're illusions,
but they can turn solid!
[GOKU grunting]
What are you guys?
[BOTH roar]
Well this is strange.
I've been thinking
that a lot lately.
[BERGAMO laughs]
You can't escape your doom.
If they are some
kind of a trick,
that would explain why I
can't sense their energies.
Not theirs', but I am
sensing two beings nearby.
One's not moving, and the
other is circling around.
[gasps] You're right.
Maybe the stationary one
controls these illusions,
so the other one can use
them as cover to attack.
[ALL gasp]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[XIANGCA gasping]
[PICCOLO yells]
[XIANGCA yelps]
Xiangca! What was that?!
Were you even trying?
Oh, I don't fight.
I'm so very sorry, my lord.
[PICCOLO grunts]
There's another invisible man?
Oh give me a break--there's two?
Heh. Once you know
how to deal with them,
it doesn't matter
how many they've got.
Besides, unlike that first guy,
this one hasn't learned
to suppress his energy.
Oh, no! They've figured it out!
It's all over! This is a
disaster! We're through!
If I can sense him,
I don't need to see!
But I could feel him
up there, I'm sure of it.
[PICCOLO]
Hm? Gotchya!
That can't be...
[PICCOLO groaning]
[screams]
[gasps] Piccolo!
[QUITELA laughs]
Now that's how a trick is done!
You big sucker!
You literally fell for it!
[GRAND MINISTER] Contestant
Piccolo of the Seventh
is eliminated.
Hey, what happened
to you down there?
I clearly sensed the
invisible man's energy.
But... I couldn't hit him.
And why not?
I felt nothing when I struck.
It was like he was
more than invisible.
Like his body wasn't there.
[QUITELA laughs]
Don't stop with him, Damom!
That's it! Squash 'em good!
[A17]
Hm?
Hm...
Are you okay? That was close.
I'm fine.
[gasps]
[GOKU grunting]
Something's wrong.
I know he's there;
I can sense him.
But none of my attacks
are connecting.
[scurrying]
[A17 grunts]
[GOKU grunting]
Now I see. Of course.
[A17]
Hey! It's my turn!
Come at me. I'm waiting.
He urged his opponent to strike,
then closed his eyes?
[ROSHI] Just what in the world
is that robot boy thinking?
[DAMOM]
Ha!
[GOKU grunts]
[ALL gasping]
But how?
The rest of you feel his energy,
but let your theories
confuse you.
We're not dealing with a ghost
or some invisible man.
The reason you're not hitting
him is far more simple.
[DAMOM]
Ha!
[GOKU gasps]
[DAMOM growls]
[A17]
We're fighting an insect.
[GOKU]
Whoa, a bug man?
[laughing] Yeah you're right!
Well, that explains it!
Their attacks weren't landing
'cause they didn't
realize he was so small.
[PICCOLO grunts] I was
too focused on his energy
to use my other senses.
I can't believe I missed
the sound he was making.
Yes, I see. Since his
teammate was invisible,
you clung to your preconceived
notion that he was, as well.
[SUPREME KAI] And his energy
alone is misleading,
as it's far greater
than his actual size.
Most deceptive.
[QUITELA growls]
Fight, Damom!
You can't let them defeat you!
Do you understand me?
We are all depending on you!
Ah. Hold it right there.
I don't care if you've
discovered my true form,
you will never stop me!
He's effectively too small to
see, especially at long range.
It won't be easy.
[ROSHI]
They also have to be careful.
If they squash him,
they'll be disqualified.
Ha, ha! Just keep on trying,
it won't work!
[GOKU]
Ha!
Damn it! I can't hit him!
I know where he is by his
energy, but he's so small
and zips around so fast,
it doesn't matter.
This insect doesn't seem
to have wings, though.
Have you noticed he always jumps
at the start of every attack?
Yeah. You're right, he hasn't
flown this whole time.
Well that's something.
If we can make it so he can't
jump, he won't get away.
Then if we aim for the
center of his energy,
it could create an opportunity.
Oh, awesome! This should knock
the little guy off his feet!
[DAMOM gasping]
[DAMOM screams]
All right, round two!
[DAMOM screaming]
Now try to jump off of this!
[DAMOM yelling]
Stop it! No fair!
[DAMOM gasping]
[DAMOM]
Wait. What is this?
Yeah, you got him, 17.
I know.
[ALL laughing]
Hey, it looks like
they caught him!
Hang on! Let's talk
about this! Don't do it!
[DAMOM screaming]
[DAMOM grunts]
Sorry, my lord.
You think "sorry"
is gonna make up
for our universe disappearing?
Come here, you little...!
[FUTURE ZENO gasping]
[FUTURE ZENO]
Boop! Damom is bye-bye!
[ZENO] All their pictures
are blacked out!
[FUTURE ZENO]
Their team is blacked out too!
It looks like
the Fourth Universe
is out of the Tournament now!
And you know what that means!
[BOTH laughing]
Oh, no! Please, sires!
I-- But I don't want to go away!
This isn't right--
I can't be annihilated!
It's so unfair! I'll show you!
If I have to go,
I'll take all of you with me!
[BOTH]
Bye-bye!
[QUITELA screams]
[GRAND MINISTER] The Fourth
Universe has been obliterated.
[NARRATOR] An invisible man,
a conjurer, and a fighting bug.
These were the extraordinary
final members of
the Fourth's team, and the
Seventh has defeated them all
to wipe another universe
from existence.
Now, the only remaining teams
in the battle for survival
are the Third, Seventh,
and Eleventh.
Which group of hardened
warriors will prevail
and keep their Universe intact?
The competition
continues to intensify,
as it barrels toward the end.
Twelve minutes remain in
the Tournament of Power,
next time on Dragon Ball Super!
A 70 centimeter squared window
Today the sun broke
through the clouds
The rain is fin'ly gone
Gonna open up
the window for once
No reason, just because
This room has been
stained with the sighs
Of everyday regret
Now it's time to clear the air
Every moment was consumed
with my thoughts of you
Knowing in my heart those dreams
won't be coming true
I've always wanted nothing more
than to see your face
I move on knowing that your
mem'ry can't be erased
[GOHAN]
Hey, Gohan here.
Looks like the
Third Universe squad
is playing the ace
up their sleeve--
all three of these engineered
warriors are combining together
into some kind of mega-fighter
with unbelievable power,
and Dad, Vegeta, and I
will have to step up
if we're gonna survive!
Okay, here goes! Get ready
to see my full power!
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"A Perfect Survival Strategy!
The 3rd Universe's
Menacing Assassin!"
Make sure you
don't miss it, okay?