♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Super,
Goku Black arrived
from Trunk's dark future.
Yes, outstanding!
So this is the power of
lengerdary Super Sayian Goku.
Now I understand.
We're not just alike
on the outside, huh?
Fighting someone strong
gets you amped up, too.
[NARRATOR] Just as the clash
of Gokus was ratcheting up,
Black was pulled back
into the rip in space-time.
But in a cruel last move before
returning to Trunk's future,
Black destroyed
the time machine.
How could you?
[NARRATOR] With Trunks
stranded in the present,
it seemed his
future world was doomed.
Until Bulma surprised everyone
with a new reason for hope.
Ta-da! A time machine!
[BULMA giggles]
There was still
one more, remember?
[NARRATOR]
"Feelings That Transcend Time.
Trunks and Mai."
Oh, wow.
This one sure is filthy!
Mom, wait. Is this the--?
[WHIS]
A duplicate time machine?
I hope this doesn't
mean what I think.
Disgraceful. It's like
these mortals are actively
trying to provoke divine wrath.
So Bulma, is it
that time machine?
The stolen one?
Yup! I know,
I know, I'm brilliant.
Wait, I'm confused.
Where'd this come from?
Don't you remember?
It's the one Cell took
from his timeline to get here.
No way!
Did you say Cell?
But, what's it doing here?
You've had it this whole time?
[BULMA] Of course I did.
It's Capsule Corp. tech.
Back when we were
dealing with the Androids,
a group of land surveyors
called our company headquarters
saying a strange vehicle
had been found
with our logo on the body.
When they sent us a picture,
I was totally floored.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Mother. Take a look.
This is the ship you built.
I've had it with me in
capsule form since I landed.
[BULMA]
That settles it then.
This broken-down
old thing can't be yours.
No, Mom. There's only
been one of these,
which means that
as weird as it is,
there's just no other way.
It's the same one.
It's my ship. I don't know how,
but it's gotta be.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm positive.
Hope. I painted it on there
myself, just before I left.
That's the story.
As we came to realize,
Cell hijacked it in
his version of the future.
[PICCOLO] So the destroyed
machine and this one
are the same, just from
two alternate realities?
[KRILLIN]
I know you found it this way,
but come on, couldn't you
spruce it up or something?
Those instruments
are delicate, Krillin.
I didn't want to
break something. Ah!
What's this hole? A sun roof?
You can thank Cell for that.
'Cause that's how
he broke outta there.
[GOKU]
Whooooa.
That's how you found it.
But then how did it end up
with you instead of with Trunks?
Oh. Well that's simple.
Trunks reverted both
machines to capsule form
and stuck them in his case.
Then after the Cell Games,
the day Trunks
went back to his future...
[BULMA]
Say, Trunks.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Yeah?
So those time machines.
You've got two now, right?
I was kind of hoping
that we could share?
You mean... you want this?
But it's the one Cell took.
We don't even know if--
Hey, they're both
the machine I built
in the future, aren't they?
Look. I'm curious.
I just want to see how it works,
and its too tempting
to let it go.
Yeah, okay.
I'll leave that capsule
with you, Mom.
You're the best!
Thank you so much!
Then, right after Trunks
went home to his future,
I started running
some tests on this machine
to figure out how it works.
[GOKU]
Whoa!
But despite all the hours
I spent I could never crack it.
Wait. You're the one who
invented the thing, aren't you?
But that's me in the future!
Guess there's some epiphany
I haven't had yet.
Finally I just gave up
and stuck it on a shelf,
then forgot it was there.
Honestly,
I'm surprised you found it.
[chuckles]
Yeah, anyway,
since we have this, there's
still a way to get back there.
There's still hope.
Thanks, Mom.
You always deliver.
[BULMA laughs]
All right, Trunks.
This is great!
This means we can both go!
And then I can help you
chase after Black!
--Sounds good.
--I'm going as well.
--Really, Father?
--It's like I told you.
If you're determined,
there's always a way.
[BULMA] Well, there's
not a way quite yet.
I mean just look at
this thing, guys.
You think it's ready
to fly right now?
It's completely covered in moss!
Okay. So when can we go?
Before I answer that,
I have to read this!
All right! Good thing
you have those lab notes!
[BULMA] Exactly! With this info
and the included software,
I can finally
understand how it works!
The energy it needs,
the systems.
I can do the repairs
and reload the settings
so it's just like
Trunks' machine.
This should show me how!
That's great! So we
should have some time
before you finish, right?
Well, it's complicated.
[ALL]
Uh..
[BULMA]
Huh?
Whis, come on!
You have to train me!
I mean, uh, I formally request
an awesome training
session with you.
Please. Please. Please.
Please. Please. Please!
You knew he going to ask.
He's so predictable.
Come on, pretty please?
If I'm gonna fight Black again,
I need to be at my best!
Mm. You know with all of
these time machines
popping up left and right,
I'm really not in the mood
to aid and abet, Goku.
[BEERUS] And there's the matter
of the Time Ring, as well.
[GOKU]
Ooooh...
Why don't you train with Vegeta?
Yeah, I guess.
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU] But, he's in one
of his moods again,
which can get a bit scary.
I don't think we're
gonna be the best
training partners right now.
I don't think "a bit scary"
does it justice, pal.
So that's a "no"? You're sure?
[WHIS]
Mmmhmmm!
All right,
then I guess I'll just
go over to King Kai's place.
[beeping]
[squeaking]
[VEGETA]
Hell no.
[ALL gasp]
Hi, King Kai!
Oh, it's you.
Oh, come on. I just came by
so you could train me.
Go away!
What's wrong;
are you mad about something?
[KING KAI]
Are you kidding me?
I can remember every moment.
Each blow in that
battle is burning
like a bright flame
in my body and mind.
These moves of his. They're so
well-suited for this body.
So is this
the true might of Goku?
Now I want more.
I need to see
more of him in action.
If I can keep studying Goku,
my destructive power
will grow even greater.
[BOTH]
Huh?
What happened here?
Our lawn is chock full of holes.
I hope it isn't giant gophers--
they're the worst!
Oh! Mom and Dad,
there you are!
Hey, welcome back!
Thank you, dear!
Those are our grandparents.
They're super nice.
Yeah. I know, we met before.
Here! We'll carry your bags.
That's right.
Just kick back and relax.
Yeah, we live to serve!
So how was your trip?
Was it fun?
[DR. BRIEFS] You bet!
It was a full-fledged delight!
Oh my! Is that our big,
strong grandson from the future?
That's right. Long time no see.
Things are becoming
merrier, aren't they?
Do they have
my dinner ready yet?
We've barely passed
lunch time, my lord.
I think you'll have to wait.
Just look at ya!
You've grown into an even more
--handsome young man!
--Yeah? Thanks.
So did you come back to our time
to train with Goku or somethin'?
Not exactly.
Okay, Mom.
You can catch up later.
We need to talk to Dad.
I see you pulled this
old thing off the shelf--
that really takes me back.
[BULMA]
Yeah. And look at this!
[DR. BRIEFS]
Eh?
They're lab notes
from my future self.
They explain the
whole time machine!
[DR. BRIEFS] Aaah! Wowzers,
this changes everything!
[BULMA] Would you give me
a hand? It's an emergency.
Sure. My goodness,
these equations
are very fascinating.
And our fire brigade
can help, too.
[MAI, PILAF, SHOU]
Really?
I mean, you guys
are freeloading.
I think giving us a hand in the
lab is the least you can do.
[MAI, PILAF, SHOU]
Yes ma'am!
Now's our big chance!
We'll steal this future
technology for ourselves!
And use it achieve
global conquest!
With the power of time
we'll create a new machine
called the
"World-Conquering Gizmo!"
Sir! It's nice to
hear you plotting again!
That's an awesome
name for a machine.
But, what does it actually do?
We can figure
that part out later.
What are you guys
whispering about over there?
[MAI, PILAF, SHOU]
Eeh.
Whoa. What's with the smiles?
Oh, it's nothing, just a little
team-building pep talk.
Yeah! Pep talk! We love to pep!
Mai, Shou, let's go!
[MAI, SHOU]
Yeah!
Wait, Mai?
Did I miss something? Hello?
[PILAF] Yeah, future-boy!
Is this a staring contest?
Hey. He called you Mai, right?
That's your name?
That's right. What's it to you?
Wow, I thought it was you!
Aaah! That is straight-up bold!
I guess.
Of course--it's so clear now.
What do you mean?
Do you know me in the future?
Yeah. I do.
It's strange to think about.
So what am I like?
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Uh--aaaah...
Now what's come over you two?
Are you lost for words?
[PILAF]
Yeah, Mai. What's up?
Will we be close
friends in the future?
[BULMA giggles]
Okay everyone, repair time!
[PILAF]
Eeh?
[SHOU] You're working me
like a dog here!
[BULMA] Let's move this to the
lab, and get things rolling!
Krillin? And Piccolo?
What's up? You need help?
[BULMA] Yeah. Can you guys
fix up the lawn?
[BOTH]
Uh!
[BULMA]
Mom, Dad, you come with me.
[KRILLIN] Since when
are we the landscapers?
[PICCOLO] Guess we should
call this more training.
That got us through
this morning, didn't it?
[KRILLIN groans]
Can you say more?
What am I like in your time?
Well, in my future,
the Mai I know is a lot
bigger than you are now.
About as tall as me.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
In Black's first attack,
most of mankind was wiped out.
Next was the counterstrike.
Military forces from all nations
launched an attack on Black.
But all of them failed.
The survivors were few.
Those who did make it
went underground.
And before long
they banded together,
into a resistance,
and continued the fight.
And the brave soldier
at the head of it all...
That was the future you.
Wait, me?
The resistance was tenacious,
but despite all their efforts,
their casualties only increased.
I worked with Mai and the
others to hunt down Black--
try to find some weakness.
Keep it up. Just a little more.
The gunfire's drawing him in--
he's almost there.
Okay, we're clear!
[FUTURE MAI]
Here we go!
[FUTURE MAI coughing]
It worked!
You really thought you'd
catch me with that trap?
You're going to have to
do much better than that.
As creatures go, these humans
are relatively intelligent.
But apparently not smart
enough to know when to quit.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
Then how 'bout I tag in?
[GOKU BLACK]
The Saiyan again?
This is the day
I finish you, Black.
You won't be the end
of the human race. No way!
But this race
deserves to end.
That is what
you fail to realize.
Who the hell made you judge?
I look down on existence
from a much higher
perspective than you do.
I witness this world,
this universe,
and the truth of all things.
That yields deeper
understanding. Wisdom.
The realization that all
mortals should be destroyed.
The one and only mistake
among all divine creations.
That is what mortals are.
And this mistake is egregious.
To shape existence
into the beautiful utopia
it was always meant to be,
the mistake must be corrected.
I will purge all mortals
from existance
in place of the gods
who refuse to admit failure.
That's enough!
No one has the right
to make that call!
[yells]
You fight like
a naïve child, Saiyan.
As if you'll win because
you want to so badly.
You cannot defeat me
with raw emotion alone.
[gasps]
[yells]
[FUTURE TRUNKS screams]
[GOKU BLACK chuckles]
[yells]
[grunting]
A flash grenade?
[FUTURE MAI]
Trunks!
Nice shot.
Come on, let's go.
[GOKU BLACK]
Fleeing like a coward.
So much for the
"proud warrior race."
[FUTURE MAI sighs]
If we had senzu beans,
these wounds would be nothing.
True enough. But Korin's
gone like the rest.
Well, I can at least
find you something to eat.
We have to get
your strength back.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
It's too risky out there.
I can take care of myself.
Maybe. But helping you
is helping all of us.
You're our best hope.
Some hope I am. You keep
having to rescue me.
Gohan and Father wouldn't have
been this weak. I'm sure of it.
They'd have
stopped Black by now.
[FUTURE MAI] Don't blame
yourself. You survived.
And the fact you
keep going out there
is what gives
the rest of us courage.
I would have given up a long
time ago if wasn't for you.
[FUTURE TRUNKS]
You saved me countless times.
And you said I gave you courage.
Well, you gave it right back.
That's why...
I'm glad you're here.
Okay, pal! If that's true
why didn't you
bring that Mai back with you?
She's gone.
[TRUNKS gasps]
You mean in the future I--?
[PILAF, SHOU]
Am I in the future, too?
Uh. Sorry. I'm not sure.
[PILAF, SHOU]
Aw. Dang it.
Why are you out here anyway?
Why do you think?
We're here for Mai!
I'll go, too.
I want to help any way I can
to fix that vessel.
I'm only here now
'cause of Mom and Mai.
There's so much they've given me
I can never make up for.
But still, I have to
give back as much as I can.
And that means getting to my own
timeline as fast as possible.
[GOKU]
Hold on, buddy.
Where did you--?
Hey, I thought
you went off to train.
[GOKU]
King Kai was in a lousy mood.
He wouldn't fix me
anything to eat,
and fighting makes me
super hungry.
But enough about that--
you need to rest, Trunks.
You've been stressed out
ever since you landed,
and that's understandable.
But you need to take it easy
so you can see this
thing through.
I will.
[DR. BRIEFS]
Intriguing theories!
This turns physics upside-down!
I know! And eager as I am
to put them into practice,
first we need to clean up.
I'm ready! Let's do it!
Couldn't we help you
after the cleaning's done?
[BULMA]
What's that?
Nothing, ma'am!
We're totally happy to do it!
We're gonna
make it sparkle! I swear!
Earth to Mai? You there?
He's nailing that handsome
enigmatic stranger act.
He's so dreamy.
You may look like a little girl,
but sometimes
you act a lot older.
[MAI, PILAF, SHOU shriek]
[MAI, PILAF, SHOU laughing]
That energy I was
sensing from Black.
I could have sworn
I've felt it before.
[WHIS] So, it wasn't
just me, my lord?
It would seem
I should investigate.
Yes, I would think so.
[BEERUS]
Isn't dinner ready yet?
Get ready!
Instant Transmission!
Two fingers placed
right between the eyes
Get ready!
My hair will stand up!
'Cause I got
all the power of a Saiyan!
Inside we all have
a shining heart!
(Whoa, look out!)
Time warp to the future,
say konnichiwa
See the world in ways
that you thought impossible
Open open up to your intuition
No you can't give up
When your heart is still beating
Pounding out a rhythm
that'll make you wanna dance!
Ohhhh HEY!
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! (KAMEHAMEHA!)
YOKA YOKA DANCE! (HEY!)
YOKA YOKA YOKA YOKA
DANCE! It's what you need
Feel the magic of the beat
(Woo-hoo)
DANCE! It makes you smile
Nothing else can
quite compete (yoka yoka)
So when the world is lame
Don't play that game
You know that every problem
can be answered the same
Just let go and feel the rhythm
Everybody dance
with all your might!
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
Looks like Future Trunks
is gonna visit Gohan.
And now that my son's
become a scholar,
I think Trunks is in
for a big surprise.
Gohan's a far cry
from the warrior
who trained Trunks
in his own time.
While he does that, I'll tag
along with Whis and Beerus
for a very different meet up.
Does Whis know
the true identity of Black?
[GOKU] Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Master and Pupil Reunited!
Gohan and 'Future' Trunks!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?