♪ Opening Song ♪
Don't you wanna dream again?
Now it's calling for me
go back to the start
Wishing on the starlights
In the sky, let's paint
a door for tomorrow
Just step on the new stage
Don't be shy
Gonna take the challenge of god
Kyo-Let's Mo-Let's Dynamic!
Let's! Go! Go! Big panic!
I don't care 'bout limit,
no regret
Make me tougher
even though I lose
Nothing gonna stop me no mo'
Try me
So-Zet's Cho-Zets Dynamic!
Let's go! Yes! Give a kick!
Keep on going
Power pumpin' up
Something greater waiting
not so far away
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
Great Saiyaman
got his own movie!
Gohan worked as
the movie's stuntman
and faced a marital scandal,
thanks to the scheming
of jealous lead actor,
Barry Kahn.
Thankfully, Gohan and Videl's
love proved stronger
than the superstar's evil plot!
[VIDEL] It's not proof,
because he's not a cheat.
I'm sure there's a very good
reason for that kiss.
There sure is, Videl!
[NARRATOR] But Barry's anger
attracted the evil alien
mind parasite, Watagash, and
this symbiotic menace
crashed into Gohan's home
and kidnapped baby Pan!
Great Saiyaman sprang into
action to save his little girl
while the movie crew
filmed the battle
and made it their new ending,
turning the Great Saiyaman
motion picture into a smash hit.
However, one audience member
was not so entertained.
I fell asleep halfway through.
I guess it's more fun
to be in a real fight
than watch a fake one.
[yawns]
This was your son's
moment to shine!
[NARRATOR] Goku seeks a cure
for his boredom. Now!
"Goku and Krillin.
Back to the Old Familiar
Training Ground!"
[GOKU grunts, yells]
[CHICHI]
Your father's so funny.
He'll do whatever it takes
to keep up his daily training.
And in this case, it's
ploughing the fields by hand.
[GOHAN]
Uh-huh.
[CHICHI] So, the tractor
breaking down wasn't
much of problem after all.
The crops still
get planted on time,
and Goku gets his exercise.
It's two birds with one stone!
[GOHAN] Yeah, I get all that,
but why'd you call me over?
Dad's only doing this
'cause he doesn't have
a real partner to train with.
But I thought Whis
was helping him train.
Dad says he's too busy.
[WHIS]
Sorry. I'd love to, Goku,
but I'm afraid I have
a prior commitment.
All the Destroyers and
Supreme Kais from across
the multiverse are attending
a big joint summit.
[GOKU] Wow. Even gods
have boring meetings?
Okay, then. So, why can't
he go ask Vegeta?
[GOTEN]
He gave Dad this weird look!
He didn't even talk.
He just glared!
Vegeta glares at everyone,
but it's weird for him
to turn down training.
Huh, maybe he and Bulma
are fighting or something.
Couples fight, it's no big deal.
What about Piccolo?
He said he's gotta run
some errand with Dende.
That's too bad.
That's why we called you here,
Gohan--you should do it!
I'm kinda retired, Goten.
Why don't you go and do it?
[CHICHI growls]
Uh. I'm guessing you
want him to go study?
You're darn right I do!
Okay, okay!
Well, I guess I can try.
I'm just not much
of a fighter these days.
[gasps]
Oh, yeah, that's it!
[CHICHI, GOTEN]
Huh?
The real answer's just
a costume change away!
--[GOTEN] Whoa!
--Hey, now we're talking'.
--[GOKU] Uh?
--[laughing]
Why, looks like you're in
quite the pickle, Goku!
[GOKU]
Gohan, what're you doing?
I'm not Gohan now, Dad!
[GOHAN] At times, he is the
mild-mannered daddy of Pan!
At other times, a scholarly
egghead giving lectures.
He's also
Mr. Satan's son-in-law.
And Videl's faithful husband!
But behold, a fifth identity!
The superhero, Great Saiyaman!
You're fooling no one, Gohan.
[GOHAN] Uh, you've confused me
with someone else!
I am the Great Saiyaman!
I render aid in any form
it's needed to all in distress!
And that distressed one today,
looks like you, Goku!
Uh, yeah, so then
what you're saying is
you're gonna train with me?
That's correct, friend!
Now come at me!
Gohan really gets
into this, doesn't he?
I'm still not a fan
of that costume.
Hold on. After you saw
the Great Saiyaman movie
you wouldn't stop talking about
how awesome
you thought it looked!
On the big screen,
but when it's real life
he kinda just
looks like a goober.
I can't believe how fast
my little Goten is growing up.
[GOHAN]
What are you waiting for, Goku?
I thought you wanted
a partner to spar with!
Don't be shy!
This'll be good for you!
You asked for it!
[GOHAN]
He's faster than ever!
[CHICHI groaning]
Dad looks like he's havin' fun!
But I thought they'd
be more restrained!
[GOHAN] That's some
impressive power, my good man!
[GOKU]
You're pretty strong, too!
[GOHAN] Though, it feels like
you're still holding back.
I just wanted to test
where your skills are at.
So, try to match this!
[yells]
I will!
[GOKU yells]
[yells]
[groans]
[GOHAN grunting]
I'm just gettin' started!
[GOKU, GOHAN yelling]
[GOHAN]
Very impressive, Mr. Goku.
Same to you, Mr. Great Saiyaman.
Both of you stop fighting
right this second!
[GOKU, GOHAN]
Huh?
Look what you guys
have done to the field!
It's ruined!
[GOKU]
Aw, crap.
[GOHAN] And after
he ploughed it by hand!
What kind of champion
of justice allows for
nature to be
ravaged like this!
Sorry about that!
Boy, we sure did a number
on this place, huh? Ha-ha.
So help me, Goku,
if you try to laugh this off.
[BOTH holler, chuckle]
[GOKU grunting]
You gotta find somewhere
better to train.
All right, all right, fine.
Aw, man. I gotta find
another partner to spar with.
Wait, Dad.
You could ask Krillin!
Krillin has real
responsibilities as a policeman.
He doesn't have time
to goof around with your dad.
[thud]
Ow, he could warn me next time!
[CHICHI]
Goku!
I'd better warn 18
before it's too late!
[ROBBER 75B]
So long, coppers!
Few more turns and I can
lose the little piggy
riding our tail!
Fine, you wanna play rough?
[BOTH scream]
--[KRILLIN] Freeze!
--Watch out!
[chuckles]
[POLICEMAN 75A] Wow, Krillin!
We could barely keep up!
Where did you learn
to ride like that?
Well it's not that complicated--
you just don't use the brakes.
[KRILLIN]
Take cover!
[yelling]
They've got us pinned!
It's all right.
I've got this covered.
Krillin, don't!
Stay back, pigs!
--[POLICEMAN 75B] My car!
--Eat lead, cop!
[POLICEMAN 75B]
Ngggh!
Krillin!
[ROBBER 75A laughing]
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's just a flesh wound.
Oh, thank heavens.
You're a hero!
What are we gonna do
against these two psychos?
Hey, Krillin, what's up?
--Goku?
--Whoa, where'd he come from?
Who the hell are you?
[KRILLIN]
Goku! Those two are robbers!
[GOKU]
Robbers?
[ROBBER 75A]
You better not be police!
'Cause if you are, we'll fill
you full of holes, too!
[GOKU]
Uh...
How'd he do that?
Who is this guy!
He's a monster!
What're you saying?
I'm not a monster!
Thanks for all
your help, citizen!
[GOKU]
No problem!
I'm guessing you didn't
rush into town to save us.
So, why are you here?
I wanna get some
good training in!
And to do that,
I need a good partner!
You wanna train with me?
Hey, wait. Krillin, did you
just take a bullet in the arm?
Oh, yeah, it just
grazed me, though.
[chuckling]
--[MARRON] Wee!
--[MARRON, GOKU laughing]
Uh, so listen, buddy.
I don't think training
with you is a good idea, okay?
I can't give you
what you're looking for.
You gotta remember,
I don't fight anymore.
Most days I'm just
writing tickets.
Ah, don't sell yourself short!
I just want a little light
training, like the old days!
Dude, it wasn't even that
long ago Frieza resurrected
and you were right back
in the fight with everyone else!
That's because the
whole world was at stake.
Hey, Dada! Will you and
Uncle play with me now?
But, Mom!
No games, it's time
for your bath.
But I wanna play with
Dada and Uncle--oh!
Marron, your father doesn't
have time to play right now.
He can't do much of anything
'cause he got hurt by
some teeny weeny bank robbers.
[gasps]
Yeah, well the
other guys on the force
thought it was a big deal.
What happened to you?
The timid Krillin licking
his wounds on the sofa
is not the brave martial
artist I fell in love with!
[KRILLIN grunts]
Uh oh! Mama's sayin'
Dada's a wimp!
[KRILLIN gasps]
Hey, Uncle! Are you
stronger than my dad?
Well, I am strong. But I
want to get even stronger!
You do, too, right, Krillin?
[MARRON]
I wanna strong, Daddy!
[gasps]
[MARRON giggles]
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Okay! One strong
daddy coming up!
Train with me, Goku!
Wait, what? I thought
I was the one
coming here to recruit you.
[KRILLIN, GOKU grunting]
Man, this really takes me back.
Just the two of us,
going head to head.
And Master Roshi making us do
all sorts of
strange training drills.
Yeah.
[BOTH] That's it! As long
as we're training again...
...we should go do it
with Master Roshi!
Okay!
[gasps]
You heard that?
It's fine. Just be safe.
Wow, it's great seeing you
in the old gi again
rather than police gear.
Just so we're clear,
this little training session
doesn't mean
I'm back as a fighter.
[GOKU]
Really? Are you sure?
[KRILLIN] Yeah.
I saved that other officer,
but I shouldn't have
let myself get hit at all.
I want to be stronger
so I can be a better cop.
That's why I'm training again.
Yeah, right. We're gonna
get so strong together!
[laughs]
Why are you guys here
so early in the morning?
[KRILLIN] Sorry, Master Roshi.
I know it's been a long time,
but I'm humbly asking you
to train me again.
I know it's not much,
but I brought you a gift.
[ROSHI]
Ooh-ho-ho!
[ROSHI] Those are some
prime cuts of babe!
Wow. They're even tastier
than my breakfast!
Krillin, didn't you
give him a gift like this
back when we first met him?
[ROSHI grunts]
Ow! Hey, why'd you hit me for?
Because! You didn't
pay your respects to me!
You'd think a man
with a grandkid of his own
would treat his elders right!
Jeez, I'm sorry. You don't
have to hit me, though.
Master Roshi, we'd be honored
if you'd train us again.
That's much better.
[GOKU] Great! Where should
we start the sparring?
In here, or on the beach?
Goku, if you've already
obtained divine power,
I don't really think I can give
you what you're looking for.
[GOKU] What? That's almost
the exact same thing
Krillin told me earlier!
But there is a way
for Goku and I
to both get what we want.
If you'll train me, he'll have
a better sparring partner.
Maybe he's far beyond
what a mortal can teach,
but you can sure help me!
Make me stronger, Master,
so I can be a proud father
and better officer!
[ROSHI]
Heh...
[GOKU] Hey! How come
I'm stuck wearing the goofy
turtle costume!
It's not even comfortble.
This thing weighs a ton!
[ROSHI laughing]
It looks good on you!
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa!
I can't even walk in this thing!
You are not allowed
to fly against me, either.
[GOKU]
Aw, man.
The same goes for
turning Super Saiyan.
[GOKU]
Ah, come on!
Well, I gotta handicap you!
You've gotten so powerful,
you could kill me
with a single attack, Goku!
Look, to be honest, I don't
trust you to pull punches.
[GOKU] Man, this won't be
training for me at all.
[ROSHI]
Just get to it, already!
We'll start with some freestyle.
All right, I'll give
this turtle suit a shot.
Come at me hard, Krillin!
Okay, here goes nothing'!
[KRILLIN yells]
[GOKU chuckles]
[ROSHI]
Hmmm.
--[KRILLIN] Huh?
--[GOKU chuckles]
[KRILLIN] This is crazy!
How does he do it?
Even wearing that
silly turtle costume,
he seems as fast as ever!
[GOKU grunts]
Uuh!
[ROSHI]
Enough!
[KRILLIN panting]
[GOKU]
Krillin! Nice work!
You actually made that
a halfway decent
training session for me!
[KRILLIN]
Oh, great. He-heh.
[GOKU snoring]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[sighs]
Son, I can tell you're lost.
You're frustrated
with your strength
and you want to get better,
but you don't know
how go about it.
So, you end up stuck in place,
which only makes you
feel more frustrated!
I know all that just from
seeing the little hesitations
in your fists and footwork.
[KRILLIN]
My little girl, Marron,
says she wants a strong dad.
[ROSHI]
Mm.
[KRILLIN] I got called timid.
Well, a wimp, really,
by my own wife.
[yawns]
Now then, today's training's
will not be easy!
[BOTH gulp]
[ROSHI]
You're running an errand.
An errand?
Huh?
Yeah, well, the truth is
I'm actually not as young
as you probably think I am.
So. I need you to go pick
a rare medicinal herb
to help boost my strength.
Whaddaya mean, pick it?
Like, pick it up at the store?
They don't sell it
in stores! Look!
Ooh!
I've never seen that
herb before. What's it called?
They call it the paradise herb.
It's a rare, precious plant
found on only one island.
And on that island,
it's found in only the deepest,
darkest part of the forest.
Sounds like fun!
There's more.
The errand's also a race.
Oh, yeah? Now this is
sounding better and better!
A race, huh?
And whoever brings me back
one of the herbs first
will win this prize!
My treasured
magazine collection--
each one approved
by yours truly!
Come on. You gotta give us
something better than that.
Krillin, help me out here, bro.
Yeah.
You want a better
prize than this?
Nothing's better than this!
I can't believe young fellas
like yourselves
have no need for my magazines!
Look, if we don't want 'em,
we don't want 'em. That's all.
All right, fine. And here
I was thinking I might also
give the winner a bonus prize.
I was gonna teach him
a secret technique
that instantly boosts
his fighting energy.
--[BOTH] Ooh!
--[KRILLIN chuckles]
That sounds awesome!
We'll take that prize!
[ROSHI chuckles]
Well, good luck then!
He's a funny guy.
Master Roshi never changes.
You haven't changed either.
Do you really think so?
What has changed is how
strong you are compared to me.
What? Can ya
say that again please?
There's too much wind noise.
Oh. It's nothing important.
Aw, c'mon!
Now you got me curious!
Really, Goku, it's not
important. I promise.
Okay.
We're almost there!
[birds chirping]
[GOKU] Aw, man! We gotta search
all this for one little plant?
[KRILLIN] Man, I wish he
gave us a hint or something.
[GOKU]
I know, right?
[BABA]
Hold it right there!
--[GOKU, KRILLIN gasp]
--[GOKU] It's you?
[BABA]
Long time no see!
Master Roshi's
older sister, right?
The fortune-seller!
[BABA]
Aah!
That's fortune-teller!
I don't really see
much of a diffence.
Of course there's a difference!
So, what are you doing
on this island?
[BABA] I'm here
'cause my brother asked.
He wants to use my crystal ball
to watch the rest of the race.
Does that mean we still
have further to go
to reach the plant?
Oh, yeah, this is perfect.
If you know where the plant is,
you can just tell us, right?
[BABA] If I told you,
it wouldn't be training!
[GOKU]
Aw.
You better start looking, boys!
The herb is somewhere
in that forest!
You hear that, Krillin.
The paradise herb race is on!
And, they're off!
They're calling this a race,
but it seems more like
it'll be a marathon!
We could be running around
this island for months
until we stumble upon it.
[GOKU]
Whoa!
[KRILLIN] It's like a giant
sculpture of Baba's face!
--[BABA] I heard that!
--[GOKU] Ah!
[BABA] This is where
your true training begins!
--Hey, uh, Goku?
--[GOKU] Hm?
[KRILLIN] Is it just me,
or does this place
give off a weird vibe?
[GOKU] Oh, yeah.
It's way creepy in here!
[KRILLIN] I'm actually
getting a little scared.
Huh?
[KRILLIN]
Aah. Goku, what's going on?
[GOKU]
I don't know,
but somehow
it just got creepier!
Oh, no way!
What are these guys doing back?
[GOKU] It's everyone we've ever
defeated, all in one spot!
Uh! Goku! Look over there!
[hollers]
[KRILLIN]
Oh, no. What're we gonna do?
An angel and a demon sit
One to my right,
one to my left
In between I'm tryin'
to figure out the right way
Is one way good?
Is one way bad?
Too much confusion in my head
I can't think with all
this noise, I'm goin' crazy
Is there any way to know
what's right or wrong?
Demons in an angel mask
Hopin' that I'll do
just what they ask
Telling me
they know what's right
Lead me to the light
"For the sake of everyone
You have to destroy
the evil ones
That's the only path, you see"
So they said to me
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
What's going on
in this weird forest?!
It's like everyone
we ever defeated
just stepped out of the fog.
Krillin, watch out!
They're attacking us!
C'mon, man, this is
no time to freeze up!
We gotta lay these guys out
so we can get
the paradise herb
for Master Roshi!
Next time
on Dragon Ball Super:
"Conquer the Terrifying Foes!
Krillin's Fighting
Spirit Rebounds!"
Make sure you don't
miss it, okay?