♪ Opening Song ♪
Time has come,
I'm ready to go
Venturing into the unknown
Fires inside me,
must be unleashed
People talkin' nonsense all day
Chin pun kan,
that's all they can say
I can't get no satisfaction
Challenges may come
Fighting's just begun
But there's no stopping me
from spreading out my wings
(let's fly high)
Concentrate my power
In the final hour
In the end, I am gonna win!
Don't you know
I'm unstoppable?
Don't even try,
'cause you will fall
I got a strength,
deep in my soul,
that gives me
courage and control
I'll go beyond the limit break
The universe is mine to take
I have no fear,
I think it's clear
Let's kick it up into high gear
Oh this is Dragon Ball Super
We've got the skills
to blow Zeno away!
[inaudible]
[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Super,
the Tournament of Power
was in full swing.
While Goku battled Caulifla,
her sworn sister Kale
performed an incredible
transformation
that stopped the other
fighters in their tracks.
[KALE wails]
[KALE screams]
You're taking my one
and only away from me!
And you're going to
regret that, Goku!
I'll make you pay!
[KALE yelling]
[KALE roars]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[CABBA, VEGETA grunt]
[BOTAMO screams]
[CAULIFLA] Hey, Kale!
Bring it down a notch!
No dropping bodies!
Do ya hear me?!
[NARRATOR] Not even the voice
of her trusted friend Caulifla
could calm Kale, whose
rampage continued unabated.
Until Jiren of the
Eleventh Universe
finally brought her down.
[JIREN]
It's over.
[NARRATOR]
After witnessing Jiren's
phenomenal strength firsthand,
Goku approached the powerhouse
for a challenge like no other.
These two exceptional warriors
meet face to face, now!
[NARRATOR]
"Warriors of Justice Close In!
The Pride Troopers!"
[CAULIFLA grunts]
[CAULIFLA]
Hm?
[KALE groaning]
Uh? Huh? What happened?
You were so incredible
out there!
Um, I was what?
What are you talking
about, Caulifla?
You mean you don't remember?
No... I don't...
Man, you really are somethin'
else, you know that!
[KALE]
Uhh...
All right. Let's do this,
Jiren. You and me!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU gasps]
Take this. Justice Flash!
[GOKU yelping]
At ease, Jiren.
I've selected a team
of five to deal with him.
You and I will
fall back for now
so that we can
preserve our strength.
[crash]
[BOTH gasp]
[GOKU groaning]
Sheesh. He just came
outta nowhere.
[CAULIFLA]
You got some nerve!
Showing up to attack Kale
when she's vulnerable,
does that make you feel
like a big man?! Huh?
Hey, hold on! I was
blasted here--
--Hm?
--[KALE gasps]
[GOKU]
What do you guys want?!
Judging by your outfits, I'm
guessing you're on Top's team?
[KAHSERAL]
Indeed we are!
My name is... Kahseral!
I'm Tupper!
The name's Zoire!
Behold Cocotte!
And I'm Kettle!
[ALL]
And we are the Pride Troopers!
[GOKU]
Uhh...
[KALE whimpers]
Top told us there would
only be one of them
for us to take care of.
That girl there.
She's the one who ousted Vewon!
I swear it now:
the Pride Troopers
will make you pay dearly
for taking out one of our own!
Under orders from our
valiant comrade, Top,
we will eliminate you!
[GOKU]
Hey, what gives?
I thought I was the one
he told you to get rid of!
[KAHSERAL]
This is a battle royale!
It makes no difference what
order we defeat you in!
[GOKU]
Sounds like this could get ugly.
You both might wanna hang back.
Oh, come on!
And let you do
all the fun stuff?
Yeah, I don't think so, buddy!
Yeah, but, is your friend okay?
[KALE gasping]
Sorry, but I really
don't like that man.
Hey, watch your mouth!
[gasps]
[CAULIFLA]
Kale isn't some delicate flower
you need to take pity on!
She's a warrior, and I'm proud
to call her my sworn sister!
Really, you're... proud?
Yeah, now let's go.
You're rested and ready to kick
some more butt, aren't ya?
Yeah, okay!
[GOKU]
Mm?
Heh, heh!
[grunting]
[yelling]
[ZA PRICCIO growls]
[ROSHI] Lightning Flash...
Surprise... Attack!
[ZA PRICCIO whimpers, screams]
[ZA PRICCIO] What is this
wretched technique?!
[ZA PRICCIO groaning]
You can't move, can you?
Unfortunately, neither can I.
Long as I'm immobilizing you,
I'm stuck in the same boat.
Luckily...
[ZA PRICCIO]
Huh?!
Here! Tri-Beam... Ha!
[ZA PRICCIO groaning]
[ZA PRICCIO screams]
[exhales]
Master Roshi, you're
not injured, are you?
I'm A-okay, thanks to you, Tien.
Excellent timing back there.
[GOHAN]
Hey, Master Roshi! Tien!
Where is everyone?
Well, uh, when that kooky
Saiyan girl was going berserk,
we all got split up.
I haven't seen
anybody else since.
[PICCOLO]
Try looking up!
[ALL]
Hm?
Good to see you!
[PICCOLO] We should gather the
rest of the team and regroup.
I'll go look for the oth--
[FRIEZA] So sorry to
keep you waiting, gentlemen.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[MURICHIM groaning]
[VEGETA]
Frieza!
That chubby pink oaf was mine!
Don't poach him from me!
[laughs]
As you wish, Vegeta. Now be
a good dog and go fetch.
[MURICHIM screams]
[VEGETA growls]
We're only missing three now.
Both of the Androids...
[GOHAN]
...and my Dad.
[FUTURE ZENO]
Tap, tap.
Za Priccio... Za Priccio...
Boop!
[ZENO]
Murichim.
Boop!
They are falling
even faster now.
I can barely keep up
with them!
Yes, sires.
As fatigue sets in, contestants
are more likely to lose.
I wonder what Goku's up to.
Oh, look there!
They're giving him the business!
Oh yes, they really are!
[GOKU grunting]
What... are you doing...?
You got sloppy.
With my power, I change
my body weight at will.
So now, let's see just how
much you can withstand.
[TUPPER laughs]
[GOKU groaning]
[ZOIRE grunting]
[ZOIRE laughs]
[ZOIRE yells]
[ZOIRE]
If you think that's bad,
wait till you get a load
of our combination attacks!
[GOKU grunting]
[ZOIRE]
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
How's my hyper-speed
spinning attack feel, huh?
You like that?
[KETTLE grunting]
You coward! Stop running away
and start fighting back!
[CAULIFLA growls]
I was fighting back, my dear.
You were just too focused
on me to notice.
[gasps]
[CAULIFLA gasping]
[laughs] Take that!
[CAULIFLA grunts]
And that! And that! And that!
And that!
[CAULIFLA screams]
I have to help!
[COCOTTE]
"Cocotte Zone"!
[COCOTTE laughs]
Welcome to my
alternate dimension.
One that I've made just for you,
from which you won't return.
[KALE grunting]
[gasping]
We can always count on our
gifted dimensional illusionist,
Cocotte. Although...
I'm not sure why they
needed five Pride Troopers.
Sounds excessive
to me just to handle
these three measly opponents.
Sure seems like a waste
of our talents.
[A17]
Well, in that case...
Uh?
[KAHSERAL groans]
[A17]
Hmph.
Impossible. How did you
sneak up behind me
without letting me sense you?
Now it's five against five.
The playing field's even.
So you can't make any excuses
when we put you away.
You put us away? Ha!
That is a good one.
[KAHSERAL growls]
[KAHSERAL]
Justice Sabers!
He turned his energy
into weapons.
Well, that's a handy
little party trick.
[KAHSERAL grunts]
[KAHSERAL grunting]
[KAHSERAL yells]
[A18 grunts]
[yells]
Well, it seems your
friend's abandoned you.
Justice Bomber! Go!
[BELMOD laughs]
Kahseral is an experienced
combat professional
who's subdued many
a world in his time.
He can concentrate his energy,
forge it into all sorts
of versatile weapons,
and then wield those
in any number of ways
to get the mission done.
Okay, that's one down.
Uh?!
[A17] Hmph. Was that
supposed to hurt me?
[ZOIRE laughing]
[GOKU groaning]
Oh, no. This guy just keeps
getting heavier and heavier!
--[TUPPER groans]
--[ZOIRE yelps]
Let him go, or else.
[TUPPER groaning]
[ZOIRE]
Are you okay, Tupper?
That woman is
absolutely merciless.
[GOKU grunts]
Thanks for the assist, 18!
Can you at least try
not to be so careless?
[GOKU laughs]
Looks like you need another
serving of my Justice Spin!
Ugh, "Justice" this,
"Justice" that.
Were you planning to help?
Oh, right.
[ZOIRE screams]
[GOKU grunting]
[ZOIRE]
Come on, Tupper! Hop in!
Yeah, let's show 'em
how we roll!
[yells] Together!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU, A18 gasp]
[ZOIRE, TUPPER]
Double Pride Spin!
Uh?!
[TUPPER laughs]
Huh?
[TUPPER gasping]
[A18] Hmph. Time for you
to hit the road!
[TUPPER screams]
No, wait, how do I stop?
Stop!
Crisis averted.
[TUPPER screaming]
[ZENOS] Tupper from the Eleventh
Universe goes bye-bye!
[ZOIRE panting]
Tupper!
[GOKU]
Hey! Guess what? You're next.
Huh?
[ZOIRE yells]
[GOKU grunting]
Uh. Uh?! He got away!
[KAHSERAL yelling]
[ZOIRE]
General Kahseral. We need you!
[KAHSERAL grunts]
We'll finish this later.
That's a letdown.
[CAULIFLA gasps, yelps]
Oh, no!
[KETTLE chuckles]
Uh... General?
We're changing strategies.
Why, what happened?
[ZOIRE screams]
Its Tupper... He's knocked out!
[KETTLE, COCOTTE gasp]
Those bastards.
Our squad just lost
one our best fighters.
These two should be
easy to take out.
Let's focus on them!
Now! Cocotte, build us a dome!
Don't let any of the other
fighters get close!
Affirmative. Cocotte
Zone Max, activate!
Whoa! What is that?
[CAULIFLA screaming]
Caulifla! Caulifla!
[A18 grunts]
[GOKU]
Hm...
What the...?
17, I can't sense
the energy in there!
[A17] There's another
dimension inside.
[CAULIFLA panting]
[KAHSERAL]
Under normal circumstances,
I would never fight like this.
But we have no choice.
Zoire! Finish her!
[ZOIRE]
Yes, sir!
[ZOIRE yelling]
Don't hurt her!
[CAULIFLA]
Don't worry, Kale.
I promise... I will
always protect you.
[CAULIFLA]
I mean...
...you are my sworn
sister after all.
[KALE]
I can't bear this.
[CAULIFLA grunting]
No, please stop!
[CAULIFLA groaning]
I'm sorry. All I ever do is
cause you trouble, Caulifla.
[CAULIFLA groans]
I'm sick of always
being this way.
So... damn helpless...
I just hate everything about
the way I am!
[ALL grunt]
[KAHSERAL]
Zoire!
Is this... really me?
[CAULIFLA]
Kale?!
[KALE]
Caulifla!
Hey, wait. You recognize me?
You know who I am?
Sure!
Oh, wow, this is huge!
You're in complete control now.
Harnessing your full power
without letting it take over!
'Course, that's no shock.
I mean, I always knew you were
capable of doing great things.
Aw, thank you.
Troopers! Time to stand firm!
The only thing that's changed
here is the color of her hair!
Prepare for a
simultaneous attack!
[TROOPERS]
Aye!
Launch United Justice Stream!
Let's do this, Kale!
Yeah!
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH yelling]
[TROOPERS yelling]
Go Pride Troopers!
Unleash Full Power!
[TROOPERS yelling]
[CAULIFLA, KALE grunting]
Dig deep! Push harder!
Friends have to stick together!
If you stay with me,
we can do this!
Right!
[KALE yelling]
What the...?!
[yelling continues]
Ha! Tryin' to show off by
going Ultra-Super, huh?
Well, I'm not lettin' you
outshine me! Now one last push!
[BOTH yell]
[gasps]
[KAHSERAL whimpers]
[ALL groan]
[TROOPERS scream]
[ZENO]
Zoire, Kettle, and Kahseral.
All three from the Eleventh
Universe, all three eliminated!
Whoa!
[CAULIFLA] Bet we had you
worried there for a second.
Uh?
Well, we blasted
three of those
uniformed dweebs outta
the ring, so you're welcome.
Is she okay like that? She's
won't go nuts again, will she?
Nah. She seems fine.
She's got this Ultra-Super
Power thing of hers
totally under control now.
Not bad, huh?
[KALE gasping]
[GOKU]
Huh?
Hey, what's wrong?
She sure looks pretty
tuckered out, huh?
[laughing]
As long as I'm inside my sphere,
you guys can't touch me!
Uh?!
All right then. I guess
the sphere goes, too.
[COCOTTE screams]
[KETTLE, ZOIRE groan]
We lost five Pride Troopers...
all at the same time?
That leaves us with only four
more competitors, my lord.
Indeed. Perhaps this
is not the time
for those remaining to be
conserving their strength.
[ZENO]
Cocotte is out, too.
The low-hanging fruit
has been plucked
and now is the time for
champions to emerge.
The fighting is likely
to get even more intense.
Wow, that is exciting!
Yes, super exciting!
Hey, last chance.
Are you sure about letting us
walk away like this?
Watching you back
there I realized
you two are gonna keep getting
stronger and stronger!
[CAULIFLA]
Huh?
[GOKU] And that's when
I wanna fight you!
[CAULIFLA] Hmph. Well, just
don't cry when ya lose.
[A18] Silly me,
I was under the impression
they were our enemies, Goku.
Oh, it'll be fine.
[A18]
Hm?
It is the human thing to do. Or,
in this case, the Saiyan thing.
Either way, I think I'll pass.
[NARRATOR]
As Goku and the others
eliminate the Eleventh
Universe's fighters,
one after another,
a shadowy figure
looks down on them from above.
Will she be their
next opponent?
And if so, what form
will she take?
The Tournament of
Power marches on,
next time on Dragon Ball Super.
When the time has come
to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever in my mind
as I look up to the sky
I was watching you
from your left side
Was trying to get
a good look at your face
The tears in your eyes;
were you laughing or crying?
Your long hair in the way
Blocking the thoughts inside
When the time has
come to say goodbye
Your voice will
echo in the night
Though we may be apart,
you're always in my heart
Forever I will wait,
for the light to show the way
For us to meet again
[GOKU]
Hey! It's me, Goku!
The warrior women of Universe
Two, led by Ribrianne,
are finally starting
to show their true power!
And their dizzying
transformations
are really shaking up
the Tournament of Power!
Things are gonna get
heated when me and 17
go up against
the Second Universe!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Super:
"The Power of Love Explodes?
The 2nd Universe's
Witchy Warriors!"
Make sure you
don't miss it, okay?