♪
Liena: Kirito.
Ronie: He finally woke up!
Asuna: Kirito.
You're back.
Vassago: 'Bout damn time
you snapped out of it.
I knew if I
waited around long enough,
you wouldn't disappoint me.
We didn't get to finish things
back in Aincrad.
Now I can check that
off my list.
( wind blowing )
It's showtime, baby.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Vassago: Is that all you got?
I wanna fight,
so get the lead out, already!
( Kirito groans )
Vassago: Come on, man!
I been waitin'
damn near two years for this!
( Kirito gasps )
( grunting )
Vassago: You'd kill me faster
if you dropped
that broken-ass sword
and used both hands.
Then you could go after
all these others
that were killin' your friends
a minute ago.
Kirito: They only did that
'cause you made them to!
That's how you do things,
turnin' people
against each other
and watchin' all hell
break loose.
That's what you did
with us in "SAO."
Well, that ain't gonna
happen here, never again!
I'll make sure of that!
( Vassago laughs )
Oh, it'll happen again.
Once those players thaw out,
they'll go right back
to slaughtering
all of your friends,
unless your pals
kill 'em first.
There's no honor
in killing the helpless,
but that's the point.
So give the order.
Kill all the red players!
( Kirito grunting )
Vassago: Hey,
if you wanna be stubborn
that's cool with me.
I'll kill you either way.
[chuckles]
But after I get done with you,
I'm gonna put Lightning Flash,
your whole crew,
and every single Underworlder
into coffins.
You can count on that!
( Kirito grunting )
Asuna: Kirito.
Tiese: Eugeo, please help him.
- ( chime ringing )
- ( gasps )
♪
( all gasp )
( Vassago laughs )
- ( chime ringing )
- Huh?
The hell...
( Kirito gasping )
Eugeo: Let's go. You and me!
Kirito: Eugeo.
( sighs )
( grunting )
♪
( yelling )
( Eugeo yelling )
( Vassago yelps )
Both: Release Recollection!
Asuna: Now what? ( gasps )
It's the life resources
of the foreign players.
Kirito logged them out
without making them suffer
the pain of getting killed.
Vassago: You're gonna pay
for that, you bastard!
Asuna: Oh, no! Stop him!
- Yuuki: Don't worry.
- ( Asuna gasps )
- Yuuki: Lookit.
- Asuna: Huh?
Vassago: Damn it!
What's goin' on?!
Wh-Why ain't they comin' to me?
Yuuki: Lives are like vessels.
They carry our hopes and dreams
and reflect our souls.
Do you think all these players
from different countries
came here just so they could be
used to kill each other? Nah.
They wanna have fun and
explore a cool new world,
a place that's totally different
from anything they know,
a place like the land of fairies
where you and I met.
They want the same as us.
Asuna: Mm-hmm.
You're right, Yuuki.
♪
Release Recollection.
Vassago: Son of a bitch!
Tiese: Eugeo once told me
that in the northernmost part
of the Human Empire,
there was
an enormous black cedar tree
and Kirito's sword
was forged from it.
Liena: I see. That explains
why it can absorb sacred power.
( both gasp )
Asuna: Kirito.
( crying )
( Liena sighs )
Vassago: Man, Kirito...
you really are the best.
( laughs ) No one, from back
in the Aincrad days to now,
ever brought out
the killer in me as much as you.
Sucks like Hell it's gotta end
after all that time,
but there's no better place
to end it than right here.
Let's you and me have some fun,
Black Swordsman!
Kirito: Okay.
I'm ready when you are.
♪
( both growl )
( woman vocalizing )
Kirito: Burst Element!
( Vassago growls )
( Kirito yells )
( groans )
( all gasp )
( Kirito yells )
( grunting )
( Vassago laughs )
- ( gasps )
- ( Kirito grunting )
( both yelling )
( all gasping )
( Vassago gags )
( chuckles )
Now that's
what I'm talkin' about.
But you didn't
get rid of me. Oh, no.
You just logged me out, is all.
I'm still gonna
keep comin' after you guys.
And I won't stop
'til I slit you and
Lightning Flash's throats
and ripped out your hearts.
You both can count on that.
Kirito: Uh-uh.
You're done for good.
You'll never
log out of here again.
Count on that.
( Vassago chuckles )
( gagging )
( gasping )
Kirito: My sword's made
from the Gigas Cedar,
a huge tree in Rulid they
couldn't cut down for 200 years,
'til two kids finally did.
I just sent
the memory of it into you.
When your friends see
all those players logging out,
they'll speed up time,
trapping you in your STL.
It'll be years before
you're let out, if you're lucky.
( wood creaking )
Then again, folks might
wanna build a village here.
They'll need wood,
and who knows?
Maybe a couple kids'll
chop you down, too.
( all sighing )
Kirito: System Call.
Transfer Durability,
Right to Area.
♪
( all gasping )
Klein: Kirito.
You did it again, man.
You saved everyone here.
But you gotta stop
hoggin' all the glory, dude,
'cause it's gettin' old.
( sniffles )
( sobbing )
Ronie: Kirito!
( Liena chuckles )
Agil: That cat's
off the hook for real.
Lisbeth: He did it!
Thank God! He did it!
Silica: He did!
And I'm so happy!
( crowd murmuring )
Renly: Ever since
I first laid eyes on him,
I had faith in him,
that at the last moment,
he and those swords
would save us all.
( Asuna sighs )
Kirito: Thank you, everyone.
I won't let your faith in me
or all the blood and tears
you shed be for nothing.
I mean it. Thank you.
( running footsteps )
( Asuna laughs )
( stammers )
Kirito...
Emperor Vecta, he's after--
Kirito: I know. It's fuzzy,
but I know he's after Alice.
Let's go get her back,
you and me, Asuna
( Asuna laughs )
♪
- Kirito: Come on.
- Asuna: Wait.
Kirito, wh-what are you doing?!
Kirito: Hold on tight.
( crowd gasping )
What's that idiot
standing around for?!
( gasps )
We got a little under
eight hours and 20 minutes to go
before the JSDF boards us.
Boss wanted me
to crank up the time again
at the eight-hour mark,
but since the other players
got wiped out,
might as well do it now.
Whatever you're up to in there,
Vassago, you better hang on.
- ( gasps )
- ( lever clunks )
What the...
That figures. I need a key.
Eh?
Brigg: We're good
at pickin' locks.
Rinko: Higa, hey!
Can you hear me?!
Come on! Wake up!
( Higa gasps )
( groaning )
H-How's Kirito?
Rinko: He's out of danger.
His Fluctlight activity's
been fully restored.
It's a little too active,
to be honest.
Higa: Really?
Oh, that's good to hear.
Kikuoka: I swear, Higa,
you had me scared
for a second there.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault
that mole got onboard.
I should've vetted
the staff better.
Higa: It's okay, Keeks.
What about Alice
and the Underworld?
Kikuoka:
They're both safe for now.
All the players
from the U.S., China,
and South Korea
have logged out.
Higa: W-Wait.
China and South Korea?
They had people
logged in from there, too?
Rinko: Yeah, tons of 'em.
They posted
all over social media
using their competitiveness
as gamers
to rile 'em up and lure 'em in.
Higa: Uh-huh. That would do it.
Kirito: The 2,000
from Japan you logged in
put up a good fight,
but they were mostly wiped out.
At that point, there were still
over 20,000 Chinese
and South Korean players left.
Luckily,
that's when Kirito woke up,
- and just like that--
- ( alarm blaring )
Kikuoka: Oh, my God.
Critter: That's not good!
Computer: Fluctlight
Acceleration rate
safety limiter disengaged.
15 minutes until
maximum-acceleration phase.
For personnel in the STLs,
initiate disengagement
protocol immediately.
Higa: Crap.
Rinko: Maximum
acceleration phase?
Isn't the FLA rate limited
to 1,200 times normal speed?
Higa: Only for folks diving.
1,200's the limit
for the life span
of a real-world human soul,
but for observing,
we can't speed it up
more than 5,000 times normal.
That said, the hardware
can go even faster.
Rinko: But how fast?
The hardware
does have a limit,
doesn't it?
Higa: During
the maximum-acceleration phase,
the FLA rate
will be just over five million.
The two STLs in Roppongi
can't keep up at that speed,
'cause they're on a SAT-link.
They'll be disconnected
automatically.
But Kirito's and Asuna's
STLs are hard-wired.
Rinko: They're in danger!
Come on!
We have to get them
out of those STLs right now be--
Higa: No! We can't!
The initial acceleration phase
already started.
If we pull 'em out
of those machines now,
it'll damage
their Fluctlights!
Rinko: What about
the disengagement protocol?
Can we start that?!
Higa: Hey, Keeks, I'm going back
to the maintenance connector.
Kikuoka: Understood,
but I'm going to go with you.
I think
I should be strong enough
to carry you
down that ladder on my back.
Nakanishi: It's too risky!
Please, sir, let me take him!
Kikuoka: No. I need you
and the other agents
to defend the stairs.
We have to open
the bulkhead again,
which means you'll have
to engage the enemy directly,
which means the risk
is greater for you.
I'm sorry, but that's
the way it has to be.
Nakanishi: Sir, yes, sir.
( Higa gasps )
Wait a sec!
When I was operating
the STLs before,
I set us up with an open channel
to talk to Kirito!
He's on line C-12!
Hurry up, and call him now!
Kikuoka: What do I tell him?
Higa: Tell him
to log himself out!
Asuna: Is Alice safe?
Can you tell?
Kirito: She hasn't
been caught yet,
but there's
a massive presence chasing her.
Asuna: Oh, boy.
I hope we can catch up to her
before it's too late.
- Kikuoka: Kirito!
- ( Kirito winces )
Kikuoka: Can you hear me?
Kirito, come in!
Kirito: Kikuoka?
How am I hearing you?
I-I'm not at a console.
Kikuoka: Never mind that.
Just listen.
You're in a lot of danger.
The time acceleration rate
is increasing,
because the hijackers
disengaged the FLA limiter!
Kirito: The limiter?
Kikuoka: Higa says
if you're still in there
when we reach
maximum acceleration,
by the time
we disconnect you here,
200 years
will have passed there.
Kirito: What?!
Kikuoka: You and Asuna
have ten minutes
to reach the console
and log out manually.
Depleting your HP
is another option,
but it's too risky.
If you die after we reach
maximum acceleration,
you'll spend 200 years
in the Underworld
in a state
of total sensory deprivation!
Kirito: Got it.
Me and Asuna are headed
for the console
at the World's End Altar.
I'll catch up to Alice in a bit,
so get ready.
We're bringing her, too.
Kikuoka: Thanks,
but you two are more important.
I want you to prioritize
your escape over securing Alice.
200 years is longer than
the life span of a human soul.
So even though
we can delete your memories
after logging you out,
if you've been
in there that long,
the odds of you
regaining consciousness here
would be almost zero!
Kirito: Don't worry.
We'll make it.
We'll all make it.
Uh, oh, and one more thing.
I'm sorry, you know,
for calling you
a son of a bitch.
Kikuoka: Not at all.
I deserved it,
and you can punch me
when you get back.
Looks like Higa's ready.
I have to go. Good luck.
Kirito: You, too.
We'll get to that console.
See you in ten.
Asuna: What did he say?
You sounded like it was serious.
Is it? Well, is it?
Kirito: Not really.
The time here's
gonna speed up in ten minutes.
He wants us
to log out before it does.
Asuna: All right, then.
I wish we could
float here forever,
but Alice does need us.
Come on. Let's go get her.
Kirito: Hang on.
We'll be goin' fast.
( wind blowing )
Alice: Amayori and Takiguri,
this is my final order to you.
Return to the Human Empire
and your nests in the West.
Amayori, find a husband,
and, Takiguri, find a wife.
Have many babies,
and raise them to be strong,
strong and brave,
so that one day,
they may carry knights
as gallantly as their parents.
♪
Go home! Go on!
( Amayori wheezes )
Alice: Amayori?
( Amayori growls )
Alice: No! Leave it!
( gasps )
♪
( dragons growl )
( chorus vocalizing )
( Amayori snarls )
( dragons wail )
( Alice gasps )
( vocalizing continues )
Alice: Amayori!
( vocalizing stops )
( gasps )
♪
( Gabriel grunts )
( Alice gasps )
( sighs )
Kirito.
♪
( singing in Japanese )