( Yui gasps )
What's this link?
It's from the old "SAO" server.
I wonder who it could be.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( footsteps scraping )
( Ronie grunts )
( gasps )
Vassago: Hmm.
Hello. Anyone in there?
Lookin' for the Black Swordsman!
Come on, sunshine.
Get your ass up, already.
Ronie: During the battle,
he kept trying to move
to get up,
and then he started crying.
Asuna: Easy, Ronie.
( grunts )
What is wrong with you?
Can't you see he's hurt?!
He's not in any shape
to defend himself!
We surrendered
just like you wanted,
so leave him alone, already!
Vassago: Are you gonna keep
sittin' there and doin' nothing?
That ain't no fun at all,
tough guy!
( kicking )
Yo! Rise and shine, ass-wipe!
Stand up! Good morning!
- Asuna: Kirito!
- ( both gasp )
Vassago: Damn, that's tragic.
Looks like he really is busted.
( scoffs ) The great hero's
just a vegetable now.
( sighs )
- ( Kirito sighs )
- Vassago: Ah.
- ( Kirito gasping )
- So you can move!
What's up? You want me
to give this back to you?
Come on, man. Say something!
Klein: Son of a bitch.
Get your hands off him,
God damn it!
( gags )
- Lisbeth: Klein!
- Silica: No! Klein!
Klein: I'm gonna kill you...
you bastard!
♪
( Vassago chuckles )
( both gasp )
( Klein groans )
( Vassago gasps )
Whoever you are, you're dead.
♪
( Asuna gasps )
Klein: Oh, my God.
Eiji?
( Vassago scoffs )
( chuckles )
You little turd.
Get out of my face!
♪
We got another hacker here!
Send his cheating ass
back to Japan!
( Asuna gasps )
( Yuna giggles )
Eiji: Yuna.
Yuna: I came as fast as I could.
- Red Knight: It's Yuna!
- ( Red Knights murmuring )
- Red Knight 2: No way!
- Red Knight 3: It is her!
Yuna: You ready, Eiji?
( "Longing" playing )
- Oh, yeah.
( Vassago scoffs )
You gonna stand there
or do something?
( Yuna inhales )
( singing "Longing" )
Eiji: Round two comin' up.
( Vassago scoffs )
( singing in Japanese )
( Red Knight 4 gasps )
Red Knight 5: I know that voice!
I-It's Yuna!
Red Knight 6: Wait. Then this
really is a Japanese server?
♪
Vassago: Bastard. Who are you?
Eiji: Your past.
I'm a Knight of the Blood Oath.
I'm Nautilus!
♪
( Asuna gasps )
Vassago: I never heard of you,
you jackass.
Eiji: Yeah,
I guess you wouldn't have.
( "Longing" continues )
Back then,
I was useless and weak.
Not anymore.
( Vassago grumbles )
Eiji: In Aincrad,
you were a murderer.
Some of the people you killed
were my friends!
This is payback!
This is for them!
( metal clangs )
( wheels clattering )
( young Vassago sighs )
( shuddering )
( growls )
♪
( Vassago roars )
( Yuna gasps )
( Eiji grunts )
Vassago: Look at
this Japanese gamer trash.
( Eiji gasping )
Vassago: You pissant.
♪
You never had
a chance in hell against me.
♪
( glass shatters )
Woman: I should have
had you aborted!
Ever since you slithered out,
you've been nothing
but a curse on my life.
( shudders )
You're a demon!
Man: I'm glad to see
you're looking healthy.
Vassago: Yeah,
like you ever cared.
I haven't seen you
in years, "Dad."
What do you want?
Father: My son,
your older half brother,
suffers from
congenital kidney failure.
He needs a kidney transplant
as soon as possible.
Vassago: And why are you
telling me this?
Father: I found
the best hospital in Japan
for the procedure, along with
a top surgeon to perform it.
Vassago: So?
Father: I want you to donate
one of your kidneys to my son.
Vassago: What the hell?!
Get someone else!
Father: If you refuse,
I can't support you
or your mother anymore.
( Vassago grumbles )
( sighs )
( winces )
( no audible dialogue )
( shudders )
( gasps )
( no audible dialogue )
Goddamn Japanese!
Reporter:
We're coming to you live
in front of Tokorozawa
General Hospital,
where victims
of the "SAO" incident
have been arriving
by ambulance nonstop.
Since the game went live
three days ago,
officials have yet
to find a solution.
Meanwhile,
the death toll reached 478,
and that number
is expected to climb.
The police
are currently at work
rounding up
all NerveGear consoles.
On the black market, however,
- they are still available.
- Vassago: Goin' shoppin'.
( siren blaring )
( panting )
( chuckles )
Link start.
Mother: You're a demon!
Vassago: Hmm.
Nothin' I hate more
than the Japanese,
and now I can kill all I want.
( Eiji groans )
Klein: Nice try, Eiji.
Vassago: You Japanese
all fight the same,
all sizzle, no steak.
Time to say sayonara.
( Eiji yells )
( Vassago gasps )
Eiji: In the end...
I still took a piece out of you.
Vassago: You lousy...
rotten ass-wipe!
( Yuna gasps )
♪
Eiji: Yuna...
I did my job as a knight
this time, didn't I?
( Yuna sighs )
Yes, Eiji. You did.
♪
Moonphase: His hand.
You see the logo on it?
Mei Xiang: Yeah.
It's the same
as the one the members
of Laughing Coffin had.
Red Knight 7: Laughing Coffin?
Red Knight 8: Yeah. They went
around killing people in "SAO."
Red Knight 9: He's one of them,
a serial killer?
♪
- ( Moonphase gasps )
- Mei Xiang: What is that?
- Moonphase: It's mind control!
- Boy: Calm down!
Girl: Stop!
You have to fight it!
Boy: That guy's a serial killer!
Girl: Snap out of it!
He's controlling you!
Girl 2: He's wants us
to kill each other!
Boy 2: Dude, you're
not thinking straight!
Mei Xiang: Everyone,
stand down, and listen to us!
♪
( tone whines )
( Red Knights yelling )
( Vassago laughs )
Moonphase:
Is he a demon or what?
Vassago: Don't worry, pal.
You'll be back on your feet
real soon.
And I promise
to keep the killing going
'til you decide to.
( metal pings )
( chorus vocalizing )
( gunshot )
( Sinon winces )
The Hecate II
holds seven rounds per mag,
and I've got one round left.
A Barrett XM500 rifle
holds ten rounds per mag.
That means he's got...
two left!
( gasps )
( groans )
♪
I'm sorry, Asuna.
I'm sorry, Yui.
I'm sorry...
Kirito.
( blade stabs )
( Leafa panting )
( wails )
Verdurous Anima!
( yells )
( tones whine )
( gasps )
( blood drips )
( panting )
( winces )
( rumble )
It's like a curse.
( blades clatter )
The Terraria account
has unlimited regeneration,
so no matter how bad I'm hurt
or how much pain I feel,
I can't die out.
( gasps )
If Kazuto were in my place,
he wouldn't care.
He'd keep going,
so...
I'll keep going, too.
I can do this.
I'll cut all of 'em down myself.
After all...
I'm Kazuto's....
and Kirito
the Black Swordsman's...
little sister!
( tones whining )
♪
( gags )
( sword clatters )
( missile whistles )
( gagging )
( rumble )
( panting )
( marching footsteps echo )
- ( spear clangs )
- ( chuckles )
( metal clangs )
( Sinon gasps )
( gasps )
♪
I won't give up.
My imagination transformed
Solus's bow into my rifle,
but I bet I can still access
the original system features
of the bow.
No way am I giving up.
I have to believe in me,
in Hecate,
in Kirito.
By automatically absorbing
the resources around it,
the bow can recharge
its main attack,
the Annihilation Ray.
Say, "Ahh"!
( groans )
( smoke whooshing )
♪
( gasps )
( chorus vocalizing )
Oh, yeah.
And I got plenty more
where that came from!
( sighs )
Kirito.
♪
( tones whine )
( Leafa panting )
I-I put up a good fight...
huh, Kazuto?
- Rinko: Higa, look out!
- ( Higa gasps )
( Yanai gasps )
( Higa gasps )
( Yanai screaming )
( Higa sighs )
Rinko: Higa!
You okay? Answer me!
Higa: Yeah, I'm okay,
just freaked out.
I didn't know
you could scream so loud.
( Rinko gasps ) How in the hell
can you be so calm?!
Are you hurt?
Did he shoot you?
Higa: Oh. Well, um...
No, not really!
He just winged me!
But I'm okay to keep going here,
so don't worry about me.
Just make sure Kirito's stable!
Rinko: Are you sure you're okay?
You better not be lying to me!
If you are,
I'm gonna kick your butt!
Higa: I'm not lying, I swear!
I'm fine!
Rinko: All right.
I'm going back to SubCon, then.
I'll let you know if
Kirito's condition changes any!
Good luck, Higa!
Higa: Uh, R-Rinko! Wait!
- Rinko: What?
- Higa: I was...
sort of wondering...
do you wanna get
some food sometime?
When this is all over?
Rinko: Yeah, of course!
Hamburgers, beef bowls,
whatever you want to eat,
you got it!
My treat!
Higa: That'll be a cheap date.
( grumbles )
I probably jinxed it
by asking her, anyway.
Connecting STL 1 to 4.
Connecting 5 and 6.
( wincing )
All right, Kirito,
let's wake you up, already.
♪
( Vassago chuckles )
Asuna: Please, Kirito.
I'll give my heart,
my life, everything.
Please, please...
open your eyes.
Leafa: Kazuto.
Sinon: Kirito!
Eugeo: Come on, Kirito.
♪
( Kirito sighs )
( sighing )
( gasps )
Eugeo: Kirito.
( Kirito gasps )
Was it all a dream?
( singing in Japanese )