♪
( Alice gasps )
( sighs )
Kirito.
( Amayori squeals )
Alice: Amayori?
Thank you.
And welcome back, Kirito.
Kirito: Sorry I took so long and
for making you worry about me.
Thank you, Alice.
Alice: No. Kirito, wait!
Asuna: Don't worry.
He'll be fine.
( Alice gasps )
Asuna: We just have
to have faith in him.
But we better hurry.
We don't have
much time left here.
( chorus vocalizing )
( chorus ends )
( groans )
Alice: Asuna!
( Asuna gasps ) Don't worry.
I-I'm okay.
The Altar's closing.
I have to get you out.
♪
Alice: Kirito...
I have so many questions
and even more to tell you.
You must prevail.
Triumph over that demon,
and come back to me.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Kikuoka: Higa says
if you're still in there
when we reach
maximum acceleration,
by the time
we disconnect you here,
200 years
will have passed there.
♪
Kirito: All right, who are you?
Gabriel: I'm a hunter
and a thief and a destroyer.
Kirito: So what
are you doing here?
Gabriel: I'm hunting souls.
And who are you?
Why are you here?
What gives you the right
to stand in my way?
Kirito: My name--
M-My name is--
My name is...
Eugeo: You're Kirito,
Kirito the swordsman.
Kirito: My name is Kirito,
Kirito the Swordsman!
♪
Now it's your turn.
Gabriel: I'm Gabriel,
Gabriel Miller, Mr. Swordsman.
( chorus vocalizing )
♪
Kirito: Let's go, Gabriel!
Generate All Elements!
Discharge!
( Gabriel scoffs )
( sighs )
( Kirito grunts )
( gasps )
♪
( chorus vocalizing )
( Kirito winces )
Gabriel:
It should take those two
about five minutes
to reach the system console.
( chuckles )
You have three minutes.
Try not to bore me too much.
Kirito: You're so generous
with your time.
Three minutes?
That's all I'll need.
( Gabriel scoffs )
Thanks for the idea.
( Kirito gasps )
( Gabriel inhales )
( Kirito yells )
( grunts )
( gasps )
( gags )
( Gabriel laughing )
( Kirito gasps )
( Gabriel growls )
( growls )
Kirito: Up to now,
all I cared about
was fighting long enough
so Asuna and Alice
could get out.
I was okay with getting
stuck here for 200 years,
but now I'm wondering why?
Is it 'cause,
deep down, I wanna stay?
I mean, this is
what I hoped for,
a true alternate world
bigger and better
and more real than Aincrad.
I didn't think what that'd do
to Asuna, Alice,
my family and friends,
how back home,
they'd cry over me
while I've lived here
until my soul fizzled out.
Did I ever care
about how they felt?
Am I that selfish?
- Eugeo: No, you're not.
- ( Kirito gasps )
Eugeo: You wanting to stay here
isn't for selfish reasons.
That's not the Kirito I know.
You care about the Underworld
and the people you met here.
( no audible dialogue )
♪
( Kirito gasps )
Eugeo: But that's
not true of him.
He doesn't care
about anyone at all.
He's incapable.
That's why he hunts
and steals and destroys.
It's 'cause he's scared,
scared of people.
Gabriel: I know
what he's feeling now.
On the brink of death,
his confidence has failed him.
He's afraid.
I think I'll have a taste.
( slurps )
( grunts )
( laughs )
( Kirito gags )
Gabriel: I'll feast
on your feelings,
your memories,
your mind, your soul.
I'll gobble them all up.
Kirito: Good luck, asshole.
You won't find any of 'em there.
My body's just a vessel.
I'll show you
where my soul's at!
Gabriel: What?
Kirito: Release Recollection!
ection!
( Gabriel grunts )
( grunts )
( tone chiming )
♪
( Sinon gasps ) Huh?
Is that...
( sighs )
It's him,
his heart,
his soul, his everything.
Please, let all of me
reach Kirito, too.
Leafa: Kazuto.
I'm sending all the strength
I have left to you...
Big Brother.
Iskahn:
I'm startin' to wonder,
what's all of this mean,
you know, like, to have power
and to be strong?
Sheyta: You already know.
Just search your heart.
The answer is right there,
a power greater
than anger or hate.
♪
Lisbeth: Kirito...
I have a confession to make.
I really do love Kirito.
Silica: That makes two of us.
Lisbeth: Our souls
are connected,
so we're always with you,
Kirito, even now.
Renly: I see now.
To live, to struggle, to rise,
to connect hearts and lives,
they are what it means
to be strong.
They are proof of it.
♪
Selka: Eugeo, hear my prayer.
Please protect my sister
and Kirito.
♪
( Alice panting )
( gasps )
♪
Alice: Kirito!
Though my soul has existed
only a short while
as a fraudulent knight,
I know, without a doubt,
these feelings I have,
these emotions surging
within me are real!
Asuna: Kirito.
( Gabriel grunting )
( roars )
( panting )
( laughs )
( gasps )
♪
( chorus vocalizing )
( both growl )
( both yell )
( Gabriel growls )
( Kirito yells )
( chorus vocalizing )
( Kirito growls )
Shasta: Reject
your urge to kill,
for that man's empty soul
cannot be slashed
by an Incarnation of murder.
Bercouli: If you're scared,
kid, don't be.
With a swing of your sword,
the weight of this world
will come crashing down on him.
Administrator: Now, boy,
show me your resolve.
My divine willpower is now yours
to wield as you see fit.
Cardinal: Kirito,
you must believe.
Believe in the hearts
of all the people you love,
and know
they all love you in return.
♪
Kirito: Starburst...
Stream!
( yelling )
( Gabriel grunts )
Kirito: It's over, Gabriel!
( Gabriel roars )
( roars )
( growls )
( Kirito gasps )
( tone chiming )
Eugeo: Go on.
Here's your chance. End it.
Kirito: Thank you, Eugeo.
( grunts )
( yelling )
( both grunting )
( Gabriel laughs )
You can't satisfy my hunger
with this light!
I'll devour it
like everything else!
Kirito: Like hell, you will!
The power of the human heart
scares you most!
And now you'll choke on it!
( Gabriel laughing )
( inhales )
( crazed laughter )
( gasps )
( wailing )
( chorus vocalizing )
♪
( no audible dialogue )
Kirito: Bye, Eugeo.
Thanks again.
♪
( rumbling )
( gasps )
( sighs ) Thank God.
They both logged out in time.
Hope you like my world, Alice.
( inhales )
( sighs )
The next 200 years
should be interesting.
Asuna, Sinon, Leafa,
everyone...
bye.
( crying )
( gasps )
Asuna: I didn't go.
Kirito: Asuna.
♪
( singing in Japanese )