♪
( clock ticking )
( Kirito sighs )
Guess I'll go home.
It feels like--
like there's
something I need to do.
I just can't remember what.
( crowd murmuring )
( train wheels rattling )
Announcement: Next stop,
Hon-Kawagoe. Hon-Kawagoe.
( commercial music
playing faintly )
♪
Sachi: Kirito.
( Kirito gasps )
Sachi.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
- ( Moonphase gasps )
- Mei Xiang: What is that?
- Moonphase: It's mind control!
- Boy: Calm down!
Girl: Stop!
You have to fight it!
Boy: That guy's a serial killer!
Girl: Snap out of it!
He's controlling you!
Girl 2: He's wants us
to kill each other!
Boy 2: Dude,
you're not thinking straight!
Mei Xiang: Everyone,
stand down, and listen to us!
( tone whines )
( Red Knights yelling )
( Vassago laughs )
Moonphase:
Is he a demon or what?
Vassago: Don't worry, pal.
You'll be back on your feet
real soon.
And I promise
to keep the killing going
'til you decide to.
( chuckles )
Why, hello there!
Maybe he'll wake up
if I murder you.
( Asuna gasps )
I have to stop him.
( grunts )
No use.
I can't get up.
- Yuuki: Asuna...
- ( Asuna gasps )
Yuuki: It's okay. You can do it.
( Asuna gasps )
Yuuki: Go on.
I know you got it in you.
Stand up,
and protect everything you love.
( Asuna sighs )
( soldier whimpers )
( Vassago laughs )
( Asuna yells )
Vassago: Huh?
♪
( grunts )
( gasps )
( Asuna winces )
( grunts )
What do you want?
Why are you doing this?
Vassago: Isn't it obvious?
- I wanna kill your boy.
- ( Asuna gasps )
Vassago: I've been wanting to
since the first time I tried
on Floor Five in Aincrad.
I don't think
I ever wanted anything more.
Asuna: You mean
you hate Kirito so much,
that you would cause
all this suffering?!
Vassago: Say what?
You of all people
should know better than that.
I wouldn't go
to all this trouble
if I didn't love the bastard.
The world's full of scumbags,
in case you didn't notice,
but that guy,
he's someone
you can totally believe in.
No matter
how much I screwed with him
or tried peelin' back
that honor of his,
he never took the bait.
I respected that.
Hell, I cheered him on!
That's why...
seein' him end up like that,
I'm friggin' pissed I wasn't
the one that got to break him.
But I'm gonna be the one
to snap him out of it.
I'll kill whoever I have to
and however many I have to
to make that happen!
( Asuna grunts )
You're sick.
That's why you're doing this.
You don't respect him.
You just get off
on making him suffer.
You're insane!
- ( gasps )
- Vassago: Guess I finally
got the hang
of how things work in here.
Bet you didn't know
all the spilled blood
and lives lost in this world
get converted to energy.
Back in Aincrad, any time
I used the ol' Mate Chopper here
to kill a monster,
its stats would go down,
but if I used it to kill
a person, they'd go up.
Look at it now!
Here in the Underworld,
it can suck
the energy from human lives
right out of the air
and power up all on its own.
Life energy's
swirling all around us
from the American players
you killed
and from Japanese players
the Chinese and Koreans killed.
And soon as they're done
killing each other,
this place is gonna be
overflowing with energy.
My Chopper's going
to absorb it all, and then...
I'm gonna hunt down
every artificial Fluctlight
and kill all of them, too.
I'll start
with the Dark Territory,
then murder my way
across the Human Empire.
What do you think, hot stuff?
You think all that death'll
wake him up?
If he's the Black Swordsman
I remember, it will.
( Asuna gasps )
Vassago: Don't you worry.
You ain't gonna die just yet.
I'll cut your arms and legs off
and keep you alive for a bit.
I want you to stick around for
what I got planned for him...
to see the big hero...
wakin' up
just to die in my arms!
( Asuna grunting )
♪
- Yuuki: It's okay.
- ( Asuna gasps )
Yuuki: I'm with you always.
♪
( chorus vocalizing )
( Vassago gasps )
Lisbeth: Asuna!
Show that creep who's boss!
Silica: You can do it!
I know you can!
Agil: You got this, Asuna!
Klein: Kick his ass!
Asuna: You...
all you know is hate.
I'll never give in
to someone like you.
I'll fight you to the end!
( yells )
( Vassago gasps )
♪
( gasps )
( Asuna grunts )
( Vassago gags )
( Asuna yells )
( Asuna gasps )
( panting )
♪
Thank you, Yuuki.
( energy surging )
( Sortiliena gasps ) Look out!
His weapon is still
absorbing sacred power!
( Asuna gasps )
( gasps )
( Red Knights murmuring )
( Vassago chuckles )
Y'all see that?!
You still think
these people ain't cheaters?!
Now we got traitors
in our ranks
working with the Japanese
to confuse you!
Kill 'em all, and send 'em
back where they came!
( Red Knights cheer )
( Asuna gasps )
( Red Knights yelling )
( gasps ) Kirito.
♪
( Kirito gasps )
- Ducker: Whoo-hoo!
- ( players laughing )
( Kirito gasps )
No! Wait!
- Don't open it!
- ( Ducker chuckles )
- ( trigger clicks )
- ( alarm blares )
♪
( Kirito gasps )
( Ducker screaming )
( Tetsuo screams )
Sasamaru: Tetsuo!
Damn you!
( gasps )
( yelps )
( Kirito gasping )
♪
- ( gasps )
- ( no audible dialogue )
( Kirito gasping )
- Keita: You're a beater.
- ( Kirito gasps )
Keita: You should have
never gotten involved with us!
( Kirito screams )
( sobs ) Stop it!
I don't wanna see this again!
Not again!
♪
( Kuradeel groans )
( Kirito yells )
( shards shatter )
( crying )
Stop showing me this.
I don't wanna remember.
The pain you caused Asuna...
was way worse!
( Oberon screams )
My hand!
( Kirito grunts )
( Oberon screaming )
( gagging )
( whimpering )
( Kirito growls )
( Oberon screams )
( Kirito yells )
( Death Gun gasps )
( growls )
( Kirito groans )
( yells )
( Death Gun groans )
( Kirito yelling )
( crying )
- ( ax chops )
- ( gasps )
( no audible dialogue )
( Kirito gasps )
♪
( weeping )
I'm the one--
I'm the one that should've died!
( gasping )
( screams )
( grunts )
( cracking )
Asuna: Kirito.
( Kirito moans )
♪
Asuna.
Sinon: Kirito.
Kirito: Sinon.
Suguha: Kazuto.
Kirito: Sugu.
I know you wanna comfort me...
tell me it's okay...
but I don't deserve it.
I failed everyone.
I'm sorry, Asuna.
I'm sorry, Sinon.
Sorry, Sugu.
But I can't stand
and fight anymore.
I'm sorry.
( Higa groans ) Damn it!
What's going on
with you, Kirito?
( sighs )
I thought three people
would be enough.
I guess we need another person.
Come on. Think!
Who else can we get
to link up to him?
Someone who's mental image
is strong enough to fix him.
- ( screen beeps )
- ( gasps )
It's an object
from the Underworld's
Main Visualizer
connected to him.
Eugeo: Kirito.
( Kirito gasps )
Eugeo: Hey there.
Kirito: Eugeo!
Y-You're alive?
Eugeo: Mm-mm.
I'm the Eugeo
that lives in you, your memory,
also a piece of my memory
I left for you.
Kirito: A memory?
Eugeo: That's right.
Think back
to what we told each other.
Remember?
How our memories live forever?
I'm not gone.
I'm right here.
( Kirito gasps )
( sobs )
Yeah.
♪
You're in here forever.
Asuna: Our hearts
are what connect us,
so we're always with you.
Sinon: We're right here,
no matter how far apart we are,
always, even after
our last goodbyes.
Suguha: Our memories
and feelings,
they're what
keep us together forever.
Kirito: Is it okay, Eugeo?
Can I--Can I get back up again?
Can I move on?
Eugeo: Of course, Kirito.
Everyone's waiting for you,
so let's go.
You, me, all of us together.
( Kirito sighs )
( grunts )
( Red Knights yelling )
( Vassago laughing )
Asuna: K-Kirito.
( gasping )
( crying )
It smells like...
roses.
( Vassago laughs )
( gasps )
♪
Huh?
( laughs )
Ah.
( Kirito inhales )
Kirito and Eugeo:
Enhance Armament.
( ice crackling )
Ronie: Oh, my.
Sortiliena: That was
Perfect Weapon Control.
( Asuna gasps )
Kirito.
( Vassago grunts )
( Asuna gasps )
Vassago: I waited
a long time for this.
Come on. Let's dance, Kirito!
- ( grunts )
- Sortiliena: Villain!
♪
( Sortiliena screams )
( both gasp )
- ( both grunt )
- ( Asuna gasps )
- ( Vassago gasps )
( gasps )
♪
( Vassago screams )
( growls )
( Asuna gasps )
- Agil: Yeah.
- ( all murmur, laugh )
( Asuna gasps )
Kirito...
you're back.
Kirito: Yeah.
I am back.
( singing in Japanese )
♪