♪
Rinko: Thank you all
for taking time
out of your busy schedules
to be here.
Today, the institute
is announcing the birth
of the world's first true
artificial general intelligence.
( cameras clicking )
( no audible dialogue )
I'd like to introduce you to...
Alice.
♪
( cameras continue clicking )
Alice: People of the real world,
good day to you.
My name is Alice,
Alice Synthesis Thirty.
( singing in Japanese )
♪
Alice: My name is Alice,
Alice Synthesis Thirty.
Silica: Wow! She's wearing
our school's uniform!
Lisbeth: I heard
she asked for it specifically.
She said she wanted
to wear the same uniform
as the knights who came
to help the Human Guardian Army.
It wasn't her first choice,
though.
She really wanted to wear
the same gold armor
she had in the Underworld.
Leafa: I bet Rath
saw how much it'd cost
to make gold-plated armor
and were like, "Nope."
( all laugh )
Sinon: They sure didn't skimp
on getting
her looks just right.
It's like a one-to-one copy.
Rinko: We'll take
your questions. Yes?
Reporter: I'd like to start
with what we're all wondering.
How is Miss Alice here different
from any of the other
programmable robots
that have been
developed so far?
Rinko: Her brain, actually.
I'm referring to the mind,
not the organ.
Her consciousness,
which is stored
in the photonic brain
in her skull,
isn't a program
made up of binary code.
Essentially, it functions
the same as a human brain.
That's what makes her different
from the robots
we have currently.
Reporter: Perhaps you
could show us what you mean
with a demonstration.
I'm sure my colleagues here
and the viewers at home
would appreciate it.
Rinko: If you look
in the handouts we provided,
you'll find
her Turing test results there.
Reporter: I was hoping
for something more,
a visual example,
say, opening her skull
and showing us
what this photonic brain
looks like.
- Rinko: I--
- Alice: Of course.
Rinko: Uh...
Alice: I would not mind.
But first,
could you please prove to us
that you are not a robot?
It is only fair.
Reporter: Well,
I-I'm obviously human.
How would I go about proving it?
Alice: It is simple.
I could open your skull
and show everyone here
your brain.
( crowd murmurs )
( Leafa chuckles )
Alice isn't messing around.
Reporter 2: Um, this question
is for Dr. Kojiro.
Labor unions have raised
the concern before
about the use
of advanced A.I. in industry
causing unemployment
to rise even further.
Are those fears unfounded?
Rinko: Let me make
one thing perfectly clear.
Our institute has no intention
of providing true A.I. for
application in simple labor.
( reporter 2 gasps )
But the financial sector
seems to have hopes you will.
In fact, the stocks of
industrial robot manufacturers
shot up when you
announced this presser.
Rinko: A true A.I.,
or rather what we like to call
an Artificial Fluctlight,
is not the sort of thing
that can be mass-produced
in a short amount of time.
They're born as infants
and raised by their families
from children to adults,
just like us.
They mature and develop
their own unique personalities,
just like us.
To force
an intelligence like that
to spend their existence
as a robot in some factory
is inhumane
and should not be allowed.
Reporter 2: Doctor, I'm sorry,
but are you saying A.I.s
should have
the same rights as humans?
Rinko: At this point in time,
I don't expect any of you
to accept
Artificial Fluctlights
as human beings
with human rights.
That's a topic that requires
a more thorough discussion.
However, I believe,
in a century or two,
our society
will advance to the point
where we'll be living
with them as equals,
interacting freely with them,
and accepting them as ordinary.
We'll even marry and
start families with them.
It's only a matter of time,
really,
and since a shared future
with them is inevitable,
it would be immoral
to subject them to slavery.
Reporter 2:
But they're not like us!
Their existence is
totally different from ours.
They're mechanical,
made by humans in a factory.
How are we supposed
to accept them as equal to us
when their bodies
aren't even flesh and blood?
Rinko: I--Eh?
Alice: If I may speak frankly.
I accept you real-world humans
for what you are, my creators,
and I am grateful
to you for creating me.
When we learned
of your existence,
a man from my world
pointed something out,
"Suppose the real world
also had a creator.
"Who created them?
And how many more creators
are there behind them?"
I ask you, if your creator
appeared before you one day
and made you their slaves,
how would you respond to that?
Would you grovel,
pledge loyalty, beg for mercy?
♪
As of now, I have met
so many of your kind
and enjoyed their company.
And even though
I am a stranger here,
they have welcomed me
and supported me.
I have learned much from them,
and they have shown me
so many sights.
I am very fond of them.
And that is not all.
I feel deeply for one of them.
Dare I say, I love him.
And the thought of not being
able to see him now,
pains me so.
It feels like
this metal chest would burst.
I extend my hand in friendship
to the people of the real world
and hope you will take it.
But I will not kneel to you,
nor grind my head
in the dirt for your favor.
I will not,
because I am human, too.
Newscaster: I have to admit,
I never heard of the Oceanic
Resource Exploration and
Research Institute before today.
Apparently, they were
testing autonomous subs
on the Ocean Turtle
when the hijacking took place.
Commentator: Yes. And according
to the latest reports,
the hijackers were
trying to get their hands
on this A.I.
we just heard speaking.
Newscaster: We also just learned
a JSDF officer
was killed in the raid.
( Higa sighs )
Damn it, Keeks.
I can't wrap my head
around the fact
that out of all of us,
you were the one
that had to die.
It ain't right.
Kikuoka: I know.
It took me by surprise, too.
Oh, well. It's better this way
than the alternatives.
They could have either
had me dragged into court
and turned into a scapegoat,
or they could have
had me disappeared for real.
But with me dead,
the public's attention
is right where we want it to be,
on the bureaucrats
in our government
trying to sabotage our goals.
I didn't think it went
all the way up the ladder
to the Vice-Minister
of Defense, though.
That was truly shocking.
Higa: No, not really.
Who needs ethics when
the U.S. weapons industry's
throwing cash at you?
Anyway, back to your plan.
Are you sure going public
with the A.I. Fluctlights
was the right move?
I mean, by doing this,
it's totally screwing
with Rath's big goal
to use 'em in weaponized drones.
Kikuoka: Maybe it does.
But now the Americans know
we have the capability,
and that, my friend,
is a good thing.
Now their weapons manufacturers
can't force us
to hand over our tech
under the pretext
of joint development.
This press conference
tells the world
we perfected the A.I. Fluctlight
without their help.
Even if they had
other plans to get it,
they won't try
after seeing this.
Higa: Yeah, I guess not.
And we have him to thank
for getting us here.
( sighs )
Kikuoka: Hey. Higa, look. Look!
Higa: What? What is it?
Isn't the press conference
over by now?
( monitor buzzes )
( gasps )
Rinko: Ultimately,
our hope is that you'll meet
Artificial Fluctlights
in the virtual world
to experience who they are,
and then perhaps
you'll change your mind.
That's all we ask of anyone
watching this broadcast today.
Go and see for yourself.
Reporter 3: Uh, Doctor!
That all sounds nice,
but have you considered
all the possibilities?
What if they decide to,
I don't know,
rise up and take us over?
Rinko: We have considered
that possibility,
but it's a stretch.
( Alice gasps )
Rinko: That could only happen
if, say, we tried to exterminate
their kind first.
Reporter 3: Okay,
but when you think
of all the movies
and books up to now--
Alice: Please excuse me.
( crowd murmurs )
Alice: I must take my leave now.
( monitor beeps )
( Higa gasps )
They're coming out of it!
( both gasp )
( Alice gasps ) Kirito!
- Kikuoka: A-Alice.
- Higa: Whoa, careful!
( Alice gasps )
( Kirito moans )
( Alice shuddering )
Kirito: How's it going, Alice?
It's been a while, huh?
Alice: It has.
( crying )
Kikuoka: Listen.
It's about your little sister.
She went into Deep Freeze,
'cause she wanted
to wait for you.
She's up on the 80th floor
of the Central Cathedral
on that hill sleeping.
( Alice gasps )
( crying )
Kikuoka: Higa, I'm ready.
Dump the last 200 years
from my memory,
back to when
the max-accel phase kicked in.
Me and Her Highness
are done there.
( Kirito moans )
( sighs )
( moans )
( knock at the door )
Yeah, come in.
( door opens )
Asuna: Hey, you!
Sorry I'm so late.
Kirito: You're not.
I only woke up a second ago.
( Asuna sighs )
It feels to me like you're
only 90% back to normal.
Are you eating enough?
Kirito: Yeah, I'm eating.
I'm eating all the time.
Have some patience.
Remember, I've been
stuck in bed for two months.
Anyway, you know when
they're letting me out of here?
Three days from now.
Asuna: Really?
Then we should celebrate
with a party or two!
We can have one in "A.L.O."
and in real life!
Kirito: Sounds good to me.
( sighs )
♪
( static crackles )
( winces )
( sighs )
Asuna: It's okay.
Deep down inside,
the memories are always there.
Eugeo: That's right, Kirito.
Don't cry.
Stay cool.
Kirito: Yeah. You're right.
And we'll see 'em again.
( cries )
- ( knock at the door )
- ( both gasp )
Kirito: Come on in.
Kikuoka: Hey there!
A little bird told me
you were getting out soon.
This calls for a celebration.
Kirito: Nurse Aki
just told me about that,
so either you have my room
bugged, or you're psychic.
I don't wanna know, either way.
Kikuoka: Who cares?
The point is you're doing great.
I mean,
bouncing back from a coma
after only a week of rehab?
( chuckles )
Talk about the power of youth.
Asuna: Now that
everybody thinks you're dead,
what are you going to do?
Are you going to retire now?
We heard about
what happened at Rath,
about how they
put Rinko in charge.
You can't go
to the Roppongi office anymore.
Kikuoka: Don't worry about me.
I'm still around,
just working in the background.
I have enough
on my plate as it is
trying to keep the Ocean Turtle
and the Underworld safe.
Kirito: You are? That's great!
So do you know what'll
happen to the Underworld now?
Kikuoka: At the moment,
things aren't looking
that good for it.
The government still hasn't
picked a scapegoat to save face.
It's only
a matter of time, though.
They've been itching
to dismantle Rath,
and when they do, all our tech
will get divvied up
by the major conglomerates.
They'll seize Alice.
Then they'll
probably reinitialize
the Lightcube Cluster
on the Turtle.
Asuna: But they can't!
Kirito: You're not gonna
let that happen, are you?
You got a plan, right?
Kikuoka: A plan?
Not really.
It's more like a hope.
While the government's
running around,
trying to save their asses,
I'm hoping the public
will come to acknowledge
the human rights
of the Artificial Fluctlights.
And the way to achieve that
is to get as many people
from the real world as possible
to have as much contact with
the Underworlders as they can.
Sounds like the kind of thing
the Seed Nexus is for,
doesn't it?
Kirito: Yeah, I guess.
Kikuoka: The problem
is the Underworld
needs a high-bandwidth
connection to the Seed Nexus,
and the bigger the bandwidth,
the better the access.
Right now, the Underworld's
cut off from everything.
The government shut down
the Turtle's sat-link.
Restoring that connection is
next on my to-do list, in fact.
That press conference
the other day
was a step toward that.
It bought us attention
and, even better, time.
Kirito: The connection.
( grunts )
Kikuoka...
please...
don't let it die.
Please save it.
Kikuoka: You don't
have to beg me.
After all, the Underworld
is the one dream
I'd risk my life for, too.
( door opens )
( typing )
Higa: It's not gonna work.
No way.
It's gonna collapse,
like always
just like the copies
of me and Keeks did.
Hmm.
Once it finds out it's a copy,
there's no way a human soul
saved on a Lightcube
can survive the strain,
not even his soul.
( sighs )
( Lightcube buzzes )
Kirito: Who is that?
Is it you, Higa?
Higa: Yeah, it is.
Kirito: So you didn't delete me.
Instead, you copied
and saved me.
Higa: I did.
I-I couldn't delete you!
You're the first Fluctlight
I've ever seen
that survived 200 years.
Do you know what that means?
You're the longest-living person
in human history, you!
( stammers )
I can't hit delete on that.
You get why, don't you?!
♪
Kirito: I had a feeling
this would happen.
Is my Fluctlight the only one
you made a copy of, Higa?
Higa: Uh, yeah.
I only had time for yours.
During
the memory-delete process,
Keeks and Rinko
were doing other things,
so I went ahead and copied you.
Kirito: I see.
The queen--that is, Asuna--
she and I talked about
the possibility of this.
She said that if she were
the only one who got copied,
she would have herself
deleted right away
and if we both got copied,
we'd use whatever time
we had left
to unite the real world
and the Underworld.
Higa: What about
if only you were copied?
Did you talk about that?
Kirito: Yeah.
We decided if that happened,
I'd protect the Underworld
and fight only for it
if it came to that.
Higa: What do you mean, "fight"?
Kirito: The Underworld's fate
is extremely unstable
over there, isn't it?
Higa: Yeah, it is.
Kirito: The Underworld
is powerless,
compared to the real world.
It relies on a power source,
hardware,
maintenance, and a network.
Its existence depends
on real-world people
to keep the infrastructure
running.
Its safety in the long term
is precarious at best.
Higa: You're right, but there's
just no getting around that.
The Lightcube Cluster,
that is the Underworld,
and it can't be moved
off the Ocean Turtle.
Besides, the government's
got control of the Turtle now.
If they wanted to, they could
cut the power tomorrow,
reinitialize the cluster,
and wipe it clean.
Kirito: How long
will the reactor's fuel last?
Higa: Um, I guess...
since it's a pressurized
water reactor from a sub...
and it's just powering
the cluster,
then four or five years?
Kirito: Then there's no need
to refuel during that time,
and as long as we prevent
outside interference,
the Underworld will continue to
exist for that length of time.
Do you agree?
Higa: Y-Yeah,
but h-hold on a sec!
There's no weapons system
on the Turtle,
and without weapons, we can't--
Kirito: I said I would fight.
Higa: But how? There's no way
to connect to the Turtle
or the cluster now.
The satellite link's
been cut off.
Kirito: There's another link.
We use that.
Higa: What link?
Kirito: It's Heathcliff,
Akihiko Kayaba.
We need to find him right away.
You will help find him,
won't you?
Higa: H-He's still alive?
Kayaba?
A copy of Akihiko Kayaba
and Kazuto Kirigaya,
what would happen
if those copies--
I mean, people,
came into contact?
Oh, my God.
I think I might have opened
Pandora's box here.
But I wanna see that.
I have to know what'll happen.
All right, you're on.
I've got some old contacts.
I'll send a few emails,
encrypted of course.
( car door closes )
( vehicle drives away )
( Kirito sighing )
♪
Eugeo: You can take a nap
after you finished doing
your sacred arts homework.
No, you can't copy mine.
♪
Hey! I tweaked that skill
you taught me the other day.
Let's go to the training hall
so I can show you.
I knew it. You snuck out
to buy snacks again.
I hope you got some
for me this time.
Come on, Kirito. Wake up.
( singing in Japanese )
Eugeo: Kirito.
( Kirito crying )
I should've had all my memories
of that place deleted,
everything,
especially the time
I spent with Eugeo.
( singing continues )
( crying )
Leafa: Hey, tell me about it,
all the fun things
and the sad things,
from the beginning to the end.
Kirito: When I met him,
I was walking through a forest.
Eugeo was chopping at a tree.
He was a woodcutter
in the Underworld.
His job was to cut down
this big cedar,
a tree that, for 300 years,
couldn't be cut down by anyone.
( traffic whizzing )
- ( chamber music playing )
- ( overlapping chatter )
Alice: Kirito.
I feel...
I feel like I might die.
( birds chirping )
( cell phone buzzing )