♪
( Red Knights screaming )
( Asuna gasps )
Sinon: I'm late. Sorry.
( Asuna laughs )
Shinonon.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Found them truly
♪
Sinon: As I was landing,
I saw some old ruins.
They're down the road
about five klicks south.
Looked like a good place to make
a stand and not get surrounded.
Asuna: We'll hole up there,
then. ( sniffles )
The VRMMO community
in the States is huge,
but I think this is all
that were available now.
If we beat them,
maybe whoever's behind this
will think twice
about sending more.
Sinon: All right, then.
I'll bomb the heck out of 'em.
Oh, by the way, um,
is it okay if I see Kirito?
Asuna: What are you
asking permission for?
Of course it's okay.
He's here in the wagon.
Sinon: Oh, h-he is?
Then, I guess
I'll go in and say hi.
( clears throat )
( both gasp )
Ronie: L-L-Lady Solus?!
Sinon: Huh?
Sorry.
I'm not who you think I am.
I'm just borrowing this outfit
for a little bit.
My name's Sinon.
Ronie: Huh?
Tiese: Uh...
( Asuna gasps )
Sinon: That's right.
I'm from the real world, too,
just like Asuna
and Kirito, too. I'm his friend
Tiese: Really?
You are, too, huh?
Ronie: So many women friends.
Sinon: And he's got
even more back home.
♪
( crying )
( Kirito groans )
( Sinon crying )
Your soul might be broken,
and you might not remember
who you were,
but all your friends do.
There. Can you feel that?
It's the Kirito I remember,
the sarcastic prankster,
stubborn and sometimes immature,
and the strongest,
most kind person I ever knew.
( gasps )
( Asuna crying )
( Ronie crying )
( Tiese gasps )
Sinon: Don't worry.
He'll be back
and better than ever.
And in the nick of time,
as usual, right, Asuna?
Asuna: Mm-hmm.
Sinon: Well,
I'll be back in a bit.
I wanna check those ruins out,
make sure they're really safe.
I'll fly right back
and let you know if they are.
Asuna: Wait! Hold on.
Did I hear that right?
Can you? You know, fly?
Sinon: Uh, mm-hmm.
They said the Solus account
had the power to,
and there's no time limit on it
or anything.
Asuna: Don't worry
about us, then.
You have to get Alice back.
The emperor's got her now.
If you hurry,
you can catch them!
♪
Lilpilin: Len.
( no audible dialogue )
What were we fighting for?
For this?
Why'd you all
have to die for them?
( crying )
( wails )
( woman screams )
( both groan )
( Lilpilin gasps )
Leafa: Ow-w-w-w.
Jeez!
I always have the worst luck
with new gear.
Hmm?
Eh?
( Lilpilin gasps )
( grunts )
Don't you look at me!
( gasps )
Leafa: Uh, hang on.
Let me straighten up.
Ah, that's better.
Good afternoon or morning.
( Lilpilin sighs )
You're human.
You should be scared of me,
but you're not.
Leafa: Of course I'm not.
Why would I be scared
of another human?
Lilpilin:
Wh-What are you saying?
I-I'm no human.
Something wrong with your eyes?!
Can't you see I'm orc,
what you white Iums
call pig-people?
Leafa: You're human
as far as I can tell.
I mean,
you're standing there, talking,
so that pretty much
makes you human.
Lilpilin: What are you up to?
( Leafa sighs ) Never mind.
Do you know where we are?
- ( Lilpilin sighs )
- Leafa: Oops, I'm sorry.
I forgot to ask your name.
( wind blows )
Lilpilin: My name is Lilpilin.
Leafa: Lilpilin.
( laughs ) I like it!
It's so unique!
Nice to meet you. I'm Leafa.
( Lilpilin gasping )
Leafa: Uh...( sighs )
Lilpilin: Human,
I don't care what your name is.
You're my prisoner now,
and I'm taking you
to the emperor!
Leafa: Is this emperor of yours
also the dark god Vecta?
Lilpilin: Y-Yeah.
Leafa: Okey-dokey.
I'll let you take me to him.
( Lilpilin gasps )
Talking makes me human?
This girl is weird.
The goblins, ogres, and giants
can all talk, too,
but humans treat the lot of us
like we lower than dirt
all the same,
so why don't she?
Come on.
♪
( gasps )
What's going on?
- ( Leafa gasping )
- Lilpilin: Huh?
( grunting )
( gasps )
( Dee Eye Ell laughs )
Lilpilin: I-It's Dee Eye Ell!
Dee Eye Ell: The smell.
Oh, the smell!
The scent of life
is strong in this one!
Yes, you've captured
a wonderful specimen, indeed.
Well done, little pig-person.
Well done.
- ( Leafa grunting )
- Dee Eye Ell: To celebrate,
I shall reward you
with some entertainment.
( metal thumps )
- ( Leafa winces )
- ( Dee Eye Ell chuckles )
I assume you've never seen
a human woman's body before.
This must be quite the treat
for your piggy eyes.
But the fun is only starting.
Keep watching.
( Leafa gasps )
( yelps )
Dee Eye Ell: System Call!
Transfer Human Unit Durability,
Left to Self!
( Leafa gasping )
( Dee Eye Ell laughs )
( growls ) Oh, how delicious.
Her life is so thick and sweet!
- Lilpilin: Hey, You let her go!
- ( Dee Eye Ell laughing )
Lilpilin: That Ium
is my prisoner!
I was gonna take her
to the emperor!
Dee Eye Ell: Silence!
Filthy wretch!
Have you forgotten
that His Majesty
put all of his forces
under my command?
My will is his will,
and as long as I live,
you will obey my orders.
( Leafa gasping )
( grunting )
( Lilpilin gasps )
Dee Eye Ell: I don't believe it!
Her life surges.
It is overflowing again.
( Leafa gasping )
( Dee Eye Ell grunts )
( Leafa yelps )
( Dee Eye Ell laughing )
It is mine!
Life is mine forever!
( Leafa thinking )
I can't die here...
but she can.
I don't want to kill
an Underworlder.
( teeth stab )
( Leafa wincing )
Lilpilin: Leave her alone.
Leave her alone!
Dee Eye Ell: What?
Was that an order?
Are you out of your mind?
( Lilpilin gasps )
Dee Eye Ell:
Know your place, piggie!
She is my prisoner now.
And whether I decide
to suck the life from her
or snap her neck
is no concern of yours!
- ( Lilpilin growls )
- ( Dee Eye Ell laughs )
On second thought,
you were the one who found her,
so perhaps a slight concession
is in order,
but only if you strip naked
before me right now.
Lilpilin: You wa--
What did you say?
Dee Eye Ell: Ever since I
first saw you strutting around
in those ridiculous garments,
I was so repulsed,
I quite nearly gagged.
A mere pig
trying to pass as human!
Strip for me.
Get down on all fours
and squeal,
and then perhaps
I might let you have her back.
( Lilpilin gasps )
( Leafa in memory ) You're human
as far as I can tell.
I mean,
you're standing there, talking.
( Leafa groaning )
♪
( Lilpilin gasping )
Leafa: Don't.
I'm fine.
I can take it, really.
It's not worth it.
Dee Eye Ell: Go on, pig! Strip!
Or are you having
second thoughts?
Perhaps the sight of her
in this state arouses you
and you're too ashamed to?
( laughing )
( Lilpilin gasps ) I-I'm a--
I'm a--( gagging )
I'm...
I'm a human!
( groaning )
( Dee Eye Ell gasps )
You rotten treasonous swine!
You dare
raise your weapon against me?!
( growls )
- ( yells )
- ( Lilpilin grunting )
Dee Eye Ell: I'll chop you up
into little chunks,
mix your carcass with hay,
and feed you to the boars!
( energy whines )
( blood gushing )
( gagging )
( whimpers )
♪
How could a human slash
another human to save a pig?
Leafa: You're evil,
and I'll slash evil
to save a human!
♪
( Red Knights yelling )
( girls gasp )
Asuna: Please keep an eye
on Kirito while I'm gone.
Ronie: Yes, ma'am! We'll keep
him safe, no matter what!
Tiese: We won't
let anyone near him.
Liena: We'll guard him
with our lives.
Asuna: Don't worry. We won't
let the enemy get this far in.
♪
Renly: Now! Attack!
( soldiers yelling )
( armies yelling )
( Asuna yells )
♪
( Vassago chuckles )
Man, she's vicious
when she's got her game face on.
Rackin' up the kills
like there's no tomorrow.
( chuckles )
♪
Bercouli: He's not slowin' down.
I'm switchin' dragons,
and I still can't catch him.
He must have the power
to heal his dragon's life.
That settles it.
Time-Splitting Sword, you're up.
Sorry, dragon!
Uragiri!
Uragiri slashes the past.
Whoever that bastard is,
he can't rewind time.
If I get cut down, head back
to the others, and help 'em.
( grunts )
( chorus vocalizing )
Emperor Vecta...
not all real-worlders
are demons like you.
That Asuna girl's
proof of that.
You whipped up
the Dark Territory
and drove its people to war.
You caused the deaths of tens
of thousands of them and us.
As far as humans go,
that right there's proof
you're evil to the core.
You're gonna pay.
You're gonna feel the weight
of every life lost, so help me.
I'll make you pay!
( yells )
Slippery bastard.
♪
Time-Splitting Sword!
Karagiri!
( energy humming )
( gasps )
You can absorb
Incarnate abilities?
( humming fades )
Gabriel: Is that
what it's called, "Incarnate,"
your fusion of mind and will?
Yours tastes
like a vintage wine,
rich, thick, heavy,
with a finish
that lingers a bit too long.
It's not my favorite,
but as a palate cleanser
before the main course,
it's not bad.
Come on. Let me drink more.
Bercouli: You'll choke on it!
♪
( Gabriel chuckles )
( both grunting )
Bercouli: Got him!
( Gabriel growls )
( growls )
( chorus vocalizing )
Bercouli: What's happening?
I was about to do something,
but I forgot.
( gasps )
What the hell?
I can't believe
I let my mind wander like that!
( gasps )
You bastard.
You leeched my Incarnate ability
right out of my sword!
( chuckles )
That was a nifty trick
you pulled just now,
but if we can't cross swords,
we're gonna be here all day,
Your Highness.
Gabriel: True.
That reminds me.
I have another trick to try.
Bercouli:
You've gotta be kidding me.
( gasps )
( chorus vocalizing )
( yells )
( chorus ends )
He clouded my mind just
by pointing his sword at me!
How can I counter that?
I used Karagiri,
and that didn't work.
The only other skill
I got is Uragiri,
but he's not gonna stand there
as I fire it up. ( gasps )
Administrator: Have you ever
felt you were going to die?
( Bercouli chuckles )
If this is where
it's supposed to happen,
I'll make it count, Milady.
( chorus vocalizing )
- ( Gabriel chuckles )
- Bercouli: Kiddo...
I don't know if I did it right,
but I tried to be
some kind of father to you.
( chuckles ) I can't even
remember mine, so it's not like
I had a clue as to what
being a dad's all about,
but there's one thing I do know
A good father would give
his life to protect his kid,
and that's something
you're never gonna understand!
( Gabriel chuckles )
Bercouli: You monster!
Red Knight: God...
this game sucks so much ass.
Might as well log out
and go back to--( gags )
♪
( Asuna panting )
As long as I can stand,
I'm gonna keep fighting,
so come on if you dare!
I can do this all day
if I have to!
- Red Knight: Get her!
- ( Red Knights yell )
- ( energy pulsing )
- ( Asuna gasps )
Oh, no. There's more.
( gasps )
That was a sword skill.
No way!
Klein: Hey there!
Sorry for the wait. You okay?
Asuna: Klein? How--
( gasps )
( singing in Japanese )