A bird.
I know somewhere,
I've seen this...
What is this?
Hey! Wake Up!
What?! What?! What?!
Oh, Kana.
Don't "oh" me.
You said that you were going
to help me with work today.
Yes, I know. What time is it?
Six thirty-four in the morning.
I'm tired. 'Night.
Oh, no! Time to get up!
Stop it, stop it!
One, two.
Rakka.
Huh?
Okay, let's go.
Did you leave this out here?
I thought the birds
might eat it.
You shouldn't.
It'll attract the crows.
They're enough trouble as it is,
making a mess from our trash.
Um... um... but I...
Oh, the trash. Rakka, let's
take out the kitchen trash.
Kana! Wait for me.
Ugh, again!
Get out! Damn birds!
Damn, they've timed out
the swing of my broom.
Kana!
Oh, sorry.
That was mean!
I know I closed this door tight
yesterday. The crows must have
figured out the way
to unlock the door somehow.
Wow, they're really smart.
Don't act so impressed.
Ugh, just look at
this mess they've made.
Uh, I know, oh, why don't
we just take out the things
that crows might like to eat?
If you keep
feeding them like that,
that become dependent on us.
Then, how will they
live on their own?
Oh, um...
Just like the Haibane...
the crows have rules.
You can't spoil them!
Come on, we better get moving!
Oh.
The birds are the only
creatures that allowed to go
beyond the walls in this town.
If we continued to feed them,
we create a place where they can
survive without any struggle.
In the end, they'll decide
to only inhabit this town and
will probably never
fly free on their own again.
They might seem to be
happy here, but it's just sad.
Hey, don't you give me
that wistful look!
If you don't keep
your eye on them,
they're gonna
crap all over you.
Oh.
Let's go.
Did you sleep well?
You look out of it.
Well, um, I can't really
remember, but I think
I was having a bad dream.
Well then, good thing
I woke you up so pleasantly.
Uh, I think maybe
that's what caused it.
Well then, time for breakfast.
Where did you get that watch?
Nice, isn't it?
I found it gathering dust
in the storage room
over there and fixed it up.
By yourself? Amazing!
Oh, there was nothing to it.
I only had to
replace one little spring.
It's still amazing.
It's only a warm-up
compared to my next project.
I'm gonna challenge
a biggie soon.
A biggie?
Wanna see?
So, where did you get tea cups?
Aren't they nice? They were a
gift from the old man who owns
the antique shop, for
gathering reference materials.
Oh, now you're a librarian
abusing her power, right?
Don't go ruining my
good name. He was being kind.
I worked over a month for it.
Besides, these are second hand
items, as is the tradition.
Sad isn't it.
The older you get,
the more deceptive you become.
Kuu, breakfast!
Hurry up inside!
One, two.
Finally.
Come on up.
Isn't it like
a secret hide out?
Yes, amazing. Don't tell me
you are going to fix this?
No way. The big one's
completely done.
I wouldn't even know where
to begin on my own. However,
this is the one
that I really wanna fix.
What is that?
Somebody must've been living
here before, and that person
seems to have attempted
to modify this clock,
so that the gears would
move by electricity instead of
by pendulum. Whoever it was
that worked on this,
was good. It's just about
done. If the rusted parts
are replaced and the hands start
moving agin, even the bells
on the very top
might start to ring.
Wow. I wonder if
that person was a Haibane.
I don't know. There were
drawings and engineering notes,
but they're only
written about the clock.
They don't say anything about
who wrote them or how many years
ago they were written. I went
exploring in every room here
right after I was born,
and I found these in the end.
How should I put it, this is
like a treasure map for me.
Anybody would wanna
continue with this work
once they read it, right?
That's why you work
at the Clock Tower?
Yeah. There I'm still nothing
more than a lowly trainee.
I hope that you can fix it.
Ha.
Oh, no! My job!
Today is very relaxing.
You're right. This is how
every morning should really be.
Having good tea
makes a difference.
Ah... Kana.
Rakka, breakfast!
What's that? Good tea?
Kana.
There.
Jump on, hurry up!
That's insane!
Stop, Stop, Stop it! Please!
Shut up! You'll
bite your tongue!
Are we flying?!
I guess we just made it.
All right! Seems like
Master's late for once.
Let's go around back.
Looks if I didn't have to
speed here like that after all.
Come on, over here.
Oh, good, everything's working.
What?
Lately we've been replacing
the old parts in clock.
last night. A-ha, so that's
the reason Master overslept.
Don't judge others
by your standards.
You're seven minutes late.
Good, perfect time.
You fool! That's useless if the
screws in your head are loose!
Who are you?
The new girl I told
you about, remember?
She's trying out
different jobs, to pick one.
then, if you want to work here,
you'll have to make a
better impression than this.
Who'd want to buy a watch from a
clock maker that's always late?
Do you buy clothes from
a clothier wearing rags?
Do you buy liquor
from a tea-totaler?!
I'm too young to buy liquor.
Shut up! Stop your quibbling
and go open up the shop already!
Alright, Alright!
I hear you already, Man.
And your bicycle! It's
supposed to be in the back!
Yeah.
Damn it, he must've been
watching me from up above.
Hey you, what's your name?
M- m- my name is Rakka, sir.
You're new to Old Home,
aren't you?
Ah, yes.
Got used to this town yet?
Er, uh a little bit.
And Kana,
she's being nice to you?
Yes.
Is there anything
you like me to do.
OK then, you can go upstairs
and clean the room for me.
It's been pretty hectic
up there these days.
Hey Master, are we gonna be
tending the store again today?
Nah, you go upstairs
with her and clean up.
It's a total disaster area.
Already? Come on, Rakka.
And if you have any
questions, just ask Kana.
OK.
How come you're so nice
to everybody else, but me?
I'm treating you hard
because you have potential.
Don't complain.
So he says.
Wow!
Ugh!
Man oh man. It gets
like this every time
they replace just one gear.
I hope the clock doesn't
get drunk, really.
Late-night snack?
There's a lot of people who
work here at night. And I guess
the mess is understandable.
But, how can he be such
a stickler about time, and so
sloppy about things like this?
So where should we start off?
Let's do the trash first. Heh,
seems today I'm the garbageman.
Kana, can I have a rag.
Here you go.
Seems like everybody has a job.
You're already knew that.
But, I wonder why
the Haibane work.
'Cause we have to. It's a rule.
That's not what I meant.
Mmm, well let's see. Have
you noticed that this town
is extremely
protective of us?
Yes, sort of.
Doesn't it bother you?
It's kinda like...
we're being
treated as children.
So I think that we work
so is not feeling indebted
to the town.
I see. That kind
of makes sense.
Ah-ha. Now I get it, you
are helping Reki yesterday,
weren't you?
Yes. Reki, Hikari, you and
everybody else is working
in a job that they really
like to do. I don't know
what I'm supposed to be doing.
If there's nothing,
why don't you help Reki
for the time-being?
She's always short-handed,
having to take care of lots
of high-maintenance kids.
She's very accommodating.
Oh, but unless you work hard,
you could end up being one of
those high-maintenance kids
instead of an assistant.
Ah, really?
Oh no, that's not,
that's not what I meant to say.
What I meant to say is that
Reki is always too kind.
Rakka, you just got here, so
don't worry about it so much.
And you're working
really hard today!
Umm.
Oh yeah, why don't we go up?
Come on, it's OK.
There're railings out here.
Nice view, isn't it?
This is the highest point
in all the town,
so if you can stand this,
you won't be scared of anything.
Uh, I'm fine... not really.
That's 'cause you're
looking down. Look far ahead.
Uh, look far ahead?
The farthest is... the walls?
Yeah that's it. This town is
cone-shaped and this Tower's
at the bottom of it,
so maybe the walls are higher.
What's beyond those walls?
Do you ever wonder?
Who could really know. The
Haibane aren't allowed to go
anywhere near them. Nobody
but the Toga come into town,
and townspeople can't
go outside. If you did,
you'd never be allowed
to come back in again.
Oh, the birds.
Huh?
They're flying over the walls.
The Haibane believes that
they carry our lost items.
Lost items?
Things we left behind and
forgot about when we went
into the cocoons.
Oh, well, that's how the legend
goes. It's probably because
the birds come and go over
and back from the walls.
Rakka?
Huh?
Feeling any better now?
Yes, much better.
You see, you've
become fearless now.
Cleaning's done.
And this is for you.
What's that?
Mind your own business.
What's next?
Nah, that's it.
What's this?
Punishment for being late.
The, uh, clock tower that's
in your home,
uh... go repair that.
Can I really?
Yeah. We're really not
supposed to meddle too much
in the Haibane's daily lives.
Alright!
Ah, wait!
Thank you for letting me
work here today.
Hey, is Kana going
to leave this place?
No! Really. Kana didn't bring
me here to replace her at all.
I'm just visiting everyone's
workplace each day because
I wanted to see what kind of
job they have. I believe that...
she really does love it here.
That's good. It's just that
whenever I see those wings
of yours, they make me think
she might just fly away on me
one day.
They might look fancy,
but the truth is that
they really don't work at all.
Oh, I see. That's a relief.
Rakka, can't you go any faster?
No, safety first.
Damn.
I wanted to say
thank you for today.
Yeah, did it help you out?
Yes, I discovered
a lot of things.
Like what, Rakka?
Don't judge people
by appearances.
Oh, you mean Master.
Don't be fooled by him.
He may be friendly to customers.
Ah.
But he's always
barking at me.
No, not him.
What?
Never mind. It's nothing
You're strange.
I think I can smell the river.
Huh.
May be I've seen scenery like
this one time somewhere before.
There you go at it again.
But this time I know
just what you mean. So,
do you remember anything?
Funny, isn't it? I can
remember things like how
to talk or how to ride
a bike, but nothing else.
Hmm.
What is it?
I think I remember that
I used to sing whenever
I was feeling like this. So I
just thought now it'd be nice
if I could remember a song.
Hey! I spent a lot
of time finding that net!
And you stupid bird
rip it up the next day!
Never give up, huh?
Yeah, they don't
those damn crows.
No, I meant you.
What'd you say!?
Oops, backfired.
You shouldn't give up.
You aren't trying to
patronize me, are you, Rakka?
No, that's not true.
Both of you, don't give up!
Huh? Just what does that mean?