Rakka, are you up?
Uh...
yes.
We're all
going into Kuu's room.
O...
kay, I'm coming.
Do you like the wing covers?
Uh...
I'm so glad.
Every one of us,
will take one of Kuu's
belongings to remember her by.
Rakka, how about the bed?
Do you want anything else?
Just those.
Coming through.
And...
there...
Wow, it's cold.
Good thing you got
yourself a proper bed
before it starts
to snow, right?
How are your wings doing?
Do I have to keep
using the medicine,
and keep hiding
my wings forever?
The walls' power to protect
us weakens in a winter time,
so we become even more
susceptible to the evil.
So until winter ends...
Umm...
I still wonder,
what the Haibane are.
Everyone says that both
the walls and this town exist
for the Haibane.
But, the Charcoal Feathers are
born into this world suddenly,
and just as suddenly
they disappear.
I don't know the reason
why I became a Haibane.
I'm here, but can't remember
anything about who I was,
and if I'm to disappear someday
without accomplishing anything,
what's the meaning
of my existence?
You know, at one time,
I felt the same way as you.
I think there is a meaning.
But only you can find it.
Come on,
walk in a single file!
OK.
Rock, paper...
Scissors!
Hey!
You'll fall into the river if
you walk on the edge like that!
Oh boy.
This is the last time
we'll see it like this.
Huh?
We'll have snow soon.
Then everything around here
will be covered in pure white.
As white as if you are
floating in the clouds.
That's why we have to get ready
quickly before winter arrives.
Hmm.
Floating in the clouds...
In my dream in the cocoon, I saw
like I was in the clouds, too.
Your dream of
falling from the sky?
But you know, I don't remember
what happens to me after that.
Even though I think I met
someone or may be something
very important during my dream.
But there're times when
I can almost remember something
about my dream that I'm afraid.
As if...
Hey, don't get so far ahead!
Reki!
Come on!
I'll be by your side.
I went down the wrong pass
because I lost Kuramori.
But no matter
what happens Rakka,
I will always be by your side.
What...?
Oh no!
I told you to be careful!
Didn't I tell you
to walk in a straight line
in the middle of the road?
Everybody, fall-in!
About-face!
Mmm.
Man, the lengths
are completely wrong.
We gonna have to
redo the all hems.
Oh, great.
Ah, don't you start
give me that look.
I deserve a commendation
just for finding ten
in the same style.
I guess.
OK then, I'll give you a hand.
Rakka, pick winter wear
for yourself while you wait.
We won't take long.
Send them in after
they take off their coats.
OK.
Yeaah!
Hey!
I told you to take
your coat off first!
Come on!
Not all at once!
Sorry about that.
Hey, stop fumbling around!
You'll get hurt!
Ouch!
Hey, stop pulling my beard!
I'll finish taking
the measurements.
Why don't you go
and wait outside?
Yeah, I think I will.
Thanks.
Man, I hate kids.
Got used to the town yet?
Ah.
But, you are
surprised at how early
winter comes
around here, right?
This one.
OK.
Hmm...
You need some shoes, too.
Huh?
But I...
You must be cold
in those sandals.
It's gonna be snowing soon.
How about you try on these?
Well, but...
Ahh, be my guest!
A Haibane should
always be in high spirits
with a smile on her face.
But why?
Why?
Well, how should I put this?
Since I was a kid,
my mom's been telling me
that the Charcoal Feathers
are like the ones who
receive blessings from above.
So you're kinda
a good-luck charm.
Well, no offense.
Blessings...
But I'm not...
Oh...
Don't mind what I said.
It's only what we
simple townsfolk believe.
Here.
Oh no, my notebook...
there's only one
sheet left inside.
Well ah, why don't we say
that the boots are ah, maybe,
a New Year's present.
Might be a little early, huh?
Look, I don't know
what happened,
but things gonna get
better at some point.
No, they won't.
I'm just...
a big failure as
a Charcoal Feather.
Huh...?
Hello.
Oh, hi there.
Let's see.
Do you have this
in different sizes?
Oh, this one comes
in only one size.
It's a little Haibane!
Oh, she's so cute!
Wow!
She's for real!
Look, it's a little
Charcoal Feather!
We're so lucky!
Something good
will happen today!
Leave her alone,
you're bothering her.
No!
I'm not bothering her.
Right?
Don't touch me!
Huh?
Hey!
That was a big fall you took,
young miss.
Aah.
Thank you.
Uh, um...
Thank you very much.
Here, I think you dropped this.
I don't belong anywhere.
Nowhere at all
It's better...
if I didn't exist...
at all!
It's calling to me?
The Western Woods.
It's going there.
I feel it, he's calling me.
The air here feels different.
What is that?
You wanted to show me this?
You called to me for this?
It's better...
if I didn't exist...
at all!
A dream...
I had somewhere, sometime?
But now...
It's so cold.
Yes...
I remember.
You can't.
But thank you anyway.
I guess this well
is being here for a long time.
What's wrong with me?
I should be afraid, but...
Are you the one
who called to me?
You've taken the form of
a bird now, but it feels like
I've known you from somewhere
else, a long time ago.
Where's Rakka?
Did she come back?
I wonder what happened to her.
Hey, do you think
that maybe she's...?
It's different from Kuu's time!
Rakka hasn't...
Were you the last one
with her, Reki?
Sorry about that.
I guess I messed up.
She's not a kid who needs
an adult supervision.
But should we go look for her?
Or wait?
Even though it's
still not too late for her
to be outside of old home.
But it is better to go look
for her now than to wait until
the middle of
the night and panic.
Even if this turns out
to be needless worry.
Alright, then.
Let's go!
You're not thinking she's
running away like you did,
are you?
The situation does have
a familiar ring to it.
You're right.
The situation is similar...
But she is not as stupid as...
As you were?
Sorry.
It's OK.
Let's go!
Forgive me.
I wish there are something
more I could do for you.
You know, I can't even
remember my own name.
They say the Haibane
are all like that.
So I can't remember
anything about who you are
as much as I want to.
Except that you are
somebody precious to me.
I was always lonely
and I thought that nobody
would ever grieve for me,
even if I was gone forever.
I felt so alone.
I just wanted to disappear
and never feel anything again.
But you were always by my side.
You became a bird, just to go
over the walls and let me know
that no matter how sad I felt.
I was never alone.