Kuu.
Rakka.
Rakka, if you keep crying
like that, Kuu can't go on
her journey without
worrying about you.
Yes.
But...
Rakka, we'll be
seeing her again.
We have to believe that.
Kuu just went there
ahead of us.
You shouldn't be
feeling sad for her.
Let's go.
I wonder if Kuu
can hear the bells.
I'm sure she can.
May the bell be a guide
through her day of flight.
I have to find a bed.
Winter is here, Kuu.
I can't.
I shouldn't cry.
Good morning, Kuu.
It's already been
a month since you left.
Winter has finally come
to this little town.
But thanks to your advice,
I didn't catch a cold.
How are you doing, Kuu?
So what it's like
where you are now?
What do you do there?
I hope people there are as nice
as those in the town of Guri.
In case you're wondering,
everybody here at Old Home
is doing fine...
And I...
Sorry, but I can't congratulate
you like everyone else.
I wanted to be
with you much longer.
I wanted to go shopping
with you, eat with you,
and talk about a lot
of things with you.
There were a lot more things
I wanted you to teach me.
Pea soup, please.
Hey, I see a lot
of you these days.
Is that all you want?
You know...
I haven't seen that kid around.
Know him?
That boy he's just
a little shorter than you.
Kuu.
Ahh, that's it.
I didn't remember his name.
Oh, she's a girl?
Now, I feel bad, I kept calling
her "Boy." Tell her I'm sorry.
Kuu...
isn't here anymore.
What?
Then she's disappeared?
Well.
I guess that's how it always
ends up with all you Haibane?
I understand.
So this is to go, isn't it?
Oh, don't worry; it's on me.
Save that for when
you come here to have
a big full-course dinner.
But I...
Here you go.
Have some more coffee.
For the people of this town,
Kuu's disappearance
is not a big deal.
Life goes on.
Soon they'll probably
forget that she was even here.
Kuu...
Don't you care about that?
Hey.
You live in that run-down
house in the South District,
don't you?
It's called Old Home.
Oh, sorry.
But you guys call
our place "Waste factory",
so it seems only fair to me.
Get it, I'm from
the East District.
You're Hyoko.
Not Hyoko.
It's HYOHKO!
It means "ice lake"!
Hiyoko means baby chicken.
It doesn't matter.
So listen.
Do you remember seeing
that light that came out
of the Western Woods.
You know, about a month ago,
when the storm came?
My friend told me something.
The light only shows up
when a Haibane is gone...
When they are supposed
to go beyond the walls.
But everybody's
still around at our Factory,
so we thought maybe it was
someone from your run-down...
Oops, sorry I meant
to say Old Home.
So tell me...
Was it Reki?
That's good.
I was worried.
Oh, um, don't tell anyone
that I asked especially...
What do you mean
saying "that's good?"
We just lost a close friend.
Hey wait!
Kana!
Overcooked!
It's cooked fine.
No it's not.
Where's Rakka?
I went to get her
but she wasn't there.
She doesn't eat with us
much any more, does she?
Maybe she's on a diet.
Kana.
I was only joking.
I heard that she likes
to go into town more often
to eat these days.
Alone?
Maybe she wants
to be left alone.
She was the most depressed out
of all of us when Kuu left.
Did you know?
Rakka's been cleaning up
Kuu's room all this time.
Oh.
So Rakka did it too?
Kana, you went
to Kuu's room, too?
Just one time.
I've accepted it, I know
Kuu isn't with us anymore.
I wonder if Rakka
just can't accept it.
You know, I thought maybe
we should leave her alone
until she's ready to let it go.
But...
she has to find closure
to this event sometime.
I wish there was something
we could do to help.
I know!
Let's do this.
What am I going to do?
There's more of it.
I didn't have it this morning.
Good morning!
Rise and shine!
Are you awake?
Uh huh.
That's good.
I was thinking...
It's been a while since
everyone ate together, so...
Oh OK, hold on...
I'll join you when I'm dressed.
You go ahead.
Fine, we'll be waiting.
Looks too difficult for me.
Come on, help us.
Help you sew?
You're kidding right?
We all have to!
Even the kids
need to have them.
But Kana can't sew.
Whenever she starts out
making a glove,
it winds up looking like a sock.
I just don't like
doing stupid work like that.
Your Clock Master would
be in tears if he heard
what you just said.
I don't mind machines at all.
They're all built rock solid.
But with cloth...
Ah...
Um...
good morning.
Hey.
Good morning, Rakka.
Oh, what happened
to your dress?
Oh, it got dirty,
so I washed it.
Here, take a look at this.
What is it?
They are wing covers
because it'll get cold soon.
So I thought it would be
nice if we made everyone's
with the same design.
Rakka, are you good at sewing?
Me?
Well, not really.
I haven't had much experience.
Alright!
Welcome to the club!
Kana!
Really...
It's OK.
I'll teach you how.
It's easy.
Watch!
Just spread your wings.
I'll take your
measurements now.
Hmm?
What happened
to your feathers?
Uh, it's nothing.
They look frayed.
Are you taking care of them?
Well, not really.
See, it shows.
That's not good.
You're a girl,
you should know better.
Rakka.
What's this...
Um, well, my sofa
is really hard.
So I might have
hurt them in my sleep.
Oh yeah,
you don't have a bed yet.
I guess moving is a hard work.
Why don't you just put
this one in there?
Because it won't
fit through the door.
Oh, I know.
How about if you take
the bed that's in Kuu's room?
What?
Hey, that's a great idea.
I'll help you if
you want to move it.
But...
it's Kuu's
I think Kuu would be very happy
knowing that you would have it.
Maybe she would,
but I don't know...
But...
Rakka!
What happend, it seems like
I said something wrong to her.
No, it's not
your fault at all, Hikari.
I'd better go
upstairs and talk to her.
I'll come with you!
No, leave it to me.
But...
It's all right.
Rakka.
Rakka, I'm coming in.
What have you done?
Stay away!
It's alright.
They keep spreading.
I'm scared.
It's gonna be alright.
Am I sick?
You're not sick.
So, please don't worry, Rakka.
You have nothing
to be blamed for.
It stings.
It stings because
you cut off your feathers.
Just rinse them with
cold water when you wake up
tomorrow morning.
That should make the
black seem less noticeable.
It's medicine, isn't it?
So I am sick, I was right.
This is just a dye
collected from an Elderly Tree.
The legend says that can
blind the eyes of the evil.
An elderly Tree?
A snow scale tree, I guess.
They grow only near the
walls, and they are named
Elderly Trees because their
trunks are very much twisted.
But you stay away from
the walls no matter what, OK?
It's dangerous.
Reki, why do you have
such special medicine?
How do you know
about these things?
This town exists
for the Haibane.
The walls are there
to protect us.
A good Haibane lives here
happily and goes beyond
the walls when
their time comes.
But once in a while,
a Haibane is born who
cannot be blessed by the town.
A Charcoal Feather
who cannot remember
anything about
their dream in the cocoon.
The day of flight
never comes to him or her.
For such an
unblessed Haibane,
the town becomes a cage
which offers no escape.
This Haibane is
declared to be Sin-Bound.
So am I...
No, absolutely not.
I'm the one who
first found your cocoon,
and I'm the one who rinsed
the blood out of your wings.
Your feathers were
beautiful charcoal gray
when you were born.
You're a good Charcoal Feather.
You're not like I am.
Reki...
You don't have it...
The wings that broke out
from my back had black,
spotted feathers.
I was Sin-Bound
from the very beginning.
I could hardly remember
the dream I had in the cocoon.
Because of the black feathers,
everybody was afraid of me.
I was an outcast.
Even Nemu avoided me
when I was a newborn.
If it weren't for Kuramori
who had protected me,
I would've been
all alone to this day.
Kuramori?
She's beautiful.
Yeah.
She was like a mother
to the kids and a good mentor
to Nemu and myself.
And despite her delicate
health, she helped me by going
to the heart of the forest
to collect the medicine
from the elderly tree.
She's the one who decorated
the guestroom as it is now,
so she, Nemu, and I could
live there together.
Kuramori wasn't afraid
at all to be near me.
She was always
there by my side.
Not out of pity.
She was just there
for me when I needed her.
She was a good person.
But Reki, I think you
are a good Haibane, too.
Whatever you might think,
I'm still a sinner.
Five years ago,
Kuramori left us.
I didn't know anything
about the day of flight,
so I thought that
she had abandoned me.
I was so depressed that
Nemu became concerned for me,
so she did some research at
the library on the old legend.
She told me about
the day of flight.
But I didn't believe it.
I had became too
emotionally blinded.
I hated a lot of things,
and I think I said many
terrible things to Nemu.
I ran away from Old Home and I
kept repeating the same mistakes
at the place I ran away to.
In the end, I was caught by the
community watch and eventually
punished by the
Haibane Renmei as well.
But you, Rakka, haven't done
anything to be punished for.
You've done nothing at all.
So, I know in my heart this
must be some kind of a mistake.
It'll be all gone in no time.
Reki, you don't remember
your dream in the cocoon?
Not completely.
I've been drawing pictures
and pictures of it,
trying to remember.
Since I came here,
I've been haunted by nightmares.
In my dreams,
it's a very cold night,
and there's
a red moon in the sky.
I'm all alone.
Just walking on
a stone-laden path.
Then something happens there.
I can't remember what it was,
but it's something
very horrible.
Every time it happens,
I scream myself awake.
Always the same dream.
I don't understand at all.
Why are there good
Haibane and cursed ones?
Why was I born Sin-Bound?
Until now, I had thought
that this town was a paradise
to live in.
Yet, despite everyone's caring
and compassionate hearts
and willingness to do
their best for each other,
sad things still happen.
Some suffer from
the curses given to them.
What are the Haibane?