Two-thousand-two-hundred
and eleven, twelve, thirteen,
fourteen, fifteen, sixteen,
seventeen, eighteen...
...nineteen, twenty.
Sumika?
You got me.
How did you know it was me?
Your shoes.
Oh?
Stop wearing heels.
You'll fall down.
Damn, you sound
just like my mother.
So, how much longer
can you work?
Just till the end
of this month.
Huh? Four more days.
That's not very long.
That's just for
the official record.
I'll help as long as I can.
But I can't do heavy lifting.
Don't work too hard.
So, are you all prepared?
There's so much left to do.
Handing over my work to others
and submitting paperwork.
Oh, speaking of which,
is the Director here?
Downstairs I think.
I guess I'll take care
of the hard part first.
You're a friend of Nemu's?
Yes, my name is Rakka.
Nemu's letting me visit
here since I'm a newborn.
I'm Sumika, a librarian here.
Nice to meet you.
But I don't know how much
longer I'll be here though.
Say, let me help you.
No it's OK, I'll be fine.
It's too heavy
for just one. Come on.
Thank you.
Newborn means you just
came into this world, right?
But you don't
look like a baby to me.
What did it feel like
when you were being born?
Were you scared?
Not much, I can't remember
very well, but in my dream
I think that I remember that
someone was protecting me.
Really.
Oh!
Thank you very much.
Not at all,
thank you for the advice.
Huh?
On how a parent
should frame her mind.
Did you bring them up
all by yourself?
A nice lady named Sumika
was helping me.
Oh, Sumika is the
senior librarian.
Actually, I meant
she used to be.
All the books here,
we acquired them through trade
with the Toga, so we never
know what kind of books
will arrive or when.
So it's very hard to keep
them organized, and...
Then all of these library books
were written by somebody
in the outside world.
And they're very old,
so you should be careful.
Only 20 minutes left.
I'll go bring these
to the book book binder.
Rakka, can you help me
by doing the labeling?
Uh...uh huh.
Nemu?
Ah.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for helping me again.
Oh, it's supposed to be
my job to begin with.
But what were you reading that
held your interest so much?
Oh it was nothing very special.
I just wondered if I could find
a book that could tell me
what's outside this town.
Ah, I know what you mean.
I looked everywhere
for a book like that
a long time ago.
Really? Did you find it?
No, not at all.
I guess that's to be expected.
I guess I could tell you,
I once thought about
going out beyond the walls.
I wanted to find the
beginning of the world.
The beginning of the world?
The way that this town exists
as it is now, is because
someone first began by building
it. So along the same line,
no matter how wide
the world is, I think there's
a beginning to it somewhere.
I wanted to find it...
Of course I couldn't go.
Because my life here
is so much happier
than chasing that dream.
Well, a dream is only beautiful
because it remains a dream.
But still I wonder
about it once in a while.
Ahh, that's why
life is so difficult.
Oh. No!
Sumika is really
something else.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to be.
This is your first time here.
But Sumika is a senior
librarian. She should...
She should what?
...set a good example for
everyone else. You're right.
So I'll take over here for now.
It's time for Storybook Lady.
And so, the evil wizard was
transformed into an ugly frog.
In order to rescue all
the little children,
the young man climbed up
the stairs in the high tower.
He planted the seed that
the old lady had given him,
and vines grew out of it
instantly, allowing the
young man and all the
children to come home safely.
And peace was once again
restored to the village.
The end.
Yay!
Stop it, it's embarrassing.
Now, did you say "thank you"
to the Storybook Lady?
Thank you!
This place sure has changed a
lot. Whenever I used to visit,
it had an air of
"scholars-only."
I know, we've put a lot of
effort into changing this place.
Oh I forgot, I have to go
pick up some things.
Hikari, do you think
you can take the kids home?
Sure, that's fine,
Kuu can help.
Eh?
Kuu, do you want to be
a substitute teacher?
A teacher? All right!
Thanks.
See ya.
Ah, I'm all worn out. How can
Reki deal with the children
so easily day in and day out?
But you seemed like you were
having a good time with them.
It's only once in a while.
I couldn't possibly
do it every day.
Sorry. The meeting for
tomorrow's assignments
dragged a bit.
It's okay. I'm sorry
I wasn't much help today.
Oh, you did great.
But, only four more days.
Huh?
I meant Sumika.
I was making her a gift,
but there's no time
to finish it.
What is it?
Knitting something?
It's a secret.
I can help if you
tell me what it is.
It's somewhat embarrassing.
Well uhm, here's a hint,
the beginning of the world.
Huh?
There was a book with that title
in the library a long time ago.
But it's discarded now.
An old and crumbling book
only the first few pages
were legible. Sumika and
I racked our brains to come up
with the rest of the story.
And then?
That's the only hint.
What?
Reki.
Reki!
Where's she...?
Um.
She's going in
the opposite direction.
Oh, she just needed
some gas for her scooter.
See. I told you.
It's just Reki.
What are you doing here?!
Hyohko!
Whoo hoo!
This is gonna be classic!
What was that for!?
Quit smoking you stupid girl!
And stop riding that bike!
You're the one who's stupid!
I have permission from town;
it's perfectly legal
for me to ride it!
Jerk.
Too bad, Hyoko You lose.
Come on, let's leave now
before we get caught.
Uhm...okay.
There's a place called Abandoned
Factory in the East District.
It's also a nest for the
Haibane, and lucky for them,
it's coed.
Really?
That boy with the cap
is one of the Haibane
from Abandoned Factory?
Yes, and one thing led
to another with those two.
What kind of things?
Back then in Old Home there were
only Reki, the children, and me.
And Reki was, well, troubled
and bit more rebellious.
Things led to a big fight
between us, and Reki ran away.
Later on I'd heard that
she had actually run away
with that boy we saw.
Oh, wow! That's sounds so cool.
Don't you follow
in her footsteps.
Because of what they did,
neither one is allowed to go
into each other's district.
I don't think having boys
around would be too bad,
but I don't like the ones
in Abandoned Factory.
They're so rowdy.
In my memories there exists
another version of myself.
Nemu and others said it isn't
so, but I can't quite shake off
the feeling from my mind that
maybe my parents and the town
I used to live in still exist
somewhere. I wonder if this
sense of confusion will
disappear when my wings have
completely become
a part of my body.
Here, everyone, even someone
as little as Kuu, has a job
and has become a self
sufficient part of this world.
Yet, the truth is that everybody
is mutually supporting
each other in ways that
are not apparent to the eyes.
It's a perfectly natural, but
I didn't realized it until now.
I wonder if I deserve...
to be as happy as I am.
Good morning.
Is it okay if I help?
Well sure I'd love your help,
but I won't be
leaving till late.
Well, I'll do some
research until then.
What are you researching?
The beginning of the world.
So what's she
studying so intently?
It's a secret.
Just leave her alone for now.
Oh.
When I think about it,
you were acting just like her
when you first
started working here.
Was I?
In the beginning of the world,
there was nothing but a dark
mist called the Nothingness.
And then God appeared. By merely
being there, He brought, umm...
let me see, light into
the Nothingness.
When God... something...
glowing over His head...
It... Er... Er...
it became the sun.
It's hopeless, this book
is too damaged to read.
Oh, well! We'll
just have to come up
with the rest by ourselves.
Oh, you should wake me
instead of watching me.
But you looked so happy
sleeping like that...
How did your research go?
Fine. The beginning of
the world is very interesting.
I found some different
references to it in many books,
but they all have
some common similarities.
And, what's the answer?
Nemu, why should I tell?
If you just gave me a hint.
Alright, then.
Don't laugh when you see it.
Wow, this is great!
How did you do this?
I asked the man who
repairs our books to do it.
It was a lot of work.
Can I read it?
You won't laugh?
I won't.
Ahh.
Oh, is this all?
Well, I can't decide on how to
write the ending. Got any ideas?
You won't laugh, right?
I promise.
You're laughing! You promised!
You gotta be joking.
I'm not joking.
I was thinking something
like that a minute ago,
when I was looking
at your sleeping face.
That's not funny! Be serious!
This is a story about
a great and powerful being.
But it's a book written by you,
so I think it should remind
the reader of the author,
don't you?
But I don't have such bad
manners. How can you even think
like that? I should inspire
ideas with a lot more dignity.
Well, I've got to work
overtime to finish this.
I'm so glad you picked me up.
Overtime is exhausting.
Where's Nemu?
She's got double overtime.
Huh?
She had to stay late to
talk to the book repairman.
I learned a lot from working
with her. Even though
she appears sleepy,
Nemu is a hard worker.
Of course she is. Nobody
gets mad at her for her naps
because she always
gets the job done.
I understand.
But it's still hard to believe.
Here you go.
Thanks a lot.
Yeah, see you later.
Hmm, oh yeah.
Goodbye
Alright. You take it easy, boy.
Here you go.
Bye-bye.
Kuu!
Oh, Rakka.
What are you doing?
Hmm?
Just saying goodbye.
Saying goodbye?
I said no!
Come on, it's OK.
No way!
Morning.
Hey, where's Nemu?
She's still in bed.
What now?
I thought that she was trying
to get up early for a change.
But she was at the library
very late last night.
What? For work?
Uhh, it's something
private but it's also
a very important thing,
I guess.
Huh?
Whatever it is...
she'll probably be sleeping up
until the very last minute.
Rakka.
Look. It's supposed
to be a triangle.
Oh.
Oh, no!
Rakka! Forget about breakfast!
Oh.
Right on time.
I really hope that
Sumika will like it.
Mmm... If she
thinks it's stupid,
it's gonna
be all your fault.
What, why?
Well, because
I collaborated with you.
Your name is now
on the cover, too.
Huh?!
It's too late for that.
No! It's not that.
But is it OK?
Well, you're jointly
responsible. Better be prepared.
Nemu, I'm very happy.
I hope Sumika will be, too.
How can she not be?
When God...something...
glowing over His head...
When God took into his hand
the halo glowing over His head
and held it high, it became
the sun. God waved His staff,
and the Nothingness was ripped
into two, one part forming
the sky and the other
the land. However,
his hand was not straight,
thus creating mountains
and valleys. God said "It was a
mistake, but it's just as well."
When God drew pictures on
the land, grass and trees grew,
and birds and animals came
to life. God then envisioned
creatures that looked
almost like Himself.
But these creatures were
too similar to himself
and that gave him concern.
So he colored their
wings charcoal-gray,
and made holes on their halos
and named them Haibane.
Then he tucked them away
in the back of his mind.
After that, God started over
and created human beings
that did not have wings
or halos. And this time,
he was satisfied with his
creation. Completely content,
God...
God, despite his omnipotence,
fell asleep. The Haibane,
who were destined to be
erased, were able to escape
from his mind. When God awoke,
the Haibane were already
floating in the sky. However,
ever tolerant of mistakes,
even his own, God decided
to let the Charcoal Feathers
and their tiny world be.
So, that is why
the town of Guri is still
floating somewhere today.
Somewhere that is neither
on the land nor the sea.