You look a little pale.
I didn't sleep enough,
but I'm all right.
Oh, here. You left this
on the table.
You can have it.
I don't need it any more.
Good morning.
What on earth are you wearing?
Hey, go get changed
and wash your hands.
Uh oh, she's becoming
a full-blooded housekeeper.
No, you're becoming a slob.
Reki, the Bell Nut Market
is being held today.
You do remember that,
don't you?
Bell nuts?
We need them for the
Passing of the Year Festival.
Are all of these from
the same kind of tree?
Yeah. You see,
the colors are changed by
mixing iron and
verdigris into the soil.
Good nuts are ones
with thick shells that
make a solid sound
when you shake them.
This one's a "thank-you" nut.
You give it to the people
you want to thank.
Oh.
Having fun?
The sound is very soothing.
Yeah.
So, these symbolize
appreciation?
Different colors mean different
things. Appreciation, apologies.
It's custom to mark the end
of the year by giving these
to the people close to you.
Oh.
Why can't you at least pretend
to be part of the group?
Shut up, and stop following me.
Hey.
Stop being so... Reki!
What do you want?
It's nothing.
If you have
something to say to me,
then why don't
you just say it.
I'm sorry for causing you
all so much trouble
and dragging you both
into my personal problems.
I was just really alone.
Reki?
The festival's not
till next week.
I don't have much time.
And, I might not see you again.
Huh?
The first saw her five
years ago. It was raining.
Her wings were all black,
she was crying as she walked,
all soaking wet.
She looked just like
an abandoned cat.
Right there, I knew
that I had to help her.
Oh, you've got to be kidding.
Shut up! Anyway,
that's the story.
That was the day when
Reki became one of us.
And then, she left,
taking you with her.
Back then, she was always
crying, missing her friend...
...who'd gone beyond the walls.
So, I tried to do
something for her.
And this idiot took Reki and
tried to climb over the wall,
by driving a wedge into it.
Hyoko... Hyoko...
Hyoko!
We didn't think
he would survive.
Reki didn't even
have single scratch,
and I will never
forgive her for that.
It wasn't her fault.
I did it on my own.
Reki is still selfish.
You were one of
her best friends.
Why don't you shut up!
I have to...
I want to help Reki.
So that she can receive
the blessing properly.
You' are just getting her way.
Reki is not a kind of person
who asks for other's help.
You're wrong! You just
don't see what's going on,
cause Reki smiles
even when she's suffering.
I'll help.
After all, I have to
pay her back for the gift.
Idiot! You aren't allowed
to enter the South District.
Remember?
Don't you worry about me.
I got a brain.
What brain?
Good morning.
Oh, good morning.
Can you wait a bit?
It'll be ready in a minute.
Okay.
I'm starving!
Hey... Kanna why don't
you help for a change?
Yeah, I know, alright.
Rakka, have you seen Reki?
I don't know what I should do.
You just do everything
that you're capable of.
After that...
just have faith in Reki.
Very soon, I will be forgotten
by everybody... and vanish.
Where did I go wrong?
What is it that I am supposed
to do in order to help Reki?
Kuu!
Where did you learn that?
I permit you to speak.
I felt Kuu's presence near the
sign that produces light leaves.
It's Kuu's sign, isn't it?
But its letters do not
mean the word "air",
the name given
by the Haibane.
It's a different name
with the same sound.
Kuu has a different name?
It is proof that the Haibane
attained a true identity.
When the time comes, the name on
the sign hanging from the wall
is changed to the true name.
Yes, now may be
a good opportunity.
We created this, using the
tag on the wall as a model.
Rakka.
Can you tell me
where that name came from?
It's because I isolated myself
inside the shell like a nut.
And because you sprouted here
and connected with others.
Therefore, it will be
your true name.
But! What about Reki?
She does not know
her true name.
She is not willing
to listen to my words.
Why not?
Five years ago,
she brought to us a Haibane boy
who had fallen ill.
I know. He tried to climb the
wall by driving a wedge into it.
A serious crime. I had to
call for the community watch.
Reki was deemed guilty,
and she shut herself inside
the Circle of the Sin.
She has been blaming
herself all this time.
Why is it only Reki
who can't be forgiven?
Why do you think
you were forgiven?
It's not because
I forgave myself.
That is correct. Nobody is
able to forgive themselves.
However, you had the bird.
Someone believed
in you and stood by you.
By recognizing one's own sin.
You can't help going around
in circles if you are alone.
But, if you have someone
it's by your side...
Give this to Reki
after the festival.
Now Go.
Reki's name. Her true name.
Stir lightly, being careful
not to flatten the meringue.
Like this?
That's right. Then pour it
into a dish, and bake it
in the oven preheated
to about 390 degrees
for 10 minutes or so.
Okay.
Hello. Good morning.
Good morning.
Yeah, this is good.
You've been a tremendous
help with this Reki.
I can't start getting ready
for my special dinner until
you relinquish
control of the kitchen.
Yes, I know.
The Passing of
the Year Festival.
Rakka, I don't think
I'm going into town today.
Reki?
Sorry for being so selfish.
But today of all days,
I would like to stay here.
So I can etch the memories
of my life here into my mind.
When I looked out from here
for the first time...
I was a little afraid,
thinking that I came to a world
I didn't know. But now, this
is where I feel most secure.
Because you are always here.
Thank you. And even
if you forget about me,
I hope that you will
always remember this view.
I won't forget.
There's no way I can forget.
Because, the time I spent with
you is everything I remember.
It's so busy here.
It'll all be quiet once
the first bell starts ringing.
You're supposed to observe the
Passing of the Year in silence.
You are?
That's why we have these to
express feelings without words.
And at the end
of festival... oops.
And at the end?
You'll see. It can't
be explained in words.
It this coming through...
Honestly. You really are
a meddler, aren't you?
Rakka!
Dai
It's a cake!
I know I'm getting
in the way, but...
That's alright.
Because of you,
we feel like it's finally time
to have a talk with Reki.
What? But...
We have our own way of doing
things. We're totally different
from the snobs at your house.
Because you've got
no class, right, Midori?
Anyway, we have a little
entertainment ready for
the Passing of the Year.
Reki's in town, isn't she?
Na-nah. She said she wanted
to stay in Old Home today.
What?! Why? It's the festival!
It's the bell!
Oh, no! We're
running out of time!
Wait a minute!
What's the matter?
We're just doing
what you asked us to do.
You're too dainty
to run, aren't you?
You need a break?
Not at all. I'm the one
who started all of this!
Where's Reki's room?
West wing, third floor.
We won't make it
in time. Reki! Reki!
I came to see you!
Open the window!
Reki!
Well done.
Rakka? Midori!
What's wrong...?
We'll explain later!
Look towards the
Abandoned Factory!
This is the answer
from Hyohko and I.
That's what Hyohko
wants to tell you.
Yellow...
What does yellow mean?
It means "I've been acting
like an idiot." That's true.
"Good-bye and
thank you, Reki", huh.
Hey, Rakka!
You're back early.
Did you see the fireworks?
Can you wait for a second?
What's going on?
Just stay here.
The bell stopped.
So ends the year.
That's right.
So what happens now?
The walls send the thoughts
they've been receiving
from everyone over
the past year into the sky.
The thoughts?
You just listen for it.