I'm so glad
that you've recovered.
My name is Kuramori.
Come on Nemu, say hello.
Nemu!
We can go to town later.
Sure.
Do you remember
your cocoon dream?
I will permit you to speak.
Now tell me, what did you see
while dreaming in the cocoon?
All I remember,
was I was walking,
and the path I was
walking was rocky.
It was pitch-black.
Is that all?
Is there a cure?
I will show you how
to create a medicine.
From now on,
you are to be called Reki.
It means small stones.
Reki.
I'm by your side.
I'll always,
always be by your side.
She said she'd go get
medicine for my feathers.
Kuramori's health is delicate.
It's too much for her to go
into the woods by herself.
If she dies then it's
going to be all your fault.
Um, I went to go
buy some food.
I thought maybe you
might be getting hungry.
Let's cook together.
Sorry about before.
Oh, thank goodness.
There.
Everything is clean now.
I don't know, I think
it might be too big for me.
Well then, why don't
we make this a guest room?
You can live here and take
care of the newborn Haibane.
That can be your new job.
Really?
That sounds great.
And you can take care of the
kids when you have free time.
I swear I'll do my best!
Now you're a
full-fledged Haibane.
Kuramori...
Please don't go.
You said you'd be by my side.
You promised me.
Damn it!
How is she?
I'm glad you're here.
I was debating if I should
go wake you up or not.
Medicine working?
I gave her some,
but her fever won't come down.
I was going to take her over
the doctor in the morning.
Where are you going?
I'll be right back!
Go ahead.
How could you leave
her alone like that?
You knew that she touched the
wall she will develop a fever?!
Because you're in Old Home.
I suspected that, should
something ever happen to her,
you would come here,
as you had for Hyohko.
We're not talking about Hyoko!
You have to cure Rakka!
It's not like she was climbing
the walls, why do this to her...
The walls are absolute.
There is nothing within
my power to do for her.
The walls are supposed to
protect good Haibane,
aren't they?
And Rakka isn't Sin-Bound
any more, is she?
Even a good Haibane must
be punished if she
touches the wall.
Rakka did overcome
her ordeal, however...
So it's true,
she really did it.
She had a bird help her.
And there was no question that
eventually she will find a way
to break out of
the Circle of the Sin.
Then you mean, you gave
Rakka and I the same riddle?
So then...
did she find an answer?
I know not.
However, the bird
gave her forgiveness,
and therefore she is
no longer Sin-Bound.
Oh.
Only little time remains for
you to stay here as a Haibane.
You need to prepare
yourself mentally.
The Day of Flight never
comes to the Sin-Bound, right?
I'm fine staying here.
Besides, I need to stay
and watch the kids.
That is not for you to decide.
You know what becomes of
a Haibane whose time expires
before she becomes
ready to take the Flight.
You have no choice but to
prevail against your own ordeal.
As you well know,
The Day of Flight comes
equally to all good Haibane.
What do you mean "equally"?
Kuu was the youngest of us all.
And yet, she was not
afraid of the walls.
She believed that...
if she went beyond the walls,
the rest of you
would soon follow.
It was Kuu's dream to become
a role model to all of you.
How do you know that?
I know nothing.
I am merely giving voice
to the thoughts
that you have deep in your mind.
How about Nemu?
She's always
being a good Haibane.
Nemu deserves to take the Day
of Flight with your blessings.
Nemu wishes to see you
take the Flight first.
She never voices it,
but she is more concerned
for you than for herself.
She is?
Then you're saying
I'm a burden on her?
No.
That's not true.
Nemu's issues are not
your responsibility.
That is simply
how it is for her.
Now go.
Rakka is awaiting you.
Help yourself and pick
the medicinal herbs you need.
I trust you know which ones.
You have always
been there for Rakka.
You always do the right thing.
And now, you must not be envious
of Rakka for moving forward.
Be envious?
Me envious?
You must be out of your mind!
The water's boiling.
Eww.
What's that smell?
Is it really going to work?
Be careful.
It's very hot.
It's bitter.
It's medicine.
You just have to take it.
One more mouthful.
Thanks Reki.
I hope you get well soon.
Reki!
On the bulletin board!
From the Renmei!
Haibane Rakka, you are
ordered to appear at the Temple
of the Haibane Renmei
before the end of the day.
Once there, you are to be
punished for committing a crime
of touching the wall.
What'll we do?
We'll just ignore it!
I'll take full responsibility!
They don't have
the right to punish Rakka!
Reki.
Rakka, you shouldn't
be out of bed!
I promised them that
I'm going to return the cane.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
The fever's gone,
and my wings feel lot
better than they used to.
Your medicine
made me feel better.
Thank you so much.
And I'm sorry for making
everyone worry about me.
It's okay.
Take care.
Reki.
Descend.
Put this on.
This way.
You may use your voice
here if you wish.
Does this mean
I'm gonna be put in prison?
Prison?
Because I...
Where are we?
Inside the wall.
The wall?
Look over here.
These are called light leaves.
These are what
your halos are made of.
You are to circle this
corridor and gather the leaves.
You must also purify
the rusted tags.
That will be
your job in this town.
It is an important task.
Can you do it?
You mean, by myself?
Are you frightened?
I'll do it.
I will come
to collect you later.
And remember, you must
never take off your robe.
Do not be frightened of
anything you may see or hear.
Regardless of what it is,
it cannot touch one
who is wearing the robe.
Are you saying
something lives here?
These are...
Like I said.
Why do I have to do
something like this?
There's no choice!
I'm not allowed
to enter the South District.
Then why are you
coming with me?
I just bet you're hoping that
we're gonna run into Reki,
aren't you?
Right.
Jeez, and I'm the one
who made all these for you!
Why can't you do
anything by yourself!
What?
When did I...?
There's a girl in your place
with funny hair that sticks up,
right?
You mean Rakka?
Hyohko wants to give her this.
Hmm, What is it?
No, don't open it!
Just promise us that
you'll give it to her, OK?
Midori?
Here, you'll catch a cold.
You should really
stop smoking, Reki.
You look stupid.
We're going home!
Don't order me around!
You jerk!
What are you doing?
Oh- nothing, nothing at all.
Sorry.
I was going to come get you,
but an idiot held me up.
Oh, and the idiot asked me
to pass this bag on to you.
Anyway, what was
your punishment?
It wasn't too
horrible was it??
Well it was...
cleaning the Temple.
They told me
that's my job now.
Cleaning?
This world is
filled with idiots.
Wow!
One, two, three...
There's enough here
for the housemother
and all the kids as well.
How polite.
I'll have to think
better of them now.
What is that?
Oh, check it out!
What a crappy handwriting.
We should really give them
something in return.
Shouldn't have to.
The note says it's an apology.
But we still should.
What do you think Reki?
I really have no idea
what we should do.
Anyway, Dai would be going back
to Abandoned Factory very soon.
Shouldn't we pay a visit
to them prior to that?
What do you mean?
They can't take care
of the young feathers
at the Abandoned Factory,
so we've been fostering them.
They get to go back there
a few times a year.
Oh, I see.
If it's the
Abandoned Factory, then I...
I know.
Someone else
will host the visit.
Oh, I want to go.
But I have to warn you,
the boys in the factory
can be pretty rowdy.
No kidding.
I would like to go.
Well then,
I'll make some treats.
Is that okay?
It's up to you.
Good night.
'Night.
Nemu.
Yeah?
I want you to know something.
Stop worrying about me.
I'm perfectly fine on my own.
Your what?
What are you saying?
I'm saying I don't want
to be a burden to you anymore.
Reki, what's wrong?
Reki?