Mmm... There.
Feeling this pain must mean they
really are a part of my body,
I guess.
Reki, play with us!
How many times that I told you
kids not to come into this room
with muddy shoes on!
Reki, why aren't you
coming to class with us?!
I told you before
I won't be there because
I have to take care
of the new girl.
Oh, you have a scrape on
your arm. Did you fight?
Uh-uh, I just fell down!
I'm gonna catch you.
I'm gonna get you.
Better watch out!
Are you dressed?
Does it fit?
Ah, yes. I think it's ok.
Glad to hear that. Otherwise,
you wouldn't be able to get you
to go outside. Let's go
out onto the balcony.
It's such a nice day.
Hey wait up!
Hey, Rakka, why don't you sit
out here and let your wings
dry in the sun for a while.
They're still little damp.
I don't know this town at all.
Even though I can't remember
where I used to live before,
I can somehow tell in my heart
that I've never
been to this town.
Hi there. Are you the new
person from that big cocoon?
Hey, can you do this? Watch?
Well, I...
Huh, what's wrong?
OK.
One, two,
Hana! Don't teach her
that silly stuff!
You gonna hurt your wings
if you use them too much.
You should be careful.
You still have scabs.
You see.
Oh, I'm sorry.
They do that on their own
when I try to move my arms.
Ah, I see. Don't worry.
You'll soon get used to it.
Uh.. OK.
Hey, she's got a halo holder.
It's a halo holder!
Hah? Holder?
Can I take a look at your back?
Uh, yeah sure.
Wow, that must've hurt.
So, did you cry?
I didn't cry.
That's a lie.
How do you know it's a lie!
Because it is!
Hey guys, cut it out!
Hey! I'll practice with you.
Hold your hands out
in front of you.
Like this?
Follow me, in-out,
in-out, in-out,
in-out, in-out, in-out.
Reki! Good morning!
We picked up some breakfast!
Oh, thank you.
You look well,
Rakka. I'm so glad.
Yeah, me too. How's the fever?
Well, it was all gone when
I woke up this morning.
Honestly, what makes
everybody think my room
is their hang-out?
Well, it's comfortable
here for some reason.
You always come in without
asking, as if it was
your own room, and that's why
the kids are doing the same.
The truth is Reki just moved
herself into the guestroom.
Excuse me! It was my room
from the very beginning!
Honestly, I shouldn't have
picked up such a big table.
Which room are you
going to move into?
The end room on the floor above.
But there's a vacant room
right next door.
I've been using the room
upstairs as my studio,
and I have a feeling I won't be
sleeping quietly on this floor.
But you're the noisiest person
whenever you get out of bed.
I don't believe
I'm hearing that from
someone who never
even wants to wake up.
Yeah, Nemu's snoozes
are really hard-core.
She was even sleeping
during in her cocoon dream.
Right, Nemu?
Oh come on, can't we
just drop the subject.
Oh, that's right.
You're all named according
to the first dream
that you had in a cocoon.
Yep. We don't know who started
it, but that's the custom.
Too bad that young feathers
don't have any respect
for it at all, though.
I like flowers,
so I want to be a florist.
That's why I'm Hana.
I wanna be a carpenter!
A dream for the future.
Shortcake!
Huh?
That's just your
favorite food, Shorta.
No it's not. I really
did dream about it.
You two, I told you
to stop fighting.
Mmm...
What about Reki?
What it's mean?
Huh? I, uh...
Reki means little stones!
What?
Well uh, it's Reki as in
gareki, meaning pebbles.
I remember a moonlit night,
and I was walking all alone down
a pebble-laden path. Walking.
Come to think of it, you like
to walk, don't you, Reki?
Yeah, and switching rooms, too.
Give me a break.
You made me move.
Hey, everyboby!
Let's go for a walk?
How about it, Rakka? Let's all
go to town, think you can walk?
It's OK, isn't it?
Only if Rakka wants to.
Aren't you
coming with us, Reki?
No, I have to finish
moving the rest of my stuff.
And bring these 3 back
to the other Young Feathers.
Well, see you later.
Rakka.
Hmm?
You should try to take it easy,
you're still recuperating.
Uh, yeah.
Well now.
All right!
Let's go!
They say it was some sort of
dormitory building for a school.
But everyone started
leaving it over time.
It was completely
deserted at some point.
And that's when it became
a nest for the Haibane.
We call it the Old Home.
It's a nice place.
Although it's kinda scary
at night without a lamp,
since half of that
has no electricity.
And now, the only residents
left in old home are us,
the kids we call Young Feathers
and the old lady who works
as a housemother. Say, you
can pick any room you like.
Sure.
You gonna be hanging around
with us a lot anyway, right.
Ah.
Watch out!
Not everyone has
wings like we do.
Of course not.
To be precise, the humans
are letting us Haibane
live in their town.
That's right. And it's supposed
to be the Haibane's obligation
to only use things that
humans no longer need.
Really?
I know. Hey everybody,
Rakka needs some clothes.
Let's go shopping.
That sounds pretty good,
but you mean that
thrift shop, don't you?
Thrift shop?
It's a rule that the Haibane
can only wear used clothes.
But that's the reason why we've
all become very good at sewing.
So we can make wing slits.
Wing covers, too,
so when it gets cold.
Wing covers? Mmm? Mm...
Welcome.
Eh? Oh, just some
of you Haibane.
Hey, looks like you've
got a new face there.
Oh, she's a newborn.
Yeah? Ahh. That's why.
Uh? Ah...
All right, then why don't
you pick out something you like
from that clothing
section over there.
Is it OK?
Hey, what about us?
For you guys... these.
Ugh.
Don't "ugh" me. This is
a box full of absolute steals,
just unsorted and unwashed.
You should at least wash them!
Yuck!
This is disgusting.
Hey, you can only have
one piece each, all right.
Ya, we get it.
What a cheapskate.
Now, you gonna tell me being
a Haibane isn't easy, right?
Although you seem not
to have a care in the world.
'Course it isn't easy.
Rakka, have you decided yet?
Ah, uh, well.
Yes, this one.
What's that?
This? It's the Haibane-Notebook
of the Haibane-Renmei.
We use it in place of money.
Oh that's right, you don't
have a notebook yet.
Well, in that case,
you can sign here.
Oh, and leave a feather.
Sorry, did I hurt you?
I'm OK. Thank you.
Oh all right.
Our extra special service!
Rakka!
Yeah!
We got some tea!
Coming!
Oh, one thing, what's that
Haibane-Renmei you spoke of?
It means Charcoal
Feather Federation.
The group which
guarantees our living.
Soon, you should be
receiving a notebook from them
just like ours.
The Haibane are not allowed
to receive any money
from their employment.
So you jot down in the Notebook
what you earned from your
work, and you use it when
you buy things. I work at the
Clock Tower just over there.
You should come
and see it sometime.
I work at a bakery and
Nemu works in the Library.
You need to find work once
you get used to the town, too.
Oh.
Hey, look over there.
They're holding market
at the Great Gate Square.
The Toga must be here.
Toga?
See, those people there bringing
in the carts are the Toga.
Look at those walls.
This town is surrounded
by walls on all sides.
Both the Haibane and townspeople
are forbidden to leave it.
That's the way it's been
since I've been here.
The only exceptions are the
Toga. They come from the outside
to trade with the town. And
those standing next to them
are the gate keepers
and the Communicator
from the Haibane-Renmei.
Communicator?
The residents of the town
aren't allowed to speak with
or touch the Toga. Likewise, the
Toga would never come near us,
and they are forbidden to use
their voices while in town.
The only person who can
"speak" with the Toga
during that visits is the
Haibane Renmei Communicator.
They communicate with
each other by making shapes
with their hands just like this.
But I'm just making it up.
It's a language that
only they can understand.
In short, the Haibane-Renmei
serves as an intermediary
for the trade between
the Toga and the town.
Part of the profit pays for
things such as the utilities
for Old Home and helps
support for the Young Feathers.
Oh, I didn't know about that.
Thank you very mu--
Idiot!
Let's go. We'll get
into trouble if we stay
close to the wall too long.
Ah, a crow.
You dirty little scavenger!
Look at those pitch-black
wings flying away!
You don't know if that's the one
who's been scavenging our trash.
I hate crows!
Rakka!
I can see the wall over there.
Yes, you can. This town
is surrounded by walls.
So what's beyond the walls?
Nobody knows. I've read every
last one of the library books,
and there's nothing about it.
Maybe you thought
you were reading,
but really just snoozing.
You want to read them
yourself instead?
Ah, I'm suddenly
attacked by drowsiness.
Beyond thjose walls...
I wonder if the town
I used to live in
is somewhere over there.
Hmm?
Look! Rakka's got a nametag!
The Haibane-Renmei
were already here.
Look at this?
To the newborn Rakka, you are
hereby accepted as a Haibane.
You are expected to be at
the Temple tomorrow morning.
The Haibane-Renmei.
Oh, I have to go there tomorrow
to return the halo mold.
Why don't we go together?
Okay. But... how did they
even know what my name was?
I'll tell you why.
Because the Haibane-Renmei
is the organization that uses
frightening magic!
Knock it off, Kana!
Re... Really?
You wrote your name down
when we went clothes shopping.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
All right now,
Rakka's so quiet I was
just trying to cheer her up.
Oh come on.
You're exactly like Reki used
to be, acting just like her.
Oh, rats.
Kana's just trying to make you
feel welcomed in her own way.
Oh, look, the lights
are off in the guestroom.
I wonder if Reki's
finished moving out.
So should we all say
goodnight right here?
Hikari and I live over
there in the East Tower.
Bye.
Well, see you tomorrow.
Okay, see you.
Bye.
Rakka, I'll come
to get you tomorrow.
Until tomorrow.
I wonder if Reki's in her room.
Oh, Rakka, so,
how was going to town?
I had a lot of fun being there.
I also got this today.
Really.
Did you eat?
We all ate at a café
on the way back.
Oh, I see.
Oh, I'm sorry,
were you waiting for me?
Hmm? Oh, don't worry about it.
I don't feel much like eating
after inhaling all that dust
from cleaning the rooms.
I'll make you some tea.
Oh, thank you.
Rakka?!
Well, uh...
It's OK. Just rest.
Sorry, I should've known.
It's strange. Until
a minute ago, I was just...
Too much emotional strain.
Are you alright, can you walk?
Yes.
Ouch!
Try lying on
your side for a while.
It takes some getting used to.
Huh?
Is it staying?
Ah-ha
You haven't slept? Reki,
I'm fine so please go to bed.
I will when you're sleep.
I already am.
Good night, Rakka.
Good night, Reki.