As the winter progressed,
many things changed in the world
that I was now living in.
Kuu's day of flight,
the Sin-Bound illness
I suffered from,
the death of the bird...
I recovered my cocoon dream and
found a job with Haibane Renmei.
But Reki is still under
the Sin-Bound curse and
is struggling to find the
dream that she cannot recall.
Sleep over?
He's so Lucky!
I wanna go, too!
Next year, Shorta.
Why does only Dai get to go?
No fair!
Dai!
You take care.
Of course!
I like the smell of the river.
For some reason,
it seems so familiar.
Yeah?
You are too hot?
Reki made me wear this.
She said I had
to wear I catch a cold.
So, are you going to miss her
much while you're away?
Why should I miss her?
I'm only gonna be gone
for half a month.
But you know...
I wonder if
something's wrong with her.
She's a lot quieter lately,
and spaced out.
Maybe that's because
she already misses you.
She makes me feel kind of
weird acting like that.
It's not gonna going
away forever, you know.
Yeah, that's very true.
Over here!
Maybe nobody's home.
Did I scare you?
Wha...
what was that for?
Those are valuable.
You shouldn't be wasting them,
or we'll run out
before the festival.
I was just saying hello
to the visitors down there.
It's that funny-hair chick.
Wow, thanks a lot.
Hey, you didn't
have to do that.
Did you make these by yourself?
Na-nah, Hikari did.
You know her?
Oh, I know her.
The girl who works
at the bakery, right?
Hey, what's your name?
I'm Rakka.
Try it.
Hey now, don't let
the kid get hurt!
Don't worry!
Man, he's such a child.
Well at least that makes him
a good playmate for the kid.
Are you still angry?
At Hyohko, I mean.
No, not at all.
Well that's good.
Anyway, I just wanted to say
thank you for taking in Dai.
Actually, We should be
thanking you for taking care
of our kids all this time.
We should be
visiting the Old Home
to thank you guys
in person, you know.
But we've all grown so far apart
from each other because of
that trouble that happened
between some of us.
I guess there's just never
been a chance to break the ice.
What trouble?
Oh, right.
I forgot you're still new here.
Well, let's just say
there's a lot of history.
Right, Midori?
I wouldn't know!
Aw, she can be so pigheaded.
Hey, wait up!
I forgot.
Could you give this
back to Reki?
She let me borrow it.
O-Okay.
She is always such a
little do-gooder, isn't she?
So, tell me, what do
you know about us?
All I saw, I saw you guys and
Reki arguing over here before.
What else?
And also I heard that Reki
and Hyohko of Abandoned Factory,
tried to...
Run away together, right?
Give me a break.
Isn't it true?
Reki and Hyohko
were kind of together,
but Hyohko was a victim
of Reki's selfishness.
You know he almost died
because of her.
Reki...
Reki wouldn't do
such horrible things.
You know nothing about
what Reki's capable of doing.
Nothing.
Reki would never hurt anyone.
Reki has always been kind.
She is always
considerate of the others,
even when she's
suffering inside.
Although I didn't realize it
at the time, but when Kuu left
on her day of flight, when
I first became Sin-Bound,
it was Reki who
was suffering more.
And yet I was
always leaning on her.
Oh no the raft!
W-Wait!
What is that?
Wow...
These letters...
Are you finished?
Reki has come to get you.
She seems concerned.
Reki has been acting
a little nervous lately.
The fact that her Day
of Flight has not arrived
is weighing heavily on her mind.
And yet, she silently hopes
that it will never come.
I know...
It hurts me a lot to see
her suffering like this.
But, I still don't
want her to go away.
She is still lost in the dark.
Rakka, you had the bird come
to you, enabling you to fill in
the missing pieces
of your memories.
However, Reki has no one.
She must face the
darkness on her own.
It is a trying ordeal.
Reki keeps painting the scenes
from her dream in the cocoon.
I saw her paintings once but
I couldn't tell what they were.
I don't think
Reki knows, either.
There is not much time
left for Reki.
I know not how or when,
but by the end of this winter,
her journey will have
come to a conclusion.
If Reki is still
in darkness by that point,
she will be bound
to this place forever.
Is it possible for
a Haibane to remain here?
It is quite rare,
but some do remain.
However, they are
no longer called Haibane.
They lose their wings and
halos, and must live far away
from both humans and
Haibane, and with time,
they will grow old and die.
It is a quiet and peaceful,
but lonely life.
I, or rather, the Haibane
Renmei wishes for all Haibane
to take flight without problem.
But as it is, Reki refuses me.
Everything I say
makes Reki close her mind.
I want to help her.
She was suffering
inside all this time,
but she hid
her pain and helped me.
So this time no matter
what I have to help her.
In order to save Reki,
it will mean parting with her.
If she leaves here,
I think it's very likely that
you will never see her again.
Are you prepared
to pay that price?
Thanks for meeting me.
I had to pick up
some paints anyway.
With snow like this, I won't
be able to ride this thing
for the rest of the winter.
So how's your work?
Is it going well?
I't's okay.
Are you painting again?
No, I'm just...
I'm just smearing a few
paints around in studio.
Oh, yeah.
This is for you.
From Midori?
Ah-huh.
Is she a friend of yours?
She was, once.
Did she say anything
mean to you?
No, she didn't.
Don't worry about her.
She says nasty things, but
deep down she's a good kid.
It's been five years already.
Oh well, the truth is
both of us are so stubborn,
we could never go back
to being friends.
Reki!
I'll do my best!
Yeah, good luck.
Your job does sound like
a bit of a drag, but remember,
you're not a full-fledged
Haibane unless you work.
Thanks for breakfast.
Damn, you're so lucky Rakka.
Your work starts
in the afternoon.
You shouldn't complain so much.
By the way, I'm very glad
you finally found a job.
What's the matter?
I have a cold.
What?
Don't spread it!
You're all heart.
Hey, where's Reki?
She said that she needs to paint
today, so I'm going to take over
her job of cooking
for the young feathers.
She's been doing
that a lot lately.
I wonder what's going on.
I was hoping she'd take
the scooter to the library
and tell them
I'm taking a day off.
Why don't you ask Kana?
Oh, no!
That's gonna make me
late for work.
Only ten minutes late.
That's OK, right
Actually for Master,
ten minutes is not OK
I have some time. I'll go.
You will?
Thanks.
Sure.
It's no problem.
Kana will give me a ride.
Right?
Thanks!
She is?
Oh.
I guess it did get
cold all of a sudden.
Well, thank you
for letting us know.
What's this...
Oh, Hey Rakka!
Why are you here?
Hi Sumika.
Wow.
It's almost my due date.
Is it still okay
for you to be out?
Of course.
I'd feel suffocated if I had
to shut myself in the house.
Besides, we have to
get ready for the festival,
and I still enjoy taking walks.
It's so mysterious, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Sometimes I find
myself wondering.
Where this life came from.
By the way, where's Nemu?
Oh, she has a cold
and won't be in today.
I came by to tell them that.
Oh that's too bad.
Wow, its one of
the petrified books.
Petrified books?
Nobody knows what they really
are, but the story goes that
there was a ruin deep in the
Western Woods a long time ago,
and this was found
buried in the stones.
It looks like it was
turned to stone
by some sort of magical force?
So, what is the book about?
I don't really know.
See all these
weird pattern things
that have been engraved on it?
Some say those are letters and
another says ancient drawings.
Like kind of look
like someone's hands.
Almost got it, one more time.
Rek--
You know nothing about what
Reki's capable of doing.
Reki!
Nemu?
That's very unusual.
You know, I should've
bought some canned peaches
or something else for her.
Oh, I didn't know
peaches were good for colds.
You're kidding, right.
Wow.
You've never used Peaches?
Well, don't worry.
I was just joking that they
would make a good get well gift.
Oh, really?
We walk with empty smiles
plastered on our faces.
Reki is always kind.
She doesn't want to worry
anyone, and she doesn't want
to lean on anyone,
so she smiles.
Why didn't I
realize that sooner?
I was always
right next to her.
Why couldn't I see it?
I wish tomorrow
would never come.
What, that was sudden?
I wish the day
after today was today.
And the next day,
and the next day, too.
I wish it was always today.
Then I'd be able
to be with you, forever.
There is no such thing
as forever.
Sooner or later,
everything ends.
Just like it should.
Because now is only meant
to be now, and this moment is...
so precious.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Guess you're right.
Off to work, huh?
Good luck.
You, too.
Don't cry!
I'm the one who will help Reki!
Smile...
Rakka...
Nemu, thanks for everything
over these years.
If you see Kuramori someday,
tell her that I'm sorry
and that I said thanks.
I don't think I'm ever gonna
make it to whatever world
she's in.
Reki...
Now, it's time
for me to end it.