[waves crashing]
[birds cawing]
[Misato] Why did it have to show up
right now?
[Ugh] Just my luck!
[beep]
[female voice] We're sorry,
regular phone service has been suspended,
due to a state of special emergency.
[Shinji sighs] That sucks.
Plus I can't get a signal, here.
And the buses and trains
are all shut down.
I guess I won't meet her, after all.
I'll never make it.
Might as well go to a shelter.
[birds fly off]
[crashing sound]
[wind]
[gasps]
[crashing sounds]
[thudding]
[blasts]
Oh!
[explosions]
[pilot] All missiles have hit the target!
[blasts]
[crashing sounds, broken glass]
Huh!
[car tyres screeching]
[Misato] Good morning. Sorry I'm late.
[blasts]
[Aoba] Target remains unfazed.
It is continuing to advance
toward Tokyo three.
[female PA] Air units ineffective
in stopping the target.
This is total war. Deploy all units of
the reserve fourth Division immediately.
Send in everything we have.
We need to crush that target at all costs.
[explosions]
This makes no sense!
We got multiple direct hits!
A whole armored battalion
turned to scrap metal.
Neither guided missiles nor heavy shells
are making a dent on the enemy.
Damn it! We need far more powerful weapons
against that thing!
[Fuyutsuki] Is it because
it's protected by an A.T. Field?
[Ikari] Yes. Conventional weapons
are useless against the angels.
[bleeping]
[card beeps]
Affirmative, Sir. Yes, Sir.
We'll deploy it according to plan.
[bleeping]
[beep]
Hey wait a minute! Please tell me
they're not planning to use an N-two mine!
Get down!
[explosion]
[both react]
We won!
Well, then! It seems
we won't be requiring
your services this time.
[shock wave]
- [Misato] Are you alright?
- [Shinji] Ugh!
[Shinji] I swallowed some sand,
but I'm okay.
That's good to hear. Now...
Push on three... Three!
[efforts]
[heaving]
I couldn't have done it without you.
Thanks a lot for your help.
My pleasure. I should thank you,
Miss Katsuragi.
You can call me... Misato.
It's nice to meet you, Shinji Ikari.
Thanks, you too.
- [Officer A] Current status?
- [Officer B] You saw that explosion.
It must’ve been obliterated.
[Aoba] Visual feed is back online.
Oh!
[crunching sounds]
[rumbling]
That was our most powerful weapon.
[groans] I can't believe it.
Damn monster!
[car engine]
[Misato] Thank goodness,
my little car is still moving!
I still have twelve months
to pay on my loan.
Would have sucked so bad
if they had totaled it! [laughs]
By the way,
I booked us an express transport.
So! We should make it on time.
Feel free to ask me questions.
You must have a lot.
Mh, okay.
I’m the one doing all the talking,
so come on now.
Oh. Yeah. I'm sorry.
No, I didn't mean it that way, Shinji.
It's just that...
I bet you have
a bunch of questions about all this.
Between that big monster
and my invitation, you must be curious.
I am... but...
I assumed you wouldn't give me
an answer even if I asked.
You think through these things
quite a bit for your age.
You should be more carefree!
Oh.
Please, ma'am... Look, I am only trying
to follow my teacher's advice.
OK. Well... Moving on.
That big thing back there is a mysterious
enemy creature we call an ‘angel’.
[helicopter sounds]
[Fuyutsuki] The fourth angel.
It has a remarkable ability
to regenerate itself.
It is an independent life-form,
fully complete unto itself.
It's not surprising.
They are the ones that ate
from the "Tree of Life"...
Yes. And so, it's here to destroy us.
We, of the "Tree of Knowledge".
[female PA] Attention,
automatic doors now closing.
Stand clear of the closing doors.
[Shinji] Special Government Agency,
- NERV?
- Yeah.
It's a secret department of the UN.
My father works here, doesn't he?
That's right. Do you know
what your father's job is at NERV?
[bell rings]
My teacher once told me that my father has
a very important job protecting humanity.
As of this very moment, we are giving you
command of this operation.
- So, let's see what you can do!
- Very good sir.
Ikari,
it's quite clear that nothing
in our arsenal even comes close
to having an effect on the target.
Do you think
you have a chance of beating it?
That is the very purpose of NERV.
So, are you bringing me to my father?
That's right. That's the plan, yes.
[whispers] Father...
[train]
Oh, by the way! Did your father
send you any ID cards?
Erm...
Oh, yeah.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Right... Now, take a look at this.
Welcome to NERV?
This is where my father works?
Am I supposed
to do something here at NERV?
He sent me this letter.
He must have had a good reason
to ask me to come.
I wonder what it is. Do you have an idea?
[Misato] So you have issues
with your father?
We have that in common, you and I.
Oh! [gasps]
Look at that!
- A real Geofront!
- That's right.
We're passing above NERV command center.
Our secret base.
The fortress that protects us all.
Our only hope of rebuilding the world.
[crash]
So... Wait a second.
At the station, take the western exit, OK.
Then go right at the north gate.
Which leads us to Road 08.
Seriously, are they trying to make it
more complicated on purpose?
Anyhoo... it looks like
we're more or less on track.
Hey... Are you lost?
I don't know this place very well.
Let's keep moving, I'm sure
we're going to get there eventually.
[female PA]
Stage two cooling cycle complete.
[male PA] All crew must exit now.
[Ritsuko] Have the right arm nerve graft
thawed in 3 minutes.
- Remember to collect the apoptosis data.
- Roger.
[female PA] Dr Akagi, your attention:
Lieutenant colonel
Katsuragi and a young man
have arrived at HQ, by elevator S 36.
She's late again.
I really can't believe it.
[elevator pings]
How are you, Ritsuko?
You're late.
You should've been here 12 minutes ago.
Lieutenant Colonel Katsuragi.
I thought you got lost.
We have no time, nor manpower to waste.
[giggles] Sorry.
Uh.
- Is this the boy you went to get?
- That's him.
I am Ritsuko Akagi.
I am the director of Project E,
and NERV tech R & D.
A pleasure.
Er.. Me too.
I'll leave you in charge while I'm gone.
Father and son,
meeting again after three years.
[Man] Sir!
The target is on the move again.
Understood.
Order all personnel to battle stations.
[speed boat on water]
[Ritsuko] Shinji Ikari. I have
something here that I need to show to you.
The ultimate weapon
created for the ultimate battle.
[gasps]
Behold Shinji.
The artificial humanoid weapon.
We call it: Evangelion. This is Unit One.
Mankind's very last hope.
So this is my father's work?
[Ikari] Correct.
[Shinji gasps]
So. It's been a while.
Father...
Launch the Eva.
What? Right now?
But Eva Unit Zero
is still out of commission!
Wait. You don’t intend
to deploy Unit One, do you?
It's the only option we have.
[sighs]
- Listen carefully Shinji.
- Yes, ma'am?
You will pilot the Eva.
Uh?
Father... Why did you send for me?
You already know the reason why.
So you want me to get inside this thing
and fight that monster I just saw?
That’s correct.
I don't want to do this! No way!
Why are you bringing me here?
You abandoned me
because you didn't need me, right?
A need arose, so I had you brought here.
[sighs] But why me, Father?
Because it would be impossible
for anyone else.
It's impossible for me too.
[sighs]
I've never even seen this thing before.
There's no way I can pilot it!
They'll explain how to do it.
But... That's...
There's no way I can do this!
I can't learn to pilot this thing, Father!
[Ikari] Stop wasting time. Get in the Eva
or get out!
[blast, explosion]
Bastard! He must know where we are.
[female PA] Layer 1,
Armor plating number eight destroyed.
Come on, Shinji.
There’s not a lot of time.
[Man PA] Fire alarm in Sector D.
Initiating emergency closing
of all fire doors.
Please pilot the Eva.
This is crazy! I don't want to be a pilot!
Come on, I just got here!
Tell me, then Shinji.
What was the purpose of you coming here?
You mustn't run away.
Not from your father.
And especially, not from yourself.
No, I know! I know...
But there's no way I can do this!
Fuyutsuki. Wake up Rei.
Will she be able to fight?
She's not dead yet.
Understood. [sighs]
- Rei?
- Yes.
The backup isn't working out.
- I need you again.
- Yes.
[piano music]
Reset Unit One's core system!
Configure to L00 properties
and reactivate.
[Ibuki] Roger. Suspending all
current tasks and initiating reactivation.
Initializing transfer command routine.
I knew it.
No one wants me.
[female PA] Target has breached
absolute defense perimeter.
Approaching area above HQ.
[piano music]
[Rei gasping]
[panting]
[blast]
Ah!
[Shinji] Are you OK?
[Rei gasping]
Ah! [suffering]
Ah!
[in pain]
[gasping]
Don’t run away. Don’t run away.
Don’t run away.
Fine, I'll do it.
I'll pilot the Eva.
[liquid gushing]
[female PA] Stage 3
cooling cycle complete.
[male PA] Flywheel rotation shutdown.
- Disengage flywheel.
- Auxiliary voltage level...
Shutdown signal plug extraction complete.
Roger. Inserting Entry Plug into Eva one.
[Hyuga] Unlocking spinal conduit system.
- Prepare connection.
- Probe plug, entry complete.
Monitoring. Psychological corruption level
within operational safe range.
Interior array locked down.
[Ritsuko] Roger. Connection, level one.
[Ibuki] Flooding Entry Plug interior.
Oh, what is it? Huh? Ah!
Relax, Shinji. It's normal,
let the fluid fill your lungs.
The L.C.L. will bring oxygen
into your bloodstream.
You'll quickly get used to it.
[male PA] Main power connection complete.
[Ritsuko] Roger.
[Ibuki] Initiating Level 2 contact.
Connecting interface system.
A-10 neural connection achieved.
[Ritsuko]
L.C.L: ionization levels, normal.
Set Japanese as the linguistic norm
for cognitive interface.
Initial contact... all systems nominal.
[Ibuki] Pilot Comm link... established.
Full process list green, up to line 1405.
Measuring synapse levels.
Synchronization rate at 41.3 %.
And the boy’s not even wearing
a Plugsuit. That's incredible.
All readings nominal on harmonic levels.
No sign of system runaway.
This is going to work!
Prepare for launch!
[Hyuga] Prepare for launch!
[male PA] Release
lockdown bolt number one.
[female PA] Confirmed.
[male PA] Initiating retraction
of umbilical bridge.
Release lockdown bolt number two.
[Male PA] Removing
primary restraining gear frames.
Now removing
secondary restraining gear frames.
Disengaging safety systems
one through fifteen.
[female PA] Disengagement confirmed.
Unit One is ready for transport.
[Male PA] Internal power supply
fully charged.
External power source connector,
status green.
Roger.
Moving Eva Unit One to launch bay now.
[Woman PA] Maglev rail track displacement,
nominal.
EM induction system function, nominal.
Transporting Unit One via K-52.
Primarily rail magnetic field adjustment
is complete.
The Eva has arrived
at the launch hub terminal.
Lift stop position
has been set to elevation point zero.
All blast doors open
except the final elevator gate.
[Ibuki] Launch tube clear.
All systems green.
- Pre-launch sequence complete.
- Copy that.
- Do we have a GO, commander?
- Of course.
The future of humanity
depends on defeating the angels.
Ikari, are you absolutely sure
about doing this?
Hmm.
Launch Eva!
[blast]
[triumphant music]
[strains]
[beeping]
[Misato] Ready, Shinji?
Uh, yeah.
Disengage the final safety systems!
Evangelion Unit One, ready for battle!
Listen, Shinji.
I want you to just focus on walking.
Walk.
It's walking!
Just walk.
[effort] [strain]
[Misato] Shinji, Stay focused!
And get up! Come on, quickly!
[strain]
Ah!
[Misato] Just stay calm, Shinji!
It feels like your arm is hurt. It's not.
- What about the Eva's defense systems?
- Signal is inactive!
- No A.T. field projection!
- It isn't working!
Damage to left forearm!
Shinji! Break away!
Argh!
Fracture in front section of the cranium!
The armor won't hold much longer.
[Aoba] Major skull damage.
Severity unknown!
Give me a sit-rep.
[Ibuki] Synchrograph inverting.
Neural pulse flow reversing!
- Shut down circuits. Block the flow!
- I can't!
Eva's not receiving our shutdown signals.
- Sitrep on the pilot!
- Biometrics are down. Condition unknown!
[Aoba] Unit One complete system failure!
Misato!
Damn. That's it.
Abort operation.
Pilot recovery has top priority!
Emergency plug ejection, now!
I can't eject.
System's not responding to command.
What? Not responding?
- We have lost control of Unit One.
- Impossible!
There's no way it should be operational!
- Is it going...
- It’s going berserk!
[whirring]
Ah. We've won.
A.T. Field, activated!
It's hopeless.
Unless you breach its A.T. Field...
You can't even touch an angel.
- [Aoba] Left arm restored!
- Incredible!
Unit one is generating its own A.T. field.
Angel phase space is being neutralized!
No, it’s not.
It’s being outright corroded.
It ripped through the angel's A.T. field
like it was paper.
Where's the Eva?
That's the real Eva.
Its true nature.
[Yui] Have you decided on a name?
[Ikari] Shinji if it's a boy.
Rei if it's a girl.
[Yui] Shinji. Rei.
[laughs]
Shinji. Shinji.
Ayanami.
Shinji.
Rei.
Rei. Ikari.
No. Rei.
Rei Ayanami.
Rei.
[Shinji gasps]
I’ve never seen this ceiling before...
[SEELE 1] The attack of the fourth angel
and its destruction.
The requisition of the Third Child
and the first activation of Eva Unit One.
Everything is proceeding
according to plan.
[SEELE 4] The enormous cost of repairing
Unit One was not part of the plan.
[SEELE 5] That's a trivial issue compared
to repairing the grounded Unit Zero.
[Ibuki] We've completed
the recovery operation of the Eva.
Unit One is currently secured
within Cage Number Six.
Inspection is scheduled to begin
today at ten o'clock.
[Misato] Any data on the rampage
in the black box?
[Ibuki] It's completely blank.
Apparently, it didn't record anything.
[Misato] It means
we're clueless about what happened.
As for the Eva's reliability as a weapon,
I can't say I'm overly optimistic.
[SEELE 1] It may not be perfect,
but that's fine
as long as it's effective
against the coming fifth angel.
[Ikari] No need for concern.
Following
the operational deployment of Unit One,
field testing of Unit Two and its pilot
have begun in Germany.
[SEELE 4] Production of Units Three and up
must go according to plan.
[SEELE 3] Your duty is to make sure NERV
and the Evas serve their purpose.
You know better than to disappoint us.
[SEELE 6] Agreed.
Defeating the angels is just
a small part of our covenant with Lilith.
The Human Instrumentality Project.
The execution of that project
is our paramount objective.
[Ikari] I am well aware.
Everything shall proceed
according to SEELE's scenario.
[birds chirping]
[door clanking]
[engines whirring]
[Ritsuko] An angel's destruction following
its loss of A.T. Field leaves a mark.
[Ibuki] It's like the lakes of blood
in the ancient depictions of hell.
It's creepy, how much it reminds you
of the Second Impact, don't you think?
[Misato] Our Eva can defeat an angel.
This should bring humanity the glimmer
of hope that everybody craves right now.
And I just got a message
about our young pilot: he finally woke up.
[female PA] Announcement for doctor Ugai
of the Internal Medicine Department One.
Doctor Ugai
Please contact Doctor Azuma
of the Surgery Department One.
Doctor Ugai, please contact
doctor Azuma, thank you.
[elevator door pings]
[Misato] He'll be living all alone?
[Officer] Correct. He's been assigned
a room in block six, close to HQ.
- Is there a problem?
- No, Sir.
Will you be OK, Shinji? Are you sure?
Yes, it's fine. I don't mind living alone.
I'm used to it, you know.
What did you say?
It's no big deal: I invited Shinji
to come live in my apartment.
I even got permission from the top.
And don't worry about it,
I promise I won't mess around with him,
I know he's just a kid!
Of course you won't!
How can you even say things like that?
- Do you realize...
- Miss researcher has no sense of humor!
[Misato] Alright!
We're going to celebrate in style tonight.
Celebrate what?
The fact that my new roommate
has just moved in with me, of course.
[phone ringing]
[Housewife A] You decided to move away?
[Housewife B] Yes.
We never thought this city
would turn into such a battlefield.
[Housewife A] Well, nobody did!
My husband actually wants me
and our children to evacuate, too.
I heard that today alone, more than
a hundred people gave their moving notice!
[Housewife B] Well, I'm not surprised!
This city is supposed to be a fortress,
but how can you count
on an organization like NERV?
[Housewife A] I get chills just thinking
about what happened yesterday.
[Housewife B] You're right...
[Misato] I hope you don't mind.
- But we're taking a little detour.
- Where are we going?
I'll show you something really cool.
[Shinji] Look at that...
It's a bit too depressing for my taste.
Just a minute.
[siren wails]
[trumpets play]
Incredible!
The buildings are rising up!
[Misato] This fortress city was built
specifically to fight the angels.
This is Tokyo three.
This is our home city.
And it's the city that you just protected.
[Misato] Look! Your stuff
has already been delivered!
You know, it's funny,
I actually just moved in here myself.
- Come in! Welcome roomie!
- Oh, thank you.
Thank you for having me.
Relax Shinji. This is your home too, now.
Uh...
OK. I guess I'm home.
Welcome home, Shinji.
[Misato] So... I know...
It's a little messy,
but make yourself at home.
That's what she calls "a little messy"?
Oh, hey! Do me a favor!
Put the food we bought in the fridge, OK?
Um, yeah, sure.
Ice...
Snacks...
And beer. That's it?
What does she do when she's home?
[ping]
[Misato] That looks amazing.
Come on, dig in!
[Shinji] Yes, amazing.
[gulps]
Ah! [laughs]
Boy, oh boy, I'm telling you,
this is what makes life worth living!
A feast for a king.
You're not hungry, or what?
I know it's all microwavable food,
but it's pretty good.
No, It's just... It's just that I'm not
used to that kind of food, that's all.
Hold on a sec!
I don't like picky eaters!
No, sorry... I didn't mean it like that.
Not at all...
- This is fun, isn't it?
- Uh...
Just you and me,
sharing meals and conversation.
Uh... Yes...
Great!
Well, this is going to be
your home from now on.
So get comfy, roomie,
you need to chill out!
(uh) Yes, ma'am.
Uh! Yes ma'am! No ma'am!
Stop being so uptight!
You're a fine young man!
Grow a spine! Be bold and confident!
- Yeah, okay.
- Fine, whatever.
Why don't you go take a nice bath? Relax!
It’s just what you need right now!
A bath to wash your life and begin anew.
Aaah!
Mi... Mi... Mi... Miss Misato, help!!
- What's wrong?
-The... There's... This... Thing...
I mean...
Oh, him, yeah!
He's a hot spring penguin.
It's a type of bird.
[bird caws]
I've never seen a bird like that before!
They were common 15 years ago.
But there aren't many left, now.
His name is Pen Pen.
I came across him one day
and now he's my roommate.
Don't you think
you should throw something on?
Huh?
Woah!
Maybe I laid it on too thick
by acting so confident.
He might see right through it.
[Shinji] Misato Katsuragi.
She seems nice enough.
A bath to wash your life and begin anew.
But... For me, taking a bath
often brings back bad memories.
[Ritsuko] May I ask how Rei's doing?
I understand you visited her today
at the hospital.
[Ikari] That's irrelevant.
Getting Unit Zero back into operational
condition is far more important.
[Ritsuko] What about your son, sir?
I imagine
he must be feeling quite distraught.
[Ikari] Leave him be.
That'll give us an excuse
to bring Unit Zero back to active duty.
[Ritsuko] Then we'll go ahead
with Katsuragi's suggestion.
[Misato] The third child gets chosen
suddenly, and without any prior reports.
Then an angel attacks,
minutes after his arrival here.
Commander Ikari
recruits his own child into NERV.
No way that can be a coincidence. Strange.
I've worked so hard
towards defeating the angels.
I should be much happier right now.
[Shinji] Another ceiling
I've never seen before.
No surprise. There's absolutely
nothing familiar about this city.
[Misato] This is your home too, now.
[Shinji] What am I doing here?
[sighs]
[Misato] Shinji, excuse me a sec.
There's something
that I should've told you:
people will thank you
and praise you for what you did today.
You should be proud.
Good night, Shinji.
Keep it up, okay?
[punch]
Ah!
[Tohji] Hey, I'm sorry, newbie.
But I just had to straight up deck you.
At least once, to get even with you.
[Kensuke] It's not personal.
He blames you because his little sister
was injured during the last battle.
Just try to see it his way.
That's so unfair.
It's not like I pilot that thing
because I want to.
[Kensuke] Hugh!
[growling]
[Shinji] So much for people
thanking me for what I did.
Why do I have to get beat up
just for being an Eva pilot?
- [Ritsuko] Listen, Shinji.
- [Shinji] Yes.
[Ritsuko] Every angel
has a component that we call the core.
The only way to defeat an angel in battle
is to destroy that core.
That's what we'll practice today.
Target the core and pull the trigger.
[blasts]
You need to repeat it again and again
to make it second nature.
[Shinji] Yes.
Good job, Shinji.
- Keep practicing in induction mode.
- Yes.
I'm amazed Shinji would be willing
to go through with this so obediently.
Perhaps following
other people's instructions is how Shinji
makes life easier for himself.
Target the angel's core
and pull the trigger.
Target the angel's core...
[Ritsuko] I heard Shinji
got bullied by a classmate
on his very first day of school.
I thought he had
an appropriate security detail.
[Misato] He does. The Covert Ops Division
is keeping close watch.
He was never in any real danger.
We believe it's best for him
if we give him
as much privacy as possible.
But he lives in your apartment.
So making sure
he's operational is part of your job.
Makes things trickier.
He's much more of a sensitive boy
than I ever expected.
Already having second thoughts?
Weren't you the one
who was excited about the whole thing?
Give me a freaking break.
[Ritsuko] But yes... You might be right...
Shinji might be the sort of person
who has a hard time making friends.
- Ever heard of the hedgehog's dilemma?
- Hedgehog?
Those things with all the spikes?
[Ritsuko] Imagine hedgehogs
in winter trying to get close
to one another, to share warmth.
The closer they get,
the more they end up hurting each other.
People are like that, too.
I think part of Shinji is afraid of
that pain, and that makes him withdrawn.
He'll outgrow it.
[girl giggling]
[Misato] He'll figure it out eventually.
As you get older, you try
again and again,
and through trial and error,
after a while, you get a feel
for what the right distance is.
I certainly hope so.
[Misato] What’s it going to take to get
the budget approved to upgrade the B Wing?
It's so Spartan here!
[Ritsuko] They're prioritizing
Eva repairs and weapons production.
Maybe they're broke.
[Misato] But we're freezing our buns off!
We got an emergency call.
I'm going. Meet me there.
[Aoba] Direct visual on inbound object.
[Female PA] E747 confirms inbound object.
Pattern recognition system: blue.
This must be the fifth angel.
Everyone! Battle stations. Condition One.
[Hyuga] Roger!
Ready ground to air intercept.
[Female PA] Initiating deployment
of Tokyo 3 into combat configuration.
[siren wailing]
Retracting central block structures.
[female PA]
Retraction of buildings complete
in central blocks
and wards one through seven.
[Aoba] Government and agencies
have been notified.
[female PA] Target approaching,
course unchanged.
Current air defense systems
operating at 48% capacity.
Status of noncombatant personnel
and civilians?
Emergency evacuation complete,
shelters locked down.
[female PA] Students in grades 1 to 9,
please remain with your class,
under teacher supervision.
[Kensuke] Damn, this again!
Still nothing but text scrolling across?
Yeah,
it's a complete news blackout, as usual.
Stupid government
wants to keep us in the dark.
I feel like we're missing
a once in a life time event!
[blasts]
What a waste of taxpayer money.
Some people get uncomfortable unless
they burn through ammo at times like this.
The government called, they're asking
to launch the Evangelion now.
Annoying bunch of jerks.
We don't need them
to tell us when to launch.
[female PA] Begin Entry Plug checklist.
Pressure clamps, unlocked.
[Ibuki] Ionizing L.C.L.
[Shinji] Father's not even watching me.
Why am I doing this?
My only reward is people hating me!
[crash]
Hey, Tohji, can I talk to you in private
for just a minute or two?
- Why? What's up?
- Come on, please?
Alright, alright, sure.
[Hikari] She forgot he was there!
- Hey, Class Rep?
- What is it?
We're going to the bathroom.
We need to take a leak.
Oh. You couldn't have done that
before you got here?
[Tohji] So... what's up?
[Kensuke] I want to see what's it like
at least once before I die.
- You mean the battle?
- This is the real deal!
And there's no way to know
when the enemy will come next...
Come on, Kensuke, what is it with you?
Please, it might be our only chance!
Pretty please!
Just help me unlock the doors.
Okay, okay.
You don’t know when to stop sometimes.
You just got to do your thing!
[Kensuke chuckles]
[beep]
[Misato] Shinji, launch imminent.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Remember: a burst with the Gatling gun
while neutralizing the angel’s A.T. Field.
- Just repeat your training. All right?
- Yes.
And launch!
[triumphant music]
Oh yeah! Seeing this
makes it worth the risk of suspension!
And look: here comes our guy.
There he is!
Target the angel's core
and pull the trigger.
and pull the trigger. Yes, ma'am.
[efforts]
What an idiot!
Now he can't see a freaking thing!
[blasts]
[crashing]
[panting]
What the hell?
He's already lost the battle?!
He's not done yet.
Sending up a spare rifle!
[Misato] Go on, grab it!
- [Shinji crying]
- [Misato] Shinji? Shinji?
[Kensuke] Oh boy...
Maybe he's still shook up
from your beating.
What? Just shut up!
[suspenseful music]
[gasping]
[Aoba] Umbilical cable severed!
[Hyuga] Eva has switched
to internal power.
[Ibuki] Operational time limit:
4 minutes, 53 seconds.
[effort]
[Kensuke] It's coming right at us!
[Both scream]
[Misato] Shinji, are you alright? Shinji!?
Damage report!
[Hyuga] Damage minimal. He's OK!
[boys panicking]
- Two of Shinji's classmates are there!
- What are they doing?
Why isn't he fighting the monster?
I think maybe because we're here?
He's afraid he'll squash us if he moves!
[Ibuki] Unit One operational limit:
three minutes, 28 seconds.
Contact surface overheating. Damage 58 %.
[efforts]
[Misato] Shinji, let those two
inside your cockpit!
Return to base
after you've retrieved them.
We'll start over.
You two! Get in! Now!
[splash]
[Tohji] Is this water?
[Kensuke] My camera! It's not waterproof!
[Ibuki] Contact surface meltdown
reaching the third protective coat.
Now's your chance! Retreat!
[Misato] Use Recovery Route 34.
- Fall back to...
- Newbie, listen!
She's telling you to fall back!
Don't run away! Don't run away.
Don't run away!
[Hyuga] Progressive knife deployed!
[Misato] Shinji, obey my order!
I said fall back! Shinji!
Aaaah!
What an idiot!
Uh!
Aaaah!
[screaming]
Unit One operational limit critical!
Thirty seconds! Twenty-eight...
Twenty-seven... Twenty-six...
Twenty-five...
Twenty-four... Twenty-three...
Twenty-two...
Thirteen... Twelve... Eleven... Ten...
Nine... Eight...
Seven...
Six... Five...
Four...
Three...
Two... One...
[Ibuki] Eva Unit One
has completely shut down.
[Aoba] Target
has completely disintegrated.
[Shinji heaving]
[panting]
[Shinji crying]
[raining]
Care to tell me why you ignored my orders?
I'm sorry.
You're aware
that I am your superior officer?
Yes, ma'am.
It is your duty
to fully adhere to the orders I give.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, ma'am.
Make sure this doesn't happen again.
Yes, ma'am.
Is any of this getting through to you?
Yes. I understand, Miss Misato.
But why does any of it matter anyway?
After all, when you say fight, I fight.
Isn’t that what you want from me?
[Misato humphs]
[effort]
[sighs]
I've had enough of this.
Go home and get some rest.
[door opening]
[female PA] Next stop Nagao-touge,
Nagao-touge.
Please exit on the right hand side.
[street atmosphere]
He’s avoiding me. What a jerk.
[cat meows]
[string music]
[Teacher] Ikari? Shinji Ikari?
Missing school already?
He just transferred in, a few days ago.
Nevermind. All right,
time for a pop quiz on last week’s lesson!
[students react]
[Shinji] OK... I've had enough of this.
You can take me back to Miss Misato, now!
[Misato] So, Shinji,
how was your little outing?
Did it calm your nerves?
[Shinji] Not really.
Nothing matters. I don't care.
I have no freedom, anyway.
All that's left for me
is to pilot the Eva, right?
That's the only reason
my father brought me here.
That's fine. I'll do it.
Just as long as that makes
everyone else happy.
[Misato] Forget about everyone else.
What about you?
[Shinji] Well I, for one,
know I can't do this.
And I'm sure everybody knows that as well.
But what can I do? Ayanami's hurt
and father wants me to be the one...
That's enough, Shinji!
Who cares, what others think!
You need to decide for yourself
if you want to pilot the Eva or not.
And if you don't, you are free to go.
The choice is yours.
It's all up to you.
[Fuyutsuki] Apparently your son behaved
exactly the way we had anticipated.
[Ikari] Yes, he did. Now, I just
have to push him a little closer to Rei.
Everything is proceeding
according to plan.
[Fuyutsuki] A scenario all laid out
fourteen years ago.
Children
with predetermined fates.
It's rather cruel, I must say.
[insects singing]
[Tohji] Come on, just do it!
And don't hold back, OK?
We've got to settle this.
Got to even the score.
[Kensuke] Sorry. He's big on scores
and that kind of thing. Play along.
[punch]
[effort]
OK, so now we're even.
Sorry about punching you
in the face, Ikari.
[chattering]
Yeah, go Kayoko!
[girl] You owe us a pizza if you lose!
[Ritsuko] Rei Ayanami, fourteen.
The first child approved
by the Marduk Institute.
The first girl.
The designated pilot of the Evangelion
experimental prototype, Unit Zero.
All records of her previous life
have been erased.
[Shinji] Rei Ayanami.
And to save Ayanami, my father.
[Ibuki] Critical error
in activation system.
[female PA] Multiple critical errors...
Autonomous rejection
by central nervous system.
[male PA] Neural pulse flow reversing!
[Ibuki] Neural pulse flow reversing!
I can't stop it!
We lost the direct camera feed!
[Ibuki] Entry Plug malfunction.
The interior array is being pulled in!
[Ritsuko] Abort contact process. Emergency
shutdown of circuits one through six.
[Ibuki] Command fail!
System is unresponsive!
We have lost control of Unit Zero!
Abort the experiment. Shutdown power now.
[Ritsuko] Yes, sir.
[sirens and alarms]
[Ritsuko] Power cut.
Unit Zero on internal power.
[Ibuki] 35 seconds to system shutdown.
[Man PA] Automatic fail-safe system
not activating.
Sir, get back! It's dangerous!
Pilot emergency ejection system engaged!
No!
[Ritsuko] Release bakelite!
Rei! No!
[Ibuki] Total system shutdown
in ten seconds.
Eight... Seven... Six...
Five... Four... Three... Two... One...
Eva inactive. Full system shutdown.
[efforts]
[grunts]
Rei... Are you alright?
Rei!
[Rei pants]
I see. That's good.
[piano music]
[Misato] It's hard to believe
it really happened.
[Ritsuko] The incident was erased
from the official records,
but it's all true.
[Misato] If Unit Zero went berserk,
why rush it back into active duty?
[Ritsuko] The angels have returned.
We're going to need all hands on deck.
[Misato] Well, sure,
I know you're right, but...
[Ritsuko ] We're being careful.
We've completed
all the re-activation tests on Rei.
Unit Zero itself is operational.
Once neural calibration is complete...
[Misato] They'll be thrown
back onto the battlefield, right?
I wonder why Ayanami is always alone.
[female PA] Level three
cooling cycle of Eva Unit One.
Cage Six, shut down systems
up to phase three.
T minus one-fifty until Unit Zero
conductive systems restart and testing.
Synchronization test complete.
No abnormal results.
No signs of psychological contamination.
Copy Caspar's situational data
to Melchior. Unit One’s
plug depth currently...
Begin circulation of CBL.
All waste water to be directed
to the Level Two water treatment system.
...as soon as possible. Priority One.
T minus 1:50 until Unit Zero
conductive systems restart and testing.
[Ibuki] Roger. Routine check 508.
We're done, all systems checked and ready.
Thank you, Shinji. Good work.
[Ritsuko] So...
Do you like living with him?
[Misato] It's OK. I'm getting used to it.
[Ritsuko] You seem a little nervous.
You shouldn't be, it's not
your first time living with a man.
[sighs] Yeah,
but it's not like eight years ago.
It's not
a romantic relationship this time.
I wouldn't be so sure.
After all, Shinji decided
to come back because of you.
- You're wrong there.
- Hmm?
It's not me.
It's because his father is here.
He wants his father to look at him,
pat him on the shoulder. Talk to him.
Give him a few words of praise.
Even if it's only a few.
I think he needs love.
Cause only love could ease his loneliness.
The kid's hung-up on his father.
Just like you, Misato.
It feels very weird.
Why does commander Ikari want
to keep his own son at arm's length?
He's got no problem talking to Rei.
Doesn't seem right to me.
That's how all men are, now.
They're just
completely wrapped up in themselves.
Right now
is not the best time to be a woman.
Well...
It's late. I need to get back.
You just live to work, don't you?
By the way, if you're going home,
can you bring Shinji
his official security access card?
There's a new one for Rei, too.
I forgot to give it to them earlier.
Can you ask your roommate
to bring it to her?
Yeah, sure.
[Shinji] Rei Ayanami.
Why was father smiling
when he talked to her?
Why won't he smile for me?
Anybody home?
Hello? It's me, Shinji.
I'm coming in, okay?
Are these hers?
[curtain draws]
[gasps]
I... Uh...
I didn't mean to...
Ah!
Could you move now?
[stammers]
Oh!
Woah! I...
Oh! Uh...
What is it?
I... Erm... I'm... I mean...
I didn't mean...
I came here because Miss Misato
told me to. I was supposed to...
Oh right! The card!
I was supposed to bring you your new card.
I didn't know you would be...
[gulps]
It's just...
Oh right! Miss Ritsuko
said she forgot to give it
to you.
Honest.
I didn't want to spy or anything...
I rang the bell. but no one answered.
And the door was unlocked so...
[door squeaks and shuts]
[female PA] Access to Central Dogma
is currently allowed.
Category three visitors,
please use gate number four.
[beep]
As I said before,
they issued you a new card.
And they told me to bring it to you.
- I'm sorry for earlier...
- Sorry for what?
Hey... Ayanami...
Don't you ever get scared?
About having to pilot
the Evangelion again?
Why would I?
Well, I heard you got hurt pretty badly
during the last test.
So I was wondering
if you're worried or not.
I see. No. I'm not worried.
But the Eva could go berserk again.
And hurt you.
Or an angel could kill you. And me too.
Tell me...
You're Commander Ikari's son, right?
Hmm.
Don't you have faith in him?
Don't you trust the work he does?
No! Of course not.
I know what kind of father he is.
Erm...
[female PA] Warning: target approaching
Odawara Defense Line.
[Aoba] Analysis of target complete.
Pattern Blue confirmed.
Target is an angel.
It appears to be the sixth angel.
I agree. Launch Unit One
on intercept course.
[Misato] Prep Eva Unit One for launch.
[female PA] Re-checking ordnance.
All green.
[Aoba] Target approaching.
It's above Lake Ashinoko.
Eva Unit One prepped and ready for launch.
Launch Eva!
High energy readings
from inside the target!
What is going on?
Alert him!
Take cover!
Lower synchronization rate!
Deploy blast shield!
[Misato] Cancel mission!
Initiate emergency recovery of Unit One!
[Hyuga] No go!
The catapult lift has melted.
- Status of A.T. field?
- Deployed at maximum intensity.
Barely enough
to protect the Eva's integrity.
Aaah!
[Shinji screaming] Help! I can't take it!
Let me out! Father, please!
Cancel operation!
Prioritize pilot recovery!
Eject entry point now!
[Ikari] Ignore that order.
Once there's no pilot in the Eva,
the unit will immediately lose
its protective A.T. field.
Things will go from bad to worse.
But Shinji...
[screaming]
There's no other choice...
[female PA] Second breastplate layer...
Emergency recovery!
Blow the explosive bolts!
[explosion]
[Aoba] Target has ceased fire.
[Ibuki] Expedite recovery!
Take Unit One to Cage 99.
[Misato] Rescuers, stand by!
[Ritsuko] Priority One:
L.C.L cooling in Entry Plug.
[Hyuga] Pilot is alive! Heart rate, low!
Increase Plugsuit life support
to maximum. Cardiac massage!
Yes, ma'am.
Ah!
[beeping]
[Hyuga] Heart rate stabilizing.
Force eject Entry Plug, now!
[female PA] Plug surface temperature
has dropped to 300.
- Drain L.C.L from Entry Plug!
- Draining!
[female PA] Draining L.C.L.
Medical team to pilot!
[alert]
[angel singing]
[Hyuga] The target
is hovering directly above us.
It's drilling down toward the Geofront.
[Misato] So this one wants to launch
a direct attack on NERV HQ, huh?
I want a report from
all the heads of department in the agency.
Tac report from the first battle suggest
that the enemy automatically engages
any hostile coming within a certain range.
So close combat is out of the question
because we can't approach it.
- What do we know about its A.T. field?
- Still active.
Furthermore, its phase pattern is randomly
shifting and its exterior shape in flux.
It'll be very difficult to neutralize.
According to MAGI calculation,
in order to breach this A.T. field
with airdropped N2 mines,
the explosion would have to be so powerful
that NERV HQ would end up being
completely obliterated in the process.
That’s true. MAGI-2 at Matsushiro
reached the same conclusion.
The Japanese government and the UN
are requesting that NERV HQ
should self-destruct to defeat this angel.
Easy for them to say.
They think it’s just our problem.
Don't they know
we're all doomed if NERV HQ falls?
But ma’am, the drilling is relentless.
Two layers of armor plates
have been pierced.
And now it’s boring
through the third layer.
[Aoba] 22 layers of kakumo type armor belt
plating have been installed so far.
Provided
the drilling speed remains constant...
Estimated time of final breach:
6:54 after midnight.
In less than
ten hours and fifteen minutes.
[Hyuga] Unit Zero still needs critical
calibrations before it is operational.
And Unit One won't be able to do much
until extensive repairs are complete.
The outlook appears to be rather bleak.
We're short on both time and resources.
[Hyuga] Maybe we should wave a white flag?
I'll think about it.
But I just might have an idea.
Something I want to try before giving up.
Our Covert Ops has a file
on SSDF's secret research, right?
Uh-huh.
[aircraft]
[Ritsuko] I have to say.
This is your most reckless plan to date,
"Operations Chief Katsuragi".
Reckless? That's not very nice.
It's doable before our midnight deadline.
And, anyway,
we both know it's our best shot.
[Ritsuko] Operation Yashima:
as the name implies.
The entirety of Japan
will devote its electricity
to power a self-propelled
high-power positron cannon
you requisitioned from the SSDF.
Since the cannon
is not fully operational yet,
an Eva will execute
the high precision targeting.
Convincing the UN Forces is one thing.
But the Home Ministry and
the Strategic Self Defense Forces as well?
Well, I called in a few favors.
[Ritsuko] It takes a fox to catch a fox.
[beep]
[female PA] Electrical black-out warning:
tonight at midnight,
power will be cut off
for the entire country.
Thank you
for your cooperation in this matter.
I repeat.
Electrical black-out warning:
tonight at midnight,
power will be cut off
for the entire country.
I repeat.
[Tohji] Alright. Let's go.
[female PA] Electrical black-out warning:
tonight at midnight...
[siren wailing]
Electrical black-out warning:
tonight at midnight...
[birds chirping]
[Aoba] The angel's drill
has breached Armor Plate 7.
How's our power supply doing?
[female crew] Progression steady.
Power will be directly routed through
Shingotenba substation and two backups.
We're currently laying down superconductor
power lines toward Shimofutagoyama.
Estimated time of completion
and final connection
to the main transformer: 22:50 tonight.
Status report on ordnance preparation?
[team leader] Assembly
proceeding steadily.
We'll have
the weapon operational by 23:00.
Status report on Eva One?
[Ibuki] Currently undergoing refit
to Type G sniper configuration.
Unit one will be ready in 2 hours.
Copy that!
The only thing missing now is the pilot.
Do you think Shinji will agree
to pilot the Eva again?
[Fuyutsuki]
So what about Unit One's pilot?
[Ikari] The Dummy Plug
is not even ready for the trial stage.
We're going to have to make do
with the current pilot we have until then.
If nothing else works,
there's always brainwashing.
[Ikari] If nothing else works,
there's always Rei.
You want her to pilot Unit One?
Don't you think
it's a rather dangerous option?
We must win, no matter what.
We need to do whatever it takes
to defeat eight more angels.
I suppose everything depends on that.
I don't want to pilot my Eva anymore.
Everybody assumes success.
So I hardly ever get praised.
And if I fail, people hate me. And worst,
I'll just die. What am I doing here?
I came here hoping for change.
I thought things might get better.
I didn't come here to be put through hell.
Is that it? Are you going
to live your life running away from pain?
Me? Live? What for?
I used to wonder
if there was any point in living.
No one wants me.
Not my father. Not Miss Misato.
No one wants me unless I pilot the Eva.
That's why I have to be the pilot.
Otherwise, I can't stay here.
That's all I have left.
But when I pilot the Eva, I end up...
[gasps]
This ceiling again...
Seems like piloting always brings me here.
Ayanami?
You've been here all this time?
Listen.
The timeline for the Operation Yashima
set to start at midnight is as follows:
first, Ayanami and Ikari
will report to Terminal two
at 19:30.
At 20:00, both pilots
will accompany both Units One and Zero.
At 20:05, we depart.
At 20:30,
we arrive at Futagoyama Fortress two.
Once there,
we are to await further instructions.
Then, when the clock strikes midnight,
Operation Yashima begins.
Here's your meal.
No thanks. I don't want it.
We report in 90 minutes.
So we have to pilot those things again?
We do.
But I don't want to.
I can't go through
that kind of hell again.
It's so... So scary.
But I can even run away.
[Rei] Are you scared of the Evas?
Then, just stay and sleep.
Stay and sleep?
Yes. I'll pilot Unit One.
Ayanami!
Farewell.
[drill humming]
[Aoba] Target's drill
has breached Armor Plate number 17.
[female PA] Estimated time before
final breach: 4 hours 55 minutes.
Nishihakone Shinsen and Minami Tounosawa
link-up via Kakuu Route three, complete.
[female PA] 50,000 volt standard
installation will begin on schedule.
Stage four...
Transformer Group 28 has arrived
five minutes behind schedule.
[male PA] Hurry with the shunting of
rolling stock from No. 3 loading platform.
[female PA] Supervisor,
please expedite link-up.
Roger. Please forward completion report
to power link C&C center.
[male PA] 4th Electrical Relay
Group’s integrity has been checked.
All systems green.
...Stage One power merge circuits...
[female PA] Ultra-high voltage
superconductor transformer arrays
checked and certified.
[Hyuga] This is the experimental
large-caliber positron cannon?
[Ritsuko] Assembling it was a rush job,
but in theory, it should work.
[Ibuki] We'll take care
of battle sight zeroing
by linking it to the Type G components.
You bet! We're counting on you for that.
I guess the one thing
we can't count on is the pilot.
But hopefully, Misato can take care of it.
Hey Shinji, you were supposed
to report for duty a while ago.
Apparently, you decided
you wanted to remain a pilot, right?
Then you have to follow through
and actually come do your job.
[Shinji] Piloting the Eva is really scary.
You people have it easy!
All you do is stay below in HQ
and give out orders.
I'm the one out there, doing scary stuff!
You're all a bunch of hypocrites!
[Misato] Come with me for a sec.
[Shinji gasps]
[Misato] Fifteen years ago,
half of humanity died
following the Second Impact in Antarctica.
If we let the angels set off
the Third Impact, we're done.
What's left of humanity will perish.
No one will survive.
I know all that.
I've heard it over and over again.
What you don't know
is that if an angel gets
into Level triple E, below NERV HQ,
this whole place
will automatically self-destruct.
If we have to sacrifice ourselves
to prevent the Third Impact, we'll do it.
Everyone who works here
fully understands and accepts that risk.
[beeping]
[ping]
[gasps]
I can’t believe it.
It can't be...
An Eva?
[Misato] It's not.
This being brought life to our planet...
And it could be
the agent of its extinction.
This is the second angel, Lilith.
- Lilith?
- Yes.
Yes. Some believe
it can trigger the Third Impact.
You need to guard Lilith
by piloting the Eva.
You are the only person who can do it.
Shinji, we are entrusting
the future of humanity
to you and to your Eva.
All that responsibility.
Why does it have to be me?
There's no specific reason.
Actually, fate chose you, Shinji.
But, you know,
you're not the only one
who's putting his life on the line.
We all are.
I'll do it, Misato. I'll pilot my Eva.
[humming]
Right. I will now inform you
of your roles in this operation.
- Shinji.
- Yes, ma'am.
- You will be the gunner in Unit One.
Rei, you will be in charge of defense
in Unit Zero.
Yes, ma'am.
To succeed, this operation
requires an extreme level of precision.
For that reason
and because Unit Zero needs calibration,
we chose Unit One as gunner,
even though it's not fully repaired.
So listen carefully, Shinji.
Positrons are affected by many factors:
gravity, the rotation of the Earth,
its magnetic field.
You have to take all that into account.
Target the core
and deliver a precise shot in the middle.
Easy to say,
but we can't even see where the core is.
[Ritsuko] Don't worry. Part of the angel
materializes during its attack phase.
We believe that's where its core is.
We will identify the targeting specifics
and supply you
with the firing solution.
Just follow the instructions on screen.
Then when the crosshairs
line up in the center, you just shoot.
The machine will do the rest.
But there's a catch:
only one location has been set up
to receive all the power up
for the massive electrical discharge.
For that reason,
Unit One's firing position is fixed.
So retreat will not be an option?
- Correct.
- But what...
What if I miss and the angel shoots back?
Don't think about that for now.
Focus on your job
and hit the enemy with your first shot.
So... Hit the target,
or we're in big trouble?
[Rei] So I...
- I'm supposed to protect Unit One?
- Yes.
Understood.
[Misato] It's time.
Get ready, both of you.
[Rei and Shinji] Yes, ma'am.
[Shinji] You know...
You know... we could die tonight.
No, Shinji.
You won't die.
I will protect you.
I don't feel I'm worth protecting.
[Misato] Here's a message
left with HQ public affairs.
Oh.
[soft music]
[caws]
[beeping]
Hello? It's me, Tohji Suzuhara.
Ikari... No.
Let me call you Shinji, OK?
Hey Shinji, I'm counting on you.
[shelter atmosphere]
Hey! It's me, Aida. Ikari...
Go get them.
[string music]
Tell me, Ayanami.
Why do you pilot your Eva?
Because it's my link.
- It's your link?
- Yes, my link.
- You mean, to my father?
- To everyone.
You sure are tough, Rei Ayanami.
It's just that... this is all I have.
It's time. Let's go.
Farewell.
[siren wailing]
[female TV] At the tone, it will be
12 o'clock, midnight. Precisely.
[beeping]
- Midnight, ma'am.
- Listen Shinji.
You chose to get back in the Eva.
If for only just that, I am grateful.
Thank you.
Begin Operation Yashima.
Positron cannon, pre-firing sequence.
Stage One, power connection.
[Hyuga] Roger. Connecting circuits
with primary and secondary substations.
[female PA] Stage One
power connection circuits engaged.
Increasing frequency modulation capacity
to 65 GigaWatts.
Stage One circuit breaker system
function optimal. All power stations,
maintain full capacity.
[male PA] Confirmation: systems ready.
[female PA] 0.7
to maximum power threshold.
[Hyuga] Districts One through 803,
enable transmission power lines.
[male PA] Voltage stable.
Maintain grid frequency at 50Hz.
Begin stage two power connection.
[male PA] Bringing
Shingotenba Substation online.
[female PA] Bringing Shinyugawara
Auxiliary Substation online as well.
[male PA] Cooling systems operational.
[Misato] Stage three power connection.
[Hyuga] Roger, redirecting all power
to the Futagoyama installation.
[female PA] Maintain maximum
allowable power transmission voltage.
Superconducting battery banks...
Verifying all indicators: status green.
Maintain highest possible
frequency modulation
on power from Western Japan.
[Hyuga] Stage three power connection:
status green.
OK, very good. Inform
Fortress Command Centers four and five.
Begin operations as planned.
Pull back surveillance aircraft.
[blasts]
Number Three Anti-Air Defense System
vaporized!
Keep piling it on. Keep it preoccupied.
Next!
[shooting]
[explosion]
[Hyuga] Turret Battery has been hit.
[female PA] VLS Battery Group vaporized.
No. 4 Anti-Air Defense System,
initiating attack.
Positron accelerator, charging.
Currently at One Terrawatt.
No. 7 Turret Battery, open fire.
Transmission loss increasing.
Shutting down...
Circuit has been isolated.
No abnormal over-voltage.
Power loss within acceptable range.
Circuit breakers operational.
Recovery in progress.
Positron canon.
Circuit cut-off nominal. No abnormalities
detected in intake overvoltage.
Safeties, operational,
proceed with operation.
At 0.019 %.
Final safety devise. Disabled!
Arm gun to fire!
Initiating final input
of sniping parameters.
Targeting scope calibration correction:
plus 0.0009.
The rangekeeper is autotracking target.
[Ibuki] Target Scope calibration complete.
[male PA] Positrons accelerating:
reaching firing threshold
in two seconds, one second.
Initiate final stage five
power connection.
[Hyuga] Route all energy to extreme
high-voltage discharge subsystem.
[male PA] Ready for full power influx.
[female PA] Proceeding
with final calibration of positron
acceleration chamber.
[Shinji] I don't have
Rei's courage and resolve.
I don't have much confidence
in piloting my Eva...
I don’t understand what I’m doing.
I’m just doing what I’m told to do.
Protecting humanity?
I can't even begin
to understand that responsibility.
So why me?
[Hyuga] Thirteen... Twelve... Eleven...
Ten... Nine...
Eight... Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Fire!
[blast]
[angel screaming]
We got it?
- No! We missed!
- Impossible! The timing was perfect!
High energy readings coming from target!
All personnel, brace for impact!
[angel screaming]
[explosion]
[alarm]
Energy systems, status report.
Systems operational!
Recharging is already underway.
Status of the Positron Cannon?
Still operational.
Initiating barrel cooling process.
But cannot verify
if another shot is possible...
Forget the diagnostics.
We have to do it anyway!
Shinji? Are you alright?
Hurry and get Unit One
back in firing position.
Shinji?
[Shinji gasping]
[efforts]
[Shinji crying]
[crying]
[Ikari] As of now,
Unit One pilot is relieved of duty.
Make Unit Zero's pilot the gunner.
But Ikari...
[Ikari] If he can't do the job,
we cut him off.
Please, delay that order!
He didn't run from piloting the Eva.
He should be left in charge
unless he wants out!
[Shinji strains]
[Tohji] And Shinji?
I'm counting on you.
[Kensuke] Ikari. Go get 'em.
[Misato] I'm begging you, sir.
Have faith in your son.
I assure you
I do have faith in him right now.
As you wish. You can carry on.
Thank you, sir.
- Shinji.
- Yes, ma'am.
We're going to entrust you
with all the energy produced in Japan.
With our hope, all humanity's future
and the future of all living things
that've survived...
It's all up to you, now.
- Go for it.
- Yes, ma'am.
[Hyuga] Cannon locked in position.
[Ibuki] Unit One,
removing Type G components.
Switching Fire Control Systems
to manual mode.
[drilling]
[Aoba] Enemy drill has breached
point zero, directly above HQ!
Ready the second shot now!
Fuse replaced!
Barrel cooling process complete!
[female PA] Power transmission systems...
[male PA] Ground crew evacuation complete.
Cooling subsystem pressure
is exceeding max limit.
[Ibuki] Final firing solution
data input complete.
Final adjustments entrusted
to pilot’s manual control.
[male PA] Firing threshold reached
in zero point two.
[Ibuki] High energy readings
from target again!
Damn it!
[gasps]
[explosion]
Shinji?
[efforts]
[explosion]
Ayanami!
[blast]
Shield is breaking up!
How long can it hold?
Twenty seconds!
[Shinji] Come on!
[Shinji] Come on! Come on!
Come on!
[angel screaming]
We did it!
[rain]
[crashing]
[crashing, broken glass]
Ayanami!
Ayanami?
[efforts]
[strains]
Ayanami!
Are you OK? Ayanami? Ayanami!
[sighs]
I never want to hear you say things like,
like: "This is all I have."
And I never want
to hear you say "farewell",
like we're never going
to see each other again.
[crying]
Shinji... Why are you crying?
I'm sorry.
But I don't know
how I should act at a time like this.
You could smile... that would be good.
[gasps]
[Kaworu] I know.
The boy down there has awakened,
and is now
in the generalization stage, right?
[Kiel] Yes.
The Dead Sea Scrolls Apocrypha have
been fulfilled up to the Book of Codes.
The time of the pact draws near.
Number three again?
You don't change, do you?
I'm looking forward to meeting you,
Shinji Ikari.
[end credits]
[Misato] Provisional Eva Unit Five
scrambles to action!
Eva Unit 02 and its pilot appear!
Eva Unit Four vanishes!
The forced activation test
of Eva Unit Three.
And Eva Unit Six and its pilot
descend from the Moon.
Our story unfolds and Shinji unravels.
How long can it last?
Don't miss: Evangelion two
point twenty-two!
Get ready for all that,
plus many surprises, coming up!