This seal won't
last much longer.
Sure won't.
[AZAZEL] Odin's gonna head back
up north to retrieve Mjolnir.
Says we'll need it
in the coming fight.
And while it's great that Ajuka
teleported Loki out of our hair,
he'll only be restrained
for about a day,
and you can bet he's gonna be
pissed when he gets back here.
One day? That's it?
[AZAZEL]
Yep, and when that happens,
we're not gonna have any choice
but to fight him head on.
Because if the Devil
King class members
elect to attack Loki outright,
it could result in another
large‐scale war,
which wouldn't be
good for anybody.
That's far too risky.
[AZAZEL] Plus, it would
play into Loki's hand.
He wants to bring
about Ragnarok,
and the Chaos Brigade
wants pandemonium.
A war like that would further
all of their goals.
It'd be the beginning
of the end, kiddos.
Nothing would survive.
If Loki gets out before
Mjolnir arrives, we're screwed.
Seems that way.
Yeah, I think we need
to go talk to my brother.
You want to act as a
diversion for Loki?
[AJUKA] I hope you understand
I can only teleport about
ten people at once.
That's not much.
I'll only be able to send
one or two more later.
You won't have reinforcements.
Yes, I'm well aware of
the danger involved.
That's really sweet. But, don't
think you're the only volunteer.
[door opens]
[RIAS gasps]
[LEVIATHAN]
Right, Sona?
[SONA] The three of
us would like to offer
our services in this as well.
If that's not a problem.
I tried to talk her out of it,
but she wouldn't listen.
Then again, this
whole mess with Loki
is kind of our fault
to begin with.
So our little sisters being
assigned clean up duty
shouldn't get much objection.
Won't look like we're playing
favorites, either.
It's not like there's
time to object anyway.
That said, there's two people
we've already decided on.
[MICHAEL]
Yes. The first one...
[MICHAEL] I have no doubt
she will be an asset
to you in this endeavor.
As you wish.
I will be in attendance
as well. For Asgard.
Since we all seem
to be in agreement,
prepare yourselves
to depart shortly.
Buy as much time
as you possibly can.
[RIAS] I'm sorry that we
can't bring you with us,
but it's just too dangerous.
You'll be safer here
with the defense force.
Oh, of course. Listen, Issei.
Please be careful,
and come back safe, okay?
Hey, don't worry about me.
You just focus on having fun
with the other devils, cool?
[ASIA]
Right.
This feels like old
times, doesn't it?
Yeah. Well, kind of, anyway.
It might seem weird coming from
a devil, but try to be careful.
I was about to say
the same thing to you!
[XENOVIA]
Huh?
[ROSSWEISSE] Guess I'll
introduce myself to the team.
[ROSSWEISSE] I should have known
things would get out of hand
traveling Odin. I'm the
Valkyrie Rossweisse.
[SAJI]
You seein' what I'm seein'?
That's one Valkyrie
I'd like to ride!
Business suit, suit of armor,
or birthday suit, I am down!
[ISSEI, SAJI groaning]
Would you look at the time.
Down boy.
Okay, kids. Just try to
be careful out there.
The time has come.
Right. These are Phoenix Tears.
Unfortunately, this is all
we could obtain on
such short notice.
[SIR ZECHS]
They may not look like much,
Especially since you won't have
a bishop's healing powers.
Thank you. That's a good idea.
Just remember to keep
your guard up out there.
[RIAS]
We will.
[KONEKO] I won't let
you leave me behind.
Won't let me?
That's not your call.
Please, I need to do this.
I'll allow it.
[KONEKO]
Hey, Blue Balls.
If I was scared, what
would you say to me?
[ISSEI]
That you're fine.
You're not alone
anymore, Koneko.
I'll be right there to protect
you if anything goes wrong.
I gotta say I'm
impressed, Issei.
she won't be able to deny
her feelings much longer.
Whoa! We're just friends!
Will you protect me?
I'll be counting on that resolve
of yours to get me through.
I won't let you down.
[AJUKA]
All right. Off you go.
[SAJI] I dunno 'bout you,
but I'm not diggin' this.
We just finished training,
and we're fighting a god?
That's nuts.
But still. I'm fightin'
for Sona here,
and there's no way I'm
gonna let her down.
[ISSEI]
I feel ya, man.
Sona wants to make a school
in the underworld.
A place where even low‐level
devils are welcome,
so they can play
the rating game.
Wow. That'd be cool. Although...
I don't get how that
has anything to do
with fighting Loki.
[SAJI]
A lot of devils hate her idea
because it goes against
the class system.
They're not big on
any kinda change.
[ISSEI] Guess there's no
rags‐to‐riches for devils.
[SAJI] Yeah, and mixing
with other mythologies
will only open even more minds.
If Loki has his way, her goal
doesn't have a chance in hell.
Don't pun me.
Anyway, I'd be down
for teaching kids at that
kinda school, y'know?
If you teach girls' gym.
[laughs] Maybe so,
but that's why I'm standing
in this nightmare right now.
I don't care if they're
a god or a stuck‐up devil.
I swear I'll own anyone
who gets in our way!
Yeah, and I'll be
right there with ya.
[RIAS]
He's coming!
[SAJI, ISSEI grunt]
[LOKI] Well, that was annoying.
Not to mention rude.
[ROSSWEISSE]
Hear me, Loki!
Attacking the All‐Father
is unforgivable!
you should file your complaint
through the proper channels!
[LOKI] And who will
"unforgive" me? You? Please.
Talented, though you may be,
you cannot challenge a god.
You were always
such a spoiled brat.
I was hoping for better in
the opening act of Ragnarok.
[ROSSWEISSE]
Fenrir!
And his runts Hati
and Skoll, too.
Could this get any worse?
[chuckles]
[RIAS]
The Midgard Serpent is worse.
It's one of the
Five Dragon Kings!
[IRINA] Did we plan on there
being legendary monsters?
No we didn't. Though, I really
should've known better.
[SAJI] Hey, guys!
We're surrounded, now!
[RIAS]
Will you suck it up?
Our families are counting
on us to keep Loki at bay,
so that is exactly what
we are going to do!
Touching sentiment, but I must
tell you it will never work.
[roars]
Yeah! It's time to put
our training to good use!
Rias!
[RIAS, SONA]
Mm.
[BOTH] Promotion to Queen!
Balance Breaker!
[DDRAIG]
Welsh Dragon Balance Breaker!
[LOKI] Oh, my, the
Red Dragon Emperor.
And yet I'm still
disappointed.
[ISSEI grunts]
[ISSEI]
Sticks and stones, dude.
Three weeks I trained
for crap like this,
and that's the best you've got?
[ISSEI groaning]
Look ou... Never mind.
[ISSEI screams]
[ISSEI sighs]
Thanks, you guys!
Hey, no problem at all.
Just leave this beast to the
knights! Let's go Durandal!
[KIBA]
Taste my Sword Birth!
[ISSEI] Man, Kiba and Xenovia
have gotten a lot stronger.
But so have I! Dragon Shot!
Down you go.
[RIAS] Figures we'd be left
with the biggest one.
[yells] Lightning!
[AKENO]
Pathetic, I barely did anything!
You know what they say about
playing with fire! Mirror Alice!
[SONA]
That's Tsubaki's Sacred Gear.
When the Mirror Alice
shatters from taking a hit,
it reflects the attack back at
the enemy with twice the power.
[RIAS]
Thanks for the heads up.
could spell big trouble for
an offensive team like mine.
[SONA] Desperate times.
Planned to save it for a game.
I see. Well then, I'm happy
to return the favor for you!
Well, as long as we're
feeling generous...
Okay, so it's resilient.
Good thing we're only
trying to buy time.
Cause beating this thing
is way out of our paygrade.
You're always such an optimist.
[ROSSWEISSE]
Don't underestimate these dogs.
Their bite is much
worse than their bark.
[IRINA]
That's what I wanted to hear.
No reason to hold back!
Irina! Remember,
you're still only human!
These guys have you outclassed!
I think you're mistaken.
How 'bout I show you...
the new me!
So that was unexpected.
[ISSEI]
Since when is she an angel?
It's kind of a long story.
All right, bad dog!
Now, by the blessing
of Lord Michael.
I have been reincarnated
as an angel to provide
divine retribution and holy
wrath, so repent! Amen!
[ROSSWEISSE grunts]
I guess these two
can't take a hit as
well as their dad!
Yay, me!
Did she say... "reincarnated?"
[ISSEI] Angel or not, she
hasn't changed one bit.
We'll take care of Fenrir,
you get the other mutt!
[ISSEI] It's you and me, Koneko.
We got this. Let's put him down!
[KONEKO]
Word.
They have done rather well
for a group of weaklings.
[gasps]
[SAJI] You underestimated us!
Big mistake!
[LOKI] The only thing big
is your talk, little boy.
[SAJI] You need to work
on your comebacks, man.
They're pretty lame.
[LOKI]
Noted.
Saji!
[ISSEI]
Saji! You bastard!
[KONEKO]
Pay attention!
[ISSEI gasps]
[KONEKO yells]
[KONEKO]
Meow.
[ISSEI]
Koneko.
[KONEKO] Don't worry,
I've got it under control.
I will master this power.
My fear will not define
who I am anymore.
You said you'd protect me.
[KONEKO]
But I can protect you, too!
I can do this!
[ISSEI yells]
[AKENO]
Wow. I never imagined Koneko
would become that strong
just by accepting herself.
Well, if she can
do it, so can I!
[AKENO] I am the daughter of
Shuri and Barkiel Himejima.
A fallen angel.
But also, I am the devil queen
of Rias Gremory. Akeno Himejima!
[ISSEI]
You can do it.
Thunderbolt!
[AKENO yells]
[RIAS]
You did it!
You finally put it behind you.
I'm so proud.
I smelled teenaged angst.
How disgustingly cliché.
Lord Loki. It isn't
too late to apologize.
The All‐Father may
still forgive you.
But before, you said
I was "unforgiveable".
And why should I be
the one to apologize
when he is clearly in the wrong?
You leave me no choice!
[LOKI grunts]
[SAJI]
I caught a big one!
‐‐[SANJI chuckles]
‐‐[SONA] Ha.
[ISSEI]
Saji! That was awesome!
I'm fightin' for
a school out here, man!
[ISSEI] It's that kind of talk
that makes you my best frenemy!
Oh, please.
This can't hold me.
But how? Why didn't it break?!
[SAJI] Azazel gave me an
upgrade this past month.
Now all the Vritra‐Type Sacred
Gears are at my disposal!
Ah. So, these are the Vritra
Dragon's dark flames.
And even a god can't shrug
off my cursed power
[SONA] Perhaps you should have
had higher expectations of us.
Just give it up, Loki.
[ISSEI]
Hot damn. I should have known
Azazel'd pull out all the stops.
All right! You're done!
[LOKI]
Such outstanding arrogance!
Lord Loki, stop!
Please, I beg you!
At this rate, you'll destroy
not only the underworld,
but the mythological
worlds as well!
[LOKI] Which is exactly
what I want, dear!
[ISSEI]
Rias!
[LOKI]
Ragnarok is coming.
This moment is what I've
been working toward
from the beginning.
How can he do this?
[ROSSWEISSE] He's strong
enough to do what he wants,
even destroy hell! He's a god!
[ISSEI]
What?
[screams]
Kiba, no!
[KIBA groans]
Dammit!
[LOKI] Oh, don't be like that.
This is the dawning of Ragnarok.
At least your lives will
have an epic finale!
[XENOVIA, KIBA scream]
‐‐[RIAS] Issei!
‐‐[ISSEI groaning]
[SONA]
Saji!
[LOKI]
And so it ends.
What could be a more fitting
reward for your efforts
than being the first of
Ragnarok's many sacrifices?
I expect you all feel honored.
Xenovia!
[ISSEI]
What a scumbag!
He's pounding us like
we're blow up dolls!
Let's take him. Sona, here.
Get the others back up.
Hey, what happened?
Loki made us his bitches.
You gonna take that?
Or you gonna get
back up and fight?
I'll fight... till my last
breath for what you want.
Thank you.
Uh! Wait a sec.
Did she just thank me?
I don't like that side of her.
Xenovia! Thank God!
Rather not. You want to
take this guy together?
Sounds like fun!
We'll be an unstoppable
Heaven‐and‐Hell combo!
What a surprise.
You're helping me?
It was by order of my mistress.
In this fight, I'll use
all the help I can get.
So how 'bout we take this to
the next level and team up?
It's not the worst plan
I've heard today.
You know, I can think of
much worse ways of dying.
At least I'll be by you.
[gasps]
You shouldn't say
things like that.
[ISSEI yells]
[LOKI]
Pathetic.
[RIAS] Reviving everyone used
all of the phoenix tears.
We won't survive another
of Loki's attacks.
[gasps] Yes, I understand!
I've got good news, guys!
[ISSEI]
The hell is that?
[ROSSWEISSE] It's the mighty
Thor's weapon of choice.
the god of thunder rains
down divine punishment.
[LOKI]
Mjolnir?!
[ROSSWEISSE]
Right. Odin sends a message.
Give Mjolnir to
"The Red Dragon Emperor.
He's the only one there
powerful enough to wield it."
[ISSEI]
No shit?!
I'll kill you all!
[SAJI]
Where you goin'?
All yours.
[ISSEI]
Badass!
It's hammer time!
[ISSEI yelps]
[ISSEI screams]
Issei, no!
[KIBA yells]
[ISSEI groaning]
[RIAS]
Issei!
[RIAS] Hang in there!
You'll be okay! Come on!
I'm... so sorry. I almost
had him. My bad... Rias.
I hope one day you'll
be able to forgive me
for letting you down like this.
Issei, please.
[ISSEI] You've gotta go.
Save yourselves.
No way! I'll help you, Issei.
You won't be alone.
I won't let you die here!
You're going to be okay. Issei!
The... hammer... [groans]
We need it.
[RIAS gasps]
No. He can't.
Did the pervert not make it?
[ROSSWEISSE yells]
[AKENO panting]
He can't be gone.
[RIAS] Wake up, Issei.
I told you to wake up!
Oh, Rias.
You're gonna die! Bastard!
[IRINA]
How dare you?
[KONEKO yells]
[KIBA yells]
[ROSSWEISSE]
He was the only one of us
strong enough to wield Mjolnir.
We don't stand a
chance without him.
Loki is going to kill us
for sure. I'm so useless.
No, please. Not him.
[groans]
[LOKI] None of you should
be getting this worked up.
After all, Ragnarok will
rejoin you with him soon.
I will not let you
die here alone.
How dare you, Loki? You monster.
You thought you could
take what's mine?!
[RIAS] I don't give a damn
about your Ragnarok.
I swear, even if the
world does end today...
And even if every last drop
of my blood boils away.
You will pay for
what you've done.
I will take you down with me!
[AKENO]
Mother, I want to be strong.
[ARTHUR] My name is
Arthur, of the Vali team.
Looks like you've
accepted you power.
Do you think this is
what he'd want? Stop!
I will develop a new
skill to bust out
in addition to Dress Break!