[AZAZEL] Mind if I ask
you a couple of questions?
I don't mean Issei.
I'm talking to you,
Welsh Dragon.
[SIR ZECHS] Still nothing?
That's unfortunate.
[AZAZEL]
Yeah, we haven't been able
to bring him out of his coma.
The kid's devil power
is replenishing,
and his body's
healing up all right.
It would seem that his
extent of his injuries
go deeper inside, though.
[SIR ZECHS]
Deeper inside?
[KIBA] He's never had such
an intense transformation.
Seems for now, our only
option is to wait it out.
Issei's suffering because
of me. I'm so sorry!
No one's blaming you.
This isn't your fault.
She's right, Asia.
Any blame goes to those
Chaos Brigade jerks!
[AZAZEL]
Hmm.
Huh. Hey Asia, I got a question.
[ASIA]
Uh‐huh?
[AZAZEL] You still haven't
done it yet, right?
I'm talking about what
you worked on in training.
[ASIA gasps]
[AZAZEL] Because of his
incomplete transformation,
it seems apparent that
the dragon inside of Issei
is malfunctioning.
The fact that his arm
is still in dragon form,
only serves to prove the point.
[RIAS] If that's the problem,
then how do we start fixing it?
[AZAZEL]
Asia's Sacred Gear
might present a solution
to our conundrum.
[RIAS]
Might is the operative word.
Will Asia be in any danger?
I honestly couldn't tell you.
No way!
It is a possibility,
but it's not inevitable.
[ASIA] I'll do it.
I at least have to try.
Are you sure Asia?
Issei promised he'd
always look out for me,
and he kept his word
by beating Diodora.
Now it's my turn
to look out for him,
and there's no way I'm
gonna just give up!
I owe him more than that.
[RIAS]
I have full faith in you.
Your training up to
this point has focused
on healing from a distance.
This time distance doesn't
matter, it's about depth.
[ASIA]
What do you mean?
[AZAZEL] Issei needs your
help healing the wound
deep in his heart.
Do you really think
it's a good idea
to leave Asia all
alone in there?
we have no way to determine how
powerful the force would be.
And as long as that's the case,
it's not safe to be
in the same area.
You're not gonna let her go
through with it, are you?
[RIAS] I'd be lying to
you if I said this
didn't scare me to death,
but it's my duty to trust Asia.
[ASIA]
My darling Issei.
I treasure you
above anyone else,
and you've always
been there for me.
[ASIA] Cheering me up
whenever I'm feeling down.
Put yourself in harm's way
to protect me from danger.
I'm so grateful for you.
And I thank God for this
opportunity he's given me.
I'm thankful for this chance
to pay you back
for all you've done.
[ASIA] So, please!
Please open your eyes!
Come back to me, Issei!
[ISSEI gasps]
[ISSEI]
Huh?
That's weird. Normally when
I wake up, Asia's not alone.
Hang on. What happened to
her shirt? Did I do that?
[gasps]
Is this a dream?
You're awake again!
Issei, I'm so sorry!
It's fine.
[ASIA] You're all right!
Thank goodness.
I was so worried.
[ISSEI] Wait, I was in a coma?
And you brought me out of it?
Thank you for saving my life.
[ASIA] I couldn't bear
the thought of my life
without you in it.
Now, come with me.
If you're feeling up to it.
Everyone's anxious to see you.
Of course. I feel like a
douche making everybody worry.
But first, Issei.
[ISSEI gasps]
I love you, Issei.
More than life itself.
I've never been so sure
of anything before.
[ISSEI]
Uh, uh, uh.
[AKENO giggling]
So passionate.
I feel bad walking in on
such a private moment.
Oh! Hey, guys!
Didn't notice you there.
It looks like Asia has won
today's battle for Issei.
Yes. It would seem that way.
[ISSEI laughs]
[ASIA giggles]
I'm serious though! I'm super
grateful for what you did!
[ASIA] No, Issei. Really,
there's no need to thank me.
[ISSEI] Of course
I'm gonna thank you.
Are you all right, Rias?
Of course. I'm fine.
Okay, everyone!
Now that Issei
has gotten better,
it's time to
celebrate with a feast!
[ALL]
Your wish is our command!
[SIR ZECHS] Our recent encounter
with the Chaos Brigade has made
one thing abundantly clear.
The Old Satan Faction
has fallen into ruin.
Apparently, Vali never
thought of them as comrades
in the first place.
Just a means to an end.
Great Red.
[AZAZEL] Orphis intends to kick
him out of the Dimensional Gap.
Thus, Vali's interests
lined up with hers.
As it stands now,
the lines between the
worlds remain stable,
and have done so ever since
Great Red was confined there.
But, if somehow he
were to be freed,
then the world as we
know it could be in jeopardy.
No matter the cost,
we can't let that happen.
When Loki attempted
to destroy time and space.
Perhaps a tiny fissure between
the worlds was created.
And that was
enough of a window
through which Great
Red could appear.
At least, this is
what Ajuka believes.
Loki, huh? A real pain in
the ass from beginning to end.
[LOKI] That accursed
Ouroboros bitch,
with her unnecessary meddling.
However...
[SOLDIER]
Huh? What's this?
[EVIL SPIRIT screams]
[LOKI] Certain options
are still available.
The kind you'll feel in
the marrow of your bones.
Red Dragon fool.
You and your beloved
Ruin Princess will suffer.
[ISSEI groans] It's so good
to finally be back home again!
[ISSEI] It's weird to think
I was asleep for three days.
I feel kinda bad you guys
missed school because of me.
I told the school that we would
be spending a few days overseas
for a practice match, so our
absence has been excused.
I'll just let them
know our return flight
was delayed due to
weather or something.
[ISSEI] So, your solution
to the problem is to lie.
What kind of occult club
even has practice matches?
The entire excuse was
predicated on a lie.
There are other
problems besides that.
[ROSSWEISSE sobs] It's no fair!
How could Lord Odin be so cruel?
I stupidly thought he returned
to take me back home,
and instead he sends me
into battle! I did it,
no complaints. And when
it was all over and done with?
He's gone back to Valhalla
and left boring old
Rossweisse behind!
[IRINA] He probably had a
load of admin to wade through
after such a mega conflict!
I'm sure he'll come back
‐‐soon to pick you up!
‐‐You don't get it!
and now he's returned to Asgard
without me there to escort him!
Then I'll be the ditzy valkyrie
who wasn't up to the task
‐‐All‐Father's bodyguard.
‐‐Hey, cheer up!
They're gonna
demote me for sure!
I felt terrible when I saw
Odin leaving her behind
in the underworld. I had no
choice but to bring her home.
If she's always
acting like this,
how can you really blame
old what's‐his‐beard?
Cuz right now she's
totally Queen Buzzkill.
She'll be fine. And if
the Asgardians decide
not to take her back,
I have an idea.
Like what?
Not yet! Uh‐uh!
[ROSSWEISSE sobs]
Asia, how are you feeling?
Fine!
[RIAS]
It's so strange.
I'm thankful that Asia was
able to help Issei get better.
[IRINA, AKENO giggle]
[RIAS] But for the
briefest moment, jealousy?
[ASIA laughs]
[RIAS]
What's wrong with me?
[ISSEI, ASIA]
In‐Out! In‐Out! In‐Out!
Nicely done. Lookin' good!
[ISSEI sighs]
Now, let's take a little break!
Sure. Great!
[AZAZEL]
Hey, kid!
[ISSEI]
Huh?
that really help remind you
what's worth fighting for.
I guess. Is that it?
While you were unconscious,
I had a nice little chat.
Went through a few things with
your buddy living inside you.
Inside me? Y'mean Ddraig?
The same.
[DDRAIG]
What does the Governor‐General
of fallen angels want from me?
[AZAZEL] I needed to
ask you about the power
Issei released at
the end of the fight.
[DDRAIG] It was a skill that
until now had remained dormant.
A volatile technique
called Juggernaut Drive.
[AZAZEL] That maneuver
is expressly forbidden.
It's dangerous
to forcefully vent
the power sealed in
a sacred treasure.
[DDRAIG]
Yes, and when activated
it will temporarily give
the user enough power
to make the gods envious. But
the price is the user's death,
or a drastically reduced
lifespan, at the least.
Swear to me! Promise
that you won't tell Asia
any of that, no matter
what happens!
I'm wondering how
you were even able
without knowing it was in your
wheelhouse in the first place.
[DDRAIG]
My partner's despair and anger
surpassed their critical limits,
and Juggernaut Drive was on
the other side of the threshold.
[AZAZEL]
Hm?
[DDRAIG] Some outside force
was controlling Issei's
emotions at the time. Who or
what it was, I'm uncertain.
[ISSEI] Outside force?
What'd he mean?
[AZAZEL] So you don't know
what he was talking about?
[ISSEI]
No. Not a clue.
[AZAZEL]
That's what I thought.
[ISSEI]
Hmm. What now?
Try not to worry
about it too much.
[ROSSWEISSE] Rias was
kind enough to give me
a place to stay
sans rent, but I refuse
to lounge around
like a freeloader.
I can help keep the
place tidy as thanks.
What? This is from Valhalla?
Oh, yay! He finally
came to pick me up!
I wonder where Koneko is.
It's not like her to be late.
I hope nothing's wrong!
[GASPER gasps]
What's up, Issei!
[RIAS sighs]
[ISSEI]
Hey, gorgeous!
[RIAS]
Huh?
I wasn't expecting you.
Have you finished practicing
for the festival?
[ISSEI] Yup. I swung
by to pick up my bag.
Ah. I hadn't realized
it had gotten so late.
And what's keeping
you here after hours?
Nothing important.
[ISSEI] You seem like you're
worried about something.
[RIAS scoffs] What have
I got to worry about?
Don't know. That's why
I asked, but sometimes,
I think I see depression
masked by beauty.
Uh. I'm sorry about that.
I just made things weird.
No. If anything, I find your
concern to be quite touching.
But I promise, I'm fine.
[ISSEI chuckles]
And look,
I know I'm not exactly
Dear Abby and junk.
[RIAS gasps]
I don't want you to feel
you have to force things.
I know what's going on.
Even if it means you
have to lie to yourself,
you always try so
hard, don't you?
You don't need to worry
about these problems anymore.
[RIAS gasps]
That's right. Let it go.
I'll take over from here.
[ASIA, ISSEI]
Out‐In, Out‐In, Out‐In, Out...
Looks like we've got the
rhythm part figured out!
I know! That extra
training really paid off!
Now let's try crankin'
up the pace!
I left the stupid stopwatch
in the club room. Hold still.
I'm gonna go grab it.
[ISSEI]
Hey, Koneko!
Hi, Issei.
[KONEKO]
I came to pick up Gaspie
and take him to the
bread eating race.
[ISSEI laughs] That little
dude's gonna freakin' explode!
[ISSEI]
Gasper!
[KONEKO]
Gaspie!
[ISSEI]
What happened to you?
[GASPER]
Issei. Thank goodness.
It's you, isn't it?
The real one?
[ISSEI]
What're talking about?
I can smell him.
[ISSEI, KONEKO gasp]
[ISSEI]
It's me!
Well, it's not, but
you know what I mean.
Why're you pretending
to be me, you dillhole!
‐‐Get a life!
‐‐Be careful! He's dangerous!
[RIAS chuckles]
[gasps, yells]
[KONEKO, ISSEI grunt]
[ISSEI grunts]
Rias, don't.
Come on! You've gotta snap out
of it! That guy! He's a faker!
[RIAS sighs]
[gasps]
Huh.
[ISSEI]
Rias.
No. Wake up!
[ISSEI grunts]
[XENOVIA, IRINA gasp]
[ASIA gasps]
[KIBA gasps]
I wasn't fast enough!
[STUDENT B] But, what? There
wasn't even anything explosive
[TSUBAKI] Please stand back.
It could continue.
Issei, what happened back there?
We're still not clear on any of
the details. But, thank Gasper.
He was able to stop time
right before the explosion
and pulled the two of
you out here to safety.
Thanks a lot, Gaspie.
[XENOVIA]
We're proud of you!
[SONA] I'm ashamed
that something like this
could transpire
on school property.
[SONA gasps]
Where's Rias?
[KONEKO grunts]
Damn it!
[GASPER]
Azazel!
[AZAZEL] Valhalla sent an
emergency message to Rossweisse.
Loki was responsible.
That sneaky bitch.
So, now we've got a
fake Issei in the mix?
It's true. I saw.
He was an exact double.
His aura and scent were both
practically
identical to Issei's.
His scent?
[KONEKO] If the real
Issei wasn't standing
right in front of me when
I saw his doppelganger,
I wouldn't have even
noticed the difference.
How can you be so certain that
Loki was responsible
for the attack?
Because, the cocky little
prick took credit for it.
You're telling me you placed
a curse on Rias Gremory
and the Red Dragon Emperor?
[LOKI] I lost to the dragon boy
due to last minute interference.
Luckily for me, I'm the kind of
fellow who thinks on his feet.
And with my new plan in tow,
I thought it the right time for
the prodigal son to return.
You impudent brat. Did you
choose to attack children
because you're no match
for Sir Zechs or myself?
Come, brazen old fool, think.
I am a proud Norse god.
Why would I waste my energy
doling out vengeance
on a few young devils?
What are you planning,
you self‐righteous bastard?
[LOKI laughs]
It's already too late.
The twilight of the gods
is fast approaching.
But, the reason I placed a
curse on those two children
couldn't be simpler. The devil
king sent his own little sister
to fight his battle for him.
Then you placed Mjolnir,
along with your hopes, into the
hands of her oafish consort.
And you shall reap the harvest
of the poor choices you've sown!
Loki!
[AZAZEL]
When he had finished speaking,
he placed a magical
barrier over himself.
The act of a true coward!
Sometimes the psychological
approach can be more effective
than merely defeating
an enemy in combat.
I suffered with
it for a long time.
But, I still don't really
understand why Loki
would go through
all this trouble.
He wants the twilight of
the gods. Ragnarok.
The ultimate end to
existence as we know it.
Excuse me, but where's Issei?
[AZAZEL] Rossweisse is
debriefing him upstairs.
[ISSEI]
A curse?
Apparently, he was able to
place a curse on you and Rias
before being taken into custody.
[ISSEI]
But, what does that mean?
Curses lay siege
to a person's heart,
gnawing away at
it piece by piece.
They cling to doubts lingering
in the depths of your soul.
Doubts you've forgotten about,
or worse,
doubts you never even realized
you had in the first place.
Loki used those buried
feelings against you.
[gasps]
Have you remembered something?
[ISSEI]
Yeah, one of my deepest fears.
[ROSSWEISSE gasps]
[ISSEI]
It's true. I'm scared.
Afraid of finding out what
the girls really feel about me.
It's not that I don't
believe them. It's just.
I've been burned before.
We're here for you, but if
you're not ready to talk,
there's no pressure.
Sorry. I can't.
No, I should be the
one to apologize.
But, I was following orders
to confirm the veracity
of Loki's words,
and they ring true.
But wait, you said Rias
was cursed as well.
How could someone
like her have any doubts?
You would have
to ask her directly
if you wished to find out.
Or, the doubt could be buried
so deep within Rias's psyche,
she doesn't even
realize it's there.
[ISSEI sighs]
[ISSEI] With the graceful
way she carries herself,
and eyes that pierce your soul.
She's the smartest,
most beautiful girl
in the entire school.
How could any doubt
live in the heart
of someone so
absolutely perfect?
I have to help her.
[AZAZEL] How're you
holding up, Sir Zechs?
[SIR ZECHS]
I am the devil king first,
and a concerned brother second.
I will conduct myself according
to my station in this matter.
[AZAZEL] Glad you're
keeping a clear head.
[SIR ZECHS] Per our last
message from Asgard,
it will be a rather long time
for them to break through
Loki's barrier; which is
a luxury we don't have.
[AZAZEL]
We just need to get him to talk.
Find out exactly where
Rias has been moved.
My sources say she's been
taken to the Dimensional Gap.
Dimensional Gap?
Isn't that where Asia
was sent by Diodora?
I have searched the kingdoms
of gods and devils alike.
It is the only
remaining possibility.
[XENOVIA]
So, if we can get there,
we should be able to
save Rias, right?
doesn't behave according to
our laws of time and space.
If Vali hadn't stumbled across
Asia at that precise moment
while traveling, we could
have lost her in there forever.
[AZAZEL] Simply put,
being thrust into the Gap
is more often than
not a death sentence.
Then, how are Vali and
his friends able to do it?
[AZAZEL] The Chaos Brigade
is a diverse assortment
with members from all factions.
They must be using a method
still unknown to our coalition.
It could be possible. We'd have
to lock existence on this plane.
We could use this world
as a beacon of sorts.
Koneko.
[ISSEI] We don't have a choice.
I need to contact your sister.
Do you need Kuroka
for some kind of plan?
To go see Vali. Now.
[VALI] The ones involved
with the red or white dragon
have never had a good life.
Don't you believe this
to be destiny as well?
Who cares! Destiny shmestiny.
I do what I want.
I'll just change it if it
doesn't work out for me.
Rias! Is that really you?