[MALE FIGHTER yells]
Damn you!
If this is it, then you
can bet your balls
‐‐I'm going out swinging!
‐‐[SAIRAORG] Then bring it on.
Bastard!
He blocked it?!
It's my turn, now.
[ZEPHYRDOR grunts]
[SAIRAORG grunts]
[ZEPHYRDOR screams]
[SAIRAORG yells]
[ISSEI]
Holy crap balls.
They say he's the strongest
devil in the Rating Game.
Zephyrdor's power was
ranked almost as highly.
He's done quite well
stepping in as a substitute.
[RIAS] The first heir to his
house died in an accident.
[RIAS, AKENO gasp]
A magic circle?
Astaroth, of course.
[ISSEI]
Huh?
Salutations, everyone.
How lovely to see you all again.
[ASIA gasps]
Shall we proceed to business?
I'd like to offer a
bishop trade, Lady Gremory.
No! Please! I don't
want him to take me!
[ISSEI]
Heh. He's comin' for ya, dude.
[RIAS] You want to trade
for Asia, you mean.
[DIODORA chuckles]
Am I really that transparent?
I can assure you,
it's a fair exchange.
‐‐and will serve you well‐‐
‐‐[RIAS] I'll stop you there.
Your offer is rejected.
Asia is not only a valuable
member of my peerage.
I also think of her as the
little sister I never had.
Using a roster trade to try and
get the woman who turned down
your marriage proposal shows me
that you're not only uncouth,
but have no idea what she wants.
[ISSEI]
Damn, Rias isn't holding back.
Can't blame her though.
I hate this guy!
How very disappointing.
You didn't find my
offer acceptable today,
but I won't let
that dissuade me.
[DIODORA] Our meeting and
reunion were both predestined.
Even if all the forces in the
underworld stood in our way,
I would do anything necessary
to overcome them all.
I'll never give up.
I love you, Asia.
[ISSEI]
Get your damn hands off her!
‐‐[DIODORA grunts]
‐‐[ISSEI gasps]
Baseborn should
know their place.
I can't stand being touched by
a filthy dragon
such as yourself.
Revolting.
You dick!
[ASIA gasps]
I refuse to sit here and
let you talk to Issei that way.
Yes, I understand. My apologies.
This isn't over,
Red Dragon Emperor.
We'll pick up where we left
off in the next Rating Game.
And once I've defeated him,
I hope you'll accept
my love, darling.
You ain't gonna beat me.
Dildo‐ra Ass‐to‐mouth!
I'll show you the kind of badass
power this filthy dragon's got!
Then I'm gonna
jumpstart your face!
Issei and Koneko
haven't come back yet.
Are they still out
fulfilling contracts?
We had some last
minute requests.
Being a devil seems
like a lot of work.
Hey, where's Rias?
[AKENO]
She's holed up in her room,
plotting out a strategy for
our approach in the
next Rating Game.
Asia, there's no
reason to get worried.
Just remember that Issei
will be there to protect you.
Right. Fortunately, Issei's
there to look out for all of us.
Yes, of course. He always does.
What gives? I never
would have guessed
a bunch of girls would
trust him so much.
We're here now
because of Issei.
He even allowed us to
share his home with him.
That's true. I feel bad
we haven't actually
thanked him for all the
kind things he's done.
Then what are you waiting for?
Let's thank him!
[ALL]
Huh?
[ISSEI]
Cool! Have a good one!
That was one of the weirder
pacts I've done so far,
but at least he wasn't handsy.
It doesn't seem normal
for a guy that age
to own that many puppets.
I'm sorry it's so late.
Even though I've been able
to jump through magic
circles for a while,
everybody seems more comfortable
with me swinging by on my bike.
It's cool. Plus, it was a nice
night for a ride, anyway.
Issei, something's wrong!
‐‐[ISSEI gasps]
‐‐Can you sense it?
‐‐[KUROKA] Long time no see.
‐‐[KONEKO gasps]
[KONEKO]
Hello, Kuroka.
Come on! No means no, lady!
[KUROKA giggles]
Your face looks like
less of a little bitch,
since the last time I saw it.
Is that because you've
achieved Balance Breaker?
Or, did you finally grow
a pair and get lucky?
Uh... The first option I guess.
Mmm. Yeah. You definitely
still taste like a virgin.
[ISSEI] Ya don't have
to say shit out loud!
Hey! So, uh, you wanna change
that status with me sometime?
[ISSEI gasps]
I wouldn't mind having brats
with that kind of strength.
There is no way I'm
letting that happen.
If he wants to stay a virgin,
that's 50% up to him.
if that's the kind of
thing you're looking for?
[VALI]
Because I turned her down.
[ISSEI]
Oh, shit!
Ha! I think somebody's
itching for a fight.
You're the one who unleashed
Loki on us, you asswipe!
Loki's attack was just
him doing his thing.
And that wasn't the first time
I've been called an escort.
If anything, you should
be thanking us.
We took Fenrir out of the
equation, if you recall.
[VALI] I heard you'll be
participating in a Rating Game.
And your opponent is the
heir to the Astaroth family.
[VALI] I wouldn't let my
guard down around him.
Wait, what?
but I wonder if your mistress
will heed my warning.
At the very least, I thought
I'd caution a fellow dragon.
[AKENO]
He's back!
Welcome home, Issei!
Hey. That outfit.
What's going on?
Oh, no! Don't you like it?
[ISSEI] Of course!
It's the freakin' best!
[ASIA] Welcome home, Issei.
We put these on for you.
[XENOVIA]
Yes. Welcome home, Issei.
[laughs]
Am I dreaming?
[IRINA]
It was actually all my idea.
We wanted to show you how
much we appreciate you.
Irana?
[IRINA]
But of course, as an angel,
I didn't expect things
to get this extreme.
Should it just be a flagrant
display of nubile flesh?
Or, should we make it a
touching moment to cherish?
Sexy see‐through outfits?
Give me sight beyond sight!
[IRINA] Looks like they knew
exactly what to get you.
[RIAS] What's going on
down there, you guys?
Oh, hi there, Rias.
We're making Issei happy
to show how thankful
we are for him.
[ISSEI gasps]
[RIAS]
Hmph.
[ISSEI]
Wait. Am I in trouble?
Do you think she got upset
about being left out?
[ISSEI]
I'll go up and check on her.
Uh, she's fine!
So how 'bout it, Issei?
Don't you think this
looks amazing on me?
Yes! Without a doubt!
I'm well aware of your
personal proclivities,
wouldn't you agree?
[AKENO grunts]
Presto change‐o
bikini technique!
You don't think you've won yet?
Be honest. Your imagination
is pretty weak,
so you like clothes that
leave very little to it.
[ISSEI]
Uh‐huh. Uh‐huh.
Good. Put your finger up.
Good. Put my finger up.
[AKENO giggles]
[ISSEI gasping]
Jackpot! This is the best!
That's good. Just like that.
Sweet! Squishy‐Time Jamboree!
[ISSEI]
Huh? Uh... Huh?
Oh, yes! When you touch my
breast I get hot all over.
There. Feel my heartbeat.
I'm never going to give him up.
[AKENO]
Same goes for me!
Issei's way more into the
size of my girls than yours!
Issei prefers the gentle sloping
of my snowy peaks, got it?
[AKENO] So not true, and you
sound ridiculous, bdubs.
[RIAS] This from the
girl who says "bdubs."
[ASIA]
Well, that escalated quickly.
[XENOVIA]
Yeah, but we're too smart
to try and get between them.
[KONEKO]
Hey Issei?
[ISSEI]
Huh?
[ISSEI gasps]
So many mixed emotions!
This is not like you!
Meow!
Seriously. Akeno can
be such a pain.
[ISSEI] I'm sorry.
It was all because of me.
It was actually the perfect
way to relieve a little stress.
However, Vali is
a different matter.
Coming and going as he
pleases in my territory.
[ISSEI] I know he wasn't
trying to start any trouble.
He even told me to cool my jets.
Be that as it may, I still need
to send the report up the chain.
I certainly don't intend to
trust Vali completely in this,
but there's something
about Diodora's attitude
that doesn't sit well with me.
I don't care how strong
he's supposed to be.
He wants to take Asia away.
It won't happen.
I refuse to let it!
Huh?
You feel responsible for
bringing Asia into this world.
Blaming yourself
changes nothing.
Plus, Asia told me how happy she
is to be living here with us.
I'm glad she sees
things that way,
but then I think about
everything that she lost and...
Well, that means one thing.
We're all going to have
to work to make sure
she has the happiness
she deserves.
Of course, I hope the same
for the rest of the household.
You especially.
[ISSEI]
Thanks, Rias.
That's why we should
cherish moments like these.
[RIAS]
Oh, I almost forgot!
The TV studio of the underworld
sent a request for you to
make a guest appearance.
An appearance?
Why would they want me?
It won't happen until sometime
after tomorrow's Rating Game.
So, let's focus all of
our energy on winning that,
Right on! Let's kick ass!
[SHALBA] I was hoping
both Sir Zechs and Odin
would be eliminated during
Loki's brazen assault.
It would seem a
heathen god has limits.
But, Loki's one of the major
deities in the Nordic religion;
which means whoever
took him out of the fight
‐‐is not one to be trifled with.
‐‐[ISSEI humming]
Huh?
[XENOVIA grunting]
[panting]
Just stepped out of the bath
and saw the lights on.
A little last minute training.
[ISSEI] You were really tearing
it up in here this morning, too.
I had to. I'm not
as strong as Kiba.
but Kiba's got a lot more talent
at sword‐fighting than I do.
The way I see it, you and
Kiba are both total asskickers!
[gasps]
That means a lot to me.
Booyah!
Ascalon!
[DDRAIG]
Blade!
[XENOVIA gasps]
[ISSEI]
Use it.
It may not be as badass
a sword as Durandal is,
but you'll use it
better than I will.
[XENOVIA]
Are you sure?
Yeah.
If you need it, ask me anytime.
We're all part of Team Awesome.
Yeah, got it.
Hey. One day you'll leave
the Occult Research Club
and head out on your own.
To try and reach the top?
Yeah. I'll have to someday.
[ISSEI] I want Rias to see me as
a man worthy of being with her,
not just a boy she saved.
[XENOVIA] Asia said that
she would follow you
Yeah. We promised each other
we'd always be together.
In that case, when you go,
take me as well.
What? Seriously?
My life's more interesting
when you're in it.
Yeah, I'm pretty cool. Heh.
'Kay. I'll let you know
when the time comes.
I'm really glad you
walked by when you did.
Just talking to you has
already helped calm my nerves.
[ISSEI gasps]
That was a thank you. Would you
have preferred it on the lips?
[ISSEI] No! It's fine! Gesture
of appreciation fully received!
[ISSEI]
Bye, now! Have a good night!
I was not expecting that.
[giggles]
[ASIA]
Hi, Issei!
[yelps]
[ISSEI]
Hey, girls. What's up?
We've been waiting
for you in bed.
[ISSEI] I was talking
to Xenovia downstairs.
She's been practicing
for the fight all day.
If we lose the game, I just
want you to know that, um‐‐
[KONEKO] Let Diodora say what
he wants. There's no way in hell
we're handing you over
to that weirdo loser.
‐‐Thanks, Koneko.
‐‐Look at me, Asia.
Don't even think about losing.
We're definitely dishing
out an Astaroth beatdown.
So, let's go show that
Rating Game who's boss.
Then, we'll win that
three‐legged race
while we're on our
kickass victory streak!
Let's do it!
[AZAZEL] Sorry for
calling so late, Sir Zechs.
It's about the
accidental death
of the heir to the
Glasya‐Labolas family
and the sudden
unexplained increase
in Diodora Astaroth's
devil power.
[SIR ZECHS] You think
they're related, after all.
[SIR ZECHS] I see.
Then perhaps Rias's report
on Vali's warning factors
into this somehow;
which, of course, assumes
it isn't disinformation.
Or, maybe they're not as
unified as we first assumed.
[SIR ZECHS]
I see no other options.
Prepare to set your
plan into motion.
Both Michael and old man Odin
are on board with us as well.
Though, I'm not very proud
of using those kids this way.
[ROSSWEISSE]
Have a good trip.
[IRINA]
Just do your best!
[AZAZEL] Well, then.
We should head out ourselves.
because Lord Michael gave me
a direct order to work with you.
But, why are we keeping
our involvement a secret?
we just showed up as a surprise
to cheer our friends on.
If something does happen,
then bam, we can make
it right by being there.
[ISSEI]
Whoa. That's metal.
[KIBA] Is this where
they expect us to fight?
The referee should have
announced our arrival by now.
But, what if there's been
some kind of problem?
[ASIA gasps]
[ASIA]
A magic circle!
[RIAS] That's not the crest
of Astaroth. Be on your guard!
[ISSEI]
Boosted Gear!
[DDRAIG]
Boost!
[KIBA, XENOVIA grunt]
[KONEKO]
Nyah.
[AKENO yells]
If memory serves, I've seen
that crest somewhere before.
[DEVIL SOLDIERS growling]
[RIAS] Those devils are loyal
to the Old Satan Faction
of the Chaos Brigade.
So, you're saying
they're terrorists?
[SOLDIER A]
To the despicable usurpers
in the false royal
house of Gremory,
we're here to take
back what's ours!
[ISSEI] Where the hell
did these guys come from?
‐‐[ASIA yells]
‐‐[ISSEI gasps]
[ISSEI]
Asia!
Diodora!
Greetings. Asia Argento
will be coming with me.
[ISSEI] What're you doing
to her, you douchebag?
[RIAS]
I demand an explanation!
These devils of
the Chaos Brigade
have come to murder
every last one of you.
Is that sufficient enough?
[AKENO] So, you've allied
yourself to lowly criminals.
You traitorous dog!
First, you've defiled the
sanctity of the Rating Game,
which alone deserves death.
And second, you laid your
filthy hands on Asia!
Well, if you want to
do something about it,
you'll have to fight
through all my friends.
I'll be taking my time getting
to know this little creature.
Biblically.
How's that sound, Dragon?
[growls]
[All grunting]
Issei! Pass me Ascalon!
[ISSEI]
Right!
Ascalon!
[XENOVIA grunts]
[XENOVIA]
Asia is my friend, creeper!
I won't let you
get away with this!
[DIODORA giggles]
[gasps]
[XENOVIA]
Coward!
[DIODORA laughs]
[ISSIE]
Asia!
[ISSEI]
Dammit!
Asia, I've failed you again.
I'm so sorry. I let you down!
[KIBA]
Snap out of it!
Focus on the enemies
in front of us first!
Then, we'll go give
Diodora a beat down!
One step at a time.
You're right. Let's do this.
I'm not sure if Akeno and I
can take this many at once.
[AKENO yelps]
[ODIN]
Mmm. That's a sweet piece!
[AKENO]
Um, uh?
These cheeks alone were a good
enough reason to tag along.
Hey, it's that guy.
Lord Odin!
What're you doing here?
[ODIN laughs] We discovered
that Diodora Astaroth
has been making deals behind
everyone's backs for a while.
I'm the great All‐Father
of the Norse gods!
Whoever can take my head will
become a warrior of legend!
[DEVIL SOLDIERS yell]
[ODIN chuckles]
That brat Azazel's plan
was brilliant in its
sheer simplicity.
Lure them in, and take them
all down in one fell swoop.
[AKENO]
So, what does this mean?
It means instead of
fighting a Rating Game,
we were brought here as bait.
I'll hold the frontlines while
you kids make your escape.
Besides, I'm aching
for a good fight!
We can't leave you here
to face them alone!
A pup who hasn't
seen two decades
is a thousand years too young to
worry about a warrior like me!
Come forth, Gungnir!
[DEVIL SOLDIERS scream]
[ISSEI]
I gotta get one of those!
[ODIN laughs]
[RIAS] Lord Odin,
we shall take advantage
of your generous
offer immediately.
[ODIN] Excellent. Once you're
all out of harm's way,
I can really cut
loose on these vermin.
Let's double‐time
it to the temple!
[ALL]
Double‐time it. Understood!
[ISSEI]
Azazel! What the hell?
[AZAZEL] You can gripe
at me all you want later.
For now, shut up.
They're all over the Game field,
and swarming
around the VIP room.
The Old Satan faction is
pressing a full‐scale attack!
Fortunately, we have
a contingency plan.
[RIAS] What kind of contingency
are we talking about?
We've sprung ambushes
all over the area.
The fools walked
right into our trap.
I had to leave you
all in the dark
or risk having Astaroth
become aware of our plan.
[GASPER] But, what if
something had happened?
Any one of us could have
gotten hurt or killed!
[AZAZEL] As the
strategist of this battle,
I would take
full responsibility.
If you still want to take
your anger out on me
when this is finished, then
my life is yours in payment.
[gasps]
[XENOVIA] Then you've
prepared yourself for death.
The point is, stay hidden
until this battle's over.
Just let the rest of us deal
with these terrorist scumbags.
[KIBA] Then that means you're
on the battlefield, too?
[SAIRAORG yells]
But, the zone is huge, so I'm
pretty far away from you kids.
But, we can't run and hide,
don't you understand!
As long as Diodora has Asia,
I'm not going anywhere!
He took Asia away and
we're gonna go save her.
We can't just let him have
his way! She's our friend.
She's like family!
I swore to her we'd never
be apart ever again!
We will go find
and rescue Asia.
We won't stop until
we have her back,
and have Astaroth's
head on a pike
as an example to any who
would harm my household.
Excellent! Just as I've
come to expect, Gremory.
I'd be glad to clear
out the way for you.
Now go rampage your hearts out!
Oh, hell yeah!
Thanks, Azazel. Not that
we needed your permission.
[AZAZEL]
Listen up, kid!
You show that betraying bastard
the power of the
Red Dragon Emperor!
And pop him once in the
mouth for me, all right?
[ISSEI]
Deal!
I ate 'em both. They were
finger‐lickin' good!
[DIODORA'S QUEEN] I demand
you stop this nonsense!
You ignore me and fight
amongst yourselves over a boy?
I'll come to you.
Horny thoughts, release!
Max Imagery, go!
You won't get away with this.
It worked!