Boobs!
Issei.
Ooh! Issei.
Hi, Issei.
Hello, Issei.
[ISSEI blusters] It's like
a rack‐centric smorgasbord!
I don't know where to start!
[RIAS] Why don't you start
with something prime?
Touch and squeeze all you want.
Don't forget these!
Let me be your second course.
I can cater to all of your
depraved appetites!
Please, go on.
I can do it if I close my eyes.
But it feels so embarrassing!
Don't get carried away,
but you can touch them.
Then they're going to be
used to feed our babies!
Well okay, this is
my kind of dilemma!
[FEMALE VOICE] Uh, would
you please go out with me?
[ISSEI]
Of course. Why wouldn't I?
[ISSEI thinking]
Wait, whose voice was that?
[FEMALE VOICE]
You're so cruel.
Have you forgotten?
You and I dated once.
[ISSEI thinking]
What the crap? Yuma?
[YUMA]
Yuma. It means "dusk."
because that's when
I planned to kill you.
The perfect time for death.
Would you die for me, Issei?
[gasps]
[ISSEI sigshs]
That's weird. I haven't
thought of her in forever.
[giggles] Morning, you!
Uh... Hey, Akeno.
Hello, handsome.
[AKENO moans softly]
[AKENO]
Does my body feel nice?
Pressed up against yours?
[ISSEI] Uh‐huh.
As if you had to ask.
[AKENO]
Of course. I like it too.
I think we should get to
know each other even better.
[ISSEI thinking]
Know each other even better?
At this point, there's only
two ways to make that happen.
And I don't have an X‐ray
machine, so that can only mean.
[RIAS]
Akeno!
Care to explain how you
ended up in Issei's room?
[ISSEI]
Morning?
I'm just trying to
develop an intimate bond
with my cute little Issei here.
[RIAS]
"My Issei"?
And when exactly did you
become the master of his soul?
[AKENO] I'm not his master,
but I am his senior.
It's my duty as an upperclassman
to take care of him.
Clever girl. But alas,
you've exposed yourself.
Exposed...!
Just five more minutes, 'kay?
We've still got plenty of time
to stay here in bed, Asia.
Good.
Then I'm going to
snuggle up closer to you for
a little bit longer, if that's
not too much to ask, Issei.
Nighty night.
[sighs]
I'm getting tired of you trying
to put your greedy hands
on what is rightfully mine!
A taste here and there
doesn't hurt anyone.
Now stop being so stingy!
[RIAS] And we just finished
remodeling the house!
Your behavior is
unacceptable! Yah!
Nice try... Not!
[ISSEI] Come on girls.
Pump the brakes! Just Relax!
Wait, you remodeled? Huh?!
When the hell did this happen?!
Yeah. I'd say I was surprised.
to find a six‐story palace
with three basements.
I never even had a
clue that Rias's father
was some kind of big‐deal
construction magnate.
He transformed our home
into a Tony Montana wet dream,
[MOTHER] And I can't
believe we slept through
the entire
remodeling process, too.
Talk about convenient!
The kitchen is so big now,
with plenty of room
to move around.
It's spacious enough for a few
other activities, eh honey?
[MOTHER] Stop that,
you old letch you!
I'd be glad to help you out!
Somehow, devil power
fades in comparison
to my mom and dad's ability
to roll with the punches.
[ASIA]
We're off for school!
The remodeling has really put
some bounce in our steps!
[ISSEI thinking]
Not just your steps!
I'm still psyched that we
expanded to make room
for such a sexy
stable of babeage!
[gasps]
[thinking]
Why her? After so long?
Is something wrong?
Hehe! Everything's fine.
[ISSEI] Asia!
Asia, I want you to know
I'll do whatever it
takes to protect you,
no matter what it may cost me!
[ASIA]
Oh. Thank you, Issei.
That's very sweet.
[AKENO] My, my...
You're still feeling feisty
after everything we
shared this morning?
My mind was wandering,
thinking of some strange stuff.
[XENOVIA]
Strange? Like making babies?
In fact, nothing could be
further from the truth.
It's still too early
in the morning to put up
with this pervert's stupidity.
Wow. I'm standing right here.
Come on, we can all
keep making fun of Issei
Don't worry, you can still try
to manipulate Asia's feelings
on the walk to school, okay?
I'm trying to bend all of
your feelings to my will!
But for you, Big Red,
I would sacrifice my very life!
I know you would.
You've already
proven that to me.
[AKENO] Pick up the pace,
Shogun of Harlem.
Otherwise we'll be
late for school.
Yeah, Akeno's right.
Let's get going, Asia!
[ISSEI]
Wait up!
[RIAS thinking]
How strange.
I've never been
the jealous type.
But seeing him
hold her like that.
Suddenly, it feels like,
like he's so far away.
So dish. I bet you've got
lots of cool things planned out
I've never had such
a long break before,
so I'm feeling
kind of unprepared.
Me too. I also don't
know what I'll do.
OMG, I'm the same way.
But this is your first
summer off ever, right?
Last day of school,
you jive‐ass suckahs!
And you guys know what
that means:
Sexy summertime!
Babes in bikinis at
the beaches and pools!
My spy‐dork sense is
tingling with anticipation!
[KIRYUU]
So the perverted trio
is keeping their summer
schedule open?
And what's this
"perverted trio" junk?
We only need one creep with
glasses and Motohama's our dog!
Hmph! Don't lump me
in the same category
as that spectacled freak.
It insults me.
Motohama's glasses can
accurately measure the size
of a woman's bust in the time it
takes to finish this sentence!
Hehe. I'd say you're
packing a very respectable 36C.
Ha! Hate to break it to you,
but you're not the only
one with that technique.
You've got scouting
sight as well?
Now then, gentlemen,
what do we have here?
[ISSEI]
Stop it!
I see!
You see what?
[KIRYUU] Length is...
The width is..
At peak performance...
Her scouting level
is over nine thousand!
Oh snaps!
The gloves are off!
Now I'll gauge the
size of your areola!
Shut your yap
and do it, if you can!
[MATSUDA]
Stone cold.
Scout skill standoff!
[KIRYUU]
You're a very lucky girl, Asia!
Your boyfriend is
smuggling serious kielbasa!
Really?
[XENOVIA]
Kielbasa smuggling?
Sounds like an issue that should
be relegated to the authorities.
[KIRYUU]
I mean his big dick!
Stop trying to warp
their young minds!
While you calculate dongs,
I'm'a pick up a fly girlfriend!
And I'm definitely
gonna serve up your defeat!
[ISSEI]
Girlfriend, huh?
I had one, I guess,
but she ended up murdering me.
[ISSEI thinking] Why am I
thinking of such bad memories?
And why did I dream of her last
night?
You seem kinda out of
it today. Are you all right?
All good, thanks.
So, tell me Kiba...
[ISSEI] ... have you got
anything special planned
for over the break?
We do! I forgot this is
your first time with us Issei.
Well, what about you, Koneko?
What are you going to do?
[door opens]
[RIAS] It looks
like everyone is here.
[ISSEI] Going home
to the underworld?
Well, naturally!
Summer's finally here.
This is a yearly tradition.
Is everything
all right, dear?
But when you said you were
going back home all of a sudden,
I was afraid that
meant leaving me behind
and never coming back again!
Hmm. Cloying
neediness is so hot.
Now stop worrying.
I plan to keep you around
for a few dozen millennia,
at the very least!
I would never leave you
behind. Understand?
Yeah. I got you.
We'll all head to the
underworld tomorrow morning.
And it's a long trip,
so bring a book or something.
[ASIA]
Wait, did you say all of us?
[RIAS] Masters and servants
must always be together.
Going to the underworld
while I'm still alive
but I wouldn't feel anything
if I were already dead!
So then, starting tomorrow
morning, we're gonna spend
our vacation in the same hell
I once tossed infidels into?
For a once‐believer
turned devil, that's irony.
I'll be going along as well.
[RIAS]
When did you get in here?
if you didn't notice
my presence until just now,
then you've still got a
lot of training left to do.
I'll tell Matsuda and Motohama
that the Occult Research Club
is heading out of town
to a secret training camp.
[ASIA] I never expected
to go to hell on a train.
[ISSEI] Last time, we went
courtesy of Grayfia's magic.
Then we came back on griffins.
It was pretty sweet.
[AKENO] Well this is a
proper trip, and all new devils
should enter the world through
the appropriate channels.
Hey, Koneko? Your lunch
is gonna get cold, y'know.
What is it?
Nothing. Nothing to worry about.
[ANNOUNCER] We will soon arrive
at the Sitri Domain terminal.
Sitri domain?
[chuckles]
[SAJI]
Yo! Hyodo!
[ISSEI] Saji!
Student Council Prez and VP!
[RIAS]
Good to see you, Sona.
to give us a ride
on the Gremory train,
I thought I'd see how
you were before we got off.
Fine, if not a bit anxious.
Perfectly understandable.
After all, this is no
ordinary trip home.
You're heading out to train in
the underworld too, right bro?
Huh?
[XENOVIA]
Up to now,
we've only been told we're
accompanying Rias on break.
Oh, well. I'm about to
go and work my butt off
so that the next
time we meet up,
I'll be a lot stronger
than you, got me Hyodo?
Saji. It's time to go.
All right. See ya!
Goodbye and good luck.
Goodbye. See you again soon.
since we dropped off
Sona and her entourage.
Goes to show you how
big the underworld really is!
[ANNOUNCER] We will soon arrive
at the Gremory domain terminal.
All right! It's about time!
[giggles] Just take a look.
[gasps]
[XENOVIA] Wait, do you
mean that all that land?
[AKENO] Yes. This all belongs
to the House of Gremory.
[ISSEI] Really?
It's freakin' huge!
[KIBA] If you were
to compare it to Japan,
they own roughly the
size of its main island.
[ISSEI]
Whoa! Ahh!
[screams]
[XENOVIA]
Why did we stop?
[ANNOUNCER] The emergency
brake has been activated.
How strange! I wonder why
someone stopped the train.
Who knows? Whatever
happened, I'm cool with it.
We could even do it again!
[GASPER]
Ow, my neck.
Did we get into an accident?
A few VIPs will be
gathering here soon.
Maybe the stop was
a security precaution.
What VIPs?
Looks like we might be
stuck here for a while.
I'm gonna go take a peek. Ciao!
[sighs] One of the
representatives of Asgard
will be joining us
for a conference.
[ISSEI]
What's an ass guard?
[KIBA] They're the forces
behind Norse mythology.
Asgard's the home
of the Viking gods.
Then there's Olympus
from Greek mythology,
and the legendary
Mount Meru in Asia.
It's more than just
Angels and Devils.
Don't have
to tell me twice.
Was that guy who escaped
with Vali one of 'em?
Son Goku or something?
this conference we're going
to is about the Chaos Brigade!
That's right.
Terrorist countermeasures.
Asgard is joining our alliance.
[thinking] Vali, I will
kick your ass next time.
Something's wrong.
[groans]
[ISSEI]
Where are we?
[KIBA]
Forced teleportation?
[ASIA]
Where is Rias?
[AKENO]
I don't see her.
[GASPER]
Azazel's missing too!
Be quiet!
[XENOVIA]
That's not good.
[roaring sound]
A dragon?
So I'm going to assume
this guy isn't friendly.
Duh! Ya think so?
Koneko, watch out!
[grunts]
[GASPER]
Koneko!
[roars]
You have to run!
[AKENO] Since Rias isn't here,
it is my duty to take the lead!
Kiba! Xenovia!
Do whatever you can
to distract the dragon.
Issei, focus on activating
your Sacred Gear!
Asia, protect Koneko!
I will give orders to
coordinate our response!
You got it, Akeno!
Let's rock some Boosted Gear!
[DDRAIG] Boost!
[ISSEI]
A little help here!
[AKENO] I love
dishing out punishment!
[XENOVIA]
Hey Scale‐y, over here!
It was able to
deflect Durandal?
[grunts]
Koneko,
please just stay still!
You got it! Sword Birth!
[DDRAIG]
Boost!
I'm still powerless! I haven't
generated enough energy
to take this thing down yet!
[DDRAIG]
Boost!
[AKENO thinking]
Why does it keep reacting
to Issei's Sacred Gear?
[GASPER]
I, I have to do something.
I've got to! After all...
...it's my
responsibility as a man!
Nicely done, Gaspar!
Uh. He's unfrozen, bro.
I'm sorry!
He's too scary!
I can't keep focused!
[DDRAIG]
Explosion!
[ISSEI]
Awesome!
Time to strike! Attack!
Dragon Shot!
You're kidding!
No way!
‐‐[ASIA] Leave him alone!
‐‐[GASPER] Watch out, Issei!
‐‐[XENOVIA] Hold on!
‐‐[KIBA] We're coming!
[AZAZEL]
Stop! That'll be enough.
You guys are here?
Dude. What the hell?
[ISSEI] This dragon is a devil?
That's awesome!
Thought I recognized you Ddraig!
[DDRAIG] Yes.
Good to see you again Tannin.
And you apparently
know each other?
[AZAZEL] Blaze Meteor Dragon.
A. K. A. Devil Dragon Tannin.
Vassal to the former
Dragon Emperor.
He allowed himself
to be turned into a devil,
for reasons I don't feel
like going into now.
[KIBA] A dragon
that's become a devil?
[ISSEI] Just how balls‐out
powerful can you get?
[AZAZEL] The big guy's
come down to help out
with your training, children.
Is it special training
with a full‐on montage?
[TANNIN] Hmm... I don't
know what that means.
But Sir Zechs
asked me to come help.
And from what I've seen, each
one of you needs a lot of work.
[AZAZEL]
Hmm...
I hope he didn't
hurt you too badly.
I never wanted
to play a trick on you.
I was against the
ambush ploy from the start.
But my big brother
can be rather insistent.
[AZAZEL] I can sum up why
your retinue isn't improving.
Besides a tendency
towards spoiling them,
you act with uncertainty.
What uncertainty?
I wanted to gauge
the kind of power
you could muster when surprised.
And trust me, I learned plenty.
This fight showed me what
kind of training regimen
Exactly the plan a fallen
angel would come up with.
I'll do whatever it takes
to make you kids stronger!
I am your teacher, after all.
Were you in on this too, Ddraig?
Why didn't you pipe up
if you knew him?
[DDRAIG] I have lived
for years beyond counting,
and learned that those who
spoil Charades are the worst.
[ISSEI]
Wait, Charades?
Tannin wasn't even using one
thousandth of his strength.
I can't very well take you
all home scraped up like that.
So it's time for
our obligatory bath!
[GASPER] No, really! It's fine!
I can just go in later!
We're both boys, so what're
you so embarrassed about?
[ISSEI]
Gaspar, you're a dude,
so you don't need
to cover up like that.
It's making me uncomfortable!
What seriously?
I never thought you'd
noticed me in that way.
[ISSEI]
Dude, not even!
[AKENO] Oh, Issei! You shouldn't
be sexually harassing
poor sweet Gaspar like that!
[ISSEI] Akeno? Whoa!
The girl's bath is up there?
[ISSEI thinking] That means
a heaving heaven of hot hooters
is just a few feet away!
This is better
than good, it's great!
Underworld hot springs
for the win!
Add a bottle or three of sake,
and this hot spring
would be paradise!
Say, I've been
meaning to ask you.
What's up?
Tell me, Rias' melons‐‐
have you got any
good squeezing in?
Yes sir! With this hand here,
my form was flawless.
So... you ever pushed
in a girl's nipple like so?
No, not yet, sadly.
[sighs] So you still haven't
poked her protrusions yet.
You can't just poke
lightly either, boy.
You gotta really
get it in there.
The feeling of your
finger being enveloped
by funbag flesh is unparalleled.
[ISSEI thinking]
It can't be real.
My finger buried in bosom?
Nipples aren't the bell of a
front door, you damn deceiver!
True, but in a way the two
are actually quite similar!
If you press them,
they cry out, "No!"
[gasps]
No!
[ISSEI] I had no idea.
I've always thought that boobs
were there to grope,
suck or to squeeze.
My world's brand new. Limitless.
Like the wool has
been pulled from my eyes.
And you're still just a kid,
the future's bright.
But never forget.
Jubblies have
infinite potential!
I've already learned so much!
And I swear to you,
I will continue my training!
I wanna poke a
pink piñata right now!
[AZAZEL]
Good! Never give up!
You let those bra balloons
know who's the boss!
[ISSEI]
Yes. I swear!
Once Issei gets passionate about
something, he doesn't give up!
Hey. Can I ask you something
about the fight we
were in earlier today?
What's that?
It's Koneko. She was so
careless. That's not like her.
Yeah. That was weird.
But she hasn't been acting
like herself at all today.
So you noticed
it as well, huh?
[GASPER]
Should we say something?
No. She'll be back
to normal soon.
It seems like
some special training
is just what Xenovia
was looking for.
[AZAZEL] I can sum up why
your retinue isn't improving.
Besides a tendency
towards spoiling them,
you act with uncertainty.
[RIAS thinking]
I don't know what I could be
that uncertain about.
Wanna share
what's on your mind?
I do wanna apologize
for forcing you to step in
and take the lead today, though.
[AKENO] Don't worry.
It was my duty as your Queen.
[RIAS] I know that.
I also noticed that your plans
led to a combo
attack with Issei.
Should I be jealous?
[chuckles]
To tell you the truth,
that was one of the few moves
I hadn't been scheming.
So you say,
and it's over, now.
I guess so.
I think it's about
time to get out.
[BIKOU] Hey babe!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[KUROKA] You're late, Bikou.
I've gotten so bored
from lounging around here.
when confirming
things with Vali.
That said, we should go see him.
He gets outright cantankerous
if he has to wait too long!
[KUROKA]
Well, Vali is one thing,
but I don't really
care about Loki.
Now, you shouldn't
say such things, Kuroka.
Just think of this
as part of the job.
[KUROKA] There's only
one thing I care about,
and that's getting
my little sister back.
I know you'll wait
for me, Shirone.
[ISSEI] This is not how
I imagined winding up
between your thighs
would be, Xenovia!
[SAIRAORG] I know it's strict,
but that's your only warning.
[RAVEL] You, boy who thinks
he's the Red Dragon Emperor,
are an inferior devil at best.
Therefore you should
gratefully accept the offer!
[RIAS]
Oh, get it together!