[ISSEI]
I'll go see Vali. Now.
[SIR ZECHS sighs]
I understand how you feel Issei,
but that's impossible.
[ISSEI] Why, cause he's
in the Chaos Brigade?
You don't think I
already know that?
But, if it'll work,
then what are we waiting for?
[SIR ZECHS] Our very way of
life is under constant siege
by those terrorists
in the Chaos Brigade.
The underworld was
attacked again, yesterday.
[gasps]
The casualties from
this most recent assault
are still being tallied.
Families and friends from
every corner of the realm
are left grieving for
the departed tonight.
We can't associate
ourselves with such filth.
Collusion with the Chaos Brigade
to save the devil king's sister?
The people would
stand against me.
If the public heard about our
collaboration with Vali Lucifer,
in no time at all. Shalba
Beelzebub would find a way
to spin the civil
unrest to his advantage.
This decision could affect the
stability of the underworld.
[ISSEI] I don't mean to
sound disrespectful, sir.
But, you know your duty.
Please let me do mine.
I'll do whatever it
takes to rescue Rias.
Or, at least die trying.
Did you not hear me?
I respect your
position on the issue
because of the potential for
revolution and that stuff,
but Rias need me.
That's enough.
[AZAZEL]
Hold on, Issei.
Just think. Are you ready
to give up being a devil?
[IRINA]
Give up being a devil?
[AKENO] What exactly
are you telling us?
Try to keep up. The Devil King
can say you kids went rogue,
and remain blameless.
If you kids go rogue and
attempt to rescue Rias,
it's no longer Sir
Zechs's problem.
It's not that simple.
[AZAZEL] Should things go bust,
you can still cover your ass.
And if that's not good enough,
I can take care of the kids.
[ISSEI]
Like how?
[AZAZEL]
Hmph. If worse comes to worst,
I can see to it that they're
all made fallen angels.
What!?
Then, you can just scapegoat
any backlash on me,
the acting Governor‐General.
A false‐flag operation could
quell any potential discontent.
A drastic gamble.
This may sound odd
coming from an agent of
the Holy Church who
was turned into a devil.
Is something like
that even possible?
You're a fallen angel because
you were a regular angel
who fell from grace.
But a devil?
I don't know where
to start with that.
I hate long division.
The point is, we're just talking
worst case scenario here.
if you kids bring Rias
back safe and sound.
Yes.
If she's trapped in
the Dimensional Gap,
then we have a narrow
window of time to rescue her.
Your decision?
[ISSEI]
Please, Sir Zechs!
[ISSEI] I don't want to quit
being a devil, your lordliness.
Look. I have to help her,
even if it means punishment.
I will accept it willingly
after I've saved Rias!
And then I'll take
it like a man.
Please, sir. I'm begging you.
He won't be alone. We owe Rias
too much to abandon her.
We're fully prepared to
sacrifice anything we can
to bring her home safely.
Rias took me in when
I had no one else
and treated me like a little
sister. There's no way
I can sit back and do
nothing while she suffers.
Sir Zechs, I remember making a
promise the day you put me under
your sister's care. I intend
to make good on it.
I swore I'd protect her
with my life, if needed.
She gave me a forever home.
Rias Gremory gave
me a new lease on life,
taking me in when I thought
I'd lost everything.
We're all ready, sir.
Just give the word.
[SIR ZECHS gasps]
[AZAZEL] What's the worst
that can happen? Ragnarok?
[AZAZEL]
HM.
[sighs]
Please save my sister.
[gasps]
Are you ready?
'Kay.
[ISSEI]
Uh...
You really think
she's gonna show up?
If I call for her, she'll come.
There's no doubt about it.
[KUROKA giggles]
[KUROKA] First you tell me to
piss off, then you call for me.
Is somebody a little indecisive?
Not quite.
I have a favor to ask.
[gasps]
What's a boy like you want?
I don't think it was a good idea
to let Issei and Koneko
go wait out there alone.
I'd rather avoid the
potential misunderstandings
that arriving in a large
group might convey to them.
We're keeping an eye out
for further developments.
And if anything arises...
We can jump straight there
in a moment's notice.
For now, we'll just have to
see how the negotiations go.
I'm sorry, were you
being serious?
Yeah. It's important that
I meet with Vali now.
Aww, it's adorable when
a little bitch like you
tries to be forceful. Okay,
I'll consider helping you out.
I'll agree, on one condition.
Shirone has to come
back with me.
[KUROKA]
How is that surprising to you?
I've tried to get
her back before.
Besides, what other
bargaining chip
are you bringing
to the negotiation table?
Right? They say one good
turn deserves another.
[KONEKO, ISSEI grunt]
Not a chance. I can't do that.
Koneko is my friend, and I
don't plan to give her up.
[KUROKA]
Oh? That's too bad.
So, uh. Is there a
second thing you want?
You were the one that asked
me for a favor, remember?
That's it.
The negotiations are over.
Can't believe you called me all
the way out here for nothing.
[ISSEI]
Please wait!
[ISSEI panting]
[gasps]
What's up, kid?
I know that I'm asking for
a lot, but as things stand,
it's the only shot
I've got left! Take me!
I gotta meet up with Vali!
Guess someone grew a
pair since last time.
[KUROKA grunts]
This is starting to bore me.
So yeah, feel free to
jump in whenever, Vali.
[ISSEI, KONEKO gasp]
[ISSEI]
Vali?
You guys listened in the whole
time?
It's unsafe for a lady,
I use that term loosely,
to be unescorted at night.
What're you tryin'
to say, Wiseguy?
That you're quite the strumpet!
Look, you know I wouldn't ask
you if it wasn't important.
The only way I can get
to the Dimensional Gap
And if I were to
refuse your request?
[ISSEI]
Then I'll have to use force.
[DDRAIG]
Boost!
And make you take us!
[KONEKO gasps]
[VALI] The ones involved
with the red or white dragon
have never had a good life.
Don't you believe this
to be destiny as well?
Who cares! Destiny shmestiny.
I do what I want.
I'll just change it if it
doesn't work out for me.
[VALI]
Hmph!
[VALI] I told you our
duel would have to wait
until you'd become stronger.
If I defeated you now,
I'd have nothing left
to look forward to.
Arthur.
[ISSEI, KONEKO grunt]
[ARTHUR] The Holy
Royal Sword, Collbrande.
Passed to the heirs of
the Pendragon name.
It bestows the power to rule.
And cuts a path
between dimensions.
Between dimensions?
What are you, a parrot?
Or, was the baby Red
Dragon dropped on his head?
So like, are you really
going to take us out there?
[VALI] We'll take you
to the Dimensional Gap.
However, I can't promise
that you'll survive
long enough to return.
Considering most
who go die there.
[ISSEI huffs]
[ARTHUR] Take a moment
to prepare yourselves.
The trip is fraught with danger.
Done.
What's this?
Fafnir will protect you in case
there are any surprises
out there, so keep it close.
Thanks, but why?
It's entirely my fault
that you got kidnapped
by that bratty little
bitch, Diodora.
This is just my way
of saying I'm sorry.
I'm sending them into the
jaws of potential death.
Seems weird to thank
you for your help.
I give you my word.
I have no intention of
harming any of your charges,
Issei included.
Meaning you have plans
further down the line.
[VALI]
Hmph.
It's a real shame
that all we can do
is wait here and pray for them.
You and I are neither devils,
nor part of Rias
Gremory's household.
Our involvement would only draw
in our respective factions.
I know!
The bond they've
forged through their time
working and training together
is stronger than steel.
Such a bond will bring
our friends back to us.
At least, that's what
I want to believe.
[IRINA gasps]
I guess you're right.
But, I'm still gonna pray.
Now, then.
All right then,
it's time to go home.
Sure thing.
[KUROKA]
Stupid Shirone.
[ISSEI gasps]
It's safe to say we've arrived.
[ARTHUR grunts]
[ARTHUR]
Stay within the light.
Leave the field and you'll be
swallowed by the nothingness.
This field will remain stable
for one human world hour.
Once the time limit is reached,
you will be ejected
into our dimension.
One hour.
That's not very long at all!
I know squat about the
Dimensional Gap
or how big it is,
but how likely are we
to actually find Rias
somewhere inside this field?
It's about conviction.
The strength of the
Gap can ebb and flow,
but not for the weak of heart.
Make sure to steel your
hearts against its forces.
Our hearts?
But, what does that mean?
Were I to explain further, then
my warning would be meaningless.
This is the extent of
the help I can offer.
[ISSEI gasps]
[XENOVIA] How should we
start searching a place
where left and right are
completely meaningless?
No! It's not only left or right.
I can't tell what's up or down!
Steel our hearts against it.
But how, and against what?
Not for the weak of heart.
[ISSEI gasps]
[ISSEI]
What was that?
I was just thinking about
the warning that Arthur guy
gave us before he left.
We're in a space where the laws
of physics no longer apply.
Therefore, distance
and direction
are both meaningless
concepts here.
That right, of course.
Well then, maybe.
Then maybe what, Kiba?
Rias has got to come. We'll
definitely see her. No doubt.
[gasps]
Our feelings will summon her.
Give her a way to find us.
It's her!
Rias! Is that really you?
Rias! We found you!
Come with us!
I'm so glad!
[gasps]
[ASIA yelps]
[ALL gasp]
It can't be.
[GASPER] What? Is she
some kind of imposter?
'Fraid not. It's the
real Rias, Gaspie.
Yes. Koneko's right.
That is definitely the
aura of a Gremory.
Don't be such an idiot!
That's impossible!
The real Rias would
never attack Asia.
[AKENO grunts]
[gasps]
Oh, come on!
[XENOVIA] Maybe she's under
someone else's control?
[GASPER]
Controlled? By who?
Hey! Look at me!
I'm here for you!
Damn it! Have you lost
control of your mind?
Tell me this is just a joke!
[ISSEI]
What the...?
We need to get her to safety
before the field wears off.
Forcing her to attack
her best friends?
Way to be a dick, Loki!
[KIBA, XENOVIA grunt]
Lightning. Strike!
Let's do this!
All right!
I can't do it!
[GASPER] I don't have
any power over time!
In here, both time and
space are irrelevant!
[ASIA gasps]
This is bad. Retreat!
I can't take it!
[ISSEI gasps]
[gasps]
That blast! Are you okay?
Cool doohickey.
Did it make the barrier?
Fafnir shrouded us in
his protecting light.
Well, I guess that's neat,
but what about the light
that's coming from Rias?
This is the power that gave
her the title "Ruin Princess".
[ISSEI]
Huh?
[AKENO] Up until now,
her power only released
whenever she felt
a surge of emotions.
But, this time
it isn't the same.
She's made the opposite true.
[KIBA]
Such destructive power.
[AKENO] Something's keeping
her from using her power
to its fullest.
[ISSEI]
You're serious?
If her power were
at its fullest,
there wouldn't be a safe
place to hide in this field.
We would all be dead.
Listen! You've got to calm down
so you can come back with us!
Please stop! I don't
want to lose you!
I thought so.
[GASPER]
Huh?
She's still able to hear us.
So, what do we do?
Please, Rias! Remember us!
That pause.
She's reacting!
You were the one who
gave me my new name!
I won't forget that
day as long as I live.
I was lost, but you
gave me the gift
of a new and wonderful life.
I will always appreciate
everything you've done for me.
You're the best
sister I never had!
If you hadn't come
along and found me,
I would've had to walk the
earth alone as a pariah.
Or even worse, I might've
died on the streets.
When I was dying in pain.
When I was consumed with hate,
you took me in;
saved me twice over.
You've got to wake up!
Please, try to remember!
Remember my voice!
[AKENO]
My face!
Come back!
[gasps]
Rias?
Issei.
I'm here!
[gasps]
Rias?
[gasps, screams]
[ISSEI grunts]
What's wrong?
[RIAS screams]
[gasps]
I'm guessing that trick's new.
It looks like a less
protective version
of Issei's balance breaker!
How can that be?
[KONEKO] Her armor.
It gives off the same aura
as Issei's did when
he went berserk.
[LOKI] I lost to the dragon boy
due to last minute interference.
Luckily for me, I'm the kind of
fellow who thinks on his feet.
[AKENO]
Loki. Is this what he meant?
[KIBA yells]
[ALL gasp]
Kiba! Xenovia! Rias!
Please, you've gotta stop!
[AKENO gasps] You have
to get a grip on yourself!
Rias!
[AKENO screams]
[KONEKO]
Asia, get down!
I've gotcha!
Akeno! Are you gonna be okay?
Yes. Issei.
Please save Rias from herself.
I've been thinking of what
Arthur said. About how the
Dimensional Gap is greatly
affected by our hearts.
If that's true, then
you are the only one
who can bring my friend back.
Do you mean it?
But, How am I
supposed to save her?
You'll have to beat
her in combat.
[gasps]
No way!
That's impossible! I don't
wanna risk hurting her.
You're asking too
much of me, all right?
There's no way! And I'm supposed
to live with myself after that?
I understand how painful
this must be for you, I swear!
With that said. She needs
you now more than ever.
The only thing she wants
is for you to rescue her.
[gasps]
But, that can't be okay.
[ISSEI] No. It just feels wrong.
I would never fight Rias.
Don't you get it?
[ASIA] Don't think of
it like that, Issei.
[ISSEI]
Asia.
[ASIA]
It's like this.
You're fighting to free her!
All right.
Let's get it on.
Big Red.
[ISSEI yells]
[DDRAIG] Welsh Dragon
Balance Breaker!
[ISSEI]
Geronimo!
[ALL grunt]
Why's everything getting dark?
The field's down!
It's from the power
of their attacks!
Looks like they've disrupted
the stability of the rift!
[ASIA gasps]
[ASIA gasps, screams]
[XENOVIA]
Asia!
[ASIA screams]
[XENOVIA]
Asia!
[ASIA]
I believe in you.
You'll definitely
come back, won't you?
Both of you.
[AKENO]
Rias.
[LOKI laughs]
It's already too late.
The twilight of the
gods is fast approaching.
No! It's not over!
[ISSEI] Because I
need her in my life.
Because she's so
important to me.
[ISSEI]
I will fight! I promise!
[ISSEI] If I don't
put a stop to this,
then Loki gets
exactly what he wants.
[XENOVIA] You have to stay
strong for her, Issei.
[ASIA]
I believe in you both.
Fight with all your heart.
[AKENO]
Come back to us.