[LOKI] Well, well, well, what do
we have here? Lovely red hair.
Judging by its hue and her age,
she must be the devil
king's little sister.
[AKENO]
Don't do this! Rias!
Issei. I'm sorry.
I'll fix this.
[SONA] Rias. Do you think
this is what he'd want? Move!
[RIAS gasps]
[LOKI]
Odin, you sly bastard,
sending these young pups
Thor's warhammer was a shrewd,
albeit risky
proposition. Fenrir!
I have a new chew toy
for you. It's over there.
[roars]
He broke loose!
Watch out!
[LOKI]
That sigil. What is this?
The magic chains of Gleipnir?
What's going on?
I might've had something
to do with that.
[KONEKO]
Kuroka.
Looks like you've
accepted your power.
What a relief your ears and tail
have finally made an appearance!
Maybe, but I will never
be like you, Kuroka.
I suppose we'll just
have to wait and see.
We are a violent species,
and peace isn't a big part
of our genetic makeup.
You'll see. One day.
[LOKI] I can't believe
a lowly cat devil
would dare betray Loki!
What now?
[ARTHUR] Salutations. My name
is Arthur, of the Vali team.
[KONEKO gasps]
We will be taking custody of
Fenrir from this point forward!
[LOKI]
And why would you do that?
[KUROKA]
Apparently, Vali has a hard on
for his fangs since
they can devour gods.
The Holy Royal Sword,
Collbrande.
Even a god as powerful as
you cannot scratch it.
[LOKI] Tell your master he
will regret this decision.
Suck it! The only one
regretting things here is you.
Fare thee well, everyone. Ta‐ta
Oh, and sis?
[KUROKA] I'm in a
bit of a rush today,
but I'll come back for
you again sometime.
Damn you, White Dragon!
You were after Fenrir
from the very beginning!
[DDRAIG]
Boost!
[LOKI]
Oh great. You're alive now?
[ISSEI]
Yeah, thanks to a parting gift
from a sweet little Phoenix!
Thought it was some
sorta gem or whatever,
and didn't bother opening it!
Right, got sidetracked! Hey,
jerk! Time to get hammered!
[DDRAIG]
Boost!
[ISSEI]
Sucker's heavy!
But I know I can do this!
[DDRAIG]
Boost!
[yells]
[LOKI grunts]
Those meddling kids!
[LOKI gasps]
Not so fast, creep!
Release me at once, boy!
[DDRAIG] Transfer!
[ISSEI]
Underestimated us kids, huh?
That's gonna cost you!
Damn you, Red Dragon!
Damn you, Odin!
Psycho devils and evil gods?
When do I get to meet the great
creator of rockin' boobage?
[LOKI]
A plague on all your houses!
[ISSEI, RIAS]
Uh!
[LOKI]
A plague on your houses!
May you suffer
greatly before death.
[ISSEI] Have I heard
that somewhere before?
[RIAS]
Shakespeare?
[SAJI sighs]
So, does that mean it's over?
Good work, Saji, really.
Thanks a lot.
Uh... Hey, you know,
it's no big deal!
I just did things like
in training, that's all.
All this smiling's startin'
to make me nervous.
Watch out!
[roars]
[KIBA grunts]
Kiba!
[gasps]
[KIBA groans]
[SAIRAORG] Remember: The fight's
not over till it's over!
[ISSEI]
Sairaorg!
[ISSEI] Uh! Dude, that
was just one punch?
[SAIRAORG] It was, but
seems like you already had
things under control
here anyway.
You must be pretty strong!
Yeah! I guess.
I'd like to fight in a
Rating Game against you
and Rias one of these days!
To find out who's number one!
We don't plan to lose that
fight.
Should be a lot of fun!
[SAIRAORG chuckles]
Agreed! Then, I look forward
to a balls‐out power battle
against you one day.
[ROSSWEISSE]
It's odd.
I wonder where they took Fenrir,
and what they plan
to use him for.
You and me both.
I've got no idea what Vali
needs with a giant wolf.
[ARTHUR] Such is the power of
the last fragment of Excalibur.
The sword of total control.
[VALI]
Sorry, Loki.
But when I saw
Fenrir, I thought,
"Hey, I wouldn't
mind having a dog."
You may think you've got
a handle on your new power,
but soon, that will
all change. Very soon.
[ODIN] It was fortunate we had
the Red Dragon Emperor there.
A tremendous amount of power is
needed to capably wield Mjolnir.
The kid saved me the trouble.
[MICHAEL] But Lord Loki was
an important god in your fold.
What if he has allies?
[ODIN] The times change,
and we must change with them.
[RIAS] Thank you once
again, Mom and Dad.
We're off. Bye, Millicas!
But you only just got here!
Do you have to leave already?
I'm sorry, Millicas,
but yes, we do.
Lady Rias is incredibly busy.
We can't be greedy and
keep her to ourselves.
Okay, guess you're right, Mom.
Whoa! That's his mom? No way!
Seriously?
So Grayfia is Sir Zechs's wife!
[ASIA]
Huh...?
[XENOVIA, KIBA gasp]
[ISSEI]
Um, Koneko?]
[KUROKA]
We are a violent species,
and peace isn't a big part
of our genetic makeup.
She's wrong. I'm here,
and I've found peace.
[AKENO laughs] I would have
never expected Koneko
to get so friendly with Issei.
it would've been impossible
to imagine, but look!
Right? It's adorable!
So, I have a request.
Hear me out.
Maybe... Could I borrow
Issei for just one day?
He's not a pair of shoes!
Be serious.
[gasps] I see.
You plan on telling
him the truth.
Yes. I think I'm ready to
come to terms with it now.
For the most part.
Once again, Issei
steps in to rescue
another friend from their past.
My hero.
[RIAS]
Yes, mine as well.
[AKENO] Mother, what can
I do? I want to be strong.
[XENOVIA] All that training made
me forget about the real foe.
It's bizarre! Maybe they
give us this much
homework as a punishment
for going on vacation.
[XENOVIA groans, sighs]
has already finished all
of their assignments.
Not yet. We aren't alone.
Suck my ass!
There's still so much to do!
Training camp is no excuse
for unfinished homework.
If it were, that would
reflect poorly both on me,
and the club at large.
Time to play a little catch‐up.
[ISSEI]
Mom and Dad're both on vacation.
I thought I'd be able to coast
by without any real effort!
[sighs] Besides, I've got
bigger things on my mind
than a buncha stupid math!
When I was training,
I tried to shut down
the horn dog inside so
I could get stronger.
But spending all that
time sweating with young,
sexy ladies made me
realize the truth.
I'll never, not want to bury
my face in sweater bazookas.
I can't deny who I am!
‐‐[GIRLS laugh]
‐‐[ISSEI sighs]
[ISSEI] In the end,
I even had a fantasy
that I was talking to a giant
pair of space knockers.
It was a moment of
perverted clarity.
I have come one step closer
to the truth of erotica!
With this knowledge,
I swear to develop a new skill
to bust out in addition
to Dress Break!
Uh. Yes! Hello!
[AKENO] Issei? Sorry to
interrupt, but I brought tea!
Sweet. Thanks a bunch.
[door closes]
[AKENO]
This one. Check it.
I don't think you have
the right answer.
[ISSEI]
Um. Uh... Oh, no, my bad.
It's all right. You just
need a helping hand.
Yeah, sure.
Now don't be shy.
I'd be happy to tutor you
until it comes naturally.
[ISSEI]
Oh!
[AKENO]
Something wrong?
[ISSEI]
No. Sorry about that.
I feel bad making you
help with my homework.
No problem at all. I was
in that class last year.
But now, in return,
I get to ask a favor.
There's something
I'd like to do.
[ISSEI]
Uh! Yeah...?
We both live in the
same damn house.
Why do we have to meet
all the way out here?
[AKENO]
Sorry!
Hope you weren't
waiting too long.
[gasps] No, not at all.
The way you're staring at me
makes me feel embarrassed.
You hate this outfit, don't you?
Actually, just the opposite.
It's really doin' it for me!
[AKENO]
Exactly what I like to hear
from my boyfriend‐for‐the‐day.
Which sounds kinda
nice, doesn't it?
Yeah, that sounds great!
All right! Then let's
go have some fun!
[ISSEI] She's so cute
when she gets that excited.
So then. Where to?
Well, what do people
do on a dates?
[ISSEI gasps] Ok. This is
a one hundred percent,
certified real deal date.
[AKENO] I ask because...
I've never been on one.
[ISSEI]
Uh...
Elbow on boob action!
Another deposit to the spank
bank for pending withdrawal!
Hey! I gave her permission
to go on a date.
I thought they'd go to
get lunch or something!
But no walking arm in arm!
Gaspie, if you see
something happen,
make sure you stop it in time.
[GASPER]
If I see something happen?
This mask won't make that easy.
Wow. Our friends
are crappy spies.
Don't look now, but I
think we're being followed.
Then let's make a break for it!
[RIAS gasps]
They clocked us somehow!
[KONEKO]
Let's roll, Gaspie!
‐‐[AKENO laughing]
‐‐[ISSEI panting]
[BOTH panting]
Rias is definitely gonna murder
me when we get home.
Coast is clear.
I'd say we lost 'em.
[ISSEI] Well, as long as Akeno's
having a good time today,
I'll deal with the consequences.
[ISSEI gasps] I didn't realize
it while we were hauling ass,
but we're in love hotel central!
If people see us now, they
might get the wrong idea!
Let's make like a tree
and get outta here!
Uh... I meant leave.
It's fine.
If you want to go in, fine.
Let's go, honest. I'd like to.
[ISSEI gasps]
No way! Seriously? Akeno!
You said that in
cutesy girlish mode
instead of smoking hot sex on
a stick flirty mode like usual!
Okay, breathe, Issei.
I gotta thank the
great and glorious
Devil King for this blessing.
[ODIN]
A little afternoon delight, huh?
Most impressive! I've heard
tales of your perversion.
[AKENO]
Lord Odin?
I don't suppose
we've properly met.
Sorry Loki stirred up trouble.
[ISSEI]
Captain Wrinkle Beardsley here
is the king of the Norse?
Lord Odin! Of course this
is where you wound up.
[ISSEI]
Oh. Hey there, Rossweisse.
[BARKIEL] I kindly request you
not wander off on your own.
Remember, I'm supposed
to be your guide.
Akeno?
After this little Loki debacle,
I've come to a realization.
To withstand future attacks,
we must strengthen our forces.
A fact further compounded
by just how new our relationship
is with the gods
of this country.
And that's why we had
Barkiel escort him
He knows the region well and
has the best beard of us all.
That's true.
There's something I'd
like to go over with you.
Cut to the chase,
my time's precious.
[ISSEI] I knew that Akeno didn't
care much for her father.
But damn, that was brutal!
Why were you meeting with
the Red Dragon Emperor
in such a lascivious
part of town?
[ISSEI groans]
I can do whatever I want.
What gives you the right
to have any kind of say
in how I live my life?
Because I'm your father!
Why weren't you there when we
actually needed you around?
You were the one who left mother
behind to die, sad and alone!
I like spending time with Issei,
because he's nothing like you!
Just looking at you
makes me sick!
and I hope we never
see each other again!
Look, Akeno. Maybe‐‐
‐‐[AKENO whimpers]
‐‐[ISSEI grunts]
[AKENO]
No. Don't say anything.
Just hold me for a little while.
Don't let go.
Please, Issei. Don't let go.
Carry the three,
and there it is.
Twenty‐seven with
a remainder of one.
Thanks Rossweisse! You
made it amazingly clear!
You're a human world
homework champion!
She's beautiful, intelligent,
interesting, and quite
formidable in combat.
You're the perfect woman.
A real life warrior
princess.
Thanks, but it's just algebra.
[ROSSWEISSE] If she was being
honest in all her compliments,
then why haven't I ever been
able to land a single lover?
‐‐[ROSSWEISSE cries]
‐‐[XENOVIA, ASIA] Huh?
[ISSEI] Akeno, I wish
I knew how to help you.
I'm the daughter of Shuri and
Barkiel. I'm a fallen angel.
[ISSEI exhales]
[knocking]
Uh? Yo!
[door opens]
[ISSEI]
Hey, Akeno.
[AKENO] I want to explain
myself. Why I yelled at Barkiel.
[ISSEI]
Uh.
My mother, the priestess Shuri,
born and raised at
a Shinto shrine.
One day she found a fallen angel
who'd been injured in battle.
They fell in love, and
before long, I was born.
Because of the scandal, the
Himejima family disowned us,
and kicked us out on our own.
So we left to start a quiet life
together with my father,
the fallen angel.
Naturally, those days of peace
didn't last very long.
When my black wings
started coming in,
I had no idea people would hate
them as much as they did.
What kid thinks their neighbors
are going to try to murder her?
My mother tried desperately
to shield me from them.
She died protecting you?
[AKENO]
Mm. Life suddenly changed.
I spent my days running from
those who hunted me. Too long.
In the end, I was just a child.
And children have their limits.
When both my spirit and body
failed to go any further...
[RIAS] You can die alone,
or you can live for me.
[AKENO] Rias showed up
and saved my life.
So that's how you guys met.
I needed to tell you everything
about my history.
That way, I could finally try
and put it all behind me.
But I can't do it!
The jerk tossed us aside
to fend for ourselves!
There's no way I can call
that bastard 'father'.
Hold on, look.
He may be a bit uptight,
but he doesn't come
across as a bastard.
Maybe he couldn't make it.
I don't care what
could've happened.
because he wasn't there when
we needed him! It's too late.
[AKENO] I don't know! I don't
know anything anymore!
What I said back at the hotel.
That's how I honestly feel.
Please.
I want you.
[ISSEI]
Oh man... I want to.
But no, this isn't what
Akeno needs right now.
Touch me. Make me forget.
[gasps]
You're the only person I
trust enough to ask.
[gasps]
Wait. What's going on?
Are you seeing this?
[AKENO]
I was lonely.
[ISSEI, AKENO gasp]
[AKENO] I think your wings
are really neat, Daddy!
They're black, but also soft
and shiny, kinda like my hair!
[BARKIEL] You think so?
Thank you, Akeno.
[AKENO] Hey, Mama? Do you
think Daddy is proud of me?
[SHURI]
Yes, of course.
[AKENO] I'd like it better
if he was always here with us.
[SHURI] You can't do this.
She's just a little girl!
Please stop, her father and I
love her more than life itself!
[SPECIALIST A]
How unfortunate.
It seems your heart has been
tainted beyond recovery
by the darkness and evil
of the fallen angel.
I'm afraid it can't be helped.
Leave Mama alone!
No! Mama!
‐‐[BARKIEL] Akeno.
‐‐[AKENO] Don't touch me!
You should've been here
to protect me and Mama!
If you hadn't been gone, Mama
would still be alive right now.
Those people told me!
It's all 'cause my father
is a fallen angel!
They said all fallen
angels are bad people.
None of this is fair!
I hate stupid black wings!
I hate you! I hate everyone.
I hate everything.
[AKENO] I knew at the time it
wasn't Barkiel's fault,
but I couldn't keep myself
from blaming him.
I'm pathetic, weak, and
that's why I'm always alone.
What I really wanted was
for my Dad to be around
more than he was. I wanted
him to pat me on the head,
and tell me everything
was gonna be all right.
I wanted to play
with him more.
I want...
I wanted just a little more
time in that life together.
I wasn't ready for it to end.
[ISSEI]
Akeno.
A dream?
Yeah, I guess so.
Doesn't really matter.
But thanks to you,
I think I can finally come
to terms with my past.
Come on.
I didn't do anything.
[ISSEI] That sensation just now.
I've felt it before.
During my training.
[AKENO] I'm so sorry, Issei.
I don't know what came over me.
Well, I need to go
make dinner now.
It isn't easy subbing in for
your mother, you know.
[ODIN] Yes. I was able to meet
with most of the local gods.
I also went to the titty
bar and made it rain!
So you admit why you really
came all the way out here.
Odin, sir. It's almost time.
Akeno?
I thought you might want
to take a lunch box.
I'm in charge of cooking
this week, so...
I see. I'm grateful.
[ISSEI] Hell yeah!
I thought I smelled pot roast!
I haven't made this
dish in a long time.
You can have a taste
if you'd like one.
Cool. I would like!
Here. Say, "Ah."
Uh. Ahh.
Thank you. For everything.
[BARKIEL]
Look at that.
Tasty.
[BARKIEL]
Just like Shuri used to make.
Has anyone told you
about this, yet?
Girls our age are having
secret affairs with boys.
Yes. You're the reason
I'm here, Asia.
Of course. Issei's
always like that.
so I was worried something
had happened! But this?