[ISSEI]
It's simple.
I just wanted to protect her.
it doesn't matter if
we have a contract.
I'm bound to her just the same.
The way she holds herself,
standing dignified and strong,
her long crimson hair
flowing in the breeze.
She is my master.
I will serve her.
[ISSEI]
My Ruin Princess.
[AKENO] You are the only one
who can bring my friend back.
[ASIA]
You're fighting to free her!
[ISSEI] I'd go to hell and
back to bring her home.
[AKENO] You'll have to
beat her in combat.
[ISSEI] After everything
she's done for me,
I can't leave her behind.
Wake up!
[ISSEI groans]
But more importantly, I did it.
And your boobs get
to stay perfect.
Oh, Issei.
[RIAS]
Can I ask you something?
Be honest. Are you
glad that you met me?
[RIAS]
I'm very happy here.
[ISSEI groaning]
[RIAS] No matter what,
it's going to be okay.
I will do everything in
my power to protect you.
[ISSEI groaning]
[RIAS]
Issei.
You just saved my life.
Thank you.
[ISSEI]
Wake up!
Whatever! I like you and I
don't care what your name is!
I like you for who you are!
Rias, I... I love you.
[RIAS]
Next time, do your job well
whether there's a reward or not.
[ISSEI groaning]
[RIAS] Just a little spell to
strengthen your stamina.
[gasps]
Great job today.
I was very impressed.
[RIAS] My name is Rias
Gremory, and I'm a devil.
[ISSEI]
Rias, please!
[RIAS]
You're mine now.
Nice to meet you, Issei Hyodo.
[screaming]
[ISSEI]
Rias!
I understand.
I know what I've gotta do now.
But... I'm so afraid
of hurting you.
[ISSEI] I just wanted
to be your protector.
[ISSEI]
Not on my watch.
If I don't put a stop to this,
then Loki gets exactly
what he wants!
Please! Stop it, Rias!
Don't let him win!
You're better than that!
[gasps]
[ISSEI]
I won't let you down.
I'll do whatever it takes.
Nothing is gonna stop me.
[ISSEI]
I'll do whatever it takes.
Nothing is gonna stop me.
[ISSEI]
I'll always save you.
I'm your pawn, after all.
It's my job, right?
[ISSEI] That's right.
I am Rias Gremory's pawn!
[ISSEI]
Rias.
Wake up!
Issei?
[RIAS]
It's you!
Thank you. My darling.
You saved my life.
Rias! You're you again, right?
I was so worried!
[ISSEI]
Asshole.
You're gonna pay
for what you've done.
Using my body. Using my face!
You're goin' down.
[DDRAIG]
Boost!
[ISSEI]
Eat a bag of dicks!
[ISSEI gasps]
It morphed.
[ROSSWEISSE]
I'm relieved you're all safe.
when you guys suddenly popped
out of thin air like that.
Us too. But Rias and Issei
are still stuck in there.
Loki somehow managed to get his
hands on a powerful fragment
left over from Issei's
transformation.
So he has to fight
his exact duplicate?
Do you think Issei will
be able to beat himself?
Don't know. For now,
all we can do is believe.
If there's anyone who can
beat himself, it's Issei.
Let us pray for his success.
You're right.
[XENOVIA] You have to stay
strong for her, Issei.
[ASIA] I believe in you both.
Fight with all your heart.
[AKENO]
Come back to us.
[EVIL DRAGON roaring]
We've gotta do something
soon, or else we're toast.
[ISSEI]
Loki was able to take advantage
of my deepest, darkest
insecurities,
and found the same kind of
weakness in Rias's heart.
You got a plan?
[ISSEI]
Mh‐hm.
That's right. I've got a plan.
I'm gonna get super pissed off
and totally flip out
on this jabroni!
No matter what happens,
I'll keep trying.
[DDRAIG]
Welsh Dragon. Balance Breaker!
[ISSEI] I straight‐up
refuse to let her down!
So, uh, what's that?
Think of it as an evil piece
of downloadable content,
but still in beta.
I transferred those additions
to the piece inside of you.
And since this is the
trial run for the process,
any results have yet
to be determined.
But assuming there
are no defects,
it should enhance your
special characteristics.
It responds to the strength
of the end user's will.
[ISSEI]
Promise me.
Promise you'll stay the
strong and regal woman
you've always been.
that's kept hidden from
everyone, it doesn't matter!
[ISSEI] You'll never have
to worry about that again!
If it ever becomes too
much for you to handle,
I'll be there to
pick you back up!
[ISSEI]
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
[RIAS]
The field's dissipating.
[ISSEI gasping]
What the hell's going on?
[DDRAIG] We're being pulled
into some kind of vortex
between dimensions.
[ISSEI]
What's going to happen to us?
I'm not a self‐aware
encyclopedia, y'know.
I know. You don't
have to be a dick.
[DDRAIG] Hush. Can't
you sense his approach?
Great Red. Sucker's huge!
Of course. He's the
Dragon of Dragons.
[DDRAIG]
The Dragon of Dreams.
Another chance like
this may not come along.
We should follow his lead.
Okay.
Where are we?
Dunno. We were on this
beach before I realized it.
How strange.
Poor guy. Battered and
bruised for me again.
Yeah, it hurts, but these
injuries are no big deal.
As long as we're together,
I can put up with a lot.
[ISSEI]
What's up?
[RIAS] I don't want you all to
myself, or anything like that.
I'm not the jealous type.
At least, I never thought
that was the case.
But you're so close to Asia.
And... the way the rest of the
girls throw themselves at you.
I was so terrified of
becoming an afterthought.
But now you've shown
me how you really feel.
Why don't we head home?
Everyone's waiting for us.
[inaudible]
[gasps]
You came home!
[ASIA] Oh, thank goodness.
You both came back!
[AKENO]
Mh‐hm.
You sure took
your sweet time.
Akeno.
is beating that fake me
in the Twilight Zone.
You kicked your own ass?
I've come to expect
no less from you!
[ISSEI] I think so,
but it's all kinda hazy.
My memory's been fuzzy
since the mind control.
Wow. What happened here?
Uhh.
We're just happy you're
home safe and sound.
Me too. Thanks, you guys.
the worst was going to happen,
and you'd never make it back!
Now that that's over.
What's next?
I'm pretty surprised
those kids made it back
from the Dimensional Gap.
to witness something
well worth the trip.
[AZAZEL] The Red Dragon
Emperor's encounter
So that was your game
plan all along, huh?
[VALI]
Hmph. Yeah, sure.
[AZAZEL chuckles]
Ha.
Yeah.
[SIR ZECHS] Azazel just
contacted me with good news.
It seems Rias has
returned home safely.
[GRAYFIA]
How wonderful!
I don't know how I'll ever repay
Issei for rescuing my sister.
Issei didn't do it with the
thought of a reward in his mind.
He's always been
the honest type.
and keeps moving full steam
ahead, straight as an arrow.
[ISSEI]
Ddraig!
since I've manifested
myself in this form.
You're right. Does that mean
I'm dreaming right now?
[DDRAIG]
I have some big news for you.
Lay it on me.
[DDRAIG] Aside from
the dragon transformation,
it seems another possibility for
growth has presented itself.
[ISSEI]
What does that mean?
[DDRAIG]
I don't really know for sure.
But you live with
a bevy of beauties,
so what's one more cock‐tease?
Hey! No fair!
Akeno's squeeze‐bag!
Sweet! The bed's never
been this crowded before.
[RIAS] After everything
that's happened,
the girls wanted
to stay extra close.
Good morning. Sleep well?
[ISSEI] Good morning.
Yeah, I slept like the dead.
I feel bad for causing so much
trouble and worry for everyone.
There's really nothing
to be embarrassed about.
None of that was your fault.
[RIAS]
It's strange.
I can remember bits and pieces.
[RIAS]
The details are all foggy,
but I remember the warmth.
The phantom memory
of that feeling
still lingers in my chest.
What about you?
I got nothin'.
I'm sorry, really.
It's fine. You mean
the world to me.
I'm happy being with you
just the way you are.
[RIAS] That's right.
That's how it should be.
[ISSEI] I don't really
get what's going on,
but I know one thing for sure!
Rias's boobs are the tits!
Nipplage in my face!
Welcome home!
Hope you had a nice trip!
Looks like travel suits you.
[FATHER laughs]
Such a pleasant surprise
your family owns
a travel agency!
And were gracious enough to
give us a trip around the world
as a gift for opening our home!
Good to see you, Irina!
[ISSEI chuckles]
The trip provided a great way
to mask our time
in the underworld.
Welcome home!
I'm so glad that you're back!
‐‐[MOTHER] Hi, Asia!
‐‐[FATHER] Oh, Asia, dear!
[FATHER]
We missed you most of all!
It's true. Hardly a day went by
where we didn't ask ourselves,
"What's Asia up to now?" or
"I wonder how she's doing?"
Well, as you can see,
I'm doing just fine!
And you can thank Issei
and the rest for that.
I'm so grateful!
[laughs] Please, dear.
It's nothin' to cry about.
Sweetie, we didn't mean
to get you worked up!
[ASIA]
Oh, no, I'm sorry!
It's sweet that they treat Asia
like one of their
actual children.
While my place as their real son
continues to shrink
in the distance.
[MOTHER] Can you blame us?
I mean, take a look!
Asia is just so much cuter!
I'd take Asia as our
daughter in a heartbeat!
Thanks! It's just...
I never knew my
real mom and dad,
so hearing you both say
something that generous
makes me really happy.
You can think of us
as your real parents
from here on out, if you'd like.
Thank you, mom.
Thank, you dad.
[ISSEI]
That's right.
Family. That means
you're not alone.
We're all in this together,
no matter what comes at us.
Now let's make sure to
look after each other.
Okay then. It's a deal!
would you extend your
hospitality to our new friend?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
[ISSEI chuckles] Mom and Dad,
I'd like you to meet Rossweisse.
She's, uh...
She's a new teacher
at the school,
and since my father
renovated your home,
I knew there was enough room.
Huh?
It's a summary of the benefits
package for servants
[ROSSWEISSE] No way! The
insurance premium's so cheap!
And no term life
policy mumbo jumbo!
Valhalla never offered dental
or paid vacation days!
I know.
If Rias ever needed work,
she'd do really well
as an insurance rep.
She's actually buying a
Valkyrie on the cheap.
And the devil's whispers
were woven with temptation.
I could learn a lot from her.
[IRINA, AKENO laugh]
[RIAS]
So, what do you think?
Sign up with Team Gremory
for the big win!
The underworld would
be glad to have you!
You're really going make
her one of your evil pieces?
That's a pretty unusual
choice, isn't it?
Right now, Rias and I are the
only wizard‐type spellcasters
our squad has on the roster.
She complements our style.
[ISSEI]
I think Koneko's right.
would be best utilized
in long‐range attacks.
I'm thinking artillery support.
Perhaps the Norns themselves
spun the thread of fate
that led me to your house.
Ever since our first meeting
in the underworld,
things just seemed right.
[ROSSWEISSE]
Due to the Gremory family's
record of financial solvency,
and the top‐tier health
insurance and pensions plans,
I feel like I finally
have a secure future
now that I've become a
devil in your service.
Everyone, I look forward to our
joyous days of working together.
And so, Rossweisse
is part of our crew.
She's officially
our second rook,
and newest member
of Team Gremory.
the whole thing seemed more
casual than I expected.
[XENOVIA]
I prefer them short and sweet.
It was the same for me as well.
[ROSSWEISSE laughs]
This is a dream come true.
You can take your crummy
job and shove it,
you prune faced old pervert!
Now all your pieces
are in place, Gremory.
You're sitting in my chair,
without permission. Again.
Which means from here on out,
you face any challenges head‐on.
We will. I swear.
[AZAZEL]
I see that glint in your eyes.
It was a lot of trouble,
but in the end,
I guess it was worth it.
That's right. Hey, Issei!
[AZAZEL] The date of your
appearance on underworld TV
has finally been scheduled.
TV?
Oh shit, I nearly forgot.
So you're going to
be on television?
What do they want me to do?
After everything that's
happened to you,
maybe it'll be an up‐close
hero interview?
Hero? Who, me?
Ha! Yeah. I guess
I'm a big deal.
This dragon is ready.
How 'bout you?!
[KIDS]
It's Grabbin' time! Sing it!
This took a strange turn.
[KIBA]
"The Grabbin' Dragon Song"?
[KONEKO] Lyrics by Azazel,
and, apparently,
Sir Zechs wrote the music.
[GASPER] Choreography by
Serafall Leviathan.
[IRINA]
I expected underworld TV
to be a different
kind of sinister.
Uh. I went with him to the
studios on the day of the shoot.
I couldn't bring myself to
tell any of you guys about it.
You've become a beloved
kid's show host!
You're the coolest
guy I know, Issei!
Well, I wouldn't
say that. [laughs]
Hey, Asia.
The three‐legged race.
Let's show 'em how it's done!
Right!
[ISSEI]
♪ Then the Grabbin' Dragon ♪
♪ went walking
through the woods. ♪
♪ Gropin' and grabbin'
at anything he could. ♪
♪ What was he grabbin'?
Jubblies! ♪
♪ The Grabbin' Dragon's
struck again. ♪
[ROSSWEISSE] I am your
new civics class teacher.
Feel free to call me Rossweisse.
Some platinum‐haired
babe‐age at last!
It looks like the time for
sexy older women has come!
[MATSUDA] This new Rosewater
teacher chick is bangin'!
I can't wait to spit some
game at her fine ass!
so you losers might
stand a chance.
I'm still quite inexperienced.
I hope you'll be
gentle at first.
[ANNOUNCER] Our next event
is the three‐legged race.
All competitors to the start
line, all runners, gather up.
You ready, Asia?
Sure! Let's kick some butt!
[ISSEI] ♪ Once a Grabbin' Dragon
roamed across the land. ♪
♪ Gropin' and grabbin'... ♪
Issei! Asia!
You're amazing!
First place is all yours!
You guys're doing great!
Issei! Asia! Kick some butt!
Your form's lookin' really good!
You can do it! Go for the gold!
They actually have a shot.
I'll accept nothing
less than record time!
[AZAZEL] Inundating power is
what created the Chaos Brigade,
but you used the
overflow of power
to protect the people you love.
I'm sure that's how
it'll always be.
But hey, one day, if
the fighting ever ends.
If it ends?
when there's no one
left for you to fight?
I'm not like Vali, you know.
If a time of peace
like that ever arrives,
then I'll just shift my
focus to my dream.
To your dream?
[STUDENTS cheer]
[ISSEI, ASIA]
In‐out! In‐out! In‐out!
In‐out! In‐out!
[ISSEI] Asia will always
be by my side.
And we've got our friends
looking out for us.
And Rias is the glue that
keeps us all together.
That's why I can always find the
strength to try my very best!
[ISSEI]
Oh, yeah!
My dream?
[ISSEI] I thought I'd
made it pretty obvious.
My dream? It's to become
a harem king! Ha, ha, ha!
[ISSEI]
Rias!
[RIAS] My friends will
always come for me.
Issei will always
stand by my side.
I can read it in their smiles.
That's right.
Just as it should be.
And for now, it's enough.
No matter what troubles
might lie ahead,
or what may transpire
in our world.
I will do everything in my power
to keep those smiles in place.
Yes.
[RIAS]
Any time. For all time.