[ISSEI] Asia. Hold on
just a little longer.
[ISSEI] Comin' to save
you as fast as I can.
You'll be okay. I swear!
[RIAS, AKENO gasp]
[gasps]
[DIODORA]
I knew you would follow me.
That's why I put together
this little welcome party.
Piss off!
[DIODORA]
Now, it's time to play our game.
Unfortunately, today's Rating
Game has been cancelled.
Of course, you
already knew that.
So, we'll play my game instead.
Should you refuse to play,
or lose, Asia will become mine.
[ISSEI grunts]
[DIODORA] You'll have to
fight two separate battles,
simultaneously.
On the right path, two rooks
and eight pawns await.
The battle on the left will be
against my queen and bishops.
You can split your forces
any way you see fit.
Issei, Koneko,
Xenovia, and Gaspar,
take out his forces
on the right.
Ten of them against
the four of us?
Don't forget that Issei absorbed
all eight of our pawn pieces.
So, as far as power
is concerned,
we have a slight advantage.
[DIODORA]
Then let the game begin.
Oh, man! Here they come!
all of my pawns have already
been promoted to queen.
I like to hedge my bets.
[RIAS] Ha, ha. I knew you
weren't one to fight fair,
but this is a new
low, even for you.
Just a queen and two bishops?
They must have a lot of
confidence in themselves.
[RIAS] Xenovia, I need you
to keep those rooks busy.
[XENOVIA]
Fine.
I was made for fights like this.
[RIAS] Koneko, work crowd
control on those pawns.
[RIAS] Issei, give Gasper a
quick taste of your blood.
[gasps]
All right! We're cocked,
locked, and ready to rock!
[RIAS] Time to level
the playing field, Issei.
[ISSEI gasps]
Huh?
Hang on a sec, are you
sure that's okay?
No jokin'? Thank you, sexy boss!
Promotion to queen, bitches!
[ISSEI]
Koneko! Cover me!
[KONEKO]
Hm?
[ISSEI yells]
[ISSEI]
All too easy!
I make kicking ass look good.
Dress Break Snap!
[ISSEI chuckles]
Now you won't be able to fight?
‐‐[PAWN A yells]
‐‐[ISSEI grunts]
[GASPER] Is your face
gonna be okay, Issei?
Yeah. I'll be fine.
I just saw full frontal!
Dumbass. You're such a pervert.
‐‐[PAWN B grunts]
‐‐[ISSEI] Swaying!
‐‐[PAWN D yells]
‐‐[ISSEI] Okay, bad plan!
I can't concentrate when
I'm checkin' the curtains
and the drapes!
they're not responding
to your vulgar technique.
[ISSEI grunts]
Yeah. Thanks asshole.
that seals away any feelings
of embarrassment or modesty.
But, Dress Break
thrives on that!
It's the only thing
that makes it work!
[RIAS]
Enough!
[DIODORA'S QUEEN laughs]
Underestimating my master
was a foolish mistake.
Akeno! Kiba!
[BOTH grunt]
[AKENO]
Thunderbolt!
[DIODORA'S QUEEN gasps]
‐‐[KIBA yells]
‐‐[QUEEN grunts]
[yells]
[DIODORA'S QUEEN chuckles]
[Both gasp]
[KIBA] Any damage we do is
getting immediately healed
by the combined power
of the two bishops.
They fight well together!
Even better than
Riser's evil pieces!
[ISSEI grunting]
[PAWN F yells]
[KONEKO grunts]
[ISSEI grunts] What the hell
is up with these pawns?
Their attacks are
perfectly coordinated.
[GASPER]
The way they move.
It's almost like
a violent ballet.
Dancing as if their
hearts beat as one!
Heartbeat, huh?
Of course! This is
the perfect chance
to put my new special
technique to the test!
So how do we not die?
We have to do something, now!
[ISSEI]
Raw power isn't everything.
I have to look inward,
and harness the strength
of the Perv Side!
Horny thoughts, release!
Max Imagery, go!
Just like I did when I saw
all these sweet naked babes!
What's going on?
I'm confused.
[ISSEI] Dear enemy
Chi‐Chis, I'm a big fan.
could you tell me your
owners' attack plans?
[PAWN A]
Our first move is to stun,
or even blind the
little vampire kid.
[PAWN B] The six of
us against one of them
[PAWN C] Attack the vampire
while they're distracted!
It really worked!
That girl, that girl,
and that girl
are all targeting you, Gaspar!
Use your power to
freeze 'em, dude.
Okay, I'll do it!
[PAWN D] I can't believe it.
They stopped the attack cold!
Do you think they were
able to read our minds?
they would know we were
attacking the cat girl!
Those three are coming
after Koneko now.
Stop them in their tracks!
You got it, boss!
[KONEKO grunts]
I'll come to you.
Bastard! How are you
predicting our every move?
Are you reading our minds?
No, but I was able to hear
what was in your heart.
your lady heart's been
gossiping to it's neighbors.
I heard the voice of
your rib cushions!
[ISSEI] Behold, my new special
attack! Titty Translation!
But, I prefer to call
it Boobielingual!
[PAWN H, F yell]
That was amazing, but you
still gross me out.
The pawns.
[XENOVIA] Ha, ha.
It looks like I'll be able
to really cut loose now.
What?
When I first met my friend Asia,
I said some terrible things
I've now come to regret.
I called her a
witch and a heretic,
she still accepted me
and made me feel at home.
I will protect her.
Aura transfer!
Durandal to Ascalon!
With your powers combined,
I will smite my enemies.
I have the strength because
friendship is magic!
[ROOK A, B grunting]
[ROOK A, B scream]
[ISSEI]
Dude. I have a total chub.
We have to take
out both bishops
and the queen simultaneously.
The question is how?
I wish there was a way
we could help them out!
I have an idea. Try this.
[RIAS, AKENO grunting]
[ISSEI]
Hey, Akeno!
[RIAS]
Issei?
Oh, man. If you
can win that fight,
then I promise to take you
out for a date next Saturday.
You really think this
is gonna work, Koneko?
I doubt a date with me
is that kind of incentive,
but I'm flattered, though.
[ISSEI]
Hm?
What?
[AKENO giggles]
[RIAS] Issei! I can't believe
you'd ask her out like that
right in front of me!
It only shows
there's room in Issei's
heart for my love.
[RIAS] I don't want to hear that
from someone who has a sudden
wellspring of power after
being promised one measly
[AKENO] I'm not gonna
think of him as "your man,"
until after you've slept with
him and sealed the deal!
[RIAS] I sleep with
him all the time!
Last night was no exception.
In bed together,
He didn't stop touching
my breasts the whole night.
[AKENO] Issei tosses and turns
a lot when he's unconscious.
Yeah, well, how many of
you have kissed him twice?
Jealousy. It truly is
women's kryptonite.
[DIODORA'S QUEEN] I demand
you stop this nonsense!
You ignore me and fight
amongst yourselves over a boy?
[RIAS, AKENO]
Back off!
[DIODORA'S QUEEN screams]
Nice. Looks like we've won.
As I'd expect from
our king and queen.
One hell of a double
attack finisher!
Word.
‐‐[RIAS] This isn't over, Akeno.
‐‐[AKENO] Right, right.
[RIAS]
Listen, I'm serious!
[AKENO giggles]
So am I!
I think you and I are going
to need to have a little chat
about boundaries after
we've rescued Asia.
I have no objections, Rias.
Asia is like a little
sister to me as well,
so let's focus on getting
her back for now.
Only the king and his
two knights are left.
[RIAS] It's unorthodox to send
your queen out to the front.
Why keep knights in reserve?
[FREED] Yo, yo, yo!
Long time no see, suckers!
Yes! Yes! I'm hard
to kill, that's a fact.
As you can see, I'm still
totally alive and kicking!
What are you doing here?
After our last encounter,
I was scooped up by
that whack‐job, Vali.
To make a long story short,
the Chaos Brigade picked up
the psycho‐priest free agent
standing in front of you.
And that's why you're
here as Diodora's knight?
His knight?
[laughs]
[FREED]
I ate 'em both!
They were finger‐lickin' good!
Gross, dude.
[KONEKO] Okay. I think
I might actually puke.
[laughing]
[AKENO, RIAS gasp]
[FREED continues laughing]
That's nasty.
[FREED] Since we're
all old friends here,
let me share a tidbit
of gossip with you.
It's a tasty secret about
Diodora's household.
You know, all those pretty
young girls you just beat up?
Every one of them was
a well‐respected nun
before Diodora got his
greasy mitts on 'em.
A couple of 'em
were even saints!
Diodora the explorah loves
bringing passionate holy women
down to the depths of hell
with smiles and sweet talk.
That's how the freak gets off.
[FREED laughs]
Then Asia's just
another conquest?
there was a spoiled
highborn devil brat.
He saw a holy woman that
was as pretty as a peach.
Blonde, petite. I'm talkin'
totally his type.
But, the woman was a guarded
treasure of the Church,
so he knew there was no
way he could kidnap her
and get away with it.
So, the clever devil brat
came up with a plan.
If the people of the Church
saw her healing an injured
agent of Hell like him,
then they would excommunicate
her, so he took a chance.
Sorry. I was thinking, I don't
regret saving Diodora back then.
What the hell, man?
What are you telling
me here, you mutant psycho?
This is no time to be reckless.
[FREED] Once she hit
rock bottom in despair
over the Church's betrayal,
he'd snatch the girl up
when she was at her lowest
and make her his completely!
Ravishing both body and soul.
A man's gotta have a vice!
And Diodora loves breaking
the will of little young girls
like her more than
anything else!
[ISSEI]
Shut the fuck up!
You should save
those feelings of rage
for your upcoming
battle against Astaroth,
Oh, come on, man!
You expect me to let him live?!
I will face Freed.
Kiba.
Let me put a stop
to his filthy talk.
[FREED]
Look what we have here!
It's the pretty boy knight
who used his scary sword
to cut me down last time
we met! But, no hard feelings.
I got this bodacious body
upgrade because of you!
The super invincible
mutated monster Freed is
coming to getcha,
Mister Beauty Mark!
You wanna throw down,
I'll throw down, Nancy!
We'd all prefer that
you ceased to exist.
Oh, come on! When the hell
did you get so strong?
Well, it won't matter soon.
You chumps don't stand a
snowball's chance
in hell of beating the
big shots pulling the strings.
Perhaps, but you should
have saved your last words
for the god of death.
[FREED groans]
[ISSEI]
Diodora.
Come out, you douche hole!
You hear me?
Asia! Hey!
I knew you'd come.
[DIODORA laughs]
[DIODORA] What took
you guys so long, huh?
You should've seen her face
when I told her the
particulars of my plan.
Her expression was
absolutely priceless!
You're a real scumbag,
you know that?
[DIODORA]
I never get tired of it!
My favorite is the moments
when a woman of faith
and conviction
gives in to despair!
[DIODORA laughs]
That's enough, dickweed!
Dear Asia still clings to hope.
She still has her dear friends.
Especially you, Big Bad
Red Dragon Emperor.
Of course, I'm certain
he remembers
the fallen angel Raynare.
[ISSEI gasps]
had killed poor little Asia,
I had planned to off Raynare
and give Asia an Evil Piece,
and I mean both literally
and euphemistically.
You are disgusting!
I was caught off guard when
the Red Dragon Emperor,
or a reasonable facsimile
thereof, interfered in my plan.
I made the costly
mistake of waiting,
assuming a weak devil like
you would die instantly.
And to add
insult to injury,
Rias comes in to snatch
Asia up into her peerage.
[RIAS] You were behind it
all from the very beginning!
[DIODORA] But, don't worry.
I've forgiven you.
After all, being
part of your club
is the reason she's gotten
her hopes up so high.
She'll drop into the
deepest despair imaginable
once I've killed her friends
in front of her very eyes.
Asia is still
a virgin, isn't she?
I don't want the Red Dragon
Emperor's sloppy seconds.
[ISSEI]
Shut your mouth.
[DIODORA]
I do rather enjoy the idea
of stealing her away
from you, though.
Our own custom version
of Prima Nocta.
the mere thought of taking
Asia as she calls out your name
is absolutely delicious!
I said shut up!
[DDRAIG] Welsh Dragon!
Balance Breaker!
[ISSEI]
Diodora!
May I?
Go ahead.
[DDRAIG] Yeah. I'll back
your move, partner.
[DIODORA laughs] Nice armor!
The lights are a cute touch.
But, I have a snake direct from
Ophis supposedly so venomous,
its bite is rumored
to be an instant kill!
‐‐[ISSEI yells]
‐‐[DIODORA groans]
[DIODORA grunts]
Lumpen oaf!
I'm a high ranking devil,
you wretched boor!
Part of the bloodline of the
current Great Devil Beelzebub!
How can a well‐bred noble
like me lose to a lowly,
reincarnated savage like you?
It just isn't right!
It isn't fair!
[DIODORA screaming] It hurts!
It hurts! My beautiful face!
[ISSEI] Your barrier is
nothing compared to Vali's.
Pathetic weakling.
[DIODORA]
I don't understand.
I've gotten so much stronger
with the power Ophis gave me.
‐‐[ISSEI shouts]
‐‐[DIODORA grunts]
I refuse to let a filthy
dragon beat me like this!
[ISSEI grunts]
[DIODORA laughs]
And now you're trapped!
My magic barrier
is impenetrable!
A knuckle dragging idiot
like the soon‐to‐be‐dead
Dragon Emperor hasn't got a
chance in hell of beating me!
[ISSEI] I'll drag my knuckles
across your face, jerk‐off!
[DDRAIG]
Boost! Boost! Boost!
[DIODORA laughs]
Keep trying, it's cute!
[DDRAIG]
Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost!
[DIODORA gasps]
[ISSEI] I don't care
what happens to me.
No one makes Asia cry!
[DIODORA gasps, grunts]
[screams]
[DIODORA] Impossible!
I can't be defeated!
I beat Agares. I even had a
plan to deal with Sairaorg.
[DIODORA] There's no way
I'd ever expect to lose
to the Gremory family,
whose main claim to fame
is fraternizing
with their servants.
I am Diodora of
the Astaroth family!
[DDRAIG]
Boost! Boost! Boost!
[DIODORA screaming]
[DIODORA gasps]
[DIODORA screams]
[gasps]
Stay away from Asia, you prick!
If I ever see you near her
again, I'll smash your nads
into a thin, pinkish
paste, you got that?
[DIODORA gasps]
[ISSEI]
Asia!
[ISSEI gruning]
[ISSEI]
Dammit! She won't come loose!
Surely the power of the Welsh
Dragon is enough to break it.
[DIODORA]
This is a custom‐made seal
created especially for me
by a certain Longinus user.
I was given the promise it would
disarm when everything was over.
On the off chance that
you Gremory clowns
were actually able to defeat me.
I had the seal set to consume
her entirely, rather
than let her escape!
[DIODORA] I'd rather have
her disappear from existence
than hand her back over!
There's nothing you can do!
You will not get away with this.
[ISSEI]
Asia.
I'm still here.
[ISSEI] Ddraig, I'm
putting my trust in you.
[DDRAIG]
What are you talking about, kid?
Issei! Careful!
[ISSEI]
Asia. I'm sorry ahead of time.
[ASIA gasps]
Amp it up! We've got one chance!
Now, let's make it work!
[DDRAIG]
Boost! Boost! Boost!
Dress Break!
Balance Breaker!
Boosted Version!
[ASIA screams]
[GROUP gasps]
Beautiful.
Man, you're the worst.
But hey, you're also the best,
for a walking hard on.
Please be all right!
[DIODORA]
No way.
The Longinus seal's been broken.
Asia! Thank god. I wouldn't know
what to do if you were gone.
I mean it!
I'm not going to go anywhere,
because I'll always have you
and Issei to protect me,
right, Xenovia?
I'll look out for you no matter
what the future throws at us!
I'm so sorry.
You haven't done
anything to apologize for.
I'm just glad you're back with
us, where we can keep you safe!
Yes. I feel the same way.
I'm so glad that Asia's back.
But, now my brain's freaking out
about all the scary stuff
that happened today!
It's alright.
There, there, Gaspie.
[ASIA]
Issei!
Asia!
Sorry for bein' late.
I believed in you! I was sure
you would come for me, Issei.
I know you always will.
I'm so sorry you had to
go through all of this.
I'm fine, now, because
you're here with me, Issei!
Then let's get outta here.
It's time for us to go home.
All right! But, before we leave,
I'd like to say a little prayer.
You just got rescued.
What's there to pray about?
That's a secret.
[ASIA] Heavenly Father,
please hear my earnest prayer.
Continue protecting Issei and
help him grow, as you have done.
And please. From this day
forward, until the end of time,
let us live together in
peaceful bliss with Issei.
[ASIA] Swear to me.
We'll be together forever.
I don't want to be alone.
You promise, Issei?
How cute, but it's
impossible to defeat me.
It looks like he had an
incomplete transformation.
[GASPER]
Where is she?
[KONEKO]
What happened?
[RIAS gasps]
[ISSEI roars]
[ISSEI]
Asia!