[ISSEI]
I don't understand.
Asia?
[GASPER]
Where is she?
What happened?
[SHALBA]
I think that's quite enough of
this nonsense, Diodora Astaroth.
[RIAS]
Who are you?
Dear little sister of the
despicable and fake devil king.
Who I am is the one
and true descendent
of the Great Devil Beelzebub.
I am Shalba Beelzebub.
[RIAS]
What do you want?
[DIODORA]
Please, Shalba. Help me.
Imagine if both the old
and current devil kings
combined their strength.
[grunts]
And thus, a maggot dies.
[screams]
Current devil king, did he say?
Calling the true bloodline old
was the fool's first mistake.
His imagination was his second.
[RIAS] Of course, you were
the one behind the death
of the Glasya‐Labolas heir,
weren't you?
Can you believe the
sheer arrogance there?
Claiming to be the Devil King.
[CREUSEREY] I am the true
descendant and heir of Asmodeus.
I am Creuserey Asmodeus.
So, one of the great masterminds
finally shows themselves.
[CREUSEREY] As a member
of the True Satan Faction,
I have sworn to avenge
Cattleya Leviathan.
We are here to make use of
the power received from Orphis!
We will destroy this land,
and a new world created
for devils will be ours!
[RIAS] It doesn't
matter who you are.
You will still suffer for
what you did to Asia!
Little sister of the
imposter, Sir Zechs.
Nothing personal, but I
think I will kill you.
[ISSEI]
Asia? Asia?
Where did you run off to?
Come on, let's go home.
If you hide from me,
we won't be able to leave.
You're so silly, Asia.
Now, come on out.
Please, enough already!
He's lost it.
[ISSEI] I beat up those guys who
were bullying you, by the way.
[ISSEI]
I don't wanna play anymore.
Come on. Please, Asia?
[ISSEI whimpers]
Asia!
[IRINA yells]
[ROSSWEISSE grunts]
It seems like we're
about good to go here.
Agreed. I hope Rias and
the crew are all okay.
[ISSEI]
Please, Asia, can we go home?
We're supposed to do
the three‐legged race
in the sports festival.
We need to practice.
[RIAS]
Issei!
[KONEKO, GASPER sob]
[KIBA, AKENO sob]
[yells]
I swear I will kill you
for what you've done!
I'll cut you down piece by piece
until you scream for mercy!
[XENOVIA grunts. screams]
Xenovia, no!
[XENOVIA grunts]
[SHALBA]
Don't test me.
[XENOVIA grunts]
Bring Asia back, now!
Please, she's one
of my best friends!
She was so gentle,
and unbelievably kind!
Asia!
Hey, Rias. Do you know
where Asia might have gone?
We need to find her fast,
so we can leave. Help me.
Please, we can't go without her;
she's practically family.
Oh, Issei.
The princess of the Gremory
household has horrible taste.
Would the red filth like to
know where that girl went?
I sent her far
beyond our reality,
into the Dimensional Gap.
The exposure has surely
consumed her flesh by now.
To put it simply,
the bitch is dead.
[ISSEI growling]
[AZAZEL]
All right, Fafnir.
I'm gonna need a
little back up, 'kay?
[CREUSEREY grunts]
Prepare yourself and your
artificial existence for death!
Asmodeus. Understand that if
devils are going to flourish,
the last thing we need is
to have an unnecessary war.
An imposter who deals
not only with fallen angels,
but angels themselves has
no right to speak as a devil!
So what, we should
listen to you, a traitor?
Someone naiïve enough
to fall for the obvious
lies of the Chaos Brigade?
[SIR ZECHS] Creuserey,
as the Great Devil King,
I will eliminate anyone
who stands against
the current underworld.
What? What is this?
No, that's impossible!
How can this be?
You're a fraud, yet,
you defeat me? No!
That also eliminated
the snake and power
Orphis had placed within him.
Oh, perfect.
Well, I certainly didn't expect
you to show up in person.
Hi, Azazel.
It's been a while.
[RIAS]
Issei?
[DDRAIG]
Rias Gremory.
[gasps]
What is it, Ddraig?
[DDRAIG]
If you'd rather not die,
you should leave this
place immediately.
[RIAS]
What?
[DDRAIG]
As for you, Devil.
The one who calls
himself Shalba.
You made a poor decision,
and now you must pay.
[grunts]
[KIBA] His aura and
power are incredible!
[KONEKO]
And dangerous.
[RIAS]
Issei!
Answer me right now;
what's going on? Issei!
Who are you?
[SPIRIT VOICES moaning]
[ISSEI]
I, who shall awaken.
[SPIRIT GIRL'S VOICE]
The time has finally come.
[SHALBA]
I don't know you.
[ISSEI] I am the Heavenly
Dragon who stole the principle
of domination for God.
[SPIRIT WOMAN'S VOICE A]
It has always been this way.
[SPIRIT OLD MAN'S VOICE A]
That is correct.
Always and forever.
[ISSEI] I mock the infinite
and fret over the dream.
[SPIRIT MAN'S VOICE A]
What the world desires.
[SPIRIT WOMAN'S VOICE A]
What the world rejects.
[ISSEI] I shall become the
Red Dragon of Domination.
[SPIRIT MAN'S VOICE B]
Has always been power.
[SPIRIT WOMAN'S VOICE B]
Has always been love.
[SPIRIT MAN'S VOICE C]
No matter the occasion,
you always choose
the path to ruin.
[ISSEI] I shall drown you in
the depths of crimson purgatory.
Juggernaut Drive!
[AZAZEL]
If we defeat you here,
are you finally going
to let peace win out?
How cute, but it's
impossible to defeat me.
Well, then can you clue us in
as to why you're doing this now
when you've never shown any
interest in this world before?
Indeed. I would also like to
know why you are leading
a brigade of terrorists.
[ORPHIS]
For a world of silence.
All I want is to return
to the Dimensional Gap,
otherwise known as my home,
and reclaim that silence.
[AZAZEL]
The Dimensional Gap is her home?
If I remember correctly...
[AZAZEL]
Of course, Vali. I understand.
I know what you want!
Vali, do you truly believe
we shall find it here?
The Dimensional Gap
is almost a void.
I am confident we will find it.
[VALI]
Issei Hyodo.
There's been a change of plans.
We're going to the underworld.
Why so suddenly, though?
Is that a person?
[ISSEI roars]
I need you, Asia!
Oh, Issei.
[ISSEI growls]
[SHALBA grunts]
[SHALBA grunts, yells]
Don't play with me. Face my
light of judgment, if you dare!
[DDRAIG]
Divide!
Divide! Divide! Divide!
[SHALBA]
He has Divine Dividing power?
I remember that.
Issei's using the power
that he stole from Vali!
[SHALBA] Why must Vali insist
on standing in my way?
[ISSEI roars]
[SHALBA yells]
[ISSEI yelling]
[SHALBA]
No. You bastard!
This creature must be
the Dragon of Domination!
[GASPER gasps]
Hey, Gasper, did you
just try to stop time?
I did, but it didn't
even faze him!
[ISSEI yelling]
[DDRAIG]
Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost!
[SHALBA grunts]
We can't stay here, Rias.
If we do, we're
all going to die!
Let's go. I don't want
to either, but we must!
No. I won't.
[AKENO]
Rias!
[KIBA]
I'm sorry, we're going!
[DDRAIG]
Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost!
Longinus Smasher!
Damn you! Red Dragon and
White Dragon, damn you both!
[ISSEI roars]
I wish there was more we could
do than just sit here and watch!
Yeah, you and me both.
Anyone know how we can make
Issei change back to normal?
I don't know.
[VALI] I had a feeling it
was the Juggernaut Drive.
[RIAS]
Vali, why are you here?
I sensed a change
in Issei's power.
I wanted to see what it was.
Is that him down there?
It looks like your servant had
an incomplete transformation.
Do you know if there's any
way to change him back?
[VALI]
In an incomplete state,
there is a chance it
will happen naturally.
But if not, he'll use up
his life force until he dies.
[ARTHUR] Either way,
you should be worried;
his life is most
certainly in danger.
[ARTHUR] Oh yes, we happened
to cross paths with her
while we were moving through
the Dimensional Gap.
[BIKOU]
That is one lucky girl.
She would have been exposed
to the void, if not for us.
A body cannot withstand
that kind of pressure
and will usually dissipate
into the nothingness.
[RIAS] If we tell him
that Asia is safe,
Issei should be able to
regain control over himself.
Merely approaching him will kill
you. I won't stop you, though.
I will go with you!
[RIAS]
I'm going alone.
[GASPER]
Rias, wait!
[RIAS]
I won't let you die.
[VALI]
Hm?
I'm begging you to do whatever
you can to save Rias and Issei.
Can you with the power of
the White Dragon Emperor?
Do you think you're
strong enough?
[ISSEI roars]
[ALBION] Vanishing
Dragon Balance Breaker!
What are you
planning to do, Vali?
[VALI] I'm just going to
contain his power a bit.
[ALBION] You have to touch the
opponent to use Divine Dividing.
I don't recommend
that right now.
[VALI]
Yeah. An eye for an eye.
A dragon for a dragon.
[VALI]
I, who shall awaken.
I am the Heavenly Dragon
who lost all to the
principal of domination.
I envy the infinite
and long for the dream.
I shall become the White Dragon
that masters the
path of domination.
I shall lead you to the
farthest limits of innocence.
Juggernaut Drive!
[gasps]
[ISSEI growls]
[ISSEI roars]
[VALI]
Issei Hyodo. Tell me.
Are you not my rival
and sworn enemy?
[ISSEI roars]
[ALBION]
Divide!
Divide! Divide! Divide!
[RIAS]
Issei!
I can just leave
the rest up to you.
[RIAS]
Issei, please.
Issei, come back to me!
‐‐[RIAS yells]
‐‐[ISSEI roars]
Issei!
[ISSEI roars]
It was sweet of you to help.
My name's Asia
Argento, by the way.
But please, just call me Asia.
To make lots of
life‐long friends.
To get to know them well,
and do cool things.
To care for each other,
and have fun.
That's my dream.
[ISSEI]
Asia.
Issei. I know it was short,
but I was blessed to
have a friend like you.
You made me happy.
[RAYNARE]
But she's dead, isn't she?
She's stone cold dead
and you're still whining
about protecting her.
Oh, come on, as if
I couldn't tell
you were a virgin from
the first time I saw you.
‐‐[RAYNARE laughs]
‐‐[ISSEI gasps]
I know! It was so stupid the way
you'd try to play super hero if
I complained or looked helpless.
It's true. You wanted
to believe it so badly
that you never even caught on.
Would you please die for me?
[ISSEI screams]
[RIAS] Look at me, Issei.
Don't you know who I am?
[VALI] Strange. His energy
signature is not purely dragon.
[ORPHIS]
Something else is inside him.
Look who showed up.
Hello, Orphis.
[RIAS] Calm down!
Listen to my voice! Issei!
[RIAS screams]
I never meant to
make you cry, Issei.
I'm sorry. Please, forgive me.
Goodbye.
I couldn't protect my friend.
Again, I couldn't protect her.
[RAYNARE] You wouldn't
have been able to save her
back then anyway.
And surprise, surprise,
you can't save her now.
[ISSEI roars]
Asia!
[RIAS screams]
Issei, please!
[ISSEI roars]
No!
‐‐[RIAS] Issei.
‐‐[ISSEI gasps]
[ISSEI]
Rias?
[RIAS] Issei. I want
you to be in my life.
You give it meaning that
I never knew existed!
You better come back
to me right now,
or else I swear I'll disappear
right along with you!
Please come back.
Issei!
[ISSEI gasps]
Rias. It's you.
[ISSEI]
Rias, it was you.
You came back to me.
Oh, Issei, you came back.
Issei. My Issei is back!
What's that?
Something that
was inside of him.
[grunts]
‐‐Welcome back!
Nice moves!
Issei!
How do you feel?
[ISSEI]
Okay. I think.
You guys, um, hey.
[ISSEI gasps]
Asia!
[KIBA]
Vali and his allies rescued her.
It was a chance
thing, that's all.
[ISSEI]
Asia! Asia!
Issei?
What happened?
Asia! You're o‐‐
‐‐Asia! Oh, Asia!
‐‐Um.
‐‐I thought you were gone.
‐‐Xenovia, I'm okay. I swear it.
‐‐You're alive!
Oh, Asia. We'll be
friends forever, won't we?
‐‐Like forever forever, though?
‐‐Of course.
Then you can't leave me
like that ever again, okay?
I won't. I'll always
be here for you.
[XENOVIA sobbing]
Asia!
I know.
[VALI]
Issei Hyodo. Take a look.
[ISSEI]
Huh?
That is what I wanted to see.
[RIAS]
It can't be.
[VALI]
Dragon of Dragon.
He is often called DD,
the true Red Dragon God Emperor.
Great Red.
[ISSEI]
He chooses to live in
the Dimensional Gap,
and flies around for
all eternity in there.
Orphis wants that, as well.
My goal is to defeat him.
[ISSEI]
For real?
To become the true
White Dragon Emperor.
The White Dragon God Emperor.
Someday, I'll take
down the Great Red.
[ORPHIS] Great Red.
It's been a while.
[ISSEI gasps]
Who is that?
I didn't see her until just now!
The dragon god of infinity,
Ouroboros Dragon.
Wait, what did you say?
No, the bad dragon is her?
So, that's the leader
of the Chaos Brigade?
[ORPHIS] One day. One day soon
I am going to obtain my silence.
[VALI]
Tell me something, Issei.
Do you want to defeat me?
I still don't want you dividing
Rias's or Akeno's boobs in half.
Actually, I don't want you
dividing anyone's boobs.
[laughs]
You are such a
bizarre little man.
Get strong, Issei.
Don't you let me down.
We should probably head back.
Come on, let's go home, now.
Yeah! Let's roll!
[KUROKA yawns]
[KUROKA] Welcome back.
Did you find Great Red?
Only for a moment,
but we did, yes.
[KUROKA]
That's all?
[ARTHUR] Well, a few other
things happened, too.
[KUROKA gasps]
Cattleya, Creuserey, and Shalba.
The honorable blood of the of
the previous great devil kings
ran through them. They should
have lived honorably as well.
[BIKOU] Why did you choose to
save the Red Dragon Emperor?
That's rather unlike you.
It was only a whim.
Nothing more than a whim.
[VALI] And perhaps, it isn't
actually over yet.
Remember this, Issei Hyodo.
Look, um, I'm such an asshole.
I didn't mean to make things
difficult for you again.
I'm sorry.
You are the absolute best.
Yeah! You are the absolute
best servant that I have!
Score! And you have
the absolute best‐‐
[RIAS]
Issei?
[ALL gasp]
Issei!
[VALI] Remember that what
you consider to be peace,
can often be painful for others.
[RIAS]
Issei!
To go see Vali. Now.
[LOKI] The twilight of the
gods is fast approaching.
Oh, yay, he finally
came to pick me up!
[AZAZEL] You still
haven't done it yet, right?
I know what's going on.
Even if it means you
have to lie to yourself,
you always try
so hard, don't you?