How is he? Is Kanata okay?
I had to operate
without any anesthesia.
It's amazing how well
he tolerated the pain.
He's so strong. Really.
He's stable and resting up now.
Well, that's good.
So his arm is gone?
[QUITTERIE] Yeah. There's
no way to get it back.
But, I'm sure someone will
buy him a nice prosthetic.
Right? Your majesty?
[LUCA] Quitterie, we could
do without the snark,
I can't be nice right now.
While I sympathize with
Charce's upbringing.
I'm just still
upset about Kanata.
[CHARCE] Zack. You should
probably lock me up.
When we get to Astra,
I want you to call the
police and report me.
Along with the originals
who created all of us.
You sure?
[door opens]
[KANATA]
There's no need for any of that.
[CHARCE]
Kanata?
[ARIES]
What are you doing?
[QUITTERIE]
You need to be in bed!
No, it hurts too much to sleep!
Also, I'm kinda lonely.
Look, Charce.
I'm not mad at you
for what happened.
I made a decision,
and this was the result.
In fact, if you hadn't shut down
the sphere when you did,
I'd probably be dead.
So, thank you.
If we explain what happened,
they shouldn't charge you.
Everything's going to work out.
But you have a choice to make.
Will you live for yourself
from here on out?
Wait, you're willing
to trust him?
Yeah, I am.
What if he activates the sphere?
He can take my left
arm, too, Ulgar!
Look, we've gotta
trust each other!
'Cause we've been through
way too much crap not to!
Nothing has changed!
If any of you have got
a problem with that,
then I'll take
you on one‐handed!
Oh, yeah? You gonna
bleed on us, pal?
No one's gonna fight you on it.
We just wanted the
captain's opinion.
It's not like we're
planning to shun anybody.
We're a team, after all.
That's right. So work hard.
Make that twice as hard.
To cover for Kanata.
You guys. I am truly sorry.
Thanks to you all,
I can be myself.
From now on, I want
to be my own original.
And I want us to
go home together!
Of course.
That's the plan.
Besides, we still have
a few questions left to ask.
I know.
I'll tell you the whole truth.
The secrets of Astra handed down
through the Vixia royal family.
‐‐[KANATA groans]
‐‐[CHARCE gasps]
‐‐My arm hurts.
‐‐[QUITTERIE] No duh, stupid!
‐‐What can we do?
‐‐[KANATA] I'm kinda dizzy.
Again, I say "no duh!"
You've lost a ton of
blood, Captain Obvious!
He needs to be
resting right now.
This Vixia truth stuff
will have to wait.
Yes. Of course.
Listen up. We still
need supplies.
Tomorrow, we forage!
[STUDENTS]
Aye, yeah!
[KANATA weakly]
[ZACK]
Not you, Kanata!
[ARIES]
Team B‐5, camp log.
Day seven on Planet Galem.
Fortunately, this
place has both food
and water in abundance.
And the climate's stable, too.
Replenishing our supplies
is proving to be easy.
Kanata's been
focusing on sleeping
and nourishing his body,
so that he can heal up
as fast as possible.
[chiming]
[KANATA groans]
[ARIES] To be honest, I think
he might be a bit bored.
I feel bad for the guy.
[KANATA] ...it's so easy,
it's almost stupid.
[ARIES]
It's okay, though.
I've been visiting him
a lot to keep him company.
[ARIES]
Everything here is so shiny.
This planet really is
beautiful, don't you think?
For sure.
It's definitely
a sight to behold.
You know, I'll never
forget this trip.
The pretty view, or the
time we've spent together.
[KANATA chuckles] Thanks to
your photographic memory.
[ARIES]
Come on, that's not what I mean!
I'm talking about feelings!
[KANATA]
Right. No need to shout.
I feel the same way, actually.
This was all a very
precious experience.
Though to be fair, it did
have a few rough patches.
[ARIES] Speaking of.
How's your arm feeling?
[KANATA] It hurts like nobody's
business, but I'll live.
I need to toughen it up.
[ARIES]
How are you gonna touch it up?
[KANATA] That's not what I said.
Please don't touch it, okay?
[laughs]
[gasps]
[ARIES]
Despite everything,
I kinda wish this trip would
last a little bit longer.
[BOTH gasp]
[ARIES]
In a way. I'm sad it's ending.
At long last,
we've gathered enough food
and water to leave Galem!
It's finally time
to head home to Astra.
[KANATA] All right!
Everyone ready to leave?
[QUITTERIE giggles] You guys,
I thought we were totally
done for when that Burr‐Burr
attacked us head on!
[YUN‐HUA] Right? I never would
have imagined that the dull
fish's tentacles would
prove to be so useful!
Get this, Luca.
Did you know the purple
mandala flower smells awful?
[KANATA] Thanks a lot, everyone,
now I feel all left out!
Ah! Heh! Ha! Hoo!
[KANATA]
What are you laughing about?
Is that even a laugh?
This was our last
stop before home.
We'll be on Astra
next time we land.
Yes, if it all goes smoothly.
It's always possible our
originals could find out
that we're still alive.
They may do something
to sabotage us.
Yeah, I suppose they might.
Isn't there a way we
can prepare for that?
Maybe. Let's hear what
Charce has to say.
[CHARCE sighs]
[ZACK] Now entering
faster‐than‐light travel.
Destination: Planet Astra.
[KANATA]
Right.
Everyone is here and
there's lots of time.
Charce, can you tell us
everything you know?
Please.
[CHARCE] Yes. These are
the secrets of Astra.
[CHARCE] In the past, there
was a planet known as Earth.
When an enormous asteroid
threatened Earth's extinction,
humanity made the bold choice
to migrate to a new planet.
"Per Aspera. Ad Astra."
Overcome hardships
to reach your goals.
That was their slogan.
The idea that humanity
rallied behind.
[CHARCE] Two years later,
they discovered a planet
with a similar
topography to Earth.
It was a miracle.
The planet, which was
5,000 light years away,
was dubbed Astra.
Yeah, that all adds up
with what Polina told us.
The question is...
Why hide it?
Especially since it's such
an important part of history.
Because it's a long‐kept secret.
Few people know.
Only the highest‐ranking
government officials
and the king of Vixia.
The Vixia Royal Quarter was
built to safeguard this secret.
Which is why it's such
a heavily protected area.
The information has
been passed down
the royal line from
one king to the next.
Unfortunately, our
current king intended
to be the last one,
ruling for eternity.
So, there must be
facts we don't know.
Like actual historical events
that were never taught
to us in school.
[CHARCE] The history you know
is a distortion of the truth.
But it was all done
in the name of peace.
The artificial
wormhole was the key
to making humanity's
exodus project possible.
Gates were built
all over the world.
Over 10,000 tunnels
connected Earth to Astra.
[CHARCE] However, creating
cities out of nothing
was a massive undertaking.
Construction was
quite the challenge.
But... since existing
technologies could be
transported via wormhole,
it accelerated the
process exponentially.
Meanwhile, back on
Earth, the exodus plan
which had been secret up to that
point, was finally revealed.
Not surprisingly,
the people were confused
and began to panic.
And then...
...war broke out over
who would control
the new territories
and resources on Astra.
[ALL gasp]
[CHARCE]
Religions, cultural histories,
political power struggles.
The impending exodus
served as a trigger
to make all of humanity's
conflicts come to a head.
In the year 2052 we lost
half of Earth's population
in just two short months.
Wow, I can't believe
that many people died.
The wormholes only served
to exacerbate the problem.
With that technology,
assassinations,
as well as other acts of
terrorism, became commonplace.
How awful‐‐the wormholes
were created to help people.
Much of ou history
is like that.
Doomed to repeat itself.
[CHARCE] Horror comes
after creation. Always.
Afterward, the survivors of the
war regretted their foolishness
and unforgiveable actions,
and henceforth vowed
to make their new
world one of peace.
The concept of
nations was erased.
Natural resources
became public property.
We adopted one unified
language and removed
potential sources of conflict,
such as religion and weaponry.
Humanity used the
opportunity presented
by the exodus to
reset everything
and achieve world peace.
Sounds familiar.
Not too unlike
the history we know.
[CHARCE] It took the next
four years for humanity
to complete its emigration.
On July 5th, 2057, shortly
after the move was completed,
the asteroid struck Earth
right on schedule.
Once society had settled
into their new home,
the world government
was established.
Its first order of business:
the permanent closure
of all wormholes.
They just decided
to get rid of them?
Given the course of events,
it was the most rational
decision to ensure peace.
All existing wormholes
were destroyed,
along with the
technology behind them.
The predecessor of the royal
family, Vix Industries,
was the company integral
in wormhole development,
and thereby charged
with disposing of them.
As a reward for their
contribution to world peace,
they were granted
high status as rulers,
establishing the
Vixia Royal Quarter.
[KANATA] So, where'd you get
the wormhole that you used?
[CHARCE] Even though they'd
reported them all as destroyed,
the Vix family secretly
kept one open.
Wait, but if the world
government terminated
all the portals, then...
Yes?
[KANATA] How'd they explain
the big move to everyone?
[CHARCE]
Good question.
Without the wormhole, there was
no plausible explanation.
That's why
they removed the event
from history altogether.
‐‐[ALL gasp]
‐‐[LUCA] For real?
[CHARCE] There was no way
to explain the migration,
so instead they created
an alternative history.
That's crazy!
You can't just up and
erase history like that!
What about all the
construction and development?
Civilization doesn't just
pop up outta nowhere!
What did they tell everybody?
Additionally, it doesn't
make sense the immigration
finished in 2057.
It's 2063 now.
That's only six years.
It would take longer to reach
our level of civilization.
Yeah, for sure.
Even with the advanced
technology that sorta thing
would take, like,
a century or something.
[gasps]
[ZACK]
That's it. I get it.
They rolled back the
calendar 100 years.
‐‐[ALL gasp]
‐‐[KANATA] No way!
What does that even mean?
According to our history,
the world government
was founded in 1963,
but really, it was 2063,
back in the early
pioneering days.
Changing the date justified
our level of technology.
You can't turn
back civilization!
How'd they pull that off?
The government made the choice,
and then they didn't tell
new generations about the lie.
That was all.
Like it'd really be that easy!
[CHARCE] Well, did anyone
here know the truth?
[gasps]
[CHARCE]
Your parents didn't know.
Nor their parents before them.
The only citizens
who would know
are those who
experienced the exodus.
They'd have to be
over 100 years old.
Only a handful of people
from that generation
are alive today.
This new history is the
only truth humanity knows.
That's messed up.
[YUN‐HUA]
Hold on.
I'm trying to keep up.
According to the history
we were taught, 1963 is the year
World War Three
broke out, right?
The world was all but destroyed.
It's the event that
unified us as a whole
and helped us strive
for world peace.
What happened to all that?
It was a clever fabrication.
Nothing more than
a fictitious conflict.
Resetting civilization
and the recovery from the
war would line up nicely.
Conveniently,
there was an international
crisis 100 years prior.
It nearly led to nuclear war.
So they used that to
connect the timelines.
Whoa. Please slow down.
You're really starting to
lose me a bit, professor.
Yeah, same here.
[YUN‐HUA]
Okay.
If we summarize
everything we know,
it looks kinda like this.
Humanity moves to a new planet
and shuts down the wormholes.
Then they rewind the
calendar by 100 years
so the era matches
the societal level.
They connect Earth's
history with a new story.
Hold on.
So the history before
that time is just gone?
That's impossible. It has to be.
It's not, though I
imagine revising history
proved to be a rather
difficult project.
While changing things
like electronic records
wasn't a huge
challenge in itself,
silencing the general population
was a different matter.
Still, the new history
was eventually
accepted by the population.
The first generation prohibited
the truth from getting out,
and everyone played along.
The unification of
nations and languages
was a big factor.
But more importantly...
The first generation
was completely
on board with everything.
They were given a second chance
to finally clean up
their foolish history.
That desire won out.
All for the sake of peace.
Our foolish history.
Uh! I'm sorry, Polina!
I didn't mean it
as an insult to you.
[POLINA]
It's fine. Believe it or not,
I do understand where
they were coming from.
But, it's a bit
sad to think about
all the things that were
erased for the cause.
[CHARCE] Well, I wouldn't say
it was completely erased.
In Vixia, there are still
a few records of the past.
Thank you‐‐that's something
to look forward to
when we get to Planet Astra.
And perhaps I could
even tell everyone
more about Earth's history.
[BEEGO]
You weren't frozen forever
in a big ice machine
for nothin'!
Hey. That's rude!
[FUNICIA]
It's Beego, not me.
Huh? Wait, so as
far as we know,
the year is 2063, right?
[LUCA]
Yep, it's the 100th anniversary
of the world government.
So then that means
the real year is...
...actually 2163?
Wait, that means...
Polina's really...
This might be tough to hear.
But you didn't sleep
for 12 years,
it was more like 112.
[POLINA sighs]
[KANATA]
Whoa! Polina down!
[ZACK]
Bring her over here!
[QUITTERIE]
Move you, idiots!
[FUNICIA] That means she's
actually like 140, right?
[LUCA] Maybe don't say
that out loud. Ever.
[BEEGO] One‐hundred‐and‐forty!
One‐hundred‐and‐forty!
I'm so old.
Man. This is insane.
I don't even know
what to say right now.
It never occurred to me
to question our history.
Like whether it was
real or not, y'know?
It's not your fault.
That's just how the
education system is on Astra.
My brother did say
the adults were lying.
So, yeah.
But they aren't
lying on purpose.
They're only repeating
the lies they were taught.
The fault is with the generation
that started all this.
It's kind of complicated.
A few lies don't seem
like a big deal
if it's for the sake of peace.
Yeah, you're not wrong.
And it might sound weird,
but in the end,
we're not really that
different from Charce.
We think this way because
it's how we were all raised.
Still though.
It doesn't mean that
has to continue.
We have to look at the
world with our own eyes,
think about it,
and ask questions.
Once we can do those things,
we'll be able to grow
into our true selves.
"Our true selves," huh?
That's some heavy stuff.
[KANATA]
Yeah well, maybe it needs to be.
It's not something we can
think about by ourselves.
It's something every
citizen on Astra
needs to consider.
We've gotta make it back home.
That way we can tell
them all our story!
[STUDENTS]
Aye, yeah!
Our first problem is:
What do we do
about our originals?
Once they find out
their plan failed,
they're sure to come after us.
There's more to that.
We can't return
to Astra unprepared.
What if the truth
about the wormholes
and history fell
into the wrong hands?
It might not matter, but,
there's a division in
the government tasked
with keeping the secrets hidden.
I bet they're the
ones responsible
for takin' out my brother.
He found out about
the clones, and in turn,
uncovered the secrets of Astra.
[KANATA] Why don't send
a message to the media
before we land?
Once we get close to Astra,
we should be able
to send a message
from our handhelds.
You wanna contact the press?
Wouldn't it be risky
to get in touch
with an unpredictable
group like that?
If the government finds
out, we're done for.
So, basically,
we need to find someone
trustworthy who can help us
make a big reveal,
but in such a way
that the government
can't possibly deny it?
That's kind of a tall
order. Any ideas?
[ALL sigh]
Yeah. Maybe.
There was a police officer
that worked with my brother,
and he even investigated
Eposito's corruption.
Lieutenant Grace,
I think. In Mousanish.
[KANATA]
That's it!
[ULGAR]
Oh, but...
I don't have his contact info,
and I can't look
him up from here.
[ALL sigh]
I've got it, we could just
send a message to my mom!
I'm sure she'd be
happy to get in touch
with Lieutenant Grace
on our behalf.
We can trust her.
I know she's on our side.
[YUN‐HUA gasps]
[LUCA]
That's an awesome idea!
[ARIES]
You really think so?
Yeah.
When all's said and done,
she did raise you after all.
If you're anything alike,
then I'm sure
she's a good woman.
[gasps]
[KANATA]
Let's do it.
'Kay. That sounds great.
Let's make that the plan.
Huh?
Yo, smooth move, Captain.
Even I'm a little jealous.
Yeah, but they're still
not as cute as us.
Obviously not.
You're all idiots.
[BEEGO] Ah, young love,
blooming in the depths of space!
[ULGAR grunts]
[giggles]
[ARIES]
Team B‐5, Camp Log.
Before arriving at Astra,
we decided to drop out
of faster‐than‐light drive
in order to send
an important message.
[ARIES] One vital to
not only our future,
but the future of
Planet Astra as a whole.
It's a big responsibility.
A lot has happened on our
journey through space,
but since the message
is for my mom,
it only feels right that I
would be the one to send it.
[ARIES] I thought it would be
best to attach our camp log
along with the message.
[ALL gasp, laugh]
[chiming]
[ARIES]
Mom, we're all doing okay,
and we're coming home!
[ALL gasp]
Well, we've come this far.
Now it's up to your
mom and the police.
[ZACK] I just hope our message
got through to them okay.
[QUITTERIE] Mm... I don't
know if I can take this.
I'm so nervous!
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Don't worry. Have faith.
In both my mom
and Sergeant Face.
[KANATA]
Lieutenant Grace!
[ZACK]
Hey, Charce.
[CHARCE]
Yes, what?
[ZACK] If the king can
no longer rejuvenate,
who will be next in
line for the throne?
He technically has
no direct heir,
so it'd probably be someone
from the extended
Vix royal family.
I have a good guess
who it could be.
The man behind
Seira's assassination.
Once I get back,
I intend to expose
his entire scheme.
[ULGAR]
You need some help?
I'm gonna be a
journalist, remember?
I'd like that.
It's sad, but I guess
our adventure is over.
[KANATA]
No, it's not.
If anything, it's only
just beginning.
When we set foot on Astra,
our lives will change forever.
[alarm beeps]
What is that?
It's a proximity alert.
Everyone to the bridge.
[LUCA]
Could it be our welcoming party?
[ZACK]
I don't know.
[YUN‐HUA] What if the
government found out?
[gasps]
This is the Spaceship Astra.
Do you copy, over?
[ZACK]
Can you hear us?
Please. Awaiting response!
We are Team B‐5. Do you copy?
[MARK]
You summoned me, sire?
Yes, Mark.
There's something I
must discuss with you.
[MARK]
At last!
He's finally going to
designate me as the next heir!
Of course, first, I had to
get rid of Princess Seira
and arrange for her clone
to go into space.
But all of that waiting and
effort is about to pay off.
After all these years,
I will be the new king.
[SOLDIER 12A]
Hold it! Stop right there!
[NOAH]
What's the meaning of this?
I ordered you not
to let anyone in here.
We're the police.
[NOAH gasps]
King Noah, you are
hereby charged with
illegal production
of human clones
and solicitation of murder.
[NOAH]
I beg your pardon.
Just who are you
suggesting I killed?
[GRACE]
Oh, excuse me.
What I meant to say was
"attempted murder."
Attempted?
[GRACE] We received a message
from a group of teens
claiming to be the missing
students from Caird High.
After reviewing their
claims and photos,
we confirmed all of
Team B‐5 is alive.
[NOAH gasps]
Impossible!
Your reaction tells me
you understand the situation.
I'm afraid you have
no authority over us.
So, we'll be taking you
into custody now, "sire."
Damn you, Charce!
[gasps]
Not so fast. You're
Mark Vix, correct?
We'd like to ask
you a few questions
regarding the murder
of Princess Seira.
[POLICE RADIO chatter]
[DETECTIVE 12A]
Lieutenant Grace.
What's the story
behind Vixia anyway?
It's a locked box of
secrets, and I suppose
you could say that the king
holds the key to all of them.
But that won't be
the case much longer.
The secrets will get out,
and that will throw
the world into chaos.
When the dust settles though,
I think it'll make this
a healthier place to live.
[DETECTIVE 12A]
Forgive me.
I'm afraid I don't
quite understand.
[GRACE]
You will soon enough.
Everything you think
you know about Astra
will be turned upside down.
[ZACK] This is Spaceship Astra,
crewed by Caird High,
Team Group B‐5. Please answer!
[COMM OFFICER 12A]
Can you hear us? Please respond.
This is the Astra.
We hear you! Over.
[COMM OFFICER 12A] This is the
Astra Planetary Government.
Thanks to your help,
your originals have
been taken into custody.
[GROUP gasps]
[COMM OFFICER 12A] When you're
ready, we'll escort you
back to the surface.
And welcome home.
[BOTH gasp]
[KANATA]
Aw, yeah!
Oh, man.
We've gone through
so much together.
Yeah, like way too much.
What part of the trip sticks
out to you guys the most?
Well, for me.
I think it was the time
we almost crashed
on Planet Shummoor.
That was a close one.
[QUITTERIE] What about
when the ship's reactor
was totaled back on Icriss?
That was pretty
devastating for me.
[LUCA] I'll never forget
having to strip naked
while Ulgar pointed a gun at me.
[ULGAR]
Ah‐‐ You ever gonna let that go?
[YUN‐HUA] Remember the time
I sang for everyone
on Shummoor, when
you were all sick?
Or when Kanata carried me
out of the tsunami in his arms.
[ARIES]
Yeah, same.
When he took me into
his arms in space.
[FUNICIA]
Me, too!
He wrapped his arm around me
as we fell and saved me!
[CHARCE]
And me.
When you sacrificed your
arm to save my life.
[ARIES whimpering]
Uh‐‐
Thank you, Kanata.
We're here thanks to you.
Yeah, thanks, Captain!
[ALL crying]
Hey, c'mon on,
you guys, cut it out.
[KANATA] We're here because
we worked together.
If even one person was missing,
we would have never
made it this far.
What was your favorite
part of our journey?
My favorite part is right now.
The moment we all come home.
[gasps] Doesn't the
view make you guys
feel kind of nostalgic?
[CHARCE] We've seen so
many different places.
[QUITTERIE]
Yeah, but...
I think this one
has the prettiest view.
Humanity may have tried
to bury the wormholes.
But if they're used right,
then we could explore
space much faster.
And grow that much more.
[ARIES] Kanata said that
we should move forward
without fear.
Humanity did achieve
world peace,
but it was an unnatural one,
built on lies and deceit.
After our journey,
we agreed it was time
to tear down those lies
and embrace the truth.
I'm sure that means
facing all kinds of danger.
It'll mean new problems.
But we'll be okay.
As long as we take
each other by the hand
and support one another,
we can reach out
into the darkness,
and find the light.
Whoa!
There's like a ton
of people down there!
[YUN‐HUA]
Look at all those cameras.
[LUCA]
I guess the press came through.
Hey! It's my mom!
Hi, Mom.
You guys. That was
a long, hard, camp.
But you all did really
well out there.
[ALL]
Aye, yeah!
[ARIES] Through
difficulties to the stars.
Overcoming hardships
to reach our goal.
We will move forward.
Aries Spring, Team B‐5
Camp Log Secretary.
[ARIES]
We're home!
[NEWSCASTER 12A]
This just in.
We have an update
regarding the story
of the nine Caird High students
who went missing last summer.
They have been found.
Additionally,
the children involved are
claiming to be the products
of illegal cloning
and have accused
their creators of
attempted murder.
The officials in charge
of the investigation
have already arrested
several individuals,
including the seven
directly implicated
in the illegal acts of cloning.
Police are also looking
at Senator Marco Esposito
as a potential
suspect in the case.
The senator is being
charged with conspiracy
and will be taken into
custody for questioning.
Next up,
please join us for an
interview with the students,
filmed earlier today.
[KANATA]
Injuries?
Well, if you just mean
significant ones.
Uh, I can only really
think of my arm
getting blasted into space.
Oh. But it actually
made for a fun game.
The "Who can come up
with the most ridiculous
prosthetic arm idea" contest.
PS, the winning one
was an arm made of
a three‐pronged crayfish claw.
There was a big
deciding factor though.
The claw could move.
[KANATA]
I can't believe you won!
Hi, there.
Many of us here are curious
about the food situation.
Surely you must
have fought through
starvation and terrible thirst.
How did you manage to survive
on such little sustenance?
You wanna take
this one, Yun‐hua?
[YUN‐HUA]
I'd rather you tell them.
[ARIES giggles]
Actually, I gained
about two kilos.
[CROWD gasps]
[REPORTER 12A]
One more question!
Nice work out there.
For security purposes,
we've arranged for you kids
to stay at a nearby
hotel for the night.
[LUCA]
Cool!
Sir. What'll happen
to the Astra?
Now that we're here?
It's an important
part of the past.
A museum already contacted
us about keeping it.
It's going to a museum?
[ARIES] The story of our
miraculous return spread
like wildfire all
over the world.
People were genuinely
surprised when we told them
our trip was kind of fun.
They were expecting
more hardship.
We were interviewed on all
the major media outlets
and appeared on television
almost every day.
Regarding the
secrets of Astra...
Kanata and Charce
attended several meetings
with important
government officials.
They insisted that the world
deserved to know the truth.
In fact, many scholars
had already caught on
to the historical inaccuracies.
The government frowned
upon the idea initially,
but when Kanata said we'd
release the information
with or without their help,
they agreed to cooperate,
and share the details of Astra's
true history with the world.
Naturally, the news threw
everything into chaos.
And there were even a few
anti‐government protests
that occurred.
Thankfully, something
that helped suppress
the uproar was a book Kanata
wrote detailing our journey.
It was titled "The Adventure
of the Spaceship Astra".
The book covered the
entire trip with both humor
and sincerity, and quickly
became a best‐seller.
The final chapter discussed
how important it is
to see the world
with your own eyes.
That lesson resonated with
people all over the planet,
shifting humanity's
chaotic energy toward
understanding the truth and
vowing to uphold peace.
[ARIES] Quitterie jumped
onto the bandwagon
and became a model
for a fashion magazine.
[QUITTERIE]
And what's wrong with that?
[ARIES] But Charce became
the most popular of us all!
[QUITTERIE]
Talk about unfair!
[ARIES] Speaking of Charce,
we were initially worried
about what would happen to him.
[ARIES] In the end,
the government decided
not to charge him
with any crimes.
They determined his
actions were the result
of severe brainwashing,
and none of us
wanted to press charges anyway.
After that, things
started changing.
Like really changing,
in a big way.
And well, he became
the next king of Vixia!
[ARIES] Not long after
he was crowned king,
he relinquished all of
his political power.
He publicized all of the secrets
held by the royal family,
opening them up for
historical research.
Then he allowed the
public access to parts
of the castle and
tore down the walls
surrounding the royal quarter.
I think that was
Charce's way of taking
responsibility for
what he had done.
The young king's bold
and daring reforms
caught the world's attention.
Making him more popular!
[QUITTERIE]
Are you serious?!
[ARIES] Time passed in a flurry
of activity and change,
but slowly, we started to
return to our normal lives.
[EMMA]
Aries!
[ARIES] Eventually, we
graduated from Caird High.
And then we each
set out to pursue
our own paths and dreams.
Oh. Great, it's you. Ulgar.
[GERT] A filthy clone like you
has no right to visit me.
[ULGAR]
Yeah, well, here's the thing.
B‐5 were issued
new birth certificates.
We're no longer
related, old man.
[GERT]
I see you've grown taller.
You're actually beginning
to resemble my real son.
[ULGAR] That's who
I'm here to talk about.
My brother, Finn.
Huh?
[ULGAR]
Who ordered the kill?
Was it Marco Esposito?
[GERT]
Finn was a talented journalist.
He had managed to
trace our connection
back to the secrets
of the Vixia Royalty.
He knew too much.
So Marco took care of it.
[ULGAR]
And you were okay with that?
Huh?
The day we found out.
You were sad, too!
[GERT] I meant it when I said
I wished you had died instead.
I still wish it.
But my real son is gone.
If I ended the project,
I would have lost everything.
I needed to complete it,
for his sake, too.
So I thought, anyway.
[ULGAR] But despite all that,
the project still failed.
And you weren't
able to erase us.
[GERT]
Hm.
Hm? You know.
Finn was a really good man.
And he was an even better son.
[ULGAR]
Yeah. I know.
[GERT gasps]
I often think.
If only that old
ship hadn't been
at the exit of the wormhole.
[GERT laughs]
[ULGAR]
Old ship, huh?
I suppose.
[beeping]
[ULGAR]
See ya.
[FUNICIA]
Hey. Polina!
Whoa. Did you forget
I'm your teacher now?
Show some respect.
[FUNICIA]
Oops, sorry Miss Livinskaya!
[POLINA]
Are you done for the day, Funi?
Yep! What about you?
Are you going somewhere?
[POLINA] Yes. I'm getting ready
to do a quick interview,
and then I'm giving a lecture
on history at the university.
[FUNICIA] Sometimes I think
you're the busiest one
out of all of us.
[laughs] Well, I'm
an important witness
of the old era, right?
And over 100 years old!
I'm 36, okay?
Are you still going to Yun‐hua's
concert later tonight?
[FUNICIA]
Uh‐huh, that's the plan.
[POLINA]
I'm jealous. I wish I could go.
Please, send my regards.
[gasps] It's Ulgar!
[ULGAR]
Hey. What's up?
Did you come here
to pick me up?
Are you going to the concert?
Unfortunately, I
gotta do some work.
Oh. I guess journalists
are super busy.
[POLINA]
Well, Mister Reporter.
Thank you for escorting me.
‐‐Aye, yeah.
‐‐[FUNICIA] Wait!
You never mentioned that Ulgar
was gonna interview you!
I'm way jealous!
This is just a date, isn't it?
Later, kid.
[BEEGO]
Take me for a ride, Ulgar!
Please, please, please!
[giggles]
[ULGAR]
Sure. Sometime soon, okay?
[BEEGO]
Ah!
[ULGAR chuckles]
What's so funny?
Well, she looks
identical to Quitterie.
It's pretty crazy.
Yes. But then again,
she's as old now
as Quitterie was back then.
By the way, you said you aren't
going to Yun‐hua's concert.
Does that mean you're
headed to the spaceport?
They'll be leaving soon, right?
I actually stopped
by there earlier.
Said my farewells
and all that stuff.
I see, that makes sense.
I wish I could have at
least seen the captain,
but I'm sure he'll be back soon.
Maybe I'll even interview him.
Whoa. Look, pal.
We're Yun‐hua's closest friends!
Move aside! We're
part of Team B‐5!
[LUCA]
It's okay, Quitterie.
We don't have to go
backstage like right now.
Yeah, we can always go
see her after the concert.
Besides, we're still
waiting for Funi, right?
Where's Ulgar?
That guy's always
flying all over,
he's hardly ever home.
Heck, last night he asked
to crash at my place.
I wouldn't waste your time
worrying about that busy bee.
Oh! Speaking of flying around.
They're supposed to
take off today, right?
I know they said they didn't
want us to send them off,
aren't you worried though?
Please. If that dolt
wants to leave
his gorgeous wife behind,
then that's his business.
[LUCA] Translation: you're
actually pretty peeved.
I bet you're feeling upset,
too, huh, Aries?
[ARIES]
Uh.
Come on, is everything
okay between you two?
[ARIES]
The thing is, well...
Kanata and I recently decided
we'd like to get married.
[BOTH gasp]
[ARIES] Sorry, I should have
told you guys sooner.
[LUCA]
Ah!
[BOTH]
Congratulations!
[QUITTERIE] Your dream
is finally coming true!
[LUCA] That jerk sure did
make you wait long enough.
[ARIES]
He never really had time,
he's been so focused
on becoming an explorer.
But then, the other day he and
I made the trip out to Vixia.
It was all just a formality,
but we scheduled
a meeting with Charce.
[ARIES]
And then Kanata asked him
if he could marry his daughter.
[QUITTERIE, LUCA laugh]
[LUCA]
When he gets back.
We're gonna throw you
guys the biggest party.
[QUITTERIE]
Wait, didn't you mention
you'd like to have a baby soon?
Yes! I'm really hoping that
we'll have a little girl.
I would name her Seira.
[applause]
[YUN‐HUA]
Thank you all so much.
Next, I'd like to sing
you a brand‐new song.
And I'd like to dedicate
it to my closest friends.
You see, today is very special.
A few of them are
going back into space.
When I was 17 years old,
I spent five long months
lost in space with them.
But that time was
incredibly precious to me.
We worked together as a team
to reach our goal and move
forward against all odds.
I was trapped in my own shell,
and I couldn't express myself.
But thanks to them, I was able
to grow into the person
standing before you.
I won't forget those days,
or the adventures
we had together.
We encountered
life‐threatening dangers,
we fought, we cried,
and there were times
we got depressed.
And yet, the thing I remember
most is everyone's smiles.
Our fearless captain went
on to make a fortune
with his book and managed
to buy back that old ship.
[AUDIENCE laughs]
[YUN‐HUA]
But I think I understand why.
Because in a way,
that spaceship represents
the bond between us all.
We may have come home,
but our journey is never over.
The Astra will move forward,
towards the future.
This song's called
"The Adventure of Astra"!
[AUDIENCE gasps]
[KANATA]
So, hey.
Are you sure this
craft is good to go?
It looks more beaten
up than the others.
[ZACK] Well, the Ark series
is over 100 years old.
It's practically a fossil.
But don't you worry, Captain.
I made sure I
conducted the interior
maintenance personally.
Besides, exploring
space in this ship
should come fairly easy to you.
Heh. Yeah. It is
our ship after all.
[ZACK]
I'm impressed.
You really did get your own
vessel in seven years.
How's the new prosthetic
arm treating you?
[KANATA]
You gave it too many features.
An electronic ear pick
is just superfluous!
Is it though?
[KANATA]
Yes, 100 percent!
[ZACK] Our mission is to scout
out potential locations
to place wormhole
exits. So first up,
we'll go to Planet McPa,
and once we're there,
we can use the wormhole to
head out towards Gazenette.
After that, it's up to us.
[KANATA] Beyond Gazenette,
it's uncharted territory.
Nice.
I meant to tell you that
Ulgar stopped by earlier.
For real? He could
have joined us!
I invited him.
"Last time I followed
Cap anywhere,
we got dropped way out in
the middle of space." He said.
Excuse me?
It's not like any
of that was my fault!
Huh? Wait, it can't be.
What?
Hey. How are you?
[KANATA, ZACK]
Charce?
But... what are you doing here?
Well, I RSVP'd as "maybe."
[KANATA]
This isn't a party!
Can the king really just peace
out for a space adventure?
I can. Afterall,
I did make a promise.
That I would be
your right‐hand man.
[KANATA] You know I only said
that to sound cool, right?
[CHARCE]
Yes, I do.
But I'll be more
useful than you.
[KANATA] Dude, I can shoot
missiles from my elbow.
[ZACK]
That's not a feature.
[KANATA]
But you added an ear pick?
[ZACK]
You're welcome!
[KANATA]
Whatever.
[ZACK] Hey, you ready?
Let's go. Captain.
[KANATA]
Aye, yeah.
We've come pretty
far, haven't we?
Thanks, guys.
Prepare for takeoff!
Aye, yeah!
Destination...
[KANATA]
The unknown!
To the depths of space!