[KANATA]
Something up, Aries?
It's strange, but...
...I don't remember ever
seeing Charce in class before.
I may have transferred
late in the year,
but I still went to biology
class several times
before we left for camp.
There's not a doubt in my mind‐‐
Charce wasn't in that class.
Be honest with me. Are you...
...hiding something?
[KANATA]
What's going on?
You, uh, wanna tell us anything?
So you would really take
Aries' word over mine?
That's hurtful.
[sighs] I'm a transfer student.
[STUDENTS gasp]
I enrolled at Caird High School
not long after Aries did.
Right before planet
camp started.
[LUCA]
Whoa, for real?
So there are two
transfer students?
What are the odds
of that happening?
Okay, so what day did
you transfer then?
[CHARCE] The beginning
of July, on the first.
There were no
biology classes held
between then and the fourth
when we left for camp.
[KANATA]
Why didn't you tell us?!
Well, I didn't think it
was all that relevant.
Why does it matter so much?
Hello?
When Aries mentioned she
was a transfer student,
wouldn't the natural
reaction be to chime in?
Like, come on!
[ARIES]
We all like you, Charce.
And there's no doubt
that, without you here,
we probably wouldn't
have made it this far.
You're important to us.
Still though, I admit
it does bother me.
You're such a mystery,
and we hardly know
anything about you.
I thought we were all
supposed to be friends.
[ZACK]
No one is required to give out
their personal information.
He is entitled to his privacy.
But these aren't
normal circumstances.
Saying you transferred
in right before camp
is almost like admitting
that you were the enemy
sent to kill us all.
Zack is right, Charce.
You owe us an explanation.
[CHARCE]
And if I refuse?
I'll throw you in the brig.
Okay. Understood.
Solid performance, Captain.
I didn't mention the transfer
because I didn't wanna
talk about my family.
I could have made up
a more plausible story,
but I didn't want to lie to you.
To my friends.
Truth is...
...I'm a noble from the
Imperial District of Vixia.
You mean like, Vixia Vixia?
Seriously?!
Never heard of it.
What makes it special?
It's the only
place in the world
where we still have
monarchs and nobles.
I've never talked about this.
I was ordered to stay
quiet about my family.
But also... I wanted
to forget about them.
[CHARCE] After the end
of a years‐long world war,
a new global government
was established
in 1963 CE.
All nations were abolished
and the land was
reorganized into districts.
Only one region was allowed
to be ruled by a monarchy.
And that was Vixia.
Life there is idyllic.
Science and technology
are restricted,
so the district resembles
a sort of antediluvian era.
It has a fairytale‐
like atmosphere,
making it a popular
tourist destination.
But, there's a central area
that's surrounded by walls.
It's off limits to tourists
and ordinary citizens.
That's where the
royalty and nobility live.
Since I was born into such
a family, that was home.
And out! There!
I made it through!
Come on, Seira!
[SEIRA gasps]
You're right! No alarms!
[CHARCE] I found a hole and
just cleared it out a little.
I'm sure they'll fix it soon.
But at least we can play
in the noble area for today!
[SEIRA] I don't know,
I doubt this noble's outfit
will fool anyone.
It's pretty obvious
I'm just a commoner.
Listen, don't worry!
You look fantastic!
Then again, you look
stunning in anything.
[SEIRA] Thank you, Charce.
You're always full of flattery.
[CHARCE] Seira was a commoner,
but we got along well,
so we spent a fair
amount of time together.
Normally, we met on the
other side of the wall.
But that day,
I decided to take a risk
and invite her into
the royal quarter.
I wanted to take
her somewhere special.
[SEIRA]
The Royal Zoo?
[CHARCE]
Yes.
You said it was something
you wished to see, right?
There's a variety of
unique animals there.
[SEIRA]
Really?
Uh‐huh, it's quite superb.
[SEIRA]
Come on! Let's go right now!
Careful, Seira, watch
where you're running.
[SOLDIER 7A, SEIRA gasp]
‐‐[SEIRA] I'm sorry!
‐‐[alarm beeps]
[SOLDIER 7A]
Wait. This girl is a commoner.
How did you get into this
area without a permit?
It's my fault, okay?
How did you get inside?
‐‐[SEIRA] Let me go!
‐‐[SOLDIER B] She's trespassing!
[CHARCE]
Please, let me explain!
Come with me.
Little piece of filth!
[SEIRA gasps]
[CHARCE]
Seira!
[COMMONER 7A]
Someone fell off the wall!
[COMMONER 7C]
Call a doctor!
[CHARCE'S FATHER]
You're not going to see
that commoner again!
Don't forget your noble blood!
I'm nothing more than a
caged animal here, Father!
I want to live freely!
[CHARCE] Seira. You've been
asleep for quite a while.
I promise to visit every day.
I'll study biology, so I can
teach you what I've learned.
And then, when you wake up,
we'll go to the forest.
But take your time.
Focus on healing and rest.
[CHARCE]
Four years later,
Seira's family
suddenly left Vixia
without telling me
where they went.
I'm sure she's still
quietly sleeping
somewhere in the world.
Not long after,
I left Vixia as well.
"Lacroix" isn't my real name.
It belongs to my adopted mother.
I lost my closest friend
and cut all ties with my family.
I was just starting my new life,
and things were
already complicated.
That's why I've
never discussed it.
Please forgive me?
[ARIES]
That's so sad!
‐‐[GROUP sobs]
‐‐[CHARCE] Whoa!
Hey. What's wrong?
Why are you all crying?
How terrible, I'm so sorry!
It must have been so hard!
I won't ask about
your past again, okay?
No, if anything, it's my fault
for not telling you sooner.
And honestly, I didn't think
it was of any real interest.
I'm not sure why all of
you are crying so much.
It's not as though she
was someone you knew.
[KANATA]
You idiot!
It was about a person
who was close to you!
It doesn't matter
if we knew her!
[gasps]
[laughs]
[KANATA] What the heck
are you laughing at?
[CHARCE laughing]
Don't be mad‐‐
I'm laughing because
you're all crying.
[LUCA] We're crying because
we're sad, you big jerk!
[CHARCE]
I know, and that makes me happy.
[ARIES] So, we're crying
because we're sad,
but Charce is laughing
because he's glad...
[CHARCE] I left everything
behind, cut ties with my family,
and found a new one.
[ARIES]
Huh?
I'll go make some
more mushroom tea.
[QUITTERIE]
That sounds good.
Yeah, thanks, man.
I'll come help.
She must've been
very dear to you.
Will you tell me? What was
your friend Seira like?
A lot like you, Aries.
[ARIES]
Oh, really?
Team B5, camp log.
With a lot of new
thoughts on our minds,
we've begun the approach
to our next planet.
I'm sorry, Seira.
Ah‐ha, ha! Check it
out, planet four!
[ARIES] ♪ It's turning.
It's turning. ♪
[CHARCE] I'm starting to
grow accustomed to this.
[KANATA, ARIES, LUCA] ♪ Carrying
our hopes and dreams... ♪
[BEEGO]
What are they singing?
[QUITTERIE]
It's the Caird High choir's
competition piece,
"The Planet Turns."
Except... this new
planet is not turning.
[STUDENTS]
What?!
[ZACK]
To put it simply,
the planet's rotation and
orbital revolution are in sync.
Hold on.
Wouldn't that mean that
the sun never sets here?
Awesome! Time for
some fun in the sun!
Sounds like it's
time to bust out
the ol' swim trunks
again, am I right?
Idiots!
[KANATA, LUCA, ARIES gasp]
[ZACK]
It's a giant burning death zone!
There's no water, and definitely
no life on the sun side!
Nothing can survive there!
[KANATA] For real? To think,
you guys were cheering.
[LUCA]
You were, too, genius!
[KANATA]
So what's the other side like?
[ZACK]
Frozen. Dark. Also a death zone.
[LUCA] Hold up. Are you
sure there's even any
food or water on this planet?
[ZACK] According to the data
I have available on it,
yes, there is,
probably on this strip
that separates the two zones.
[KANATA] Good, at least
we know where to land.
Let's go!
Whoa.
[KANATA]
So this is Planet Icriss.
Are those tall things trees?
They're as big as skyscrapers.
What are those? Birds, maybe?
Wow. They're enormous.
[ZACK] I don't think
they're aggressive.
They seem to be
pretty light‐weight
despite their large size.
Yes, they are quite
similar to insects.
We should be all right as long
as we're inside of the Astra.
Look. Balloons!
Are you sure?
[KANATA gasps]
[QUITTERIE] What the heck?
Are they electric?
They're killing
those bug things!
Quick, Zack! No zappy!
Don't hit the bad
jellyfish umbrellas!
[ZACK] If you're going
to give commands,
speak like an adult!
[KANATA]
Did we make it through?
I already hate this planet!
It seems as though
there are a variety
of carnivorous plants here.
Most likely they're designed
to ensnare and eat
all of the flying creatures
that inhabit this region.
Then we gotta find
somewhere to land
before we get eaten!
We can't stop here.
The area is dangerous.
If we're to stray away
from the sunlight more,
I expect the amount of
plant life would be less.
Head toward the colder zone.
Aye, yeah, Captain.
[STUDENTS yell]
[KANATA gasps]
[STUDENTS scream]
[QUITTERIE]
What's happening?
[KANATA]
It's breaking the ship!
Get it off of us, Zack!
How can a dumb plant
be so crazy strong?
It's almost like a giant muscle!
I'm not even sure
this thing is a plant!
Hold on! I'm spinning the ship!
[STUDENTS yell]
All right!
We're free!
[gasps]
What is it?
There's an error in
the control system!
I'm losing the attitude
and deceleration controls!
[KANATA]
That sounds bad!
[CHARCE]
Watch the out for the cliffs!
[ZACK] No portside controls
either‐‐I can't turn left!
[KANATA] Why are we losing
all the controls at once?
This is too much!
I suppose things have been
too easy up until now.
This is a real space adventure,
which means real danger.
I'm counting on you, Zack.
This is our only ship.
If it breaks, we're done for.
[ZACK] I've got this.
I can do it. Almost there.
Brace yourselves!
[STUDENTS yell]
I'm sorry, but...
[ZACK]
...the Astra can't fly.
I've assessed the damage.
The bridge and the aft
engines are all right.
We can fly a little.
[KANATA]
But?
We cannot go into space,
and it is impossible to fix.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[ZACK] I'm afraid the
front fusion reactors
are beyond repair.
Without them, we can't
generate the energy
needed for light speed.
We don't have parts,
tools, or a dock.
Maybe I could coax some limited,
low‐atmosphere flight, but it's
incapable of space travel.
What's going to
happen to all of us?
Well, this marks the
end of our journey.
This planet will have
to be our new home.
[QUITTERIE]
Are you kidding me?!
How are we supposed to live
on this terrible planet?
Only the control areas
of the ship are damaged,
the residential areas are fine.
We can use the ship as housing.
You know that's not
what I mean, Zack!
I wanna go my home
and my bed right now!
But that's not possible.
Do you need me
to explain it again?
You're lying. It can't be.
[QUITTERIE whimpers]
[QUITTERIE]
Are you really serious?
We can't go back home?
Why is this happening?
[QUITTERIE sobs]
It's all my fault.
I should have been
paying more attention
while piloting the ship.
You're wrong. Your
flying was fine.
I'm responsible for this mess.
I just... I thought
we could get home.
If we worked together,
one step at a time.
[ULGAR]
Thanks for the pep‐talk, Cap.
I thought the captain's
supposed to act tough
when things are bad.
What about those survival tips
you're always spouting?
Something like
"If you stand still,
then you don't move
forward" or whatever.
Good point, Ulgar.
[KANATA]
You're right. Thanks. I'm sorry.
Wherever we're gonna live,
we'll still need food.
We're running low on supplies.
So let's explore.
Survival tip number ten:
"If you stand still, then
you don't move forward."
[LUCA]
Hey, you totally stole that!
[ARIES, CHARCE laugh]
Thank you, Ulgar.
[ULGAR sighs]
[FUNICIA]
It's starting to snow!
[CHARCE] Probably because
we're on the edge
of the belt area. So,
closer to the frozen zone.
Thankfully our crust suits
keep us from freezing.
[YUNHUA] I see berries.
Do you think they're edible?
[ULGAR]
Yummy.
Yep.
[YUNHUA]
That was so impressive, Ulgar.
It was oddly neat to watch.
Still though, I don't see
very many animals around,
so that might limit our hunting.
[FUNICIA]
Oh, maybe we could catch
some of those big bugs!
[CHARCE laughs]
That might be difficult.
We would need nets
as big as soccer goals.
[sighs] So, everyone's
just accepted it, huh?
I really admire you guys.
Those are some nerves
of steel you've got.
[ULGAR] They're just
puttin' up a good front.
If we don't keep
moving and focus on
what's ahead of us,
then we'll end up
drowning in despair.
Nobody can come to terms
with this that fast.
Oh...
Hold up.
You're actually scared,
too, aren't you?
With that perma‐scowl,
it's hard to tell sometimes.
[ULGAR]
Wha‐‐ I'm not scared!
Hey, c'mon, Charce.
Let's look on the other
side of that cliff.
Can we please go?
Behind the cliff?
But there won't be
plants growing there
since there isn't any sunlight.
[FUNICIA]
Okay. I was just asking
'cause I saw something.
[gasps]
[CHARCE]
You did? No way.
At least... the
water's drinkable.
Indeed.
Good thing we were
able to move the ship.
Quitterie, you need
to shift gears.
We have to focus on surviving.
Why should we try to survive
on this stupid planet?
There're so many things
I wanted to do.
Believe it or not,
I had a vision
of the future and what I wanted!
Like going to college.
Becoming a doctor.
Getting married one day.
But now I'll never be able
to do any of those things!
How the heck can you
be so calm right now?
Because it's my job
to be calm, Quitterie.
When others panic,
I have to be calm
and level headed.
Listen. You have to
make a decision.
Live here or place your
bets on a low probability.
I'm not sure what you mean.
Did you know?
On board the Astra,
we have exactly one
functioning hibernation device.
And if you wanted, you could
use it to wait for help.
Are you serious?
How would she even let
someone know she was here?
There's no way to communicate.
[ZACK] That's why I said
"low probability."
You would have to wait
for someone to come.
It could take decades,
or even centuries.
Long after we all
died of old age,
you'd still be waiting,
peacefully asleep.
It's possible that
you'd never be found.
You'd be betting
everything on the chance
that someone might
explore this planet
in the far‐off future.
[QUITTERIE]
Why? Why would you tell me this?
That's just like telling me
I would have to die
here by myself.
I'm sorry. But
that's the only way
I can think of to
get you back home.
But I don't wanna be by myself!
Don't you get it?
Why do you have
to be such a jerk?
[ZACK] Let's live here.
Together. With everyone.
Kanata, it looks like
you've come to terms
with it already.
It's pretty impressive.
[KANATA]
Nah, not really.
I haven't accepted it
and I probably never will,
but I have to try.
That being said, I'm not
very hard to please.
I feel like I can
survive almost anywhere.
It sounds crazy,
but I was kinda hoping
we could make some stone tools,
and then maybe fix this thing
over the next ten years or so.
[laughs]
[ARIES]
I'd be okay with that,
‐‐as long as you're around, too.
‐‐[KANATA] Huh?
I mean... I kinda...
[KANATA]
Right. Yeah. I got you.
What?
It's Charce.
He said he needs us.
[ARIES]
Where does he want us to go?
He's over by the cliff.
[STUDENTS panting]
[KANATA gasps]
What is this?
I don't understand.
Nor do I. But still.
There it is.
Can it really be...
[KANATA]
...another Astra?
[ZACK] No, it's the same model,
but a different ship.
It's more weathered, and
the damage isn't the same.
Okay, let's investigate.
Team of three. Me and
Zack, and, who else?
Ulgar, let's go.
All right.
It has power.
[ULGAR]
I'm goin' in.
[KANATA]
Same internal structure.
It's in pretty rough shape.
Like an old house.
The ship must have
crash landed here
just like ours did.
There's a fair amount of
damage on the ship's bridge.
I doubt it's capable of flight.
Well, that sucks.
I checked the cabins back there.
Nobody else is on board.
[KANATA]
So maybe the crew was rescued,
but the ship was damaged
and left behind?
That would make sense.
[gasps] No, look,
I just found a message
from one of the crew.
"Help me."
What? But weren't
they all rescued?
Why leave a message for help?
I've no idea. Wait, hold on.
It's the hibernation device!
[KANATA]
Looks like it's running.
[ZACK]
There's someone inside.
It was activated July 2051.
Which means this person's
been in there for 12 years.
[ZACK] Twelve years? That's
a long time to wait for help.
What should we do?
Wake them up.
[gasps]
[KANATA]
A woman?