[KANATA] Wow. So, Yun‐hua's
singing was that awesome?
Really?
[ARIES] Yep! I would even
go so far as to say that
it was the most beautiful sound
I've heard in my whole life!
For real, it made me feel
super relaxed and stuff.
Not just mentally,
but like physically, too.
[CHARCE] It's almost as if
her song served as a life line
to help us make it
through that moment.
[ZACK] I'm certain it
saved our lives. Thank you.
Oh, sure.
So, I've been
wondering something.
Did you know she wants
to be a singer, Kanata?
Huh? Oh, yeah.
I mean, Yun‐hua's
mom is Lucy Lum.
Uh.
The Lucy Lum? Are you serious?!
What? You mean the
super‐famous singer?
I see!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa! Hold up!
[gasps]
[QUITTERIE]
Now that I'm really looking,
you guys do look similar!
You're actually, like,
crazy cute, Yun‐hua!
[YUN‐HUA]
Please don't stare at me!
[KANATA] Hey now. There's
no need to be so shy.
You're with friends
here, remember.
You can express yourself freely.
[YUN‐HUA]
Yes.
It's kinda like what Aries said.
This trip has been a lot of fun.
[YUN‐HUA] I like being on
this adventure with everyone,
even if it is
a little dangerous.
You're all so warm and reliable.
That's why I feel this way.
It's silly, but singing
is the only talent I have.
I still promise to help
as much as I can, though.
So let's go home.
Together!
[ALL]
Aye, yeah!
[ARIES]
Team B5 Camp Log.
[ARIES] We were still struggling
to find food for our journey.
[FUNICIA]
Yum, yum, yummy!
[CHARCE]
I knew it!
[KANATA]
Seriously?
[ARIES] But then, Charce
had the idea that we might
be able to actually
eat the Pole Trees.
I just hypothesized that since
they're giant mushrooms
and not trees at all, there was
a chance they were edible.
[ARIES]
Wow! They look super tasty!
I'm glad you and I
are on the same page!
Great minds, am I right?
[KANATA]
Yeah, more like strange minds.
[ARIES] After five days
and a near death experience
on Planet Shummoor,
we finally had enough supplies
for the next leg of our journey.
Goodbye, Gruppies!
‐‐[ARIES] I miss you already!
‐‐We'll never forget you!
[QUITTERIE]
Wow, they're really attached
to those alien bird
things. Weirdos.
Well, they did
help us out a lot.
[ARIES] Our experiences
on this planet weren't easy,
but I think we've all
grown a lot from them.
We're stronger than ever.
[LUCA]
Uh?
[YUN‐HUA]
Hey, Luca?
Can I ask for a favor?
[LUCA giggles]
[ALL gasping]
[YUN‐HUA]
Um...
Please don't stare at me.
[ALL sigh]
[QUITTERIE]
Ugh, boys can be such pigs!
[ARIES] Then, a scary beef stole
my bag so I called out for help!
Things were really bad!
Luckily, someone named Kanata
Bive Domb came to my rescue!
The patrol bots were all
like, "One‐two, one‐two,"
but he came back and said
he wanted to be our champion!
[TEACHER] Hey. We're
getting ready to land.
Everyone take your seats.
Okay. I'll send you
a message tomorrow.
It'll be like your very own
camp log. Bye for now, Mom!
[sighs]
[REPORTER] Nine students from
Caird High are still missing.
It has now been almost 40
days since the children were
last seen during
a trip to Planet McPa.
The incident is quite
mysterious. All of the students,
as well as their luggage,
appear to have vanished,
leaving behind no evidence...
[EMMA]
Aries.
[REPORTER]
Authorities are baffled.
[GERT] I want to thank
each of you for coming today.
I understand how difficult
this must be for all of you.
These are indeed trying
times for everyone involved.
As I'm sure you're well
aware, my own son is one
of the students who went
missing on Planet McPa.
Allow me to get
straight to the point.
It has now been one month since
the search for our children
was officially suspended, and
I think the time has come for us
to accept the undeniable
truth of this matter.
I say we file for a judicial
declaration of disappearance.
You can't be serious!
You want us all to declare
our children legally dead?
Don't you think
it's too soon for that?
You're really willing to
give up? Because I am not.
Listen, I understand how you
feel, however, we simply cannot
allow the children to
remain missing indefinitely.
[gasps] Well, what about
the rest of the parents,
how do you all feel?
Look, we did everything we could
in order to continue the search.
Unfortunately, at this time,
I believe we've simply
exhausted our options.
I see no reason
to oppose this idea.
[WEI] We need to take
a more realistic stance
regarding these discussions.
Do you think your
daughter will just reappear?
Simply believing she will isn't
enough to make that happen.
[gasps] Well, no. Not exactly.
But that's why I want us
to continue searching!
[OLIVE] Oh, and where
else do you suggest
we search, Ms. Spring?
We've scoured every
inch of Planet McPa,
except the deepest oceans.
An accident on the water
means that our children
have been lost to the waves.
Face the facts, it's hopeless.
[EMMA]
Mm... Possibly.
But I don't think they're
anywhere in the ocean.
The boat was still docked,
and the engines
were never activated.
Besides, why would the
children swim out to sea
with all of their luggage?
None of this makes any sense!
Then in that case, where
do you propose we search?
We search space!
[GERT]
Wha‐‐? Are you being serious?
Yes, of course I am.
What method would they
have used to get to space?
I'm not entirely sure.
I suppose they could have found
an old spaceship or something?
[RAY]
Unbelievable.
How absurd.
So, your only idea is that
maybe they found a spaceship?
But there's no evidence.
You'd be better off trying
to convince me there
was a second boat.
In fact, at least that story
would be more plausible.
You're wrong! What's
unbelievable is we haven't found
their remains or luggage!
There's no trace
of them anywhere!
Look at it this way;
if they did go to space,
then there's still
a possibility they're alive!
So, let's find them!
[GERT]
Ms. Spring.
I'd be lying if I said I hadn't
thought about it, as well,
but, unfortunately, the cost
of such a search party
would be phenomenal without
government assistance.
The odds are just
not in our favor.
This is difficult for me, too.
For every one of us.
It feels as if
I am being torn apart.
[EMMA]
I'm sorry, everyone.
Of course you're all
in the same situation I am.
Please don't worry about it.
Every person in this room
is struggling right now,
so we need to do our
best to support each other.
[SOPHIE]
Speaking of the government...
Well, I can't help but
notice that Luca's father,
Mister Esposito, seems to be
absent from today's meeting.
And I do believe he is
a senator, isn't that correct?
Do you think that
there's a chance
he could talk to the
government on our behalf?
He already did those
things a long time ago.
You see, while they sympathize,
he's informed me that
the government won't help us
with any future searches.
The senator couldn't
be here today
because he had to attend
his scheduled DNA sampling.
[JED] I wonder how
he feels about that,
seeing as he was
a leader of the faction
opposing the genome
management project.
This must be hard for him.
[REPORTERS chattering]
[REPORTER A] Senator Esposito!
What are your thoughts on today?
About getting your DNA sampled?
I have to obey the laws
just like everybody else.
[REPORTER 5A]
What about the allegations
of illegal campaign donations?
[REPORTER 5B] Your son
is still missing, correct?
Do you care to
share your feelings?
[grunts]
Yes, it feels as if
I am being torn apart.
Please be safe...
[EMMA]
...Aries.
[ARIES]
Heads up!
[STUDENTS laughing, chattering]
[ARIES]
This planet is incredible!
Camp log.
It's day 49 of being
lost in space.
We've spent five days
on this ocean planet
after finally discovering
that it has land.
It's been relaxing!
All right, I caught a fish!
[gasps]
And I caught a fish!
Yeah, well, my fish
is a lot bigger!
[ZACK]
No, mine's bigger!
[KANATA]
Nuh‐uh, look at this thing!
[ZACK]
Mine's the biggest!
[KANATA]
In your dreams, pal!
[QUITTERIE] Did you make
those harpoons yourself?
The Luca Lance isn't
too tricky to modify.
All I had to do was sharpen
up the point a little bit.
I'm glad I thought to
bring some along with us.
Aren't you gonna go swimming
with them? Looks like fun.
I explained this to you
earlier. I can't swim.
[QUITTERIE]
Huh?
[LUCA]
Hm?
[ULGAR]
I got three of them today.
[LUCA]
Whoa! Excellent marksmanship!
Thanks for the bow,
Luca. It's good.
Can you tighten up the
string a bit for me, though?
[LUCA]
Sure, I'm on it.
[FUNICIA]
You guys!
You won't believe how
many different kinds
of fruit we found out there!
[FUNICIA]
Yummy!
[YUN‐HUA]
[CHARCE]
Yum, yum, yummy!
Sounds like they're fair game.
[CHARCE] Why don't we
go ahead and try them out?
Ah!
[CHARCE]
Please enjoy, my lady.
[QUITTERIE]
Oh, how nice.
Goodness, it's exquisite!
Wait a second!
[yelps] What's the
matter with you?
It dawned on me so suddenly
that I just needed
to yell about it!
What is this place,
some kind of paradise?
We're practically on vacation!
I don't even need
to go home anymore!
Relaxing with you guys
for the rest of my life
doesn't sound half bad...
[LUCA]
She was so eager to go home.
Maybe this is such
a departure from
impending doom
that she's confused.
[yelling]
Um, where'd Aries
and Yun‐hua go?
Oh, they said they were
gonna head down to the lake.
Wanna join them?
[ARIES]
Hey!
Quitterie, Funi, what's up?
You know something, Aries?
You may not realize it,
but your swimsuit
is pretty provocative looking.
Huh?
Just saying,
with those boobs, you are going
to get all kinds of attention.
I'm not sure if you're trying
to attract guys or what,
but that outfit'll definitely
do the trick if you are.
Just remember that
they're all idiots, okay?
Every last one of them!
You're looking
provocative, too, though.
[FUNICIA laughs]
[QUITTERIE]
Hm? Forget about "provocative."
I'm sexy. I mean,
just look at me.
[YUNHUA] Hey, what's
everybody talking about?
And Yun‐hua's really got
it going on, doesn't she?
Ugh, what do you know?
Anyway, you've got this! If you
approach him looking like that,
then you'll have him wrapped
around your little finger.
Believe me.
Okay...?
Kanata, obviously.
[ARIES]
Uh... Wait, what did you say?
[CHARCE] I discovered
something interesting about
this planet's ecosystem.
All of the creatures
here are parthenogenetic.
[KANATA]
Partheno‐what?
Basically, it means that they
reproduce through cloning.
[QUITTERIE]
Wow, that sounds unusual.
Actually, it's not. A lot
of species have that trait.
Certain types of lizards,
carp, turkeys, bees,
and dandelions are
also parthenogenetic.
The females can
breed on their own.
[KANATA gasps] So, this planet
doesn't have any males?
[CHARCE] That is certainly
possible, but it could just be
that we haven't encountered any.
[LUCA]
Huh, weird.
[CHARCE]
Judging by the way so many
kinds of lifeforms
coexist peacefully here,
I'd be willing to believe
this is a paradise resulting
from the ultimate evolution.
[laughs] Yeah,
a world without boys
sure sounds like
a paradise to me!
Aries, you agree, don't you?
[ARIES]
Oh, come on!
‐‐[KANATA] Hm?
‐‐[QUITTERIE giggles]
[QUITTERIE]
Don't try to fool me.
I can read your mind
like an open book!
Just tell us the truth.
You like Kanata, don't you?
That Quitterie, so aggressive!
Go ahead and get her, sis!
Kanata saved my life
when we first met, remember?
I mean, obviously I'm kinda
fond of him for that!
Uh‐huh. I guess that
could be how it started,
but it's not just that.
He's so reliable! It's easy
to fall for someone you trust.
[ARIES]
Mm...
Aw! Come here!
You're usually so
spacy and quiet,
but when it comes to boys,
you're way obvious!
Well, you're not very hard
to read either, Quitterie.
[QUITTERIE squeaks]
You like Zack, right?
[QUITTERIE]
She just turned the tables!
[gasps] Uh... No,
I don't. No way.
I told you.
I only know him because
we grew up together, that's all!
[ARIES, YUNHUA laugh]
Don't laugh at me! Since
when are you two so judgy?
So, what's your plan of attack?
I don't have one.
[QUITTERIE]
Then just confess!
[gasps] That's
not gonna happen!
[QUITTERIE] Okay, maybe
not right out of the gate.
But hey, for all we know,
Kanata's a real
ladies' man back home.
Even I felt my heart skip a beat
when I saw those
rippling muscles.
In fact, it's possible that
he already has a girlfriend.
You should ask him.
Quitterie looks like
she's really enjoying this.
So am I!
I can't just ask him!
[ARIES whimpers]
[KANATA]
Huh? You need the bathroom?
[ARIES]
No, I, uh, had a quick question.
I was wondering if
you're, like, you know...
[ARIES] Like, I mean,
at school and everything.
Do you tend to, uh, get around?
[KANATA]
What?
[QUITTERIE]
Girl, word choice!
[KANATA] Well, I'm popular,
if that's what you're asking,
with girls and guys!
[giggles]
[QUITTERIE] Not a smart
response from him, either.
[ARIES] I guess what
I want to know is...
Do you have, like, uh, a
steady girlfriend or something?
[QUITTERIE]
Good, nice and direct!
Now, out with it, Kanata!
[laughs] Of course!
The way I see it,
every girl is my girlfriend!
[QUITTERIE]
Wow, really?
I knew guys were dumb,
but he's like, the dumbest.
[ARIES]
That's stupid.
What'd you say?
Forget it. What the
heck is your problem?
[QUITTERIE groans]
[KANATA]
Hm?
[QUITTERIE growls]
[gasps]
‐‐[QUITTERIE] Idiot!
‐‐[KANATA sputters]
[KANATA]
Hm?
[ARIES] Team B5 Camp Log.
Planet Arispade, Day Five.
For personal reasons,
I've decided to retire
early this evening.
[BIRD squawks]
[CHARCE] Wow, six of them,
that's impressive!
There don't seem to be any
edible creatures on land.
We're fortunate
you can hunt these.
You've improved,
Ulgar. Nice job.
Hey, how's the tighter bow
string been workin' out for ya?
[ULGAR]
Not bad.
Six down! That's not bad at all!
You just keep getting
better and better!
Looks that way.
[LUCA]
I whipped up a fishing rod, too,
if you'd like to
take it for a spin.
[ULGAR]
Sure.
And yet I can't get
a word out of this guy.
Aw, try not to
take it too personal.
Luca has a way of hitting
it off with everybody.
Guess he's easy to talk to.
[CHARCE]
Hey, I'm easy to talk to!
[KANATA]
Nah, you're kind of annoying.
[LUCA] So, do you have
a favorite celebrity at all?
Like, how do you
spend your time?
Got any hobbies?
Do you ever shut up?
What kind of people do
you hang with at school?
Who are your friends? Tell me!
I don't bother
with makin' friends.
They're always
too much trouble.
Just like you!
Well, sorry. I don't plan on
changing the person I am.
Which means, if you're gonna be
around me, this is what you get.
Just like you, Ulgar.
[ULGAR]
Tch.
[LUCA] You said your dad's
the vice‐principal.
So is he like, mega
strict at home, too?
[ULGAR]
I hardly ever talk to my dad.
He's not "family" to me.
Oh.
Dude, that's a rough situation,
but I gotta admit,
I was totally surprised
when you dropped that
bomb on us about him.
You'd think that his last name
would've tipped me off.
Nah, what kind of
weirdo keeps track
of everybody's
full names though?
I dunno, after I hear 'em once,
I guess they just stick
in my brain really easily.
Hey, do you remember
my last name?
You should, since we're
basically best friends now.
I told you before,
I'm not your friend.
Anyway, it's Esposito.
Luca Esposito.
[ULGAR gasps]
[LUCA] It's fine if you don't
remember everyone else's though.
That's your name? What?
Yeah.
And your father‐‐
what's your father
do for a living?
He, uh, he's a politician.
Come on, man, I'm pretty
sure I told you that.
[gasps]
[ULGAR]
Marco Esposito.
[ARIES] It's so nice,
eating outside together!
[YUNHUA]
Yeah, it's like a big party!
[KANATA]
Got enough over there?
[FUNICIA]
Oh, yeah, looks great!
Thanks to you guys
and all your hard work,
we were able to collect
enough food from this planet.
We'll be leaving tomorrow.
You know, I think
I might miss this place.
It turned out
to be really unique.
[ZACK]
Huh. I never thought
I would hear that
from you, Quitterie.
Yeah, she said she'd
like to stay forever.
She's right, this
planet was a paradise.
At times, it almost felt
like we were on vacation.
It sure did.
[camera clicks]
No matter how many photos
we take while we're here,
we'll still never
be able to capture
the way it feels, will we?
[CHARCE]
True, it is different
when you experience
it firsthand.
Looking at a picture
simply can't do it justice.
I guess the memories
we made here will get
more and more foggy
as we get older.
That's kind of sad.
Well, it doesn't have to be.
My father is researching
memory transplant technology.
You should know‐‐your mother
is assisting with it.
So in the not‐too‐
distant future,
we may be able to save
and revisit our memories.
‐‐In fact, we‐‐
‐‐[QUITTERIE] That's not what
I was referring to at all.
Don't you understand how
to think romantically?
Oh, Aries, get this.
I heard that Zack and
Quitterie's parents
work together as
colleagues of some kind.
Ah, memories.
It's kind of strange.
This place makes it easy
to forget we're in danger.
Yeah, the fact that
we're lost in space
5,000 light‐years
away from home,
plus the whole
assassination plot thing.
[QUITTERIE]
Oh, right, this is bad.
I totally forgot.
[KANATA]
Thanks for the reminder.
[YUN‐HUA]
Sorry.
But hey, we're still
making good progress!
Some of the shiest people on
the team are opening up lately.
Our relationships are really
starting to move forward.
[LUCA] Yeah, you're right, we're
all getting along pretty well!
Like, if there is a traitor,
I can't imagine who it would be.
[ALL gasp]
Don't move.
Ulgar!
[ULGAR]
The gun I'm holding is real.
Move, and I'll shoot.
It can't be.
I don't believe this!
[KANATA]
Ulgar is the enemy?