[KANATA]
Come on. Tell us everything.
Why did you have to be the one
to complete this mission?
Talk to us. Tell us who you are.
The truth is I'm a clone.
The name of my original
is Noah Vix. He's
the ruler of Vixia.
I am the king's clone.
[CHARCE] When I recall
my earliest memories,
I see stone pillars.
So many. Row upon row.
Like a marble forest
with no end in sight.
Now then, Charce.
Tell me about your
mission again.
What is the purpose
of your existence?
My king. I exist to
become your new body.
That's right.
You're not a person;
your life belongs
to me and me alone.
Someday, you will surrender
your very being unto me.
[CHARCE]
As you wish, my king.
[CHARCE] Growing up, that
mission was drilled into me.
I lived under a false identity,
claiming to be the son
of a close aide to the king,
forbidden to leave
the castle grounds.
I was allowed to learn
everything I could
about the outside world, though.
What fascinated me most
was flora and fauna.
I suppose being
confined to the grounds
is what made me so
interested in biology.
Full of wonder, I
dedicated myself to learning
everything I could
about what lived
beyond the castle walls.
The princess, who saw
how much I loved science,
looked after me every day.
Together, we studied
all the insect
and plant life we could find.
I loved spending time with her.
It was the only real fun I had,
with no idea the world had
anything more to offer,
I was content.
Until everything changed.
Your new mission is to
perish. Leave no trace.
[CHARCE] When the
Genome Control Act passed,
the king decided
to kill his clone
and sent me into space.
[NOAH] This device
has been passed to us
in secret through Vixia.
You will exit above Earth,
where no one will ever
be able to find you.
You will be transferred
to a civilian high school.
In your few, remaining days,
you will have the opportunity
to make some friends.
And then you will
die alongside them.
[CHARCE] I existed for
the king, and him alone.
A mere vessel, I was not
permitted to have goals.
It was a fact I accepted
without question.
It was just how I was raised.
No way. I can't believe this!
[CHARCE]
The king's orders were absolute.
I became an assassin for him
so that I could kill all
of you, along with myself!
But what about the
story you told us,
the one about being a noble?
[CHARCE] Not bad for something
I improvised on the spot, right?
[gasps]
[ZACK] I don't understand.
Why would you agree to this?
[KANATA]
Charce...
Do I see pity in your eyes?
You have no right to judge me!
You don't understand
what my world's like.
I'm willing to die for my king.
I consider this mission
to be the highest honor.
It wasn't dissimilar in
your era. Was it, Polina?
No.
[POLINA] Many in my era
happily gave their lives.
They were willing to
sacrifice everything
in the name of what
they worshipped.
The fraught nature
of human relations
plunged the entire planet
into darkness and chaos.
That was just the
way things were.
[CHARCE] And who could blame
them for their crimes?
They were molded to be that way,
raised to become martyrs
for their beliefs.
There are scores of
people out there,
existing without any
purpose or direction,
but no one could
say that about me!
My life is wonderful and
filled with great meaning!
[ARIES sobs]
[KANATA] Are you telling
us it was all an act?
I am.
[KANATA]
You're lying.
I know you think of us as
your friends, as your family.
Stay away from me.
I know you, Charce.
I can tell when
someone's forcing it.
You love us, I have
no doubt about that.
Don't flatter yourselves.
[KANATA]
How else do you think
we could've made it this far?
[CHARCE gasps]
[KANATA]
We've had each other's backs,
clawing our way home
from the brink of death!
You'll never convince me
that we aren't friends!
[CHARCE] Shut up!
I don't have any friends!
[KANATA]
Then answer this:
Why did you retract
the sphere twice?
[CHARCE gasps]
[KANATA] On Vilavurs,
and then on this planet.
You had your chance,
but you didn't take it.
You could have hunted
me down and killed me.
I wanna know what stopped you.
You couldn't murder your friend!
[CHARCE]
You're wrong.
I have no hesitations
about my mission.
But I'll tell you why I stopped.
I couldn't let Aries
be taken, too.
[gasps]
A‐Aries?
There's one thing
you misunderstand...
...about my mission.
I can't return to Astra alone.
Originally, I did plan
to kill everyone.
But, along the way,
that changed.
All because I discovered Aries.
What are you saying?
[CHARCE] The moment I
saw you at the spaceport,
I noticed the resemblance.
Then, in the
forests of Vilavurs,
I was struck by something else:
your photographic memory.
And, of course,
your heterochromia.
[CHARCE] There's no denying it.
You share the same genes.
Aries, you are the
king's only daughter.
[CHARCE]
You are Princess Seira's clone!
[ARIES gasps]
[SEIRA]
Charce. Wait, I can't keep up!
Oh, sorry, Princess.
I'll slow down.
Come on, please
just call me Seira!
After all, as my personal aide,
you have to obey me.
Consider it a command.
[CHARCE]
Yes, Seira.
[SEIRA]
It's kind of funny.
Technically, or, genetically,
rather, I'm your daughter.
But, to be perfectly honest,
you've always felt more
like my little brother.
Is there a reason
why you've always
been so kind to me?
I'm only a clone,
you don't have to‐‐
Quiet, Charce.
I couldn't care less
how my father sees you.
I'm nothing like him.
As I've said many times before,
I am fundamentally
opposed to my father's
rejuvenation plan.
Clones are people, too.
I can't forgive him.
[CHARCE]
Hm...
[SEIRA]
As a matter of fact, Charce.
I used to have a clone, as well.
Wait, really? Are you serious?
[SEIRA] Yes. When they first
told me about their plan,
I adamantly refused to
let them make one of me.
But then, they took
a sample of my DNA
without my knowledge.
[SEIRA]
Father! How could you?
One is your clone,
and one is mine.
The surrogate mothers
who birthed them
will also have the
honor of raising them.
[gasps]
[NOAH] Think of it as a spare
in case of emergencies.
If, for example,
you fall gravely ill,
we can harvest its organs.
No, I won't allow this!
Don't you remember?
How your mother fell
ill and passed away?
I refuse to lose anyone
else, do you hear me?
Please understand, Seira.
Together, we shall live forever!
[EMMA panting]
Come, her highness awaits you.
Hurry! This way.
Emma!
[EMMA]
Your highness!
You don't know what
this means to me.
You must take the child
and leave Vixia at once.
We're ready to execute
the escape plan now.
We must go!
All right. Tell me once again.
Do you have the courage
to raise this baby?
I do. I've no doubt, Princess.
She may not be
my flesh and blood,
but I carried her in
my womb for nine months.
I cannot bear to raise her here,
knowing the terrible
destiny that awaits her.
Thank you.
Emma, forgive me, but
you're the only person
I can trust with this task.
I promise she'll be
loved and cared for.
We must depart at once.
[SEIRA]
Now, dry your eyes and go.
Okay.
[gasps] Your Highness, wait.
The child doesn't
have a name yet.
You should name her.
A name?
[SEIRA]
"Aries."
How lovely.
Yes. Aries suits her well.
My sweet daughter. My Aries.
Goodbye, Aries. Live well.
[SEIRA]
I lied to father and said that
the baby had died from SIDS.
He tried to force me
to create another clone,
but I continued to stand
firm and defy his wishes
until he eventually gave up.
[SEIRA] But I am powerless
to stop his ambitions for you.
I'm so sorry. Oh, Charce.
What a sad, terrible
fate you have!
What's so awful about it?
[SEIRA]
The fact that you don't know...
That's what pains
me most of all.
[CHARCE]
Seira was strong,
but noble and gentle
at the same time.
A truly rare soul.
[CHARCE]
Though my only purpose in life
was to be the king's vessel,
I made it my secret,
personal mission
to protect and entertain her.
Look at this tree.
It's grown so quickly!
[gasps] Wow.
[gasps] Up there!
A white‐eye, the same one
we saw the other day!
Uh, okay.
You're boring.
I'm sorry, I honestly
don't remember.
I don't have the same
kind of memory that you do.
But, look over there,
a worm is being carried away
by a small army of ants!
[SEIRA] I'd rather enjoy
those flowers instead.
[CHARCE]
Huh?
[gasps]
[CHARCE gasps]
[SEIRA gasps]
[gasps]
[CHARCE]
Seira!
[CHARCE] An assassination
made to look like an accident,
with no way to prove it.
As a lowly aide,
my testimony was ignored,
everything swept under the rug.
[grunts]
[NOAH] You deserve
to be sentenced to death.
But, luckily for you,
your body belongs to me.
Rot in this cell and
think about your sins.
[CHARCE]
They locked me away in solitude.
I had nothing to do but
count the bricks in my prison.
I thought a lot about
the person I was.
Tormented by my
shame and regret,
I soon came to realize that
I was a worthless human being.
Now then.
The laws of the
land have changed,
and it seems I will no longer
require the use of your body.
Your new mission is to die.
[CHARCE]
Ah. Finally, I'll be put to use.
My life will have
meaning after all.
[CHARCE]
Yes! As you wish, my king!
I have no doubt.
You are Princess Seira's clone.
You were smuggled out of Vixia
when you were an infant.
So... Then my mother...?
[CHARCE]
One of Seira's handmaids.
Not your biological mother.
Oh! A Mother's Day gift? For me?
Wow. Aries!
[ARIES]
Please?
What? No, hon.
If there's something you want,
then you have to wait
until your birthday.
Happy birthday, sweetie!
Here! Your present!
[ARIES gasps]
[giggles]
She is my mom! I know it!
Hold on a second.
If Aries was hidden
away somewhere,
then how did she
end up on this team?
[CHARCE] My guess is that
Seira's killers orchestrated it.
They found out about
Emma and made certain
that Aries was put
onto team B‐5.
If it were ever
discovered that she was
Princess Seira's clone,
she could potentially
be named the king's heir.
That's why they
tried to kill her.
So the king would never
know she was still alive.
But I'll protect her.
I won't let Aries die.
Seira's life was
taken away from us,
but now we've got it back.
I can already see
the tears of joy
flowing down King Noah's face!
Aries will return to
him as Princess Seira.
I will deliver her to him!
[KANATA]
No, this is over!
Aries is Aries!
Not Seira! You idiot!
You clearly do not
understand King Noah
and just how much he wants‐‐
Quiet! It's not about the king.
This is about you and your pain.
Who was the most affected
by the princess' death?
And who was the happiest
to find Aries alive?
You! More than anyone!
[CHARCE grunts]
What happens if you
take Aries back?
They'll kill you anyway.
Right?
You're forgetting that you're
still the king's clone.
They want you dead, you moron.
That's true.
I'd return to outer space.
Where I'd die alone.
[gasps]
‐‐[ARIES gasps]
‐‐[ZACK] Kanata!
Don't tell me that's
what you really want!
You're not supposed to lie
to your friends, you jerk!
Now I understand why this trip
seemed like so much fun for you.
Why you were so happy.
You finally got
out of that castle
and had a chance
to see new worlds.
[gasps]
It's a dream come true for me.
[KANATA]
What you really want is to live.
Let's go home together.
We can see what
Astra has to offer.
I mean, the truth is,
none of us got the chance
to know our home planet‐‐
Not nearly as well as we wanted!
It's not too late! He's right!
Please, Charce!
Just come home with us!
The originals will be
punished, not you, Charce.
King or not, it's still a crime.
There's no reason
you should die.
[KANATA]
You didn't choose to be born,
and you had no say
in how you were raised.
But you can make
the choice to change!
I can't change.
Where I'm from,
no one ever does.
[YUN‐HUA]
I know you can! I did it!
I was able to transform!
And it was because
of my friends!
[whimpering]
Yeah, and I'm no longer the girl
my mother raised me
to be. Funi either.
Your parents and your
genes don't matter!
The people you meet,
and the experiences
you have can change you,
if you allow them to!
[CHARCE]
I understand that. It's clear.
I've been on this journey, too.
But... I...
[CHARCE]
There's nothing I can do!
[sobbing]
[CHARCE] I kept the sphere
generation device hidden.
It was in the left
sleeve of my suit
so that I could bring it out
whenever I needed to.
[gasps]
But I have a spare one.
[KANATA gasps]
Stand back, you guys!
No, Charce.
‐‐[ULGAR] Damn!
‐‐[ZACK] You can't!
There isn't a clear
shot from here!
[KANATA] It's okay. He won't
do anything to hurt us.
Not while Aries is by our side.
But then why did he just...?
I understand you, Charce.
I know exactly what
you're thinking.
I won't let you.
[BOTH gasp]
The sphere it's‐‐
[KANATA] Charce is...
trying to kill himself.
[KANATA]
Stop this!
I'm sorry, my friends.
I really do love you.
Kanata, no!
No! Please, don't!
Kanata?
[LUCA]
What's he doing?
Trying to get around it?
He's not fast enough!
Wait, no.
He's running straight
into the sphere!
[ARIES]
Yes, of course he is.
He's always running
headlong into things.
Straight on. No hesitation.
[ARIES]
From the first day we met,
that's been his way.
[ARIES gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
Anti‐gravity shoes!
Ultimate Dive Bomb time.
[CHARCE grunts]
That's enough!
What are you doing?!
Quick, get out of there!
All of you, get away
from us, fast,
or else you'll be‐‐!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[screams]
Kanata!
[STUDENTS panting]
[KANATA screaming]
[QUITTERIE] Keep him still!
I'll stop the bleeding!
My arm‐‐it hurts
so much! Quitterie!
[KANATA screaming]
‐‐[ZACK] Just hold on!
‐‐[ARIES] Try and stay calm!
[QUITTERIE]
I can't stop it. Zack!
Bring up the controls
in his suit!
Set the right arm
pressure to maximum!
Roger that!
[KANATA grunting]
I'm so sorry!
Kanata. Please forgive me!
Listen. When we get
back home to Astra,
you owe me.
You have to help me.
Be by my side.
[CHARCE]
Kanata. I...
[KANATA] I'm gonna...
have my own ship someday.
You promised to
join up, remember?
Sounds nice.
You can count me in.
I'd like to join you.
Perhaps I can be your
second in command.
So, now, you can be
my right hand man.
[CHARCE gasps]