[LUCA] Look, everyone!
We're almost there!
Oh, cool!
I see. So that's
Planet Vilavurs.
[ARIES]
Ah! I'm so excited!
I hope the food there's yummy!
Ugh, I totally forgot
to pack my sunscreen.
Check out this baby.
I made an awesome bug net!
Aw, sweet!
We should try to
catch some beetles!
Guys, this is a foreign
planet, not a camping trip!
[KANATA]
Dude!
‐‐[LUCA] Hey! We could even...
‐‐[ARIES] Team B‐5 Camp Log.
We've reached the
first planet, Vilavurs.
Hopefully, we'll be
able to find 20 days'
worth of food and water
that we can store
while we're here.
[LUCA]
Oh! Great idea!
[ARIES] I have to admit,
I'm a little nervous
about exploring a new planet.
But it's still cool!
[KANATA] Awesome! This
planet seems pretty cool.
[LUCA] We should probably
still be careful.
‐‐[TUR‐GON roars]
‐‐[STUDENTS gasp]
[QUITTERIE] Whoa! What
the heck was that sound?
Look there!
[LUCA]
Crap! It's as big as a dragon!
[CHARCE] If it decides to
attack us, we won't last long.
[ARIES]
Uh. Hey, you guys?
Since its head is
shaped like a turtle,
we should call it a Tur‐gon,
what do ya think?
[QUITTERIE] That monster
could swallow us whole
and that's your first thought?
Aw, stop being
such a worry‐wart!
If it tries to start
anything, then I'll kill it
and we can serve it for dinner!
You know, that's exactly
what the first character
to die in a horror
movie would say.
This is stupid!
[yells] Let's get off this
dumb planet before we die!
‐‐[yells]
‐‐[YUN‐HUA yelps]
Huh? But why?
[ARIES giggles]
That's the loudest I've
ever heard you speak.
I got you pretty good, huh?
That was not cool, Aries!
You do know we're all connected
via helmet communicator!
Oops! My bad, you guys!
[laughs]
[QUITTERIE] What's the deal?
Stop messing around.
That was loud!
[YUN‐HUA gasps]
[CHARCE] Seems like your
communicator is all fixed,
‐‐huh, Aries?
‐‐[ARIES] Yep!
Zack actually helped me
with it before we got here.
If he left it alone,
we could have skipped
the heart attack.
[laughs]
[KANATA]
I get it.
That should have been my job.
This time, I won't fail.
I'll be a reliable leader.
We'll split into three teams.
Zack and Funicia will
take care of the ship.
Roger that.
[BEEGO]
We're on it!
Ulgar and Yun‐hua are
both on water duty.
As for the rest of us,
we'll go forage for food.
I'll pass.
[KANATA]
What?!
I am not doing
anything dangerous.
[KANATA] Sure, it might
be a little risky,
but I promise to take
care of everyone!
Nope, denied.
[KANATA]
Come on!
Um. I was just wondering,
is there, like, any
particular type of food
we should be looking for?
[KANATA]
Excellent question!
Nuts are usually the most
nutritious of the options.
Followed closely by berries.
Avoid red plants.
Most mushrooms will probably
be poisonous as well,
so it's best if we skip those.
Wow, that was super impressive!
That's the first time you've
ever sounded knowledgeable!
[laughs] Just stick with
me and you'll be fine!
[LUCA]
So... Which ones are the berries
and which ones are the nuts?
It's a different planet, okay?
Sorry I don't know
about this weird food!
This is interesting!
From what I can see,
the local flora and environment
appear similar to the
Treepeel Spat system.
I bet these have well‐developed
fibrovascular bundles! Hah!
Wow, I have no idea
what he just said,
but he sounds
smarter than Kanata.
You sure do know a lot
about plant life,
don't you, Charce?
Well, I am the curious sort.
Whatever. Just grab
anything you can find.
We'll figure out if it's
safe to eat or not later.
Sheesh, so much for
Mister‐Know‐It‐All, huh?
[TUR‐GON screeches]
Do you think it's going to
try and attack all of us?
Creatures that large won't
be able to fit down here.
We should be safe as long
as we're in the forest.
[growling]
[QUITTERIE screams]
Ew! Look out!
Weird space creature thingy!
Aw. Cute. He must
live around here.
[screams] Oh, my gosh,
they have us surrounded!
Hey, Charce! They're not
dangerous, are they?
Well, it's hard to be
sure at the moment.
[laughs] That tickles, Juliano!
[QUITTERIE]
Why are hot dudes always crazy?
What if they, like,
lay their gross eggs on you
or something strange?
[KANATA]
Check it out!
This stick looks
like a cool sword!
And mine looks like a spear!
I dub thee, the Luca Lance!
[QUITTERIE]
Boys are so dumb.
Hey, morons, this
isn't a field trip!
[ARIES yelps]
[ARIES laughs]
[KANATA laughs]
This tree is mad bouncy!
It's like a trampoline!
[CHARCE] The top is covered
in a kind of grass,
perhaps for photo‐synthesis?
[LUCA]
Hey, let's play sumo!
[QUITTERIE]
Why isn't anyone afraid
of all the nutso
things around us?
Are you crazy?
[ARIES] You should come
up here, Quitterie!
It's a ton of fun!
Please. As if.
I guess I'll have to
be the mature one here
and keep foraging for food.
[QUITTERIE screams]
[ARIES]
Look, Quitterie is flying!
[KANATA]
Cool!
[QUITTERIE pants]
[CHARCE]
Interesting!
The parachute‐like
structure must serve
to help spread the seeds
of the heavy fruit.
How can you be calm
when I'm literally
falling to my death?
Oh. It's a star shape.
[KANATA]
This is awesome.
Everything is totally new here.
It's kind of exciting, isn't it?
[CHARCE] Yes, but we
shouldn't slack off too much.
[LUCA]
He's right.
We need to find some more food.
[KANATA] Hey, weren't you
the one who suggested
the sumo match?
[LUCA giggles]
[sighs]
[FUNICIA]
Um, Zack? Is something wrong?
[ZACK]
No.
We're lucky that this
planet seems to have a lot
of food and water, huh?
Yep! Don't give up
and it'll work out.
Just keep moving.
All right! Tomorrow,
let's hunt some animals!
[QUITTERIE screams]
Gross, no way!
[LUCA]
It'll be fine!
One swift jab of the Luca Lance
will take 'em down! O‐Oh.
I think you may have
left it back on top
of the trampoline tree.
[LUCA]
My bad.
[ARIES giggles]
[KANATA]
Don't give up.
Uh‐‐
[gasps]
It's the sphere!
Let's go! Get to the ship!
Man, what the heck
is that thing?
Helmets on!
Which way do we go?
[STUDENTS panting, yelling]
‐‐[KANATA] Is it this way?
‐‐[LUCA] No, over there.
[QUITTERIE]
Pick a direction!
I remember that tree! This way!
Once we're past that rock,
we're outta the forest!
Aries.
Do you really remember all
the scenery that we passed?
Uh‐huh! I actually have
a photographic memory.
[panting]
What is up with that
stupid ball thing?
I'm beyond sick of all
this crap‐‐I wanna go home
and I don't wanna be on
this dumb planet anymore!
[KANATA]
We're trying to get home, okay?
What about our idea, though?
Is it possible the orb could
take us back to Planet McPa?
No. I really doubt it can.
When we were running away,
I looked back at it.
All I could see was stars.
We'd end up back in space.
What's weird is that
this is the second time
we've seen it. Like what if it
isn't a natural phenomenon?
Like maybe...
...we got caught up in
something bigger and scarier
than we originally thought?
[KANATA grunts]
[ALL gasp]
Dude, was the silence
really so awkward
that you had to
start pigging out?
[QUITTERIE] We don't even
know if that's safe or not!
Are you dumb?
Shut up. I'm just hungry, okay?
When I was lost
on that mountain,
our biggest enemies were
hunger and our thoughts.
Was help coming?
We had no way of knowing
and that thought nearly
drove me insane.
You don't know what
you don't know,
no matter how much
you think about stuff.
Captain Obvious strikes again.
Although he makes
a pretty good point.
[KANATA]
We have to survive.
And that means tackling
the issues in front of us.
So eat up! Captain's orders.
No way!
And why should we
have to listen to you?
If anything, you've proven
to be nothing but useless!
[yelps]
[QUITTERIE] I think Charce is
much better suited for leading!
[ZACK]
That's enough, Quitterie.
Hey, Kanata. Don't mind her.
[KANATA grumbles]
If you wanna do
something useful,
then get rid of
the stupid Tur‐gons!
Or better yet, get rid
of the ball of death!
Fine then, challenge accepted!
I'm gonna go out there and
catch a Tur‐gon right now!
[LUCA]
Wait, what?
And when I do,
you'll have to admit
I'm an awesome captain! 'Kay?
Calm down! She's obviously
just trying to rile you up.
[KANATA]
I'm perfectly calm!
That was unnecessary.
You know that?
[QUITTERIE]
Hmph.
You haven't changed at all
since we were children.
Tell me. How many friends
do you plan to drive off?
Shut up!
Friends and people
are so overrated!
And FYI. Nobody on this ship
counts as a real friend anyway!
Quitterie.
[BEEGO] We should really
all try and be friends!
[QUITTERIE growls]
Don't you tell me what to do!
You're not even my real sister!
Quitterie, stop!
[gasps]
Awkward.
That could have gone better.
[ARIES] I hope Quitterie
didn't wander too far off.
She's not a child; I'm
sure she'll be just fine.
I don't mean to pry,
but have you guys
known each other for
a long time or something?
Yes we actually
grew up together.
[LUCA] Ah, and has she
always been so "spirited"?
She has.
Quitterie has no father.
Her mom is a doctor
and is never home.
Her entire life she's been
raised by caretakers,
and it's made her a bit selfish.
She doesn't know how
to deal with people,
so it's no surprise
that she didn't know
what to do when she
was handed a new sister
out of the blue.
[ARIES]
"Out of the blue"?
Yes. You see, Funi is
from an orphanage.
Quitterie's mother
adopted her recently.
But I like being
her little sister.
I don't have any other
siblings or friends,
so it's nice having
a pretty big sister
that I can look up to!
[QUITTERIE]
Huh?! An adoption?
What do you mean, Mom?
[sighs] Which part was unclear?
A friend just passed away
and left her daughter.
So adoption seemed appropriate.
Take care of her.
[gasps]
[QUITTERIE]
Me? Take care of her?
But you don't take
care of children.
You don't even love the
child you already have.
[QUITTERIE]
So why have more?
I'm Funicia.
[QUITTERIE]
Don't get close to me.
I don't know how to love.
No one taught me.
[ARIES]
Huh? Where'd Funi go?
Uh‐‐ She's missing?
She must have wandered off while
we were looking for Quitterie.
[FUNICIA]
I'm up here!
[ARIES]
She's on the trampoline tree!
[gasps]
[FUNICIA] Look, you guys, I
found a really pretty flower!
[gasps]
[ZACK]
What the‐‐?
[ALL gasp]
[CHARCE]
Did the trees all just grow?
[ARIES]
Funi!
[QUITTERIE pants]
[gasps] Quitterie?
[QUITTERIE]
Funicia!
[screams] Quitterie!
[whimpering]
[QUITTERIE]
Funicia!
Don't move an inch!
I'll find a way to get you!
[CHARCE] If they're
reacting to the sunlight,
then they'll probably retract
back to their normal
size at nightfall.
What? There's no way I could
possibly wait that long!
We don't have much choice;
we can't build a bridge up here.
[TUR‐GON growls]
It's a Tur‐gon!
[screams]
It's going after Funi!
[QUITTERIE]
Funicia!
[ARIES gasps]
[footsteps]
[ARIES]
Kanata?
What, where?
[KANATA] The first jump looks
like it's... seven meters.
Can I make it?
Is he going to jump without
the anti‐gravity shoes?
[KANATA]
When things seem hopeless...
...you have to act tough!
[ZACK]
He made it!
[CHARCE]
All right!
[LUCA]
That was awesome!
I don't get it‐‐
isn't he scared of dying?
Falling from this height
would be lethal.
Kanata... Hoshijima...
That's it, now I remember!
I saw a news article about him.
He's a track and
field decathlete!
It's no wonder he displays
such advanced agility.
He's been thoroughly trained.
I guess that explains why
he's so athletic, then.
He didn't make that jump
just because he's
been trained, though.
What makes him different
is that he has the ability
to risk his life
for his friends!
[LUCA, ZACK] Yes!
[CHARCE]
You've got this, Kanata!
[LUCA]
Just one more!
[panting] I'm coming.
Just hold on.
He looks exhausted.
Yes, well, I'm sure he would be.
He's used a lot of energy.
And now he's running low.
[gasps] I've got it!
[ZACK]
Hey, Quitterie!
[TUR‐GON screeches]
[FUNICIA screams]
‐‐[ZACK] Funi!
‐‐[screams] No!
[LUCA]
It's got her!
[CHARCE]
We can't just let it fly away!
[KANATA]
I can't reach it from here!
There has to be
something! But where?
[KANATA]
That's the...
It's the Luca Lance!
Excuse me?
[LUCA]
He's gonna throw it!
[ALL]
Go! Kanata!
[FUNICIA screams]
[gasps]
[FUNICIA grunts]
[GROUP cheer]
[ZACK]
He did it!
[LUCA]
Look, Funi's okay!
Dang, I'm exhausted.
[FUNICIA cries]
[KANATA]
I'm coming!
[ARIES] It's just like
the time he rescued me.
He came flying through
space, and he told me...
[sobbing]
[ARIES]
"You did really well."
You di‐‐
[yells]
‐‐[GROUP gasps]
‐‐[LUCA] Oh, no!
[screams]
[KANATA grunts]
[KANATA]
Whoa!
[QUITTERIE pants]
Just in time!
That jerk, he
seriously almost died!
You did really well.
Thanks!
[QUITTERIE panting]
Funicia!
[KANATA groans]
I'm so sorry, Funicia!
It's my fault! I'm sorry!
[FUNICIA]
No. It was my fault.
I shouldn't have wandered off
without telling anyone.
But I saw a flower that
looked kinda like yours.
‐‐So I‐‐
‐‐[QUITTERIE] A flower?
Like mine? What do you mean?
[giggles]
Please forgive me, Funi.
[QUITTERIE]
I'm sorry.
[gasps]
[KANATA]
Uh‐‐
[QUITTERIE]
Kanata. Thank you.
[KANATA]
Huh?
[QUITTERIE] And I'm sorry for
the things I said earlier.
No. For how I've acted
this whole time.
Because...
...I couldn't be
honest with myself.
[QUITTERIE] And I don't know
how to handle having friends.
[ZACK] Then you'll have
to be honest from now on.
With your family
and with your friends.
You know, you really
don't have room to talk.
[yelps] Not that honest.
‐‐[KANATA chuckles]
‐‐[QUITTERIE] Hmph!
[CHARCE] Wow! You were
amazing up there, Kanata!
[LUCA]
Yeah!
I mean, the athletics
were all cool and all,
but, man, you've got
nerves of steel!
You've gotta be
like, part robot‐‐
show us your wires and stuff!
[KANATA] That's kind of
a weird compliment, Luca!
[LUCA chuckles]
[ARIES] It's so cool
that you're a decathlete!
You really think so? I mean...
It's just something my
dad was training me in.
The thing is,
my dad used to be a
world‐class athlete himself,
but then he got injured one day,
so he had to retire
at a pretty young age.
He was forcing his dream
onto me and I wanted out.
And then... in middle
school, I met my teacher.
He got me interested
in space exploration.
I was finally free of my dad.
But, then we got lost
in the mountains.
[KANATA]
If only I had more stamina,
or a little bit more courage...
Then maybe I could
have done more.
[KANATA] Maybe my teacher
would still be alive.
So I begged my dad
to train me again.
It's whatever. I don't
intend to compete.
I'm not taking on
my dad's dream.
I'm here to take
over for my teacher.
It's always been my intention
to go into space
research one day.
If you have the need,
and the ship, I'm there.
Sounds nice. Count me in.
I'd like to join you.
That's wonderful!
And in the meantime,
you can practice by
leading this team!
No can do. I'm not fit
to be this team's captain.
I took a stupid risk up there.
If Quitterie hadn't helped me,
I'd be dead right now.
She was right earlier,
Charce should be the captain.
[CHARCE] Not many people
can make and execute
critical decisions
without hesitation.
Not like you did.
We're all in agreement.
[gasps]
[ARIES chuckles]
Perhaps I can be your
second in command.
But you're the captain.
Okay then. I won't
let you down. Promise.
You've got this!
What're your
instructions, Captain?
Right! First.
Haul this dude back to the ship!
[ARIES, CHARCE, LUCA, ZACK]
What?
[KANATA] Man, who knew Tur‐gon
would be crazy delicious?
[LUCA] Aw, yeah, I could totally
eat this every single day!
Me, too!
[FUNICIA]
So yummy!
[CHARCE] It's important
to balance our diets though.
Especially over
the next 20 days.
[ZACK]
About that.
Using some spare parts
from around the ship,
I've made an edibility tester.
[LUCA]
You can do everything!
Watch this. I'll show you.
[EDIBILITY TESTER]
Yummy.
[KANATA] Check out how
cute the display is.
[LUCA] Did you record
your own voice for it?
[ARIES laughs]
Is something wrong?
[ARIES] I'm sorry. I just
thought it was really funny.
This might sound
a little bit crazy.
But I... I'm enjoying
myself a lot on this trip.
See I grew up in the country,
and I didn't have a lot
of friends out there.
So being here with
you guys makes me happy
and I'm super glad
we all get to be friends!
[ARIES]
Team B‐5 Camp Log.
[ARIES] After just two
full days, we had enough
food and water so that we
could leave Planet Vilavurs.
Also, I think we're
all a lot closer
to each other now!
[ZACK] Kanata. I need
to discuss something
with you in private.
What! Someone broke
the communicator?
Are you sure?
Yes, I took a closer look.
The missing parts weren't
damaged over time‐‐
they were actually
cut out of it.
Worse, the cuts seem
new. They're fresh.
Hold on. You mean...?
Exactly. Whoever's
responsible is on this ship.