[POLINA]
What do you call that planet?
If that's not Earth, what is it?
What planet do all
of you come from?
What's our home planet?
I thought that was obvious.
Our planet is Astra.
[POLINA]
What's this continent?
That's Carifa.
[POLINA]
This one?
[LUCA]
That'd be Aria Sue.
Like I thought, this planet
is nothing like
the Earth I know.
And why would it be?
It seems we come from
different home planets.
It's the only explanation.
[LUCA]
But that doesn't make sense!
Does that actually mean
there are humans
living on "Earth"?
[KANATA]
Listen.
This might be a shot
in the dark, but...
What if Polina's a space alien?
[QUITTERIE]
What if you're stupid?
Seriously, she could be
mimicking a human form!
[QUITTERIE] Maybe you should
follow her example, idiot!
Sorry, Polina.
He just has whipped cream
where his brain should be.
No, it's fine.
From your point of view,
I am some weirdo
from an alien planet.
[QUITTERIE]
Way to go Captain Moron,
you made her cry again.
I'd say it's obvious that
we're all human beings.
I'm certain of that.
But we cannot ignore
that we originate
from different planets.
[POLINA] It's a bit odd
that we all speak English,
though my native language
is actually Russian.
Have you heard of Russia?
[KANATA]
Mm... Uh‐uh.
Wait. Russia? I know
that! It's a country.
So you have heard of it?
[ZACK] "Country"? An outdated
geopolitical term.
They've ceased to exist.
No countries? But that's...
[ARIES]
Russia was in the northern part
of the Aria Sue Continent.
At least, before it
became the Soviet Union.
China used to be over there.
The small island next
to China was Japan.
And I think right
below that was India.
Whoa.
[LUCA]
Those are Old Era maps.
I can't believe
you remember them.
[POLINA]
Everything seems out of place,
but the relative
positions are correct.
The difference is... time?
[POLINA] I think if we really
want to get to the bottom
of this conundrum, then we
need to compare our histories.
[ARIES]
At that point.
We started sharing the
histories of our two worlds.
Let's see, there's the
industrial revolution,
and then we had the first
and second world wars, right?
Yeah, everything seems
pretty similar so far.
That's true, but your knowledge
of world events is vague.
Don't they teach
you kids any history?
[CHARCE]
There are a few classes,
but not much regarding
the Old Era.
[ARIES] I thought it was
all pretty interesting,
so I studied a lot on my own.
But there aren't
many books about it.
Not many books?
You see, in school,
we're taught to always
look towards the future instead
of dwelling on the past.
How sad.
History's such an important
facet of a good education.
This whole thing feels
deliberate somehow.
Like something is
being covered up.
Anyway, let's get back on track,
after the cold war there's
a key turning point.
And that was World
War Three, in 1962.
[POLINA gasps]
World War Three?
That's can't be!
Because that was the year
of the Cuban Missile Crisis!
Never heard of it.
Same here, but there
used to be a country
called Cuba whose
base got bombed.
And from what I read,
that event became the trigger,
leading us to World War Three.
Hold on. My history
is different!
Cuba's base was never bombed‐‐
the whole war was averted!
That must be where
it branches off.
This is the juncture.
[POLINA] A war broke out after
the Cuban Missile Crisis?
I don't understand.
Dear God. Help us.
[KANATA]
God?
That's weird.
What does "God" mean?
[POLINA gasps]
[POLINA]
He doesn't know about God?
So, they don't have
countries or religions?
Please, tell me, what happened
after the third world war?
[ARIES] On October 27th,
1962, all‐out war began
between the USA and
the Soviet Union.
Nuclear missiles were
launched which affected
nearby countries,
plunging the world
into a full‐blown nuclear war.
The conflict only
lasted two months,
but half the world's
population was lost,
and our planet was reduced
to a barren wasteland.
The survivors regretted
what had happened
and vowed to strive for
a more harmonious way of life.
In 1963, the United World
Government was established,
which unified the planet's
remaining population.
A common language was adopted,
and guns were outlawed.
People set aside
their differences
and worked together to rebuild
society at a rapid pace.
That's how humanity
was finally able
to create a peaceful world.
[POLINA] Their history
is completely different.
How is this possible?
More importantly,
did these things even
really happen at all?
Okay, now it's
your turn, Polina.
Please tell us. About the war.
Is it true that
Earth really managed
to avoid World War Three?
[POLINA] Yes. And though
it was far from peaceful,
we avoided starting
a global war.
However, a far greater
threat emerged,
one that overshadowed
petty human conflicts.
In 2049, an asteroid
was discovered,
predicted to hit earth
within eight years.
[ALL]
An asteroid?
[POLINA] It was 300
kilometers in diameter,
and it would have annihilated
every living thing
on the planet upon impact.
[KANATA]
No way. Are you serious?
[LUCA] But the year 2057
has already passed!
And we weren't hit
by any asteroid!
Listen, we already know that
our histories are different.
So let's hear Polina out.
There was only one logical
solution to the problem.
We would have to immigrate
to a new planet.
All of humanity,
our plants and animals,
our historical relics...
Once we found a new home planet,
the idea was to
move everything there.
But that's so much!
You could never move an entire
planet's worth of people.
[POLINA] It's possible.
Thanks to artificial wormholes.
[KANATA]
Artificial what now?
[gasps]
No way.
Um, what's a wormhole?
It's a tunnel that passes
through time and space.
It allows for instantaneous
transport between two points,
though I had no idea
the technology existed.
[LUCA]
Wait, then maybe that's...
Oh, yes.
That thought had
actually crossed my mind
when you told me
about your story.
It's possible that
the "ball of death"
you described to me
was a wormhole.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[POLINA] At the time
the wormhole technology
was being developed,
we were scrambling
to find a new habitable planet.
In fact, the Arc
series of spaceships
were built specifically
for that task.
This ship is probably
the Arc Seven,
which was never used.
You already know
the fate of the Arc Six.
Because that was our ship.
Do you have any idea what
happened after you left?
Did the exodus work?
Yes, it did. I'm sure of it.
It was successful.
[STUDENTS gasp]
So then what you're saying...
Yes. The planet that was
chosen had to be Astra.
You and everyone else on Astra
are descendants of Earthlings.
‐‐For real?
‐‐[ARIES] That's crazy!
[POLINA] There are still some
things that don't make sense,
but that's the only
logical conclusion.
We found a new planet.
And inevitably, the
asteroid struck Earth.
[QUITTERIE]
Did it survive?
[POLINA sighs] You said that
when the sphere swallowed you,
it spat you out into space
above an ice planet.
That there were
no signs of life.
Isn't that correct?
Over an ice planet?
[gasps] Yeah, I remember!
Then that was...
[POLINA]
That's right. It was Earth.
[KANATA, CHARCE, ARIES gasp]
There would certainly have
been debris from the impact.
Which blocked out the sun,
causing an ice age.
That would explain it.
The sphere of light was
a gate for the exodus.
[POLINA]
Your ship, the Arc Seven,
was probably parked over
the terminal above Earth.
It was most likely
knocked into free orbit
shortly after the
asteroid struck.
Oh, I see. All this time,
we've been traveling
from Earth to Astra.
We just never knew it.
Hold on, something's
not making sense here.
It's 2063.
According to Polina's timeline,
the exodus was
completed in 2057.
That was only six years ago.
The planets may be similar,
but there'd still
be construction.
Colonization should've
taken much longer,
don't you think?
I don't wanna sound paranoid,
but do you think it
could be another secret?
[ULGAR]
It's definitely possible.
"The adults are lying to us."
That's what my brother told me.
We can't trust the adults.
Not when they're
hiding the truth
from younger generations.
Hey. Let's stop here.
There's no point in
stressing about something
when we don't have
all the facts.
You think so?
[ARIES]
The mood's so tense.
Throwing around conspiracy
theories won't help.
What's important
is making it back.
Then we can discover the
truth with our own eyes.
I mean, we're great when it
comes to learning new things.
After all, planet exploration
is kind of our specialty, right?
[KANATA] Exactly.
Let's go home. To Astra.
[ARIES]
Team B‐5, Camp Log.
The Astra is headed
to the next‐to‐last stop
on our journey, Planet Galem.
We've decided to set
aside the mystery
of our world for now.
And the ship is back
to its peaceful state.
"Never mind the idiot,
let's go to the lodge."
"You guys see that?"
"What is that thing?"
"It's coming toward us."
"No way it's real, I bet
it's all just theatrics."
Whoosh. "Let's get
the heck outta here!"
[gasps]
[door buzzes]
[ARIES]
Just a second!
[gasps] Whoa, Kanata?
Uh. What are you doing here?
Isn't it time for lights out?
Yeah, sorry. Can I talk to you?
[ARIES]
Huh? Like, as in right now?
But I'm not prepared yet!
There's nothing to
prepare, just let me in!
[yelps] No! I mean yes!
Wait, no! I meant no!
Come on, hurry up
before someone sees us.
But why would that matter?
[KANATA] I'm serious here!
It'll only take us a minute!
Only a minute? For real?
[KANATA grunts]
Aries. Please.
[ARIES gasps]
Uh, do you really promise
it's just talking?
Yeah, it's important.
Okay.
[ARIES] I can't believe
we're at the last planet.
[KANATA]
Same.
[QUITTERIE]
I'm oddly kinda sad about it.
That's weird when
you think about
how much you've complained.
It's been an interesting
journey, huh?
Hey, Aries. How's the
trip been for you?
Good question. A lot
of stuff has happened.
But I still achieved my goal.
Your goal?
Yeah, you don't remember?
To become friends with everyone!
[gasps]
I'd say you probably
overachieved it.
[KANATA] Let's keep
exploration within 500 meters
of the ship for today.
Quitterie, you're on standby.
Funi, you stick with Zack.
[BOTH]
Aye, yeah.
[KANATA]
How's the atmosphere, Charce?
All is well.
‐‐[KANATA] Our focus today...
‐‐[POLINA] You're so efficient.
It's quite impressive.
Well, this is our fifth stop.
[STUDENTS]
Aye, yeah!
Awesome catch! You're so
good at this stuff.
It looks delicious.
I worry about your sense
of taste sometimes.
[ARIES] This seems like
a beautiful planet;
there's a lot of nature.
[KANATA] Yeah, it should make
finding food pretty easy.
We're so close to Astra.
I know.
[ARIES] I wonder what
our lives will be like
when we get back.
I mean, I'll still live
with my mom of course,
at home, but I know
that's not an option
for the rest of you.
[KANATA]
True. But I bet the government
will help us out
until we graduate.
That being said,
I'm sure any one of us
could make it on our own.
After running around
the galaxy like this,
there's not much left
to be afraid of.
Yes, I agree.
I definitely feel like
I've grown stronger
over the course of this trip,
probably because of you.
[KANATA]
When we get back to Astra...
[ARIES]
Yeah?
Uh‐‐ Um. If you want,
I'll walk you home.
I don't get it.
A camping trip isn't over
until you're home safely!
And I'm the captain.
[gasps] Y‐Yes, I'd like that!
I'll introduce you to my mom!
Uh. Okay, cool.
Well, I think we've
covered this area!
I should go look in
the southern parts.
Why don't you go
meet up with everyone?
They're in the forest.
[ARIES]
Sure, sounds good!
I'll heat up with everyone
for a good rest.
[KANATA] That's definitely
not what I said.
[KANATA]
Things are going well.
The odds of making it
back are pretty good.
I'm worried about
the enemy among us,
but now we all share a bond
that's deeper than friendship.
I'm sure they value
that, as well.
There haven't been
any attacks in a while.
Nobody's trying to figure out
who the traitor is
because of that bond.
I don't have to worry about it.
It's gonna work out and
we're all gonna get home.
I doubt that person's
our enemy anymore.
[gasps]
[KANATA]
The sphere!
Dammit!
I didn't think it would
follow me into the cave!
[KANATA]
Aries!
Kanata? What's the matter?
Why are you running?
[KANATA]
Aries! It's the death ball!
Are you sure?
It vanished.
Hey, what's going on?
Are you okay?
Let's return to the ship.
[KANATA] The enemy intends
to kill us all on this planet.
My gut says they'll use
the Astra and go home alone.
I've figured out
who the enemy is.
I don't think they know
that I've caught on yet.
I'll have to make
my move tomorrow.
It's going down.
Guys. Listen.
I need to talk to you alone.
Yesterday, I was attacked
by the death ball.
‐‐[ZACK gasps]
‐‐[CHARCE] You're kidding me!
That means it's the enemy.
[KANATA] Yes. They're
trying to kill us here.
But I'm going to take them
down before they can hurt us.
Do you know who it is?
Please tell us.
It's Ulgar? Are you sure?
Really? He's the one?
It's true. I don't have proof.
So I'm going to need your help
to lure him out of hiding.
Just hold on. Why is it Ulgar?
I can't explain everything.
But for right now...
Just hear me out.
Remember the first day of camp?
When we were all
swallowed by the orb?
If the "exit" for
that thing was used
for the exodus, then why
was the "entrance"
on a different planet?
Like why McPa?
Or even Vilavurs
for that matter.
It must be a portable wormhole
that someone could carry.
[KANATA]
That's right.
Assuming that is true,
why would he resume
the killing spree now?
Doesn't he want to get
back to Astra, too?
He only worked with us
because it improved
his chances of survival.
But now we're only one
stop away from home.
Now he can finish his mission
and escape without
the rest of us.
[ZACK] Can't we just
lock Ulgar in the brig?
That would be safer, right?
[KANATA]
It won't be that simple.
He has two powerful weapons.
The gun.
And the sphere.
Do you have a plan, then?
I tried to guess his actions.
He came after me
when I was alone.
Probably thought
it was too risky
to go after all of us together.
That's how we'll win.
So then?
I thought Charce could
go forage with Ulgar.
You want me to be
the bait? Come on.
Please, just listen.
[KANATA]
Zack and I will tail you.
So try to go somewhere
that's easy for us to hide.
Like that cave in the south
where I was yesterday.
We'll adjust the helmet comms.
That way the three
of us can talk.
We can take our positions
while you lure Ulgar
into the cave.
Eventually, he should
bring out the wormhole.
That's when we'll
strike from behind.
You really think
it'll be that simple?
We have a good chance.
He thinks he can surprise us,
but we already know his game.
You just need to be on guard
for the moment he
brings out the orb.
Something else to note:
he's tried to attack us
with the sphere three
times now and failed.
He might try to use
the gun this time
to make sure he succeeds.
But I made a few alterations,
so it won't be able to fire.
[CHARCE]
I see.
He'll be vulnerable while
trying to figure out
why the gun is malfunctioning.
[KANATA]
Can you handle it?
[CHARCE]
I trust you, Captain.
We've entered the cave.
[KANATA]
Go straight down the path.
You can use the fluorescent
plants to guide the way.
[ZACK]
We just got here.
[KANATA] Try to keep some
distance from Ulgar.
Don't get too close.
There's a chamber.
I'll pretend to search
the area for food.
Wish me luck.
[KANATA]
Wait, Charce, abort!
[gasps] What's wrong?
[KANATA]
It's an emergency!
I just got a call from
Quitterie. Funi's missing!
That's terrible!
[KANATA]
Return to the ship.
Zack and I are leaving
now to go look for her!
[CHARCE]
Got it.
[gasps]
[ULGAR gasps]
[CHARCE gasps]
[KANATA]
Turn off the wormhole.
So you were the enemy
the whole time.
Huh, Charce?
[KANATA] Is this what
controls the sphere?
What's going on here?
How dare you!
You tell me what's going on.
I saw you bring
out the wormhole.
I took the control. Now what?
Explain yourself!
[gun clicks]
PS, nobody tampered
with this gun.
It shoots fine.
[gasps]
[ZACK]
We were all working together.
[CHARCE] So, it was an
elaborate act. To trap me.
Rather, to trap your
would‐be enemy.
[KANATA]
Exactly.
[CHARCE] Well, it would
appear I was the only one
who didn't know
about the charade.
That's quite unfortunate.
Look, I'm really sorry, Charce.
For what it's worth,
I still believe in you!
Be honest with us.
This was all a mistake, right?
Say it was!
How'd you know I was the enemy?
Charce, no!
I was thinking about the time
we all ran away on Planet McPa.
If the enemy was sent
to kill all of us,
then they would need to
see it through to the end.
Meaning, the killer was whoever
entered the wormhole last.
Hah. That's all you have?
You really think, in that
confusion, you could identify
the last person
swallowed by the sphere?
Did I miss the part
where you filmed it?
[gasps]
Ah, I see.
Yeah. Aries remembered.
Okay, then.
And just what were you going
to do if you were wrong?
Please, Charce!
Say that it wasn't you!
I'm out of excuses, Aries.
Anything is fine!
I refuse to believe
you'd hurt us!
Because... no one
here's the enemy!
We're all friends, aren't we?
You were always so kind to me
and everyone else on board.
You knew about biology,
and you even cooked for us.
You were always
so supportive, Charce!
And I know that, if we
didn't have you with us,
we'd never have
made it this far!
So... tell me I'm wrong.
[CHARCE]
I'm sorry. But I had a mission.
[ARIES gasps]
Is it because we're all clones?
Did one of the originals
order you to exterminate us?
Tell me.
Yes. It's just as you suspected.
This entire trip was
nothing but a cover up.
To hide the crimes of cloning.
It was supposed to
be a simple mission.
Push the button on McPa
and send everyone to space.
I would die alongside you.
But then you went and
activated the wormhole
too early into the trip.
We were still wearing
our crust suits,
so we were able to
activate our helmets.
[CHARCE] Yes, you're right.
It was selfish.
But I wanted to do it while
I still had my suit on.
I wanted to die while
gazing into space.
‐‐How sad.
‐‐[ARIES whimpers]
But then we came upon the ship.
Not exactly part of
your plan, was it?
[CHARCE] No. After we found
the ship, and rescued Aries,
I pretended to investigate
the communicator
and disabled it.
I couldn't have
you contacting home.
Once I was done though,
I decided it would be best
to work with everyone
to get to the last planet.
And that's how we
got to this moment.
I'm quite impressed. I mean it.
You've surprised me.
I never expected
that working together
would yield such great results.
Astounding. Truly.
[ULGAR] Shut up! You
don't get to compliment
the people you intended to kill!
Come on. Tell us everything.
Why did you have to be the
one to complete this mission?
Why did it matter so much that
you'd be willing to die for it?
Because that's unacceptable!
Talk to us. Tell us who you are.
[CHARCE]
The truth is I'm a clone.
But, the difference
between you and me
is that I've always
known that about myself.
The name of my original...
...is Noah Vix.
He's the ruler of Vixia.
I am the king's clone.