[ARIES]
Team B5 camp log.
We've reached the next
leg of our journey.
We managed to avoid
a crash landing
and have arrived safely
on Planet Shummoor,
the second planet of our trip.
[QUITTERIE humming]
[ARIES]
I'm so excited. I feel dizzy!
[QUITTERIE humming]
Whoa, listen, Zack, I get it!
And I understand how you feel!
But I've gotta be honest,
your timing sucks like big time!
[ZACK] Sorry. I failed to
notice the "in use" sign.
[ZACK]
Hurry up and get dressed.
We'll be landing shortly.
[QUITTERIE grumbles]
[screams]
[BEEGO]
Aye, yeah, guys!
Right? I grabbed
the cable, said,
"Aye, yeah" and saved the day!
[QUITTERIE]
How can you be so calm
after seeing a girl naked?
[ZACK]
I've seen you naked before.
As kids! I have curves now, duh!
I was wondering.
What's "aye yeah"
supposed to mean?
[BEEGO]
Are you for real?
You gotta check out my
anime someday, Mister Luca!
[FUNICIA]
It's what Beego says when
he's receiving instructions!
‐‐Oh? That sounds cute.
‐‐[FUNICIA] Mm‐hm!
Maybe we should all say that.
Plus, it feels super
weird to be so formal
to Captain Obvious.
‐‐[KANATA] Excuse me?!
‐‐[ARIES, LUCA, FUNICIA laugh]
We're lucky. I'm
surprised we made it.
I thought for sure
we were all done for.
[LUCA]
Yeah, same.
For a minute there,
I figured the murderer
was behind everything.
But, everyone's still
here and alive.
[ARIES]
So, um.
I've been giving this
some thought, and you know,
if there is an enemy
hiding among us,
I'm positive that person
is doing their best
to try and survive
right now, too.
In that case,
it might be better to
continue working together.
And quite honestly,
we're going to need
everyone's help to survive.
What's your opinion, Captain?
[KANATA]
Same as before.
The truth is, we just
don't know, right?
The worst thing we can
do is doubt one another;
it would tear our team apart.
Once we lose control,
it's over, for real.
I forbid anyone to
look for the culprit.
Is that clear?
[ALL]
Aye, yeah!
[KANATA]
To the enemy that's hiding here,
I say, do your worst!
But seriously, which
one of you is it?
[LUCA] You literally just
said not to look for them.
[LUCA] I wonder what
0.85 G gravity is like.
[ZACK] It might be noticeable,
but only slightly.
Nothing too disorienting.
[KANATA] Oh, please. I read
about this in a manga.
Just one small jump and you
should go flying in the air!
Aw, man, I can't wait to try it!
Right, First step
on Planet Shummoor!
Let's go!
Ah...
[LUCA]
The planet's eating Kanata!
[CHARCE] Parts of the ground
seem to be soft and fluffy.
Almost like moss.
[QUITTERIE]
That's what you get for
leaping before you think. Idiot.
[KANATA]
I did that on purpose!
A spectacular gag for
a spectacular landing!
[LUCA] Okay, great.
We've definitely landed.
But this planet
seems kinda barren.
Look, there'd better
be some food here.
There's no way I'm eating,
like, moss or whatever.
My intel said this
planet has food.
But actually finding it
is the real issue here.
Well, that sucks hard.
[KANATA]
No.
The captain doesn't
get to say things suck.
I think we should
try and enjoy this.
We may be lost in space,
but that doesn't mean we
can't make the most of it!
Most unique Planet
Camp ever, right?
Let's go explore!
[STUDENTS]
Aye, yeah!
[LUCA]
You think that's edible?
Looks kinda like a wild flower.
And it's got a really
cool glow to it.
[ZACK]
Let's check it.
[FUNICIA]
Yummy!
[ARIES]
Aw, that was so cute!
[LUCA] Wait, was that
Funi's voice just now?
[ZACK]
Yes. I wanted to improve it.
[KANATA]
Great use of your time.
You sure it's okay to eat?
It said, "Yummy."
Or didn't you hear?
That doesn't have taste buds!
[screams]
[LUCA]
A‐Are you okay?
[KANATA]
Delicious!
[LUCA]
What?
[KANATA] It's like the
tastiest things in the world
got together and
had a food baby!
C'mon, you've gotta
be exaggerating.
[LUCA]
He's not!
[KANATA] I'm naming these
guys "Candy Flowers."
Let's grab as much as we can
and take 'em back
to the others.
[ARIES muffled] 'Kay! I can't
believe how delicious they are!
[KANATA] Talk or chew,
Aries, pick one!
[LUCA] Now sit down, Zack.
Come eat with us.
[ZACK]
Gee, thanks, "Mom"
[sighs] Okay. Let's hurry.
Uh‐‐ [gasps]
Check it out, guys!
[ARIES, LUCA gasp]
[LUCA]
Cool satellite!
It's beautiful.
I don't think I've ever seen
anything this incredible before.
[ARIES]
Space is amazing!
[CHARCE]
Aha! My suspicions were correct!
This cactus‐like plant
is full of water!
[BEEGO] Ta‐dah, and just
like that, we've managed
to solve our water problem!
Yeah, it's real promissing.
We should gather up a few
and bring them back
to the Astra.
[BEEGO]
But how are we gonna carry 'em?
[CHARCE] I suppose we
could always go and get
the anti‐gravity carts.
[ULGAR]
Hey, ogre chick.
We don't even know if any
of those will keep well.
Don't bother getting too
many of the same type.
Man, you really are useless.
[YUN‐HUA]
I know that.
Believe me, I know.
[QUITTERIE] Look! There's like,
a ton of different vegetables
growing around here!
Yes, they seem to
grow the thickest
around these pole‐shaped trees.
[FUNICIA]
It's kinda stinky.
[BEEGO]
Something reeks!
It's not me, I just showered!
She's right, there's an odor.
Hey, look!
A carcass.
[yelps]
[CHARCE] If I didn't know
better, I'd say the moss
on this planet feeds
off dead animals.
Ya, see? They're all around us.
Dead things everywhere.
No!
[CHARCE] Judging by the teeth,
it was an herbivore.
[QUITTERIE] Ew. Doesn't
anything gross you out?
[CHARCE gasps] Wait a second,
if there are dead herbivores...
[gasps]
...then there might
be carnivores, too!
Awesome! I wanna see!
I could study them!
Why are you so excited
about that, idiot?
What would we do if they're
like, violent or whatever?
What if they make us
into human snack packs?
[CHARCE]
Uh.
Can you stop pulling
my hair, Funi?
[GRUPPIE 4A grunting]
Monster!
Gruppie!
Aw, I think this
sweet bird thing
wants to be your
friend, Quitterie!
‐‐You want some food?
‐‐[QUITTERIE] Space creature!
‐‐Charce, do something!
‐‐[BEEGO] Good birdy thing!
‐‐Now! Please!
So... lovely!
[QUITTERIE]
I hate you so much!
Gruppie!
[FUNICIA]
He wants you to get on.
Huh?
[CHARCE]
Hiyah!
[FUNICIA]
This is so much fun!
[QUITTERIE] This is like,
an actual nightmare.
Is it?
But we're exploring
an uncharted planet
on the back of a creature
no one's ever seen before!
For me, it's a
dream come true!
[KANATA] Seems we've added
some new members to our party.
We call these guys "Gruppies"!
Yes, Funi fed them
some vegetables,
and in return,
they gave us a ride.
They're quite well‐mannered.
Repaying debts, huh?
[FUNICIA]
Mm‐hm!
I can't believe you guys
are cool with this.
[CHARCE] We found some
water, but unfortunately,
we didn't find much
in the way of food.
Don't worry about it,
'cause we got plenty of grub!
Check it!
Smells like death.
Did you fart, Quitterie?
[QUITTERIE]
Die!
You're gonna smell like death
if you don't shut up!
I have never passed
gas, got that?
Um, that's impossible.
[QUITTERIE] Congratulations
on being my first ever
drop‐kick, Captain Insensitive!
Oh, man. Thanks, 0.85 G gravity.
That did send me flyin'.
What is this dried up
plant on your shoulder?
Huh?
This must be what
you were smelling.
[FUNICIA]
Disgusting!
[ZACK]
Inedible. All of it.
It seems that this
vegetation spoils
at an unnaturally fast rate.
It's not suitable for
long‐term storage.
[KANATA]
Well, that sucks hard.
[ZACK] These are the only plants
we gathered that are both
edible and fit for storing.
The Gruppies were also tested.
It turns out they aren't
an edible source either.
[FUNICIA]
Don't eat our friends!
[KANATA] How much food
do we have on board?
There's three days' worth.
Possibly five, if we
very strictly ration it.
Uh...
Well, hey!
We managed to find some
edible plants, didn't we?
I'm sure we'll find some
animals we can eat, too!
Are ya with me?
‐‐[stomach growls]
‐‐[ARIES] Huh?
[KANATA]
I wasn't asking your stomach!
Look.
This planet might just be
a bust; maybe it's better
to grab whatever food
we can and move on.
The calculation is
based on the minimums.
And if we leave with less than
that, we won't make it far.
If we run out of food in space,
then we'll be done for.
[QUITTERIE] I think you just
want an excuse to stay here
so you can keep studying
dead animals and stuff!
‐‐[ARIES] Let's all calm down.
‐‐Kanata?
[KANATA] Right. We're not
leaving this planet
until we have our target amount.
Let's cut our meals
by 30 percent.
And conserve water. That
means no bathing or laundry.
Starting now, because I'm kinda,
sorta washing my dirty
clothes as we speak.
[LUCA]
How is that fair?
Crazy.
I guess this trip won't
be so easy after all.
Can we get through this
just by conserving food?
I mean, Yun‐hua looks like
she needs to eat a ton!
[gasps]
[KANATA]
Dude! Luca!
[LUCA] Sorry! I think I'm
gonna hit the hay early.
‐‐[QUITTERIE] Same, I'm so beat.
‐‐[stomach growls]
[KANATA] Your stomach
sure is vocal today.
[ARIES laughs]
[ARIES panting]
[KANATA] Man. Hurry up
and dry, you stupid jacket.
[ARIES]
Kanata!
Huh?
It's about Yun‐hua!
[KANATA]
"I will stay on this planet.
Please leave me here"?
What, she ran away?
[KANATA]
Yun‐hua...
Quitterie, stay with the ship!
[QUITTERIE]
You got it!
Hello, Yun‐hua!
Are you there?
Where are you, Yun‐hua?
This is all because I said
those mean things to her, huh?
[ULGAR]
I said some mean things, too.
[LUCA]
Like what?!
[ULGAR]
Ogre chick.
[LUCA]
What?!
That's terrible, maybe
you're why she ran off!
[ULGAR] Nah, I doubt it.
It's prob'ly your fault.
[KANATA panting]
I mean, Yun‐hua looks like
she needs to eat a ton!
[KANATA] Is this her idea
of a sacrifice? That idiot!
[KANATA]
Yun‐hua!
[gasps]
[YUN‐HUA yelps]
[inhales]
[YUN‐HUA] ♪ I'm not afraid,
no. I'm not afraid. ♪
♪ The forest animals
are all my friends. ♪
[WEI]
The lead role in the class play?
[YUNHUA]
Uh‐huh! The teacher chose me!
Is that so? You'd be singing?
[YUN‐HUA]
Yeah.
[WEI sighs] I told them not
to let you do things like that.
Quit the play.
Huh?
[WEI] I'll speak to
the teacher for you.
You can't handle this.
You'll just fail and
cause everyone trouble.
Do something that
won't draw attention.
[CHILDREN] ♪ I'm not afraid,
no, I'm not afraid. ♪
♪ The forest animals
are all my friends. ♪
[KANATA]
Yun‐hua!
[gasps]
[KANATA panting]
[KANATA]
Wait!
Come on!
[KANATA] You can't outrun
me! I've got you now!
[gasps]
[KANATA]
I don't got you!
Look, I'll stay over here,
and we can chat via
helmet comm, okay?
[KANATA] Oh, you left
your glasses on the ship.
[YUN‐HUA] I don't need
them. They're not...
[KANATA]
...not prescription.
[gasps]
[KANATA]
Aries was the one who noticed.
[FUNICIA]
Kanata, here.
Will Yun‐hua be able
to see without them?
[ARIES]
I think so.
They're fake. Those
are just for looks.
[KANATA]
You probably think no one
pays attention to you, right?
But we're your friends.
We've got your back.
Let me guess, the glasses
are there to keep
your bangs out of your eyes.
And the bangs are there
to hide your face.
I don't want to draw
attention to myself.
I'm so big,
but I'm also useless.
Sure, you're tall, but that
doesn't make you useless.
But I can't do
anything to help out.
Everyone else on board
has a special talent.
But I'm worthless. Which hurts.
[KANATA] Hey, you don't
need a flashy talent.
And it doesn't mean that
we don't need your help.
[YUN‐HUA]
I'm sorry. I...
I don't want to fail
and draw attention,
and I don't want to succeed
and draw attention.
If you can't do anything right,
then don't draw
attention to yourself.
[YUN‐HUA] That's just
how my mother raised me.
No matter what, I'm not
allowed to stand out.
What? For real? But...
I wish... I were invisible.
The wind's getting stronger.
Oh. Here come Zack and Funi.
Still no luck?
Not yet.
Maybe we should head back
to the ship and regroup.
With the temperature dropping,
we should probably
wear our crust suits.
[rumbling]
[ARIES]
Charce... What's that?
Weird.
[CHARCE] Huh. Interesting. It's
like it's spreading its seeds.
Or are they spores?
The Pole Trees might be
like ferns in that regard.
[CHARCE]
Aries?
[CHARCE gasps]
[CHARCE]
Everyone. Don't breathe.
The spores are poison.
[CHARCE]
That's it.
I'm a fool for not
realizing sooner.
With so many poisonous plants,
the dominant species on
this planet aren't animals...
...but fungi.
Man, it sure got windy.
[GRUPPIE 4C groans]
[KANATA gasps]
What's the matter, big guy?
Are ya hungry?
[KANATA]
Yun‐hua.
[YUN‐HUA]
Here.
I found this flower thing
by one of the trees earlier.
Maybe it'll like it.
[laughs]
Good, you seem to
be feeling better.
Gruppie!
Number seven on my
survival tip list.
Eat and you'll feel
better! Well then?
Wanna go back and have lunch?
[ringing]
Yo, what's up?
[CHARCE weakly]
Kanata.
[KANATA gasps]
Charce? What's going on?
[CHARCE] Thank goodness.
You're wearing your helmet.
Come to the location
I send you.
Please hurry.
Keep your helmet on, Kanata.
[KANATA]
Quitterie, help me!
[QUITTERIE]
Wait, them, too?
Luca and Ulgar came back
in bad shape, earlier!
It was the Pole Trees.
They release spores.
Spores which are highly
poisonous when inhaled.
[panting]
The symptoms are a high fever,
coughing, and soreness.
Okay, can you cure them?
I've never seen this before now,
so why are you asking me?
Because you have to know!
[KANATA]
You're the ship's doctor,
and the best hope
that they have.
[QUITTERIE]
I'll do what I can.
I'm putting everyone
on the bridge.
Get some mattresses.
Okay!
I need you, 'kay?
We can talk later.
[KANATA]
The trees are mushrooms?
They are, and able
to spread poison
with their spores.
I could be wrong, but here's
what I think happens.
The fungi and plants
all work together.
Let's say a fungus has a
symbiotic relationship a plant.
Then it wouldn't be unusual
for that fungus to have a poison
that actively kills animals.
The moss would
then grow on top
of the animal's carcass,
photosynthesizing energy
for the mushroom to grow.
Making those mushrooms
the dominant species
of this planet.
They're not getting any better!
We just don't have the
right supplies on board.
[KANATA]
There's gotta be something.
Like a balance in the
ecosystem or whatever.
Or else all these
crazy mushrooms
would kill everything off.
You may be right.
It's possible that the
plants and fungi have
some sort of method
to control how many
animals they take down.
[QUITTERIE]
What do you mean, Charce?
[CHARCE] There could be
an antidote or something.
Like a medicinal mushroom
that could cure us.
[gasps] Kanata!
Do you remember the thing
we fed the Gruppie?
Could it be that was actually
a medicinal mushroom?
[KANATA gasps]
[KANATA panting]
[KANATA] Yes! It's the only
thing that makes sense!
Oh, but now that
I think about it,
it was the only
one around there.
[KANATA gasps]
[KANATA grunts]
[KANATA]
At least we know there's a cure.
I promise I'll find some.
[ZACK]
Hey. Check the roots.
Of the Pole Trees?
That's right.
They need to have the
carcasses near them,
so they have to lure
the animals there.
The antidote plant
could serve as the bait.
[KANATA]
I get it!
[ZACK] The sick animals go to
the Pole Trees to get medicine,
and if they manage to
find it, they're cured.
And if they don't find it,
then they die right there
at the base of the tree.
That's how it does it.
How it controls which animals
live and which ones die.
[KANATA panting]
[gasps] No!
C'mon, where the heck are they?
Why aren't there
any good mushrooms?
Um, hey! You're burning up!
Are you poisoned, too?
I don't know how to
help them. What do I do?
I was only able to
make them comfortable.
That's it, so...
All we can do now
is wait for Kanata.
[KANATA]
These footprints are fresh,
but there aren't
any new carcasses.
Does that mean that
all the mushrooms
were eaten already?
No.
Maybe it won't give them to me
because it knows I'm not sick.
[KANATA] I really hate that
word. Nothing is hopeless, 'kay?
[KANATA] There's no way
you wanna be invisible!
[gasps]
There must be something you
wanna do with your life!
[inhales]
[singing in japanese]
[CHARCE]
Is someone... singing?
[KANATA] Seriously?! Your dream
is to become a singer?
[YUN‐HUA]
You don't have to yell.
My mother told me
that I was not allowed
to tell anybody.
And to not sing
in front of others.
[YUN‐HUA]
But...
I still love hearing
my mother sing.
[YUN‐HUA]
And I love singing.
Because...
[YUNHUA] ...I've always found
it to be very soothing.
[GRUPPIE 4C] Gruppie!
[ARIES]
Team B5 Camp Log.
After an adventure‐filled day,
Kanata brought back
the medicinal mushrooms
we needed to live,
thus saving all of our lives.
[ARIES]
You did really well. Good job.