So I was running a little
behind on fixing her bike.
I even felt kinda bad keeping
them stranded here so long.
That was 'til that broad
totally screwed me over.
She calls me, wakes me up
before dawn, and tells me
to get my ass to the hotel
and bring her chopper.
Not only doesn't she pay me
a single talgo--But then
she just guns her bike,
tearin' the bridge all to hell
with me standing on it!
And since she was my customer,
they're sticking me
with the bill
for the bridge repairs.
I mean, have you ever heard
of anything so ridiculous?
Excuse me.
Inspector.
Think we finally got
a line on Malandro.
According to the front desk,
she was on her way to Osso.
Osso?
Several witnesses overheard
her say she wants to meet up
with Satoshi Batista.
This trip's been
a real bitch.
Ma'am?
Like that overpriced
Chinese place.
After eating in that dump
for three days straight,
we only got one word
outta that fat fuck.
"Hatchet."
You're a hot mess, honey.
Then back to Vermelha,
something I swore I'd never do,
so those two queens
could shit-talk me.
Here you go.
And of course
Old Lady Zélia shook me down
while giving
nothing in return.
All we had to show
for that detour--
--was a pound and
a half of stringy beef.
And even that's gone now.
Play me a song, pops.
Somethin' nice n' funky.
Yo, Hatchin, can you--
Why'd you run off
on your own like that?
I was thirsty, so I'm getting
some juice, if you don't mind.
Hey, watch the attitude.
Knock it off!
Listen, Hatchin.
I don't wanna hear
anything you have to say!
Stop it!
Hey, why are you so
pissed off all of a sudden?
If you don't tell me,
how am I s'posed to--
Now you wanna
know why I'm mad?
'Cause it's not
all of a sudden!
Wha'd I do?
You destroy
everything in your path!
You run off without
paying for stuff!
You--
What are you lookin' at?
Seriously, what in the
world is wrong with you?
I've seen you make too many
people cry with the way you act.
Like just the other day,
when you threatened that poor,
old mechanic.
I really hated that.
That's how grown-ups,
y'know, negotiate.
What, with a wrench
in their hand?
I can't stand it anymore!
Any of it!
Sorry for the wait.
Suit yourself.
Goin' out for a bit.
I'll try not to stay out
too late, though.
Don't even think about
wandering off on your own!
Fuck!
Yo, yo!
I brought over
the creamy cocoa!
'Ey, homes.
What's wrong
with this machine?
Motherfucker's busted!
I ain't won
jack shit all night!
I don't know what to tell you.
That so?
You do know who I am,
don't you?
Yes, of course,
Mister Satoshi.
I know.
Then you also know
I'm the goddamn president
of Monstro Preto.
And it's a fucking bad idea
to make me angry.
So clean out your ear-holes,
you dumbass hick
and listen real careful.
You're gonna go get two thousand
arcas and bring it to me now.
That's everything I lost
and what I shoulda won.
Otherwise, this unpleasant
motherfucker's thunder-stick
is gonna shoot a huge
load of fire up your ass.
I'll go get you your money!
All right, son!
I got a question for ya.
Satoshi Batista.
You seen him around here?
I heard rumors he was
somewhere in the city.
Sorry, ma'am,
I can't help you.
Yeah, figures.
Keep it holstered!
Evenin', Cue-ball.
Mister Shinsuke?
What's the matter, Pogo?
No need to be so nervous.
What brings uh--What
brings you here?
Not that I'm not happy
to see you, of course.
See, thing is.
Talkin' on the phone
was gettin' us nowhere.
And this whole matter's
completely unacceptable
ta our Satoshi.
You can see why, right?
We ain't been gettin'
our cut from you Presa guys.
But now--
Here's this Satoshi and
you pay up like a bitch.
That's a little, I dunno, odd.
Sorry, don't mind us.
Dig in, I'll be leaving soon.
So I thought, maybe I should
drop in, meet this fella.
N' word on the street
is you're putting him up.
Spill it, Colonel Kurtz.
Where is this imposter?
You're bad.
I know.
Please, don't do this,
Mister Satoshi!
What is this?
You mistake me for a big,
brown, cuddly, teddy bear?
Who is it makes this crap-hole
bar of yours possible?
You, Mister Satoshi! You do!
You're damn straight.
So no more fuckin' excuses.
Pay what you owe or
I'll crush your bolas.
What'll it be, homie?
Want me to mash on
this pedal and play us
a thumping samba beat?
Huh?
I'll pay you!
Whatever you want!
Now we're talking, meu mano.
I'm so touched by
your change of heart,
I can barely
hold back the tears.
Y'have any idea
what time it is, girl?
Let go!
--Why, you little--
--Don't hit me!
Jeez you're so quick
to turn violent.
You haven't even
let me talk yet!
I happened across a guy named
Satoshi, and I followed him.
Satoshi huh?
Where'd you follow him?
A hotel.
Which one?
Estrela.
Every time we open
our mouths, we argue.
I've been thinking.
Maybe we just shouldn't
be together anymore.
I don't even want to look
at your face, Michiko.
But I promised that
I would protect you.
It's okay.
You don't have
to keep that one.
Hey, Pogo!
I thought you said
this was supposed to be
a four-star joint.
So how come the security
here is zero-star?
I mean, some bitch-ass prowler
just waltzed on in here
like it was nothing.
Yo!
Is your ass asleep?
Say something,
for fuck's sake!
I don't have that luxury.
I can't sleep like this!
You gonna upgrade me
to your finest suite.
Ya feel me?
And Pogo, get some armed
escorts down here for us.
Yeah.
I'mma let you pick up
the tab for that shit, too.
Where the hell
those escorts at, huh?
That Pogo fool
ain't pickin' up.
For real?
I kick his ass!
Gimme that!
Fat bastard!
Lemme have it.
Oh.
Pogo, you dumbass.
That what you thought
I meant by escort?
Not that I'm complaining.
Where's Satoshi Batista?
Right here.
Satoshi, Prez of the Slums, but
you can just call me "Daddy."
You ain't foolin'
no one, wannabe.
Whoa, that's a little
cold, don't you think?
How 'bout I warm you up some?
Make a little
friction together?
Maybe work up a sweat?
Come on, lemme get you
all hot and bothered.
Bad move.
You're up next, big boy.
You can call me
"Jesus H. Magnificent"!
Wanna take a swing
at my divine jaw?
Oh, babe.
Looks like you just made me
spill my love juice--
Baby, don't go!
I think I'm in love wit'chu!
Move the hand,
or I clobber you.
Yeah, I like it rough!
For real.
When you kicked
me in the balls,
you gave my heart
a reach-around.
You got fuckin' issues.
I'll come with you!
Yo, boys, grab us a cab!
Like, three seconds ago!
I ain't leaving.
What happened to him?
Is that blood?
Marque?
Hey!
Stay here.
My boy.
Well, good morning,
"Mister President".
Who the fuck is this?
You know who we are.
We're known as the
Black Monster, Monstro Preto.
And we got the
hotel surrounded.
Yo, Davi, what
was that all about?
It's all over!
We are so screwed!
Don't hang up on me.
I got more to say to you.
Hello there, Shinsuke.
Whozzis?
Oh come on.
You forget my voice already?
Aw, holy shit!
I hear you did
a number in Vermelha.
What's shakin'?
I came to see Satoshi.
Sucks to be you!
Yeah.
Anyway, would you mind putting
"o presidente" on for me?
Think he's done.
So anyway, Shinsuke.
You gonna let me
see your real boss?
Damn girl, I ain't
no fuckin' charity!
You want cash?
I gots cash.
Naw, what I want
is to play a game.
You fuckin' with me or what?
You know the kinda
person I am, right?
Just come on down here
and talk to me.
Oh, I don't think
I wanna do that.
Where's the fun?
If that's how you're gonna be
guess I got no choice
but to force you to talk.
Hey, bitch, that's my bag!
Get a new one!
Hey I only said I was Satoshi!
Never said Satoshi Batista!
We got some muscle, so we
went ahead and told people
we were Monstro Preto.
Big fucking deal!
We lived up to
the reputation.
Didn't we?
Say something,
goddamn it!
You got no clue who you picked
a fight with here, do you?
This guy is a monster.
Fo' real.
What'll it be?
I'll play your damn game.
Yeah?
In exchange, you agree
to leave this fake Satoshi
and what's left of
his crew here alone.
I'll make sure they give back
all the money they've taken.
Also.
I'm planning to win
this hands down.
When I do, I see Satoshi.
Those are my terms.
Sure thing!
But the fakers
gotta play too.
That's not what--
You said you're gonna
win hands down, right?
If you do, I let the
rest of 'em go free
and I'll let you see
your darling Satoshi.
That's not a problem is it?
--Ya got a deal.
--Great.
Lemme 'splain the rules.
You're gonna come see me.
And you're gonna ride the
trolleys I'm about to give you.
Make it here in one piece,
and we'll call it a win.
I call this--
"The Nonstop Transfer Game!"
O' course, you ain't gonna
know where the
trolleys're comin' from.
And if you miss a train,
it's game over.
Yeah, we'll shoot you
without a second thought.
But if you outrun us--
--and get back on track?
We'll let it slide.
'Kay, now, here's your route.
I'm only tellin' you once,
so remember it--
Get the hell on with it!
Don't rush me.
Now, listen up.
The trolley bound for
the obelisk is runnin' by
you right now, ain't it?
Board it, then transfer to the
westbound Parque Triângulo.
From there, take the
Salão line, got it?
Ride that for a while, then hop
on the Santa Estrela bound--
Oh, wait, no, I messed that up.
Fuck you!
Mercado Central, right.
Get on that one then
jump to the Santa Estrela.
Parque Triângulo, "PT".
Salão, "S".
Mercadoo-something, "MS"?
Santa Es, "SE".
Next comes the Truta line,
followed by the Centro,
and after that, the Rua Nova.
And, uh, that's pretty much it.
..."C".
..."RN".
Just transfer in
exactly that order,
then at six o'clock
sharp, hop off.
When you do, you'll find out
where your final transfer's at.
Hey, are you listening?
Shut up!
'Kay, that's it for now.
I'll keep the guys out
front from shooting
for the next
five minutes or so.
Hotel Ilha Solitária,
how can I help you?
I have a message
for room three oh three.
A promise is a promise.
I'll be back.
Wait for me.
That's it!
Get on!
Yo!
Wait up!
Next, "PT."
Look!
Isn't that the Parque?
Shit!
"SE".
What'd that stand for?
Yo!
São Emar!
That has to be it.
Shit!
Ah! Son of a--!
What the hell
did we do wrong?
"SE."
Damn it, took the wrong one!
That's our trolley!
Hop on!
What?
Naw, y'never leave
a man behind!
Suit yourself.
Come on!
But what about Andréa?
Dude!
Hey come on you pricks!
Where you guys goin'?
You can't leave me
here to die!
"T"!
Truta!
Jump!
Hey!
Davi.
This is all 'cause of you!
This is all 'cause
of your louco-ass idea!
Well, fuck you and your
"Black Monster" bullshit!
Get us outta this mess!
Rocco.
If we don't go now,
they shoot our asses!
Why we gotta play
their game, man?
Dammit, Davi, just get us
outta this, okay?
Asshole!
What's up next?
"C"!
"C".
And after that?
Not sure.
Come on, lady.
You better remember.
Damn.
Which one?
Which "C" is it?
Damn it!
Left!
Take the left!
Yo.
'Ey, you hear me?
Almost time.
This the right place?
We sure about that?
Yeah.
So then where's our clue at?
Congratulations, Michi!
Just keep walkin' straight
on down the tracks.
I'll be waitin' right here
for you, promise.
See you soon.
Real soon.
Stay on your feet!
You said--
Hey, I'm a man of my word.
So here--You wanna
see him, right?
And you--
Fly!
Be free!
Yo, Atsuko.
It's me.
Satoshi.
Terra, huh?
Got it.
Ricardo, change of plans.
We're going to Terra.
Huh?
What about Osso?
Don't make me repeat myself.
I said Terra.