Hands behind your head,
step away from the bars!
Hey, that's Number
Four-Oh-Three, ain't it?
Yeah, probably.
Little wager?
Like on how far
the bitch gets?
The only way out from there is
through all of the ductwork.
She'll never friggin' make it.
How much?
'Cause I'm thinking,
knowing her,
she's for sure gonna make it.
For sure.
Hey, pigs!
If you're gonna
chase my ass down,
I hope you like
what's comin' to ya!
Who wants the
first bullet up the ass?!
Number Four-Oh-Three!
Michiko Malandro!
Give yourself up now!
Or we will shoot you
where you stand!
March Tenth, sunny.
Up at 6 today,
first one up.
Authorities have identified
the woman who broke out
of the high-security and
purportedly escape-proof
Diamandra Special Penitentiary
early yesterday morning.
Her name is Michiko Malandro.
Under the cover of last night's
storm, she has disappeared,
and as of yet, there have been
no reported sightings of her.
Malandro should be considered
armed and extremely dangerous.
Which, as the outsider
in the house, I always am.
I make breakfast, too.
Omelets, easy on the salt.
A bit of shell fell in.
And I might've
burned them a little.
Good morning everyone.
Father Pedro,
and his wife, Joana.
My kinda-sorta parents.
Oh, dear.
Were you hiding this?
Really?
Hana, we do not raise
our children to cover up
their failures.
And with that, he made me
cook the omelets again.
And clean up.
My sister.
My foster sister, Maria.
The name is way too
pretty for her.
The younger brother, Gabriel.
That's us, the members of the
Belembauza Yamada family.
My name is Hana, and this is
how my days usually start.
Bless us, O Lord,
and, these thy gifts.
Which we are about to receive
from thy bounty, amen.
And pretty much how they end.
Hang in there.
Please don't do that.
Hey, Hankie!
Below here is the ocean.
So right now,
you're underwater!
Pick it up.
You can't walk in water!
Swim for it!
I said swim!
Why am I doing this?
How can you
breathe in the ocean!
Heads up!
What is the meaning of this?
Can you explain why this
dark stain is here?
It was, the mop bucket.
I spilled it.
Do you know how much
this is going to cost?
Getting away with things
just because you're a child
doesn't fly around
here, young lady.
Towels are for wiping, stupid.
Not for wearing.
Hey, wait!
Stop it!
What are you holding on for?
Just let it go!
No!
This kind of thing
goes on, day in and day out.
Fill up the bag,
and make it snappy.
Otherwise, I open fire
and splatter blood
all over this place!
March Fifteenth.
Today, someone from the city
is coming to check on me.
But he never really does.
He just drops off
the money and leaves.
That's all it ever is.
Hana, I want for you
to have these.
Thank you very much.
Hana, do you remember
the news this morning?
Around here, children in
your situation are forced
to make their living by
either selling their bodies,
or selling what's inside them.
But you know who it was who
saved you from that fate, right?
Yes.
Who was it?
It was, God.
In other words?
It was you, Father.
"Thou shalt not avenge, but
love thy neighbor as thyself."
He just bought me off.
Using Maria's hand-me-downs.
He totally just bought me off.
An update now,
on the bank robbery
that occurred in Paraí-town.
Authorities believe it is
highly likely that the culprit
is Michiko Malandro...
This is a fine piece,
very nice.
It must've set
you back a bit.
Oh my goodness, no.
It was a gift from one of the
flock, so the price was right.
Free is always good!
Here you are.
It's nice to see you again.
You look like you're
doing all right, huh?
Yes sir.
Good to hear.
Ah, thanks.
Are you familiar with
the "Devotee of the Year"?
Sorry, I can't say that I am.
"Dee-vo-tee"?
That's it, right up there.
It's only given to those
who have performed
outstanding deeds...
And my husband was fortunate
enough to be chosen!
Uh-Huh!
Interesting.
That's quite
a prize you got there.
There was a young man
in the community;
Gonzales was his name,
truly rotten to the core.
But one sermon from Pedro
turned him right around!
Even now, he is an upstanding
member of the flock.
That's impressive!
That's a lie.
The thing about Gonzales,
is he only changed because
of the bullet that was
lodged in his head.
Gonzales, the Lord God loves
you and he forgives you
for all of your transgressions.
Ah, what an adorable kitty.
Does she belong to you?
Yes, well, Maria took
the poor thing in.
No!
I did!
Sorry dear, is that right?
They just adore
looking after her.
Branco just pooped.
Do something about it.
Would you mind taking care
of Branco for me?
I've been feeling horribly
lightheaded all day.
So, who's on
Branco duty today?
It's my turn.
Never increases, does it?
Christ sakes!
How much do they think it costs
to raise a child these days?
Geez!
Get off!
Ugh, that dirty fleabag!
Chore time!
Go get rid of this for me!
We clear?
Mom, you seen Branco?
No, not all morning,
now that you mention it.
I haven't seen her
since last night.
Hana, have you seen her?
No, sorry.
Well, I find
that hard to believe.
After all, I saw you
take her outside last night.
Where did you take her?
Hey!
Where did you take Branco?!
C'mon!
Giddy-up!
You suck at this!
You have to go faster!
What do we have here?
Look, it's Branco Two.
This Branco looks even filthier
than the first one was.
Ew!
You're gross!
Hang on, Gabe.
I know what we should do.
Branco means
"white," doesn't it?
She's got to be clean.
Whoa there, girl!
Aah!
I said "whoa"!
Not so fast!
Hey! Stop moving!
Yeah!
Rodeo time, h-yah!
Now, just hold still
for a sec!
That hurt!
Owwww!
Apologize, right now!
I told you to apologize!
For what?
I didn't do,
I didn't do anything!
Really, you think you
can challenge me now?
Alright then!
If that's the case, get out!
We just don't need you here.
And no one cares
about you anyway.
I've had it!
I've put up with
this for too long!
You treat me
like dirt every day,
and you don't care
what that does to me!
Do you even know I'm a person?
Look at me!
Look me right in the face!
Good, now remember it!
What the heck am I
supposed to do now?
I can't go back.
It was too scary to go
home alone, so I decided
to bring Branco back with me.
Someone from down that road,
is going to come for me.
Sorry about the wait, Hana.
I came to get you.
Yeah, that'll never happen.
This the Belem-something
Yamada's?
Yes.
May I ask who's calling?
Got a kid named Hana?
I'll be there tomorrow,
get her ready.
I'm sorry, but who
is this exactly?
Who am I?
I'm her mother.
Apparently, Hana's mother
is coming tomorrow.
Her mother is dead,
isn't she?
Well, that's what
I'd always heard.
So what does this mean?
Got me.
Of course.
Kidnapping.
Clearly someone
jealous of my position.
Yeah, must be.
What are they after?
Money?
Or do they just wanna stick
it to me, by cutting off
our child support?
Go and fetch my shotgun.
I'm gonna get these
sons of bitches first.
Amen.
Dig in everyone.
Go hide Hana somewhere safe.
Hey!
Yeah you, four-eyes.
Look at me.
Is your name Hana?
Then it's you.
She's just staring at me,
mouth hanging open.
Not ladylike at all.
C'mon, Hana.
Or you gonna
sit there all day?
"Someone is going
to come for me".
It's what I'd wished for,
all this time.
On the morning of March
Seventeenth, that person came.
The only problem.
I have no idea who she is!