What you're seeing now is
the prison van transporting
the defendant, Michiko
Malandro, accused of repeated,
vicious attacks against
sites connected with
the crime syndicate
known as "Fantasma".
Though she has fervently
denied all allegations,
work by state investigators has
brought other serious crimes
to light, and she is
being incarcerated today
at Diamandra Penitentiary.
Many viewers will recognize
the name Diamandra,
the remote prison where
the nation's most heinous
offenders are detained.
Her only chance of freedom now
might very well be her death.
The capture of Malandro
by Officer Atsuko Jackson...
Michiko.
Hope you suffer good.
403, you got a visitor.
Prison garb suits you.
You look good.
The brass promoted me
up to Sergeant.
Are you impressed?
Ooh.
"Sergeant Jambo" now!
Jam--?
Yeah!
You can't escape.
Face the facts.
Today marks my third attempt.
And each time I get farther.
This man who ran off.
You miss him that much?
It's like a sickness.
You're a slave to the sex.
Atsuko.
When we were kids I'd beat your
ass and you'd beg me to stop,
but the whole time you'd have
this dreamy look in your eyes.
Always creep me out.
You're the sick one.
Come here and I'll
give you what you want.
Oh, you like to pull hair now,
does that start you up?
You bitch!
Now tell me again
who ran away from who, huh?
Get off me!
You want some too?
Atsuko, you pussy!
Come here!
Fight me one on one!
Ina Telles, Pinício Yazik, Elena
Yogi, and Jucelino Vilalão.
All have been identified as
passengers in the horrific
bus explosion that rocked
São João earlier today.
While authorities
refuse to speculate
on what caused the blast
or if foul play is suspected,
Hiroshi Morenos, notorious
member of the outlaw gang
"Preto Monstro," was also
confirmed dead at the scene.
What did he just say?
What did he say?
Hey!
Armed robbery
in progress in Lenteelia.
Suspect identifies herself
as Michiko Malandro.
She's taken customers
hostage and holed up inside.
Standoff approaching one hour.
Identity not yet confirmed,
but should be considered
extremely dangerous.
This is the special unit,
proceeding to scene now.
ETA 30 minutes.
Quit your whining
or I'll shoot you next!
You've put on weight since
I saw you last, Michiko.
Fun's over, Miss Malandro.
Time to go back to Diamandra.
I don't deserve that hellhole.
I'm not really Michiko.
Yeah, no shit, tubby.
But you fucked up.
You made the mistake
of getting my hopes up.
Using her name?
You're gonna regret
that for years.
Hana Belembauza Yamada.
Look at her, Michiko.
Recognize those features?
Bet you do.
So um.
Yeah?
Could you tell me who you are?
Who am I?
My name's Michiko Malandro.
Well yeah, you
told me that much.
Then why the hell
did you ask me?
I know your name.
But I don't know
anything else.
I don't know why you
took me, for instance.
I don't even know
where I'm walking to.
Hey, hold up!
Break time.
It's fucking hot.
I know your old man pretty
well, I can tell you that.
Who, Father Pedro?
Who the hell's he?
Oh, you mean my real father.
Who is he, exactly?
That's the million-dollar
question, isn't it?
Name's Hiroshi.
Hiroshi Morenos.
Now you say it.
Hiroshi...
Morenos, is it?
Yeah even his name
sounds handsome.
Don't it?
He was one hell of a man.
Cool as a glacier.
And nice, too.
Made me fall for him
with one look.
Yeah me, can you picture that?
He was that good.
Then he left,
without a word.
Not even a half-assed goodbye.
Then he died.
Really?
Yeah, so, I was thinking
I'd go pay him a visit.
Where is he?
You know something, right?
What?
But, Isn't he dead?
Yeah.
A bus blew up.
So he is dead?
Yeah.
So how can you
pay him a visit?
Do you mean his grave?
Or do you wanna die too?
Or?
Stupid!
Just wait 'til
I finished talking, okay!
Okay, but you
did stop talking.
It was all over the news.
Hiroshi died in a bus
explosion eleven years ago.
Now tell me how old you are.
I'm nine years old.
But my birthday is next month.
So tell me this, Hana.
What's eleven minus nine?
Two.
That's right, hold on!
You're not exactly
a math whiz, are you?
Shut your mouth!
I know what I'm
talking about here.
Don't make me sound stupid.
Lift up your skirt.
And why would I do that?
To show it!
You do have one, right?
No, I don't.
--Show me then!
--I will not!
Oh come on!
No!
I don't show
anyone my bellybutton.
Real life of the party.
You ain't nothing
like your dad.
Hey, look at me
when I'm talking to you!
What do you mean
you're all out?
I mean the tanks
are empty, what else?
Then why the hell
are you open?
You telling me
you don't have one drop?
A drop or two, sure.
That should get your bike going
about fifteen, twenty more feet.
There's a town down the road.
More of a village, really.
Thing is, it's
a ways from here.
But they'll have gas
at their market.
You'll pay out the nose,
but it's your best bet.
Ladrão's the name.
How far down the road?
On foot, uhhh.
Maybe like, three hours
if you're lucky.
Ain't you gonna
drink that, Hana?
Um.
What?
Can you not call me Hana?
That's your name, right?
Yeah, but I hate it.
And I saw what you did, too.
You just stole these sodas.
Yeah so?
Who cares?
I bet that man does.
He was watching you.
Nice, who's gonna
clean that up?
I'll get it.
If you show me
your damn stomach.
Hey, get back here,
Ha--um, chin?
Chin?
Let's go.
And when you heard the
woman on the bike outside,
what'd you do?
I got up from the table
and waited in here,
so I could protect my family.
And that was when she came
crashing in through the window.
So you then fired your shotgun
from the living room?
Yes.
Four rounds?
Lady, are you a cop, too?
Uh-huh.
You in charge?
Kind of.
Inspector, we just got
a report that a woman
matching the description
of Michiko Malandro
was spotted at a gas
station near Ladrão.
The witness says
a young girl was with her.
All right, we're done here!
I remember those eyes.
Oh yeah.
Hiroshi used to stare
at me in the same way.
Usually it was right
before grabbing my tits.
You keep your ears
way cleaner than him.
But the resemblance.
Your nose is
all wrong, though.
And your chin too.
It doesn't look
anything like his did.
In fact, it's kinda
pissing me off.
Who'd ya inherit
those from, huh?
I don't know.
You sure this isn't
some kind of mistake?
You calling me stupid again?
No, never mind, sorry.
That's the little girl
who saved me.
I can't tell you how many days
I've stared at that face.
She's Hiroshi's
daughter for sure.
Yeah, but.
What if that's not?
What if there's
no tattoo on my stomach?
What would you do then?
I'd ditch your ass.
I can't babysit
some stranger's kid.
Not my style.
Breaking news.
We now have a suspect in this
morning's appalling kidnapping
at the rectory
of São Pedro Church,
on the outskirts of Laranja.
The religious family's
soon-to-be ten year-old
daughter, Hana Belembauza
Yamada, was abducted
after a motorcycle
crashed into the home.
Authorities are now saying
the culprit is escaped felon
Michiko Malandro.
Police describe a chaotic
scene at the humble parish,
as shotgun shells
and broken glass...
I'll do anything for
the girl with that ink.
Made a promise.
So, do you have it?
Sorry, I don't.
...vow a quick resolution
to this heinous crime.
While Milandro's motivations
are not yet clear,
experts say it's most likely
a kidnapping for ransom.
Gimme a sec.
Yeah, I'm telling you, she
was just here with the girl.
No they left a minute ago.
Thanks.
Nothing to worry about kid.
We're old friends.
Sorry to spoil
your joyride pal.
Still obsessed with me, huh?
Wow!
You get taller, Jambo,
or is it the heels?
Don't call me Jambo,
you dirty bitch!
Sorry, who's the dirty one?
Shouldn't use that word
knowing all the filth
rattling around your head.
You ever get that counseling?
Funny, the lifelong
screw-up thinks I'm crazy.
Now that's the pot
calling the kettle black
if I've ever seen it.
Pot's fine, kettle-face.
I'm sparkling next to you.
You're about the filthiest
bitch I've ever met.
I'm gonna put
a bullet in your head!
You're embarrassing yourself!
Let it go already!
Sinner!
Let the girl go and
accept your punishment!
Who's the Padre?
He looks kinda familiar.
Have we met before?
Hana!
Get over here!
What about my child support?
After everything
I did for you!
You want to saddle me
with debt?
This is how you thank our
family for giving you a home?
It's all right, look at me.
I believe in you, Hatchin.
So you believe in me.
The devil sent you to test me,
but you won't succeed!
God will have the last word!
Hey Michiko.
Little baby Michiko,
pinching off her poo.
Damn you!
Hey Atsuko.
What?
You know ending it this quick
won't be any fun, right?
Lean in for a sec, you don't
want your men to hear this.
Come on.
It's the words you
been waiting for.
Back off, boys.
You know we should do
this more often, Atsuko.
Take care.
Hold on tight.
Insurance money.
If Hana were to die here.
Then I would get
the insurance money.
Get her!
Move it!
Ah, shit.
You all right, kid?
Hana, get back here!
You're going to be
with the Lord now.
Hana.
No!
Michiko!
Hey Padre, you dead?
You crying, Hatchin?
I can't tell if it's tears
or snot on my chest,
but it's definitely gross.
I'm not crying.
That was convincing.
Be quiet!
And what's with
this "Hatchin"?
What kind of name is that?
Ah, who cares?
It's cute.
Michiko!
Um, Michiko?
Yeah?
I lied to you.
About the tattoo?
Yes.
I know, I told you
I believed in you.
Yeah, thank you.
Sure.
Um.
What?
What'd you do?
To get arrested?
I didn't do nothing.
Just raised
a little bit of hell.
A little.
That's all?
Yeah.
Okay, and how about that song
your friend was singing?
What was that all about?
Everyone has little accidents
when they're kids, right?
But fuck that.
You know it's rude
to ask grown-ups
so many questions,
don't you?
I'm not rude!
Rude as they come!
I am not!