I have a fairly,
prominent mole on my right arm.
When he discovered it
and discovered the hair
growing out of it.
I could feel my face
burning with embarrassment.
But he was amused.
And just kept touching it.
Flicking it back and forth.
What are you saying?
That I'm some kind of poison?
That perfume is pretty intense.
Your face tells me you have
no need for a wreck like me.
We should end this
while we can both still
look back fondly on it.
I get it, your feelings are
so transparent, Feliciano.
Fine!
I'll make it a game for you.
Run away, if you like.
I'll chase after you.
After all, the only future I can
see is the one with you in it.
What a crock.
Jeez, we're going nowhere fast.
Ah, no rush.
We know where she's heading.
Won't be long at all.
Yo!
Sorry for the wait.
What do you think?
Yeah, um.
Who exactly is, Rock Morena?
Where'd you hear that?
From the picture
in the newspaper!
It said the man holding
that crazy tomato is named
Rock Morena, not Hiroshi.
Hey, I don't know
where he got the name.
--Does it even really matter?
--Yes, it matters!
It absolutely matters!
What if it's the
wrong person again?
You know, you tend to
miss these kinds of details.
Look at it again!
It's fuckin' Hiroshi!
There's no way
I'd mistake him!
Of course he
looks even hotter now.
That's the kind of guy he is.
But, how have I held up?
Shit!
Goddammit!
I'm going to change.
Hey, hold it!
No entry, unless you
have business here.
I do have business here.
This is the main gate.
I've got an intruder.
No, wait! Listen!
--The hell are you doing?
--I'm using my brain!
Are you sure this is the place?
I don't see any
tomato fields around here!
Look, just like the picture.
We've already come this far.
I'm going inside.
Fine, suit yourself.
Wait for me right here.
Our happy ending's coming soon.
Hey!
I told you,
this area is off lim-!
Damn it!
Idiot!
Ma'am!
Seems we have
an intruder situation.
Uh, no.
This is the woman
we're concerned with.
Shall I call this in?
Damn, you guys are persistent!
Hey! Freeze!
We've captured
the intruder, ma'am.
Excellent work.
If you wouldn't mind, bring
her in here for me, please.
She is our guest, after all.
Go on!
Are you okay?
All done.
What're you doing in here?
What do you think, jerk?
I came here for you!
You dummy, I told you
to wait outside!
Why the hell did you come in?
Quarreling?
That's a bit surprising.
So, where is he?
Where's who?
This ain't a game,
and I ain't playing!
Damn it!
Aright, bring it on you bitch!
You have, long legs.
Anyway, have you had lunch yet?
We grew these here.
Have it.
Vitamin A.
I don't need
your damn handouts!
Excuse me!
We came here, to see
a man named Rock Morena.
Yes, I know.
What're those doing there?
What's this room for?
Shit!
Damn it!
Son of a--!
Hiroshi!
You here?
Damn you!
Where'd you hide Hiroshi?
Michiko! Let's go!
He's not he--!
Shut up!
You stay outta this!
The grown-ups are talking!
You're an awfully cruel woman!
You know that?
Yeah? So what if I am?
What's the big idea?
You trying to
distract me or something?
You could've
just kissed me back.
Would've been nice.
You've got something
in your hair.
Knock it off with
this coming onto me crap!
Bring him out here!
Bring him out here, right now!
He ran away.
He ran.
Away?
Really?
Yeah, because he knew
you were coming.
Hmm.
It's Hiroshi, is it?
He told me he didn't have
a name, and I believed him.
When he came here,
he said he was looking for work
as a farmhand.
I was still just starting out
at the time, and my research
consisted of one long
string of failures.
After failing again and again,
one day I finally
found a sprout.
I was so happy, I wept.
And then, he wept with me.
He was a hell of a guy.
That Rock Morena.
That was the name
of a dog I had once.
Like it?
When I suggested it
to him, he just laughed.
"Woof!" he said to me.
That's enough!
That perfume.
Did he, like it,
once upon a time?
He did.
Which one started it?
Answer me, you thieving hussy!
He started it.
Hey, you wanted to know;
I'm simply laying out
the facts for you.
Shit!
I guess, he knew.
Huh?
That I'd go as far as it took.
He wants me to tell him,
that I forgive him.
He's a selfish brat.
I don't think,
that's true of him now.
Oh yeah?
That's the man
Hiroshi Morenos is!
So, are you using the child
as an excuse to see him?
She is his, right?
How disappointing.
You sure talk
a good game, though.
I don't give a fuck
what you think.
The religious
family's soon-to-be
ten year-old daughter,
Hana Belembauza Yamada,
was abducted after a motorcycle
crashed into the home.
Authorities are now saying
the culprit is escaped felon
Michiko Malandro.
Police describe a chaotic
scene at the humble parish,
as shotgun shells
and broken glass...
Someone you know?
Crazy.
Where do you
suppose they're headed?
Yes?
Ma'am, the police are here.
She hung up.
What floor is it?
She's up on six.
Ricardo.
Yeah?
Security office.
Follow them on the monitors.
Hurry up, Hatchin!
He went to São Paraíso.
São Paraíso?
Take the elevator
down to the basement.
That's the farm level.
I'll make sure
the door's open for you.
Run for the emergency
exit, and you should come
out on the street.
Why are you helping us?
Because I find you adorable.
A silly little lovesick fool.
Tell me this; know how
many women there are
in the world better than me?
He sure as hell does.
Where they at?
The elevators.
Aw, which floor?
Currently on the fifth.
Stop them! Now!
Right!
And keep your eyes on them!
What the?
The hell's going on?
Fire on five near Passageway A!
I repeat there is a fire on.
Wait!
Aw, hell!
Fire on four too!
Another fire on three!
Near Passageway B!
Those two are-.
Son of a bitch!
Damn it!
We're almost there!
Don't let go!
Michiko!
You are not getting away!
Hatchin, come on, quick!
Michiko!
Inspector,
it's Ricardo, come in.
Damn it!
What's up?
We had them in the elevator,
but we lost them
in the second basement.
What's down there?
That's just our
agricultural space, however.
The power to the plant
has been shut off,
and I can't confirm anything.
I, have to go.
Yeah, so.
Should we like,
kiss or something'?
It's the end for us and all.
That just wasn't right.
I got a few questions.
You know her?
São Paraíso.
São Paraíso?
Yeah, they're
heading to São Paraíso.
You gave them up awfully quick.
Sure did.
We appreciate your cooperation.
Feels good to move on.