Lenine!
Yeah, I'll do it now.
I can't believe it.
It feels like her hand is
reaching out to the light.
And touching my heart.
Whoa, hey!
How much for an hour?
Come on name your price!
I won't haggle I got money.
João, what happened to that
"Toucan in the Rain" book?
Did you sell it?
I did.
Do you remember to who?
Was it a blonde girl?
Well, she was an older lady.
Maybe she was blonde once.
That bike really screwed us.
It's like, talk
about your bad luck.
We're almost there.
Hiroshi is in
the next town over!
Isn't that what you heard?
Now what's up your butt?
If there's something on your
mind, then let's hear it.
It's just;
there's a book I want.
A book?
What kind?
It's about a boy who
takes a bird from its cage
and they go on a journey.
They're trying to track down
the bird's family.
Back in Laranja, I was
reading it in secret.
But then you came and took me
away and I never finished it.
All right, so go buy it.
Can I go now then?
Yeah, but you know, money's
tight so I can't let you
have any more than ten arcas.
If it's more than that,
you got to scrounge up
the dough yourself.
Fresh vegetables
at low, low prices.
Grown by the best farmers,
and picked by the best
field hands just this morning!
Then why do these
look so messed up?
Oh, they're not bad;
they're full of growth hormone,
which is
perfectly safe to eat.
We call them "Monstro-matoes"
Just one of them is worth
twenty-five regular ones.
And I'm the only one in
the market who sells them.
Yeah?
So the guy who
trucks them in is this him?
Hey, move your foot!
Don't change the subject,
just take a real close look.
Is this him?
The scruffy-looking handsome
guy, carrying the tomatoes.
Fish!
Get your fresh
caught fish here!
Nice and cheap!
Fresh fish!
Cheap fish!
You bought a lot, huh?
Hi, there.
Oh, the fish!
I'm helping a friend,
it's just temporary.
No, I mean.
The book?
Sorry, someone bought it.
It was "The Toucan
in the Rain" wasn't it?
Uh yeah.
Oh.
Don't be sad.
Hatchin!
Where'd you run off to?
Hatchin?
That's a pretty name.
I should go now.
I'll wait for you!
This afternoon!
Outside the church when
the bells ring, at three.
Here.
Oh, and this too.
Oh uh, how much for it?
No, it's a gift.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
You want to go up with me?
To the top of the tower.
So Hatchin, is this
your first time here?
Yeah.
I've been wondering.
What brought you
to Penínsoola, Hatchin?
Listen, could you please
not call me by that name?
Oh um, sorry.
It's fine.
My name's Leniñe.
At least I think it is.
That's what they call me.
Hana, that's um, my real name.
I'm searching for my father.
We've been on
the road for months.
Planície's our next stop.
But our bike broke down again,
so we're stuck here for a bit.
You're searching for your dad?
That sounds kind
of familiar, huh?
It's like in
"The Toucan in the Rain!"
So, uh.
I can't accept
this gift from you.
I have to give it back.
"Soyokaze, I've caught you".
Wait, it's just a quote.
"There is a kind
of bird called the 'toucan'".
"A species not native
to this land.
So when I saw one, I took her,
and we went on an adventure".
"She wanted a new world.
So that's where we went".
Here you go.
Says he's down there
waiting for you.
What?
This is for you, right?
--Hey watch it!
--Go getcha some!
I'm going shopping.
What's with her?
Hana!
It's okay; I won't
hold it against you.
Because, no matter what.
I'm still in love with you.
Good, you're finally back!
We split town tomorrow.
The bike's all fixed.
We're ready to hit the road.
Sure took his
sweet ass time though.
Michiko what's
that book doing here?
That little artsy kid
dropped it off for you.
Anyway we're heading
out bright and early.
Are you packed?
Hey!
Don't go getting
all mopey on me now!
You knew from the start
we were only going
to be in this town
for a little while.
What's that mean?
You read it!
Didn't you?
Please, I need to know.
Lenine, is that his name?
You did read it!
What are you stomping me for?
Why do you think?
So that's what this is.
First time some boy's
paying attention to you,
and now you're thinking
you're hot shit.
Right?
Wrong!
Why is everything
about boys with you!
I am nothing like you!
Listen!
If it weren't for the fact
that you're Hiroshi's daughter.
Right now you'd be taking a dirt
nap out in the high desert!
But, I am an adult;
I forgive you.
Now, say you're sorry!
Come on in.
Um sir, can you return
this to Leniñe please?
I get it now.
You must be the angel
he told me about.
It's all right.
I'll smooth
things over with him.
Actually, um.
I should return it myself.
Lenine hasn't told you
about his accident, has he?
He doesn't have any memories.
There was an explosion.
An old building had
a gas leak that ignited
just as Lenine
was walking past.
Debris flew everywhere, and
some struck him right on top
of his head.
When he came to, he had
no memory of anything
that had come before.
Other than that, his personality
didn't really change.
He still soars through life,
as free as a bird.
But they'll come back.
Eventually, I hope.
Though, when those old memories
return, they say he'll forget
everything that happened
to him since the accident.
Like he was just
waking up from it.
If that happens, will you
still be able to say goodbye
to the Lenine you
know with a smile?
Today's all I have left.
Tomorrow, I'm heading
out to Planície.
I'm leaving for good.
Hana!
Hang on!
I was wrong!
I didn't come to see you,
it's not like that!
Hana.
Ever since I met you,
I've become so much more
grateful for the
things in my life.
It feels like I've found someone
who can be a part of my soul.
But you're going to
forget all about this!
Everything about me!
The old man in the bookstore.
Told me all about the explosion,
and your memory loss.
I won't forget you, I swear,
I'll never forget you.
I may not remember
what kind of person I was.
And this town I grew up in
may feel strange and foreign.
Every day,
the world's a blank slate.
But I still know I'm me.
I still keep moving forward.
Leaving only footprints behind.
I'm just trying to fill in that
slate, one new memory at a time.
And I promise I've etched
your memory into my heart.
Hatchin, trust me.
Stop making me
feel so confused!
I hate you!
I hate you and
your stupid face!
No!
I don't want to lose you!
Hana!
Hello there.
Haven't seen you around.
Just passing through?
This?
This is "Toucan in the Rain".
Sounds kind of silly but,
this book is magic.
Never fails to make me
feel better whenever I read it.
And that's no lie,
I wanted the girl who lived
here to read it, too.
Actually, you seem
a lot like her somehow.
The first time
I laid eyes on her.
I thought I was
looking at an angel.
I feel like I was
scared of waking up.
And I stayed asleep
for a long time.
Too long.
Thank you.
Goodbye, Hana.
We're leaving this afternoon?
Yeah.
Are you all packed?
Cause I'm not
helping you this time.
You good?
What's wrong?
I was actually happy.
Michiko, it hurts so much.
Why?