ID Number: three-four-five-
six-seven-four-two.
One-three-seven-zero-zero.
Class B license.
Nidia da Glória.
Ama Alexandro Gigio.
Hometown is Neiro.
Address is Fifteen
Ostra Street, Marisco, Neiro.
Hundred year-old, man?
You sure?
Uh.
Hatchin!
Let's roll!
Hey!
Freeze kid!
Come on jump!
An illegal entry at an São
Paraíso border checkpoint,
is having unexpected traffic
repercussions, with thousands
of travelers delayed as officers
shut down the entire gate.
Given that it's Milenãrio
de Samba season in the city,
the delayed, would-be-partiers
are making the best of it.
Getting an early start on
the celebration postponed
by the illegal entry.
Authorities tell us
the checkpoint jumpers
are both female, one of
them a ten-year-old child.
I'll never forget
that face, brother.
I'm so sorry.
Don't apologize.
You made the right choice.
Should we check the
surveillance tapes?
Tell me, Ricardo.
Ever think about, going home?
Huh?
Can't sleep, huh?
Bunch of spoiled-ass rich kids.
Find any new info?
Nope, same old hunch.
Don't get down, Hatchin,
we're going to find him.
Your Dad's got loads of talent.
I bet he's rich by now,
which makes him easy to spot.
Only reason he'd
come here's to make bank.
You see?
All that matters is we're here.
I'm sure he's working
some scam or other.
I hope you're right this time.
I really hope you're right.
What's he doing?
Hey!
Who are you?
You want to fight with me, pal?
No, Miss!
Your kid looks familiar's all.
She resembles this guy I knew,
name of Rock Morena.
Hold on!
You talking about this guy?
Yeah, it's him all right.
Rock Morena.
Hear that, Hatchin?
He's here.
This is the place
he used to shack up.
Two of us even ran
a little racket together.
We'd boost iron in copper
gates and manhole covers,
then flip them to junk metal
dealers for quick cash.
I ain't real proud of it,
but when times are tough,
you do what you got to survive.
But then he took off,
with my half of the score
and all I had before.
I earned that money, dammit!
And I'd kill to get it back in
my pockets where it belongs.
Yeah, we're after him, too.
Did he ever
open up about stuff?
Like how he had a woman who
loved him and that he'd die for.
Or like a family that he
wanted to settle down with?
Maybe this ain't the same guy.
All he talked about was
becoming a big shot in Monstro.
But he couldn't throw a punch
for shit, or how he used to
grow tomatoes bigger
than King Kong's balls,
but he'd never eat them.
Could never tell
what was real with him,
or what was lies
to impress folks.
Oh, and one more lie!
He once claimed some
TV actor saw him in a bar
and invited him to be on his
show, but he turned it down.
Ridiculous!
What, was I born yesterday?
So I ask him, "what's this
actor guy look like;
what TV show is he on?"
And he's all, "You know,
that douchey-looking guy
on the big drama."
Rock was a good crook,
but a terrible liar!
Hey, let go!
Listen up, Mister:
Hiroshi was in Monstro,
he did grow those tomatoes
and he ain't no liar.
And you ask me?
He could be an actor
because he is super-hot.
Then why'd he turn it down?
Because he's
still in love with me.
You're so gullible.
Listen, toots,
he abandoned you and the girl.
Don't sound like love to me.
Damn you!
Proceeding to reported area.
Arriving now.
No immediate sign.
Looks like they cleared out.
Will investigate on foot.
Why did--
Why did he come to this city?
Maybe he really
was just running away.
I guess, I always knew.
That's just the kind
of man Hiroshi is.
Some prefer to get lost
in the weeds of character,
but I like a bird's eye view
of the whole production.
If I don't have
that level of perspective,
I won't be able
to perform at my best.
And the best is what
my legions of fans deserve.
Anything less is a betrayal.
The success of the show clearly
owes so much to you, Feliciano.
Yes, but without all those hard
workers behind the scenes,
my greatness
wouldn't be possible.
And, of course, the fans...
"Douchey looking guy
on a big drama?"
That must be him!
And fans have even more
to look forward to...
Hiroshi did grow
those giant tomatoes.
And was in Monstro.
I guess he met this guy too.
Even with all the tragedy,
this show's a love story.
And as long as I
give it all I've got,
the viewers will
fall in love too.
That's great to hear!
Thanks for your time, and
for your wisdom, Feliciano.
Please come back soon.
We are mere moments away from
the new Museum of Modern Art
being lit up, like a
UFO for a big TV shoot!
Dang it.
I like it when she smiles.
I will get Michiko
smiling again!
No matter what it takes!
Feliciano's using the city's
frenzy around Milenario de Samba
as a backdrop to shoot
a climactic scene
at the museum right behind me!
How we gonna end
this thing with a bang?
Do we go up into space,
or come down from it?
How many times can
we argue over this ending?
Just stick to the damn script!
The script blows!
Viewers want us to ratchet
things up for the finale!
Love surrounds us!
It's the whole universe!
Men are cool, icy planets,
and women are black holes!
They suck us in and
trap us for eternity!
Feliciano will finally come
to realize this cosmic truth!
You feel me, man?
We open with me
standing on this roof.
I shiver with emotion,
then throw out my arms,
tears streaming down my face!
I love you.
Fade to black!
Boom! The End!
Well, you love it, don't you?
Well, it's certainly an idea.
You're passing on this?
You don't think it's gold?
Guess what pal, this
is primo-24-karat stuff!
It's shit.
It's art!
Go back to film school, son!
I ain't working with
no bush league rookie!
Mr. Feliciano's
running off the set!
Someone stop him!
The hell?
Crazy-ass groupies
keep getting younger.
Hey, stop!
You just ran a red!
Michiko, I have to do
whatever it takes.
Feliciano!
Report: female matching
description of one of the
gatecrashers from yesterday, was
clipped by a car on Route 43.
All units proceed to the scene.
It's her.
You're not him.
He tricked me!
Suspects spotted on route 43.
On foot, heading southeast
to the Sichuan District.
Kid, wait!
I'm not going to arrest you!
Shut up!
I don't believe you!
Stop it Jambo!
Let me go!
What is she thinking leaving
you alone like this?
You're just a helpless kid.
You trying to go back?
To that creepy foster family?
Huh-uh.
Okay, then what?
I was chasing
this guy, Feliciano.
Feliciano?
He's this jerky TV actor.
Supposedly, he ran into
my father not that long ago.
I wanted to find him
and get him to tell Michiko
what he knows about Hiroshi.
I doubt Hiroshi's given us
one thought since he left.
That's just the
kind of guy he is.
But still, I wanted Feliciano
to tell her that Hiroshi
said something nice about her.
Even if it's not true.
She'll be happy again,
back to how she used to be.
He's up there.
Go on.
What?
This should make us even.
Have you not figured out,
I ain't answering?
Look at me!
Do you recognize this face?
You do know you're
wearing a mask?
Don't tell me
you've never seen it!
Or this symbol, either!
Just take my wallet.
Watch the face!
Call the number and read this.
All right, that's enough!
Just knock it off!
Do I know you?
--Hiroshi's kid!
--Who the hell is that?
Hiroshi Morenos,
guy who steals junk metal.
Rock Morena,
grows big tomatoes!
You asked him
to be on your show!
Hold on a second,
you gotta slow down there.
Now, you're Hiroshi's
daughter, right?
That's right.
But the dude who steals
junk metal is named Hiroshi,
and the dude with
big tomatoes is Rock?
I'm confused,
who are they to you?
My father!
Which one!
Both of them!
So, Rock and Hiroshi
are the same guy.
And you're saying I once offered
him a gig on my show, huh?
Thing is, I've never done
that for anyone before.
But, I could swear you were
that douchey-looking guy
on that popular soap opera.
Well, maybe your Dad
just ran into an actor
from one of the
knock-offs of my show.
Knock-off?
What?
Yeah, copycats, fakes.
Look here; change the
channel all you want.
Whole damn line-up's
full of cheap imitations
of my brilliance.
No originality at all.
That's just how show
business is, kiddo.
I guess I was wrong.
Its cool, listen: The
soap I been carrying
on my back is super popular.
But the reasons why go beyond
my good looks and fans.
It's because I push to keep
the stories fresh and awesome.
But, if that's all it took,
those other knock-offs
would be popular, too.
You see.
You also need an actor who
grounds his performance
in truth.
That is what I bring.
I'm able to turn a boring old
love story, into something
that will give the audience
an emotional breakdown.
And yet the director can't see
that it's these skills of mine
that keep him employed!
What's wrong with him?
Why is he being such a diva!
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm so sorry for this!
Go ahead, little one,
cry it all out.
What am I going to
do with this girl?
Dangit!
Ah, is this Michiko?
Who's this?
Great to finally get a hold
of you, my name is Feliciano.
I'm an actor, and I have
some news you might
like to hear about your
old friend, Hiroshi.
Met him in a bar recently.
He was such a charismatic man
I had to go say hello.
I asked him to come on my
TV show and play my rival.
But, much to my chagrin,
he passed on the offer.
I tried to convince him, but
he kept telling me about
the beautiful woman who
meant so much to him.
I used every negotiating trick
in the book, but alas.
Hiroshi refused every time.
Michiko, I know he's still
out there waiting for you.
Don't lose hope;
keep searching!
You'll still get your
happy ending, okay?
Um, thank you for doing that.
Don't worry about the mess.
I have people for that.
I am rich, after all.
Yeah, but?
Hey!
Dance with me!
Samba Time!
From Goinia, Rock Morena.
Ricardo!
This is where we part ways.
What?
I can't hear you!
No, listen!
No, I'm grateful
for all your help!
I-!
Yeah, you're getting it!
I get the feeling; we're going
to end up busting through
another gate tomorrow.