A photo?
No, I don't think so.
Your baby Michiko's always with
you, so you don't need one.
Right, Hiroshi?
Come here!
A photo, huh?
Hey babe.
Michiko.
Hey.
--What?
--More great music coming up.
But first, let's get an
update from the newsroom.
Thanks, Pepper.
In Vermelha, apparent tumult
in the criminal organization
"Monstro Preto" continues
to alarm authorities.
Many of the group's
highest ranking members
have disappeared, and now
they're turning up dead,
one body at a time.
Officials fear an all-out
war with "Fantasma--'
Whaddya say we
take one together?
Easy, honey.
That's your tenth shot.
Don't make me cut you off.
Aw, come on!
What are you doing?
Put me down.
You really outdid yourself.
I said put me down!
Let go of me!
Now!
I'm quitting Monstro!
I went to see
Satoshi yesterday.
You serious?
Yeah.
No fucking way.
S'not gonna help
to run, you know.
I'll come after you,
no matter what.
You belong to me forever.
Yeah.
Attention in the terminal.
Passengers for Bus 104,
bound for São Marcelo;
boarding is now underway.
Now you are one hard man
to track down, Manabe.
Long time no see, huh?
What's wrong?
You haven't forgotten
your old pal, have you?
Well say something.
So, a family man now.
Drive.
Why?
Where to?
Home sweet home, Daddy.
We can talk right here!
You don't wanna be pushing
my buttons today man.
I'm sleep-deprived.
Now go.
Welcome home.
Sit down.
Where's the little guy?
He's playing outside today.
He's gone.
Sure about that?
Yo it's me.
How things going?
Mission accomplished!
Alright, good, good.
I still gotta finish up here.
You put Michiko on the train.
Then head to Mãn
for some bill collection.
No way, that's gofer work.
I ain't doing that.
You have some kind of a stroke
that fucked with your head,
Shinsuke?
Forget who's boss?
Huh?
I don't discriminate,
and I don't play favorites.
We only need one man at the
top, and I'm the strongest.
You're just a foot soldier.
Got me?
Right now, in here,
I ain't the boss of Monstro.
I'm just barefoot Satoshi
Batista, the boy you made cry.
Chazzo!
Hide this somewhere
in Michiko's clothes.
Time to find out who's
the strongest one there is!
Personally,
I'm bettin' on her.
A little luck an'
Satoshi's gonna die!
We'll be there by morning.
Michiko's gonna be there?
She should be on her way now.
Everything cool?
I put Shinsuke
in charge of her.
Hold on.
She is alive, right?
Ricardo!
Change of plans.
We're going to Terra.
Satoshi.
Satoshi?
Sir.
One more time?
Mr. Satoshi, sir.
When I was running things,
I was crazy, I know.
I won't ask you to spare me.
But I'm pleading
with you, man to man.
Spare my wife and so--
What, you ready to die?
Gonna roll over,
just like that?
Don't fuck with me.
You took being
boss so serious.
All grim n' shit.
And always plannin'
three moves ahead.
Murderin', extortion,
wife-jackin'.
Yeah.
That was all just business.
Crazy was never part of it.
Your asses stay
on the hammock.
Mama?
Papa?
Now, unless you want your
precious family killed,
Manabe, you're gonna
do exactly what I say.
Train's coming about
an hour from now.
And onboard there'll be
a woman in real bad shape.
You're gonna bring
her back here.
Hi, sir, who're you?
Screw this up, and your
boy loses his future.
He has nothing
to do with this!
If you need a
hostage, take me.
That's my decision to make!
I'm the damn boss!
Hey kid.
How old are you?
I'm ten.
So you got any friends?
Got any hair down there yet?
Who's there?
C'mon!
Get that punk!
I saw him go this way!
Was that them?
Yeah.
You saved my skin.
So dude, you got a name?
Hiroshi Morenos.
Well my name's
Satoshi Batista.
Don'tchu forget it.
Got any hair down there yet?
Yeah.
A little.
I'm full-out bushy.
We adults now, man.
And soon I'm'onna
be in charge.
You know Seiji Manabe?
I'm gonna take over
his whole gang.
You can help me
when I make my move.
Take 'em.
This too.
Since I'm gonna
be el president.
S'pose I'll make you
my right hand man.
Shinsuke, you overdid it.
Where are they?
Huh?
What'd you do with my family?
Answer me!
Make me laugh before I'm
finished with this smoke--
--and maybe I won't
take your life.
Don't know 'bout your ass,
but I'm having Déjà Vu.
What is that,
physical comedy?
Can't say I'm a fan.
Jeez I'm beat.
I bet you couldn't sleep
much either, right?
Back when you were boss-man?
Huh?
That's the face
I'm looking for.
Just hang in there.
We're almost done.
Nothing but enemies
on every side.
No one you can trust.
Run!
What's wrong?
Satoshi got caught
trying to kill Manabe!
That means we're screwed, too!
If they catch us,
we're all dead!
Well shit.
I'm outta goddamn cigarettes.
Here, sir.
Here's the deal, kid.
Make me laugh before
I finish this smoke,
and I won't take your life.
See, I'm feeling generous.
I'll just settle
for your feet.
Hey.
This ain't a bathroom,
you filthy, little prick.
Hold on.
Did I just laugh?
Well fuck me.
Okay.
Feet it is.
One'a you boys
get me a knife!
Good and sharp.
What's wrong?
Hey!
What the--?
After all this time,
Michiko, what do you want?
I just wanna know where
the hell Hiroshi is.
And I'm sorry.
You're the
only one I can ask.
I know he's alive.
You are aware that the bus he
was riding on exploded, right?
Blew to high heaven.
I saw his body with my own eyes,
burned to a fuckin' crisp.
I don't buy that shit.
You persistent,
meddlesome, bitch!
He's dead!
I don't know what
Hiroshi told you back then,
but I took out all the
top guys in Monstro.
Everyone!
Yeah.
It was all my doin'.
Figured if I pinned
the bloodbath on Fantasma--
--then the whole fucking
show could be mine.
Called it "Operation:
Blitz the Devil's Triangle."
Got a real nice
ring, don't it?
I got some brains.
You're an idio--
Thanks to your rampage, hitting
Fantasma hard as you did,
Kiril asked for a sit down.
Wanted to work out a truce
or something, I don't know.
Didn't matter.
When he showed up--Blam.
End of an era.
Then, just as the
real fun was startin'--
--Hiroshi told me
he was up and quitting.
He said he was
running away with you.
Crazy right?
So I made up a story 'bout
dead-ass Kiril going missing.
Told Hiroshi if he wanted out,
he had to find Kiril first.
With him busy, I could
eliminate the problem:
your interfering ass.
It's your fault!
If it wasn't for you, it
wouldn'ta gone down like that!
Oh, what's this?
Damn it Shinsuke,
this is your handiwork.
A'ight.
Just don't miss.
Shoot me right here.
Or right here.
Come morning, it's back
to the big house.
I sold you out to Atsuko.
--Tell me, please!
--Get off me, you headcase!
Hiroshi is still alive.
Isn't he?
Hiroshi.
Damn it.
I don't know where the hell
he is either, alright?
Hang on.
Who's the old-ass bald fuck?
Just my trusty sidekick.
Who else you got with you?
No one.
Cash?
It's a sunny day after all.
Don't move.
Satoshi Batista,
we have got you surrounded.
You backstabbing bitch!
It's not me!
What is this?
I requested backup
from the local precinct.
You know that's not
what I'm asking you!
No!
Stand down!
This is my fuckin' collar!
God damn it!
If we let Malandro slip
through our fingers again,
we'll be writing parking
tickets until retirement.
You didn't have to do this.
I'm bringing her in.
Inspector, let me give it
to you nice and straight;
I'm done cleaning
up your messes.
You know how hard it's been
tagging along with some
"wonder-girl" inspector
younger than I am?
I have a family to feed, and a
mortgage on a brand-new house.
I'm not even this interested
in a double suicide with you.
The last thing I need
is to get demoted.
I'm taking the lead.
We've got two targets.
Michiko Malandro,
and Satoshi Batista.
Both have violent personalities,
and may be armed.
If necessary, you have
permission to shoot to kill.
Be careful.
Asshole!
Finally, I get
to be rid of you.
Today will make sure of that.
It looks like
they've both fled.
In pursuit now.
Copy that.
I'm coming to assist.
Hey!
That was not a suspect,
that was a mouse.
Repeat, that was only a mouse.
Suspects still at large.
Your face looks like hell.
You gonna shoot me or what?
Just let me go.
This once.
Sorry.
Got my head in a noose, too.
We're friends, right, Atsuko?
Don't even try
that shit with me.
What's the use in
pointing an empty gun?
Is that the kind of
woman you are, Michiko?
Go ahead and sneer, and spew
some crap, and call me "Jambo."
Then pistol-whip me and run!
Or I can shoot you.
I found him!
Hurry up and go.
Thanks.
Inspector.