Alright!
And the Macaco Princeza
is now standing up!
The Macaco Princeza
is coming.
Now, return the
hidden treasure.
I am afraid
I cannot do that.
Oh, Jesus!
It's the end of the world!
It is the end of the world!
Yes, the end of the world!
Macaco.
Vasily.
Go tell the guys in the plaza to
come inside and eat some lunch.
Sure.
Oh!
Jesus!
Somebody's here.
Which one of you's
Kiril Chapek of Fantasma?
Go screw!
The hell you think you are?
You Kiril?
How about you return
everyone from Monstro?
We were just
sitting down for abiet.
That means lunch.
Would you care to join us?
Not hungry?
Who's faction are you with?
Creasy?
No, I'm bettin' Satoshi.
You are with Monstro?
No, sorry.
I'm not Monstro, but
if you give them back,
everything'll
work out just fine.
Granted, we don't take kindly
to Monstro, but still,
we do honor the
cease-fire agreement.
So how can we give 'em back
if we know nothing about it?
M'I right?
Don't play dumb with me,
Mister Handsome Fuzzy-face!
Bitch!
There is a film crew that
was good enough to come
to Vermelha today.
My lovely Sasha here is making
her debut as an actress.
An auspicious day,
to be sure.
You can stay for abiet,
or you can leave.
But you need
to decide for me.
You really ought to
take some time to stop
and smell the roses.
Or all that beauty
will be for nothing.
Nyet!
What are you doing, Kiril?
Stop pawing all over
that woman!
If you don't get your hands
off her in five seconds,
I am leaving you!
I mean it!
I'll bite my tongue and die!
Sorry, but you heard the lady.
Down to four seconds.
Go now, or I will
pull the trigger.
It's rainin'.
You can see through those?
Wow.
Go on, say hello, dear.
Hi, I'm Marisa.
My!
Oh, for you.
We can't thank you enough.
What are you doing, Joaquim?
Shut up, hag!
Tell me where you sent Marisa!
Somewhere she can be happy.
Liar!
What's wrong?
You don't trust me?
Why should I?
Settle down, kiddo.
You're not the first
delinquent we've had here.
Yo!
Omigod-Omigod-Omigod, Michiko!
How've you been?
All right?
Yeah.
Goodness, I have been
so, so, so worried about you!
So, where did your brother go?
Scooch over a bit,
wouldja darling?
He's there.
Bullfightin'?
Yep.
We do some direct sales at
the fights but my brother's
the one who goes.
It's Marco!
Such a fine man;
I'm going all aquiver!
What's that look?
Marco is our great hope.
Even Romão the Fourth
is nothing to him.
Romão the Fourth?
The be-all-end-all of steers.
So, it's a bull.
Yeah but look, every matador
who faces him gives up.
But Marco is way more brave.
Oh dear.
Now I'm getting all tingly.
Maybe it's your stubble.
Oh, no, now I've made
the girl uncomfortable.
Hatchin.
Hiroshi's kid.
Yeah, bu-- wha--?
I came back to see Satoshi.
Listen, Michiko, everything
has changed since back then.
Monstro is now a
full-fledged crime syndicate.
And Satoshi, you see,
is their leader.
Yeah I know.
Then what good will
seeing him do at this point?
Pretty sure he knows
where Hiroshi is.
Hiroshi?
Sweetie, he's been
dead for years!
He's alive, I'm sure of it!
Didn't you hear?
About the bus incident?
Yeah, it proves my point.
Oh, you silly, busty hot-head.
What are you talking about?
Do you need me to explain
to you what went down next?
After you went all
cray-cray on Fantasma?
Enough, I don't
wanna hear it.
Leggo!
Once Kiril was gone,
you got arrested, right?
Immediately after,
a Monstro body was found,
and it was all-out war.
Lemme be clear,
a lotta people died.
Fantasma, Monstro,
and plenty of innocents.
Yeah, so what if they did?
You're the one who started
all of it, aren't you?
You can't go and kill
someone like that,
just because
they beat you up!
I didn't--
Didn't what?
Gonna say you didn't kill him?
Then why did you admit to it?
First, Kiril said he was
going out to meet with you.
Then he doesn't come back,
and they find him dead!
Anyone would think
that you were the one who--
Shut up!
I only ever saw
Kiril that once!
I forgot what he even
looks like, years ago!
Long as I'm at it I'll tell
you this: Satoshi Batista,
he isn't here.
The only ones left are Fantasma,
under the control of Monstro.
Where is he then?
Please.
I'll say it again.
Fantasma are
the only ones here.
Whatever story you're stickin'
to these days, Michiko,
everyone else thinks you're
the one who killed Kiril.
And now that you know,
you need to leave.
Otherwise, you're
gonna get killed.
Besides.
I've done all I can.
I can't look at you anymore.
Yeah fine.
Same here.
Come on in.
'Kay.
Sit anywhere.
So, is this--?
Is this the place where
you were born, Michiko?
Dunno if I was born here or not,
but this is where I grew up,
yeah.
It's where I met your old man.
You mean here?
Yeah.
Don't move, Sasha!
Try anything and we blast
a hole----right through you?
Beat it.
Go to hell.
They're still wet.
Dude!
What choice we got?
Take it!
Now just stay put,
and don't look at me.
Do like we tell you,
and we won't have to--
'Ey!
Hold on!
Whoa!
Wait!
Damn it!
Next time I load my own gun!
Don't look at
those without askin'.
The other one?
So uh, I'm guessin'
that man is Hiroshi.
Isn't it?
Yeah.
Goofy lookin' face.
We're here.
Yeah, so 'here' would be?
It says "take care of you."
What's that supposed to mean?
It means to look after you.
When you get inside,
find an old lady named Zélia.
It's all written down there;
your favorite foods,
personality.
Everythin' about you,
far as I know.
And what do you plan on doing?
I gotta go find
a guy named Satoshi.
He's been hangin' with Hiroshi
ever since they were kids.
He's gotta know
somethin' about 'im.
Then, Hatchin,
I'll come for you.
Take this.
I'm coming, too.
You can't.
Why not?
You just can't.
It's too dangerous.
I can take care of myself!
You'll get in the way!
I didn't--
Then why have you been
dragging me around?
Just so you can dump me off?
Why should I let someone
I don't even know look after me?
Huh?
Tell me!
No, hang on--It's
not like that.
Hatchin!
Are you even sure he's alive?
'Cause if he is, then why
the hell has he left
you and me alone all this time?
You don't think he's alive?
No.
Then you don't
believe in me, either?
No!
So you wanna
just part ways here?
Yeah, I do.
I think it's for the best.
How'm I supposed
to get by with no money?
Vasily, sir?
It's Peixe here.
What is it?
I just spotted Michiko Malandro
over on Pintinho Street.
She had a kid with her, who she
just dropped off somewhere.
She's currently on
a bike, heading east.
Michiko Malandro.
So, Kiril, this woman you
let go, she's makin' noise
all over town, asking about
Monstro, kicking up a ruckus
we don't need.
The film crew is starting
to get nervous too,
saying they might even
cancel the Vermelha shoot.
This would be quite
a loss, Kiril.
So then, your plan?
It's too late.
You shoulda just
shut the bitch up then.
Once this is all over,
we're gonna ask you
to step down as leader.
I know.
Where the hell's Sasha?
I see.
Kiril, I am coming with you!
Forget it, Vaseely.
I'll be just fine.
I have to protect you guys.
Comes with the job.
You taught me well, Kiril.
Now that
responsibility's mine.
"I ask on yarrs of frennship
that you tack keer of hor."
What on Earth is this?
"Take care of her?"
Um, I guess.
This is not the kind of
letter you give to someone.
Ah, how pathetic.
I did not want her
to grow up like this.
So?
What about her?
Where is Michiko now?
She just left.
I'm not sure where.
I trust you have money, right?
No.
Alright listen up,
short stuff.
Seems like it's asking an awful
lot to drop you off here
without any money, yes?
What do you expect me
to do with this?
Start a line of credit?
The world simply
does not work that way.
Come back when
you've got some cash.
We'll talk about it then.
Thanks for humiliating me.
And here I thought
she was gonna protect me,
no matter what!
That's right.
That is what she said, but--
But she slapped me!
She'll pay for that.
I'll hit her!
I'll hit her good!
Always acting so cool.
"Get in the way" my butt!
And after she got
all teary-eyed.
I know what's up!
Truth is, she's just lonely,
puttin' up a brave front.
Whatever, I'm still
gonna hit her!
No matter what!
Then maybe we'll talk!
So, to help your pals who
were taken by Fantasma,
you wanted to grab
this Kiril Capek guy's lady
and take her hostage.
Instead, you found me.
That the gist?
Yeah so um,
she must be pretty hot.
Right?
So, you're still goin, huh?
All alone?
You're not scared?
I mean, you could get killed.
Killed, you say.
Hell, if just me dyin' is what
it takes to save the others--
Then fine.
I decided to
do this on my own.
Gotta finish it the same way.
Why not jus' call it off?
Hey, look.
Sun's out.
Hey.
Are you hungry at all?
Let's eat.
I decided to come
with you to Kiril's.
It's not like that, Hatchin.
He's a coward.
That's why I hafta go to him.
You and I hafta
go and find him.
So, you've got quite a bit
of money saved up, don'tcha?
Sure do, been squirrelin'
away what I can for years now.
Everyone's layin' odds on
what you're gonna use it for.
I'm gonna spend it
all on myself, of course.
I mean, who else is gonna
look after me in the future,
you know?
It's been a lot harder for me
to get around lately.
There are days I'm so
miserable, I just want to cry.
You've still got
the children, though.
None of them give a damn
about poor little old me.
Once they're gone,
they're gone.
No one comes back to visit.
Besides, I never even liked
children all that much
to begin with.
They're so loud,
and dirty, and rude.
I can't stand them.
What have we here?
No!
She is not in here.
Not here, either.
There's just some kid.
Must be the one
who was with Michiko.
All right.
Bring her on back here.