Are you okay?
Michiko?
Yeah, I knew it.
Knew what?
That you've got a fever!
I told you we needed
to stop and get some rest!
Why won't you ever
listen to anyone?
You're wrong, Hatchin.
The reason I'm hot--
--is because unlike you,
I'm jus' a hot woman.
There's sump'm
wrong with yer face.
But I'm hot.
Michiko!
April Twenty-Eighth.
Michiko has collapsed.
Well hello!
Oh, hello.
You're the young'un next door.
I hear your mom is sick.
Huh?
She is your mom, right?
Yeah, course she is.
Here, sweetie, have this.
So how old are you?
'Bout ten? Such a lovely age!
After that, they
all just turn rotten.
But you're not that
kinda girl. Your mom's
one of the lucky ones!
You must be taking a trip, huh?
As it happens, I'm a traveler
as well. 'Course, I'm on my own.
It's a lot harder than I
thought, you know what I--?
Oh, right, you wouldn't.
I'm so alone.
But I won't let it get me down!
Also, you shouldn't
leave that running.
Later! If you need
anything, just holler!
Take care!
I wonder how long
this medicine takes to work.
That hotel bill
is gonna keep growing.
If it's too many more days,
we'll have to sneak off
and that's no good.
Okay, yeah, if that's the
direction you're heading--
There's a dormitory where
you can stay for 27 arcas.
I know, right?
'Scuse me.
Yes? How can I help?
Do you know of any jobs?
I'm a hard worker,
and I'll do anything
I'm suitable for.
Maybe, can ya start tonight?
Yes.
Give this number a call.
It's real simple work
and the pay's good.
Thank you very much, sir.
Five arcas.
So, um.
I'm also looking for a clinic
where someone without I.D.
can go? Cheap, if possible, but
one with a skilled doctor?
Is there anywhere like that?
Michiko, I found a doctor!
Not goin'. No way.
Stop acting like such
a baby. You have to go,
or you'll never get better!
I am better. Hale an' frickin'
hearty. And I'm not a baby,
I'm a grown-up. You go by
yourself if you wanna, Hatchin.
Like I said. "Baby".
Do you know what
fundamental principle
governs this entire universe?
That of causality-- of cause
and effect. And I am the one,
supreme god, who is
able to break it.
As such, people
refer to me as "Deus."
Bem-vindo à Galáxia! In God's
hands, any and all ailment
is alleviated in an instant.
I want to leave.
But this man--
--is all I have right now.
Gérson.
Mm-hm. Prepare to operate.
Operate?
Miracle show time,
satisfaction one-hundred-twenty
percent guaranteed.
I dare you to try stickin'
that thing in my arm!
I'll put you on an
express train to hell!
It's just an anesthetic.
Gérson, hold her down!
Here is the void.
Nothing but nothingness.
Big bang!
The universe expands! Into the
living darkness of galáxia,
I call forth
the light of the sun!
I make the
Heaven and the Earth!
The dust begets rain,
which begets the seas!
The land grows forth! And flora
and fauna to thrive upon it!
And then, finally,
I created you.
It is a failed creation,
full of defects.
Do you hear that sound?
It is--
The rhythm of life itself.
Rebirth.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I feel better somehow.
That doctor's pretty awesome.
This was the cause
of it all. You can relax now.
A divine feat. Magic hands.
Her chart and invoice.
Um, this is not what
we had discussed.
Take a look.
"Additional
services cost extra?"
That's right.
But I don't have that much.
Besides, you didn't--
--tell me any of that!
You've been told now,
haven't you?
I can't. I can't accept this.
I am an evangelist of
happiness and you doubt me?
I have never once thought
of myself as being a god!
Not once! I am merely
a humble conduit!
And yet you dare--!
Gérson.
Amigo.
Yes. That's right,
I'm your amigo.
If you do not have faith
in my treatments,
all my sacred efforts
will have been for nothing,
and she will remain
sick forever more.
Naturally.
I have a job. I'll work
to get the money tonight.
I promise I'll
bring it tomorrow.
I see, then you do
believe in Deus?
Sure.
All the same, I'll take
that promise in writing.
Fine.
It was like I was all alone
on an express train to Hell.
You try'na getcher
self killed, ya little shit?
Look at him eye-ballin' me.
Next time kid.
When those cock-suckin' bandits
show up, you shout good
and loud, got it?
Don't let 'em get away.
Bandits, great.
Um.
Yeah, what?
May I use your phone?
Mister!
You got even less sense
than the damn dog.
Didn't really earn nothin'.
I ain't gonna pay ya.
Take as much'a this
as you like though.
Let's go, Buddy!
I understand what
you're saying. However.
What is this?
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow? Tomorrow doesn't
come the same for everyone.
What's this? "If payment
is not made by the due date,
then for each day overdue,
I agree to pay double
in interest? Hana"?
What the heck is this?
That's not the paper I signed!
Don't be silly,
young lady, of course it is.
My writing is not that sloppy!
We can settle it in court,
amigo. I don't mind at all.
You came calling on God. And
I'll bet you have not just one,
but a hundred skeletons
in your closet! Hm?
Michiko!
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Fever hasn't gone down at all.
What?
And why are you
drinking this poison?
'Cause I'm in pain.
Makes my throat feel better.
I only had a little.
What? Are you nuts?
You're not getting any better
'cause you're drinking
this and nothing else!
Yeah, I know.
No, you don't! You don't
know anything! Argh!
Hatchin.
Shut up!
You know I feel like shit.
You could at least be nice.
Well look who's here!
Please, c'mon in.
Yeah, no. Here.
Oh, thank you, dear.
Little bruised,
but they still look tasty.
Um, I need a favor.
What's that?
I have a good feeling.
Everything will be fine.
Hatchin!
Hiroshi?
It is him. Hatchin!
Who the hell are you?
Shit!
Why, Hiroshi?
The bandits are
coming tonight. No question.
That's what my sharp
sixth sense is telling me.
Um, who're you?
Ah, you're awake. I'm
a friend of your daughter's.
There you go, the fragrance
sample you requested from us.
Then, these are--?
Those? Yes, they're mine.
Get out, would you?
Oh, keep it down for a minute.
You know how Feliciano
just got dumped? He's in
a delicate place right now.
Feliciano's about to get lucky.
He's gonna do that lady doctor.
Lady doctor?
They have a
fantastic wine list.
Mm-hm.
Do you not like it raw?
I am a bit apprehensive.
Oh, I'm sure you'll
be just captivated.
It's good to be adventurous.
What do you think?
That's something I should
be asking you, isn't it?
Maybe.
Hey! Hold on!
What're you doing?
So, try to guess the color of
the panties I'm wearing today.
I can't stand
to feel constrained.
Kimonos are smooth.
I love the way they feel.
I truly mean that.
See?
I knew from the day we met.
I knew that you were
the one for me.
Free me.
No, Doc, I can't.
Wait, of course I can!
Just sit tight, Hiroshi.
I'm comin' to find you,
right now.
Do you not like it raw?
Oh, I'm sure you'll be
just captivated.
Hey Doc.
I'm constrained. Free me.
Hiroshi's about to get lucky.
He's gonna do that lady doctor.
Hiroshi!
What the fuck?
This is the void! Nothingness!
Big bang!
I'm cursed!
These guys.
These guys put a curse on me.
They're here.
Hold it!
It's you!
So now you're gonna
become a bandit, huh?
No!
Buddy!
Don't move!
That's it. Out of options.
Oh hi!
So tell me hon, I thought you
were going to take your mom
to see the doctor.
Well, I took her to
a man named Deus. But um--
Oh, no. Not that quack.
Everyone in town
knows his story.
Used to be an unlicensed
general practitioner,
but he was a gambling
addict. He started that
psychic surgery business as
a way to pay back his debts.
"Psychic surgery?"
Yep. He doesn't use
scalpels, he claims he
"extracts the focus of
the disease from the body."
But it's a bunch of hogwash.
Third-rate magic trick,
at best.
No different than pullin'
a rabbit from a hat.
And I bet he did his whole,
"Divine feat, magic God hands"
schtick, right?
No one ever goes
to him anymore.
I knew it.
I'm an idiot. Total idiot.
Please look after Michiko.
If you're God,
then I'll be the Devil.
Get down on your knees,
Deus! And then we'll talk!
Deus! Get out here!
Where is he?
Ow! Please stop!
Remove the curse
you put on me!
What are you talking ab--ow!
I'm talkin' about the
curse you put on me, jerk!
Don't play dumb with me!
What are you doing?
Wait, Hatchin, it's not--. I
get it now. I get everything!
All this?
It's a curse! A curse!
Why you makin' that face?
I see. You're in on it, too!
What's that for? You gonna hit
me with that pipe, are ya?
Then bring it!
S'right. I ain't
scared of you one bit.
The earth is movin'! The
whole damn world is spinnin'!
Michiko?
You got it wrong, Hatchin.
Don't get mad, hear me out.
I've been--
--terribly uncivilized.
Hatchin.
I'm not mad.
So let's get you to
a real clinic. The lady in
the next room said
she would take us today.
But more importantly, we have
to deal with the broken TV.