Police in Terra suffered eight
casualties in a raid commanded
by Inspector Atsuko Jackson,
who is now being
investigated for misconduct.
Officials have accused
Jackson of taking bribes
from the criminal
group, Monstro Preto.
A startling revelation
that came to light thanks
to the brave work of
sergeant-turned-whistle-blower,
Ricardo Solo.
We'll follow this
story as it develops.
But now, a special report
from ace reporter
Daniela Carneiro Junior.
It's a sad story of
desperate boys and girls being
preyed upon and behind it all,
the darkest of black markets.
I, Daniela Carnerio Junior
will pull back the curtain.
Tune in to see the true face
of an evil traveling circus!
Oh, my sweet corned beef!
Please come and satisfy my
hunger with your salty grease!
Te amo.
Hi.
Whassup, kid.
Uh.
Here.
You want this, right?
Go ahead, take it.
Huh?
Is it money you want?
I keep that mostly
at home, though.
All I have here is my bike.
It's a little beat up, but
it used to be quite valuable,
I swear on my life.
Don't hurt me.
I'm a good guy.
I'm on the road following
a traveling circus to rescue
a girl I love named Rita!
I don't care
about Reba whoever.
But I do care about this circus;
you say it's that way, right?
At least I lived.
Hot!
Turns out the tales
of an evil traveling circus
selling children
into slavery are true.
Any child who resists
is brutally beaten!
Hey!
Some fake blood
to make things more dramatic.
Dani.
What are you doing?
Come on, it makes
for good television.
Okay, Zoe, start
wide on the circus.
Then I'll enter, deliver
a spiel, cross to the tent,
meet this little guy over here.
Yeah, let's not do it that way.
Good point.
You shoot the kid first.
I'll spread around more
of this fresh chicken blood
before it goes bad.
Not the problem I had with it.
Yeah whatever,
I'm getting my scoop.
And just what part
of this is a scoop?
I am in charge here!
Roll tape!
Hey!
What the hell?
C'mon kiddo.
Now what are you doing?
Going back to Sao Paraiso.
You can't take my truck!
Hey!
You dumb bitch!
I'm putting your photos online!
The ones where
you're spread like butter!
The world will
see every inch of you!
All done!
What should I--
Lazy, pipsqueak!
I turn around for a second
and you're nappin' on the job?
I wasn't napping.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah.
Go hand out some flyers.
Do you have--
You get them, ya dope!
Move it!
I'm sorry, sir!
Welcome to a world
of make believe,
floating in a
universe of illusion!
It is our hope
that the excitement
you're about to witness
drives you all insane!
So bid your waking life
a fond farewell and prepare
to enter a nightmare!
Let the show begin!
Hey.
--Whoa, hold on.
--Whaddya want?
That a shiner?
You tried to run away,
didn't you?
Leave me alone!
'Ey it's cool.
I'm on your side, kid.
Do you know "As Cinco Horas"?
That's my TV show.
It'll only take one
of my 'special exposés'
to save your poor life.
Now gimme dirt,
and I'll give you this.
What kinda dirt?
Lying, neglect,
physical abuse.
The whole list of
terrible things this circus
has done to you.
Abuse?
This mark?
That's where
a kangaroo hit me.
"Kangaroo?"
And that's code for?
What?
Some psycho, hoppin' around?
Oh, I get it.
They scared you
into keepin' quiet.
Put a knife
to your throat, or worse!
Well, thankfully, I, Daniela
Carneiro Junior have found you!
--I'll tell your story!
--None of that is right.
Truth is, they're taking my
picture for something tomorrow.
I'm just bummed about
this bruise on my face.
Takin' your picture?
What for?
I don't know.
A picture.
"Michiko?"
Good morning!
Did you all get your
beauty sleep last night?
Answer the lady!
Madam Michiko wants
to know if you slept well
--and are ready for pictures!
--Michiko?
Nuno!
Okay, let's get started.
Tell me, child, do you
have any special talents?
Huh-uh.
Well, what have they
got you doin' right now?
Lately, I've just been helping
look after the animals.
I clean up, too.
That's good.
Cleaning is an important skill.
Very good!
And as cute as a button, too!
Hold on.
With this bruise
you're more like a panda!
Nuno!
Yes ma'am?
You can't go turning
our kids into pandas!
Ah!
Uh.
I don't think I--
You little fool.
So sorry, hon.
Now, what's your name?
Uh.
Michiko Menezes!
Your criminal career is over!
I, however, am back on top!
You're Daniela Carneiro!
The pornographer who lures
children into a life of filth!
How many is it?
How many lives have you
destroyed with that camera?
What?
I won't let you
lay a dirty finger
on any of these precious souls!
I'll protect them
with my life, if I have to!
What--the hell?
Time for a little nap,
you pervert.
Nighty-night, smut peddler.
The fuck?
It's getting stormy out there.
Yeah.
Sounds like the
thunder's getting louder.
You seem to make
the best of things.
What?
Just thinkin' out loud.
My clothes!
You're wearing 'em.
Yeah, thanks again.
They look good on you.
Really?
Dinner is served.
Thanks so much.
Looks good.
Dang, Hana, this is good.
You could be a chef.
Damn, you cook good, Hatchin.
Why thank you.
Oh, come on.
What's the hold up back there?
Let's get going!
Awright, awright, we're moving.
Time to clean up.
Huh?
Gotta new group
of kids coming in.
So you need ta clean
all this crap outta here!
--Got it?
--Yes!
Yes, what?
Um, sir.
Good.
And when you've got this place
spotless, report to the Madam.
Yes, sir.
Sorry.
I know the flash is bright.
Now turn so we can
see your pretty face.
Kay.
Oh, very good!
Tonight we'll be
taking you to Wonderland.
You'll have such
a lovely time there!
Is that like a theme park?
Yes!
Theme park!
Well, I'm back.
"I'm back?"
You at least gonna take off
your sunglasses to talk to me?
What happened to your face?
Were you fighting again?
No, no fight.
What are you
even doing out here?
I'm not following you anymore!
Hatchin.
You just gonna
kidnap me again?
Naw, it's not like that.
Then what?
Well, I saw you on
the TV and you looked
so pitiful and depressed.
I wanted to come by
in person and check up on you.
I'm doing fine!
I'm safe, happy and healthy.
I even made a real friend here.
Gave ya some clothes,
too, I see.
Not bad.
The casual pixie look works.
Go away.
Go away!
There's a lady here
named Michiko, too.
You have the same name but
she doesn't treat me like crap.
She actually cares about me!
I... I hate you!
Awright, then.
If that's your choice.
Go be with your new Michiko!
Hatchin!
God, I'm an idiot!
What are you doing?
We're leaving now.
Wear this!
While we're young!
Awright, awright!
Ya!
Your hero has returned!
I will not turn
a blind eye to evil!
Here's the proof!
Children, I've rescued you!
Follow me!
What?
Uh, hey!
No, stop!
Come back!
Aren't children just
so pure in their instincts?
They can always tell who the
bad guy in the situation is.
You liar!
Kids, don't listen to her!
Fight the power!
Join with me--
Sorry, ace.
Go, Nuno;
get the balloon ready.
We can't take it out
in this kinda weather!
Silence!
You do as I say!
Hatchin.
Awright!
We're all set.
Cut the ropes!
Aye-aye!
My scoop's about
to float away.
I won't let it!
I'm taking you down,
Michiko Menezes!
What'd he say?
That's her?
Michiko?
Oh, Hatchin,
you gotta be shittin' me.
You finally stabbed me in the
heart this time, you know that?
What's happening?
We got too much
weight in the basket!
Well we can't dump
any of the cargo overboard;
we haven't even
gotten paid for 'em yet!
Michiko Menezes!
You vile--
How many times do
we have to go through this?
Now, let's try this again!
Later, sucker!
What the hell
you think yer doin'?
You lied about the theme park!
You're gonna
sell us like slaves!
My, aren't you a smart one.
What the--?
But that won't save you.
You're far too adorable
for me to let go of.
Don't touch her!
No giant piece of carny trash
is stealing my Hatchin!
Who's that?
I dunno.
Michiko!
Hang on, I'm comin'!
This isn't happening.
Shoot her, Nuno!
Only tranq darts I got
left are for small game!
Just shoot her, you idiot!
Ah! What the hell!
Don't you jack with me!
Who is this crazy broad?
Hatchin!
Michiko!
I'm the only Michiko
that cares about you!
Don't ever forget it!
Nice one!
Bitch, you stole my cargo!
Screw you, bowling ball!
I don't go down that easy.
Michiko!
What do we do now?
If we show up empty-handed,
they're gonna kill us!
Let's just run away!
You ain't runnin' nowhere!
You're still there?
Just give up already!
Michiko!
Get!
Off!
My!
Balloon!
Michiko!
Hatchin?
I took care of them!
Climb up!
Your face looks like shit.
Leggo of me.
We're over the water, right?
I'll be fine.
You're barely conscious!
Hatchin, just lemme fall in.
I'll survive.
Michiko!
You're right, Michiko.
You will be fine.
Because I'm never
letting go of you again.
The scoop is mine!
What happened?
She lives!
Nice day, huh?
Really?
That's all you have to say?
Yeah, what about you?
Already said it.
Fine.
Thanks n' stuff, Hatchin.
Hey, look is
somebody over there?
Well, guess you
owe me one, Michiko.
Hana!
Rita!
Thank God.
I thought you were dead!
Rita?
I thought it was Reba.
What do you care, lady?
Met some kid looking for you.
Glasses, likes
his corned beef?
That your boyfriend?
No! He's gross!
Good bye, Hana.
Don't worry,
we'll see each other again.
Soon.
Let's go.
Long road ahead.