Okay!
Say "Cheese."
Not what I am expecting.
Young lady, so beautiful.
Boy looks good, also.
One shot together.
For make memories, yes?
Michiko!
Wait for me there.
You're going alone?
No telling what kind
of place I'm walking into.
It's fine.
Don't worry about me;
I'll wrap this up real quick.
Be right back.
All people have dream.
Come here make dream come true.
Want I.D.
and passport.
This cheapest city
in world, small price pay.
Qián.
He saying money first.
Got it right--
Old man, listen to me.
I must of been pickpocketed.
No shit, I had the cash just
a second ago, I swear to you!
Look right here!
This the eye of a liar?
Does he get a word I'm saying?
Not problem.
Seem you have hard luck,
not you fault.
Ok pretty lady find
way make money fast.
Rub some, get rub some.
Make lot, qián.
We sympathize with
the situation you're in.
But what kind of chumps
would we be just to smile
and hand over I.D.s without
some kind of payment?
We are still trying
to run a business here.
A month on your back should
get you on your feet again.
You guys in this together?
Fucking dicks!
Not matter how
lose money, you pay--!
Hey, Michiko?
Excuse me!
Sir!
"Dong gong, sea gong?"
You look lost kid?
Come with me.
Let go of me!
Where are you taking me?
Go through the market
to the main street.
Get away from here.
Yeah but, my friend.
Oh god!
Are you a girl?
All the more reason.
Watch your step.
You know what that's about?
The mother's right over there.
She's trying to get
someone to step on her baby
so she can shake them
down for money.
This place is hell.
And especially unkind
to outsiders like you.
So, go on.
I'm so lost.
Hold up.
Thought I told you
to get outta here.
I don't know what your deal is,
but you'd best leave before
something bad happens.
I'll take you to your room.
What's the hotel?
No, you don't have to.
What's the name of the place?
I'm not real sure,
the sign's in Chinese.
Then draw it for me.
Just try to remember it
as best you can.
Thank you, but I'm sure
I'll be all right.
That market you were in?
It's the turf of
the Heike syndicate.
Not a place a tourist
wants to wander.
I brought some tea.
Can't make it out.
Sorry.
It's just.
I came here with someone.
But she went off on
her own a while ago
and hasn't made it back yet.
She was having some
I.D.s made for us.
While I was looking for her.
I spotted the man who
took her to go get them,
and I tried to follow him.
But, I lost him.
Oh, wait!
While you were out, did you
happen to see this woman?
Ah!
Smile!
Michiko!
Knock it off!
It'll be all right.
But let's eat first, okay?
Bebel, sit down and join us.
All right.
I'll check around before work,
ask if any of the
Heike have seen her.
Look after our guest
while I'm out, Bebel, okay?
Sure.
Now, please eat.
If he says it'll be
all right, it will be.
It'll work out fine,
so just let us guys
handle everything, okay?
Whoops!
Yeah, what?
"Us guys?"
Um, yeah!
Why are you making that face?
While we're at it, what's with
the raggedy-ass boy's haircut?
Like seriously, do you just not
give a shit how ghetto you look?
Everything about you
just screams slob!
It's like; I can't
even look at you!
No slouching!
Stand up straight!
You really are
ghetto trash, aren't you?
Like that skank you're with.
What if I were homeless, huh?
Maybe I like being a slob!
The ugly he-girl yelled
at me like a big meanie!
Don't think you'll
get off that easy.
There's more to do.
That's right.
It's my dad.
He's not gay, if that's
what you're thinking.
He's a dan actor.
The best there is,
hands down!
And I'm going to be a
female-role-playing star,
too, just like him!
Nei Feng-yi, steals the scenes!
And you will see, that nobody
else does it better than he!
He's a world-famous superstar.
But he's something
more than that.
Dad's a real man among men!
You get me?
See, back in the day, when I
was little, he was never home.
He was a low-life bum
who was always off
getting drunk somewhere.
But things changed.
When mom died and left the two
of us on our own, Dad said he'd
straighten up to protect me,
and he became a real father.
Now he's always there.
Got nothing to worry about.
He'll come through for you too.
I believe in him!
No, scratch that!
"Believe" is a lame
word for what I feel.
But if he says
he'll do something,
you can be sure he'll do it.
Every friggin' day, it just
gets blurrier and blurrier.
Fact, I can't see
a damn thing out of it.
It's like I bumped my noggin.
Been popping
painkillers like candy.
Can't even think without them.
Anyway, what I want
to ask you is simple.
I'm looking' for my boss.
Can you find him for me?
I can pay you real nice-like.
Just one catch.
I need the sly bastard alive,
and that's no joke.
I figured he'd stay away
from Monstro territory,
but now I can't find
his punk ass anywhere.
Excuse me, got a package
from Nei Feng-yi for ya, Boss.
So.
Let's say you do find yourself
in charge of the Monstro group.
We don't need
your handsome payment.
What we want is to do
business openly on your turf.
And we would like to pay Monstro
nothing for this privilege.
Understand?
We will never fall
under Monstro's umbrella.
Starting right now,
Monstro and Heike,
we are the best of friends.
When you are in a jam, no longer
must you turn to the gods.
You come to your friends.
Well, "friend", can you
help me outta this jam?
Shinsuke, brah--.
You do see that
I'm hurting' real bad?
So will he.
Ni hao!
Thank you for waiting.
You picked out a fine bird.
It's first-rate!
I'm listening,
so start talking.
If my information
is wrong, forgive me.
But I hear that your people
may have snatched up
a young woman yesterday.
Seems she's with a little girl
I've come to know recently.
Could I possibly
ask you to free her?
You know I am truly enraptured
by your angelic singing voice.
And this duck you've
given me is quite delicious.
Can you believe how
I am devouring it?
I should stop,
but it is too divine.
Since it's too late
to give it back.
Are you performing tonight?
Yes.
I suppose I have kept
you waiting long enough
Okay!
I'll arrange for
this woman to undergo
a contest of chance, yes?
We will let them
decide her fate.
Even we are too afraid
to go against them.
They'll get their revenge.
Rock, paper, scissor,
three rounds!
It'll be nice and quick.
Woman!
Rock, paper, scissor!
I ain't playing no game!
Oh, we not playing around.
Your life is on the line here!
Wen!
You, huh?
Look.
That's what I'll play first.
I'm not trying
to trick you, I promise.
Ready?
Here we go!
Rock--
Yo, bitch, quit fucking around
before I smash your face!
Oh, shove it up your ass!
Listen, this is one of Dad's.
He's a master of
every aspect of the dan.
Guaranteed to wipe
that dumb frown away.
What the hell?
Something awful must
of happened to Dad!
Let's go!
Grab a weapon, too.
Come on!
I give up!
It's completely hopeless!
Hope! Less!
Don't you believe in him?
You're a man, right?
I guess, but you saw.
I fell and my stick broke!
Everything's going to be fine!
I can feel it, okay?
Hold on!
I'll stand in for her.
You'll what?
What the hell does that mean?
Do with me,
what you'd do with her.
So you think,
we should whore you out?
Instead of this
feisty little minx?
Is that it?
That's correct.
Any man who heard you sing
would fall instantly in love.
You'd be our
most popular escort.
But I really don't want
to see you like that, Nei;
and I'd give you a pass if
I could, but my hands are tied.
It would set
a very bad precedent.
Not to mention, people
would say I'd gone queer
for the tranny songbird.
Put on a blindfold and run
from one end to the other.
A simple chicken race.
All you have to do is run.
And hope the god
of victory smiles upon you.
Do that, and I
forget everything.
Clean slate.
Fine, I accept.
Someone fetch a rope
and tie the woman to Nei.
Your precious damsel and I, will
both be gambling on the gods.
Ladies and gentlemen: Tonight's
opera, "The Peacock Wooed
by the Duck," is scheduled
to begin at this time.
However, the arrival
of Nei Fong-yi,
pride and star of Seentwan,
has been unexpectedly delayed.
The performance will
begin very, very shortly.
We ask that you
please remain patient.
Thank you.
You ready?
We won't die here, assholes!
We won your fucking game!
Now you can honor
your deal or die!
Guan Yu, god of war!
Furious in the face of defeat.
What a foolish god!
Did she ask you for help?
No, it was me who
wanted to play the hero.
Scared me shitless.
Well, it didn't show.
So thanks.
Hey, come on!
You got to hurry!
What are you doing here?
You should be at home.
I told you to look
after our guest, right?
I'm sorry, Dad.
But still.
How many times I got
to tell you something?
Did I not tell you
to wait for me?
And I told you
not to worry, too!
Right?
Why are you always
running off on your own,
getting into trouble and causing
me all kinds of headaches?
I'm running out
of goddamn lives here
and it's all your fault, missy!
You hear me? Your fault!
Ladies and gentlemen,
we thank you for your patience.
Michiko, I'm sorry.