Hey.
You sure it'll take
two days to fix?
Cause you better not be
talking outcher ass, old man.
Sorry.
We're checked in.
Uh, thanks for this.
Is something wrong?
Nah, I'm fine.
Just bored.
Hold on a second.
You smell like ass.
When was your last shower?
--Five da--
--Get up!
Can't wash my hair
with just soap.
What am I doin'?
Yo, Hatchin!
Up and-at-em.
What's goin' on?
I can still smell your hair
halfway across the room!
You want me to wash it
with a bar o' soap?
Don't you sass me!
Wait.
Did you take
a shower yesterday?
Wha--?
Whadaya mean?
Of course I did.
Then how come you didn't know
there's no shampoo in there?
Quit hittin' me just
'cause you're mad!
Can it.
If you hair smelled like roses,
we wouldn't hafta
go through this.
Just go buy shampoo.
Store's down the street.
Shouldn't take you long, okay?
Sorry I hit you.
Like roses, huh?
Well, underneath
the roses is dirt.
--So technically--
--Buy the damn shampoo!
Hey!
Girly!
These waters
belong to the Ventos.
You wanna pass,
you gotta pay the tax.
Unless you want us to hurt ya.
Hey, nice kicks.
No, get off!
Dude, you okay?
Now you went n' pissed me off!
C'mon!
Help me toss her over!
There's another salon
in town a bit closer,
but my wife swears
this one's the best.
Run by a foreigner
named Anastacia.
She's good, though.
Beautiful, too.
Like a Russian model.
Maybe we shouldn't.
Maybe we should.
Don't play games with me.
Life's playing the game.
It finally gave you
what you're looking for.
And it put me right here,
within your grasp...
Your hair is so pretty,
I'll just trim the split-ends.
...No, it's--It's someone else.
You've already suffered
so much for someone
you may never see again.
Let me heal
those wounds for you.
I saw you yesterday.
People call me Anastacia.
Did you enjoy my tobacco?
Tobacco?
That's right.
My husband often likes
to borrow my tobacco.
I say borrow, but he is always
taking it without asking.
Still, it is mine.
Too bad he doesn't
seem to care.
So then.
Where are you from?
I take it you're
just passing through?
Yeah.
Ah.
That is too bad.
I'll give ya a lift back.
Here.
I'll come by your room tomorrow
afternoon at around one.
If I'm reading you wrong,
don't answer the door.
...some boy in a bath
towel attacked me with
two of his dumb friends!
And they held me down
and stole my shoes!
--Again!
--Bruno.
Hey?
Are you listening to me?
'Ey, when'd you get here?
What?
You mean you really didn't hear
a single thing I just said?
I got the gist of it.
Get shampoo?
See?
You really weren't listening!
Like I said, I was attacked
by a boy in a towel
who stole my money and shoes.
That's why I couldn't
buy any shampoo!
You lost your shoes
and your money?
I ain't falling
for a lie like that.
You should learn
to respect your elders.
--How can you--
--Shut up!
Hey! Cool it with the crazy!
Whadda ya think you're doin'?
Knock it off, now!
You gonna hang
around here all day?
Shut up.
Don't be mad.
I was a jerk.
Y'haven't had
lunch yet, right?
Here, take this.
Go get some shampoo, too.
S'not like that.
I missed the boat out today.
So.
I don't know.
Why are we doing this?
Do we need a reason?
It's messed up.
I know, it is.
Am I being too forceful?
It's just--You're married.
I only found out 'cause
I was at your salon.
Must mean fate's
bringing us together.
Please, just stop.
You don't believe in fate?
That's what brought me here.
What if you hadn't
been waiting for me?
What if we never
had this conversation?
Could you go through life
wondering, "What if?"
I know I can't.
Wait!
I'm with another man.
And I'm a married man,
so what?
No, it's different.
I'm in love.
Tell me, does this man
love you back?
He has to; I'm all he's got.
If that's true,
then where is he?
Shut up!
Shut up.
'Cause I wouldn't leave.
I could never hurt
a woman like you.
So, what's your name?
Michiko Malandro.
Go on!
She needs a wash.
Sure, no problem.
What're you lookin' at?
Sit down.
I'd like a shampoo, please.
The way you two get along--
is she your mom?
No.
I figured as much.
But you know, they say
the closer you are,
the more you argue.
Never heard that.
Oh, well.
It's just something
people tell me.
Though I can't speak
from my own experience.
My husband and I haven't fought
in years, and we're still close.
Is that right?
I wouldn't know.
Long ago these waters
were full of healthy fish
swimming all over.
They were free to go wherever,
whenever they wanted.
Strange as this sounds,
you actually remind me
of those fish.
And I want to
swim alongside you.
And what is it
you want us to do?
I ain't so sure.
Michiko.
I'm in love with you.
Hey, Hatchin.
Wouldn't it be nice
to float around and do
whatever you want, whenever?
It's like--
People aren't meant to
spend their whole lives
swimming in just
one body of water.
You mean an affair.
That's crazy!
All I'm saying is
I wanna do a better job
of going with the flow.
Like a big fish.
Jesus, an affair.
Don't you go
makin' things up!
Then why're you
all worked up?
Sounds bad.
What're you doing?
I've decided to go
look for Hiroshi on my own.
What the hell you
talkin' about girl?
You ain't gonna
find him by yourself!
Don't touch me!
I'll be fine!
Just leave me alone!
I don't need you anymore!
Ow!
Why did you do that?
Goodbye, Michiko!
Punkasses!
Gimme back the money
and shoes you stole!
I'll fight'cha if I have to!
Cram a sock in it, girl.
These?
Sure, I'll give
'em back to ya!
But let's have more
fun than a fist-fight.
Just name it, I'll stomp ya!
Right.
Whoever can get 'em from the
bottom of the river first,
keeps them.
And that.
Well if I win,
I get your luggage, too.
All right fine, but if
I win I get your boat.
Deal.
Hello again.
I thought these might look
kind of nice on the girl.
How'd you know
where we were staying?
I asked at the front desk.
Is there other way
I should've known?
No.
Well.
Give the girl my regards.
Were you hoping Bruno
would leave me for you?
Go!
Get her!
You are fooling yourself.
How much woman
do you think you are?
He'll go cold.
He'll lose interest,
and forget you're even there.
He'll do to you
what he did to me.
Do you really want to give up
everything you are--For
a man who acts this way?
What about you?
What are you gonna do?
I'll be fine.
You know, Bruno likes to
think of himself as a fish,
swimming freely
wherever he wants.
But what he really likes--Is
for me to come along
and scoop him up in my net.
Now.
Let me ask you something.
What did you ever see in him?
He said, "Sorry.
He left you those,
but he couldn't let
you have the boat."
What is it, child?
My birthday.
I just turned ten.
Oh!
Parabéns!