Which way?
Off your ass, kid!
How much farther
do we have to walk?
And what the heck
are you doing?
You really want to know, huh?
That's just my hysteria.
Hysteria?
Such a puny-ass town.
And I'm the one
who drove it to ruin.
Destroyed it.
Yeah, fuck this place.
Hello?
Satoshi?
I found old man Tito for you.
Yo!
You Tito Ducha?
The weaselly old prick's been
trying to convince me he ain't.
Just had lunch at your place.
Wife offered up
quite the spread.
That's a fine lady you got.
Everything was delicious.
I'm not him.
I swear!
You got the wrong guy!
Then she don't matter to you?
Can't understand a word
this fool is saying.
All right.
It's been real, but
it's time to finish this.
Wait hold up a minute!
I just had a great idea!
Ten minutes.
If he's still kicking
after that, we spare him.
Course, your average Joe
wouldn't be able to last
more than like,
seven, eight tops.
Be pretty sweet
if he survives!
Can anyone even go that long?
Oh yeah, sure.
My old man did.
Then again, he was never
really the same after that.
Mostly he just
drools a lot and shit.
I think I could do it though.
Go ten minutes
without losing my marbles.
Fuck yeah.
You could definitely make it,
no doubt in my mind.
Yeah, right?
Yo!
Oh shit, Satoshi?
Don't matter how many
piss-ant soldiers you send,
they won't save you!
If we do this,
we do it one on one.
Come alone, I'll take you on!
Yeah?
Remind me.
Which of us made
the first move on who?
You know something?
I been sitting here, thinking
about you for a while now.
Then all of a sudden, the phone
scares the crap outta me,
and it's you.
Got to say, though, Satoshi.
I was really hoping
for an apology.
Deep from the heart.
Good chance I'd forgive you.
So which is it?
Which is what?
Are we going to do this
or ain't we?
Yeah, okay, that
"which is it", huh?
So you're really
that eager to die.
In case you forgot, you only
become boss because of me.
Me.
I was the one who
did all the killing.
Remember that?
You done?
Oh, I'm at my breaking point.
Say it!
Say it to me straight up
that you hate me!
Casa Vento.
If you don't come to me,
I'm coming for you.
Yeah, um.
Here!
Eat up!
Will you please get out?
I am not sharing
a room with you.
Look, kiddo.
I don't think you appreciate
the position you're in.
On top of that, some
assassins are on their way
here to kill me.
Without my help, you'll get
caught in the crossfire
and wind up dead.
Can't have that.
What?
It's more dangerous
being anywhere near you.
You'll end up dead
no matter what!
I am not ready to die
and leave things like this.
You see?
That's why you got
to stick with me.
Nonsense!
Didn't you hear me?
This is not working!
Suit yourself.
Great.
So where am I
supposed to sleep?
No!
Not a chance!
For starters, when was
the last time you bathed?
Last time I what?
Don't you smell yourself?
I can barely stomach it!
How long since your last shower?
How the fuck should I know?
If you're sleeping in here, I'll
have to find somewhere else to--
Why are your pants off?
Ain't it obvious?
No it is not!
That was ripe!
Um.
Are you the Satoshi?
Really?
What do you mean?
Ah.
So, you're itching to hear
all about Hiroshi, huh?
Fine, I'll talk.
At first glance, ain't much
to see when it comes to him.
He's a bony-ass son-of-a-bitch
and fragile as he looks.
Did you know that?
Even so, he's still the best.
Back when I was running Monstro,
a lot of shit went down.
Everybody was glaring at me
with that fire in their eyes,
know what I mean?
That look that says,
"Let your guard down and Pow!"
But Hiroshi wasn't like that.
We'd known each other
ever since we were kids.
He just understood me.
He was the only one
I could tell everything to.
Even the embarrassing shit.
And always, he would
lend me a sympathetic ear.
What's that look on your face?
Forget it.
It's nothing.
You got something
to say, spit it.
From what I've heard, I get
the feeling he's not so great.
Honestly, I bet Hiroshi
wasn't even listening to you
when you were talking.
Probably thinking about
what he wants for dinner.
Or some other
dumb thing like that.
I knew him pretty damn well
and that's not how he was.
He paid me his full attention,
always listening with both ears.
No way!
Hiroshi's not like that!
Pipsqueak.
Why's that wretched bimbo been
dragging you across the country?
Do you know something
about Hiroshi?
I think at first that was
what she must've thought.
Just at first?
Yeah, cause I didn't know
anything about him then.
I've never even met him.
So, I couldn't really
be much help to her.
Even so she stuck with me.
Then you just been
stringing me along, huh?
Shit, you never even met him?
No, but I know
where to find him.
Yeah, where?
I can't say.
I'll let you in on something.
That cold-ass bitch
is still using you.
That's for damn sure.
Michiko told me
to believe in her.
And she made me a promise,
that she'd always protect me.
Do you believe in her?
Yes.
I'm positive
I'll see her again.
Which means she must
know where he is, too then.
--are saying both the freight
train derailment, and the bar
shootout that preceded it, may
be part of an ongoing series
of gang vendettas.
Sources say the violence
stems from an internal feud
within Monstro, as well
as a power struggle
with rival faction,
the Heike.
However, that hasn't been
confirmed at this time.
In response to this latest
outbreak of bloodshed,
officials have raised the
alert in surrounding areas
to Level Four.
It's the first
Level Four in ten years.
The last time coincided with
the turmoil caused by Monstro's
initial rise to power,
indicating the severity
of this current crisis.
Dammit!
Here they come.
Stop the vehicle!
Pull the vehicle over now!
You expect me to stop?
Car Five-Five to Dispatch,
we've got a rollover
on Route One-Seventy.
A vehicle we were pursuing,
about eight kilometers
from the checkpoint.
One suspect is confirmed alive.
A female, approximately
twenty to thirty years old.
Uh, the suspect's waking up!
Hey.
You all right?
Put the weapon down!
Hold on.
--Don't do it!
--Stay back, pigs!
Your friends try and shoot
me; they'll turn your body
to Swiss cheese.
Quit worrying and go to sleep.
I can't I'm too nervous.
But you should get some rest.
I'll take half an hour
then wake me up.
'Kay.
How far you planning on going?
I don't really know yet.
They're here!
All right, have fun boys!
Copy that.
You're a freaking pant load
and a half, Captain Diarrhea.
Kid!
Hide on the
other side of the bed!
What are you
pussies so scared of?
He's only one man.
That's one down.
There he is!
Hell, yeah!
You too.
Let's go!
Hey, he went down!
Yo, pipsqueak!
I'll go aim through the door.
If any of them come down
the hole, just blast away!
Yeah, but--!
Don't worry.
Till you tell me where he is,
we're stuck together.
So try not to die before then.
We're screwed!
We're totally--!
Yo.
Come out and play.
Satoshi's lost his damn mind.
I'm outta here!
Car's bulletproof!
Hey!
Not going to work.
Bulletproof, right?
Come on.
Let's do this outside.
All right.
If you're kicking after
ten minutes, I'll forgive you.
I still think you can make it.
No doubt in my mind.
Look, I swear
I never meant to--.
Go on.
Hang in there,
just five minutes longer.
Get up.
I guess we were both wrong
about what you could do.
Shinsuke, what the
fuck happened to you?
Requesting backup
on Route Eighty-Eight.
We've set up a blockade
at an intersection
about fifteen kilometers
outside of Goinia.
Pull it over.
This is where you get out.
I'll keep my promise to you.
Take me there.
Here they come.
Huh, looks like the woman's
the only one in the car.
That's not what we were told.
Goinia.
That has to be it.
Here it goes, Hatchin.
Move it!