First time I ever killed
a man, was back when I was
still just a
snot-nosed little punk.
Just wanted to know what
that kinda score felt like.
Why are you quitting, Jair?
One day out of the blue,
I started crying like a baby.
So I said one more
job and I'm out.
Don't make any
sense to me, old man.
But I got a real bitch
of a swan song for ya.
Tricky.
Listen, junior.
I've never used more than
one bullet on any prey
I've hunted in my life.
Understand?
Yeah, okay, I got ya.
Now.
We got a piece of shit
escaped convict.
A piece of shit cop.
And a sneaky little
piece of shit Monstro punk.
All three of 'em
done a number on me.
And any one would be
a satisfying last job.
And where am I likely
to find these marks now?
Like her.
That one's been
bouncing all over the place.
Latest word is she's headed up
north on Route Three-Thirty-One.
She should pass through
here in two days on her way
to Arónpolis.
So, which one of 'ems
the biggest skidmark?
Definitely not what
I woulda guessed.
Looks like he has to concentrate
just to keep breathin'.
I know, right?
Yet he's safe in Mãn
after trying to kill me.
That's messed up.
If you ask me, seems
a character like that
should be the first to die.
Then it's settled.
This is Car Double-O Three,
pursuing wanted escaped convict
Michiko Malandro, northbound
on Route Three-Thirty-One.
Suspect fleeing toward
Arónpolis, possibly making
a run for the border.
This is HQ.
Pursuit outside our
jurisdiction is not authorized.
Apprehend suspect
before she crosses border.
Use of firearms is permitted.
Hey pig!
If you don't stop chasin'
me while you can,
you'll be pushing up raisins!
--That's daisies!
--Open the window!
I've got a shot!
Go!
Michiko.
Look out!
Okay, sorry.
You know I don't like
to wait, Shinsuke.
What's your problem?
Huh?
Can't fight the
call of nature, man!
I just dropped a huge dump.
Had me twisting in pain.
Hey!
Wanna see it?
I'll send you a picture!
Where you at right now?
Want me to guess?
Don't you ever shut your mouth?
What's with the crappy mood?
You're the one who gave
Michiko the gun, right?
Oh that.
Surprised you, huh?
Hell yeah it did, which is
why I'm done with you, man.
Fucking done.
Aw come on, you really
mad about that?
Man, you're brutal,
can't you take a joke--?
I hired Jair to take
your dumb ass out.
Jair?
You kiddin' me?
Why would you do that?
You the one who
said I was brutal.
After all we been through?
I don't understand!
Hello?
Fuck!
If I said I was in a tight spot,
would that be an understatement?
This ain't fun, man,
Jair's the real thing.
What do I do now?
Um.
For starters,
you could apologize.
Yeah that's right.
I could just
apologize real good.
Michiko, we're smoking.
So, a woman ran out on you.
And you lose your
mind and your spine?
That's all it took to bring the
"Murano Samurai" to his knees.
Huh?
Leave me alone.
You don't know
anything about me.
I've realized my future isn't
in this place anymore, Jim.
That's why I have to go.
Nor do I really care.
But she'll come back to you
if you got enough dough, right?
I hear that's what you've been
telling people around town.
Yeah.
It's the truth.
With money I could
buy her a future.
Pick one.
I don't kill women
or children!
That's no woman.
That right there's your future.
The one you want
so bad you could scream.
I don't kill women or children.
Don't move.
Who the hell are you?
Let's just say I represent the
interests of Satoshi Batista.
So the fucker's
still alive, huh?
You're a lively one, ain'tcha?
Guess you're not afraid'a
me pullin' this trigger.
I like your nerve.
Let's have a contest.
To the death.
When you feel like you
got me in your sights
and can make it count,
then take your shot.
Miss your chance
and you're through.
Here.
Get some shut-eye; I'll
leave you some ammunition
at the front desk,
first thing in the morning.
If you wanna junk it,
I'll take if off your hands--
a hundred arcas.
How 'bout you just
do your job and fix it?
Watch how you
speak to me, lady.
Sorry.
Could you please fix it, sir?
Okay.
I'll explain this
for your sake.
Your idiot friend's got
a bike with a rotten engine
that needs to be swapped out.
And I don't have a replacement.
--Big shocker--
--Michiko!
My son's got a shop
of his own out in Corpo,
the next state over.
You can get one from him
if you can find a ride.
I see.
And where do you think
we could-- Michiko!
I gotta get to Planície,
and I'm in a hurry.
If Corpo's close,
why don'tcha go for us,
say hello to your son?
My back's killin' me and drivin'
only makes it feel worse.
I'm not runnin'
any damn errands.
Sorry, miss.
That's too bad.
Then I'll take your truck
and pick it up for you.
We'll throw in a nice massage
for your poor old back, too.
Sound good?
Be back real soon.
Why do I have to be the one
to rub his dumb back?
'Cause I hafta drive, Hatchin.
And if we wanna get
the bike fixed we gotta
give 'im something in return.
That's just how it is.
Be a good girl.
But he's fine!
He's full of it!
His back doesn't hurt at all!
Put the pedal down,
don't let her get away.
What are you laughing at,
old geezer?
Hook it to the right.
Okay, now left.
Idiot!
Damn it.
That's right.
I shoulda called
Satoshi by now.
You're one lucky junkie.
'Cause this?
This was love at first sight.
Hey.
I'm gonna give you a signal.
When I do,
you slam on the brakes.
She'll pass, and I'll
finish this dance.
Just keep driving.
Okay, old man,
make your move.
Where the hell are you?
You're not a woman.
You're money.
You're my future.
Damn it!
Shit!
Old-ass hippie.
Akasha.
We gotta postpone this.
The cops are on our butts.
Want a ride?
You'll have to
leave that, though.
Can't have you blowing my
brains out in the car, right?
Fine.
Persistent.
Son of a bitch.
One shot wasn't enough, huh?
Ah, he's done.
Who was he, anyway?
Hell if I know.
I see.
Aw, you kiddin' me?
That better be a goddamn ghost.
Motherfucker!
No wai--!
The hell is this?
It's like--It hurts.
It hurts real bad.