Hat-chin.
Hatchin, hm?
"They don't look special;
just shiny rocks."
That's what you're
thinking, right?
Yeah.
I can assure you if you
keep thinking that,
you'll never experience the true
magic each stone holds within.
This one is known
as a "Força Piedra"
It's a kind of miracle stone.
Keep it in your pocket
wherever you go to drive away
all manner of evil.
And, if you like that,
you'll love this.
Dirt from under the
fingernails of God.
Add it to boiling
water, drink up,
and you'll get
supernatural powers.
Mostly. Results may vary.
What's this old lady's story?
They say she speaks
to the spirits.
Come here!
What?
On your lap?
They're all outta chairs,
what's the friggin deal?
No thanks.
Why you giving me a face
like I'm some kinda
common street criminal?
I always have this face.
Such a pity.
A person isn't just
born with a face like that.
It grows from within.
You got that?
A person's face reflects the
energy they keep inside of them.
And yours has some
deep dark juju indeed.
Really?
That bad?
Bad is too soft,
she's the worst I've seen!
What do we do, Hatchin?
She says you're
the worst ever.
Now that you understand,
what would you say,
if I could read your futures?
Help you dodge any darkness
that might escape from her
and harm you both?
You'd want to
hear that, right?
You're serious?
Yeah, but it'll cost you.
What, is something wrong?
He's somewhere in this city.
Hiroshi, I mean.
It's all coming together.
Ah, shit!
That's the
fingernail dirt working!
See!
You really believe that lady?
Seems legit to me, here catch.
"Força Pedra" for ya!
All yours honey.
This ain't no act,
little girl!
These rolled back eyes,
are windows into the trance!
My spirit is venturing
onto the astral plane!
Now I'm flying!
Ahhh!
Higher and higher!
I'm up among
the Constellations!
I'm one with
the river of time!
I'm traveling to your future!
My future?
Yes, you!
You're looking
for someone, I see.
A man!
A man?
Yes.
I can see the
man's glowing aura!
Aura?
It's him!
The man you're looking for!
Oh, joy of joys!
Now I see a house!
Two kids!
A happy family!
When's this happen?
Where is he?
This future is near!
All you must do is try,
and your fates will meet!
--And you, child!
--What?
I see you too!
I see your right foot!
A small misfortune to it.
Will cause a greater one!
Stop!
Do not chase
the one who flees!
Don't go!
Don't climb the mountain!
I hear gunshots!
Death by the ocean!
You will die!
You!
Will!
Die!
Yeah, so, uh, those magic
stones do work, right?
Haven't failed me yet.
They'll protect her?
Sure.
Like, save her life and stuff?
Why of course.
Do not waste your
money on that junk!
How about I throw in
the fingernail dirt?
We'll call it the
"Happy Ending Combo Pack",
and I'll go
twenty percent off!
This is stupid,
I don't need it!
Hatchin, wait!
Hold on!
Where you think
you're going?
Do whatever
you want, Michiko.
I'm fed up with all of your--
Poop?
Hey, that's your right foot.
See, Hatchin!
The old lady knows what
she's talking about.
Now get back here!
Fine!
Yo, Hatchin.
Let's go out, huh?
I'm not going.
Okay.
Just to be safe though,
don't leave until I get back.
You hear me, girl?
Yeah.
Yo!
Yo, Hatchin.
Welcome back.
What?
What happened?
Got this.
It's Hiroshi.
That's him, Hiroshi?
Yeah, your father, remember?
Anyway, I found this street
artist who sketched him for me.
Pretty good, huh?
Oh, and I got you those.
Try them on.
What's going on?
With this picture.
We'll find him easy!
Right?
No! With the shoes!
How did you get these shoes?
I found them.
Where was that?
A shoe store.
And did you pay for the shoes?
Or, did you just take them?
Did you?
Umm.
Did you steal them?
These insinuations are
bullshit you know that?
The shoe store
guy gave them to me.
As a free shoe
Sample Day, thingy.
Aw, man.
Now where'd that
girl run off to?
Hang on!
Hi there.
What food you want?
No, I wanna work here.
Please.
I no hire little kid.
I'll work really hard.
Everyone always say that.
Even grown-up people.
But no one ever
keep up with me.
And you know why?
It because Lam Yin
kitchen master!
Now please get hell out.
I'm not leaving!
How do you know that
I'm not some kind of
kitchen master, also?
You can't kick me out until
you at least let me show you!
Please just give me a chance.
What your name, kid?
It's Hana More-, Hana.
Hana-more-hana?
No, just... Hana.
Have ID?
I don't.
Why you waste my time?
Wait hold on!
Why you no have shoes on?
Because.
I haven't paid for them yet.
That's why I need to get a job.
You right before
I should not kick you out.
I should give you
try out first.
Since you still just
a baby, I give you only
half normal wages for day,
so, you get ten Arca.
But you still
must try out first.
Today you work for free.
And cause you have no ID,
you work free tomorrow, too.
After that, you get ten Arca!
Yes, sir.
Got that, Hana?
'Kay, but.
Could you please
not call me that?
What for?
You just told me
that Hana is your name!
I don't like it.
Whenever I hear it
anymore it reminds me
of this bad man's face.
Girl always so damn picky!
What name you want then?
Hat-chin.
Okay, Hatchet!
Hatchet?
Now go memorize diner menu.
And when I go touch my ear
like this, it signal.
So you watch out.
Watch out for what?
Five guests welcome!
What you want eat!
Yo pops, you seen this dude?
Goes by the name,
Hiroshi Morenos?
No, ma'am.
Can't say that I have.
Try pretending this
picture's my tits.
Anything now?
Well?
Sorry.
What about this one?
It's a little girl.
Sorry.
So.
C'mon, let's go!
No wonder!
They don't look
related at all!
I wish you wouldn't run off
and scare me like that!
Where'd you go anyway?
Three pot sticker up!
The signal?
Dine-and-dash!
Skipping out on bill punishable
by death in my diner!
I remember your face!
I see you next time
I Kung Fu chop you!
You know Hatchet, I have a
daughter about as old as you.
But she way more capable.
Smarter than you.
No make mistake.
I'm sorry, sir.
It like you not here at all.
I don't need you.
But, I nice guy.
I give you try out.
Remember, you must work
free tomorrow, too, though.
More capable my butt!
You, are not a nice guy,
you're a jerk!
Today's the first day
of the new me.
I'm psyched and ready to go.
Hey!
Oh, that guy, huh.
I'm trying to remember
where I've seen him around.
What did you say?
Where'd you see him, huh?
I need to know!
C'mon, Gramps!
Cough it up!
Oh!
Yeah, that one nicer house,
just outside the favela!
Thanks, Gramps.
You sure know how
to please a girl.
I'm going!
No!
Get any closer and I'll cut
your face, you dumb bitch!
Just shut up and
pay me, you jerk!
Hey!
Those are my shoes!
Stop!
Do not chase
the one who flees!
Don't climb the mountain!
Where'd he go?
There she is!
I hear gunshots!
You will die!
I see her!
Down in there!
Oh yeah, the stupid rock.
Aw! Fuck me!
Antonio, you okay?
Hey!
Move it, you brat!
I coulda burned off
that bird-nest hairdo.
Stupid kid!
What do ya mean?
You came charging
right at me!
Hang on.
Is that you, Hatchin?
What are you doing here,
dressed like that?
Dine and dash.
--You stole?
--Not me!
Move it you old skank!
You're blocking my gun here!
Old skank, what?
I said get outta here bitch.
Or you want me to blow a hole
in them tig ol' bitties?
You got any idea who you're
talking to, little shit?
Whatever, old lady,
I don't need to put up!
I'm sorry I didn't
quite hear you.
What'd you call me?
An old what?
Say it again.
I dare you!
Last chance fuck face!
Old?
Older sister?
That's much better.
I ain't gonna forget this!
The hell was all this?
It's nothing.
What's with the dress?
I found him.
I found Hiroshi!
What are you selling?
Honey, get out here!
What is it?
Hello.
Nice to meet you, Fa--.
Hey, what are you doing?
That's Hiroshi, right?
My Dad?
--Let go!
--Not him.
What do ya mean?
It's gotta be, he looks
just like the picture.
Look I got the
wrong guy, okay!
That guy was not
your father.
Didn't have the
swagger at all.
Let's go.
Are you sure
that it's not him?
Jeez, drop it, will ya?
Is the sketch even right?
Does it actually
look like him at all?
The features are close enough,
but it doesn't matter.
No sketch artist in the world
could capture his cool.
If you're gonna blame anything,
blame that dumb fortune teller.
She didn't get
a single thing right.
It was a total rip-off.
Magic rocks, my ass.
She was right, though.
About what exactly?
You still look like you're
pretty damn alive to me!
That hag can go to hell.
Next time I see her,
I'm smacking her!
And don't you try to stop me.
I don't care what Michiko says;
I think the fortune was right.
It was the sketch
that was wrong.
But still.
If I really had met
my father here tonight.
I wonder.
What kind of face
would I have made then?