We made it.
Yeah.
Almost time.
We'll always
be together, Hatchin.
Officers say the suspect,
Michiko Malandro,
stole a patrol car and led
police on a high-speed pursuit,
which finally came to end when
the suspect drove into a river.
After pulling the vehicle out,
authorities failed to find
any trace of Malandro.
Tracking teams are currently
searching the area for
any clues as to
her whereabouts.
Authorities are cautioning all
local citizens that until
she is found or killed, Michiko
Malandro must be considered
at-large, and
extremely dangerous.
Weather coming up
after the break.
Hey!
Hey, let go!
You don't have to drag me!
You looking for someone, pal?
Yeah, where's your boss?
Juninho, there's some guy,
wants to see you.
What guy?
How many?
What's my dose?
For an adult?
Three pills, I think.
Then double the dose
should be doubly effective.
What are we doing
wasting time in this place?
We're going to get
their help finding Hiroshi.
I mean it's not like
you know where he is.
What ya doing?
Leaving!
I'm no help to you anymore,
so just let me go!
Sorry, kid.
Why not?
Put me down!
You're the only one
dumb and brave enough
to defy Satoshi Batista.
I did see a little girl like
this, but I'm not sure
she's the one
you're looking for.
I don't want to be rude and
send you on a wild goose chase.
Yeah thanks.
Now where'd you see her?
Was she with a guy?
Yeah, big ole fro.
Had a real dangerous
look in his eye, too.
Got it.
Thanks.
Hey.
Sir, may I speak to you?
My partners here
say you asked to see me.
She look familiar?
You know her Dad?
Hiroshi Morenos.
Hiroshi Morenos?
Are you paying for this info?
So, he was here?
You run with this guy, huh?
I just realized, I don't think I
ever actually caught your name.
Satoru.
All right, Mr. Satoru.
You shared with me,
now I'll share with you.
Believe it or not, I'm looking
for the little girl's dad, too.
He ran up quite the
debt with my operation
before skipping
town in the night.
I hate having to be this way.
But don't blame me for this,
blame your ole pal, Hiroshi.
You're a two-bit conman.
No, sir.
I'm the next
fucking presidente!
Suspect spotted!
Look out for a woman
in an army coat!
Back the fuck off!
We're at the bazaar!
Suspect re-acquired,
pursuing on foot!
Freeze, lady!
Suspect appears to be
leaving the bazaar
and entering Market Square.
She is armed and
extremely dangerous.
Request backup!
If you want your money back,
don't bother me.
Find Hiroshi Morenos.
I can't hear you!
Okay!
Much better.
And I promise I won't tell
anyone you pissed your pants
just now.
Police caution that
the female has fired
several rounds at officers.
I'm now hearing that authorities
have confirmed the shooter
is the escaped felon,
Michiko Malandro.
Officers believe she's holed up
inside the traveling carnival
at the Market Square Bazaar.
Escaped felon Michiko Malandro
continues her standoff
with police in the
Market Square carnival.
Officers on the scene report
the unstable woman is holding
three staff members hostage.
Authorities are urging
citizens to avoid the entire
Market Square district
until Malandro is arrested
or eliminated.
Shut up, lady!
I said, shut the fuck up!
Status report.
Miguel, talk.
Same as last time, sir.
With the hostages there, we're
trying to avoid a shoot-out.
All it takes is one psycho.
What a damn mess.
We're going in now!
Sir!
Jeez, what now?
Oh, the gun?
I'm not going to use it
on you guys, okay?
Now shut the hell up!
Drop it!
She broke through!
Oh shit.
Don't let her get away!
One of the hostages is down!
We need first aid!
Dammit, Miguel.
This was her gun?
Yes, sir.
Bag it and tag it.
Should make our case airtight.
Sir.
What are we going
to do about this?
Pin the shooting on Malandro.
And you forget this happened.
Are we clear?
Captain!
What now?
Word's come down from the top.
They're sending a special
detective to handle
the Malandro case.
They want her brought in alive.
Yeah, understood.
Dismissed.
Sir!
Stay cool, Miguel.
You're fine.
I'm the one up shit creek, now.
Breaking news.
Escaped convict, Michiko
Malandro, shot a hostage
while attemping to flee police.
The victim was
rushed to a hospital,
but died of massive blood loss.
Until now, Malandro's path
of destruction had been
mostly confined to the police
and her known enemies.
Residents in the area are urged
to exercise extreme caution.
No way.
I'm leaving.
No you ain't, kid.
You are such a liar!
You said I'm free if
I tell you where he is.
Then you say you won't
let me go until we get here.
And now you're just
sitting on your butt!
Would you shut up?
No, I'm leaving!
Wait!
Let me go!
Don't touch me!
You listen good.
Your gal pal's toast.
Wrong!
You're going to have to learn
to survive on your own.
Good! I want to
leave you behind!
I'll survive longer
than you will!
Get back here!
Where's the party?
Damn, can't see a thing.
Fuck you, Satoru!
Juninho, man.
That's Satoshi Batista.
What?
You serious?
Yeah, I overheard him calling
himself that earlier.
If that is him, he's
practically a damn celebrity.
Found you.
Well, I think
I just found Hiroshi.
Yeah, where?
You'll have to choose.
Him or me.
Come on kid.
No way.
Michiko's waiting for me.
You got balls for a girl;
I'll give you that.
That's the face I wanted.
Say cheese.
Don't move!
Michiko!
Gods are smiling
on me for once.
I'm so sick of your shit.
Hatchin!
Can you guys help me out?
I'll give you
anything you wa--.
Oops!
My-- My name is
Satoshi Batista.
Bingo!
I swear, I'm going
to kill you bastards.
What's that?
Sorry, can't hear you.
Huh?
Sure, I won't tell anyone you
done you shit in your pants.
Train now arriving
at the station.
All departing passengers
please wait on Platform J.
Your destination, sir?
Uh, to Centro.
Have a good trip.