So you've come
all the way to Perna,
but you didn't come
for the tratamento?
Our Lady of the Desert
will grant any wish.
Fantastic, huh?
And Toni Kaká's maps
will lead the way.
Only costs two arcas!
Well, normal price, but you're
so pretty, I'll go one arca,
fifty talgos!
Uh, hey!
'Scuse me.
Yo, what's happenin'?
This map.
You pressured me into
buying it, yesterday?
But I'm really
hard up for money.
So um--I'd like to return
it for a refund please.
Are you sure you
got that thing from me?
Yes.
You are Toni Kaká, right?
Sorry.
You're mistaken,
I'm Garcia Boroots.
Gabe!
Why are you here?
Didn't I already tell you
we were done, Masão?
I'll be the one who decides
when we're done, Rita.
But I'm not gonna do that.
Who's that?
Boyfriend.
But he's just
a shrimpy little kid!
Yeah, he's a little shrimpy.
So what?
So, uh--
Hey you're not
as shrimpy as I thought.
Yeah, no.
I'm not.
I like you.
Whoa!
What are you doing?
Duh. Kissing.
Wait, listen!
I'm a girl!
Whaddaya know.
How old are you?
I just recently turned ten.
Me too!
Oh yeah?
You don't say.
You talk polite.
Kinda weirds me out.
I'm very sorry.
Are you sick?
Or just hungry?
Yeah, I'm starving.
Well, let's go.
But I have no money.
That's okay.
Reporting from Osso,
where, amid the busy...
Forgot your wallet, huh?
Yup.
I'm sure I can cover you girls.
Really?
No problem!
Thank you!
The victims were reportedly
posing as members
of "Monstro Preto," and carrying
on fraudulent activities.
It is strongly suspected
that this incident
was carried out in retaliation.
The body of the group's
leader, Davi Nativa,
was found in front of a
train garage twenty-eight
kilometers outside Osso.
It is also believed that prison
escapee Michiko Malandro
was witnessed
fleeing the scene.
All righty.
What's wrong?
Well um, we didn't
pay anyone for our food.
That rube inside was
about to pay his tab
so I talked him into
coverin' ours, too.
Let's head this way.
Feels like I'm leakin'
down my string.
String?
Tampon.
Oh, I'm Rita.
What's your name?
Hana.
Hana?
Hm.
So, you sleep in the park?
For now.
All alone?
Where're you from?
Check it!
You bought that?
The map?
From Toni Kaká.
Are you hoping
for the tratamento?
Wanna look?
Know what?
I know the secret of the Maria
statue and her "tratamento".
Whole thing's a big scam.
What's up with a statue that
cries tears of blood, anyway?
S'like a bad horror movie.
The statue cries blood?
Mm-hmm.
When you see it,
you say a prayer.
Everyone says that's
how your wish is granted.
So you don't believe in it?
A Maria statue suddenly
appearing in the middle
of nowhere and wishes
being granted?
I'm young but I'm not stupid.
Those stories sound like dreams;
like a whole buncha nonsense.
The real world is a lot less
forgiving than that.
It's fine, take it.
You didn't have to
but thanks, Rita.
Curious about that?
Because I happen
to work there.
Come by anytime
and I'll get you in.
Are you sure?
It's a promise.
So come.
Oh, shoot.
Gotta go.
Okay.
See ya.
Why the heck should I be the
least bit concerned about her?
Gino!
Don't get up!
You do not look down at me!
I told you to keep
an eye on that girl!
What's your deal?
She came back, didn't she?
Don't talk back
to me, you fool!
Why didn't you come?
Why bother?
You came right back here.
Dang it Gino!
Do what I want you to do now!
Otherwise, I'm
leaving for real!
Did I wake you?
You okay?
You have anyone you like?
Because, that's
the problem I have.
His name's Gino.
We're always together and we
have been ever since I was born.
You see, my parents abandoned
me outside of that tent.
The first thing I ever
remember seeing was Gino.
I'm always looking at him.
But then,
he never looks at me.
So I've tried to make
him jealous by talking
to a whole bunch of men but
he still doesn't look at me.
Even when I run away like this,
he won't come after me.
My heart aches like it's
all tangled up in my chest.
Good morning!
Hey, dirty boy!
I'm callin' you out!
Don't you go making eyes
at my Rita anymore!
Or else, my fist is
gonna meet your face!
Whoa!
Look, I'm a girl!
I'll bet you are!
And that just
proves my-- Huh?
Listen, could you
come with me for a bit?
Huh?
Just come on!
Fine lady, right?
Name's Natália.
She's Gino's girlfriend.
Oh yeah, and he
just knocked her up.
And now you know what's what.
Go on, you can order
anything you like.
No one can make Rita happy.
No one but me, anyways.
Looking prettier
than ever, darlin'!
Oh, stop.
You think?
Hey!
You get it?
I'm askin' you
to shill for me.
I'll totally feed you whatever
you want and in exchange--
--you can talk me
up around Rita.
I really am a nice guy.
Hey, what's wrong?
Ow!
Faster, Gino!
You're okay.
Stop it!
Don't touch me!
Move it, ya little snot!
Lemme go!
You some kinda thief,
creepin' around like a roach?
No!
I am not a thief!
Hana!
Rita!
Take that,
you nasty, filthy--!
What's wrong?
You know, Rita.
I heard that Gino
has a girlfriend.
And I heard other things, too.
Did you come here
to tell me to give up?
I don't believe you!
Get out!
So uh, has that girl
Rita come out yet?
Huh-uh.
Oh, I see.
Thank you very much.
No, wait.
You're Gino, aren't you?
I'm Hana.
I'm one of Rita's friends.
She's in an awful lot of pain.
How come?
It's because of the way
she feels about you.
So please, if you could,
give her a closer look.
If you'd be so kind.
Your hair looks
like cotton candy.
Sorry, but I can't do that.
Huh?
You see, when the show closes
day after tomorrow, I'm staying.
Also, I'm gonna be a daddy!
What about Rita?
Does that mean
you can't stay with her?
That's how these
things normally work.
Then does she know
about any of this yet?
Huh?
Know what?
Which part?
Like you staying here?
Oh, she'll be fine.
She's still so young.
She's got her whole life
ahead of her, right?
She'll meet all sorts of guys,
and eventually find someone
who's right for her.
She'll be a fine
woman someday.
Rita.
I didn't know
where else I could go.
I'm sorry.
There's something
wrong with me.
Are you leaving?
I'll come with you.
Mm-hm.
It's Masão's.
Rock-paper-scissors!
One, two, three!
Get on.
Hurry up.
Ready?
Yup.
Easy, Hana!
Whoa!
What are you guys doing?
Just switchin'
the ol' lady out.
Why?
Some damn idiot ran off
with the other one's head.
Buncha savages around here.
Anyway, we swapped
it out for a new one.
But does this one cry?
Please, she just has to!
I mean, how else
is she gonna grant wishes?
Huh?
Tell me!
Please!
Rita!
Can't wait until
I'm finally a grownup.
Would you two get to work?
Rita!
Gino!
You're on!
Gino Costa and Rita Ozzetti!
Hop to, everybody!
We're outta here tomorrow!
Awesome show as always, Gino.
I'm okay now.
Hey.
You look great out there.
Thank you, Hana.
This is goodbye, huh?
I'll see ya.
Do you think I could
come with you guys?