Also in other news tonight:
Groups of unemployed workers,
who have grown in numbers
due to tax reforms enacted
by the former prime minister,
are rioting all across
the country. And confusion among
members of the parliament,
sparked by the comments of
Finance Minister Takanashi
during a recent parliament
inquiry, there seems to be
no compromise in sight between
the government and opposition.
Hey, there. Call it.
Gimme some. Three peanuts.
Let's see...
The Clown bastards
are herded out on Route No. 5.
Damn it, don't
scare me like that.
Open that damn door quietly.
You know,
you wouldn't be so jumpy
if you didn't have
anything to hide.
Why don't you sell
normal drinks for a change?
How 'bout buying
something for once?
This ain't a hangout
for damn street gangs.
Yeah, right.
Drink your dog piss?!
Twin ceramic rotor drives
on each wheel...
Let's see... And these are...
computer-controlled
anti-lock brakes.
Two hundred horses
at twelve thousand rpm.
You wanna ride it, Tetsuo?
Alright, let's hit it!
I customized that bike
for myself.
It's too wild.
You couldn't handle it.
I don't see how you can ride
something crazy like that man.
Huh, I could.
If you want it so bad,
then steal one yourself.
Huh?
Unbelievable.
Hey, waiter,
where are you going?
They ran into the alley.
After 'em!
Quit fooling around,
you idiot.
Fuck.
What?
That's the...
This is unit 375.
We've got reports of biker gangs
fighting near the intersection
of Highway 14 South.
Request immediate assistance.
Car 375 on route to the scene.
Again, request
immediate assistance.
It's the cops.
What should we do?
Oh, damn it. My motor coils
were just getting warmed up.
Bastards. Let's go Tetsuo!
I'm coming. Damn them.
Come on!
A skirmish has broken out
between student protestors
and riot police. There appear
to be some causalities. Next...
Don't make me get out
of this car, buddy!
Come on jerk, I'm in a hurry!
What was that?
Call the police!
Repeal the tax reform!
This area is off limits!
Go back, it's dangerous.
Hey, something strange
over there.
Let me through. I'm sorry.
It's blood! Look!
Please let me through.
Excuse me. Pardon me.
Watch it jerk.
So fattening...
Pardon me. I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
Ryu!
Hey, look!
They're running away!
Where are they going?
They're getting away!
He's got a gun.
Turn on that light.
Get out of here! Shoot!
Don't let him get away!
Fire!
Wait, hold your fire.
He's got a kid.
Get down. Get down. Stay down.
Run. You've gotta hurry.
Go to Ryu. He'll help you now.
Get out of here. Now.
Kay.
We gotta get out of here, Kay.
Wha-? He's gone.
He's to the west.
West? He's in the Old City.
Eat this.
Tetsuo!
Ryu! Where are you?
Kay!
No, thats-! Ohhh...
Huh? Ahhh!
How d'ya like that?
Huh?
Well? Who is it?
It's not him. It's not Tetsuo.
Alright. Move out!
Why you... Whaddya do?
You weird little...
Tetsuo. Just hang on.
What? What did you say?
That... kid.
He's really hurt bad.
Hey! You there!
We gotta get him to a hospital.
He needs an ambulance,
we can't move him.
Ahhh
What the-?
There's no escape.
We're here to
take you back with us.
You know we can't survive
outside. We all belong at home.
Well, come along.
These are army helicopters.
It's the army!
Move out!
Kiss the ground.
Hands on your heads.
We're, uh, innocent
bystanders, that's all.
Kiss the ground.
Hands on your heads.
Ahhh, that hurts dammit.
Kai!
Soldier
Sir
Who are those kids?
They seem to be
an ordinary bike gang, sir.
We're returning.
Ouch. Will you
just hold on a minute?
My arms don't
bend that way, you loser.
Pull the wounded
onto the helicopter.
Tetsuo! Hey wait-- you can't
take him away like that.
Kaneda!
What the hell are
you guys doing?
We didn't do anything
to deserve this!
He's heavy.
Alright, the story is you
and your friends went out
at night on your bikes
to visit your dying mother
and then another bunch of
other biker hooligans
called The Clowns
attacked you...
...they hurt your friend,
you lost your temper,
and that's why eight
of these clowns
are all now in the hospital
and that is the truth.
Oh wee, she's sure hot.
Hmm? This is confidential!
And how's your mother doing?
Fortunately the worst is over.
She cleared the hump.
She cleared the hump, huh?
What next, a triathalon?
Wha...? Ha ha ha
Aw, these bozos couldn't have
anything to do with it.
That goes without saying.
Wait out on that bench.
Do you understand?
Alright, send in
the next five.
So, the army's working
with the police to hunt down
anti-government groups,
or so it seems.
Yeah, that's it.
Wanna put up a fight huh?
Hey let me go!
Get your hands off me!
Long live
the freedom revolution!
He's got a grenade! Ah!
Die! ...huh?
You crazy sonova bitch!
Alright, that's enough.
Get 'im back in there.
That'll teach him
a lesson he won't forget.
You dumb bastard,
if you wanna die
just hang yourself
or something!
Listen, you kids
are free to leave.
We've contacted your school.
See your principal
in the morning.
You sonova bitch!--
Hey, hold on a second old man!
Old man?
There was someone else
with us you know.
What was that?
Will you pardon me, please?
Huh? Hey, what are you doing?
Uh, it's this one right here.
Can't leave my friend.
Don't ever call me
old man ya little punk.
That's my foot!
Ya listen here, kid.
I'm only twenty five years old.
I'm not even married yet.
So watch your mouth.
Get out of here,
and take your friend with you.
Sorry I need a doctor!
Well I think the army was
chasing that weird kid Kaneda
and Tetsuo saw,
that's what I think.
Yeah, you're right.
I think I saw him too.
And speaking of Tetsuo,
why the hell wouldn't they
tell us what hospital
they threw him in?
Huh? What was that?
What I meant was maybe we
could go for drinks
somewhere around here.
I figure we could have
a nice long chat
about something you're into
like the whole revolution thing.
Hmm. I think
you're a skirt chaser
who'll try anything he can.
You'll help anyone so long as
it's a girl, is that right?
You're wrong! I have very
high standards, you know?
Line 'em up!
Come on! Move it!
It's not their looks that
count, it's their--I dunno--
a girl's sensitivity
that makes me do it.
I suppose I owe you one.
Thank you very much, uh...
I'm Kaneda. It's nice to--
See you around, Kaneda.
Wait a second!
You're leaving just like that?
Hey! Now hold on. I am the guy
that saved you back there.
You could at least tell me
your name you cold bitch!
Yes, I'll try talking with him.
But it's risky business.
If they think you're avoiding
responsibility the whole thing
could blow up
in your face, right?
I can't believe that there's a
mole in the executive council.
Even if there is a mole.
That's not
what's important here.
What is are political
maneuvers and diplomacy,
which apparently you despise.
I never studied the two subjects
in school, it would seem.
In any case, at the next
executive council meeting,
your poor management and lack of
judgement on this last incident
will be called into question.
There's a call
for the colonel, sir.
Put your affairs in order
if you want my advice.
Yes, it's me. What is it now?
This way please, Colonel.
I'm terribly sorry
to call you here,
but there's something
you really must see.
Colonel, please observe.
It's the special pattern
I'm getting from
that young man.
It doesn't resemble
any like I've seen so far.
And I've never seen
a developmental speed
or configuration like this.
It may have begun with the shock
of contact with Number 26,
or it could be--
Have you finished
running a comparison
against Akira's pattern?
I'll superimpose for you.
This projection is made using
mixed data and the results
are not quite correct,
so direct comparison
is difficult.
But I believe based
on what we see here
that this boy's
pattern is the key
to solving the riddle of
Akira's growth pattern process.
Fine. You may continue.
Thank you very much, sir.
I'm certain he'll turn out to be
a worthy addition to the
numbers, don't you?
It may be rough on the boy
but I thought we might try
starting him off
with Level 7 capsules.
Is it safe, Doctor?
I will take care of it.
No! I wasn't talking
about the boy at all.
I'm asking that if he turns out
to reach a power like Akira's,
are you positive that you're
able to control such a power?
Uh, well, that's a--
Can I leave this
in your hands?
Uhhh-- Well then, in my opinion,
if we could use
the latest examination equipment
to collect even more data,
and also do a multifacited
analysis as we go,
then surely...
But maybe we
weren't meant to meddle
with that ultimate power.
You mean, the power of a god?
Ah
Ki
Ra
But we have no choice
but to grasp that power,
grasp that power
and learn to control it,
and if this situation
gets out of hand
then it needs
to be terminated.
And without hesitation.
Yes, Colonel.
This school is
your last chance.
If trash like yourselves
can't keep up
with the academic ability of
regular students, this is it!
If you can't live a decent
social life, you end up here
and if you screw up here,
it's the end of the road!
Also, even though
you're under fiften,
if you get more than fifty
penalty points on your record
you're sent to the
regular corps.
Eh bite me. Don't mess
with us you bald old goat.
Are any of you listening?
You lost me
halfway through, sir!
Discipline! Discipline!
Discipline!
Discipline! Dismissed!
Thank you very much, sir.
Ya loser! You and me are
gonna go at it someday, Jack!
We're gonna remember
this buddy!
Yeah ya sick mother! Damn.
Uh, ya sure?
Look hey!
Yamagata why'd they
keep you so long?
Kaneda what happened
to your cheek?
I heard you got into a fight.
So what?
My friend told me. Yeah, they
told me you faught the Clowns
in the old city.
Big deal.
Why don't you just wipe 'em all
out? Those guys are so gross.
Clowns, there were
demonstrators, cops,
the damn army, and that idiot
Tetsuo had an accident.
But what happened to Tetsuo?
Huh? He's in the hospital
but we don't know where.
Dumb loser was
tryin' a show off.
Stupid idiot.
You're talking
about Tetsuo right?
Shut up already. Why do ya
always have to be hanging
on my arm every minute?
What tha heck
has gotten into you?
Huh?
Tetsuo? It's time
for your medication.
Doctor hurry! The boy is gone.
No I can't. You know the
dorm mother always throws a fit
if you go out before ten.
Yeah, you know the one
who has a face like a goat?
That woman is such
a big ol' pain.
She's always complaining
about us girls.
Huh? Tomorrow at three?
Yeah that's cool.
Hey, what happened
to that girl? You know who.
After my friend saw him.
I don't like her at all.
Her attitude gets on my nerves.
Kaori.
What tha?
Tetsuo you're here.
Everyone's been worried about
you. They thought you were dead.
When I woke up, I was on an
operating table or something.
That examination--it's
like they were messing
around inside my head.
No, I don't wanna go back
there again. We'll run away.
Where would we go to?
I dunno. Someplace.
Someplace far away.
Hey it's self study today!
Where'd the teacher go to?
What about my burning desire
to study and learn a vocation?
Well drag his butt in here.
Ah! Kaneda hurry,
come quick your bike!
What about my bike?
See? Look it. Down there.
Wha? Tetsuo?
Is this ok?
Ah quiet. Shut up and hang on.
Huh? What tha?
What's wrong?
Aww Jesus Christ
Uh oh, we're stopping now.
We've stopped.
Oh I get it, the engine
can't drop below 5000 rpms,
even when
you're changing the gears.
Oh ouch. My butt hurts.
Hey, look. Some bikes!
Is that Kaneda and-- Wha?
No it isn't!
Shit! Kaori!
Any sign of them?
Huata and the others
went to look around Kizenyazu.
The only place we have to search
now is the industrial area.
K. Let's go!
We owe you for the other night.
Now it's time for payback.
Shut up!
Kaori! What happened?
No, don't! If you put so much as
a single scratch on that bike
I'm gonna kill your ass.
Hahaha. Huh?
Run!
After them!
No, wait.
Huh?
Tetsuo!
You're gonna kill him,
Tetsuo. You want that?
I want him more than dead.
I want to split
his friggin head open.
Just knock it off now.
This whole thing happened
just because you took
my bike for a spin.
Enough already.
Shut up! Don't order me around!
We were just worried.
Why do ya always have
to try and save me?
I coulda handled it
on my own. Ya I admit,
I gotten beaten before,
but I won't always be on the
receiving end. You hear that?
You understand?
Tetsuo.
Shut up, go away.
Hey wait! Where are you going?
Leave me alone.
Akira!
Tetsuo!
Something wrong?
Akira.
I don't know who that is! Ah!
Tetsuo... what's wrong?
A-Are you alright?
This is really strange.
I'm getting a blue pattern
on scope number three.
What? No!
Retrieve the subject now, hurry.
Why don't you guys
just leave my friend alone?
What's with the getup, huh?
You going to a funeral?
Tetsuo!
Kaneda!
Screw you! Huh?
No wait!
Kaneda, what the hell's
goin on?
Well well, I see we have
some real hip youngsters
doing their thing
inspite of the tight checkpoints
they got going around tonight.
And that just means that they're
all pretty stupid, don't it?
Huh? Oh whatever.
This is boring.
Hey, whaddya say.
Let's go home.
Wah? But it's still early.
Yeah, but without their bikes
they're just tail chasers
outta water.
You mean fish.
Come on, lets go
and toss these fish back.
Hey, Kaneda!
Aww what are we gonna do?
What tha heck?
Look.
It's that girl.
Here we go again.
Look lets get out of here
before we get caught up in it.
Huh? Kaneda?
Hey!
This area is being corded off
due to a terrorist bombing.
Those who wish to get through
line up single file,
present your ID, and precede
through the checkpoint.
Get in.
What's wrong? Hurry!
I'll meet ya shortly.
You know the
rendezvous point, right?
Be careful
You too. You be careful.
Hey! Hold it right there.
She's got a gun!
Ok that's far enough.
Alright? Drop it.
Drop it!
Don't do it!
I think it came from over here.
There were two shots, no three.
It's just up ahead.
Hey, let's get out of here.
Come on!
Kaneda!
There. Now, what's the matter?
Talk about it.
It was a dream that I saw.
A dream?
The city started to crumble
apart covered by a big shadow.
And lots of people died.
And the three of us,
we get to meet Akira again.
Wha-- Akira?
The city will crumble. So many
people. So many will die.
When will it happen?
Do you know when? Kiyoko!
You mustn't let that boy go.
His power-- it--
What's she talking about?
Well, there's a-- Uhh...
there seems to be nothing
physically wrong with her and
her medication looks accurate.
There's no sign
of any abnormalities
in her EKG or EEG either.
I think Number 25's
statement is probably
her precognitive power at work.
You know, this needs to be
brought before
the supreme council for inquiry.
Do you believe her?
I have no doubts regarding
Number 25's abilities.
We've lots of data
that substantiates it.
What do you believe, Colonel?
I'll tell you my job
isn't to believe or disbelieve.
It's to act or not act.
Of course there are
several security measures
before we enter.
Here sir.
Cold gear, Colonel. Please
put it on. You too, Doctor.
The other day
a young researcher
came to me
and asked me something.
He wondered if their power was
the form of the next stage
that human evolution was taking
and purhaps we would all
be able to control it someday.
Hmph. Scientists are
a bunch of romantics.
Military men on the other
hand always consider
the risks first.
Over thirty years
it's taken. We've come so far,
crawling up from the rubble.
We can't just trade one
for the other.
But I've always
thought that you've held
a resentment--even a hatred--
for this city, Colonel.
The passion to build is cool
and the joy of
reconstruction forgotten.
Now-- Now it's just
a garbage heap made up of
a bunch of hedonistic fools.
But inspite of that
you're trying to save the city.
I'm not a scientist.
I think like a soldier.
Colonel? We're here sir.
This way please.
Room ten. 148 degrees Kelvin.
Fluctuation tolerance range?
Check.
Room nine 108 degrees Kelvin.
Fluctuation tolerance range,
check.
Emergency power generator.
Check.
Open the door.
Sir. Uh...
The control room. Do it!
Yes, sir!
Room one is at 0.0005 degrees
Kelvin. It's within tolerances.
No abnormalities detected
within any of the rooms,
duar walls,
or defense systems.
No abnormal reactions
or concentrations recorded.
So then all systems are nominal.
Look at what they abandoned in
their panic. They were afraid.
They were too scared so they
hid it away from the public,
losing all sense
of shame and honor,
casting aside the civilization,
and abandoning the science
that created it.
Shutting the lid
of the pandora's box
they themselves had opened.
Hey, we're still young.
We could start over again.
Ryu?!
So whaddya think, huh?
Ryu!
That's the first time
you killed a man, right?
Come on, I'll go with you.
Ryu!
You aren't listening.
Turn yourself in.
I'll even go to
the police station with you.
Ryu!
Anyway, when you
get out I'll be there.
Let's go out
for drinks, alright?
Don't kick yourself over it.
What's done is done.
You've heard that.
The guy is dead and gone. Huh?
Huh? Identify yourselves.
Yaa--
Ryu. Are you alright?
Kay, it's you.
Ryu.
Who's this.
Huh? Who's this? Well, I guess
by saying I'm Kay's boyfriend
it's stretching it a bit.
Depends on your point
of view. But we haven't gotten
physical or anything.
You understand, don't you?
Are you a spy?
No I'm not.
You're lying!
Ahhh!
Well, is he a spy or not?
Whatever he is
he's certainly not a spy.
Ow.
Sneak into their lab,
that's crazy! Ridiculous!
Remember the fiasco
with that kid?!
They're last minute orders, and
the plan is in place already.
These are the lab passes
they issue once a week.
From Mr. Nezu, right?
What's the objective?
We're to gather detailed data
on the new subject.
You're kidding, a new subject?
Yes, last week. On the same
night we tried to abduct
the experimental subject
they call Number 26.
A boy who was in an accident
on an old city highway
was brought to the lab.
It seems he's a student at
a vocational training school,
but now he's their new subject
for human experimentation.
Huh?
Hey hey hey hey hey!
What's the big idea?
Uh! Kaneda!
Should I kill him?
He heard us.
Ryu!
Wait! Now just hold on
a minute. Hear me out.
Please listen to
what I have to say.
Ryu, he did save me.
Yeah, twice!
Maybe he did it
just to get close to us.
The guy who was in that
accident in the old city
is a close friend of mine.
I know it's hard for you
to believe what I'm saying
but it's the truth.
I was right there
right when it happened.
Come on. Don't they say
the only foolish questions
are unasked ones?
Huh? They don't?
That's an intriging story now,
isn't it?
Well, will you be taking
the boy with you?
He knows the subject.
And I think we could use him
as a decoy if
we find it necessary.
New Tokyo's going
to change soon.
In all respects this
city is saturated.
It's like an overripe fruit.
Buried within it is a new seed.
We need only wait for the wind
which would make it
fall to fruitition.
The wind called Akira.
Ryu. Look over here.
What is it?
We arent the ones who will
change this. But rather it's
those citizens that hope
for Akira that will.
That which is called science
perverts providence.
That which is called progress
encourages extravagance.
That which is called
civilization devastates
the spirit of man.
The time of atonement is upon
us. Are your hearts prepared?
The time is nigh! The time
of his awakening is night!
The moment of Lord Akira's
awakening is drawing closer.
Are your hearts and minds
prepared for a new coming?
Break it up. Holding
meetings here is prohibited.
This gathering is illegal!
Terrorist activities carried
out by antigovernment elements
have skyrocketed this month.
The army, riot squad,
and even traffic police
have fully mobilized.
The overtime costs alone
have used up the
public safety budget.
And then there's the
abduction of Number 26.
Isn't their existence
supposed to be
the highest of state
secrets, Colonel?
No one's ever heard of peace and
order here in Neo Tokyo-land?
And this, this request of
yours for further-- ah yes,
for further funding because of
subject number 25's prediction.
Well that's--
You must be joking!
While straightening out the
historic tax reform blunders
of our former Prime Minister,
we parliament members have
been bowing our heads down
and begging the public
to bear with us
and what does
he ask for? Money.
Where exactly do we get
that kind of money?
We've already spend a fortune
here and all we have
to show for it is that grotesque
kindergarten you've set up.
The Olympics are next near and
the post-war period is over,
how much longer will
you keep throwing away
countless amounts of money
on these worthless ghosts?
I always said we should
put all that money into
the welfare program
Shut up old man!
What was that?
You heard me!
Now listen here. That power
is starting to walk around free
as we speak.
Unless we control that power
now we'll lose everything
we've tried so hard to achieve.
You're about to take
that old man comment back!
It was your lack of policy
that started this mess
in the first place!
There is still no proof that
the last world war was caused
by Akira in my opinion.
Don't you understand?
Unless an Akira disaster
actually happens-- Don't you
people understand anything?
Has anyone ever seen
this Number 26 Akira?
You're wrong!
Break it up!
I say that the Colonel has lost
sight of his duty as a soldier.
Yes, he's right! And I
have had several reports.
Reports on
antigovernment elements.
How they're using your
Akira madness to ramp up
their terrorist ferver.
That's not true. It's just not.
Then what about that Akira
World Renewal movement?
Wouldn't you say that
information's being leaked?
World Renewal Movement? It's
more like the end of the world.
Aren't you just using Akira
as camoflage to cover up
your misconduct? Admit it!
What are you getting at?
Colonel. Please be calm
and try to understand
that we can no longer leave
the peace of Neo Tokyo
to your sole discretion.
Understood?
I'm sorry, but you're to be put
before an inquiry committee.
You and the whole military
needs a reform!
Excuse me.
What?
This discussion isn't over.
This is an outrage.
You should explain yourself!
How dare you walk--
Are you trying to insult
the supreme executive council?
His behavior is intolerable!
Need-Need water
Hey, wait a minute! Let's see...
Isn't that cable replacement
due for next week?
Well, the cable they ordered
came in a whole week early.
And besides, I got
vacation time coming
and I'm leaving this weekend,
but if I bring the workers back
there'll be overtime.
I could leave now
and come back but
the work's gotta be
done sooner or later.
Alright guys, let's go.
What tha--?
What tha hell?
It's milk! Wh-Wha--?
Stay away! No!
Ahhh!
It's blood.
I'm scared.
Weirdo.
Those kids... who are they?
Huh? Hmmm.
Patient room 887. Shema, Tetsuo.
Oh! The automatic lock's off.
Hey you! You're not
allowed to leave your room!
See to it. There,
we'll find another room.
Get a load of the room.
Looks like a tornado hit it.
Look at all that glass!
There are 58 blocks
with circuits that
the computer will display.
Of those, nearly 40
are concentrated
on underground levels
seven and eight.
That's probably the place.
The central wiring shaft
should be straight up ahead.
We'll be able to use that to go
straight down to the sub levels.
Be careful.
It's deeper in the middle.
Hoo, what a stink.
Don't you ever stop talking?
What? I said it stinks
because it stinks.
Is your nose
busted or something?
Keep up and be quiet.
Damn. Hug the walls.
Huh? What are you guys doing?
You idiot, get down!
They left?
Looks like they beefed up
security, doesn't it?
Must be that siren we heard.
Ryu, can you scout
a way around it?
No, I wanna check out
the security at the very least.
Hey are you ok?
Let's keep going.
Damn they spotted us!
Run for it!
Turn back you bastards!
Shu! Hold your fire!
Shumazaki! Ugh. You assholes.
Forget it! Run!
What the hell
is that thing huh?
Go!
Huh? He's dead.
Let it go.
Die!
This is Unit 304 Shaft Ditch.
I have encountered intruders.
Requesting backup.
Now engaging.
Here he comes!
Uh! Kay!
Dammit. The gun!
Kaneda!
Kay, over here!
Huh? Now!
Kaneda come on! Hurry!
Kaneda no!
What the hell? Where are
the brakes? That's not it.
I-- This is the central
wiring shaft, I think.
I can't figure it out.
What the--?
There now,
that's right. Behave.
Ask the Colonel for clearance
on the use of firearms.
Hey turn the radio up.
There must be some
kind of mistake here.
That boy looks like the patient
they admitted over in the lab.
Correct. The boy is a
psychic named Tetsuo Shima.
He broke out of his ward. He's
headed for the baby room!
It's Tetsuo?
He's extremely dangerous.
Do not let him through.
I repeat, do not
let him through.
It's no use hiding any more.
We have no choice then.
Use your guns.
We can't let him
go any further.
No matter what it takes. Fire!
Good. All here, are you?
Stop it!
So how long are you
gonna keep playing around?
Where's the other one
hiding, huh?
Hey you, you're a creton.
Huh?
Die!
Takashi!
What the hell is going on
with me? Am I dreaming?
These powers... are they real
or just an hallucination?
Dammit where the hell
am I going? Where?
Proceed straight.
Proceed straight ahead.
Huh?
You'll find
a freight elevator just ahead.
You can take it down
to sublevel eight.
That's good.
You're all together.
You thought you could kill me?
I'm through with it.
You tried to mess with me
and now I'm gonna kill you.
Huh?
You were there. I remember.
Takashi!
Huh?
Together, let's attack him!
Uh, uh huh.
You little twerps!
All of you, that is enough!
Who the hell are you?
Huh? What's the matter?
Is your head hurting?
Tetsuo Shima, your power
isn't fully matured yet.
If you push yourself
you might do irreparable damage.
We can help.
What the hell? What.. did...
you people... do?
You messed with my head.
Tetsuo Shima, calm yourself.
But he can't control it, sir.
Whaddyou say?
She said that big people
like you should never use
the power in
the way that you are.
And bad things will come of it.
Mind your own business,
will ya.
What?
More powerful than I am now?
He's the one.
He's the one that's been
invading my head all along.
Where is he? Where's
this Akira? Tell me now!
What?
Kiyoko says she'll wake him up,
and if you awaken
Akira like that...
...when that happens noone will
be able to stop him at all.
To prevent it
we have to stop you.
Ridiculous. Akira's already--
Where is he?
No! Don't!
Stay clear!
Red Level facility integrity
is down to level seven.
Enacting disaster protocal.
Red Level facility integrity
is past level seven.
Enacting disaster protocal.
Red Level facility integrity
is past level seven.
Enacting disaster protocal.
Hands up. Now.
Where in the hell
is the freakin baby room?
Heads up! Gang way
coming through coming through!
Ugh. Kiyoko. Uh.
Gah, that hurt.
Kaneda. What are you
doing in here?
Tetsuo! You ok?
I'm here for the rescue.
Hurry up, what are you? Stupid?
If we don't
get out of here those--
There he is! Capture him!
You keep away!
Kaneda!
Oh that's right,
I forgot you were there.
There, do you see Kaneda?
I won't be needing you
to come to the rescue
ever again. K?
From now on, I'll be
in charge of the heroics.
So if you need any saving
just ask, Kanie
Dammit, Tetsuo. Who the hell
do you think you're
talking to ya moron?
Hah. You don't like what you're
hearing, do ya? Makes you angry?
So whaddya gonna do now?
Well? Kaneda?
What are you gonna do now?
That's enough!
Stop it.
Don't hurt anyone else.
Where's this Akira?
I won't tell.
On the big stadium?
Underground?
No, don't. What you're thinking
is wrong. Akira is--
Wait!
Wai--
What the hell?
I can do this too?
Kiyoko? Are you alright?
It doesn't look like
she's hurt.
What about you, Masaru?
Look, you're bleeding.
Where'd he go to?
He flew away.
How can he have so much power?
How could this have happened?
Dammit, where are my men at?
He's developed so much power
in such a short time,
it's unbelievable.
Find him.
Start searching for Tetsuo.
Kaneda quick, come on get up!
Come on, move it!
Somebody help me with this rock.
Oh. Help me.
Tetsuo went to where Akira is.
What? That's good.
You're all safe.
He's heading for
the facility below
the Olympic construction site.
He went there.
How did he find out about it?
Dammit. You're saying that
he's managed to escape?
Alright, then, we'll follow him.
You men, look alive there!
Move those bodies!
Get this place in order.
Prepare for pursuit.
He's heading west
towards the stadium.
Come on, move! I want
additional checkpoints--
It was you.
According to the security
team, reviews of tapes
showed five intruders
disguised as workers
entered into the wiring shaft.
Besides the two--
I have to stop him
before his powers mature.
Your objective is the boy
Tetsuo Shima. If we are unable
to capture him we'll lure him
out to the old city and attack.
Request assistance from
the Eastern Disctrit Battalion.
Yes sir.
Tell them there isn't
a moment to lose here.
I've been waiting here
a long time, Colonel.
What are you doing here? Huh?
I'm here to inform you tonight
of the Supreme Executive
Council's decision.
At twenty four hundred hours
today the Colonel is hereby
stripped of his command
and rank and shall be placed
under arrest.
What the hell?
Kindly accompany us now.
You really expect me to hand
Neo Tokyo over to those fools
at a time like this?
Shoot him.
Yes, sir.
Wha-- No wait, hold on! No!
Enough! Open your eyes
and look at the big picture.
You're all puppets of corrupt
politicians and capitalists.
Don't you understand?
It's utterly pointless
to fight each other.
Announce a state of emergency,
and arrest all members of
the Executive Council.
Break their chain of command.
Lift off.
We're going after Tetsuo.
Urgent message, repeat urgent.
To all district
battalion commanders--
Yo. What's up? You're alone?
That's right.
Weren't you in an accident?
Your friends have
been really worried.
You ok?
Give me some... capsules.
Huh? You sure you want capsules
son? You look kinda woozy.
You better get 'em now.
Alright, whatever the
customer wants but you know
with all those terrorist attacks
lately and the demonstrations,
things have been pretty rough.
In fact, they're
hard to come by
so the price is pretty
expensive. Right?
Tetsuo's run off somewhere.
Kaneda's disappeared.
Damn I guess the team
is finished.
And the checkpoints are so
strict these days. Argh.
Even the clowns are laying low.
What the hell happened?
Look at--
He's dead!
What?
Who's that?
It's Tetsuo.
Why are you here?
You did this, didn't you?
Look who's here. Wanna pop one?
What tha hell are you
talking about?
You look like a damn crackhead.
Talk sense. What happened here?
Did you notice
that the owner's dead?
A fish out of water dies, huh?
Are you... Tetsuo?
Or someone else?
Kaneda sends
his warmest regards.
You saw Kaneda? Where is he?
He's probably dead by now.
Kai was right. You did this,
didn't you?
All you're good for now
is telling me
where Kaneda's bike is.
Tetsuo!
It's a piece of shit anyway.
You son of a bitch.
Yamagata.
Goddammit. Huh?
So is he off to find Akira?
Yes, that's what
that girl was saying.
Now the army, Ryu, and
yourself are all trying
at once to find this Akira guy
and that's also why
you're chasing after Tetsuo.
It must have to do
with the powers he's got.
Uh, what the hell
is this Akira thing huh?
I asked Ryu one time. He told me
that Akira is ultimate energy.
Ultimate energy?
Humans do all kinds of things
during their lifetime, right?
Discovering things,
building things.
Things like houses,
high speed trains, motorcycles,
bridges and cities, rockets.
So where do you suppose all that
knowledge and energy comes from?
Humans were once
like monkeys, right?
And before that like reptiles,
and fish? And even before that,
plankton and amoebas, even
little creatures like those
have incredible amounts
of energy inside them.
Oh, yessir-- huh?
It's in the genes, right?
And even before that.
Maybe there was genetic material
in the air and water.
Even in the particles
of dust and space.
And if that's the truth,
then what sort of memories
are hidden within them?
The beginning of the universe?
Or maybe even before that.
What's with all the crazy talk.
Are you sure you're ok?
Listen to ya. Or did you get
bonked on the head back there?
And what if everyone
shares those ancient memories?
What if there were some
mistakes in the progression?
Something goes wrong and
an amoeba is suddenly given
the higher powers
that a human has?
Akira... is an... amoeba, then?
Amoebas don't build their own
houses and bridges, do they?
They just devour all the food
they can find around them.
Is that what Tetsuo's doing?
Are you saying he has
that kind of energy?
Long ago there were people
who tried to gain control
of that power.
That is, all at the
government's request
but they failed
in their attempt
and it triggered
the fall of Tokyo.
And that power is something that
is totally beyond our--
Wha--
The door's unlocked.
It's a trap. This is just
too good of a setup.
Go back then.
No way. I wanna find out just
how much of a trap it is,
don't you?
By the way, what's going on
with you and that Ryu guy?
What in the world
are you talking about?
You're always together.
It's none of your business.
No wait, hear me out.
What I'm saying is--
he doesn't know
about us, does he?
About us? Hey wait a minute.
What's that supposed to mean?
Do you think it'll work?
It can't be helped.
At this point in time, our only
option left is to use her.
Well the fact that without us
even looking she turned up
right under our noses
says as much.
What do you think?
I guess so.
...have arrived in ward thirteen
east Ginza section, over.
Northern District Battalion
has not responded
to mobilization request.
Special Search Team to HQ.
We're at the Harokira Bar
near the highway exchange
at ward eight.
It doesn't look like any sort
of bomb explosion to us
so we think it was him.
No sir, it wasn't
a gas explosion either.
It was almost certainly
the work of the subject
that escaped from the lab.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Understood.
Huh? Kaneda, wait!
What? Yamagata's dead?
Something seemed strange about
him the second I saw his face.
It's odd. He was
wearing what looked like
a white hospital gown.
He acted like
a different person.
Yamagata asked him
if he was really Tetsuo,
or if he was someone else.
And then he... Yamagata, why?
We've always been together.
I've known everything
about him ever--
--ever since we were in the
children's home together.
They'd tease--
Everybody tried to make him cry.
Oh yeah. He really wanted
to know where your bike was at.
Where my bike was?
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna go send
Yamagata his wheels.
You dumb bastard!
Kaneda!
Kay! What's wrong?
That night. You were there.
Wait.
Kay!
Th-They're gone.
You're the one, right? You
changed my friend, didn't you?
The thing about Akira's power
is it exists within everyone
from the start.
Hey, who is that? Huh?
But, when that power
is awakened inside,
it is important to wisely
choose how to use it.
When the time comes,
you might not know it
let alone be prepared for it.
Your friend has
already made his choice.
Tetsuo is our newest companion.
He's our friend, also.
His actions are out of control,
and for that we're
partly to blame too.
Great! Then what in the hell
did you take Kay for?
We're hoping she'll be able
to help us in some way.
They're people, not toys.
Bring her back to me.
And Tetsuo's our friend,
not yours.
If someone's gonna kill him
it should be us!
Hey!
Are you sure? Mr Ame and
the others have been arrested
in a coup de tas?
Yes, that's right.
The post guards
are fighting them right now.
Yes, I'd like to have
a helicopter waiting
at West Point. Yes.
That damn Colonel, I can't
believe he's taken up arms.
I've underestimated him.
Hold them down!
Mr. Nezu, I--
Ohhh... Ryu, is that you?
I came to apologize, sir.
The mission... was a failure.
Damn you! I told you you can't
be seen here. Get out!
My two best men... they're dead.
Everyone was killed.
You bastard. You sold me out.
Wha-What?
K-Kay...
Huh? What? Yeah,
Seventh Avenue is just up ahead.
It intersects this road
a hundred meters from here.
Battlestations!
Right. The subject
has been spotted.
What? Attack the kid?
But sir, he's just a boy.
We can't attack him.
Look, there he is!
Impossible. Is this for real?
Firing preparations
are complete.
Dammit! Fire!
Wha?
Is it Akira?
Look, it's Lord Akira!
Don't be fooled, this isn't the
rapture. He's a false messiah.
Oh shut up.
Long live Akira! Akira!
Fire!
What the--?
What's wrong?
Coming to you live from News
Chopper 1 high over downtown.
Neo Tokyo Broadcasting
is exclusively
covering the news today
inspite of martial law
in the name of
freedom of the press.
What in the world is happening
here in Neo Tokyo?
What you see here seems to be
fires caused by tank cannons.
But who is this young boy
standing alone?
Is he fighting the coup de tas
forces all by himself?
I'm sorry,
we've been ordered to land.
The army's just
illegally ordered us to land.
Now what is at stake here
is freedom of the press.
I'm sorry, we've
been ordered to--
The bridge!
He's headed for the bridge!
Are you sure you wanna
do this alone?
This is what he wants, isn't it?
At least give me time to get
the gang together. Hey wait!
I wouldn't want to keep him
waiting now, would I?
Hey Kaneda, hold on!
Will you think?
Half of them seem to be
anti-government demonstrators.
The rest are--
Well, they're more like
crazy cult and onlookers.
They're following
after the subject.
And more and more
of them keep coming.
Flames of purity raise the
corrupt city and burn forever
all the unclean
believers of our time.
Give yourselves unto
the flames so that all of you
should be born again.
Now consume our hearts,
wash our unclean hearts
in the eternal fire.
Your bodies will be purified
in the flames.
Ready?
What?
Fire!
Set the switch to hold
for three seconds,
then convert your beams.
Aim. Fire!
Look out!
Let's get out of here!
Save me!
Ground forces.
Ground forces come in.
Report immediately, what is the
subject's status? Do you read?
Line to the Doctor.
We have confirmation
of his recent movements
and are in pursuit.
His present position is-- Ha--
coordinates 99871 by 4332.
That's about
two kilometers south of
the Olympic construction site
in the old city.
What?!
Where did that blast come from?
Look! That must be out
over at the tollbooth
guarded by the second platoon.
What the hell?
Please turn around now. This
area is off limits to civilians.
Huh? What? That's the
escaped subject? Stop!
Don't come any closer!
Stop dammit!
Hmm. Nice place you have here,
isn't it?
Huh?
You were the girl
that was with Kaneda.
You shouldn't use your power in
this way for it is not correct.
What's that?
Because in the end you won't
be able to control it
and it will control you.
It's the kids talking.
You're those brats, right?
Nice one.
Wait, Colonel.
It's not safe here.
Alright now, next move.
Open now!
What the hell is this?
That is Akira
before you, Tetsuo.
That's the Akira you wanted
to meet. There is your messiah.
The chosen one that
you've been looking for.
Not long after
his transcendental awakening,
his organs and tissues
were subjected
to ever test known
to modern science.
He's dead. That's it.
What you see now lying there
is all that's left of him.
And all of the
scientists back then
were unable
to solve the mystery,
so they decided to trust
all their collective data
and test samples
to future generations
by preserving them in frozen
capsules and locking them away.
SOL. We will use SOL.
Akira has been dead all this
time and now you know the truth.
Well, are you
satisfied now, Tetsuo?
Now, will you return with us?
Like hell!
Contact the Central Defense
Center, and tell them
to patch us through into
SOL's major control curcuits,
right away!
Yes, sir.
Asshole! Watch it.
Hey, watch it jerk.
Dammit, move!
Get out of the way. Move it.
What is this?
A science classroom?
What's wrong?
Have some trouble?
Yeah, but I already took care
of it. And you're too late,
you missed the show.
Tetsuo, you had me
worried again.
I figured you'd be standing here
sobbing like a little baby.
Kaneda, you've always been
a pain in the ass you know.
You've been telling me what
to do since we were kids.
You always treat me like a kid.
You always show up and
start bossing me around
and don't you deny it.
And now you're a boss too...
of this pile of rubble.
Kaneda!
That's mister Kaneda
to you, punk!
Tetsuo!
Son of a bitch.
Kay!
Aww dammit.
Let's do it.
Haha, gotcha!
What?
Huh?
The damn battery's dead.
What's the matter now Kaneda?
Ah dammit! It aint fair, Tetsuo.
Fight with your bare hands.
Oh, this is funny.
Feeling frustrated, Kaneda?
Now do you understand
how it feels being
little and helpless?
Huh?
Huh? Where's this
light coming from?
Were we on target?
Hard to tell, too close
to the impact point.
The montiors are getting
too much electrical--
Prepare a second volley, now.
Hey! Ka-ne-da!
Tetsu-- eh?
Shit!
Huh? What tha?
Correcting error now
on tracking system.
T-minus 20--
Ahh!
Get the fire extinguishers!
Are you ok? Get the fire out!
What's going on?
What happened out there?
Kaneda!
Wha? Kai! Kay!
Kaneda hurry!
Get on! Get on!
Hurry!
What is that?
Reports say it's SOL.
Magnificent.
When Tetsuo's power
reaches it's peak?
Is that what you're thinking?
That's when we do it,
but will it really work?
We know the future
doesn't necessarily
proceed along a single course.
There ought to be
a future we can choose.
It's up to us to find it.
What's Tetsuo's status, Doctor?
Ah, Colonel. We set up
a camera in the stadium
if you want to check.
We have him under observation.
Colonel, you must take a look
at this data. It's phenomenal!
We're still analyzing the energy
given off by the subject
but it's just magnificent!
Oh yes, wonderful.
Of course, this is clearly
a proton collapse.
We're also detecting a fair
number of what we believe
to be unknown
particles to science.
If we could put this into
a theoretical framework then
physics, quantum physics,
humanity itself could know
the fundamental truths--
Well, you see...
w-we still haven't finished
making out adjustments.
W-Wait Colonel! Please!
What tha? The pattern!
You bastard,
what did I tell you?
But Colonel,
I couldn't throw away such
a magnificent subject--
Shut up!
Oh! Oh shit, it's on fire!
My bike!
Quick, the battery!
The battery!
Oh, come on it's burning up!
Hey, what's losing
a bike or two, huh?
What? Then there's nothing wrong
with using yours, right?
I said that out loud did I?
Yeah, you did.
Uh, by the way your bike's
still on fire.
Huh? Oh! Oh man.
Tetsuo?
Tetsuo, why is everyone calling
you Akira? What does it mean?
It means nothing.
He never existed.
It doesn't matter who he is,
they don't care
just so long as
he destroys things.
What's that? Your arm!
Look at it!
Well, it doesn't look like much
but it still works pretty good.
What's wrong? Are you ok?
It's nothing!
Tetsuo, I just--
Shut up! Just go away!
Medicine.
What's wrong, Tetsuo?
Are you in pain?
Go back to the lab
and get that medicine.
Doctor, did you hear that?
I did, Colonel.
Well, any signs of it?
Well I can't be entirely certain
here, but it seems that
the power which had been
held back by the drugs
is breaking free.
He may not be able
to control the power
that has awakened so suddenly.
He's in an extremely
critical condition.
Come back to the lab
and receive proper treatment.
If you don't you may die.
You want me to enroll
in your kindergarten
and live happily
ever after, huh?
Be quiet and do
what you're told?
Take your medicine every day
and end up all shriveled
like those kids?
Kaori. Kaori!
Medicine, please.
N-No.
Stop Tetsuo!
Tetsuo!
Tets--
Kaneda!
Son of a-- Huh?
What are you three doing here?
You didn't learn
your lesson, huh?
Heads up, Tetsuo!
Takashi!
Akira's here.
Help! Kaneda, help please!
Kaori.
Please. Help me.
Help me!
Let her go!
Kaori. Kaori. Kaori!
Tetsuo! Are you there?
Kaori. Kaori's gonna die!
What? What did you say?
My body's not doing
what I tell it to.
My power's acting on it's own.
Kaori! Ah!
Kaori's dying. Kaneda. Help me.
Stop this, Tetsuo! Stop it now!
Kaori's pain...
is coming into me. Ahh!
Tetsuo!
Kaneda! Run away!
Kiyoko, Takashi, Masaru!
Hurry, get away from here!
Come on.
I can't believe it.
It's as if--
Kiyoko! Taka--
Hi. Akira.
Oh no. That's the--
But that's impossible!
W-Where am I?
Hurry. Get into the tunnel.
You'll be safe in there.
Kiyoko. Where are you?
Tetsuo!
Kaneda!
Hang on!
Hurry, you gotta
get out of here.
Go away.
Tetsuo!
Don't go near it!
No don't! Wait, Takashi!
If you went in now you'd
be trapped along with him.
But he-- none of this
is his fault at all.
Takashi!
If we went in there
we wouldn't be strong enough
to come back out again.
But if the three of us tried,
maybe we could save that boy.
You're right. Us three together.
Look at that. We should get out
of here now. H-Hey!
Kaneda's in there.
You see that? You're not revving
your engine enough already.
When you go into a corner,
lean in suicidally. Watch.
What the hell do you call that?
Cornering, man.
You got it, Tetsuo?
Hey look,
they brought another kid.
Is he a transfer student?
His mom and dad left him.
You can see it in his face.
Are these-- Are these all of
your dreams and memories,
Tetsuo?
W-Wait!
Is this Akira?
Yes. We called him here
to the three of us.
He's going to
take Tetsuo with him.
Take him where? Where?
It's too much for Tetsuo.
And for the three of us also.
And Akira, too.
It's way too big for us
as we are now.
But someday we ought
to be able to--
because it has already begun.
Your friend, she's--
My friend. Kay. It's Kay
you're talking about.
Tetsuo.
This is yours, right?
They're always like that
with the new kids.
Hey, you came today, right?
They beat me up too. But the
truth is, those guys are wimps.
My name is...
Tetsuo. Tetsuo Shima.
The truth is, I just got here
myself. My name is--
Kaneda. Kaneda. Kaneda!
Kay.
What in the world is
happening? What's this?
This is-- If this is correct,
it's showing that this
is the birth of the universe!
Kay!
What's going on here? Ahh!
Disappearing. It's disappearing!
Kaneda can you hear me?
Tetsuo.
Kaneda, what is--?
Thank you.
Huh?
You called me, didn't you?
And I heard you.
Kaneda. Oh my.
Where's Tetsuo?
He just left. Those kids
did too. Akira also.
Kaneda, back then--
Did you just--?
Kaneda! You're alive!
I thought you were in there.
I thought you were
in there for sure.
Tetsuo! What happened to
Tetsuo? Is he-- dead?
I'm not sure. S-Something--
But someday
we ought to be able to--
because it has already begun.
I am. Tetsuo.