[NARRATOR] Long since erased
from the records of time,
there once existed two
European Clans who served as
overseers of history
for the powers that be.
The Umbra witches,
dwellers of the darkness,
and the Lumen sages,
controllers of light.
The witches served the demons
and the sages served the angels.
Still the clans
respected each other,
and worked to ensure that
the balance between them
withstood the passage of time.
One day, that
balance was toppled,
resulting in an era of strife.
It began when a Lumen
sage and an Umbra witch
violated the
decrees that bound them
and produced a child together.
The woman was imprisoned
and the man was banished...
but that was
only the beginning.
Both clans had a law never
to be broken that stated,
"The intersection
of light and dark
will bring calamity
to this earth."
With the birth of this
child, it appeared that
old fear had become reality.
Each clan possessed an "Eye."
Together, the
"Eyes of the World"
governed the power of creation.
The forbidden child, whom
the Umbra witches cared for,
possessed the powers
of the treasured Left Eye.
When the two eyes
are brought together,
the Creator Jubileus
will be resurrected
and a New World will be born.
It is both heaven's will
and order that Jubileus
should become
incarnate once more.
Being on the side of heaven,
the sages desired that
this should come to pass, but
the witches were against them,
resulting in a conflict
over the treasured Left Eye.
The conflict escalated until
it became a full-blown war
between angels and demons,
with a myriad of battles
fueled by ambition and desire.
[NARRATOR] In the end, it led
to their mutual destruction.
And the truth
of their existence
slipped into obscurity.
[NARRATOR] The forbidden child
grew up to become a witch,
but she was hidden away and
sealed in a secret place...
[NARRATOR] Five
hundred years later...
the witch, who hunts
angels has returned.
♪
[sniff]
Fleur de Cirey...
[footsteps]
♪
[WOMAN] I am the way
into the city of woe.
I am the way to
a forsaken people.
I am the way
into eternal sorrow.
Abandon all hope...
ye who enter here.
[WOMAN] I am the way
into the city of woe.
I am the way to
a forsaken people.
I am the way
into eternal sorrow.
Abandon all hope...
oh ye who dare to enter here.
♪
The hell...?
Ah!
♪
[WOMAN grunts]
[WOMAN] Huuahhh!
[horns blast]
Now I can show the world
what you really are, you witch.
♪
[WOMAN] Naughty, naughty.
Just look at what
you've done to my outfit.
Very cheeky.
♪
[MAN grunts]
Don't interrupt a
man and his music.
Besides I ain't the partner
you came here to dance with.
Heh.
[WOMAN] Still, you gave a
wonderful performance, Rodin.
[RODIN] Any time, Bayonetta.
[BAYONETTA] By the way...
Is the new Knight
you promised me ready?
Yeah...
Like it or not,
it's ready when you are.
[RODIN grunts]
[grunts]
Enter "The Elfin Knight."
[RODIN] Not a bad name,
if I say so myself.
♪
[BAYONETTA] The fun's
just getting started.
♪
[MAN] Ah!
What the fuck
is going on here?
♪
Beautiful!
[distant crash]
[MAN gasps]
[MAN] Ahh...! My car!
[chuckles]
Goddammit! It's not
even paid off yet!
♪
[chuckles]
[power yell]
[MAN] Shit! This is bad!
[BELOVED] I must become the
cornerstone of the Left Eye.
[BELOVED] Relinquish all
your powers of darkness to me.
What are you talking about?
[BELOVED] The Creator
will return soon.
Sorry, still no clue.
Oh man! I must be going crazy!
♪
[pained outcry]
[BAYONETTA] I don't think
you've met my infernal partner.
He's telling me that
he feels a bit peckish.
[BAYONETTA] I believe he'd
be quite satisfied if he
made a meal out of you...
What do you think?
[summoning spell]
[roars]
[BAYONETTA] There's a good
boy. Dinnertime, my sweet!
[chuckles]
[roars]
[BAYONETTA] Oh, I almost
forgot. There's another reason
I'm letting him devour you.
[BAYONETTA]
I really like to watch.
I enjoy your face
distorted with pain.
[BELOVED] Transform the
world into what it should be...
That's more like it.
I'm all hot and bothered.
Ooh! So exciting!
[BELOVED] Glory be
to the Creator Jubileus!
♪
[RODIN] That was
quite a show you put on.
[RODIN] So how 'bout it?
Do you like the Knight?
[BAYONETTA] Not bad.
It's a cheap toy...
but it should do for a while.
[sigh]
Guess it's time to open the bar.
See you there.
If I can be bothered.
[RODIN] I'll fix you
a Mysterious Destiny...
with one olive.
[BAYONETTA] I
thought I saw a mouse.
But it was actually
my little Cheshire.
The name is Luka.
And you'd better
start remembering it!
[LUKA] What do you want?
[BAYONETTA] Naughty
boys who stalk the ladies
never get the girl.
[LUKA] I'm not worried.
I'm pretty easy on the eyes.
Just ask Claire, Trish,
Sylvia, and Ammy...
They're all
crazy about me. Heh.
[BAYONETTA] My... So many
lady friends. I'm impressed.
Still, it's not
nice to be a peeping Tom.
Such a bad little boy.
Ah... you...! Come on,
that's professional equipment!
Dammit! That
camera was expensive.
And then there's my car,
with a huge dent in it!
[BAYONETTA] You think
I broke those things?
[LUKA] Ha...! Did
everything just magically
slip your mind... again?
What you did twenty years ago,
I'm never going to forget that!
[LUKA] Fleur de Cirey,
Eau du Parfum.
I'll always
remember that smell.
[LUKA] It's the same smell
that clung to the air the day
my father was murdered.
The day I first saw you.
Ahhh!
Aaaughhh!
[YOUNG LUKA] Father!
[LUKA] Father...
Now I'm the journalist...
And I'll expose you
for what you really are.
Oh. What a tease.
[LUKA] Don't ever forget!
Even when I can't see you,
I know where you
are by your scent.
Fleur de Cirey with its
subtle hints of rosemary.
In the language of the flowers,
rosemary is supposed
to equate to remembrance,
but that doesn't quite
equate to you now does it?
I think you
might need to hone your
sense of smell... Cheshire.
It's Luka!
[BAYONETTA] There isn't any
rosemary in Fleur de Cirey.
The herb repels demons.
I wear it to ward off evil.
A witch with a perfume to
ward off evil? Ha ha. Funny.
[distant sirens]
[LUKA] Guess they
heard all the commotion.
[BAYONETTA] See you, Cheshire.
[LUKA] Bayonetta, wait!
Ahhh!
Oh crap!
Reawakening will come soon.
[chuckles]
♪
[meow]
Good girl.
You should go somewhere else.
There are demons
around here. Hmmh.
[door opens]
[REPORTER] I'm standing here
in front of the Ithavoll Tower,
in Vigrid, sacred
site of the Ragna.
This year, the
five hundred year wait
for the return of
the Creator Jubileus
is meant to come to an end.
Believers all
around the world are
joyously celebrating
in anticipation.
However, we are
also continuing to receive
reports of believers
committing suicide
in order to "aid
the resurrection."
The latest of these
came just yesterday
when a head Ragna
priest committed suicide
with over twenty believers.
In a related story, someone
broke into and partially
destroyed the cathedral
housing their bodies.
Many countries...
in response to these events,
have declared a
state of emergency.
And Ragna believers are
being asked to remain calm.
[REPORTER] The supreme
leader of the Ithavoll Group,
who is in effect governor
of this ancient sacred city,
is preparing to appear in
public for the first time.
[RODIN] What's
with these humans?
Everybody's freakin' out?
[MAN] It's pathetic!
Runnin' around offing
themselves for some god
no one ever heard of?
But... I ain't
complaining.
Thanks to these suicidal
schmos, I'm in business.
Uh-huh. The
business of overcharging
poor suckers for funerals...
And you weren't
exactly a peach before.
Hey, since I've
been makin' money...
I'm one of the good guys now!
Without good hearted
souls like me to put these
bastards six feet under,
where'd society be... Tell me?
When ya think about it,
I'm providing a vital
service to the community.
[laughs]
If you're such a
philanthropist you should be
donating to the church...
Or at least... giving me
that reward you still owe me.
Don't make me laugh...
You enjoy killing
them haloed douchebags!
I hear you get all fired up...
Shouldn't a thrill
like that be enough...?
[gun cocks]
[MAN] Hey, no
need to get testy!
[BAYONETTA] You were saying?
[MAN] Shit! You're the one
that trashed the cathedral.
So how come
I'm getting screwed?
You really wanna take every
cent I earned on this thing?!
C'mon! Cut me a break.
[BAYONETTA] My condolences.
But the deal was
I see to the funeral,
and you get me the
information I asked for.
[MAN] Yeah, yeah.
Did anyone ever tell ya
that you're pretty damn bossy
for someone who can't
even remember her own name?
[RODIN] Her name is Bayonetta.
[MAN] That's the name
you gave her, Rodin.
Twenty years ago, she
woke up stuck in a casket
at the bottom of a lake.
But she's still one big mystery.
The only thing she remembers
is that she's a witch.
I mean killing angels
and offering them up
to demons is great and all...
But as long as she's
working her ass off,
she might as well
make some money.
[BAYONETTA] If I
needed a biographer,
you wouldn't be my first choice.
[cheering on TV]
[REPORTER]
I've just been told...
Mr. Balder of
the Ithavoll Group...
is about to appear
for the first time.
It's fair to say...
this mutli-national
conglomerate's vast fortune
supports the economy
here in Vigrid.
Thus, many here are
looking to Mr. Balder
to handle this crisis.
[REPORTER] If he succeeds...
[MAN] Hey, that's the guy!
I got the scoop
on that big shot,
so I'll give you
the lowdown on him.
[MAN] So, he's the head of
all those Ragna believers.
And apparently,
it's the first time
he's shown his face in public.
This just happens
to coincide with the
first resurrection of
Jubileus in five hundred years.
Rumor has it, this guy's
been alive since the last one.
And if that's the
truth, he ain't human.
The Ithavoll Group also
has some cutting edge
technology that ain't
exactly in keeping with their
"friendly neighborhood
church" image.
But to believers this
tech is a freakin' miracle!
According to my sources,
this Balder guy is a descendent
of the lost sages.
Ones from old stories
that worshipped light
and were enemies of witches.
So basically, if my
informants are correct,
this guy is a modern day sage.
Let's hope he doesn't try
to burn you at the stake.
[chuckles]
There's a tasty bit of
info for ya. Not bad, right?
[BAYONETTA gasps]
[BALDER] My dear sweet
child... I'm waiting.
[MAN] See Rodin.
She seems happy with that.
[MAN] I'm going home.
My kids are baking me a
birthday cake. Cute fuckers.
Skippin' out without
paying your tab again, Enzo?
You can take
care of that.
Call it my birthday
present. Thanks a lot, pal.
[ENZO] I'll give ya a heads
up when I've got another job.
Freaky fat-ass
little undertaker man.
[ENZO] Ciao!
♪
[RODIN] That's the
thing you were holding
when you woke up, right?
Yes.
Do you think it might help
you remember something someday?
It might.
But at the moment,
that man Balder of the
Ithavoll Group intrigues me
far more than an old lipstick.
He holds the key to
my missing memories.
Of that I feel certain.
You figured that out...
from what Enzo told ya?
Call it a woman's intuition.
Hm.
So Vigrid... that's
your next stop?
[BAYONETTA] Yes.
[RODIN] Then I'll hook you up.
Take whatever you want.
♪
[BALDER] I've waited
five hundred years.
Now, the time has come.
She will find her
way here, I have no doubt.
[WOMAN] What then?
Will history repeat itself?
Or have you seen to that?
Her path is predestined.
And I'll tell you how I know.
I understand the
rules of the three worlds;
the Human world, Paradiso,
Inferno. I see it all...
And I have seen our
actions helping the Creator
to start a new
cycle of creation!
[WOMAN] How ironic
that the Right Eye
would choose chaos over order.
[BALDER] You're wrong.
The world is already in chaos.
That is why she
and I must become
the "Eyes of the World."
Until the three worlds
form a perfect whole,
there will be no true salvation.
Sound's like the
logic of a madman.
You lack the
capacity to understand.
How unfortunate that
you cannot part with me.
[BALDER] I am pleased with
how things are progressing.
The angels have
been working hard.
[BALDER] As have you... Jeanne.
[heavy exhale]
[BALDER] We've waited
five hundred years.
Such a long time.
You must be looking forward
to seeing her again.
But do not forget,
everything we do
is to prepare for the coming.
[BALDER] The creation of a
New World is close at hand.
[LUKA] The memory
card's still intact...
But I still didn't
manage to get any pictures
of her true form.
You can't hide from me,
Bayonetta. I'll find you.
The Ragna...
descendent of sages...
[LUKA] Wait... Wasn't my father
trying to uncover the truth
about the sages and witches...
when Bayonetta killed him?
[train horn]
[BALDER] Time to wake up,
my dear, sweet child.
[GIRL] Daddy?
That's right. Come dear.
[gasp]
[distant motorcycle engine]
♪
Hm.
Ha!
[screaming]
You must forgive me,
but who are you?
[scoffs]
[revs motorcyle engine]
♪
[BAYONETTA] You've
quite the familiar face.
And we seem to be
using the same powers.
So I'll ask again, who are you?
[JEANNE chuckles] Same powers?!
I think your little dip in that
lake has left you a bit rusty.
I have had trouble
remembering things of late...
But have we met? You
seem to know who I am.
It would seem I know who
you are better than you do.
My interest is piqued.
I'd be happy to explain
it all if you can defeat me.
Ha!
♪
The fun's just getting started.
I remember fighting like this.
Tell me, have I knocked
any of you memories loose?
Nothing so far.
But I have a
feeling I'll remember more
once I've knocked
you unconscious.
You can try.
[JEANNE] Haaaugh!
♪
[gasps]
[JEANNE] You've
really disappointed me.
Is that all you've got?
[BAYONETTA] Oh, I don't know.
I think I still have a
few tricks up my sleeve.
[JEANNE chuckles] Is that
right? Then show me what else
you can do with those toys.
I will... since
you're so eager to play.
[BAYONETTA] Uh!
Bloody hell!
What a waste.
You're not ready.
[grunts]
♪
[GIRL] So Daddy,
where's Mummy? Is she here?
[BALDER] Well, that depends.
If you're a good girl,
then Mummy will come
for you very soon.
[GIRL] Cereza's a good girl!
[BALDER] Can you wait
for Mummy all by yourself?
Mhmmm. I can!
[CEREZA shudders]
It's alright
isn't it, Cheshire?
[CEREZA] Hurry Mummy...
Please come quick!
[thunder]
[meow]
Hm...
[BAYONETTA] I don't recall
this bar being here before.
[RODIN] It's a
temporary outpost.
So what'll it be? You here
for business or pleasure?
[BAYONETTA] These
certainly don't live up to
the name "Knight," now did they?
[RODIN] These were
real works of art.
What did you do to 'em?
[BAYONETTA] All I did
was have a little shootout
with some awful woman.
You were shooting
at yourself then?
Hm?
I'll fix 'em, alright?
[BAYONETTA] Make them a little
tougher this time around.
Can I offer you a drink then?
No, I'm in a hurry.
I hope the next one's better
or I may have to put
a chainsaw on my arm.
[engine revs]
[CEREZA] Mummy!
Where are you? Mummy!
[BAYONETTA] Apparently,
Rodin isn't the only one
who wants me to take a detour.
Now then, where exactly am I?
This place is definitely
not a party spot is it?
[CEREZA] Mummy. Mummy!
[crying]
Mummy? Mummy!
Uh...!
[CEREZA] Mummy! Mummy!
[CEREZA] A ghost!
[BAYONETTA] You
can see the angels?
[CEREZA shudders]
[CEREZA] Mummy...! Mummy!
Ahhh...
This is inconvenient.
♪
[BAYONETTA] I'm not
usually one to play savior,
but I can make an
exception this once.
♪
[CEREZA screams]
No, Cheshire! Cheshire!
Cheshire?
[screams]
Mummy!
Stop crying now,
understand?
There are
just two things
that I hate
in this world...
And that is cockroaches
and crying babies.
Um, yes... Mummy.
You go take cover, little one.
An angel seeks my
attention. I won't be long.
[BAYONETTA] Curious
though... it doesn't seem to
want to hurt this little girl.
[BAYONETTA] Tell me!
What's going on?
Why have you gone through the
trouble of bringing me here?
We'll be safe here, right?
[ARDOR] I must become the
cornerstone of the resurrection!
Ah. Then let's dance!
♪
I'm going to enjoy this.
[power yell]
♪
[CEREZA] Mummy!
You find me
that engaging do you?
[BAYONETTA] And you
intend to take me by force?
[BAYONETTA] Bad boy! That's
no way to treat a girl.
I'll have to
teach you a lesson!
♪
Give it your best
shot! Come on then.
Let's dance, baby!
[ARDOR] Glory be to
the Creator, Jubileus!
[BAYONETTA war cry]
[CEREZA] Mummy! Mummy!
Ugh...
[BAYONETTA] What's
your name, little one?
[CEREZA] Cereza...
Did you forget, Mummy?
[BAYONETTA] Probably.
But I likely won't
remember it later, either.
What are you doing in
such a dreadful place?
[CEREZA] My daddy
told me to wait here.
He said if I was good then
Mummy would come and get me.
[BAYONETTA] He
left you all alone?
I'm not all alone, Mummy...
Cheshire's here with me.
[BAYONETTA] You
were crying like a baby.
Please, Mummy...
Let's go home.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Slow down, little one.
I am not your mother.
So stop calling me that.
I'm sure your
daddy will be ba--
But I want to
stay with you, Mummy.
[giggles]
This is awkward.
Mmm.
[sigh]
[BAYONETTA] Come along.
[CEREZA] Wait, Mummy!
Ow!
You're awfully
clumsy, little one. Hm?
Please... Save his soul...
What is it, Mummy?
[BAYONETTA] Where did
you get this, little one?
You gave it
to me, Mummy.
For my birthday,
remember?
[giggles]
[BAYONETTA] No more
falling over. Got it?
[CEREZA] Yes!
[BAYONETTA] Make sure
you hold on tight!
[CEREZA] Yes, Mummy!
[BAYONETTA] And no more "Mummy."
[BAYONETTA] Uh!
[CEREZA] Ah!
[distant running water]
[giggles]
I miss taking
a bath together!
Isn't this fun, Mummy?
Honestly, little one...
we're only doing this
because you wouldn't
stop nagging me.
[BAYONETTA] Do you with
live your mother, little one?
[CEREZA] You know I don't.
I've lived all by myself
forever and
ever and ever.
Then your mother
hates crybabies too.
But I'm not a crybaby!
Mummy... Why don't
you ever come to visit me?
Why did you leave me on my own?
I don't know why, little one.
And I wouldn't know
because I'm not your mother.
[CEREZA] Mummy's stupid.
[grunts]
[BAYONETTA] Were you
really all by yourself?
No friends?
[CEREZA] Just Cheshire.
Mmm.
Ah...!
[CEREZA] Ooh, pretty!
Like it's snowing!
That was easy.
[BAYONETTA] I don't recall
ordering any room service.
[BAYONETTA] You may want
to rethink your methods.
Someone could sue.
There're only so many
methods to choose from
when dealing with a-- whu! Ah!
Mummy, who is
that old man?
[BAYONETTA] That's Cheshire...
I mean, just a pervert who
photographs ladies
without their permission.
Pervert?
M-Mummy...? Y-You?!
You have a child? You?!
Of course not. Please.
But... making a baby;
that's another story.
Whoa! Don't
get the wrong idea!
I mean... it might
be... the right idea...
But... just... not right now.
[LUKA screams]
[CEREZA] Ahh! He fell!
Is the old man dead now?
[BAYONETTA] No ghosts
are coming to fetch him,
so he must be alive...
unfortunately.
What gives...?
I'm not an old guy yet.
They're asleep, already?
[BAYONETTA] You're
certainly persistent.
How much longer do you
intend to hang around here
with that little
toy of yours, Cheshire?
[LUKA] It's Luka!
[LUKA] Do you understand
what's going on
in this city right
now, Bayonetta?
I really don't care.
[LUKA] Why're you here then?
It's got nothing
to do with you.
[LUKA grunts]
Everything you
do has to do with me.
You killed my father.
[BAYONETTA] You know that was
all just a misunderstanding.
[LUKA] You always say that.
Doesn't make it true.
Like me, my father
was a journalist.
He was obsessed with one
case his entire career;
the mystery of
sages and witches.
[LUKA] He probably never dreamed
he'd be killed by a witch.
It's ironic really.
[BAYONETTA] Hm.
[LUKA] I thought that
once I exposed you
for the witch you
are, I might be able
to finally solve the puzzle.
According to my
father's journals...
five hundred years ago...
both witches
and sages alike
just disappeared all at once.
And their legends
vanished with them.
[LUKA] But then you, Bayonetta,
a witch like those of old,
somehow appeared
twenty years ago.
And now a descendent of
the sages, this Mr. Balder,
has come forward. It
all has something to do
with the resurrection;
I'd bet on it.
You're going to
see Balder, right?
Well... possibly.
[LUKA] When I do, I hope
it helps you remember...
what you did that
day twenty years ago...
Why you did it.
Why you killed him!
[CEREZA] Mummy... Mummy...?
Mummy, where did you go?
Little one.
Sorry but I'm babysitting.
Too bad you can't
take over for me.
[BAYONETTA] Say, that
might be a good idea.
[CEREZA] Mummy!
[CEREZA] Mummy. Where
were you? I was lonely.
[BAYONETTA] Stop that.
One more tear
and you'll be
sleeping alone. Got it?
[CEREZA] Yes. You'll never
leave me again, right Mummy?
Heh.
[CEREZA crying]
[sobbing]
What is it? What's
wrong, little girl?
[CEREZA] I'm a... I'm a crybaby.
And Mummy hates crybabies.
So she left me.
So you mean
Bayonetta's gone?
Oh no!
I didn't think she was
serious about me babysitting.
Hey. Don't cry on me, kid.
We'll go look for
your mummy together.
Thanks, old guy.
[LUKA] Listen up. I'm a guy,
but I'm not old. Understand?
[CEREZA] Yes, old man.
[LUKA] Ugh... Why
don't we just get going.
[BALDER] The two eyes
that oversee the world
are about to be reunited.
The resurrection of the
Creator Jubileus is at hand.
And all of the
angels are restless.
The followers
of light are agreed.
It has been decided.
She will be sacrificed in
order to awaken the Left Eye.
Light, dark, human. All the
strife, all the struggle...
Everything for the
Creation of a New World!
♪
Hm?
That's a rather
nice set of wheels.
Pity it's going to
end up on the scrap heap.
[GUARD A] Huh?
[GUARD B] What is that?
[GUARD B] I think
something's coming this way.
[GUARD B] Do you see anything?
[GUARD A] No.
[GUARDS] Ah!
Ahhh!
♪
Now I'm cross.
[LUKA] Looks like
we just missed her.
Too bad... But at
least your mummy
made it easy for
us to find her.
Yes!
[BAYONETTA summoning spell]
I've let you
joyride long enough...
Now it's my turn to let
loose and have some fun.
♪
Ooooh...
Next time you
want to pick me up,
have a little
more under the hood.
[bells ringing]
Uh... Another one already?
This is starting
to wear a little thin.
[TEMPERANTIA] May
my eternal soul reside
with the Creator... Jubileus.
[CEREZA] Old man, are we almost
caught up with Mummy yet?
We're nearly there...
Just be patient.
[CEREZA] Yes.
Once we get to the
airport we won't be very far
from the island where
the Ithavoll Tower is.
We'll find her.
Don't worry.
Really? Promise!
Yup.
Unless...
Something really bad's
happened to the airport.
Then, we might
have a problem.
Look! We're almost there.
[gasps]
[LUKA] What?! Oh, come on!
You gotta be kidding me!
Now that's just overdoing
it a bit, even for Bayonetta!
[gasps] That ghost... is big!
Mummy!
[BASE GUY] Retreat! Retreat!
[BAYONETTA summoning spell]
[groaning]
[BAYONETTA] The more I hunt...
the better I feel.
It's an amazing rush of power.
And power is such a turn on!
[DEMON grunting]
♪
Your new look suits you!
[TEMPERANTIA moans]
[LUKA] Dammit, Bayonetta! If
I can't find transport around
here we're going to be
in some seriously deep shit!
[LUKA] Don't be afraid!
I just spotted our way out!
Stop it! Wait!
[LUKA] Huh? What is it?
[CEREZA] Put me down.
[LUKA] Be careful,
don't get burned.
Did you see your mummy?
I see ghosts.
Great, she sees ghosts.
They're coming! Look!
Huh?
[LUKA] Stop kidding
around, little girl.
I don't see anything.
[LUKA sniffing]
Do I smell rosemary?
[CEREZA] Try these, old man.
Ah, that's sweet...
But I told you I'm not old.
My eyesight's just fine,
but it's time to go now.
You have to put them on now!
Alright then.
[LUKA] Holy shit! What
the hell are those things?
Are those angels?
[LUKA] No way! Is
this really happening?
[LUKA] Oh, come on,
these things are angels?!
I thought angels were supposed
to be pretty and play harps!
These guys are monsters!
♪
[BAYONETTA] You actually
chased me here, Cheshire?
You must be mad.
Mummy!
[distant crashing]
[LUKA] Shit is that
nightmare an angel, too?
[CEREZA] Uh! Mummy!
She'll be fine! We
have to get outta here!
♪
[LUKA] So, uh, little
girl, does your mummy
fight these big
bad monsters a lot?
[CEREZA] Mummy's a witch
and witches protect people.
They're very strong.
You think that...
witches protect people?
Mhm. Why wouldn't they?
When I grow up
I'll be strong, too.
And then I'll protect Mummy!
♪
[BAYONETTA] Hmph!
Let's see... Perhaps
you'll be prettier
when you're blown to pieces?
♪
[CEREZA] Yay! Mummy did it!
She beat all the ghosts!
[LUKA] Here. You can
have these back now.
Hm...?
Your glasses...
Are they, uh, magic?
[CEREZA] No. They're
not magic, silly.
I can see the
ghosts without them.
[LUKA] Angels? Really...?
And yet somehow I
can still smell her...
[door opens]
[CEREZA] Hm?
Mummy!
Little one... Were you a
crybaby while I was gone?
No, I wasn't!
Good.
When I asked you...
to babysit the little one
I meant at home... Luka.
How many
times have I told you?
[LUKA] I'm not Luka.
I'm Cheshire!
Now stop pissing me off
and get it right already!
[CEREZA] You're
not Cheshire. He is.
Wha--?
Do you think that
you could take us to
the Ithavoll Tower, Cheshire...?
[LUKA clearts throat]
Well ladies, you're in luck.
Because that's exactly
where Air Luka
Flight 001 is headed.
Fasten your seatbelts;
this might be a bumpy ride.
[FORTITUDO] The Umbra witch.
She does indeed possess
an outstanding power.
What the sage told us is true.
The two eyes, one of darkness
and the other of light,
have observed this
world for many years.
The creation of a
new world is upon us.
Umbra witch... may the
Creator, Jubileus, grace you.
We've arrived.
[BALDER] It will be good to
see you again, my dear child.
Your difficult
journey is nearing an end.
The key to your
missing memories is ready
[BALDER] and waiting for you,
my dear child. As am I.
Give me everything
you've got. Everything...
[sirens]
Oh shit!
It's on our tail!
[LUKA] What the--?
How are we safe?
Where's Bayonetta?
Hmh.
[JEANNE] You're late...
I've been waiting.
I hope you've got
something a little more
entertaining for me this time.
[BAYONETTA] You'll
find out soon enough.
This time I plan to
pummel you until you
spill your guts...
or tell me everything.
[JEANNE] Go ahead. Beat it
all out of me! If you can.
[grunts]
[JEANNE] Shame that's the only
thing you have to fight with.
[JEANNE] I can still
sense your fear.
[BAYONETTA] Fear?
When your memory returns,
you'll understand everything.
Even so, you'll
still fear your destiny.
[JEANNE] "The intersection
of light and dark
will bring calamity
to this earth."
That was the ancient law.
But it was broken, and the
ensuing disaster sent both
sages and witches
into a spiral of chaos
that is still felt to this day.
It was the birth of
a child that set all these
events in motion.
That child was you.
Legend states
that the Creator's power
is known as the
"Eyes of the World."
That power is an awesome one,
and it's half yours.
You are the Left Eye.
[JEANNE] It appears
we have an intruder.
Where am I?
[FORTITUDO] I've been
waiting for you, Left Eye.
[FORTITUDO] Witch Jeanne...
Any action that
hinders the coming
of the Creator
will not be tolerated.
What makes you think an
angel has the authority
to order a witch around?
Get lost.
[FORTITUDO] Insolent witch.
I'll be waiting
for you, Left Eye,
by the side of
my Lord and master.
Nice place, if
you're into purgatory!
Still it's a few
steps up from your bar.
[scoffs]
[distant screeching]
[RODIN] How many times I gotta
tell these morons?
I am not your dance partner!
Aaahhh!
[screeching]
[RODIN] I've got a
new weapon for ya...
The workmanship's solid.
Hm...
Hopefully this new
one will satisfy me.
It won't disappoint.
[power yell]
The Scarborough Fair!
[RODIN] New and improved!
This bad boy might even
be hard for you
to get a handle on.
♪
[RODIN] See you
at the gates of hell.
Perhaps if I feel
like going slumming.
Well that was interesting.
And now it seems we have
a level playing field.
Don't worry...
I'll try to be gentle.
Careful... You really
can't afford to lose...
If you do, that little girl
of yours will disappear.
Yes! Don't hold back!
I remember...
Jeanne, as heir to
the clan, the time has come
to prove your right to
fight under the Umbran name.
You may select
your opponent of choice.
Then I wish to
face the outcast.
No! It is forbidden!
[UMBRAN ELDER] The
child is of impure blood.
Challenging her
would be a violation
of our tenets of faith!
[BAYONETTA] I remember now.
I've been here before.
At last...! We can
finish what we started!
♪
You remember...
So are you still afraid?
[gasp]
Uh!
♪
[JEANNE] Let go of your fear.
Accept your fate.
And feel your power return.
[JEANNE] It is our
charge as witches
to protect the
treasured Left Eye.
Even if it
belongs to an outcast.
You said our charge.
♪
[power yell]
[JEANNE] Ugh...!
♪
[BAYONETTA crying]
Mummy... Mummy!
[shaky breathing]
[crying]
[FORTITUDO chuckles]
The treasured Left Eye of
the witches... is ours now!
[FORTITUDO] Come, Left Eye...
[FORTITUDO] The Creator,
Jubileus, awaits us.
Our treasured
Left Eye, will never...
[JEANNE] fall into the
hands of anyone else!
♪
[BAYONETTA] Jeanne,
it was you... You did it.
[JEANNE] You lost the will to
fight when your mother died.
As a witch I had to protect
you, by any means necessary.
In the innocence
of our childhood,
we used to play
together... as friends.
[BAYONETTA] I remember...
You were my
only friend back then.
So very long ago.
Apart from that stuffed
animal you fancied so.
[BAYONETTA] Jeanne...
When you chose five
hundred years ago...
why did you choose
me as your opponent?
I was the outcast
that everyone hated.
[JEANNE] I wanted to be
the most powerful witch,
and that meant I had to defeat
the most powerful opponent.
That was why.
You cannot run from the
treacherous Lumen sage Balder.
The path you are on
will soon come to an end.
But do not fear
your fate, embrace it!
[JEANNE] Stand...!
Stand and open your eyes!
And remember, for every truth...
there is another...
yet to be seen.
[gasp]
[JEANNE screams]
[BAYONETTA] Jeanne!
[distant rumbling]
Oh, Jeanne.
[door opens]
[CEREZA] Mummy!
Hm... I got us
here in one piece...
But then again it seems
like they were expecting us.
[CEREZA giggles]
Mummy...?
Little one... what treasure
do you love the most?
Cheshire?
[CEREZA] Mnn-mmm.
Cheshire is my friend.
This here is my
greatest treasure.
[BAYONETTA] When you love
something, never lose it.
You must take care
to keep it safe...
and always close to your heart.
[CEREZA] I will! And I made up
my mind not to cry any more.
Because I want to
grow up brave and strong
just like you are Mummy.
You're not afraid of anything!
So I won't be either!
Wait! Are you gonna
confront him all on your own?
[BAYONETTA]
Even if I said "yes"
you'd still tag
along, wouldn't you?
[CEREZA] Wouldn't you?
[chuckles]
[muffled heartbeat]
Ah...!
[LUKA] It does look like
someone's been expecting us.
They even rolled
out the red carpet.
[BALDER] Rise my child.
Realize your true potential!
It's time to open
the "Eyes of the World."
It's Daddy!
My daddy's here!
Wait! Little one!
Her daddy's here?!
[CEREZA] This way!
[BAYONETTA] Little one!
[CEREZA] Look, Daddy!
Now Mummy's here, too.
I have been waiting
a very long time...
for this family reunion.
Save him...
[BALDER] Did you have a good
time visiting with Mummy?
[CEREZA] Uh huh. Mummy's
very strong, and brave too!
[BALDER] I see...
[CEREZA] At first I was
scared of the ghosts,
but Mummy said not to
cry, so I don't anymore.
[BALDER] I think you've
grown up a little, Cereza.
[CEREZA] I have, Daddy!
[BALDER] So... tonight you
sleep alone like a big girl.
[CEREZA] Awww... But I don't
want to go to sleep yet, Daddy.
I still have lots to tell you!
[BALDER] You
can tell me tomorrow.
Right now it's bedtime.
Awe...
Yes, Daddy.
[BALDER] That's a good girl.
[BALDER] Sweet dreams!
[CEREZA] Good night, Daddy.
[CEREZA] Mummy...
I'm not going
to be afraid anymore.
No matter what.
That's my girl.
See you later, Mummy!
[BAYONETTA] How were you able
to bring me here from the past?
The past...?
Wha--? Uh.
[BALDER] I opened a door
of space-time distortion
through the influence
of Jubileus' coming.
I wanted you to see both
the light and dark of this
foolish world through
innocent, untainted eyes.
He manipulates time?
Who is this guy?
He is the last survivor
of the Lumen sages...
This was all
started... by him.
He is little one's--
No, he is my father.
[LUKA] Auh...!
Five hundred years...
since the last time we met.
[BALDER] And if your
memories were still intact,
this would have been a
much more emotional reunion.
Long have I waited to
purge the chaotic worlds.
Once Jubileus is
resurrected, heaven, hell,
and this world will
become void and be reborn.
And in this new world,
you and I will be gods!
Getting a bit
ahead of ourselves
aren't we Mr. Ithavoll Big Shot?
[LUKA] You take this
entrepreneurial philosophy
a bit seriously, don't ya?
But it's all diarrhea of
the mouth, if you ask me.
[BALDER] You must be Luka,
journalist extraordinaire.
I'm impressed. Like father,
like son, it seems.
He was also too
smart for his own good
and didn't know when to quit.
How do you know
about my father?!
[BALDER] I used to hire him to
do investigative work for me.
He was good.
Everything was
fine until he found
my long lost Cereza...
Then it became apparent
he knew a little too much.
[LUKA] Uh! Hey!
What's happening?!
I can smell rosemary.
[LUKA] It was the
exact same smell...
when my father died.
[LUKA] Ah...
[LUKA] At last...
I know the truth.
You're the one
who killed my father!
You must have been
very close to him.
My deepest condolences.
[LUKA] Bayonetta, I'm sorry
for blaming you all this time.
[BAYONETTA] It's not like
you mentioned it a lot.
Heh.
Well if that little crybaby
could learn to be brave...
then maybe I could grow
up and be a better man.
It's time to settle my
accounts and avenge my father
once and for all!
You are of no use, however
I am not without dignity.
[BALDER] I will
allow you to join him.
Ha!
Luka!
[BAYONETTA gasps]
[BALDER] All roads
lead here, Cereza.
This is where your journey ends.
[BAYONETTA]
I don't understand...
Why bring the
child version of myself
to this time and place?
And why go through
such a complicated
charade to lure me here?
[BALDER] Your battles, your
struggles, seeing the love
in the eyes of
your younger self.
Everything you've
experienced has been
a stepping stone
to your enlightenment.
All of this was necessary
to awaken the Left Eye.
You're a nightmare who tried
to throw the world into chaos.
You killed my mother!
How dare you speak
of the word "love."
I am not the one responsible
for Rosa's death...
The cruel laws of
this world tore us apart.
Angels impatient for the
resurrection murdered her.
There was nothing
I could have done.
But you're a fighter.
[BALDER] Any angel that
attacked you wound up as fodder
for your demons, which only
strengthened your powers.
And then there was Jeanne.
She was the key to
unlocking the full extent
of your magic and regaining
the core of yourself.
In other words, she
gave you back your memory.
Yes, Jeanne did very well.
She did an excellent job.
[gun cocks]
Oh...
You're insane.
[BALDER] I beg to differ.
Oh no, it's not
me who's a madman...
it's the world
that's gone insane.
[BALDER] Are you
really going to shoot me?
[BAYONETTA] Don't
fuck with a witch!
[BALDER] I don't think
you can pull the trigger.
I'm your father.
[BALDER] My lovely,
sweet child... Cereza.
[muffled heartbeat]
[gasps]
The resurrection has begun.
Let us welcome a new reality!
[BAYONETTA groans]
[BAYONETTA groaning]
♪
Bringing back a dead god?
You gotta be kidding me.
♪
[BALDER] Jubileus...
Arise now and walk
the earth once more.
[FORTITUDO] I must become one
with the Creator, Jubileus.
♪
[BALDER] After so many years,
the time has finally come.
We are the "Eyes of the World."
We will oversee its reformation!
♪
[LUKA] Don't tell
me that's Jubileus?!
Bayonetta!
[BALDER] It's glorious!
This is the beginning
of a brand new history
that we are helping to create!
[ROSA] Cereza...
[BAYONETTA] Mummy...?
Please, Cereza...
you must save him...
He is imprisoned by
a blinding madness.
It's destroying him.
Please, save his soul.
Yes, Mummy... I will...
I will do now what
I couldn't do then.
I'll save him.
[engine running]
[BALDER] Oh Jeanne, you
somehow managed to survive.
[JEANNE] The intersection
of light and darkness...
will bring calamity to Earth.
That law... I used
to think it meant her...
Now... I see it meant you.
[BALDER] You're too late.
The creation of a
New World has begun.
There's no
place in it for you.
[JEANNE] Oh well.
Maybe next time.
I'm here for my Umbran sister!
Fuck your new world!
[summoning spell]
Is that you, Jeanne...
Open your eyes! Wake up!
[JEANNE] You're stronger than
you were five hundred years ago!
You can overcome this!
You have to fight!
Heh.
[JEANNE chuckles]
Welcome back. I'll be
keeping an eye on you.
Oh, you're not dead yet?
[chuckles]
[JUBILEUS pained outcry]
♪
[BALDER] What have you done?
Without both Eyes, the
universe will lose its balance
and face another armageddon!
[summoning spell]
[roars]
[BAYONETTA] Our little
pet's not strong enough!
It would seem so.
[BALDER] Cereza,
my own dear child.
Not only have you
interrupted the resurrection,
but now you dare to
turn a sword upon me?
I will destroy you!
Celestial power at work.
Cereza... he must
be stopped. Now!
[BAYONETTA] Obviously.
But in order to do that
I'll need your help!
Hmm?
Something special.
Heh...
Sounds good to me, sister!
[BAYONETTA summoning spell]
[JEANNE summoning spell]
[BAYONETTA]
Sheba, Queen of Inferno.
A fitting match for any god!
[BAYONETTA] Ready! Here we go!
[JEANNE] Yes!
[BALDER power yell]
[SHEBA outcries]
[JUBILEUS screaming]
♪
[BALDER] This isn't over yet,
Cereza. There's still time!
We can still
change everything!
Open your eyes to reality!
[BAYONETTA] It seems you never
learn, do you Daddy dear?
Mother was trying
to save your soul.
[BALDER] Nonsense...
Only Jubileus and the
Creation of a New World...
...can bring salvation!
You're such an egotist.
What use is a world where you
get your own way all the time?
It sounds like a bore.
[BAYONETTA] I think I'll stick
with chaos, if you don't mind.
[BAYONETTA summoning spell]
[BALDER] Your
resistance is futile!
[power yell]
No, actually,
Father... yours is.
♪
[screams]
All tied up.
Yes. And nowhere to go.
You only have one
shot, so make it count.
Now... you're
about to understand
[BAYONETTA] exactly
how mother felt.
[BALDER] My child...
...this cruel, pathetic
world ripped Rosa and I apart.
The world must be reborn
in a state of fairness
and order where such a
thing can never happen!
Chaos must be eliminated!
[BAYONETTA] A ludicrous desire.
Run along. Mummy's waiting.
[BAYONETTA] Bye... Daddy!
[ROSA] I will always
love you, my Balder.
[BALDER] Rosa...
[BALDER winces]
And so dies the
last sage. Farewell.
♪
[BALDER] Rosa...
[footsteps]
Bayonetta...
♪
[ENZO] I can't believe
it's been a year
since Bayonetta disappeared.
I've got all this
funeral work just piled up
and she ain't around
to help with any of it.
[ENZO] I might just have
to find a new racket.
Hey, Rodin...
So do you think that maybe
she could be gone for good?
Who's to say?
I pour drinks.
And I make weapons
for killin' angels.
That's all I do.
That's a shame...
[LUKA] Sorry that it
took me so long, Father.
[LUKA] I did manage to
get it published... but...
unfortunately it isn't
selling very well.
Bayonetta, where
did you disappear to?
[LUKA] But it's okay. I know
we'll meet again. Won't we?
[bells ringing]
[BAYONETTA] They're
certainly tenacious.
I should go home.
The corpses must be
piling up at the church.
[JEANNE] It's still hard
to believe you're a nun!
[BAYONETTA] Honestly,
it's not as bad as you think.
[BAYONETTA] You should
come try it sometime.
No thanks.
I'm perfectly happy
teaching high school.
Oh, before I go...
Care to give those bad boys...
a lesson to remember us by?
[chuckles]
Alright, let's dance, baby!
♪ Ending Theme ♪