[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[bubbling]
‐ [roaring]
♪ ♪
‐ The whole Iron Tribe
shall be exterminated.
♪ ♪
‐ Open fire!
[whooshing]
‐ [roaring]
♪ ♪
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
[explosion booms]
[dramatic choral music]
♪ ♪
[boom]
[blasters firing]
♪ ♪
[boom]
WOMAN: [gasps]
[nervous chatter]
♪ ♪
‐ [groans]
Pull out!
Get out of here!
There's just too many of them!
♪ ♪
‐ [roaring]
[shimmering tone]
[roaring]
♪ ♪
[rumbling]
[nervous chatter]
‐ Retreat!
That Nodos is going
to kill us all!
♪ ♪
‐ They're so quick to abandon
the one who protects them.
It appears they are nothing
more than a race of cowards.
♪ ♪
MAN: Second engine down!
MAN: Spread out!
This isn't good!
There's too many!
I can't shake them!
[screaming]
‐ All fleets on the front line
are to begin tactical retreat.
Fleets in the rear are
to provide covering fire.
Now, access strategic data.
We need to prioritize
counterattack protocols.
‐ Yes, ma'am.
‐ Where is Bellcross now?
‐ He's currently engaging
the bulk
of the Bronze Tribe's forces
in orbit.
‐ If only there were some way
for us to communicate
our strategy to him.
‐ [roaring]
[rumbling]
♪ ♪
[roaring]
MAHITAK: When I helped out
Karkinos,
the fifth one didn't try
to hurt him anymore.
Maybe the other Nodos doesn't
want to destroy anything either.
‐ Yet he fights so savagely on
the forefront of the Iron Tribe.
Unable to find aid even from his
own people.
‐ All by himself?
By why would he?
‐ That is most certainly a Labor
that was demanded of him.
‐ I despise them.
I wish there were no Labors.
[soft rumbling]
DHIANEILA: Age.
[whooshing]
[deep rumbling]
[electricity zapping]
MELEAGROS: What are you doing?
Send in everything we've got!
It is absolutely unacceptable
to keep humiliating ourselves
in front of our ancient god.
‐ We have to focus on
a strategic counterattack.
We might actually have a chance
if we can draw them
a quarter of a cycle from their
current orbital position.
‐ Are you suggesting that we run
from them?
ATALANTES: I would use the main
cannon, if I were you.
‐ The main cannon.
‐ It would certainly destroy
the Bronze Tribe's hide.
Of course that much
planetary debris
would ignite Jupiter's core.
NILVAL: What did you just say?
ATALANTES:
An explosion of that order
would seriously weaken
the Silver Tribe's fleet.
‐ Yes, but wouldn't that weaken
our fleet as well?
‐ A few casualties in battle
are inevitable.
‐ You can't honestly be ordering
us to destroy a planet
in our own solar system.
‐ I like it.
Prepare to fire the main cannon!
‐ No, don't do it!
‐ Believe me, I take absolutely
no pleasure
in sacrificing the holy planet
of Jupiter.
But it's critical that we never
show our back to the enemy.
NILVAL: And Nodos is fighting
in the blast radius.
‐ Oh, I seriously doubt that
we'll harm our precious Nodos.
‐ And how do you know that?
‐ Prepare the cannon to fire.
‐ Target the planet Io.
Deliver orders for all fleets
to move out of orbit
immediately!
NILVAL: [scoffs]
Disregard that!
Do not fire, no matter what!
‐ Who do you think you are?
ATALANTES: [clears throat]
Explain yourself, Nilval.
‐ There are consequences.
You aren't just destroying
a planet;
you're damaging allies too.
The soldiers will be demoralized
and allegiances
will be strained.
‐ Hmm.
Well, in that case‐‐
‐ Big brother!
‐ It seems the lieutenant
general has lost her nerve.
How pathetic.
It's obvious to me she can
no longer handle the pressure
of her position.
‐ [groans]
‐ She's no longer fit for duty
and shall be removed
from her post.
I should have you arrested,
but you're popular with
the troops.
Be thankful for that.
‐ You bastards.
[tense music]
MAN: Now deploying barrels.
Activating all gravity
anti‐particle accelerators.
No errors detected.
MAN: Charging gravitational
prism.
Normal energy conduction
confirmed.
♪ ♪
‐ It's exactly like
the princess said:
This is a meaningless exercise
in destruction.
‐ I suppose it can't be helped.
This fight will affect both
Mars and Jupiter.
‐ Tell me the truth.
How much of our fleet can
survive something like this?
‐ We have no other choice but
to hope that Age will save us.
‐ He's fighting to protect us,
but we're powerless to return
the favor.
‐ [sighs]
‐ [whimpers softly]
‐ What's the matter?
‐ Something terrible.
‐ What are you talking about?
‐ [moans]
Something is happening,
and it can never be undone.
It's so awful.
It starts now.
♪ ♪
MAN: Accelerator, good to go.
MAN: All systems optimal.
Barrels are in place.
MAN: Activating
echo location device.
[inaudible] cartridge,
locked and loaded.
[zapping]
♪ ♪
‐ When this star dies...
[gasps]
♪ ♪
‐ It's been confirmed.
The main cannon
is ready to fire.
‐ [chuckles] Perfect.
Well, brother?
‐ [chuckles] Destroy them.
[zapping]
[wind blowing softly]
[rumbling]
[beeping]
MAN: Sir, Io is falling
from orbit.
‐ Hmm.
MAN: Alert fleet.
The Bronze Tribe
is abandoning the planet.
‐ Hmm.
[soft rumbling]
[deep rumbling]
‐ They would do that
to their own planet?
That must be the reason
the Silver Tribe
wishes to destroy
the entire species.
[wind blowing]
[whoosh]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
‐ Now deploy.
‐ Princess Dhianeila.
ALL: Your majesty!
DHIANEILA: [whimpers]
I don't know what's happening.
Where is he?
Where is age?
[rumbling]
ATALANTES: [laughing]
Look at them scattering
like insects.
A most excellent strategy,
Atalantes.
‐ Why, thank you, big brother.
‐ Sir, we can't locate
the Nodos.
It looks like he may have been
caught in the explosion.
‐ Find it now.
The infernal goliath
still has a lot of work to do
for us around here.
‐ Don't let this chance slip by.
Straighten the line
and charge the enemy!
‐ They ordered
an offensive charge
right after the fleet
got torn apart.
Those two imbeciles.
As long as we can keep
the enemy engaged,
I want to maintain a comm link
with the "Argonaut."
[rapid beeping]
[gasps]
♪ ♪
‐ Now drive it back.
‐ What?
♪ ♪
[music stops]
[muffled booming]
[zapping]
‐ Oh, no.
I don't believe what I'm seeing!
We're in trouble!
‐ [gasps]
The Silver Tribe wasn't supposed
to interfere.
And wasn't in the database.
‐ Soon enough we'll have
a full‐scale panic on our hands.
That'll be
the perfect opportunity
to seize control of the fleet
and order the surviving vessels
to withdraw from the area.
Got it?
♪ ♪
[cracking and rumbling]
‐ Damn their whole species.
♪ ♪
‐ Well, Bellcross,
you've made your decision.
And you shall die with
the foolish ones.
♪ ♪
[rumbling]
[whoosh]
♪ ♪
‐ Karkinos, get him.
[boom]
‐ It seems Karkinos has begun
the battle.
Soon I shall enter it with him.
‐ Let me go instead.
I don't want you to get hurt.
Allow me to go in your place,
Lecty.
Please.
‐ I must go.
I promise I'll be fine.
Thank you.
‐ Oh.
[indistinct chatter]
‐ You're looking at
the latest info from Nilval.
It's painfully clear this
is the result of executing
Meleagros' strategy.
IOLAOUS: Those idiots!
They destroyed it!
The entire planet!
DHIANEILA:
What have they done?
‐ [gasps]
IOLAOUS: Princess Dhianeila,
your condition.
[gasps]
‐ Your highness,
why have you come?
‐ I need to know what happened,
to make sense of it all.
I knew that you and Nilval had
been secretly communicating
and now I know why you would do
such a thing:
to stop them.
[beeping]
Why would they do this?
Something so horrific?
Those fools.
[crying]
‐ The alliance sustained
significant damage
during the operation,
and we still have not been able
to locate the Nodos.
We must begin rescue and repair
procedures immediately.
Then reorganize the fleet.
I apologize.
I realize that this is
the last thing
you want to hear right now,
but everyone who reports
to Lieutenant General Nilval
as well as 17 other fleets
have quietly agreed to stay
in the alliance,
after you assume command.
Ah‐‐
‐ You do realize
you're asking me
to lead a coup d'etat
against my own brothers.
No.
Now is not the time to instigate
political upheaval.
Instead we need to focus on
wounded soldiers
and damaged vessels.
We shall take them all in
at any cost.
Our primary objective is to save
as many lives as possible.
‐ Then the first step
is moving all rear units
to the terminal planet to set up
the infrastructure
for a massive rescue operation.
‐ I will be coming with you.
Make preparations for
the "Argonaut"
to move out immediately.
MOBEEDO: Yes, ma'am.
MAN: Route formation complete.
Locking in destination.
WOMAN: Setting warp path
to [inaudible].
MAN: Begin warp process.
‐ To think Princess Dhianeila
just walked into a room
full of people,
when she's so terrified
of touching another's
consciousness.
She didn't reject the plan,
just the timing.
Your awakening of our star
is near, Nilval.
‐ Are you still out there
fighting all by yourself?
Even after the ones you're
protecting abandoned you.
Just don't die.
‐ I can strongly sense
Age's presence.
We should have gone with him,
instead of staying safely behind
and letting him battle
our enemies all by himself.
Do you think I'm arrogant
for feeling this way?
When Age left, I didn't even
make an effort to keep him here.
The man who fights alone.
‐ If you want my opinion,
I think he chose to do all
of this for you, Princess.
‐ What?
‐ May I speak frankly,
your highness?
‐ Yes.
‐ Would you please
stop pretending
you aren't the true leader
of humankind?
Because of our
unwavering faith in you,
all of mankind will gladly walk
the path you choose for us,
your highness.
‐ [sobbing]
Thank you, Aneasha.
WOMAN: All sails down.
Activate dimensional route.
‐ Now commencing rescue
operations
for the alliance fleet.
All ships begin warp now.
[rumbling]
[crackling]
[shimmering]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
LECTY: Any measure of brute
strength
is utterly inconsequential
to the flow of time.
Nothing can stand up to
the power of my Erymanthos.
♪ ♪
Right there.
We're going to jump Erymanthos.
[shimmering]
Go back to 70 seconds ago.
[whoosh]
♪ ♪
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪