‐ Don't you remember
your contract?
If you break it,
your entire tribe
will have to pay the price.
‐ After I destroy the ship,
you promise I don't have to do
anything else, right?
‐ Active warp, now!
‐ No, wait!
‐ [growls]
‐ I can't.
I completely abandoned him.
I just left him for dead
back there.
I guess I'm not much
of a solider, am I?
NILVAL: We shall cease
all protective operations
of this dying planet.
From this point on,
this fleet has a new mission.
We will dedicate
our meager resources to you.
‐ The path, I will find it.
I promise.
Hold on.
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
[rumbling]
NILVAL: Status update.
LIEUTENANT: Yes, ma'am.
Our strategic positioning
is 80% complete.
There has been a slight delay
in the relocation of the core.
‐ Well, we don't have much time.
The battle is about to begin.
LIEUTENANT: Yes, ma'am.
[soft music]
[booming]
♪ ♪
PHAETH O: More Iron Tribe.
Are they trying to help
that ship escape?
♪ ♪
‐ We have found them.
Because of your failure, there
are more ships to destroy,
Mehitak.
Now go.
Refusal is not an option.
MAN: A full Hedron has been
detected.
It's the Silver Tribe.
NILVAL: Pearl Core,
maintain current position.
Ruby Core and Topaz Core,
complete formation.
All strategic fleet positioning
will be relative to Blue Core.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Ruby Core at minus 240‐13.
Topaz Core at 13‐11‐54.
LIEUTENANT: Prepare to attack.
WOMAN: Ready, sir!
‐ Fire.
[warbling]
[boom]
♪ ♪
[rumbling]
[tense music]
WOMAN: Massive spatiotemporal
shock detected.
MAN: Their gravity signature
is growing.
More vessels are coming out
of warp!
‐ How long can her fleet
possibly hold back
such an overwhelming enemy?
Please, Nilval, don't die.
♪ ♪
‐ Receiving data
via the cycle line.
‐ Coordinates from the princess.
Have navigation analyze them
and calculate our route
immediately.
[booming]
[flames crackling]
YUTY: Karkinos.
What is it?
What's happening?
Impossible.
He can't defeat you.
PROME O: Yuty's confidence has
begun to dissolve.
LECTY: If Karkinos continues
to fight,
he will perish.
I assume that is one of
the Labors in his contract.
‐ I do wonder what Mehitak
is doing.
‐ Mehitak is weeping.
If it were possible, I would
step in and take his place.
‐ His fate is his own burden.
You see, that is the nature
of contracts such as ours.
No one may shoulder the burden
of someone else's destiny.
In that respect, we are alone.
‐ Yes, but why?
It's so cruel.
The pain:
it makes no sense to me.
What is the true purpose
of these Labors?
[booming]
What good do the Golden Tribe
foresee
when they bound us
to this contract
and made us pawns in a bloody
war to control the universe?
YUTY: Karkinos!
You fool.
Kill him now.
NILVAL: Where are they now?
LIEUTENANT: The "Argonaut"
is .02 AUs behind us
and moving at full speed.
‐ But why are they moving at
full speed off of a Starway?
Mm.
What do you want to bet
Princess Dhianeila's
showing them the way?
[beeping]
‐ Unidentified vessel detected.
Estimated arrival in 20 seconds.
‐ Send orders to Pearl Core.
Deploy generators
and battlefield alignment.
[warbling]
[whooshing]
NILVAL: Status report.
LIEUTENANT: No progress
on the front line.
The enemy force continues
to grow in numbers.
[whooshing]
WOMAN: Unknown vessel detected
in Ruby Core's firing line.
It looks like it could be
a Nodos.
‐ Let me see it on the display.
WOMAN: Yes, ma'am!
LIEUTENANT: It is a Nodos.
MAN: The Pearl Core is not going
to make it.
‐ Order the Dralion unit in
to compensate
for the defense gap.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[blasters firing]
MAN: The enemy appears
unaffected by our attacks!
‐ I don't understand
what it's doing.
[blasters firing]
The beast seems invincible.
Why isn't it attacking?
‐ Does it expect some favor
in return?
Show it no mercy.
Pearl Core generator
at maximum capacity!
Synchronize with the
planetary magnetic field
and create a gravitational
force to pin that monster down!
♪ ♪
The Nodos might be able to dodge
one of the beams,
but there's no way it'll be able
to dodge them all.
Draw the net in!
WOMAN: Yes, ma'am!
[blasters firing]
[warbling]
MAN: Grab sync complete.
‐ All ships open fire.
♪ ♪
WOMAN: Captain, we've picked up
multiple anthills,
approaching fast!
‐ They must be a group that got
separated.
Maintain heading.
Prepare to engage.
‐ Energy fluctuations ahead,
sir.
Seems the ant heaps
are moving to intercept us
before we get to the source
of the pulses.
‐ Is that Age?
If it is him, then the poor
boy's been fighting
for more than 200 hours
straight.
‐ Hold on, Age.
‐ [growling]
[boom]
[booming]
[crackling]
[whooshing]
[growls]
[booming]
[wind blowing]
‐ [panting]
‐ [panting softly]
‐ [sighs]
Here I come!
[dramatic music]
‐ You barbarian.
♪ ♪
‐ Karkinos?
Stop toying with him.
I know you can do better
than that.
♪ ♪
‐ The ship we're searching for
isn't here.
Where could it be?
[whirring]
‐ High energy field
concentrating
around the Nodos.
‐ I've got a feeling
it's on the offensive now.
‐ So the monster finally stirs.
All ships disperse.
I want the medic and supply
ships to remain close
to Pearl Core.
Blue Core, release your entire
reserve of blooms immediately.
Crush every last ant!
♪ ♪
‐ [moaning]
‐ I want 80% firepower
on the Nodos.
Focus the rest on the ants.
‐ Hold on.
No, it can't be.
Its energy levels exceeds
shield limits.
‐ Begin targeting now.
WOMAN: Target acquired!
♪ ♪
[electricity crackling]
‐ Target lock complete.
‐ Margin of error is now .01%.
‐ Fire!
[blasters fire]
[cracking]
[intense rumbling]
[booming]
[both gasp]
Pull up, now!
‐ [gasps]
Oh, no.
‐ [growling]
[rumbling]
♪ ♪
‐ [roaring]
‐ Now what?
I want a full report.
‐ We detected a catastrophic
burst of energy
within the Planet Huelgoat.
‐ I can that,
but what the hell happened?
♪ ♪
‐ The planet...
has died.
♪ ♪
WOMAN: Two [inaudible]
supremely damaged!
We lost contact with 60%
of the fleet!
MAN: Ruby Core and Blue Core
have sustained casualties!
‐ Regroup with
the Dralion unit.
All ships reposition behind
the satellite fortress.
Where's Pearl Core?
MAN: It's still engaged
with the enemy, Nodos.
♪ ♪
‐ How long do we have before
total planetary destruction?
‐ Three minutes at most, ma'am.
‐ We'll maintain our hold
until then.
All vessels including
Ruby Core and Blue Core
move into attack positions.
‐ Commander,
we need to disengage
the gravitational field
and release the Nodos.
If we take one more hit,
that'll be the end of us!
‐ What do you suggest we do,
Lieutenant?
Leave the "Argonaut"
to the enemy?
Did our troops all die in vain?
Was an entire planet destroyed
for no reason?
I'm as useless as the dead
commanders before me.
I guess I should have known,
huh?
This mission is suicide.
I wouldn't blame them
for ignoring me
and deserting this battle.
WOMAN: Ruby Core standing by
at route N3.
And Pearl Core currently
standing by at point NA3.
‐ Blue Core and all other
available battleships
are standing by at
appropriate coordinates.
‐ All reserve ships
are currently en route
to take up offensive positions.
‐ Not a single person
has deserted us.
‐ Your fleet believes in you,
Commander,
and they will remain loyal
to you until the very end.
‐ Hmm.
I don't know if that makes them
honorable or just foolish.
♪ ♪
[growling]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[boom]
[roaring]
[cracking and hissing]
‐ [gasps]
Karkinos.
[warbling]
PROME O: Why?
Why would the Golden Tribe give
such a powerful Nodos
to the Iron Tribe?
I often wonder if they intended
to split the universe in two.
‐ Split in two?
[soft orchestral music]
♪ ♪
[revving]
‐ All right, this scuffle
shouldn't be any problem.
It seems Nilval has already
suppressed a majority
of the enemy fleet.
Hmm.
WOMAN: All units return
to the ship.
We are now making preparations
to move out of conventional
space and into active warp.
WOMAN: I repeat, all units
return to the ship.
IOLAOUS:
Did we find the Starway?
No, it must be the princess.
♪ ♪
‐ Everyone on board
the "Argonaut" is in danger
because of me.
I can't help but worry.
I'm so frightened.
‐ I'll be all right.
I promise you.
Do you remember?
The 12 Labors.
I'm here to protect you.
‐ But who's going
to protect you?
‐ Me and Bellcross will make
a path for you.
I promise the "Argonaut"
will make it out,
even if it means that we have
to stay behind.
But don't be sad;
you'll see us again.
‐ Age.
[gasps]
MOBEEDO:
Transmit the ship's course
to the Azz‐Azoth fleet.
They've completely lost
their way
if the Planet Huelgoat
was really destroyed.
Without that planet,
they'll never find the Starway.
Our ship is the only chance
they've got right now.
DHIANEILA: Captain, I sense
a hostile presence
coming toward us.
‐ Deploy the shield
at maximum output!
Scan for spatiotemporal shock
in our vicinity.
‐ Shock detected.
It's right above us!
‐ What?
[gasps]
WOMAN: Ship identified.
Sir, that ship's a full Hedron.
‐ It's the Silver Tribe.
♪ ♪
‐ Found you.
There's no use running.
You won't get away.
♪ ♪
[electricity crackling]
‐ There's just not enough power
to maintain
both shields and active warp.
MAN: Ceasing active warps and
all available power shields.
♪ ♪
‐ The timing couldn't be worse
for this to happen.
Damn your kind!
How do I choose between
active warp and the shields?
DHIANEILA: You must take
the path given to you.
‐ What path, Princess?
♪ ♪
[music stops]
‐ Stop this at once!
‐ [gasping and groaning]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[booming]
‐ Sir, the attack has stopped!
‐ Disengage the shields!
Enter active warp!
[shimmering tone]
‐ [sighs]
What?
What happened?
[boom]
[alarm blaring]
‐ [gasps] Oh, no!
The princess!
‐ Are you all right?
‐ Quick, open the pod!
Princess Dhianeila!
Please, talk to me!
Dhianeila?
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]