WOMAN: BNU, now on patrol.
MAN: All units,
release weapons lock
only after your designated
areas have been scanned.
MAN: Navigational data
revision complete.
Orbital trajectories confirmed.
WOMAN: Roger that.
Individual flight vectors
are set.
MAN: Communication channels
8 through 20
are ready for
all descending ships.
Unit four is on schedule
for departure
in approximately 20 minutes.
An inverted installation shuttle
will be included in that team,
per security protocol,
in sector 8‐10.
‐ I doubt that Earth has much
in the way of resources anymore.
It's difficult to believe
anyone would fight so adamantly
to keep humankind away from it.
[all chuckling]
‐ Beautiful.
‐ Our home world.
At last.
[beeping]
Damn, we're six seconds
behind schedule.
Pick up the pace.
Don't think the scenery gives
you the right to slack off.
[engines whooshing]
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
MOBEEDO:
Bee, what's the status on Age?
‐ It doesn't look like he'll
wake up anytime soon, Master.
‐ Do you think he'll wake up
before the other one does?
‐ I lack sufficient data
to answer.
‐ Hmm.
The princess assures me
that we've got
nothing to worry about.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
And yet,
I can't help feeling uneasy
with a second Nodos aboard.
‐ Why? Because the whole
crew would be killed
if his intentions
were hostile?
‐ And that's putting it mildly.
WOMAN: Gravity shock detected.
The Calydonian Fleet's flagship
squadron is approaching.
‐ That's Nilval for you.
Never one to stay far behind.
[energy whooshing]
‐ The birthplace of humanity.
It's beautiful.
‐ Welcome home, commander.
We've thoroughly scanned
the place.
I think it's safe to call in
the other fleets.
‐ You mean to tell me
you've calmed a raging Nodos
and finally located
the home world?
Does the "Argonaut" enjoy
making the rest of us look bad?
‐ Believe me, without
the princess we'd be nothing.
By the way, what became
of her useless brothers?
They're with you, yes?
‐ Yes, but only because
I'm not a jury.
If it were up to me,
they'd be ejected into space
to mingle with what's left
of our fallen brethren.
‐ There's an idea.
Lucky for them,
her highness is kind.
‐ [sighs]
Planet Earth,
we embrace you,
due in no small part to my
unbelievable military prowess.
‐ To think we'd be celebrating
our victory in a room like this.
‐ Don't worry, brother,
the council is bound to realize
that Dhianeila is merely
reaping the fruits
of our hard work.
They know injustice when
they see it.
‐ I've no doubt of that.
However, little do they know
that the real battle
is yet to begin.
‐ Huh, you mean there are
other planets to reclaim?
‐ No, Atalantes!
Other planets to be seized
and enemies to be cast out
into the icy clutches of space.
Yes, by bringing the fight
to their door,
we shall blow their planets
apart like to much dust,
and our dear sister will know
that we are not
to be trifled with.
‐ We've got to be sure that
our timing on this thing
is exactly right.
Bee, push our communication
through the council
as soon as the princes have
finished presenting their case.
‐ Yes, Master.
‐ Now then, let's hope our boy
decides to wake up soon.
‐ How likely is it
that Mehitak is dead?
‐ He fought until he couldn't
fight anymore.
Just as his contract with
the Silver Tribe required.
‐ It makes no difference anyway.
If he does survive,
he will rejoin us.
Unless of course
he wishes to perish.
Once again you have failed
to keep the enemy under control.
Can you not subdue the fifth
without exhausting
your strength, Karkinos?
‐ If you were to ask it of me,
I would gladly
succumb to the madness.
‐ As long as I join the fight,
that won't be necessary.
‐ Her anger is understandable.
The three of us did fail
to defeat the fifth
despite our best efforts.
‐ But even so,
she's relieved you're unhurt.
‐ Mehitak is still alive.
I can feel it.
Even in the throes of madness,
the fifth would not kill him.
‐ I must leave now to speak
privately with Prome O.
If you wish to appease
Yuty's wrath,
I would suggest that you
speak privately with her.
‐ Wise one,
why does the Iron Tribe
seek to recover Earth
so fervently?
‐ They are drawn to it
by an irresistible sense
of heritage.
It calls to them.
The planet is humankind's
ancestral home, Rom Ror.
‐ Why such an insistence
on ancestry?
‐ To them, past and future
hold equal significance.
It is in their nature
to believe so.
Of course, bear in mind
that they assume
the same nature in us.
That is why they fight.
‐ Not merely for survival then.
‐ Their survival instinct
is incredibly strong,
but tempered by what they feel.
And now they seek the power
of the Golden Tribe.
‐ The very thing we seek.
‐ But find impossible
to attain.
‐ Surely their quest
will be as fruitless.
They are the youngest tribe,
in no way our betters.
‐ Really?
Or do we merely hope so?
The Iron Tribe may indeed
have emerged late,
but the Golden Tribe
waited for them,
and we would be foolish
not to take that into account.
You will recall that
before their departure
from this universe,
the Golden Tribe paused
to heed the appearance
of humankind.
If they flourish now,
it is only because
some greater purpose
was thought served in the
Iron Tribe's fight against us,
whether to our benefit or not.
But whatever their reasons
may have been,
the Golden Tribe did see fit
to let humanity thrive.
[indistinct murmuring]
[birds chirping]
[tense music]
‐ [gasps]
‐ Where am I?
‐ Let me go!
‐ I‐‐I'm sorry.
‐ Ow.
‐ Yuty.
‐ [gasps]
‐ I hope that you understand.
I will sacrifice my life so that
you do not have to fight.
Even if my contract
did not require it of me,
I would still protect you.
‐ Do you not think that I rely
on your generosity?
Leave me alone.
‐ The idea that humankind
held favor with the Golden Tribe
is unacceptable.
You cannot believe it.
‐ I have no other choice
but to believe it.
Perhaps the Golden Tribe
intended for us
to share our power
with the Iron Tribe.
Perhaps both races
are meant to rule the universe
side by side.
‐ They destroy planets and
you speak of them like equals.
Collaborating with them
would mean death.
‐ The Golden Tribe
refused to share their power
with the universe.
So why should we be expected to?
We are destined to destroy
the Iron Tribe.
‐ With all due respect,
I disagree.
Forgive me.
‐ Your opinion is duly noted,
Prome O,
although you are
in the minority.
[indistinct murmurs]
Let us end this.
‐ Your Grace.
‐ Now I alone
must bear the burden
of the Silver Tribe's
greatest fear.
‐ Fear?
‐ The fear of what the
Golden Tribe knew of our fate
and why they left us behind.
And yet that fear,
no one else will face it
because emotion is seen
as a hindrance.
I alone at as a conduit
for the tribe's darker nature
so that cold reason
may prevail in all others.
I can sense the pain you have,
Lecty.
The anguish that I know
you're feeling over Mehitak.
‐ He hasn't come back.
There is but one fate left
for him if he fails to return.
Why in their infinite wisdom
would the Golden Tribe
decree a Labor that Mehitak
could never hope to fulfill?
‐ The Golden Tribe decreed
only the number of our Labors.
It was left up to use
to decipher their prophecies
in regard to the Nodos.
So much of what they intended
remains shrouded in mystery
to this day, hence the clause
in your contract
meant to help us understand.
‐ But, wise one,
I too am in the dark.
‐ Do not despair of the dark,
for it is in the darkness
that together we shall find
the light.
‐ Your Grace, together then.
‐ Behold, paradise regained!
But do not think
the battle is over.
Our enemies must know
beyond a shadow of a doubt
that we will never again
submit to the yoke
of their tyranny.
As the poet said,
let our thoughts now
be bloody or nothing worth.
We must retaliate swiftly
and without mercy,
or else the Earth again
will be wrenched from‐‐
[continues silently]
‐ He's not much
for military strategy,
but he's a wizard at rhetoric.
I'll give the bastard
that much.
What do you think, riveting?
‐ Huh, I'd say the council
seems to think so.
‐ Hmm.
It might interest you to know
that from now on Age will be
stationed with the "Argonaut,"
which is operating
independently,
as per the council's decision.
Meleagros will continue to act
as Executive Commander,
but responsibility for the fleet
really goes to you,
so congratulations.
‐ How the hell were you able
to manage that?
‐ Well now,
fortunately for us
the council
wanted to avoid a scandal
as much as we wanted
to be rid of the princes.
So I suggested that everyone
forget the whole thing
and just get on
with their lives.
‐ Which gives the little monster
a clean break,
but I guess I can't be
all that upset.
After all,
I am assuming command
of the best fleet
in the galaxy, aren't I?
You know, I never thought
I'd say this,
but I'm quite impressed with
your diplomacy skills, Captain.
‐ What can I tell you?
The princess inspires me
to be a better negotiator.
‐ The Nodos is now waking up,
Master.
‐ Huh?
‐ [gasps]
‐ Wait, which one?
‐ Which one?
[beeping]
‐ [yawns]
Hello.
‐ Yes, Age.
‐ Thank you for coming
to visit me in my dream.
You were smiling.
‐ Of course I was, Age.
You came back to us,
and after everything
we had done.
You came back.
[sobbing]
[chuckles]
‐ Is he awake yet?
I‐‐
Oh.
‐ Wow, you can laugh and cry
at the same time?
‐ Yes, I suppose I can.
[both chuckle]
‐ Hmm?
Is there something I can
help you with, Iolaous?
Or are you just going
to stand there gawking?
‐ It's like the two of them
are old friends.
‐ Hmm?
‐ Why do I even bother?
Look at those two.
They're perfect together.
‐ If I didn't know better,
I'd think you were
the only man in the universe
who's jealous of a Nodos.
‐ Can you blame me?
‐ Oh, you've got your charms.
Trust me.
[both laughing]
‐ [screaming]
‐ Oh, no. Now what?
‐ We have to call the princess
right away!
BOTH: Princess!
Princess, help us!
He's awake!
‐ The Nodos is out.
Request instructions.
MAN: Set weapons to stun.
Shoot only in self‐defense.
‐ All right, come on.
‐ Yeah, let's show this thing
who's boss.
[both yelling, grunting]
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
[both groan]
MAN: Get out of here, girls.
You don't stand a chance
against that thing.
What the hell are we
supposed to do now?
‐ Don't kill us.
‐ We were only kidding.
[both gasp]
BOTH: Age!
‐ Huh?
‐ [swallows, gasps]
MAN: The princess
just showed up with Age.
MAN: Good, let him handle
the Nodos.
You focus on keeping
the princess safe.
MAN: Roger that.
‐ We don't have to fight.
‐ [gasps]
You mean...
you're not going to hurt me?
‐ Hm.
[sweeping music]
♪ ♪
‐ [whimpers, sobs]
‐ I'll be.
Looks like we don't have
to worry after all.
The princess was right
about him.
‐ Even after seeing them
rage like that,
you took them in
like it was nothing.
I do have to hand it to you,
Captain.
You've got a talent
for making rash decisions.
‐ Just between you and me,
Nilval,
I'm still not so sure having
two here is a good thing.
The new guy
just might be in danger
from one of the crew.
‐ I'm sure you'll do your best
to protect him.
‐ I am Mehitak.
I come from the planet Pore.
‐ I am Princess Dhianeila
of the Yunos royal family,
the rulers of the Altria system.
On behalf of the crew
and all of humankind,
it is my humble honor to welcome
you on board the "Argonaut."
‐ Does this mean I have to enter
into a contract with you now?
‐ Not with us,
but it would help
our efforts immensely
if you could provide details
about the contract
you're currently in.
‐ [chuckles]
‐ As long as I obey
the Silver Tribe,
the planet Pore
will be prosperous.
I am to do their bidding
until my powers as Nodos
are exhausted.
Also, it is my duty to help
when the Silver Tribe's
Nodos is in peril.
That's my contract.
‐ The Silver Tribe's Nodos?
Is this being bound
to the Silver Tribe
by a contract
similar to your own?
‐ Yes, she is.
But Yuty's contract includes
eight Labors.
As for the others,
Karkinos has four.
Lecty has five.
In the battle against Age,
Artemia and I exhausted
our power.
Such is your strength.
‐ Huh.
‐ This means that my obligations
to the Silver Tribe
have come to an end.
‐ And what is to become
of your own tribe?
‐ If Yuty learns
of my presence here,
then it is very likely
my home planet of Pore
will be destroyed.
‐ They are willing to destroy
an entire world, your home,
over the disobedience
of one subject?
‐ Yes.
The same threat binds
Karkinos and Lecty.
Yuty would slaughter our tribes
without a thought.
She's even stronger than Age.
‐ [gasps]
‐ Your people will not
come to harm, Mehitak,
I promise you.
‐ What?
‐ The "Argonaut" is currently
en route to planet Tauron,
birthplace of our mortal enemy,
the Bronze Tribe.
Your people have
already colonized a planet
in the same system.
Is that correct?
‐ You do wish me to fight
for you.
‐ I do not.
I ask only one thing,
that you do not use
your powers as a Nodos
while you are with us.
In return, we will deliver you
to your tribe
and offer them our protection.
‐ You would do that?
‐ Of course we would.
This war should only be
between the Silver Tribe
and ourselves.
We cannot allow
any innocent bystanders
to become involved.
I urge you to take refuge
with your people
until this ends.
There is no need
for you to fight.
‐ She's actually gonna let
the little guy go.
‐ That's just like the princess,
noble as always.
‐ I would rather
stay on board the ship.
‐ Really?
Why is that?
‐ The "Argonaut" has
an arduous battle ahead of it.
If you are willing
to protect my people,
I will fight alongside Age
to protect humankind.
‐ [gasps]
‐ Huh?
‐ I know how difficult
it must be
for you to make such
a selfless and generous offer
to our people.
Mehitak, we are very proud
to call you our friend.
MAN: Navigational parameters
set to leave Earth's
orbital trajectory
once the sails are reset.
MAN: Confirming new coordinates.
No error detected
in main engines.
Astral signs specified.
[overlapping chatter]
‐ Sails set
to newly established path.
‐ Earth's scopes confirmed.
‐ Here's hoping we all see
the Earth again one day.
[triumphant music]
‐ It is my hope that humankind
will come to embrace
their responsibilities
as caretakers of such
a beautiful planet.
‐ We've finally found
our distant Eden.
How could humankind
fail to embrace it?
‐ That we ever lost this
bountiful world to begin with
gives me pause, Aneasha.
Are we ready
for a second chance?
For all our knowledge,
all our progress,
we have yet to learn
how to truly abide as citizens
of this universe,
how to flourish without ruin.
And when I think
of Age's 12 Labors,
will we ever be worthy
of the contract
that binds him to mankind?
‐ Age gives himself
to us so freely
because he believes in you.
If we're ever going
to be worthy of it,
it is you who will be
our example.
‐ There's nothing left
but to move forward.
♪ ♪
It is time.
May the stars shine
upon the path before us.
♪ ♪
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
Tensions rise in hostile forces
as humankind makes inroads
toward their destiny.
Next time on "Heroic Age,"
episode 17,
The Retributive Troops.