‐ Please, Age, come back.
MAN: Did you hear?
The Nodos left the "Argonaut."
MAN: Yeah, and now those
brothers are going to use it
to take credit for
all the princess' hard work.
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
MAIL: I don't hear anything.
TAIL: Maybe she's meditating.
‐ Why is Age
being so mean to her?
I never would've thought
that he could be such a jerk.
‐ Since we left port,
she's pretty much locked herself
in her room,
and the ship's records indicate
she's barely eaten anything.
I'm so worried about her.
ANEASHA: Stop talking
about Age like that.
MAIL: But they left.
ANEASHA: Do either of you
really believe
that Age would just abandon
all of us on whim?
[both sigh]
‐ [sighs]
Think about it.
Age had to leave in order
to protect the princess.
BOTH: Protect?
‐ Of course.
From now on, Age will be
a priority target for the enemy.
If he stayed, he'd only
be endangering her life.
At least I think
that's why he left.
‐ I get it.
‐ Well, he should've told
all of that to her.
‐ Looks like Age
really is a jerk.
‐ What was that about Age?
Is he all right?
‐ It's time for your meal,
Princess.
‐ Oh, thank you.
We have a most difficult journey
ahead of us.
It's important for all of us
to keep up our strength.
Leave it there on the table
if you would, Aneasha.
ANEASHA: Yes, Your Highness.
Excuse me.
[soft instrumental music]
♪ ♪
‐ How bizarre.
She's acting fine.
‐ I guess she finally got over
all that stuff with Age.
‐ You two should know better
than that.
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA: I mustn't worry them
any more than I already have.
Now more than ever they'll need
me to be their anchor.
♪ ♪
‐ Really?
So you believe there's
a reason that Age left?
‐ From what I know of the boy,
I'd say there's a good reason
that he left.
‐ Mm.
I see.
You're saying that he intends
to draw enemy fire
in order to protect
the princess.
‐ Beyond that, I see no other
motive for Age to leave us.
The funny thing is
that little monkey doesn't know
what a hero he really is.
IOLAOUS: Captain,
permission to speak freely.
‐ Sure.
Why so formal?
‐ Those brothers.
Is it wise to let the Yunos
family lead the fleet?
‐ [sighs]
IOLAOUS: We shouldn't entrust
humanity's future with them.
It's suicide!
‐ That was
the Council's decision.
In any event, do you know of
anyone better suited
to be trusted with such
a monumental task?
‐ I do.
Princess Dhianeila.
‐ The princess belongs
to the Yunos family too.
‐ She's nothing like them,
and you know it,
not to mention her special bond
with a Nodos.
It would give its own life
to protect her.
She's by far
the most qualified to lead.
‐ All I'm going to say
is no comment,
and I say that
as a loyal soldier.
But speaking as your father,
I must agree.
‐ Thank you, Captain.
‐ Do something for me, Bee:
establish a secure comm link
with Nilval on the "Althaia."
It's critical that no one else
in the fleet detects it.
Can you do that?
‐ I can have a secure line
ready for you in one hour.
‐ Then what are you waiting for?
‐ Yes, sir.
‐ I've got no time to lose.
[whooshing]
MELEAGROS:
Descendants of humanity,
long ago our ancestors set forth
on a journey
to explore the infinite
possibilities of this galaxy.
One cannot imagine the hardships
endured by those brave souls
in building our future.
Our great ancestors suffered
so that we might thrive!
The Silver Tribe intends
to dishonor their memory
and to destroy us all.
Now is the time for mankind
to rise.
We must reclaim
our mother planet
from the ruthless
and insatiable Silver Tribe!
Then they shall know
we will never submit
to our murderous oppressors.
Make no mistake:
this is a holy war!
All of humanity,
as well as each of our allies,
must come together.
By working as one,
we shall overcome our foe.
[rousing music]
WOMAN: We are disappointed
to report that materials
and supplies belonging
to the star system were taken
in such a forceful manner.
‐ This doesn't feel
like an allegiance at all.
It feels more like we're being
put under the boot
of the royal family.
‐ I hope you'll accept
my deepest apologies
for my brothers' aggressive
behavior.
The future of humankind
is at stake in this conflict.
We have no other option
but victory.
In order for that to happen,
it is of the utmost importance
that all of the planets
work together,
but all will be lost unless
we forge an alliance of respect.
You shall have my assistance
in this endeavor.
Instead of leading, I shall work
to strengthen our solidarity.
I solemnly swear to you
that this alliance
will never bring about a system
based on fear and mistrust.
WOMAN: Once we confront
the Silver Tribe,
we won't have
the luxury of ignoring
another star system's troubles.
We'll be in it together
until the very end.
MAN: If I may be so bold:
I can say with certainty
that I am not alone in my wish
that you were in command
of the alliance,
Your Highness.
‐ Thank you for your kind words.
NILVAL: It's impossible
to predict how many anthills
there will be or what formation
they'll take.
That means a flexible
but well‐coordianted response
will be the key.
Now, in this scenario‐‐
ATALANTES: [clears throat]
That'll be all, Colonel‐‐
oh, I'm sorry.
I suppose now it's
Lieutenant General Nilval.
[all chuckling]
My Quental Unit will take
the lead in this battle.
We'll blow the enemy
out of the sky.
‐ A reckless plan.
‐ See, that's the thing.
It isn't reckless
because that entire unit
is made up of elite soldiers.
A few worms won't pose
the slightest problem to them.
NILVAL: Then please,
share with us the basic
battle strategies
of the Calydonian Fleet.
‐ I believe I just did.
Besides, we have the Nodos
on our side.
‐ And what if the enemy Nodos
shows up?
ATALANTES: Then our Nodos
will destroy it.
‐ You're going to use the Nodos
as the primary force?
I can't believe
you would let our fate rest
with one individual.
‐ Nilval, I was truly impressed
with the efforts you displayed
on the Huelgoat.
Because of your distinguished
record, you were promoted
to the rank of lieutenant
general and invited to serve
in our fleet.
Now you're an assistant
to the commander.
NILVAL: It's an honor to serve,
sir.
MELEAGROS: Very good.
You will support Atalantes
with everything you've got.
Understood?
‐ Yes, sir, I understand.
We will never achieve victory
playing along with people
like that.
Those monkeys in there
haven't the vaguest idea
what we're up against.
‐ Ma'am.
AGE: Nilval!
‐ Huh?
AGE: [grunting]
‐ Speaking of monkeys,
here comes one now.
‐ Yes, but this monkey's going
to save all of humanity.
Hello there, Mr. Savior.
How can I help you?
‐ Paint.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
ROM: Let us begin.
PROME: The fifth Nodos
and the Iron Tribe,
about their existence
and what we can do about it.
ANEASHA: Representatives
of the Orion and Colonis systems
have contacted us.
Even the LMC responded.
And look: we're getting symbols
of friendship from planets
all over the galaxy.
This is just a few of them.
‐ They've given so much.
‐ It's not
just valuables either.
Every loading dock is filled
with small ships and supplies.
A stunning display of support.
Even planets behind enemy lines
have responded
to your initiative.
‐ Please send my sincere thanks
to all who contributed.
I'm going to give the gifts
I've received to the soldiers
as rewards for
all of their hard work.
‐ The princess
is so very generous.
‐ The gifts are because
of the war they know is coming.
It's inevitable.
ANEASHA: You might be mistaken.
I think they're sending gifts
because they believe in you.
Not only did you discover
a path to the starway,
you found the Nodos.
Just look at you.
You should get some rest,
Princess.
NILVAL: Very clever.
I never would've thought
of embedding a secure link
in the fleet's own
identification signals.
‐ I can't take all the credit.
The ship's AI unit, Bee No Bee,
came up with that one.
So about this plan
for fleet reorganization.
NILVAL: I've already sent
you the data.
MOBEEDO: Bringing it up now.
‐ Those two should be deposed.
I would do it myself if I were
up to the task of leading.
Unfortunately, I've come
to grips with the reality
that I'm not cut out for that.
Frankly, I think your princess
would be the best choice.
‐ Quite a few people share
precisely that opinion.
But Her Highness is still
very young, and she's withdrawn
from leadership roles so that
her brothers may take over.
NILVAL: We can't afford
to sit back and do nothing.
‐ We'll prepare just in case.
By the way, I've been wondering
about our little monkey.
Is Age all right?
‐ Well, Age is...
he's‐‐he's painting.
AGE: [grunting]
[quirky music]
[laughing]
♪ ♪
[explosions]
[lasers firing]
[electronic beeping]
‐ [grunts]
[lasers firing]
[electronic beeping]
COMPUTERIZED VOICE:
Enemy units remaining: zero.
‐ All units return
to the "Argonaut."
[electric whirring]
[whooshing]
Everyone's response time
is dropping.
Time away from battle
has made you sluggish.
Make sure you remedy that before
the next training session.
Dismissed.
ALL: Sir.
ANEASHA: Are you always
that strict?
‐ Hm?
I want them at their best,
right?
‐ We're just rear support now.
Is being so demanding
really necessary?
Why don't you relax a little?
‐ Age is always ready for
battle, and we should be too.
The thing about him
is that he never dwells
on his own greatness.
He's humble, and that's what
allowed him to keep fighting
for hundreds of hours on end.
‐ Iolaous,
don't compete with it.
‐ With "it"?
I'm not.
I can't.
I‐‐I'm competing with Age
and the fighting spirit
that he has come to symbolize.
But I suppose that's not
a big deal to you.
‐ Come on.
You know that's not how it is.
I guess I'll go ahead
and leave you to your training.
‐ Thanks for this.
ANEASHA: Any time.
♪ ♪
‐ I thought he'd be drawing
something more cheerful.
But that's kind of creepy.
‐ It's dark.
What is it, anyway?
AGE: A story I heard from Dad
and the others.
‐ Dad and the others?
AGE: Dhianeila calls them
the Golden Tribe.
‐ Golden Tribe?
‐ You mean...
♪ ♪
‐ Star.
‐ I get it.
You see?
It's the fiery demise
of the Silver Tribe.
‐ Yes, I see.
The boy's picture has suddenly
become quite clear.
It is the doom of our enemies.
‐ We can use this picture.
Trust me.
‐ Use?
But how?
‐ The fact that the boy
is drawing this
proves that the Golden Tribe
predicted
our triumphant victory.
We are definitely going
to send this picture
down to the PR department.
‐ Hmm.
You think that
after seeing this picture
everyone will be more interested
in joining our cause.
You're brilliant.
It must be genetic.
[both laugh]
‐ Huh?
‐ We want you
to keep on drawing.
And when it's finished,
we shall donate it
to those under the flag
of the Yunos royal family.
‐ Nilval, you are in charge
of this picture.
He is to have access to
all the materials that he needs.
‐ Put in charge of a picture.
All of
their interpretations aside,
what does this picture mean?
AGE: Future.
NILVAL: Whose future?
AGE: It's the place
where Age is going.
‐ The light,
what does that mean?
AGE: Dhianeila.
Because Dhianelia is the light
that finds everyone's path,
even in the dark sky.
NILVAL: You wanted to protect
this light that shines
even in destruction.
That's why you left
the "Argonaut," isn't it?
AGE: It isn't safe
to be with Age.
‐ This bright light, do you know
when it will lead all of us?
AGE: When a star dies.
‐ What?
‐ A very important star dies,
and Dhianelia,
she gets really sad.
NILVAL: Do you know the name
of this star?
‐ Oh, no.
[soft instrumental music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
PROME: Perhaps the Iron Tribe
and the Silver Tribe
can coexist peacefully.
ROM: No.
They are unstable beings
ruled by irrational thoughts
and emotions.
We must eradicate them
before they develop
into the scourge of our galaxy.
To accomplish this,
we must send multiple Nodos.
PROME: Chaos would ensure
if multiple Nodos were to fight.
A maelstrom of that magnitude
would indeed destroy
an entire race.
ROM: Confrontation
with the fifth Nodos
is a Labor commanded of us
by our predecessors,
the Golden Tribe.
It is unavoidable.
PROME: And if our Nodos
are destroyed?
ROM: We shall leave one behind.
The Labors also dictate
that the other Nodos
are to protect Yuty
of the Silver Tribe.
She stays.
♪ ♪
I agree to destroy
the Iron Tribe.
We'll settle the matter
by sending off multiple Nodos.
Phaetho,
I sense you're disturbed.
I have eliminated
lowly emotions.
‐ Anaesha,
Age's world was made barren.
We must make it bloom
with flowers like these.
[shimmering tones]
‐ Are you all right?
‐ I feel it,
a sudden surge of hostility.
‐ That means...
‐ Yes, Aneasha.
It has begun.
NILVAL: Fire main cannons!
[lasers firing]
Maintain formation and focus
firepower on the advance force.
MELEAGROS: Hold your fire!
Look at that.
[intense music]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[crashing]
[explosions]
♪ ♪
KARKINOS: Bellcross, he stirs.
‐ This is it.
‐ If more than one of us
becomes involved in this battle,
what prevents us from turning
on each other
rather than the fifth?
‐ A confrontation between
more than two members
of the Heroic Tribe has always
been unpredictable.
There is the possibility
that it will end
in unthinkable destruction.
Because of that,
the Silver Tribe is undecided
on the matter.
‐ I would surely give my life
to defeat the fifth Nodos.
Fear is not my nature.
After all,
that was the Labor given to me.
‐ But if you do that,
many stars will die too.
‐ That is why before
that can happen,
you must destroy
Lernaea and I.
‐ If I must...
I will.
BELL NO BELL: This is footage
from three days ago.
‐ They're using this
to demonstrate how brilliant
they are, huh?
The only strategy they have
is using Age as a shield.
‐ I knew they'd try something
like this.
[whooshing]
MELEAGROS: Attention!
We, the mighty Calydonian Fleet,
have finally
reached the solar system.
Planet of the ancient god,
Jupiter.
WOMAN: Oh, look.
It's so bright.
[all speaking indistinctly]
WOMAN: Look at the colors.
‐ At last, we shall make
our triumphant return.
The cradle of all humanity,
our true home.
[alarm blaring]
MAN: Enemy anthills approaching.
[rumbling]
‐ It's massive.
MAN: This is the largest one
on record.
Its offensive capabilities
are unknown.
‐ Those worms!
I'll be damned if we allow them
free reign in our own home!
Big brother, deliver orders
for my Quental Unit
to begin their attack.
‐ There's no need.
We shall let our very own savior
deal with the enemy.
‐ But big brother, it'll damage
our family's reputation
if we do nothing.
‐ Atalantes, do you know
what's missing from
the Yunos royal family?
[intense music]
♪ ♪
[explosions]
It's simple, really.
All that we're missing
is the one thing
that would make
our family great: a legend.
When we win this holy war
without a single life lost,
they will speak of our great
family for generations to come
as the chosen bloodline.
That legend will aid
in our family's dominion
over the entire galaxy.
The Nodos is simply a tool
to accomplish that.
‐ You're so brilliant.
‐ How ridiculous.
♪ ♪
‐ Oh, Age.
ROM: We have made a decision.
♪ ♪
YUTY: It's decided.
More than one of you
shall fight.
‐ Yes.
I'll go.
YUTY: Lecty.
MEHITAK: I'm going too.
♪ ♪
LECTY: But why?
‐ All of you will go.
Karkinos and Lecty
will battle him.
And if that isn't good enough,
then Mehitak will join in.
And don't worry,
I'll stop whoever loses control.
♪ ♪
‐ [growling]
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA: Their foolish
behavior enrages the stars
next time on "Heroic Age"
episode 12:
"The Torch of Destruction."