‐ I've jumped
far too many times.
Erymanthos has linked
every alternative
for the culmination
of this battle.
The potential energy
of every outcome
will accumulate,
imploding into
the first timeline to give way.
Ugh!
[Bellcross growling]
[cries out]
‐ Take my hand!
‐ Run away, Mehitak.
Run away!
Right now!
[explosion booms]
[Bellcross growls]
‐ Karkinos!
‐ No! Age!
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[Bellcross roars]
Something's... wrong.
‐ What? What is it?
What are you feeling?
♪ ♪
‐ It's Age.
[high‐pitched ringing]
‐ [gasps]
Lecty!
Wake up! Please!
♪ ♪
‐ Mm.
‐ You bastard.
[Bellcross growling]
♪ ♪
[shimmering and tinkling]
[militaristic music]
‐ We must continue
pushing forward at all costs!
The time has come.
We are now within reach
of our home world.
My friends, hear me when I say
that ours will be the destiny
of righteous conquerors.
Behold!
The red god of war himself
hails to us
as if to bless our advancement.
We dare not shrink
from such fortune.
Atalantes, the order,
if you please.
‐ Attention, all fleets.
The enemy will doubtless rally
in our wake.
All ships are to maintain
full speed along the Starway.
Those bringing up the rear
are to deploy
around the flagship.
Everyone,
assume battle formation!
‐ This hardly seems
like a wise strategy.
It's risky.
The Nodos ultimately rendered
the Starway unstable, after all.
‐ Those imbeciles
will be the death of us all.
They're obviously
just making it up
as they go along‐‐
this mission is suicide.
‐ Then, we intervene?
‐ No. Not yet.
First, we investigate
the Starway's instability.
We need to start by figuring
a way out of the mess we're in.
Then we seize control.
[space roaring]
MAN: The Nodos approaches.
What must be done?
‐ The Iron Tribe
must be destroyed.
[intense music]
‐ Oh, no.
YUTY:
Karkinos, why do you not resist?
It can't be!
‐ Frenzy.
YUTY: He is restraining himself
to avoid contamination
by the fifth's madness.
He can't hold on for long.
I must put an end to this!
‐ Are you troubled?
An uninjured Nodos remains.
‐ Mehitak cannot face
the fifth alone!
Send me!
♪ ♪
[gasps]
‐ To think... to think,
I cannot find you anywhere.
Oh, Age.
[shimmering and tinkling]
♪ ♪
[lasers blasting]
MAN:
The enemy Nodos has gone mad.
We are in danger.
‐ The Iron Tribe must not
be allowed to advance.
More worlds
will only be destroyed.
Their very existence
threatens this galaxy.
♪ ♪
[insects fluttering]
‐ What are you afraid of?
Break through it!
Withdrawal is not
an option for us!
Hold the line!
Do not break for it!
‐ That's insane.
They charged headlong
into battle
without waiting for backup?
‐ No doubt
it was Meleagros' order.
In the meantime, Age is fighting
out there all by himself.
Seems that the fleet is content
to leave him well behind.
‐ Those reckless idiots.
‐ Mm.
‐ There's no logic
in their strategy.
If this continues,
the Earth will become
a war zone.
‐ Princess, haven't you given
Meleagros and Atalantes
the benefit of the doubt
long enough?
‐ What are you saying?
‐ Forgive me for saying so,
Princess,
but your brothers have made
an absolute mockery
of the Yunos family name,
and now their arrogance
stands to threaten
the entire human race.
‐ You speak the truth.
How could I ever fault you
for that?
In their ignorance,
my brothers would sooner destroy
our precious home world
than lead us to victory.
And yet...
‐ And yet,
you fear risking chaos
by standing against them.
You tolerate their incompetence
because their warmongering
united the Alliance Council.
Am I correct?
‐ Yes.
‐ So your part in all of this
is done.
Now that you've
dutifully turned Age over
to those better equipped
to handle him,
there's nothing left
but to watch things unfold
from a safe distance.
‐ No, Aneasha!
That isn't true!
‐ And why not?
After all,
when everything
is said and done,
there's no reason
to have assumed
Age would be loyal to you.
[melancholy music]
‐ He did choose my brothers
over me.
‐ Only because he thought,
by doing so,
he could protect
you and the "Argonaut."
Surely, you can see that.
‐ Do you think so?
I can't see him.
Age's presence
is out of my reach now.
I'm afraid he won't come back,
that he is lost to us.
♪ ♪
‐ From now on,
many stars will vanish
from the sky,
and many paths will fade away.
But you?
You'll find the path.
No matter how dark it gets,
you'll always lead us.
‐ I can't even find
what path to take.
‐ Just listen
to what your heart says.
If Age were with us now,
that's what he'd tell you.
And don't forget,
you still have us.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
MELEAGROS: Wh‐why
are the rear units hesitating?
Tell them all to push forward
right now!
‐ Sir, we can't risk it.
There are too many enemy ships
appearing at the stern.
‐ What? Then‐‐then send in
all remaining fleets.
‐ Brother, wait.
‐ Charge, you stinking cowards!
‐ I said wait!
‐ What now?
ATALANTES: The Bronze Tribe
is using the planet's moon
as a nest.
If we focus our firepower
there‐‐
MELEAGROS: Don't undermine me!
Ready the main cannons!
‐ Something is approaching
from Sector 439.
It's big.
‐ What?
♪ ♪
[explosion booms]
[high‐pitched shrieking]
‐ [gasps]
‐ Is there something wrong?
‐ I... I can sense Age.
[whimpering]
‐ Are you all right?
‐ I'm scared.
He isn't himself.
♪ ♪
[Bellcross roars]
MELEAGROS: Look at that.
That is our Nodos.
‐ What in the hell
is wrong with him?
[insects fluttering]
MAN: The impact knocked
the satellite out of orbit.
It's gonna crash
into the planet's surface.
‐ Yes!
Now, that's what I call power.
♪ ♪
‐ What does he hope
to accomplish?
‐ [gasps]
Karkinos!
[rocks cracking]
♪ ♪
MAN: Our shields won't be able
to withstand the impact!
Sir, we've got to get all ships
to pull back immediately.
‐ Certainly not!
Our Nodos has dealt
a crushing blow
to the enemy squadrons.
‐ This is our moment of triumph.
Do not withdraw!
‐ If we don't
get out of here fast,
the entire fleet
will be torn to ribbons
by the aftershock.
‐ What? Don't be ridiculous.
We're fine.
‐ Ah!
♪ ♪
[all yelling]
[Bellcross cries out]
‐ He's gone... into a frenzy.
MAN: We must leave this place.
There will be
no stopping him now.
♪ ♪
‐ Damn it.
This foolish sensation again.
Prepare to retreat.
Leave the Iron Tribe
to their precious savior.
[shimmering and tinkling]
[Bellcross roaring]
YUTY: Mehitak, don't!
Don't be foolish.
‐ I have... no choice.
I must.
[whimpering]
Artemia!
♪ ♪
MAN: The advance fleets
are sustaining major damage.
‐ Wh‐why won't he stop?
Has he gone completely mad?
‐ Everyone brace yourselves
for a direct hit!
[alarm blaring]
‐ [gasps]
Get us out of here immediately!
‐ Damn. There's no time.
♪ ♪
[Bellcross roaring]
[both gasping and yelling]
♪ ♪
‐ What was that?
‐ I‐I don't know.
It almost looked like
another Nodos.
NILVAL: That's the same monster
that destroyed Huelgoat.
‐ And it's suddenly trying
to save us now?
How will this affect
our strategy?
‐ How should I know?
Send communication
to the "Argonaut."
Tell them everything.
‐ Hmm.
‐ At this rate,
there will hardly be
anything left
for me to work with.
Damn those two idiots.
‐ [gasps]
[weeping softly]
‐ You can talk to me, Princess.
‐ Oh, Aneasha.
It's all gone so terribly wrong.
This is not Age.
He would never do
these awful things.
Never.
Something has come over him,
something he cannot control.
[sniffles]
It's up to us.
We must save our savior.
MOBEEDO:
What you see in front of you
is the latest report
from Commander Nilval.
‐ Do you mean to say
that the Nodos is destroying
everything in its path
indiscriminately?
‐ Keep in mind,
there was a lag time of 50 hours
when we received
the information.
It's likely that Mars has been
annihilated in the interim,
along with our forces.
‐ Not once has Age attacked us!
How dare you even assume
he could be capable
of such brutality?
‐ We can't be certain.
What if he's showing us
his true colors now?
‐ An excellent point.
Let's not forget,
there's a part of him
that still belongs
to the Heroic Tribe.
‐ He's a monster, after all.
‐ [growls]
DHIANEILA: No.
‐ [gasps]
MOBEEDO: Your Highness.
‐ We are unworthy
to receive you.
‐ Please, Princess.
‐ I'll be fine.
♪ ♪
However hopeless
things may appear,
he is our savior.
You must have faith in him.
‐ Well, yes, but‐‐
‐ I will lead him away
from the path of destruction.
I'm going to save Age
from himself.
‐ Lead him?
‐ You mean...
‐ The time has come.
Will you all join with me?
♪ ♪
‐ Of course we will.
Princess,
may our undying devotion
be as a light for you
in even the darkest night.
We live to serve you.
‐ This moment has been long
in coming for us,
Princess Dhianeila.
♪ ♪
NILVAL: 300 hours have passed
since Mars became a battlefield.
The planet escaped destruction
only because of
the enemy Nodos intervention.
Fully half of our forces
have sustained severe damage.
The other half's condition
is currently unknown.
We've been attempting
to route the enemy individually
as the opportunity arises,
but likely as not,
our fleet
will be completely wiped out
in less than a hundred hours.
The blame rests almost entirely
on our executive commanders
and partly on the fact
that I failed to divest them
of their authority
when I had the opportunity.
To assist the Alliance Council,
I make
this urgent recommendation‐‐
please, Captain Mobeedo
and the "Argonaut"
must be placed at the vanguard.
This is Lieutenant General
Nilval Nephew.
End communication.
MOBEEDO:
What the hell are you doing?
‐ [gasps]
‐ What's this supposed to be,
a will?
‐ Huh? No.
MOBEEDO: Trust me,
you don't want to die just yet.
You'll miss all the fun.
Our brave little princess
has taken command.
‐ Is that so?
‐ And the council has accepted
your recommendation.
Not only will the fleet
be completely reorganized
under the princess' command,
but counting our new allies,
Colonus and Orion,
the fleet
will nearly double in size.
Take my word‐‐
you'd be hard‐pressed
to find higher spirits
in paradise right now.
My point being
that reinforcements
are on the way to you.
Promise me you'll be alive
when we get there... heh.
‐ [sighs]
So our guiding star
has finally awoken.
‐ Our homeland awaits us!
We shall push forward!
The Earth will be mine!
Thus will be my glory!
[guns cocking]
What is the meaning of this?
NILVAL: Your so‐called destiny
has left the fleet in ruins.
But I suppose I'll have to make
the best of what's left.
‐ Nilval.
‐ If you have anything
resembling good sense
between you,
you'll come along peacefully.
‐ This is a willful act
of sedition!
‐ Not quite.
Allow me
to convey a message to you
on behalf
of the Yunos royal family.
‐ Dhianeila.
‐ Please try to understand.
You've left me no choice
but the course of action
before us.
‐ You traitorous upstart!
‐ Brothers,
I beg forgiveness of you,
but this must not continue.
You have disgraced us‐‐
our name,
the posts
that have been entrusted to you,
the very principles
for which we stand.
It must end here.
Our destiny is not a plaything!
‐ How dare you slander me?
I would've led us to victory!
‐ And with this,
the Alliance Council expects
your resignations swiftly.
By the time this message
reaches both of you,
the Calydonian Fleet
will be reorganized
with me as executive commander.
You are hereby ordered
to relinquish all authority
to Lieutenant General Nilval
immediately.
I advise you to do so
without incident.
‐ Now,
who could argue with that?
Let's go.
[both wincing, sighing]
♪ ♪
MAN: Horoscope acquisition
in progress.
All sails are set
for reconnaissance.
‐ So, then, the "Argonaut"
can finally set sail
on her maiden voyage.
‐ But master, this is,
in fact, our 82nd voyage.
‐ It's a figure of speech, Bee.
I've been waiting
for her highness to take command
for a long time.
Something tells me this journey
will be unlike any other.
Now, let's get out there,
make our own way.
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA: Age...
[rockets roaring]
[epic orchestral music]
♪ ♪
[shimmering and tinkling]
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
Humanity despairs
as its last hope
lay in shambles.
Next time on "Heroic Age,"
episode 15,
"When the Light Falls."