[thrumming]
[clanking]
BEE NO BEE:
According to my estimates,
both supply replenishments
and damage repairs are expected
to be fully completed
within 90 minutes, Master.
‐ You know, Bee, I had hoped
to give the crew a little break
when we came to Titarros.
‐ Master, forgive my saying so,
but you look quite exhausted.
Why don't you take a break?
‐ If only it were that easy,
my friend.
Just look at the kid.
[wind blowing]
MAN: In all my long years
serving this planet,
I never thought I would see it
become a theater of war
for two such powerful creatures.
Fortunately for us, however,
it would appear that
the Silver Tribe does not intend
to hold us responsible
for this incident.
Their noted silence on
the matter would tend to suggest
that Titarros's political
neutrality still stands
more or less.
MAN: That said,
despite our efforts
and discretion,
news of the battle
has swiftly spread
to all corners of the galaxy.
‐ I'm aware of the situation,
and I'm sorry.
‐ We won't hear of it.
You, Princess,
have become a symbol of hope
for those living
under oppression.
For that,
on behalf of our people,
I wish you the guidance
and wisdom of the stars.
‐ And so may their glow
illuminate you always.
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
[light music]
‐ [grunting]
‐ I've heard of dedication,
but...
‐ He's been up there for hours.
‐ That's what you get
for telling him
how happy everyone would be
if he helped out.
‐ No, that's what you get
for telling him
he'd get to play with paint.
‐ Shut up.
‐ Make me!
[swish]
BOTH: Princess.
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA:
Age, how are you feeling?
‐ I feel great.
I slept for a long time.
‐ Is that so?
I'm glad to hear it.
‐ I've been helping out
with that paint.
[grunts]
‐ [giggles]
‐ [laughs]
DHIANEILA: Well, as much as
we appreciate all the hard work,
I think it's time
for you to come back inside.
‐ 'Kay.
WOMAN: Ship lock released.
Gyrostabilizer activated.
Output steady at 0.2%.
WOMAN:
Departing from docking station.
MOBEEDO:
Set a course for the Starway.
Good‐bye, valiant friends.
[clanking]
[soft music]
YUTY: Why did you not destroy
the fifth, Karkinos?
KARKINOS: The situation
did not seem to warrant
the death
of innocent bystanders.
YUTY: Tribe Daedalus scarcely
warrants our benevolence.
No less than the Golden Tribe
thought them unworthy of title.
‐ Nonetheless,
destroying their planet
means sacrificing
the planet terminal,
which the Silver Tribe deems
quite valuable.
The ability to create worlds
has been lost
since the Golden Tribe departed
from this universe.
Because of it, the Silver Tribe
is reluctant to condemn
unless absolutely necessary.
YUTY: Reluctant?
I think not.
They simply haven't the time
to concern themselves
with so trivial a people.
For the sake of your own tribes,
you would do well
to remember this.
Do not forget your sacred
pledges to the Golden Tribe
nor that according
to those pledges,
each of you is indentured
to a people
governed by the Silver Tribe,
upon whose mercies they subsist.
♪ ♪
Mehitak, you will go next.
‐ What?
Me?
I can't.
‐ No.
Allow me.
YUTY: You shall both go.
Mehitak will destroy
the Iron Tribe's ship.
Under no circumstance must the
fifth remain in their employ.
‐ But‐‐
‐ And do not worry, Karkinos.
Innocent bystanders,
they are not.
‐ As you wish.
♪ ♪
MAN: Dear friends, word of your
battle has reached far and wide.
Naturally,
we admire your courage.
Such valor is an inspiration
to us all.
If refuge were ours to give,
we would not hesitate.
May the stars continue
to shine upon your voyage.
‐ Your Highness, that's 20.
Every terminal planet
where we've requested entry
has turned us down.
Politely, of course.
IOLAOUS: Either their space port
is under repair
or the weather is bad
or they insist there's a danger
of atmospheric disturbance
due to the "Argonaut's" size.
ANEASHA: At least everyone is
cheering us on.
IOLAOUS: Hmm, shrugging us off
is more like it.
ANEASHA: They're afraid of
reprisals from the Silver Tribe.
We can't in all fairness
expect them to harbor us
at their peril, now can we?
MOBEEDO: Having a Nodos onboard
can't count much in our favor
either.
After what's happened,
everyone in the entire galaxy
must know he's
on the "Argonaut."
At this rate, we'll be forced
to leave the Starway
and set ourselves adrift.
Your Highness, why not publicize
the Nodos presence?
Force these planets
to take us in.
‐ We cannot.
The fate of our tribe
is at stake,
but we will not risk
the safety of an ally's planet
for the comfort
of our own people.
MOBEEDO: Then what next?
‐ It's time
to leave the Starway.
Though we may have traveled
long and far
to reclaim our destiny,
the journey has not yet
reached its end.
Alas, though hope springs
eternal in all our hearts,
what lies ahead
will test it bitterly.
I promise you,
I will find the strength
in myself to forge ahead
if you in turn will
find the strength in yourselves.
Home will be hard‐won for us...
‐ I don't like the idea
of leaving the Starway again.
‐ What if we get lost trying
to find our way back?
‐ Don't worry.
‐ Huh?
‐ Like she says,
just have faith.
‐ Remember that we are
the future of the human race.
We have faith that our princess
will not lead us astray.
Beside her, we will fight
for the very right to survive.
‐ The sacrifices she has made
for our sakes
are too numerous to count.
If need be, we should follow her
to the ends of the universe.
‐ By the gods, if our princess
requires it of us,
we will follow her
even to our deaths.
‐ Our faith in Her Highness
will not be shaken.
By her lights our destiny
will be fulfilled.
‐ Master,
all sections unanimously agree
with Dhianeila's decision
to forge onward.
‐ So much for going back home
even though that was
the whole point of the Nodos.
So long as spirits are high,
I guess there are worse fates
than drifting aimlessly.
I don't get it.
What the hell are we doing?
‐ Come on, Master.
Cheer up.
‐ You know,
testing our luck out there
in the great unknown
does have its charm.
MOBEEDO: Look sharp.
I want all sections on the ready
when the enemy
rears its head again,
and for those of you attending
the liaison conference,
I want those damn reports
yesterday.
‐ Well now.
The captain's fired up.
‐ Excellent work.
Now stay focused
and be prepared for anything.
ALL: Sir, yes, sir.
‐ Mm.
‐ [chuckles]
Like father like son, I suppose.
‐ Not quite.
The captain is more
straightforward
with the princess than I am.
You'll never hear me complain
the way he does.
Even if we never get home.
‐ You know what?
It's amazing.
‐ Hmm.
‐ Just think of it.
Servants, troops,
the captain, you,
everyone all working together
toward a common goal.
Such solidarity is rare.
Especially these days.
‐ Hmm.
‐ Usually,
people from such different walks
of life as we are
wouldn't get the chance to talk.
This is a special place.
‐ You're right.
‐ Huh?
‐ I'm glad that
we've become friends, Aneasha.
I really am.
‐ Oh.
You are?
‐ You're a gifted healer
and your loyalty to the princess
is an inspiration to us all.
It's encouraging to know
you're taking such good care
of Dhianeila.
I'm very grateful for the fact.
‐ The princess, right.
[playful music]
♪ ♪
AGE: [laughing]
‐ [giggles]
‐ They said
if I help take care of them,
I can eat as much as I want.
MAN: That's wonderful news,
my boy.
WOMAN: We're counting on you.
‐ Yay!
I'm helping!
[laughs]
‐ Indeed.
Understand, Age.
As our ship leaves
the safety of the Starway,
we will count on you
a great deal
according to the 12‐‐
‐ This is good.
♪ ♪
You know, I really like you.
‐ Huh?
‐ Did he‐‐
‐ He did.
‐ Me and Bellcross both.
We like everyone
on the "Argonaut."
You're all so nice to us.
MAIL: Aw.
TAIL: Is that all he meant?
DHIANEILA: Age, how could
we ever repay such devotion?
Olone will be restored
to its former glory, of course,
but is there nothing I can do
for you personally?
AGE: Sure.
You can take me with you.
DHIANEILA:
Wha‐‐what do you mean?
‐ To your future.
‐ "Future"?
[wind rustles]
AGE: Aren't you gonna eat it?
‐ Yes.
Yes, of course.
‐ Princess!
‐ Wash it first!
‐ [chuckles]
BOTH: Eww!
It is good.
[giggles]
[wind blowing]
LECTY:
Prome O, my master,
I humbly request an audience
with your grace.
‐ Lecty,
the proud daughter of time.
Speak freely.
We have a great many things
to discuss, do we not?
LECTY: Indeed, yes.
Thank you.
PROME: You are here
because of the fifth Nodos.
‐ Your Grace is perceptive.
Also, I am here to speak
of our contracts with you.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ He is mine.
This ends now.
The Nodos will not
come any farther with them.
DHIANEILA: [grunts]
The Bronze Tribe.
WOMAN: All personnel
to emergency stations.
WOMAN: Top floor,
initiate suspension plate...
WOMAN: Top floor repositioned.
Prepare for battle floors
lined to sequence.
Suspension plate transfer
commencing.
Repeat, suspension plate
transfer commencing.
Plate linkage confirmed.
Ascending to starboard‐side
isolation area.
WOMAN:
Isolation partition sprang.
Hatch doors aligned in sequence.
WOMAN: Ant hills forming
defensive line
near "Argonaut's" stern.
MAN: More ant hills appearing.
30 in all.
‐ Looks like our publicity
made them jealous,
and here we are drifting
all by our lonesome
in the middle of nowhere.
‐ I'm detecting an asteroid belt
blocking our path
preventing visual.
[epic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Asteroids?
Oh, no.
‐ It's the Cemetery Belt.
‐ Lost in a cemetery?
Not bad.
That might just work
to our advantage
if we play our cards right.
BEE NO BEE:
It can certainly provide cover
for the Organ unit, Master.
‐ Move forward
into the asteroid belt,
and commence evasive maneuvers.
Let's live to fight another day,
lads.
Get the enemy off our tail.
I expect to see all of you
in one piece when this is over.
No heroics out there.
Organ unit, prepare to move out!
Where's that monkey?
‐ Any luck?
‐ Not yet.
‐ Where did he run off to?
‐ Maybe he went outside.
‐ You think so?
♪ ♪
BEE NO BEE: Enemy now entering
the Cemetery Belt
in pursuit of the "Argonaut,"
Master.
I estimate 3,000 troops
per individual craft.
‐ Commence preemptive attack!
Organ unit, move out!
‐ Organ one,
establish a perimeter
around the "Argonaut"
immediately.
♪ ♪
‐ Prepare sickbay
to receive the injured.
Anyone on duty who appears
shell shocked or overworked
is to be brought here to rest.
♪ ♪
MAN: Area D28 is 98% eliminated.
IOLAOUS: Damn it!
Organ one through five,
follow me.
The rest of you stay behind.
Do not let them get any closer.
‐ Age.
‐ He's coming for me.
‐ The other Nodos?
The one you fought on Titarros?
‐ Yeah, and he's not alone.
‐ How many of them are there?
‐ Well, there's two of them
on the way here,
so, let's see...
with Bellcross,
that'll make four of us.
‐ Mm.
‐ Don't worry.
‐ [exhales]
Everyone onboard the "Argonaut"
is in danger
because of me.
I can't help but worry.
I'm so frightened.
‐ It'll be all right.
I promise you.
Do you remember?
The 12 Labors.
I'm here to protect you.
‐ But who's going
to protect you?
‐ Me and Bellcross will make
a path.
The "Argonaut" will make it
out of here.
Even if it means
that we have to stay behind,
but don't be sad.
You'll see us again.
‐ No, wait.
Please...
‐ Good‐bye.
[valiant music]
[thrums, chimes]
♪ ♪
‐ [growls]
‐ Oh, Age.
You go to such extreme lengths
to defend us.
Why?
♪ ♪
The future.
I swear to you.
As you wish...
it shall be.
♪ ♪
‐ [growls]
BEE NO BEE:
Massive shockwave detected.
The enemy squadrons
obstructing our course
have completely vanished.
‐ I'll be damned.
Organ unit,
the Nodos has cleared a pathway
for the ship.
I want everyone
to retreat from combat
and redeploy towards the front
of the "Argonaut" at once.
IOLAOUS:
Way to steal our thunder, kid.
‐ Age, this is
your final warning.
Surrender to us peacefully
or they will die.
‐ [growls]
‐ Such a shame.
♪ ♪
IOLAOUS: [grunts]
What is that?
MOBEEDO: The collateral damage
from this fight
will be enormous.
All ships are to stay clear
of the effected area
till otherwise instructed.
‐ Ugh!
[crashing]
YUTY: What're you doing?
‐ [gasps]
I‐I just‐‐
‐ [chuckles]
Karkinos and Lernaea are already
taking care of the fifth.
Your duty is the destruction
of the "Argonaut."
‐ [grunts]
YUTY: Come now.
What task could be simpler
for a being with your gifts?
Did not the countless tribes
you've driven to extinction
provide sufficient practice?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[crashing]
LECTY: The Golden Tribe,
could they have foreseen
this battle?
Could they have foreseen our
once proud race held hostage
by the contracts we hold
with the Silver Tribe?
What those contracts
would come to really mean?
♪ ♪
‐ That courageous boy,
he put himself
on the line for us.
‐ Come on, Age.
Where do you think you're going?
DHIANEILA: Age.
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA: Before
the battle‐weary "Argonaut"
a new Nodos emerges.
Known in the annals of legend
as Artemia.
Next time on "Heroic Age"...