[valiant music]
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA: Long, long ago
in a time all
but lost to memory..
at the farthest reaches
of our universe,
there dwelled a people called
the Golden Tribe.
They, who possessed
the power to create worlds,
and who knew the will of time,
beckoned to the other tribes
spread out across the stars.
"Come forth," they said.
"Come forth from the worlds
that cradle you
and into the wide universe
beyond."
Their words echoed
through the void
and three great tribes
there were who heeded them.
Three who came forth,
summoned by
the Golden Tribe's call.
The Silver Tribe.
The Bronze Tribe.
And the Heroic Tribe.
[explosions rumbling]
[electricity crackling]
Later, when,
in their boundless wisdom,
the Golden Tribe chose to leave
this universe for another,
a new people emerged
to answer their call.
[engines rumbling]
This new tribe came forth
into the universe
with its own unique power:
humanity.
♪ ♪
Upon men was bestowed the name:
the Iron Tribe.
[instrumental music]
♪ ♪
[shimmering tone]
These vibrations...
we're getting closer.
I can feel it.
♪ ♪
[machinery hissing]
ANEASHA: Your Highness.
‐ I've seen it.
Our destination
is very close by.
‐ Really?
‐ Please prepare
for the declaration.
The time has come.
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[all speaking at once]
♪ ♪
MOBEEDO: It's been two cycles
since we left the Starway.
Wouldn't be surprised
if we're wandering in circles.
‐ The "Argonaut" navigates
within a negative 0.3 margin
of error, master.
‐ That's not what I meant
exactly.
I'm just talking about what it
feels like to me, Bee no Bee.
MAN: Captain Mobeedo.
‐ Huh?
MAN: The Food Division
has submitted
the self supply ratio
for this cycle.
WOMAN: The Health and Labor
Division has submitted
the estimated joule requirements
for this cycle.
‐ The bridge committee will hold
deliberation within 20 hours.
‐ But the bridge committee has
granted itself the day off
by majority vote, master.
‐ [roars]
Those lay‐abouts can vacation
after they've done their job.
Ahh!
Lousy bureaucrats will turn
this into a ghost ship
before you know it.
What if we'd had an actual
food riot on our hands?
‐ Our current ration stockpile
is well over 15%, master.
‐ So what?
We're off the Starway with
no idea of our destination.
[sighs] Searching
for the remnants of a ship
lost 60 cycles ago
is a fool's errand.
‐ But according to
my program protocols, master,
the ship's discovery is
absolutely vital
to humankind's survival.
‐ Meaning the situation is
so desperate all we can do
is hope for some old legend
to help us turn the tide.
[sighs] Even so,
if it's required of me,
I'll do anything it takes
to see the princess
securely on the throne.
‐ A transmission from Dhianeila.
"Your presence is requested in
the briefing room immediately."
‐ Really? And what do you think
are the chances
she'll ask us
to set a course for home?
‐ That would be a number
approaching 0, master.
‐ Naturally.
[doors rumble]
IOLAOUS: I understand Your
Highness has located the planet.
‐ I have at long last.
‐ [chuckles]
‐ No further, please.
Men cannot come any closer
to the princess than this.
I am sorry.
‐ Oh.
My congratulations, princess.
‐ Your Highness, if you please,
the current results
of our search. Bee?
‐ Analysis of the wave form
is complete.
I have an image.
‐ A planet.
Can it be?
‐ But to think
that a planet exists
in complete absence
of a Starway...
DHIANEILA: This can only be
Oron, the ruined planet.
Upon this desolate world lives
he who will save the human race.
[wind whooshing]
[explosion]
‐ [chuckles]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[straining]
Yahh!
[laughs]
Thank you for being
so delicious!
‐ [grunting]
‐ [giggles]
[laughing]
Mom, I'm back!
COMPUTER:
Crew reentry confirmed.
Onboard activity within
Code 4 parameters approved.
‐ Check it out, Mom!
I've got a Fuuto leg!
COMPUTER: Command invalid.
Restate according
to coherency protocol 6.
‐ It's a big one too!
I'll bet if I eat
just a little bit at a time,
it'll last me till
the kobuu comes back.
[giggling]
Okay, Mom, it's ready.
COMPUTER: Command accepted.
Materials processing.
‐ [laughing]
Oh, yeah,
that really hits the spot.
COMPUTER: Command invalid.
‐ Not much rain lately.
Have you noticed?
COMPUTER: Command invalid.
‐ I wonder if maybe the sun has
had too many clouds to eat.
I know whenever I eat
too many Fuuto legs,
nothing comes out of me
for a while.
What do you think about it, Mom?
COMPUTER: Command invalid.
Restate according
to coherency protocol 6.
‐ I'd better give Fuuto
something.
For growing so big and strong,
thank you very much.
[grunts]
Thanks so much for letting me
eat your legs all the time.
They're really tasty.
‐ [grunting]
BEE NO BEE: Orbital trajectory
now aligned
to the planet below.
MOBEEDO: I should have
expected this,
but for the princess
to go down there in person...
IOLAOUS: Organ units
are standing by.
We are ready for descent.
‐ Be careful down there.
At the first sign of trouble,
I want the princess
brought back, understood?
‐ Absolutely, Father.
Understood.
[tense music]
IOLAOUS: We'll be escorting
Her Highness.
So look sharp.
I expect you all to prove
our reputation as Yunos knights.
WOMAN: Bay doors
are now open.
Basilis ready for launch.
Mooring clamp released.
Request for take‐off granted.
Engines ignited.
Launch.
Basilis have separated
from the mother ship.
The course is set.
AGE: I wonder if they're the
ones Dad always talked about.
If they are, I'll have to say
good‐bye to you, Fuuto.
‐ [grunts sadly]
IOLAOUS: Meteorite craters.
This planet is completely
in ruins.
How could anyone hope
to survive here?
‐ The atmosphere still seems
capable of supporting life.
Solar radiation levels are
significant, but not fatal.
‐ I feel a powerful presence.
There.
‐ A new location
has been designated.
All descending forces
to change course.
DHIANEILA:
The one we seek is very near.
Within an arid wilderness,
he waits, as foretold.
The only human in the universe
to have been raised
by the Golden Tribe.
IOLAOUS: Is that a signal?
‐ It's‐‐it's a ship.
♪ ♪
ANEASHA: This distress call has
been broadcasting for 120 years.
We're not picking up
any signs of life
or movement
at the moment, but...
Attention.
The Lotus unit is now cleared
to begin reconnaissance.
MAN: Will they be safe?
ANEASHA: Tail and Mail will be
sent in with them
as a precaution.
MAN: Roger that.
I'll patrol the area.
TAIL: Did someone actually
try to plant trees here?
MAIL: What did they expect
to grow in a desert?
‐ Think we'll find anything
in there, Mail?
‐ Well, the princess sure seems
to think we will.
COMPUTER: Intruders detected.
Onboard activity within code 4
parameters restricted.
‐ It's still working!
‐ Let's fix it up a bit,
shall we?
[whooshing]
[machinery hums to life]
‐ I found the ship's records.
‐ Great. I'll upload them
to the "Argonaut."
Yeah, what do you want?
‐ What are you talking about?
‐ Didn't you just tap my helmet?
‐ Mm‐mm.
I didn't do anything.
I thought...
[screaming and crying]
[whooshing]
‐ Master, a large array
of objects
is intercepting
the "Argonaut's" course.
‐ Get me a visual on that
at once.
[alarm blaring]
Ugh. Just what we needed.
‐ Just stay away from us!
‐ Stop right there!
[both grunt]
[both gasp]
No way!
‐ Is that a human?
ANEASHA: I can't get
a clear readout.
It's as though
he's being shielded.
DHIANEILA: I sense
no hostility in him.
I must address the boy
in person.
TAIL AND MAIL: Your Highness!
‐ [gasps]
‐ Please forgive our abrupt
and rather coarse intrusion.
By no means are we here
to seize your home.
We are humankind,
they upon whom
the Golden Tribe bestowed
the name the Iron Tribe.
We have come in hopes of finding
the one foretold of in prophecy,
a being said to possess
the ancient Heroic Tribe within.
Can you help us locate him?
Does such a being
dwell in your midst?
Our future may well
depend on it.
‐ A.G.E.
Hm. Very nice to meet you,
humankind.
That thing can talk?
‐ Enemy approaching.
COMPUTER: All personnel
to emergency battle stations.
Top section: prepare for battle.
[computer speaking indistinctly]
COMPUTER: Lightning hitch
confirmed.
Ascend the starboard side
oscillation area.
Reconfiguration complete.
Isolation partitions raised.
BEE NO BEE: Closing off
tactics floor.
Executing emergency
control system.
MOBEEDO: Scatter oboranas.
Concentrate artillery
portside.
It's a damn Hedron shield.
Switch to rapid fire.
‐ Fifth and sixth Organ Units
ready to engage the enemy.
MOBEEDO: Form
a defensive barrier
along the "Argonaut's"
orbital trajectory.
They're coming.
‐ Come with us. Hurry!
ANEASHA: Closing the hatch.
Take off immediately.
‐ Not yet! We can't just
leave him out there!
‐ It's too late.
♪ ♪
‐ Looks like we've got a scout.
You two come with me.
We're moving in.
♪ ♪
It sent a signal!
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
‐ Mom, no!
[panting]
‐ Be careful!
♪ ♪
‐ Aim for the ones with
teleporting abilities first
before they blanket the sky.
ANEASHA: Our airspace
is blocked.
Units advance to 2:00.
‐ Mother, look out!
‐ [gasps]
‐ What is it?
What's wrong?
‐ He's alone out there.
♪ ♪
[gasps]
‐ The bastards are within range
of Her Highness's ship.
Go as low as you can and get
her the hell out of there!
BEE NO BEE: A giant object
is bearing down on us
at great speed!
MOBEEDO: The whole damn
anthill's coming at us.
Retrieve the princess now!
If they reach us,
the "Argonaut" will be devoured.
‐ Get Dhianeila into
the escape pod.
I'll take her back
to the "Argonaut" myself.
‐ [sighs]
Your Highness.
We must do as he says.
‐ This feeling...
[gasps and whimpers]
‐ Dhianeila, what is it?
[crying]
The Great Being...
he's with us.
[mechanical whirring]
[rumbling]
[explosion]
‐ [stammers]
What just happened?
What was that?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
‐ [roaring]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
MOBEEDO: Withdraw at full speed.
Break orbital trajectory.
‐ I'm detecting a massive energy
spike on the planet's surface.
It's broke through
the atmosphere.
‐ [gasps]
♪ ♪
[all gasp]
[rumbling]
[explosion]
[whooshing]
‐ I don't believe it.
They're retreating.
‐ But why?
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
‐ The final Nodos...
‐ Huh?
‐ A human said to carry
the Heroic Tribe within himself.
At long last,
our search is over.
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA: The wisdom of the
stars has led us to our savior.
Next time on "Heroic Age,"
episode two.
The Forgotten Child.