YUTY: They simply haven't
the time to concern themselves
with so trivial a people.
For the sake of your own tribes,
you would do well
to remember this.
AGE: You can take me with you.
DHIANEILA: What do you mean?
‐ To your future.
‐ What could be simpler
for a being with your gifts?
Did not the countless tribes
you've driven to extinction
provide sufficient practice?
LECTY: The Golden Tribe,
could they have foreseen
this battle?
Could they have foreseen
our once proud race held hostage
by the contracts we hold
with the Silver Tribe?
What those contracts would come
to really mean?
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
[epic music]
WOMAN:
The rear secondary defense line
is about to be breached.
3.6 minutes until the enemy
breaks the line.
‐ Abandon the second line
and distribute those troops
to line one.
Current ship's course?
‐ Just as you ordered.
Standard evasive procedures
with an error margin of 0.5%.
‐ Good.
Now's our chance to shake 'em
before they swarm.
♪ ♪
‐ It's been a while
since we got to fight.
‐ Nasty.
Wow, that bug is gross!
Let's teach that thing a lesson.
‐ [grunts]
MAN: Iolaous!
‐ Just stay back.
Looks like Age can handle
the enemy Nodos all by himself.
If he takes care of them,
then we can deal
with these bugs.
♪ ♪
‐ Oh, Age.
‐ [growls]
[soft dramatic music]
YUTY: That's right.
[chuckles]
Very good.
It seems your opponent is just
a simple thug.
Capable only of brawling.
Karkinos,
instruct him
on the finer points
of destruction.
♪ ♪
‐ It's awful.
‐ It is,
and that's why
you must end it quickly.
Don't you remember
your contract?
If you break it,
you're entire tribe
will have to pay the price.
‐ After I destroy the ship,
you promise I don't have
to do anything else, right?
‐ [chuckles]
Do it.
‐ Artemia.
‐ [gasps]
Captain,
you must stop the ship now.
‐ [gasps]
Attention all hands,
prepare for a full stop.
‐ Sir, we've detected
a massive energy surge
and it's still growing.
DHIANEILA: It's another Nodos.
‐ Another one?
My God.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
‐ [roars]
‐ What that hell just happened?
‐ That energy field
suddenly appeared
directly in front
of our scheduled course, sir.
WOMAN: Shield limits
have been exceeded.
Captain, any closer
and we'll be incinerated.
‐ Could one monster really
stop us dead in our tracks?
Bee, calculate an escape route
immediately.
‐ Yes, right away.
♪ ♪
‐ Meet Artemia.
Even I shall keep a distance
from such a powerful creature.
MAN: We're detecting another
surge with the energy field.
It's even more powerful
than before.
MOBEEDO: It can't be.
Don't tell me
this is just the beginning
of it's attack.
MAN: All enemy troops
within range are now retreating.
‐ They're trying to escape
before they're destroyed.
Retreat now.
DHIANEILA: Captain,
prepare for active warp.
‐ Active warp?
But we don't have a course.
DHIANEILA:
I'll show you the way.
[epic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Active warp course received
via psycholine.
Begin analysis.
[electronic beeps]
‐ Hmm.
We must trust in her guidance.
Now, listen up.
All troops report back
to the "Argonaut,"
and prepare
to enter active warp.
Begin power up
of the astral turbine engine
and input course data.
‐ Power up procedure engaged.
Current energy level, 10%.
‐ Princess Dhianeila,
is Age still fighting
the enemy Nodos?
DHIANEILA: Yes.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[high‐pitch whirring]
YUTY: This is the end for you,
barbarians.
‐ Move it.
Let's go.
[epic music]
♪ ♪
WOMAN: Attention, all personnel
prepare to enter active warp.
I repeat.
All personnel prepare
to enter active warp
immediately.
MAN: Energy level at 70%.
Estimated time until
astral turbine is operation:
Two minutes.
‐ It's not our time.
BELLCROSS: [growling]
[roaring]
‐ [groans]
♪ ♪
[high‐pitch whirring]
[thrumming]
‐ Kill them.
‐ [gasps]
‐ We're at 90%
of the required charge.
‐ The enemy Nodos
has fired on us.
The beam'll reach the ship
in 14 seconds.
‐ [exhales sharply]
‐ And with this humanity dies.
♪ ♪
WOMAN: Five, four,
three, two, one.
♪ ♪
[siren blaring]
‐ [whimpers]
DHIANEILA: Bellcross?
♪ ♪
Bellcross!
‐ [growls]
[roars]
‐ You fool.
♪ ♪
‐ Please, Age,
come this way quickly.
Age?
Please, Age.
[thrum]
‐ [growls]
MAN: Charge complete.
MAN:
Dimensional ripper activated.
All sail functions initialized.
‐ Activating all
astral turbine engines.
‐ Active warp now!
♪ ♪
‐ No, wait.
‐ [roaring]
‐ No matter where you go,
we will find you .
Do not let them get away
next time, Mehitak.
‐ Now powering down.
All sequences are complete.
‐ A planet.
We're back on the Starway.
‐ Now reestablish our position.
Check the Starway coordinates.
[exhales]
Mission accomplished, Princess.
[indistinct chatter]
‐ You're exhausted, Iolaous.
You can't go on
fighting like this, you know?
Why don't you get some rest?
‐ I can't.
I completely abandoned him.
I just left him
for dead back there.
I guess I'm not much of
a soldier, am I?
‐ Listen to me.
You were just following
Princess Dhianeila's orders.
Its' not your fault.
[alarm blaring]
‐ [exhales sharply]
[epic music]
MAN: Ant hill detected
in planetary orbit.
♪ ♪
‐ Yet another war zone?
Course 2‐7‐5 at full speed.
‐ I'm picking up vessels
ahead of us.
♪ ♪
‐ [grunts]
‐ They've got us cornered.
Very well.
All hands to battle stations.
DHIANEILA: Hold on, Captain.
[high‐pitch whirring]
‐ They've fired
an energy weapon.
‐ But it's not
locked onto our ship.
It'll miss us.
‐ You're sure?
MAN: The remaining Bronze Tribe
is falling back.
‐ Allies?
MAN: That little display
just cost us 10%
of our remaining energy.
NILVAL: I would say that's
a small price to pay
in order to prove our solidarity
with our fellow humans.
Contact their ship.
MAN: Yes, ma'am.
‐ Master,
I'm receiving a transmission
from the fleet ahead
on the commander's line.
‐ Put 'em on.
Nilval Nephew here,
the acting commander
of the Azz‐Azoth fleet.
We're just confirming that your
ship is in fact the "Argonaut."
‐ Uh, it's really you.
‐ It's been a long time,
Mobeedo.
I had heard a rumor that
you were on assignment
searching
for the legendary Nodos,
but it looks to me like
you were ordered
to drift helplessly
around a war zone.
‐ Hmm, smart‐alecky as always.
Well, thank you
for saving us earlier.
‐ No need of thanks.
I'm just wondering
what the heck a vessel
that belongs to
the Yunos royal family is doing
visiting a backwoods world
like this.
Wait, let me guess?
They must have put you in charge
of finding a hiding place
for them.
DHIANEILA:
Please, allow me to explain.
[soft dramatic music]
‐ Your Highness, I would like
to introduce myself.
I am the current acting
commander of this fleet.
Nilval Nephew at your service.
‐ What do you mean
when you say "acting commander"?
NILVAL: This place is cursed
by destruction.
We have already lost
three of our commanders
and one acting commander
in the line of fire.
They have yet to send us
a new commander
or any of
our necessary supplies.
‐ I see.
‐ Princess, a war zone is
no place for the royal family.
‐ Commander Nilval, you have
done a great deed today.
Thanks to your generosity,
not only will the soldiers on my
ship live to fight another day,
so will the hope of all mankind.
‐ You mean it's true?
Princess...
[indistinct chatter]
‐ [exhales]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
‐ Looks like
he finally fell asleep.
[device beeps]
[chuckles]
So few soldiers
do so much of the fighting.
I can only imagine
how exhausting
these battles must be for you.
I wish there was some way
I could help.
‐ [grumbles softly]
♪ ♪
MOBEEDO: The Azz‐Azoth fleet.
At it's heart is
a large satellite fortress.
They're indeed
a force to be reckoned with.
Defense of this entire
planet system
used to be their responsibility,
but now they're lacking
essential supplies.
‐ You and the commander
of this fleet know each other?
‐ We were at
the officers academy together.
Though our relationship
isn't purely professional.
Apparently, she hasn't had
the best luck as of late,
but I assure you,
she is an excellent leader.
BEE NO BEE:
Receiving transmission
on commander's line.
MOBEEDO: Put it through.
‐ I've come to a decision
regarding our situation.
Because of this mission,
we have lost
more than 2/3 of our fleet,
and the site
we were sent to protect
is now a war‐torn wasteland.
Yet, we persevere.
We've continued to fight
with limited supplies
so that we may protect
the planetary systems
stretching behind us.
If we continue this mission,
we won't be able to give you
any further assistance.
‐ Mm.
NILVAL: However,
recently the enemy has begun
to withdraw from the area
for no apparent reason.
Now, to be honest,
I thought the Nodos was
nothing more than a fairy tale,
but it seems
the enemy didn't agree with me.
It withdrew most of its forces.
‐ The presence
of a Nodos could affect
not only one planet system,
but an entire galaxy.
NILVAL: Forgive me, Captain,
but I don't understand
why you would leave such
a powerful being so far behind.
‐ [exhales]
‐ Princess,
we found high energy surges
at your last known coordinates.
DHIANEILA:
Because the battle still rages.
Our valiant Nodos,
he will never surrender.
Still, it is certain the
Bronze Tribe we encountered has
since informed the Silver Tribe
of our presence.
They will appear
in this system very soon
bringing reinforcements
with them.
‐ Everything we've seen points
to the existence
of the legendary Nodos.
Therefore,
all operations pertaining to
the protection of
this dying planet shall cease,
and from this point on,
this fleet has a new mission.
We will dedicate
our meager resources to you.
‐ [sighs]
‐ Ah.
[sighs and laughter]
‐ We are most grateful.
Thank you, Commander Nilval.
‐ Ordinarily, I'd probably be
court‐martialed for this,
but as it stands,
I have the highest rank
in the fleet,
so a trial would be
out of the question.
We can devise
a defense strategy.
So you just concentrate
on getting out of here.
I regret that we can't offer you
repairs or supplies.
‐ There is nothing
for you to regret.
Words cannot express
the gratitude
all of us here feel
for the sacrifices you've made.
‐ I will pray for you,
Captain Mobeedo.
‐ Thank you, Nilval.
Mankind still has hope.
‐ Only now can I see that.
May the stars shine brightly
upon our hope.
‐ May the stars shine brightly
upon you.
[soft dramatic music]
NILVAL: Hope, huh?
I almost forgot that
such a thing
could even exist
in this universe.
MAN: Yes, ma'am.
‐ Inform all units.
We will now prepare to engage
the enemy at full force.
Now that we've made it this far,
why don't we see exactly what
this so‐called savior of mankind
can really do.
MOBEEDO: "Argonaut," move out.
♪ ♪
‐ Me and Bellcross will make
a path.
The "Argonaut" will make it out.
Even if it means that
we stay behind,
but you'll see us again.
‐ That path,
I will find it.
I promise.
Hold on.
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA:
Bellcross and Lernaea fight on,
and Nilval tries
to slow Artemia down.
Next time on "Heroic Age"...