[overlapping chatter]
MELEAGROS: An overwhelming
victory on Tauron.
Yes, the tide has most
definitely turned in our favor.
Let us seize the day
as conquerors!
Set a course for planet Codomos,
the Silver Tribe's home world.
We will descend
like a plague of locusts
upon every terminal world
within that system.
Let anyone who opposes us
feel our wrath.
‐ I don't understand
why they're all so optimistic,
but I suppose
ignorance is bliss.
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
MELEAGROS:
As per a unanimous agreement
reached by both the Council
and fleet headquarters,
the "Argonaut" will be entrusted
with a very special task.
To secure our victory,
you are to escort the Nodos
to the Alta system,
and attack planet Codomos
from a trajectory opposite that
of the Calydonian Fleet.
I believe this mission falls
within your capabilities.
Good luck to you all.
‐ That coward.
Just where does he get the nerve
sending us on a mission
like that.
He won't be happy
until all of us are dead.
‐ It simply reiterates
how terrified he is
of the "Argonaut."
He's paranoid the other fleets
will abandon him
and rally around the princess
instead.
‐ I think we should
disobey his orders.
After all,
he's only out for revenge.
MOBEEDO:
We really have no other choice.
‐ We should accept it.
The task may seem impossible,
but if we succeed,
we can reduce casualties
on both sides.
‐ Not only that,
but if we get there soon enough,
we might just head the princes
themselves off at the pass.
‐ It's worth trying.
‐ My friend, I'm afraid
circumstances force us
to ask that you take part
in yet another battle.
‐ That's all right.
I've got Iolaous.
‐ I may not be able
to hold a candle to you
as far as strength,
but I promise you
I'll do whatever I‐‐
‐ You have to come find me
if I get lost.
‐ [grunts]
Hey, what am I,
your babysitter?
[all laugh]
‐ Are you ready for this?
[soft music]
‐ Would it be all right with you
if I stayed on the ship?
‐ [gasps]
‐ If possible,
I would rather not fight.
I don't really know anything
about the Silver Tribe
that would be useful to you,
and you do already have Age.
Besides, if you lose,
my whole tribe will be destroyed
along with me.
I can't.
‐ Mm.
Then under my authority,
the Nodos of Pore
will not be required
to fight for us.
‐ [exhales]
I thank you.
‐ Mm.
‐ Right, now let's
get the "Argonaut" prepared
for our departure.
We have been given a mission,
people.
Whatever motives
may actually be behind it,
let's make sure they know
we're up to the job.
The fleet will be entering the
enemy's jurisdiction shortly.
This will be the last of our
little communiqués in real time.
‐ The last of the, huh?
All right then.
Try to say something clever.
‐ As usual,
we drew the short straw,
but it could be
a hell of a lot worse, right?
I mean, at the very least,
we're under the command
of the princess
and not those two idiot,
no‐account brother's of hers.
‐ [chuckles]
Well, that is something, yes.
My hope is that one day
we will all be
under Princess Dhianeila's
leadership.
‐ When the time is right,
we'll reorganize
all of the fleets,
but watch your back.
The fact that we've
come this far without a problem
can't bode well.
‐ Right.
You and your crew
stay safe out there.
‐ Mm.
Same to you.
‐ Checking up on your guys?
IOLAOUS: Everyone's recovering
very nicely.
Thanks for your help.
‐ Fortunately,
none of them were injured
too badly,
and I wasn't the only one
who healed them.
‐ The healing powers that
you and your crew possess
will be absolutely indispensible
in upcoming battles.
‐ That may be true.
It doesn't mean
you get to be reckless though.
Because sometimes my abilities
just aren't good enough.
♪ ♪
You've not‐‐
you've not forgotten our deal?
‐ I'm a man
who keeps his promises.
‐ I believe you.
‐ Mm.
♪ ♪
‐ [giggles]
‐ What will become of my tribe,
Age?
Or do you even know?
AGE: No, I don't.
MEHITAK: Oh.
‐ But my dad's did tell me this,
they said,
"The only way we can hope
to find the future is together."
That means you
and all the loved ones
you have back home on Pore.
[chuckles]
Everyone.
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA:
The acquisition of Codomos,
home world to the Silver Tribe.
Yet another of the 12 Labors
is about to be realized.
What was the Golden Tribe's
intention
behind alluding to the Labors
in their prophecy?
This war began long ago
before humankind had ever heard
of the Silver Tribe
or of Nodos.
What did they foresee?
Age, what sort of future
are we meant to find?
Please tell me.
‐ Senseless.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ [growls]
[roaring]
♪ ♪
ROM: Why?
What have we done?
Why did you abandon us?
‐ Why?
I feel great anguish
emanating from Rom Ror.
He has failed to intercept
the fifth Nodos.
He has also lost the way
to planet Olone.
It seems that
he has begun to blame himself
for the Golden Tribe's
departure.
Yet he refuses
to face the obvious.
‐ I don't understand.
What won't he face?
‐ His worries and his fears
of having to rule
in the Golden Tribe's stead
for eternity,
of why they left us,
and of his true intention
for wanting to eradicate
the Iron Tribe
before it's too late.
‐ So then, humankind will
target this planet after all?
‐ Probably,
and Rom Ror will send Yuty
to meet them.
She is a powerful creature,
In the heat of battle,
she may very well destroy
this world.
‐ Does he not see?
‐ The birthplace of a people
holds no significance
for our kind.
Unlike other tribes.
A sentiment such as this one
is considered weak.
I fear humankind may acquire
the Golden Tribe's lost power
through some innate means.
To which our own notions
of strength and weakness
are at a disadvantage.
LECTY: My contract stipulates
the Silver Tribe will acquire
that power, Your Grace.
PROME: One: only those who obey
the Silver Tribe in all things
shall be allowed to prosper.
Two:
You must subdue all who oppose
the Silver Tribe's rightful
stewardship of the universe.
Three: When the Silver Tribe's
Nodos faces grave danger,
you will use your full powers
to aid her.
Four: You will help demystify
the Golden Tribe's prophecy
and restore their lost power
to the Silver Tribe.
Five: That power you shall
protect to your utmost,
lest it be again forgotten.
Only their numbers have been
foretold in the prophecy.
I was the one who determined
the exact nature of your Labors,
and I, unfortunately,
cannot see the future.
‐ Perhaps
the Golden Tribe foresaw that
you would determine the contract
as you did.
Is it not possible?
Could they not have foreseen
the will of the tribe behind it,
Your Grace?
‐ Each Nodos is assigned
a specific Labor
regarding the Golden Tribe's
lost power.
Some necessarily
contradict one another,
or else point to
a very different future
than we might imagine or prefer.
‐ Contradictory?
How so?
Rom Ror determined
Karkinos' contract, did he not?
Karkinos is to be released
if the Golden Tribe's
lost power's ever found.
I do not see a conflict.
Not in his case.
‐ And yet, Yuty's contract
does indeed appear
to contradict your own.
You see, there is
a Labor decreed within it,
which declares that
you shall sacrifice your life,
not for her, but to keep
the Golden Tribe's power
from inadvertently
falling into the wrong hands.
So?
‐ So the future
cannot be determined
based on an interpretation
of our individual contracts.
But then why were they written
in such a way?
‐ They were intended to be
a safeguard against contingency.
We did not know what we wrought.
Lecty, my proud child of time,
it is my wish that
the Iron Tribe's war against us
will prove your own contract
to have been
the most far‐sighted of all.
‐ Yes, my teacher.
♪ ♪
PROME: Go now.
If you fall any further behind
Rom Ror and the others,
you will not be able
to catch up.
LECTY: Thank you.
YUTY:
Why don't you just spit it out?
Is he still alive?
Oh, you've come.
I was just asking Karkinos
if Mehitak is actually dead.
‐ Whether he survived or not,
he did exhaust all
of his strength in the fight.
His contract clearly states
that he is to be released.
‐ His Labors are not fulfilled
until he has sacrificed his life
for mine.
If he has indeed made the choice
to ignore his obligations to me,
then he must know his tribe
will pay the ultimate price.
‐ "You will subdue foes
of the Silver Tribe.
Even at the cost
of your very life."
That is one of Karkinos Labors.
Do you wish to see
that he fulfill it?
YUTY:
Our contracts are the mortar
by which the Silver Tribe
builds order out of chaos.
There's ultimately but one Labor
that need be fulfilled.
That which ensures their place
as rulers of this universe.
KARKINOS: Well said, Yuty.
Despite Mehitak's
rather untimely absence,
as per my contract,
I will remain by to protect you.
‐ And where's the comfort
in that for me?
I am the one who has to fight.
Besides,
you've already proven yourself,
haven't you?
WOMAN: The Federation fleet is
currently advancing
in full career
to seize all planets
within the Alta system
en route to Codomos.
Thus far, the strategy appears
to have proven out in our favor.
That is all for now.
‐ This is going too well.
‐ Surveillance unit ready
for deployment, Captain.
‐ The enemy may rear its head
at any time,
stay on your toes.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Let's check it out.
‐ I don't sense them.
I cannot feel the presence
of the Silver Tribe.
‐ There isn't any sign
of the enemy just yet.
It's quiet as a tomb out here.
‐ The princess
can't sense them either,
but this may be
some sort of trap,
so stay vigilant.
‐ I always do.
♪ ♪
Where's everyone gone?
[sensor beeping]
What the hell?
Hold your fire.
‐ So where have they all gone?
‐ We've only seen scavengers
from the other tribes.
There aren't any signs
of weapons or production.
All we've seen so far is
medicine and food.
The Silver Tribe's idea
of charity,
I suppose.
‐ So not even a defense unit?
What the hell is going on?
[exhales]
I smell a rat.
Surely they didn't just
abandon the place outright.
‐ And even if they had,
there's still the question
of their military.
They couldn't have possibly
relocated their entire force
in such a short span of time.
‐ Give Commander Nilval the word
to reorganize the fleet.
‐ Father‐‐
‐ But, sir,
we don't know
that this is an emergency.
‐ The situation here
is critical.
We've attempted to invade
the home world of a people
about whom we know
next to nothing.
‐ What are you trying to say?
‐ Look.
Just suppose for example,
they have no concept
of jurisdiction.
‐ Then individuals
would spread out
to any location they pleased.
Rarely running into members
of their own tribe.
They wouldn't understand
boundaries as we do.
‐ Yes, but if that
were truly the case,
how could they possibly
govern themselves?
Let alone ensure
the tribe's survival?
‐ And yet, that very well
may be their way.
Suppose they're advanced
telepathically.
They could keep track
of one another
across great distances
at the speed of thought.
Across the furthest reaches
of time and space.
‐ But that means...
‐ We've fallen prey
to our own ignorance.
They can attack us here
from any direction
that they please.
[soft dramatic music]
PROME: Only a chosen few
among the Iron Tribe
are able to leave the Starway.
♪ ♪
Perhaps only one.
Could the Golden Tribe
have intended
for the fifth Nodos
to protect this person?
What would have been the purpose
of allowing that ability
to flourish unchecked?
Unless it is indeed
the Iron Tribe
who is to discover
the lost power after all.
♪ ♪
ROM: Still these thoughts?
Do not permit them to hold sway.
The Iron Tribe
will never discover
the lost power
of the Golden Tribe.
They will perish.
‐ That's it.
ANEASHA: What's the matter?
‐ I must attempt
to speak with them.
‐ Why would you think
making contact with the enemy
is a good idea?
‐ I wish
to communicate with them
in order to obtain
their relative position.
‐ Your Highness, you can't.
What about
their telepathic abilities?
You would be enabling them.
It would allow them to hone in
on our position instantaneously.
‐ I know,
but this is the only way
to avoid a full‐blown crisis.
‐ I understand.
Initiate launching sequence.
Prepare for immediate departure.
MAN:
Spatiotemporal gap successful.
Warping sequence complete.
‐ Brother,
this means we've conquered
a record number
of terminal planets
in the Alta system.
‐ Naturally, Atalantes.
After all, the fleet is
being led by yours truly.
Sally forth.
The Silver Tribe is no longer
to be feared.
MAN: Enemy fleet's moving in.
‐ You're wrong.
We just conquered
all the terminal planets.
‐ They're approaching
from another sector.
They didn't pass through
any terminal planets.
‐ Damn it.
Those bastards have
snuck up on us!
[epic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Attack.
MAN: Enemy fleets are
blocking our line of retreat
through Sector 748.
‐ [grunts]
Don't just stand there.
‐ Change course right now!
Get us out of here!
♪ ♪
‐ [scoffs]
It's Mobeedo.
What?
Reorganize the fleet?
MAN: Emergency communication
coming through.
The enemy has arrived.
The flagship fleet is having
to break formation
in order to engage them.
‐ They what?
[exhales sharply]
‐ Enemy ships are approaching
from Sector 196
at incredibly high speeds,
Commander.
‐ Bastards!
How did they get the drop on us?
We should have seen them
before now.
What happened?
MAN: More enemy fleets
bearing down on our position.
‐ They've been lying
in ambush the whole time
waiting patiently
for the right moment
to spring
their perfect little trap on us.
Of course, Mobeedo had
to have seen this coming.
‐ She's here.
[gasps]
DHIANEILA: You alone shadow
the "Argonaut's" course.
Why?
PHAETHO: [breathing shakily]
DHIANEILA:
Have you been ordered to do so?
[soft suspenseful music]
What about your family?
Your home?
♪ ♪
Is there anything other than
this chase that defines you?
‐ Stop it.
‐ The Iron Tribe is
currently trying
to speak with us
through Phaetho.
‐ Mm.
‐ [exhales sharply]
I feel a great many minds
converging within you.
Do you never enjoy
a moment's peace
from the collective psyche
of your tribe?
‐ [gasps]
‐ Such a vile creature
shall not rule in our stead.
It will not happen.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
‐ Do not forget
your obligations.
♪ ♪
[chuckles softly]
PHAETHO:
I will not succumb to this.
[grunts]
♪ ♪
‐ [exhales]
‐ Die.
All of you die!
‐ All right, let's do this.
‐ [growls]
‐ Oh, no.
‐ Kill them, Yuty.
Show them no mercy.
[epic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Now Kervius.
No mercy.
♪ ♪
‐ [growls]
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA:
The terrifying power of Kervius
at last reveals itself
threatening to destroy
all humankind.
Next time on "Heroic Age"...