[ominous music]
♪ ♪
WOMAN: Status check complete.
Fleet formation is stable.
MAN: Ship by ship diagnostics
detect no abnormalities.
MAN: Continue transit
in defensive formation.
BEE NO BEE: Master, the Althaia
has sent us the final draft
of the mission detail
for the invasion of Tauron.
MOBEEDO: Open it.
WOMAN: Orders are being sent
to all commanding officers.
Completed operational‐‐
‐ What do they mean,
"take over"?
‐ A takeover is
military terminology
for the forcible acquisition
of resources.
‐ Yes, I know what it means.
Taking over a terminal planet
for the invasion?
Bee, prepare to send a personal
message to the council.
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
‐ [grunts]
For Mehitak.
‐ Why?
‐ It's really delicious.
‐ Yeah, that's right,
and Age grew it himself.
‐ [chuckles]
‐ Members of the Pore Tribe
never consume anything
that has life.
‐ That's so sweet.
‐ Wait a minute,
then what do you guys eat?
BOTH: Huh?
‐ Uh.
‐ [gulps]
We can eat anything
that doesn't have life.
BOTH: Ugh.
‐ [chuckles]
Ah‐‐oh.
[groans]
[spits]
‐ It's like you're staring
at your girlfriend.
‐ This unit means more to me
than that.
‐ I hope your girlfriend
didn't hear that.
‐ I don't have one.
‐ Hmm.
‐ What?
‐ Oh, nothing.
Nothing at all.
‐ Hmm.
‐ I can't believe it.
We had to leave
right after we found
what we were searching for.
I wish I could've walked
on the Earth too.
‐ We had no choice but to leave.
There was no guarantee
that the Earth was
really safe for us.
‐ It must be nice.
I suppose that I could've seen
our sacred birth place
if I had the ability
to teleport.
The blue planet,
homeland of all humanity.
‐ I'm sure you'll have
the chance to see it someday.
‐ And when will that day come?
‐ As soon as we can
end this war.
You'll see it.
I'll take you there myself.
We can visit the home planet
together.
‐ You mean that?
Because it sounds like
you made a promise.
‐ [grunts]
‐ Don't worry,
I'm not going to hold you to it.
Besides, you're just
going to forget all about it
as soon as the war starts.
‐ You don't know me at all,
do you?
A Yunos Knight is
as good as his word.
On my honor,
I promise you
that when this is all over,
we'll visit Earth.
‐ [giggles]
That sounds fantastic.
I can't wait.
[metal screeching]
‐ [gasps]
[both cheering]
‐ Uh.
‐ Whoa.
He ate the whole panel.
‐ It tasted bitter.
‐ Do it again.
Ooh, do it again!
Here, does this one
taste okay?
‐ How bizarre.
‐ Will you two quit feeding
my armor to that thing?
‐ Two of the other Nodos were
forced to fight us.
Their tribes have been
taken hostage,
which means we may have
a decisive strategic advantage.
‐ Do you think that if we were
to help free their tribes
these Nodos would
join our cause?
‐ Judging from how
the Pores Nodos
has been behaving,
I would say it's very possible.
I just wish we had some way
to contact those two Nodos
so we could suggest
such an arrangement.
‐ According to the contract
that assigned their labors,
it never stipulates
that refusal to perform them
will lead
to the extinction
of their tribe.
‐ That's true.
‐ Instead, it promises
prosperity for submission.
Mehitak of Pore abhors violence.
That is why he's aligned himself
with us.
‐ Do you believe the other two
Nodos actually desire to fight
on the side of the Silver Tribe,
Your Majesty?
‐ I just don't know.
The truth of this situation is
we really don't know anything.
Wouldn't you agree that we are
as ignorant as ever, Captain?
‐ I'm not sure I understand.
DHIANEILA:
Throughout the ages,
our enemy has aided
countless tribes.
They've devoted
their entire existence
to spreading enlightenment
across the universe.
My question is why.
Why do they wish to destroy
mankind and mankind alone?
We chose to remain uninformed
of our enemy's
ideological values
and committed ourselves
to a crusade we don't understand
against an adversary
we know nothing about.
The more I learn about Mehitak
and his deep respect for life,
the more I become concerned
about that.
‐ Yes, you're right.
Now I see.
I've been at way so long,
I never once thought
to question it.
It seems impossible.
Our two peoples have
never even spoken.
[beeps]
‐ We've detected
a formation of fleets
on course
to the terminal planet.
Such a formation might interfere
with terminal operations.
‐ I sense a strong wave
of hostility
from the planet Nessus.
Something is happening.
‐ I'd be willing to bet
those idiotic brothers of yours
are behind this.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ So, are you telling me that
you refuse to cooperate with us?
‐ Make no mistake, we will
protect our terminal planet
from this unprecedented act
of aggression.
That means we are prepared
to fight the Iron Tribe
to the very end.
Is that clear?
‐ The neutral status
of the terminal planet
is a fundamental tenet
of star way navigation.
I can assure you,
any infraction of that
will result in retaliation
from every tribe
in the universe.
‐ Am I going to have to
spell it out for you?
We are currently in possession
of a Nodos.
‐ Your military strength is
irrelevant to us.
We will never surrender.
‐ What should we do now,
big brother?
‐ We can't proceed
with our invasion
unless the terminal planet
is under our control.
If these cretins interfere,
then I'm afraid
the only course of action
we'll have to take
is their eradication.
‐ Yes.
All fleets now,
prepare to attack!
♪ ♪
‐ [shudders]
How could my brothers do this?
WOMAN: Leading fleets are now
positioned to fire main cannons.
‐ Energy energy conduction
response is now increasing.
‐ The attack satellite
from the planet Nessus
is now fully operational.
WOMAN: All frontline fleets
from the Federation
are now within range
of the attack satellite.
‐ Those imbeciles dragged us
into a war
before we could even come close
to our enemy.
Raise the shields and evacuate
the operational area.
Whatever happens,
don't initiate the attack.
DHIANEILA: Captain?
‐ Princess Dhianeila.
DHIANEILA: Move the ship
to these coordinates.
‐ Receiving data
via the psycholine.
Analyzing spatial location.
‐ [scoffs]
She's simply amazing.
I'm not sure how she does it,
but she always comes through.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[machine whirring]
‐ [chuckles]
‐ All fleets fire at will.
DHIANEILA:
Stop this now!
‐ [groans]
No, Dhianeila.
‐ Gravity shock detected.
‐ We're picking up
a large vessel
coming out of warp.
‐ What did you say?
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
‐ Is that‐‐
DHIANEILA:
Citizens of the planet Nessus.
‐ Uh‐‐
Is it really you?
The one who arrived
without the path to the starway.
‐ I've come to humbly implore
you to quiet your anger.
‐ Those Argonaut bastards,
how dare they?
‐ No, they've interfered
with our holy war!
[regal music]
♪ ♪
[people murmuring]
‐ It's him, the Nodos.
DHIANEILA: Brothers,
you must not start
a war with these people.
Such a decision would
put us at odds
with every other tribe
in the universe.
‐ [grumbling]
[all gasping]
‐ The Iron Tribe's Nodos
is here.
‐ We did not come
to wage war on you.
I can assure you,
we have no desire
to seize control
of your planet.
Please, I'm asking you
to let us agree
upon a peaceful cooperation.
‐ Very well.
However, we shall only agree
to allow passage
for those travelers who pay
the appropriate toll.
The price being
a harmonious respect
for my planet and its people.
This fee is not up for debate.
‐ Of course not, General.
‐ A message from the Council.
We are to immediately cease
the hostile takeover
of the terminal planet
and comply
with all their resource demands.
‐ Did you say a message
from the Council?
Who contacted them?
‐ It was those fools onboard
the "Argonaut," of course.
Who else would do such a thing?
‐ They're using the Nodos
as a shield.
What a devious thing to do.
What do we do now,
big brother?
At this rate,
our scheming little sister
will command the entire fleet!
‐ She has become
incredibly arrogant,
and I believe that was
her biggest blunder.
‐ Uh‐huh.
‐ There is no doubt in my mind
that she was trying to seize
control of the fleet,
but I refuse
to let that happen.
From now on,
Dhianeila will handle
all the troublesome negotiations
with terminal planets,
so that we can proceed
with our plans.
‐ I see.
Basically, Dhianeila will
have to work through every issue
concerning
the fleet's navigation.
Meanwhile,
we will only have to focus
on the war at hand.
‐ You see, Atalantes,
there's always a way
to make a troublemaker useful.
‐ You're brilliant, brother.
Now, why don't we order
the whole fleet
to charge forward?
‐ Hmm.
‐ Now they're having all
their vessels charge forward,
completely ignoring
the supply plan.
Never in my life
have I encountered
anyone as predictable
as they are.
‐ At the current rate,
the leading fleet will encounter
mission inhibiting
transit problems in 200 hours.
‐ I'll make sure
to notify Nilval
since she's expected
to meet up with them.
I can't begin to tell you
how many times I've wished
the vacuum of space would come
claim those two princes.
[soft music]
‐ Hello, Age.
I realize I've put you
in a very difficult position,
and for that I'm sorry.
‐ Everyone's angry,
aren't they?
‐ Their anger grows
from the fear of the enemy
they're about to face.
Bronze Tribe was the first
intruder from another world
that humankind ever fought.
The terrible wounds
from that experience
turned into scars of fear
and of anger.
‐ But they have Dhianeila.
I'm not frightened.
Dhianeila's here now.
‐ [groans]
Yes, I am,
and so are you, Age.
‐ Hmm.
[magical music]
♪ ♪
ROM ROR: The Iron Tribe is
aggressively pursuing war.
What is it that they seek
on the planet Tauron?
We desire to hear Prome O's
assessment of this situation.
‐ The Iron Tribe is being
completely dominated
by their own emotions,
Rom Ror.
I can say with total and
utter certainty that there are
no magnificent powers
to be found on that planet.
‐ Simply emotions.
Why are you so steadfast
in your beliefs
about the Iron Tribe and
the Golden Tribe?
PROME O: I have devoted
a great deal of thought
to the possibility
that the Iron Tribe
will discover the lost power
of the Golden Tribe,
and I do not wish for anymore
planets to be destroyed
by raging battles of Nodos.
ROM ROR: I propose
we send our Nodos
before the Iron Tribe's Nodos
has a chance
to destroy those planets.
‐ But if we should send Yuty
an inconceivable devastation
will be released.
ROM ROR: If we do not loose
this terrible power
the Iron Tribe will remain
forever unchecked.
We must destroy
or be destroyed.
‐ Do you mean to tell me
that you aren't
the least bit puzzled
by the fact that the Iron Tribe
is now preparing to attack
the planet Tauron?
‐ It seems clear enough to me
that this attack
must be revenge.
I can sympathize with that.
‐ Revenge.
Do you think it's possible
the Lost Tribe exists on Tauron?
‐ [scoffs] That's not
what this is about.
The only objective they have
is to cause pain,
the pain of being robbed
of what's most important.
‐ What do you mean,
"most important"?
‐ You must look inside yourself
for that, Yuty.
Everyone must.
‐ Right, power and prosperity
are important,
and so is my duty.
I shall execute my labors
and lead you to glory.
What else could there be?
[soft music]
♪ ♪
‐ There is so much more.
I would never sacrifice
this body or soul
merely in service
of my labors.
‐ But you would
for what's most important.
‐ That's correct.
‐ I do not understand this.
Do you think I ever will?
‐ All I've done is explain
a personal opinion.
Of course, it isn't a necessity
for you to understand any of it.
‐ Then I won't try anymore.
And by the way,
don't forget that you possess
the power of Lernaea.
It wouldn't be possible
for you to sacrifice your body,
even if you wanted to.
You regenerate
faster than all of us.
‐ I hope that'll be enough.
‐ You won't die.
I won't let you.
‐ I shall keep that in mind.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[military music]
MAN: Ant hills are moving in.
Their teleportation has exceeded
all estimates, sir.
‐ Calm down,
it'll be fine.
‐ I don't care
what they've got.
We're not backing down.
Maintain forward charge!
‐ New report
from the Calydonian Fleet.
They are expanding
the combat theater
alongside the Azz‐Azoth Fleet.
All ancillary fleets are
falling into formation.
‐ A simple charge forward
with no strategy.
Well, with Nilval in charge
of the fleet's supplies
we should have
more than adequate resources.
That should at least help.
It has given the fleet
a necessary boost,
but will that be enough?
Switch to warp positions.
We will be on the front line
of the battle in 20 hours.
[military music]
♪ ♪
[alarm blaring]
IOLAOUS: Age?
‐ Hello.
You're late, Iolaous.
‐ What are you doing up there?
‐ Oh, I can get in the battle
much quicker this way.
‐ Uh‐‐
All right, Age, listen up.
I have no intention
of letting you fight alone,
no matter how powerful you are.
Are we clear on that?
No matter what happens
out there,
I'll be fighting
right beside you.
‐ Hmm. If I get lost
out there,
you be sure to bring me back,
okay, Iolaous?
‐ I give you my word.
[ethereal music]
♪ ♪
‐ What is most important?
‐ You must look inside yourself
for that, Yuty.
Everyone must.
[inaudible]
‐ The time has come, Yuty.
We are sending you forth...
into battle.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
You must now destroy
the fifth Nodos.
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
WOMAN: Humanity invades
the mother planet
of the Bronze Tribe,
Planet Tauron.
Next time on "Heroic Age,"
episode 18, The Victorious Day.