[overlapping chatter]
[lasers zapping]
‐ Go after them!
‐ Leave us alone!
Ahh!
Augh!
‐ [roars]
‐ What the hell?
[loud explosion]
DHIANEILA: There was something
different about him.
I could sense it.
‐ Uh.
‐ [gasps]
‐ [roars]
‐ Heh, your power is no match
for the Silver Tribe's Nodos.
‐ Kervius is here.
Yuty is going to fight.
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
MAN: The enemy line is starting
to fall back.
‐ Our military might naturally
terrifies them.
MAN: High‐energy source
detected.
It's the Nodos.
‐ [gulps]
ATALANTES: Shoot it down!
Meleagros, let me handle this.
MAN: It's warping the atmosphere
around it
so to form some kind of
protective barrier.
‐ Oh, no.
What do we do now?
‐ We must fire the main cannons.
‐ But the energy that would
take,
we dare not exhaust it in one
fell swoop, do we?
‐ Our main cannons drive enough
force to blow an entire world
to kingdom come.
Surely they can take out a
single Nodos.
Are we or are we not in this
fight to win?
‐ Okay, then, just order the
fleets to act as our shield
while we divert power.
‐ Yes, sir.
Prepare the cannons.
‐ Yes, sir, right away.
MAN: Deploying cannon barrels to
to firing position.
Activating antiparticle
accelerators 1 through 12.
No errors detected in
corresponding sensors.
MAN: Gravity prisms forming.
Optimal conduction confirmed.
MAN: Amplifiers at the ready.
ATALANTES: Order all fleets in
this quadrant to form a
defensive line around the
"Althaea" immediately.
MAN: The acceleration missile is
loaded with explosive charge.
‐ Monster.
We're not afraid of you.
MAN: Charging complete.
Main cannons are at the ready.
‐ Fire.
[loud explosion]
MAN: Confirmed. Direct hit.
MELEAGROS: Did we kill it?
MAN: High‐level gravity
fluctuation.
The enemy Nodos is still alive.
Skeel fleet has been destroyed.
ATALANTES: No.
This is impossible.
LECTY: The dark matter vortex,
a singularity from whence not
even the vicissitudes of time
itself can escape.
Everything in its path will be
consumed and desiccated
beyond all possible dimension.
Behold the Heroic Tribe's most
dreadful power.
‐ Nocture and Sazare,
confirm destruction as well.
‐ The enemy Nodos is
manipulating
a singularity similar to a load
sphere.
It's creating a black hole.
‐ The other fleets are
requesting orders, sir.
If the attack continues at this
rate,
our entire battalion will be
obliterated within minutes.
‐ No.
What do we do?
‐ We have no choice but to...
MAN: The other fleets are
awaiting instructions.
‐ Run away.
MAN: Carry on, fleets, to right
formation.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ [breathing heavily]
‐ We were so close.
‐ [roars]
DHIANEILA: [sobbing]
[gasps]
Age, you have to‐‐
you have to try and save them,
please,
as many lives as possible.
MEHITAK: Let's go.
‐ But Mehitak...
‐ Age says you will find the
path.
You will be the one to lead us
all to the future,
to a place where all the tribes
can live in peace.
And if my fighting along beside
you will secure that hope,
it is a small price to pay.
Besides, Artemia is faster than
Bellcross.
IOLAOUS: What are you doing?
Now is not the time to lose your
focus.
‐ It's just that Age is gone.
IOLAOUS: What?
‐ Iolaous, fall back now.
The enemy Nodos has been
completely laying waste
to the Flagship fleet.
‐ Their forces are closing in on
us.
I don't know how we will escape
them.
♪ ♪
‐ Augh!
‐ This is it!
MAN: We're under attack with no
line of retreat.
Please send backup.
MAN: We're completely
surrounded.
Our defenses are breaking down.
MAN: Repeat: send backup.
‐ We've now retrieved all the
organ units, master.
‐ Change course, Bee.
We'll follow Bellcross back to
the Calydonian Fleet
and try to save who we can.
They're picking us off out there
like it was nothing.
The only reason the "Argonaut"
is not in the same predicament
is because we left the Starway.
There was no base for us to
attack in the first place.
Now we're all just sitting
ducks.
It's over.
We're finished.
WOMAN: An energy reading
believed to be that of
the enemy Nodos has been
confirmed
near the Calydonian Fleet.
MAN: It appears that all rear
fleets have been engaged
by the enemy as well.
‐ Well, it appears they've
finally outsmarted us.
‐ I don't see the point in
whining about it.
Let's continue to secure
communication with all fleets.
This battle isn't finished just
yet.
‐ Yes, ma'am.
‐ Control, have we received any
word from the "Argonaut"?
WOMAN: Nothing yet.
NILVAL: Come on.
Where's our guiding star?
DHIANEILA: Where are you?
Show me.
PROME O: All five Nodos are
coming together,
as it was foretold in the
prophecy.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Hard to starboard!
Get the hell away from that
thing now!
♪ ♪
‐ Withdraw, damn it!
Break away from the fleet!
MAN: 32% of the fleet has been
destroyed.
25% of the fleet is unable to
continue fighting.
MAN: The enemy is bearing down
on us from every direction.
‐ What now, Atalantes?
‐ Keep formation.
Just hold the line.
‐ The singularity is
approaching.
‐ [gasping]
‐ We're right in its path.
ATALANTES: Ahh!
MELEAGROS: Where are you going?
‐ What's going on?
‐ It can't be.
♪ ♪
ALL: Augh!
‐ [roars]
‐ Impossible.
He can block even Kervius'
power.
‐ [groaning]
MAN: The singularity has
disappeared.
MELEAGROS: That's our Nodos.
ATALANTES: Isn't that the Silver
Tribe's beast he defeated
at the battle of Mars?
What is it doing here?
It looks as though he's been
compelled to serve us
at the behest of his better.
Excellent.
‐ Why did he come back here?
‐ This is the first time that
I've ever seen Mehitak
go willingly enter battle.
I must go.
LECTY: Wait, please.
‐ I am not going to kill him.
I plan only to put him out of
harm's way.
For the time being, remain here.
One of us should be ready to
intervene
in case the other should succumb
to the madness.
I believe Erymanthos is far
better suited to that task
than is Lernaea.
Wouldn't you agree?
‐ Are you really prepared to
sacrifice your life
in order to fulfill your
contract?
‐ I have abandoned my own tribe
to protect Yuty.
What else do I have now?
I shall see this through to the
bitter end,
as will we all.
‐ Karkinos.
‐ Brother, we have to get out of
here now.
We don't stand a chance if we
get caught in the crossfire
between those two.
‐ Very well.
Order the fleets to begin
pulling back immediately.
We'll let our Nodos handle this
fight on our own.
MAN: Yes, sir.
Order all remaining fleets to
withdraw at once.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ [roars]
BOTH: [roaring]
LECTY: What is it that compels
you to fight Mehitak?
Why only now?
PROME O: The five Nodos
converge.
If this encounter genuinely
represents the will
of the Golden Tribe,
then what could they have
foreseen for us?
MAN: The Golden Tribe's will is
irrelevant.
We determine the future,
and this day the future will see
humankind finally destroyed
along with their precious Nodos.
MAN: Attention, all ships...
[overlapping chatter]
‐ Move us out.
We're going to get caught in the
crossfire.
‐ What are you waiting for?
Accelerate, you moron.
‐ We can't accelerate.
The engines are still trying to
recover power
diverted to the main cannons.
‐ Stop arguing.
Just find some way to make it
happen.
♪ ♪
‐ [roars]
‐ Why do you insist on fighting
the two of them alone?
I'm right here.
LECTY: Just as I thought.
You two will not let Karkinos
sacrifice himself.
She is loathe to see his
obligations fulfilled.
‐ [roars]
If one of them succumbs to the
frenzy,
what am I meant to do?
Why, Erymanthos?
Could it be the inconsistencies
in our labors
somehow mask a deeper
continuity?
Is my purpose here different?
[alarms blaring]
WOMAN: High‐level spatiotemporal
shift detected.
MAN: The Flagship fleet is
offline.
All vital signs have gone flat.
‐ They didn't have enough time
to get out of the way.
The entire fleet is gone.
‐ Why did those two idiots have
to go
and get themselves shot down?
The whole damn battalion will
fall like a house of cards
when word of this gets out.
Assign a rendezvous point and
advise
all remaining fleets
to pull out.
The invasion of Codomos was a
failure.
Withdraw immediately.
Our priority now is survival.
WOMAN: A message from the
Azz‐Azoth fleet:
the Flagship fleet is confirmed
destroyed.
All remaining ships are to
retreat and rendezvous
at sector 904.
MOBEEDO: Any word on Bellcross?
WOMAN: No, sir.
BEE NO BEE: Should we head for
the rendezvous point, master?
‐ Chart a course for the nearest
battle line.
We'll open an escape route for
any ships left behind.
‐ Right away, master.
‐ It's over.
Now let's focus on saving
whomever we can.
DHIANEILA: The Flagship fleet
was completely wiped out.
No.
‐ He's still out there.
DHIANEILA: Yes.
Captain.
‐ What is it, princess?
What have you found?
DHIANEILA: I sense a member of
the Silver Tribe
who's not hostile toward us.
We must try to enlist their help
in forming some kind of truce.
‐ Some kind of truce?
But surely we're well beyond
that point now.
DHIANEILA: Then learning why
this person does not share
in the other's hatred may be our
only hope.
‐ But, princess...
DHIANEILA: Set a course for
planet Codomos.
MOBEEDO: We'll be playing right
into their hands.
DHIANEILA: I'm sorry.
There is no other way.
‐ Ever the courageous leader,
our princess simply won't
take no for an answer,
will she?
Hm.
Prepare to ship out.
We're headed back to planet
Codomos.
Get a message to the fleets.
Tell them anyone willing and
able to come along
is welcome to do so.
The princess might just have
found a way out of this
whole bloody mess before any
more lives are lost.
BEE NO BEE: Right away, master.
MOBEEDO: Codomos, one minute a
desiccated hull,
the next a theater of war,
and yet our best best for a
cease‐fire.
You have to appreciate the
irony.
‐ [roars]
LECTY: Prome O spoke of
contingencies,
but what purpose would it serve
for our contracts to bear
so many contradictions?
Why would the Golden Tribe leave
us with a prophecy
which unearths more enigmas than
it dispels?
Which tribe is meant to survive,
Silver or Iron?
‐ [roars]
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
WOMAN: Words between reluctant
enemies breed hope
for a chance at reconciliation.
Next time on "Heroic Age"...