DHIANEILA: We have faith in
the Golden Tribe's prophecy
of the fifth Nodos.
And at last we have the power
to resist our annihilation
by the Silver Tribe.
Mark my words, Excellency,
we shall never give in.
‐ Are you threatening
to attack us
if we don't approve
your departure?
‐ We will depart the moment
that we are ready.
[somber string music]
♪ ♪
‐ I'm here to meet the fifth.
My name is Karkinos.
‐ I'm Age.
‐ Come with me, Age.
‐ My dad told me one, two,
three, four‐‐
all four of them need
to be destroyed.
♪ ♪
[pulsing]
DHIANEILA: The Silver Tribe
is willing to destroy
the entire planet to get to us.
♪ ♪
MAN: They're going to
slaughter us all.
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA: Your Excellency.
MAN: Princess?
DHIANEILA: They are planning
to target the spaceport.
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
MAN: The Titarros' ship
isn't following us.
MOBEEDO: Good.
Now increase speed as we
shift orbital trajectory.
Try to keep the enemy
at our back
and concentrate all
of our firepower
on the starboard side.
[doors hissing]
Deploy oboronas!
[blasting]
[thunderous explosions]
MAN: The Bronze Fleet has
deployed two squadrons, sir‐‐
one heading towards
the "Argonaut,"
one towards the Titarros
spaceport.
MOBEEDO: Damn it,
I was afraid of this.
They're targeting the spaceport
to try and obstruct
our acceleration path.
We've effectively compromised
Titarros' neutrality.
We can't just leave them
to face the music alone.
Lure as many enemy ships away
from the spaceport as you can,
and do your best
to shake off pursuers.
DHIANEILA:
I'm counting on you, Captain.
MAN: Princess Dhianeila has
been entrusted with the future
of the human race.
Surrender is simply not
an option for her at this point.
To think she was willing
to tarnish her reputation
to avoid seeing this planet
become a battleground.
That remarkable young woman
was actually trying
to spare us.
‐ Be that as it may,
we owe the Silver Tribe
for being able to move
among the stars
in the first place.
We've essentially bitten
the hand that feeds us
Still...
[rumbling]
We can't sit idly by while our
home planet is being destroyed.
‐ You're absolutely right.
Prepare to deploy Ikaros One
while we still have a chance
at defending ourselves.
Order all ground troops
to ready themselves
for sky battle immediately.
‐ And the Ikaros Two.
‐ Have the vessel relocate it.
Deportments R‐98, S‐26.
[energy surging]
MAN: Ikaros One, commencing
shift in trajectory
to defensive line.
MAN:
Spaceport fleet at the ready.
[engines humming]
[tense orchestral music]
♪ ♪
MAN: Oboronas in position.
Missiles prepared for launch.
‐ Engage the enemy.
[missiles blasting]
‐ Now!
Fire at will, gentlemen!
[missiles blasting]
♪ ♪
[powerful blast]
DHIANEILA: Age, who is this man
you fight with such virulence?
And why?
[glass shattering]
[thrilling music]
‐ [shouts]
[grunts]
Ugh!
[smash]
♪ ♪
‐ [screaming]
[whimpers]
♪ ♪
‐ Hey! Stop it right now.
We have to get back
to the "Argonaut."
AGE: I can't.
You'll have to leave without me.
‐ What do you mean?
‐ Don't worry.
I'll come back.
I really kind of like
the "Argonaut."
♪ ♪
[grunts]
DHIANEILA: Strange.
I sense no ill will in the one
with whom Age struggles.
‐ But what could his intentions
possibly be?
DHIANEILA: Perhaps he
has not come to fight.
ANEASHA: Then what is
he here for?
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
MAN: The enemy is approaching,
Captain.
They're within range
of the strike zone.
MOBEEDO:
Begin withdrawing oboronas.
Deploy units Organ and Vritarif.
Get ready to engage these
bastards in close‐range combat.
♪ ♪
[engines blasting]
Acceleration status?
The "Argonaut"'s maximum
velocity will be reached
within ten minutes, Master.
‐ So what's the outlook
‐ Once we've cleared
the planet's
gravitational sphere,
the enemy is likely to withdraw
from their offensive against
the Titarros spaceport
and focus all squadrons
in pursuit of us.
‐ If we survive the next
ten minutes,
we might make it out alive.
WOMAN: Dandelion Unit ready
to launch from Port 47.
Orchid Unit fully deployed.
[electronic buzz]
‐ Where in the hell is Age?
‐ I had to leave without him.
‐ You left without him?!
‐ That's right.
Moving out now.
Got to go.
WOMAN: Activating rapid
launchers three, five and eight.
AGE: Don't worry.
I'll come back.
I really kind of like
the "Argonaut."
IOLAOUS:
Was I a fool to take that
little monkey's word for it?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[shattering]
[heavy smash]
[crumbling, cracking]
♪ ♪
[hissing]
YUTY: Why do you
hesitate, Karkinos?
The very planet is yours
to destroy,
if you so choose.
♪ ♪
‐ I've yet to use that power
on the Nodos.
I'm curious.
Is there a numbness?
‐ Are you going
to kill this world?
‐ Come with me, Age.
‐ I am Lernaea.
Thus is spoken the name
of the heroic tribe
possessed within me.
‐ Bellcross.
‐ I had hoped to persuade you
without resorting to a full
transformation.
[wind howling]
‐ [groans] Not until we're
off the surface, Bellcross.
[rumbling]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
‐ [roaring]
DHIANEILA: A Nodos...
‐ [deep growl]
[soft wind rustling]
[creaking]
[heavy smash]
[thrilling music]
♪ ♪
[powerful blast]
MOBEEDO: Princess!
We're picking up
atmospheric readings
that suggest Bellcross's powers
virtually doubled!
DHIANEILA:
A second Nodos is present.
‐ You mean to tell me there
are two of them down there?!
♪ ♪
[vapor hissing]
‐ That the Silver Tribe
would use such a creature!
‐ They intend
to annihilate us all.
♪ ♪
YUTA: Why does Karkinos
insist on holding back?
MEHITAKE:
Because that world would perish
under the full brunt
of his strength.
LECTY: He is biding his time
to scrutinize the nature
of the fifth.
DHIANEILA: Don't be absurd.
The fifth is our enemy.
He and that entire planet
should be eradicated
without a thought.
♪ ♪
‐ I know you're in pain.
But you will live
through this.
MAN: Vital defenses
disabled by 5.8%.
Organ Unit still
holding the line.
MOBEEDO: Have the pilots focus
their ships towards the stern.
Get all spare hands
to back them up
with close‐range artillery.
Over my dead body will
a few measly anthills
manage to bring down
the "Argonaut."
‐ Red alert!
Gravity shock detected!
Distance at 967.
‐ By the gods!
‐ [roaring]
‐ Evasive action!
Get under the damn thing!
WOMAN: There's no time.
We're going to crash!
‐ All hands,
brace for impact, now!
♪ ♪
[powerful blast]
[energy surging]
[roaring]
[groaning]
[all whimpering]
[crumbling]
[shattering]
‐ This is unbelievable.
‐ Confirm all system stats.
‐ Of course, Master.
MOBEEDO:
The aftershock alone was enough
to rattle the "Argonaut"
like a tin can.
‐ Incredible.
Can no one stand against
the wrath of a Nodos?
[slow dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ [roaring]
MOBEEDO: Bellcross obliterated
the anthill.
Every last insect clinging to it
has been crushed.
‐ Master!
‐ Go on?
‐ Ikaros One is about to enter
our defensive line.
‐ They're doing what?!
♪ ♪
MAN: The law may bind us
to detain the "Argonaut"
at all costs,
but on the other hand,
as victims of aggression,
they do have the right
to take up arms
against their attacker.
Is that not so?
‐ Indeed it is, sir.
MAN: The Silver Tribe be damned.
Prosperity is a chimera if
the price is enslavement.
DHIANEILA: Captain,
Ikaros One is shielding us.
‐ Well, then, I suppose we
owe them one, don't we?
DHIANEILA: Yes.
♪ ♪
[vapor hissing]
[straining, creaking]
Age...
‐ Proceed.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
‐ Bronze battleships!
‐ Oh...
♪ ♪
[both whimpering]
‐ Major damage to outer sheath
in Sector V‐E!
WOMAN: [speaking indistinctly]
Captain, it's down 70%.
Navigational systems intact.
Prepare to move.
‐ Evasive maneuvers!
Get us out of here!
‐ [roaring]
♪ ♪
[powerful blast]
MOBEEDO:
We're not going to make it!
♪ ♪
IOLAOUS: Age! You can't!
[energy pulsing ]
Uh!
‐ [gasps]
‐ [moans]
[energy crackling]
‐ [howling]
[rumbling, cracking]
[bellowing]
[growling]
DHIANEILA: Enough.
I can't watch this.
Why, Age?
Why such extreme measures?
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
‐ Don't you do it!
Don't you die!
DHIANEILA: He's sleeping.
It seems the battle
has worn him out.
"You have the wind's voice."
Those were Age's words.
Iolaous speaks as the wind:
gentle, but strong.
‐ [chuckles softly]
WOMAN: The anthills
are in retreat.
MOBEEDO: Maintain emergency
backup systems.
Assess the damage and make
a full report.
I want reads for
Titarros as well.
‐ Will do, Master.
[groans]
The other Nodos had no intention
of defeating Bellcross.
Was he just testing him?
I shudder to think
of the devastation
a full‐fledged conflict
between them would bring.
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA:
What would compel you
to fight your own kind, Age?
What manner of destiny
has the Golden Tribe
carved out for you?
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA: The "Argonaut"
again abandons the Starway
in the hope of eluding those
who would wipe out humankind,
next time on "Heroic Age,"
episode 6, "The Cemetery Belt."