‐ [roars]
‐ Elysium.
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
‐ It's still alive.
How dare you show yourselves.
Where are you?
‐ See, now we're out.
[laughs]
‐ [panting] Hold on.
Let me rest a minute.
‐ [groans]
‐ You bastards!
‐ The Silver Tribe's ship,
did it escape the void?
‐ The pathway to Elysium
has been discovered.
We'll have to make our way there
in this vessel.
We can recuperate
during the trip.
‐ Damn you! You have all
betrayed our cause!
‐ That isn't true,
Phaetho O.
We have not.
‐ We've done nothing
that violates
the nature of our labors.
You must hear us out.
‐ The majority
of the Silver Tribe
agrees with Prome O.
Discord comes only from those
like you and Rom Ror.
‐ [grunts]
‐ Once Rom realizes
he won't gain
the power of the Golden Tribe,
he'll have Yuty destroy Elysium,
and that is the last
of Yuty's Labors.
It is my sworn duty
to protect the power
that lies on that planet.
That is one of my Labors.
Now go.
MAN: Elysium.
The path has been found.
It would be wise to listen.
LECTY:
Go, not only for your own sake
and the sake
of your own tribe,
but for the benefit
of every tribe in the universe.
But then again, you're welcome
to stay here and challenge us.
‐ Rom Ror and his Nodos
will destroy
each and every one of you.
‐ May the stars guide them
on their way.
‐ Elysium.
It is nothing but a dream,
an illusion from long ago.
The Golden Tribe
didn't leave a thing
for the new masters
of the universe.
If they wish to leave nothing
behind, I shall assist them,
by destroying every last trace
of their existence.
‐ Erase me.
Please.
You have to erase me,
Kervius.
‐ We're getting closer.
I can feel it.
‐ Bee, report.
BEE NO BEE:
The repairs are expected to take
at least 80 hours, master.
‐ Will it be possible to jump
before the repairs are done?
‐ No, I'm afraid not.
‐ There is a cease fire
with the Silver Tribe,
but factions within the group
remain a threat.
Our main focus is still
to reach the coordinates
indicated by the princess.
‐ I'm detecting
a large magnetic storm.
It's position will interfere
with the ship's current course.
‐ And there's
no alternate route, huh?
Well, it's nothing
the "Argonaut" can't handle.
Full speed ahead!
Shields at maximum capacity!
‐ No.
WOMAN: Speed is increasing.
All navigations systems are
losing function.
Celestial locations
completely off‐line.
‐ This is no magnetic storm.
‐ Pulses have penetrated
the outer shields
and are compounding
the damage to the hull.
We're on red alert.
[alarm blaring]
‐ This isn't a storm.
It's a test.
‐ "Argonaut's" interior
has been compromised.
MAN: At this rate,
we'll be torn apart!
A field is growing
in our output!
Total shield failure
in 11.6 minutes!
‐ We have no choice
but to turn the ship around.
DHIANEILA: No, Captain.
‐ Your Highness.
[beeps]
‐ Receiving a transmission.
Displaying the data now.
MOBEEDO: That isn't a course.
What the hell is this?
‐ Delphi has approved
the procedure
to unlock the frame.
‐ You can't seriously want us
to deploy the main cannon.
That's insane!
‐ That wasn't my order.
Your Highness, just what
are you trying to do here?
‐ This ordeal is meant
to test us.
The Golden Tribe is trying
to find out if we are
truly willing to persevere and
open the path on our own.
‐ I can't promise you
this is going to end well.
‐ Please, believe in me,
Captain.
‐ I guess even a saint needs
a soldier to do the dirty work.
Lucky for both us,
I don't mind.
Hmm.
Maintain shields
at full power!
Prepare to discharge
the main cannon
of the "Argonaut"
at the coordinates
provided by the princess!
‐ But Captain,
you're asking us
to pump more energy
into the shields
while we're still powering up
the main cannon.
It can't be done
under these conditions.
‐ If we don't turn around
right now,
there's no way the "Argonaut"
will survive this.
‐ The princess has never
steered us wrong before,
and you'll take
her orders now!
There's a lot more at stake here
than our own lives,
ladies and gentlemen.
It's the future
of our entire species.
Now more than ever,
we have to give it our all.
‐ Reconfiguring
shield coverage.
Now unlocking the hull.
[all talking at once]
‐ Now they need
active simulations
to determine
any possible errors.
‐ Deploy all
available Organ units!
Position them where the hull
is most vulnerable!
Now we'll see whether we pass
this test, or fail it.
WOMAN: Begin [indistinct]
the outer hull.
MAN: Starboard lock
is disengaged.
Beginning first stage
of deployment.
WOMAN: Confirming release
of the outer hull lock.
Moving on to stage two.
MAN: Releasing the middle axis.
The outer hull and sail
are now fully open.
‐ Attention, all units.
Be prepared to engage
your shields.
‐ Stop it!
Don't you break now!
[groaning]
This'll never work!
Never!
MAN: [indistinct].
Muzzle is now exposed.
WOMAN:
All locks have been checked.
The outer hull is in place.
Communication system is
off‐line.
[all talking at once]
‐ Main cannon
has been deployed.
The margin of error
for target alignment
is approaching zero.
‐ Problem in propulsion room A.
It looks like we're losing
the thruster.
‐ We can only maintain firing
position for 60 seconds,
so hurry up and aim!
WOMAN:
Connecting the firing circuits.
Activating all accelerators.
‐ It's getting even worse
out there.
We've got to try and concentrate
more energy on Dhianeila.
No matter what happens, we can't
let her become too weak.
All of us here
would give our lives
to support you in your quest.
That is our mission
and my personal oath
to you, Dhianeila.
MAN: Target is locked on.
Awaiting authorization.
WOMAN: Biological [indistinct]
has been entered.
Approving the final code
of star blaster.
MAN: Energy level is rising.
50 seconds
until launch criticality.
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
All accelerators are
functioning normally.
Ten seconds
until criticality.
Nine, eight, seven,
six, five,
four, three, two,
one, zero.
WOMAN: Main cannon is ready
to launch.
‐ Fire.
[ethereal music]
♪ ♪
‐ The main cannon was aimed
and fired.
The status
of our inertial control
and shield systems
is unknown.
‐ The fore thruster
is damaged.
We're losing pressure fast!
‐ We can try to recover
navigation
on the backup circuit.
‐ What's this?
‐ Conditions outside the ship
are now favorable, Master.
We're back on the scheduled
course with no margin of error.
‐ What the hell is going on?
How can the ship
still be moving?
‐ The unknown field is
changing rapidly.
It's amazing. It appears
to have become pure gravity.
‐ Like a path of stars.
‐ A Starway has been born.
[peaceful music]
♪ ♪
‐ [sighs]
‐ Elysium.
‐ We're here,
home world of the Golden Tribe.
‐ Wow.
‐ The shield. Captain,
is the Silver Tribe here?
‐ I doubt they've arrived yet.
Those are the shields that were
given to the Silver Tribe.
I suspect those are
the original.
DHIANEILA:
The planet is welcoming us.
Captain, please be prepared
to make your descent.
‐ Your Highness‐‐
Of course you'll go down there
on your own
no matter what I say.
Just a moment.
Allow me to restructure
the Organ unit for you.
‐ Thank you so very much,
Captain.
‐ We're so proud of you.
‐ And thank you.
I never could've found
the path,
or made here alive
for that matter,
if it wasn't
for your loyal service.
‐ Your Highness,
will you allow me
to stay be your side
until the very end?
‐ Of course.
‐ Operation efficiency
is down by half.
There's no timetable
for navigation repairs.
‐ Due to the shortage
of supplies, over half
of the 247 damaged blocks
cannot be repaired.
‐ Our defensive capabilities
have been compromised,
and due to energy consumption,
so has our ability
to mount a counterattack.
‐ Not bad, considering that
storm should have destroyed us.
But it didn't,
and I would like to thank
each and every one of you
for being at your best.
‐ Should we send out
a distress signal, sir?
‐ I don't believe this is
a ghost ship just yet.
Besides, it might attract
the enemy.
We'll use it if there's
no other option.
Start the repairs on all
our navigational components.
‐ The shuttle unit Basilis
is now prepared
for its descent, master.
‐ At long last our princess
shall set foot
on the Golden Tribe's
mother planet.
Send every available Organ unit
for her protection.
WOMAN: The course is set.
Open the bay.
WOMAN: Ready to move out.
‐ We don't know how
the Hedron shield
surrounding the planet will
react, so stay on alert.
Anything could happen
out there.
‐ Roger that.
WOMAN:
We have engine ignition.
Moving out.
[inspiring music]
♪ ♪
[balls shimmering]
‐ All descending units,
change course now.
The atmosphere changed
to accommodate
our presence here.
Those are the optimum conditions
for humans to survive.
‐ It's time.
We won't need to wear a suit.
Let us accept
this planet's welcome.
Everyone wait here.
‐ Dhianeila, please.
‐ At least take us with you.
‐ It could be dangerous.
‐ There's no need for you
to be concerned.
I just want to feel
the thoughts
that have been left
on this planet.
‐ I'd feel better
about this
if the princess had
an escort down there.
‐ Let's keep our eyes open.
We don't want to overlook
anything.
[energy ringing]
‐ Such powerful thoughts.
But now you are nowhere
to be found on this planet
or this universe.
Why did you leave?
[surging energy]
To fill...
all of existence...
with Starways.
ROM: That is a lie.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[alarm blaring]
‐ Of course,
they followed us.
WOMAN: Incoming enemy ship,
vector 1.98.
MAN: We have no effective
counter attack available to us.
MOBEEDO: All Organ units proceed
to the surface at once.
Maintain shields
at maximum capacity.
We've got to protect her!
Plot a collision course
immediately!
‐ Dhianeila!
‐ Before any blood is spilled,
please meditate with me.
Try to feel
the immense wealth of thoughts
that were left here for us.
‐ Long before you
and your vile kind arrived
I scoured Elysium
for anything
the Golden Tribe may have
left behind,
but I discovered nothing.
They feared their great power
would be taken from them,
so they abandoned this universe.
They they abandoned us.
‐ You're wrong.
We simply weren't prepared
to inherit
a power of that magnitude.
‐ The Nodos are all
they left for us.
The power to destroy it all.
That was the true intention
of the Golden Tribe.
‐ I don't care anymore.
[sobs]
Kervius,
erase this suffering.
Erase me.
‐ Don't you see?
They knew we would find
the location
of their home planet.
‐ Hmm.
That may be true.
The Golden Tribe,
in their infinite wisdom,
may have foreseen this,
and there is
only one possible reason
I could have been brought here.
‐ No, don't!
ROM: To erase all that has been
tainted by the Golden Tribe.
‐ Kervius.
‐ Keep energy on the shield
at the point of contact!
Fight back!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
It protected us.
‐ All systems are failing.
We're going to crash!
‐ Expand the ship's body
as soon as we hit
the atmosphere.
We've got to diffuse
the shock of the fall.
‐ Come, kill.
With this you conclude
your Labors, Yuty.
‐ Frenzy.
Is that the true intention
of the Golden Tribe?
Does this mean that our future
is destined
to be forged
from chaos and despair?
‐ Dhianeila.
The "Argonaut."
‐ By the gods.
It's going down.
‐ All remaining thrusters have
been rendered inoperative.
‐ Focus all the shields
under the ship!
Maintain the peak angle
of approach,
otherwise the ship will
snap in half!
‐ Impact is imminent, Captain.
‐ Release every insulating wall
on the "Argonaut"!
Spread impact of reentry!
We're not done for just yet!
[groaning]
[grunts]
Bee, report.
You've done a fine job, Bee.
‐ What happened?
The Silver Tribe!
You did this to him!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Damn it.
‐ Even if he destroys
each one of us,
the path to the future
will go on.
Our hope will never die.
‐ Let's go.
‐ [grumbles]
‐ [grunting]
‐ [roars]
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA: We embrace
possibilities and hope.
Next time on "Heroic Age,"
episode 15, "The Final Labor."