[overlapping chatter]
MAN: Warping process is now
complete.
We're currently in the center of
the Alta system
and now securing the Starways
to the planet Codomos.
‐ This area is so close to their
home planet,
they should be defending it.
I would think they'd be more
concerned about a disturbance
in their jurisdiction.
‐ Would you like to lower
the alert level?
‐ No, we don't want to
accommodate them.
We'll come up with our own
approach.
Right now, it seems obvious that
we're in a non‐combat zone.
I hope the message we send our
allies reaches them in time.
WOMAN: No sign of the enemy in
the area.
All organ units stand by.
‐ Roger.
It's a bold move to invade the
enemy's home planet
and to do it alone,
but considering the situation,
the princess has made
the best possible choice.
What happens next?
DHIANEILA: I can feel it.
It has to be.
It's just ahead of us.
PROME O: Lecty.
LECTY: Yes, Prome O.
I'm here.
PROME O: I sense someone is
making their way to me.
LECTY: Who?
PROME O: One who is capable of
finding the path
even after leaving the Starway.
LECTY: I'll protect you.
PROME O: There's no need to do
that.
LECTY: But, Prome O.
PROME O: I'll transmit her
voice.
You stay there and listen.
LECTY: Her voice?
You're going to talk with the
Iron Tribe?
But...
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
‐ [growling]
‐ [growls]
KARKINOS: Why does she insist
no fighting alone?
She's going to drive herself
into a frenzy.
Yuty.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
AGE: Don't let up.
Try to shake them off.
MAN: Commander, we've received a
transmission
from the "Argonaut."
‐ They've set a course for
Codomos.
So they're attempting to make
peace rather than surrender.
‐ There seems to be a time lag,
Commander,
and that means the "Argonaut"
may have already reached them.
‐ Walking right into hostile
territory with enemies
on every side.
It sounds reckless, but we'll
just have to trust them.
We're changing course.
Head toward the planet Codomos.
MAN: Entering the coordinates
sent by "Argonaut."
‐ It looks like there may still
be hope.
DHIANEILA: I can sense them now.
They're patiently awaiting
our arrival.
ANEASHA: But what if it's a
trap?
DHIANEILA: I don't think it is.
‐ The princess wants to see you.
Could you come right away?
‐ [gulps]
To her room?
Of course.
Yes, princess, you summoned.
DHIANEILA: Please stand up,
Iolaous.
‐ I can't bring myself to do
that,
not while I'm here in your
chambers, Your Highness.
I'm not worthy.
‐ But if you can't even stand
before me,
how can I ask you to teleport
with me?
‐ You want to teleport with me?
DHIANEILA: I need to go Codomos.
‐ Is there nothing I can say to
make you reconsider?
DHIANEILA: We cannot waste any
more time.
ANEASHA: But it's not safe for
you to go without any guards.
‐ I'll have Iolaous to protect
me.
I know you're worried,
but I have to do this alone,
Aneasha.
I have to find a way to try and
reconcile with them,
or everyone living in this
planetary system will perish.
ANEASHA: Isn't there another
way?
‐ There's no need to worry.
I'll protect the princess
with my life.
‐ But, Iolaous...
‐ Mm.
[stirring orchestral music]
ANEASHA: [gasps]
♪ ♪
I'd be honored if you would lead
the way, princess.
♪ ♪
‐ There's something I need to
know first.
Do you ever find my abilities
intimidating, Iolaous?
♪ ♪
‐ Not in the least,
Your Highness.
‐ Well, I'm glad.
♪ ♪
Allow me to show you where we
need to go.
♪ ♪
Can you see it, Iolaous?
‐ Yes.
DHIANEILA: Then let's go.
IOLAOUS: Are they ready to
receive you, princess?
DHIANEILA: Yes, they have
anticipated our arrival
and have made preparations.
♪ ♪
We should go now.
I'm afraid we don't have any
more time to spare.
‐ I'm honored to follow you.
♪ ♪
ANEASHA: Captain.
‐ She's left the ship?
‐ She has Iolaous with her.
They've both gone.
‐ Then she'll be fine.
The princess has yet to steer us
in the wrong direction.
We must have faith that what
she's doing is right.
‐ Yes, sir.
‐ Dhianeilla,
big brother...
Please be careful.
We need you.
Please come back to us.
‐ Hm.
‐ I've been waiting for you.
I have familiarized myself
with your language,
your environment,
and your civilization.
If it pleases you, we may now
exchange our thoughts.
DHIANEILA: I could feel that you
were diligently preparing
for our arrival.
PROME O: But how were you aware
of my presence here?
DHIANEILA: I could feel you,
your emotions.
PROME O: You mean my thoughts.
DHIANEILA: No, it was deeper and
more serene than that.
PHAETHO O: Prome O has welcomed
the Iron Tribe.
That is a foolish choice.
‐ My name is Prome O,
proud successor of the O family.
DHIANEILA: I am Princess
Dhianeila Y Leisha
Altoria Ol Yunos,
the daughter of the Yunos royal
family
as well as the principle of the
Altria planetary system.
Prome O, would it be too much to
ask to transmit
this conversation back to our
ship?
PROME O: Not at all, Dhianeila.
As a matter of fact, my people
are listening in as well.
DHIANEILA: I think you for your
hospitality.
You are very kind.
If I may begin, I speak for my
tribe when I say
we feel it's important to learn
more of your kind.
‐ My people feel the same way
about the Iron Tribe.
‐ Tell me, Prome, are you on
this planet alone?
‐ I am, but this planet is
simply the birthplace
of our civilization.
It doesn't hold any particular
significance for us.
DHIANEILA: So the Silver Tribe
do not claim their home planet,
even for its historical
significance?
PROME O: The notion of clinging
to a single planet
is an antiquated one.
You often see that kind of
behavior in a tribe
that is unable to come to a
universe on their own.
You are the only tribe that has
maintained their historic core
after entering the universe.
That is, you and the Golden
Tribe.
‐ Us and the Golden Tribe?
MOBEEDO: Prome O is in contact
with the Iron Tribe.
MAN: This indicates a
possibility of some sort.
His situation is worth
reviewing.
‐ Prome O is making a mistake.
The presence of the Iron Tribe
disturbs the order
of the universe.
WOMAN: And yet she has come
without a weapon.
MAN: We will allow this
conversation to continue.
PHAETHO O: But the Iron Tribe
must be destroyed.
‐ Phaetho O.
PHAETHO O: Prome O is sitting
this very moment with the one
who rules the fifth Nodos.
She has put us in danger.
If Prome O refuses to get rid of
that woman,
I will do so myself.
MAN: Your emotions seem to have
taken over, Phaetho O.
‐ Listen to me.
If we don't destroy the Iron
Tribe, we risk everything.
MAN: The enemy line is falling
apart.
MAN: What's going on out there?
‐ We've found our path to
survival.
Search for holes in their
defense and head that direction.
We'll charge the enemy line.
Please guide us through this,
princess.
MAN: It seems the vast majority
agrees with Prome.
PROME O: Well, isn't it
interesting
that we have that in common.
DHIANEILA: Our tribes are the
only ones who've received
Nodos from the Golden Tribe.
‐ And it is my firm belief the
intentions of the Golden Tribe
are hidden in that action.
‐ But what do you think it
means?
PROME O: The labors of the Nodos
seem to have
major inconsistencies.
However, it's impossible that
the Golden Tribe made a mistake.
It must be our present condition
that causes these
contradictions.
We can eradicate them by
attempting
to understand one another.
Then the lost powers of the
Golden Tribe shall be bestowed
upon both our peoples.
‐ I can't believe it.
I never thought I'd hear those
words coming from them.
‐ She never ceases to amaze me.
Dhianeila is the best diplomat
any of us could ever hope for.
‐ We have come here in search of
peace as well, Prome.
We want reconciliation, not to
take anything away
from your people.
‐ There are a few among us who
feel hatred towards your tribe.
My people are currently in a
heated debate
concerning my decision to speak
with you.
DHIANEILA: Yes, I can feel it.
And I feel the wonderful
spiritual balance
maintained among all of you.
PROME O: That power has allowed
my kind to expand
throughout the universe.
But it's frightening to be alone
in space.
So we've evolved to endure that
loneliness.
Now we can share our thoughts
and emotions
despite the distance between us.
However, even when sharing
thoughts,
we tend to avoid emotions which
should not be ignored.
DHIANEILA: Like what?
PROME O: The sense of loss we
felt when the Golden Tribe
vanished, the anxiety caused by
a sense of duty
to take over their guidance
and maintain order in the
universe.
It was those primitive emotions
which led us to believe
that we needed to destroy the
Iron Tribe.
‐ But why?
Why us, Prome?
PROME O: Because when the Golden
Tribe abandoned us,
they chose to share their power
with your tribe.
DHIANEILA: The Nodos.
PROME O: To our kind,
who have learned from
and aspire to be like the Golden
Tribe,
it felt like a betrayal,
although it was more than just
these simple emotions
that led us to believe we must
destroy your tribe.
It is also because you're a
destructive race of beings
willing to destroy your own
stars if need be.
‐ Well, unlike you, we moved
from our home
only a short time ago.
We are still a young tribe who
have yet to learn
how to live in the universe.
Understand our race can be
taught right from wrong,
but you must give us some time.
What would the Golden Tribe have
wanted,
an entire race to be destroyed
due to their immaturity?
‐ Of course there are those
among our tribe
who share that thought and would
rather not cause
needless destruction.
Both your tribe and mine should
learn from the lessons
of the Golden Tribe and try to
find peace.
MAN: The danger of causing
destruction.
That is a lesson we must learn
from the Golden Tribe.
MAN: But this is not
destruction.
This war is necessary to keep
order in the universe.
WOMAN: Can we not keep order
through dialogue
instead of with force?
MAN: We shall see.
[loud explosions]
‐ Wait.
Why aren't they attacking us?
‐ I appears the enemy has pulled
back
on their offense, Commander.
‐ No doubt about it.
It has to e Dhianeila.
WOMAN: A high‐energy source
consistent with a Nodos
has been detected.
Projecting visual image.
‐ That's just what we need.
We've lost too much power to try
and navigate through that mess.
Let's get out of here.
‐ We'll take the Starway toward
planet Codomos.
‐ Mm, Age.
‐ [roaring]
‐ [roars]
[mystical music]
♪ ♪
‐ Uh.
‐ [growls]
‐ You have learned to utilize
the powers given to you
by the Golden Tribe.
But we have yet to master
any such gifts.
‐ While you may not have
complete control of them,
you've had these gifts since
birth,
the same gifts which gave you
the power to find planet Olone
without using the Starway.
‐ [roars]
‐ Yuty.
She'll go into a frenzy at this
rate.
‐ [growls]
DHIANEILA: There are times when
I have this strange feeling.
It's almost like I can hear the
stars' thoughts,
and it's those thoughts which
direct me.
At the same time, I cannot help
but feel as if I'm somehow
connecting all of the stars
which have yet to join the
Starway.
‐ What you feel is exactly
what's happening.
‐ So those sensations I felt
are real?
PROME O: I have always wondered.
Every tribe in existence must
rely on the stars
to guide them and travel them
through the universe.
But is it not possible that our
actions
may also be guiding them?
‐ True, and the Starway has
brought together
different species and even the
stars themselves.
PROME O: Before the birth of a
star occurs,
the Starway is born.
DHIANEILA: And it disappears
before the star dies.
PROME O: It seems you're quite
knowledgeable on the subject.
DHIANEILA: It is something I've
always believed to be the truth.
PROME O: Tell me, princess, why
are you not afraid
of leading the Starway?
DHIANEILA: Before they vanished,
the Golden Tribe told my people
to go forth, and by leaving the
Starway,
I feel that we are.
PROME O: Stars are not always
born from the mysterious powers
that flow through the universe.
DHIANEILA: Stars can also be
born from the power of lives
interacting through the
galaxies.
PROME O: Filling the universe
with Starways.
DHIANEILA: If that was in fact
the ultimate objective
of the Golden Tribe.
‐ That is why they can endure an
endless battle.
They honestly believe that was
the best way to keep life
moving throughout the universe.
DHIANEILA: If through their
divination they ever felt
our actions would bring ruin to
the universe,
they would have stopped us
immediately.
PROME O: In the midst of this
brutal war,
do you think that there is even
a small glimmer of hope
for our universe?
‐ I am certain there is, because
I have witnessed it.
‐ Is there hope for Olone,
that husk of faded glory?
‐ For my own existence and that
of the "Argonaut"...
BOTH:
Help to resurrect the Starway,
which had been thought lost to
the ages.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ I think that must be why I met
Age.
[sensor beeping]
‐ Gravitational shock detected,
master.
‐ The enemy?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ This ends here.
The Iron Tribe must die.
PROME O: The time has come for
you to face your true emotions,
Phaetho O.
‐ You've done enough damage,
Prome O!
‐ [gasps]
‐ [grunts]
♪ ♪
‐ All shields to maximum power.
‐ [grunts]
‐ [gasps]
MAN: We are in support of Prome
O.
We have agreed that their
current dialogue should be
allowed to continue.
‐ [gasping]
No!
You're all wrong!
‐ Whoa.
Are they protecting us?
‐ Is this what they meant?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ [roars]
‐ Yuty, no.
DHIANEILA: Prome, how can we
find a glimmer of hope
in the midst
of such a horrible battle?
PROME O: It seems many of my
people are in support
of our conversation today.
DHIANEILA: Even so, the war is
still going strong.
PROME O: It is because of Rom
Ror,
he who rules the four Nodos.
He is one of the main supporters
of this war.
If we do not correct the
inconsistencies we spoke of,
this pattern of war will never
end,
and if the five Nodos fight to
point of frenzy,
we will be unable to stop them.
DHIANEILA: And the only ones who
can stop a frenzied Nodos
are the Golden Tribe, correct?
‐ Yes, and although they
disappeared long ago,
their home planet still exists.
However, the Silver Tribe has
never bothered to examine it.
As I said before, history holds
no significance for us.
‐ What if the secrets of their
power are still on that planet?
PROME O: Well, I suppose it's a
possibility,
but the planet lost its Starway
when they departed.
It's nothing more than a distant
memory to us now.
DHIANEILA: A memory.
‐ I trust you, the one who
guides the stars
beyond the Starway.
I will share with you the memory
that I have kept close
all this time.
[stirring orchestral music]
♪ ♪
Only you can find this planet,
Dhianeila, and its name is...
♪ ♪
‐ Elysium.
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
WOMAN:
As Kervius is thrown into
frenzy,
the world turns into
nothingness.
Next time on "Heroic Age,"
episode 22,
"The Agreement of Death."