[rattling]
‐ Bellcross's presence is gone.
I can't feel it.
ALL: [gasping]
‐ What do you mean?
‐ It's as if it disappeared
from the universe.
‐ Age is gone?
Then we have to go and find him.
He's more than a Nodos.
He's our friend
and needs our help.
[gasps]
‐ There's no way that he could
be gone forever.
He promised that he would
return to us.
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
MAN: All core procedures
completed.
WOMAN: Verifying current
coordinates.
Verification failed.
This location is not on record.
‐ Start a deep space
scan immediately.
Full spectrum.
Keep your eyes peeled
for trouble.
This is unexplored territory.
WOMAN: I shall search
for our path.
[engines rumbling]
MAN: Elysium, the planet
with no Starway.
If we don't find it, we'll be
alone and adrift forever.
Will the search for a path end
as it did on Olone?
On this dark journey
into the unknown,
only our princess can turn
our fears into hope.
DHIANEILA: Age.
The time has come
to take action.
Now, we must journey to the
mother planet
of the Golden Tribe, Elysium.
MAN: Why did the Nodos
disappear?
WOMAN: Our Nodos Labors
all have one thing in common.
They are all required to protect
the life of Yuty La.
MAN: But Kervius has destroyed
all four Nodos,
including the one who fights
for the humans.
MAN: And the Iron Tribe's Nodos
wasn't the least bit
intimidating to Kervius.
WOMAN: What if their destruction
was in fact the means
by which Yuty La's life
was to be protected?
MAN: That is consistent
with the Labors.
MAN: Now nothing connects
the Silver Tribe
to the Golden Tribe.
MAN: Was that also the intention
of the Golden Tribe?
MAN: Does this mean
that Rom Ror is right?
MAN: It may be necessary
to rethink
our position on Elysium.
YUTY: Now I'm alone.
Truly alone.
The only Nodos left.
Karkinos.
Save me.
[sobbing]
Please, Rom.
I can't bear
this feeling anymore.
You must allow Prome
to help me.
Let her take this pain.
Please.
End this torture.
Rom Ror.
Please help.
Let me go.
Release me from your prison.
‐ For the moment, you must stay
right where you are.
I can't afford to let Prome
win influence over you.
‐ [sobs]
I'm begging you.
‐ I alone can be trusted with
control of the last Nodos.
‐ [sobbing]
No.
Please.
ROM: You will execute every last
one of your Labors.
LECTY: Mehitak,
why did you come back?
Even with the power
of Erymanthos,
I'm afraid we won't be able
to jump out of this place.
Please forgive me.
[rumbling]
[clanging]
MEHITAK: Lecty.
‐ Mehitak?
I'm sorry.
MEHITAK: Finally.
It's so nice,
like I've been set free.
[grunts]
It's so quiet here.
‐ Kervius has thrown us into
a void of nothingness.
Erymanthos is maintaining our
place in time and space
for now, but soon...
[clanging]
BOTH: [gasp]
‐ [gasps]
Age!
AGE: Thank you.
‐ For what?
‐ Hmm, for this.
‐ But this construct serves only
to delay our eventual death.
‐ That's okay.
[chuckles]
‐ I'm glad you're here.
‐ Those are the Korba
and Erizal fleets.
‐ Of all the fleets combined,
those are the only ships
that survived.
How many of
the remaining vessels
will be able to make the journey
to Codomos?
‐ Systems detecting
an enemy convoy
on an intercept course.
MAN: Ma'am?
WOMAN: Change course.
We'll leave the Alta system
and adjust our heading
to pass through
the non‐combat zone.
When the coast is clear, we'll
return to the Codomos Starway.
Make sure all our ships know
where this enemy convoy is.
We simple can't afford
to get into another battle
until we reorganize the fleet
at Codomos.
‐ Ma'am, we're receiving a new
transmission
from the "Argonaut."
WOMAN: Let's hear it.
WOMAN: If I may begin,
I speak for my tribe
when I say we feel
it's important
to learn more of your kind.
WOMAN: My people feel the same
way about the Iron Tribe.
WOMAN: Tell me...
‐ What is it?
WOMAN: Are you on
this planet alone?
WOMAN: I am.
‐ I thought that all was lost.
But once again,
our princess has found
a path in our darkest hour.
DHIANEILA: Elysium.
An ancient beginning.
Please, please show us the path.
WOMAN: I feel so powerless.
The only thing I can do to help
is watch over her.
I can only imagine how badly
Princess Dhianeila
wishes Age was back on
the "Argonaut" right now.
‐ If you ask me, you do far more
than you give yourself
credit for.
Without your undying support,
the princess
would've collapsed from fatigue
a long time ago.
‐ Hold on, if I didn't
know better,
I'd say you just gave me
a compliment.
Princess Dhianeila said
she searched the universe
for Age's presence,
but it's gone.
[gasps]
‐ You know there's no way
Age would leave us, don't you?
After all, Age is
a man of his word,
and I know he'll make good on
his promise to the princess.
He will come back to us
just like he always does.
Okay?
‐ Hmm.
Right.
AGE: I heard Dhianeila's voice
right before I showed up here.
‐ You did?
‐ Hmm.
We all have to go
where she is going.
LECTY: That is simply
not possible.
Now that we have all exhausted
the powers of our Nodos
in battle,
an escape attempt
would only serve
to shorten our lives even more.
AGE: One, two, three, four.
It'll work because
there's four of us.
LECTY: Four?
MEHITAK: What's that?
[shimmering]
Lernaea.
LECTY: It's alive.
[whooshing]
‐ Huh?
‐ What's happening?
[gasps]
[shimmering]
[blowing]
Lernaea's ability to regenerate.
It's so very powerful.
‐ [stammers]
‐ Ah!
‐ Karkinos.
‐ [gasps]
‐ Four of us.
MAN: The Astral Turbine
is ready for operation.
‐ We need the coordinates
of the destination.
‐ For now, we just stand by.
When we receive word
from the princess,
we'll enter active warp.
‐ Standing by, sir.
MAN: Your highness...
‐ Huh?
MAN: Alert!
Alien fleet has been detected.
‐ Prepare a counter‐attack!
WOMAN: Boarding unit is ready
for emergency launch.
MAN: Initiate
the attack program.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
MAN: Hurry it up!
‐ I'm coming!
♪ ♪
‐ You're late again.
‐ I'm sorry, sir.
MAN: Laser control systems
are operational.
Overons will establish
a defense line against
the enemy front.
MAN: These are the ones
who despise humanity.
♪ ♪
MAN: Overons, now in position.
MAN: All turrets ready to fire.
♪ ♪
MAN: More enemy ships detected.
‐ By the gods,
they just keep coming!
MAN: Displaying the info now.
♪ ♪
‐ Let me through.
MAN: You mustn't
interrupt the voyage
of the Iron Tribe vessel.
MAN: That is our consensus.
MAN: Then at least let me
prove to you
the flaw in Prome O's judgment.
MAN: We will know soon.
MAN: That won't be necessary.
MAN: If theirs is truly
the vessel foretold of
by the Golden Tribe,
then they have
nothing to fear from me
or anyone.
Now, move!
MAN: Phaetho O's
reasoning is sound.
MAN: It's an unnecessary war.
MAN: There is no guarantee
that the power
of the Golden Tribe can be
found on this plane.
And whether the planet
called Elysium
exists is also unclear.
MAN: Are we to disregard
Prome's theories?
MAN: We must if they can't
be proven.
MAN: Prome is examining
all logical possibilities.
She has given
the Iron Tribe time.
MAN: There is no need to wait.
If Prome O is right, then I will
surely perish here.
PROME O: A foolish
train of thought, Phaetho O.
PHAETHO O: Prome.
♪ ♪
Get out of my way!
Or face my wrath!
♪ ♪
PROME O: Phaetho...
‐ [gasps]
♪ ♪
AGE: Feels kind of good.
Ah!
‐ Healing must be the true power
of Lernaea.
Not that awful poison
that kills everything.
This is incredible.
‐ [laughing]
‐ It makes me wonder.
Karkinos has died before now.
Do you think that this,
like our Labors,
is all just a part
of the Golden Tribe's plan?
‐ Bellcross and the others
were heartless.
They know only destruction.
But Age and everyone else
came together
and taught them
how to have a heart.
‐ If what you're saying is true,
then Lernaea saved her strength
to help Karkinos.
This was not a tactic for war.
All Lernaea wanted
was for Karkinos to live.
He's coming to.
‐ Ah...
Mehitak?
‐ No fighting anymore, okay?
‐ Remember when
I reached out to you?
As I recall,
you reacted violently.
You're quite stubborn,
aren't you, boy?
‐ Hmm.
[chuckles]
‐ [grunting]
‐ We think that Lernaea
saved its own strength
specifically for your survival.
KARKINOS: Yes.
‐ You already knew about it?
‐ I didn't, but I knew
that Lernaea
was trying harder
to avoid frenzy.
And it watched over me
for a long time.
It felt like eons.
This is Kervius' non‐dimension?
‐ Just like Age told us.
Now there are four of us here.
‐ I still believe
that an escape attempt
from here is futile at best.
KARKINOS: The exact nature
of this non‐dimension
is open to question.
We know nothing about it.
In fact, we may find that
we are utterly powerless here.
AGE: That's true,
but what we do have
is the words my dad told me.
‐ What do you mean?
‐ Age was just telling us
how the Golden Tribe told him
their vision of the future.
‐ [gasps]
‐ Now they have hearts.
That's what was given
to Bellcross' tribe.
To get them, they had to live
inside of us first.
With no heart,
there is no future.
LECTY: The future.
Each one of us must still
execute our Labors.
Karkinos will only be free
when the Silver Tribe
obtains the power
of the Golden Tribe.
Mehitak is bound
by his Labors
to protect Yuty whenever
her life is in danger.
I am also bound to protect
Yuty's life.
And when I have discovered
the power of the Golden Tribe,
it is my duty to inform
the Silver Tribe.
If this power
is ever threatened,
it is I who must protect it.
‐ I will too.
When all of this is done, the
star will go back to normal.
‐ What star?
‐ Olone, the most beautiful
star there is.
LECTY: If the Golden Tribe's
vision of the future
is hinted at by
the Nodos' Labors,
then why are there
only two tribes
involved in these tasks?
It doesn't make any sense.
The Labors only concern
the Silver and Iron Tribes.
KARKINOS: They must have
a reason for that.
Perhaps we are not yet ready
to fully understand it.
AGE: When I leave,
I have to rescue that girl.
KARKINOS: What girl is that?
‐ Mm...
Let's see...
Ah!
[howling]
‐ What's he doing?
‐ I'm trying to show you
who put us here.
‐ Yuty.
‐ Rescue Yuty.
Is that what you mean?
‐ Hm.
The four of us can do it.
‐ [gasping]
Release me.
Please, Rom.
I can't take this.
Let me go.
Rom Ror, please,
have mercy on me.
Ah!
ROM: You arrogant bastards.
Why did you abandon us?
Why?
‐ Ah!
[whimpering]
I won't forgive you.
Not for this.
Not until the day I die.
[sobbing]
Karkinos, help me.
‐ What did you mean
when you said,
"The four of us can do it"?
AGE: He's light,
and you're life,
and she's time.
‐ Yes, our abilities
as the Nodos.
‐ What about Bellcross?
‐ He is unique.
Bellcross is the being
that cannot be lost
on any plane of existence.
You think we can
use our abilities
to open up a point in
the suspended time and space.
And force Bellcross
back into being.
Is that right?
‐ Hmm.
‐ Well, which is it?
‐ I'm sure that's exactly
what he had in mind.
I suppose we could
give it a try.
‐ Give it a try?
If we fail even once,
then all four of us
will be condemned
to this nothingness.
‐ You're right,
but the exact same thing
will happen if we don't
do anything.
‐ Are you sure about this?
If we were to fail‐‐
‐ Sure, I'm sure.
This is going to work.
Age believes in Lecty,
and the other Lecty
inside Lecty.
‐ [gasps]
You mean Erymanthos.
That's the name of
the Heroic Tribe member
that resides within me.
‐ Hmm.
[dramatic music]
WOMAN: Front line contact with
the enemy force is inevitable.
MAN: We didn't make it.
We'll engage the enemy,
ready for war.
This means there are no shields.
For this reason
it is absolutely imperative
that the enemy does not
reach the "Argonaut."
All personnel, attack!
‐ They'll get to the "Argonaut"
over my dead body.
♪ ♪
MAN: We will stop at nothing
to hold the enemy back.
I promise.
♪ ♪
LECTY: Erymanthos
will take Bellcross
as far into the past
as our powers allow.
‐ I give you light.
LECTY: Artemia will send energy
to a single point
in the present,
tearing a hole
from this dimension
into the next
to make our escape.
‐ And Lernaea and I shall
maintain everyone's life force.
LECTY: Lernaea's
regenerative power
will keep each of us alive
until Bellcross becomes
the first presence in
the space‐time continuum.
This will happen
in a split second.
‐ Hmm.
♪ ♪
LECTY: Jump, Erymanthos!
Our very lives depend on it.
[explosions]
‐ [grunting]
[explosions, laser blasts]
♪ ♪
‐ [gasps]
Watch out, Mail.
‐ Hm.
♪ ♪
‐ What's the report
on the Schuler unit?
WOMAN: They're not responding.
‐ Ah!
[explosions]
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA: I can't stop this war
unless I find a new path.
Help me to end this.
Please, show me the way
to planet Elysium.
‐ Hold your ground
no matter what!
[booming]
Ah!
♪ ♪
DHIANEILA: Please.
There.
MAN: We've received
the coordinates
for the planet Elysium
from the psych line.
‐ [sighs]
All Organ units, return
to the ship right now.
MAN: The princess
has found our path.
Get back to the ship
immediately.
‐ Dandelion unit
is to come with me
to support all damaged craft.
Organ unit, retrieve all
escape pods on the double.
‐ You can't run away from me!
‐ [gasps]
♪ ♪
[electricity cracking]
‐ [growls]
[explosion]
‐ Ah!
[booming]
‐ Activate warp!
‐ Age.
‐ [gasping]
‐ [roaring]
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
WOMAN: Dhianeila's
wish is granted,
and the planet appears.
Next time on "Heroic Age,"
episode 24: "Elysium."