YUTY: It can't be!
‐ Frenzy.
[Bellcross roars]
‐ What does he hope
to accomplish?
[dramatic music]
‐ I have... no choice.
I must.
‐ This is not Age.
He would never do
these awful things.
Never.
Something has come over him,
something he cannot control.
It's up to us.
We must save our savior.
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
MAN: The frenzied Nodos
is unstoppable.
MAN:
They will destroy all of them.
MAN: The situation
is out of our hands.
We must withdraw.
‐ We will not withdraw.
Our Nodos requires help.
We will fight at his side.
Put everything we've got
into those sectors.
Finish this once and for all!
[Bellcross roaring]
[intense music]
♪ ♪
NILVAL:
Hold the line as best you can.
Help is on the way.
‐ The destruction of the planet
is inevitable,
and I'm afraid the Starway
is still far too unstable
to support the passage
of our reinforcements.
‐ Oh, don't you worry
about that.
The "Argonaut"
is an exceptional ship.
MAN:
More survivors are trickling in.
They're requesting to join us.
‐ Have their ships aligned
to our current orbit.
We'll pick them all up en route.
Contact
as many of the missing
fleet members as you can.
Alert everyone
to the reorganization.
‐ Wait. Lieutenant General,
this doesn't look good.
I'm picking up
the presence of something
whose total energy output
is catastrophic.
‐ Our AI system
has located the source
as a nearby star
about to go supernova.
We have approximately 100 hours
before it hits critical mass!
‐ It's impossible
for a star to go supernova
in that span of time.
Recheck the data!
Find out what's causing it!
MAN: Judging from the stats
we've collected
over the course of this battle,
the only other explanation
would be the Nodos itself.
MAN:
Its energy output is increasing
exponentially and fast.
If this continues unabated,
the whole solar system
will be destroyed!
‐ It... can't...
MAN: That can't be right.
Recalibrate the data.
MAN: But sir, AI recalibrates
the data automatically.
MAN: Confound it, man.
Do it manually!
‐ There's no chance in hell
we can get everyone
out of harm's way in time.
The whole damn system
is about to blow,
and we've got front row tickets.
MAN: Are you sure
there hasn't been a mistake?
MAN:
We've checked and rechecked.
There's no mistake.
AI keeps spitting out
the same warning.
The data is correct.
‐ According to the legend,
the only ones capable
of placating a heroic fury
were the Golden Tribe
themselves.
That doesn't bode very well
for us.
How could we possibly hope
to stop him?
So, then,
it seems that our hopes
were foolish after all.
Contact the "Argonaut"
immediately.
MAN:
Local gravity shock detected.
‐ [gasps]
[shimmering and tinkling]
MAN: Allied fleets
converging on our position.
‐ Look. They've made it through.
‐ Unbelievable. They actually
navigated through the Starway.
And in the middle
of such a huge battle, no less.
‐ I hate to say "I told you so,"
Lieutenant,
but the "Argonaut"
is an exceptional vessel.
Here I am, putting
all of these people in jeopardy.
I am unworthy of rescue.
Put me through to them
right now.
I will apologize to Princess
Dhianeila personally.
DHIANEILA:
There is no need of that.
You have shown
extraordinary courage, Nilval.
It is I who should be
apologizing to you.
Please, forgive me.
‐ Princess Dhianeila, I‐‐
‐ A great many brave ships
have gone missing
in the course of this battle.
Even so,
hope of their recovery is nigh.
Their presence
isn't lost to me yet.
‐ Lieutenant General,
their positions are beginning
to show up
on the telepathic line.
‐ Princess... thank you, but‐‐
DHIANEILA: Please, Nilval.
We must keep hope alive.
♪ ♪
Have faith.
It's true that Age is capable
of almost unthinkable
destruction,
but I know his heart is pure,
and at great peril to myself,
I will prove it.
‐ [gasps]
‐ But I will not
put the fleet in danger
while we are searching for him.
The "Argonaut" will go alone.
Therefore, I have to ask of you
and your crewmembers
that you stay behind
and continue fighting
for humanity's right to survive.
♪ ♪
‐ There is no path more arduous
than the one
you yourself must follow.
I swear my allegiance to you.
Forever.
I will defend the "Argonaut"
in your name,
with every single fiber
of my being.
‐ Thank you, Nilval,
and may the wisdom of the stars
guide you.
[alert whistles]
MAN: I'm getting a transmission
from the "Argonaut."
‐ Put it through.
‐ Well,
there you have it, Nilval.
Sorry to leave the battle
so early,
but duty calls.
The princess is trying to draw
as little attention to us
as humanly possible.
If you like,
you can have the honor
of covering our butts
while we warp out
of this little soiree.
‐ All available ships
are to surround the "Argonaut"
immediately.
‐ Humph. Look at you.
Here you are, at the brink
of the most dangerous mission
of your career,
and you're smiling
like a daydreamer.
‐ I'm a very happy man
right now.
Setting sail
for the great unknown,
pitting my wits
against the universe‐‐
who wouldn't be smiling?
MAN: Recharge complete.
Warp course confirmed.
WOMAN: Establishing link.
‐ Pleasure serving with you.
Over and out.
♪ ♪
WOMAN:
Horoscope acquisition confirmed.
♪ ♪
Suspending temporal functions.
All sails down.
Dimensional ripper activated.
♪ ♪
Max warp!
[shimmering and tinkling]
[debris shuffling]
[space roaring]
‐ The fifth Nodos...
he is frenzied.
Artemia.
Has Mehitak, too, gone mad?
Lernaea moves.
Will you fight
before fully regenerating,
Karkinos?
YUTY:
This is unacceptable, Lecty.
A frenzied Nodos raging
through the galaxy unchecked.
The three of you must put a stop
to this before it's too late.
We cannot allow
for more worlds to be lost.
‐ By fighting him
in such a state,
we risk subjecting ourselves
to the same madness.
The devastation
would be immeasurable.
And the one most likely to die
is Karkinos.
‐ What did you say?
‐ It is a possibility.
The likelihood is inferred
in his contract.
If the Golden Tribe could indeed
foresee the future‐‐
‐ The Golden Tribe
only predicted
the number of Labors
in each contract.
We are fools to surmise
anything else from them.
‐ But Yuty, they were told
of the Iron Tribe.
They knew
they would discover the fifth.
‐ Karkinos is able to regenerate
from fatal wounds.
Therefore, he is,
for all intents and purposes,
immortal.
A creature of that power
has to be subjugated.
Just think about it.
This contract must deceive
in order to be effective.
‐ Even so,
what if all of us go mad?
YUTY: Do not be concerned
with your own safety.
Leave that to me.
LECTY: I... understand.
If such is the will
of the Silver Tribe,
I shall obey.
♪ ♪
‐ If the four of them
succumb to the frenzy,
you will not hesitate
to abolish them.
‐ [gasps]
‐ If I did not think you
beyond such crude emotion,
I might read
a suggestion of dread
in that expression.
‐ No. Not at all, sir.
♪ ♪
[epic orchestral music]
[Bellcross roaring]
♪ ♪
MAN: We're obeying at our peril.
MAN: There is no hope
that we shall survive
the ruin that falls in his wake.
‐ Victory is at hand.
I feel it.
MAN: We must withdraw.
MAN: We have no other choice.
‐ So be it.
♪ ♪
[Artemia cries out]
[Artemia moans]
♪ ♪
[shimmering and tinkling]
‐ All right!
Now, let's show
this ugly bastard
what it means to tangle
with the Yunos Knights!
We've got to try
and hold this monster at bay.
We can't let him get to Age
before the princess!
♪ ♪
YUTY: What are you doing?
It's only the Iron Tribe.
Why aren't you
assisting Karkinos?
And why haven't you evoked
the power of Erymanthos?
Go back, and destroy their ship.
‐ I... I tried to,
and I can't.
‐ Huh?
‐ Erymanthos traveled
into the past
and obliterated
the Iron Tribe's ship
many times over.
But each time,
upon witnessing it,
the fifth's rage only grew.
No matter what path I chose,
Karkinos, Mehitak, and I
all perished
horribly.
Each time,
only the fifth survived.
‐ [gasps]
‐ In the end,
I had to spare the ship
in order to save us.
It was the only way.
Things have to remain
as they are.
Every other possibility
will lead
only to our eventual
destruction,
because the only ones
who can stop him
are on board that ship.
♪ ♪
[liquid squishing]
‐ [gasps]
It can't be.
Why?
You knew... and yet...
♪ ♪
You fought... for us...
all alone.
♪ ♪
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me, my friend.
♪ ♪
I treated you like a slave,
expecting Bellcross to emerge
whenever he was needed
and not thinking
of what it might do to you.
I made you protect all of us!
You only wanted to please me.
Oh, Age...
I'm so sorry!
My friend.
[gasps]
[Bellcross roars]
Age!
‐ Mehitak and Artemia have lost.
If he lives,
bring him back to me.
‐ Mm...
‐ Let what we have seen here
instruct our next move.
‐ Oh, Mehitak.
‐ What the...
‐ Lecty, what happened?
Was Mehitak able
to calm his rage?
‐ We must return
to Rom Ror's home planet.
‐ And Mehitak?
‐ He has waited a long time
to come face‐to‐face
with a being
that could defeat Artemia
in battle.
We can only hope that now,
freed from his obligation
to the Silver Tribe,
he will be at peace.
‐ Come.
We must leave now.
You and I have contracts
of our own.
[ethereal chiming]
‐ [gasps]
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
[woman singing in Japanese]
‐ Thank you...
Dhianeila.
‐ [gasps]
♪ ♪
‐ I didn't know where I was.
I couldn't see anything.
There was darkness everywhere.
Then I saw a light.
♪ ♪
You know what?
That light was you.
♪ ♪
‐ Oh, Age.
For me, Age,
you are the light.
You always have been.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
A dark crossroads,
upon which destinies
are forged or broken,
demands a choice be made.
Next time on "Heroic Age,"
episode 16,
"Overcoming the Fates."