[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ [gasps]
I don't know what's happening.
Where is he?
Where is Age?
♪ ♪
Why would he do this?
Something so horrific.
Those fools.
I will be coming with you.
Make preparations
for the "Argonaut"
to move out immediately.
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
[both grunting]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
LECTY: For all his strength,
he remains vulnerable
to the will of time.
Erymanthos can defeat him.
It requires only
that the correct path be found.
That's it!
Go back 70 seconds.
The past be rewritten!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[high‐pitched ringing]
That wasn't it.
[wind howling]
YUTY: All that must be done
is to arrest
the fifth's progress.
Why is that so difficult
for you, Karkinos?
[Bellcross growls]
LECTY: Perhaps...
Ugh!
‐ Lecty!
‐ Don't worry.
♪ ♪
‐ Jeez.
She's made so many jumps.
[gasps]
‐ Just a bit more.
The divergence must be there
somewhere.
A path where he alone perishes.
[device beeping]
‐ [grunts]
‐ Brother, the remaining fleets
have been assembled
as per your orders.
The Silver Tribe's forces
have yet to reemerge.
We believe they have retreated
to the Starway's
nearest accessible
terminal point.
‐ So they're scared.
And our special tool?
‐ It seems he's still fighting
the enemy Nodos.
‐ It's been 30 hours now.
He's a demon.
Give the order for all fleets
to continue pushing forward!
We shall advance along the path
that our Nodos has cleared away
for us.
The god of war will be the spoil
of his own auspices!
‐ Because
of Jupiter's destruction,
the Starway has default‐linked
to Mars.
It appears to have stabilized.
‐ It leveled off
because the distance
between the two planets
is more or less
easily traversable.
‐ Every last ship could've been
set adrift otherwise, ma'am.
‐ Otherwise?
Hell, we've been cut off
from the fleet behind us.
For all intents and purposes,
we are adrift.
‐ We've just received the order
that the entire fleet
is to move toward Mars.
‐ I can't believe it.
The enemy is out of sight
for a moment,
and those two morons
are breaking out the champagne.
‐ It's obvious
that the Silver Tribe
is preparing to pounce.
Perhaps it would be prudent
to advise His Highness
to proceed with caution.
‐ Good luck
getting him to listen.
Meleagros is counting on Age
to do all the hard work.
‐ If that's the case,
then what happened to Jupiter
may well befall Mars
before long.
‐ Believe me.
He's not worried in the least.
Earth itself will become
a battlefield
before he sees reason.
That is, unless...
I manage to seize command
from him.
♪ ♪
The god of joy has died.
When will our star awake?
[shimmering and tinkling]
[explosion booms]
[indistinct nervous chatter]
‐ This is madness!
♪ ♪
[alarm blaring]
[device beeps]
MOBEEDO: Aneasha.
‐ What is it, Captain?
MOBEEDO: Representatives
from Planets Colonus and Orion
are requesting
an audience with the princess.
‐ Tell them I'm coming.
♪ ♪
MAN: The people of Colonus
consider it a great honor
to host someone
of your eminence,
Princess Dhianeila.
‐ I must express
my deepest gratitude
to Colonus and Orion
for granting us safe harbor
on such short notice.
My people
are eternally in your debt.
‐ Highness, you're too kind.
Your ability to find a path
in even
the galaxy's darkest corner
is a godsend.
You have no idea
what it means to us.
‐ Coming to the "Argonaut"'s aid
in a time of such great need
is the very least we can do.
Your vision will lead
this galaxy to freedom.
‐ If there is anything more
that we may do
to help the cause,
you have but to ask,
and it will be done, Princess.
‐ My heartfelt thanks to you.
[shimmering and tinkling]
MAN:
The Iron Tribe moves forward.
They intend to reclaim Mars.
‐ Let us end this now.
‐ [gasps]
This planet will become
a battleground.
[shimmering and tinkling]
Another world will die.
LECTY: We will stop him
before that happens.
[both growling]
[explosion booms]
[Lernaea groans]
[glass shatters]
YUTY:
What are the two of you doing?
[intense music]
♪ ♪
‐ Lecty!
LECTY: Why can't I find it?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
It has to exist.
The continuum cannot exclude
his death.
♪ ♪
[glass shatters]
[explosion booms]
MAN: The Nodos draws closer.
MAN:
The Starway will lead him to us.
‐ All four Nodos
fighting together.
MAN:
A devastating frenzy may result.
‐ Going back 70 seconds
won't work.
‐ Why not?
‐ He's too enmeshed,
too integral to this time point,
but if only‐‐
if only I can jump back
a little further...
‐ Don't push yourself.
I can take care of him.
‐ No, Mehitak.
I will not let you fight.
Further still, Erymanthos!
We must use
every last modicum of our power!
♪ ♪
[insects fluttering]
[electricity sizzles]
♪ ♪
LECTY: Impossible.
His presence
in the space‐time continuum
cannot be absolute.
♪ ♪
PROME: Doubt is a shadow
that is completely foreign
to the fifth's nature.
And the 12 Labors
of the Iron Tribe
are a fire
which his heart has forged.
Why would such certainty
of purpose be bestowed upon him?
ROM: We are being tested.
The enemy's fortitude
is a bulwark
against which to prove our own.
The Golden Tribe
would make masters of us.
PROME: Be that as it may,
in his fury,
the fifth tears this galaxy
asunder.
If he continues unbridled...
we will surely see desolation
that is truly heroic.
IOLAOUS: It looks like
most of our backup units
are reforming the line.
If we're going to get out,
it has to be now!
‐ Not yet. There are still
a few stragglers out there.
We'll wait for them.
‐ The longer we sit here,
the longer Age continues
to fight on our behalf
without even a unit ship
to watch his back.
This is disgraceful!
‐ If we move out now,
Meleagros will force us
to join the offensive.
What good would that do Age?
‐ Master, an incoming
transmission for you.
Lieutenant General Nilval
has informed us
that the fleet will move
towards Mars again
at 1900 hours.
‐ That's absurd!
‐ The situation is dire,
Princess.
Your brother is spreading Age
too thin.
If he keeps this up,
he not only stands
to jeopardize Mars
but Earth as well,
to say nothing
of the shape our forces are in
thanks to him.
DHIANEILA:
That he could be so blind,
even after
annihilating Jupiter...
‐ We need to reorganize. Now.
Princess,
I implore you to take action.
For all our sakes.
[footsteps rustle]
‐ [gasps]
‐ Your Highness, please.
‐ Aneasha... how can I?
‐ I want you to have faith
in yourself.
That's all.
‐ Ugh...
‐ Lecty!
‐ [panting]
I can't.
This is my 18,000th defeat.
It is hopeless.
‐ It's not! You have to let me
fight alongside Karkinos!
‐ I forbid you!
‐ [gasps]
‐ Hear me.
If the fifth engages
two Nodos in battle,
he will be bound
to succumb to...
‐ Frenzy.
‐ In
their uncontrollable frenzy,
the Heroic Tribe
once brought this galaxy
to the brink
of total destruction.
Only the Golden Tribe possess
the power to stop them.
‐ But then... at this rate...
‐ Do not fear.
Erymanthos and I will succeed.
The divergence will be found.
It exists.
It must.
We will explore every option.
Each point.
‐ Be careful.
‐ Trust me, my friend.
♪ ♪
[Bellcross growling]
YUTY: Karkinos!
The fifth is attacking
far too quickly.
Lernaea doesn't have time
to regenerate!
You have to let me go out there.
Please! As long as Karkinos
is able to fight,
I must help him.
‐ You will not.
‐ I beg you!
‐ You appear
to be frustrated, Yuty.
[Yuty gasps]
♪ ♪
YUTY: Frustrated?
No. Emotion is beneath me.
LECTY: What?
‐ [gasps]
‐ I've reached
the limit of the continuum.
All points are fixed.
That's impossible.
Different timelines
are starting to converge.
This is... this is well beyond
my power to contain.
‐ What... what is it?
What is going on?
‐ I've jumped
far too many times.
Erymanthos has linked
every alternative
for the culmination
of this battle.
The potential energy
of every outcome
will accumulate,
imploding
into the first timeline
to give way.
♪ ♪
[Bellcross growling]
[electricity crackling]
Ugh!
[groans]
[cries out]
‐ Take my hand!
‐ Run away, Mehitak!
Run away!
Right now!
[explosion booms]
[high‐pitched shrieking]
[distant roaring]
DHIANEILA: Age...
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
A terrifying change
comes over Bellcross‐‐
the beginnings of madness...
and death.
Next time on "Heroic Age,"
episode 14,
"The Raging One."