DHIANEILA:
Before they vanished,
the Golden Tribe told my people
to go forth,
and by leaving the Starway,
I fell that we are.
PROME O:
Stars are not always born
from the mysterious powers
that flow through the universe.
‐ Stars can also be born
from the power of lives
interacting
through the galaxies.
‐ Filling the universe
with Starways.
‐ I am certain there is
because I have witnessed it.
I think that must be
why I met Age.
["Gravitation" by Angela]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
[ethereal music]
WOMAN: I trust you,
the one who guides the stars
beyond the Starway.
I will share with you
the memory
that I have kept close
all this time.
Only you can find this planet,
Dhianeila.
The home world
of the Golden Tribe.
‐ Elysium.
[gasps]
‐ Princess.
‐ I'm fine, Iolaous.
‐ You may find our memories
overwhelming.
Just try to keep your mind
clear of thoughts.
And now, please open your heart
to the memory.
‐ [growls]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ [screams]
‐ Mehitak, no!
‐ It is foolish to continue
to listen to their conversation.
The idea that the power
of the Golden Tribe
is hidden on an archaic planet
somewhere is nothing but a myth.
ROM: But you have no proof
to dispel the idea.
‐ They abandoned our kind
in this galaxy
without explanation.
Why would they leave clues?
‐ I understand your concern,
but that has nothing to do
with whether or not
their power exists.
‐ Rom Ror has a point.
The Golden Tribe betrayed us.
‐ But we do not know
their true intentions.
‐ Let us allow them to continue
their conversation.
‐ I agree.
‐ We must be patient.
‐ There's no need for you
to worry, young man.
They are only hoping
to witness
a reconciliation
with the Iron Tribe.
My people are eager to establish
order in the universe.
Can you feel it, Dhianeila?
The place where the Golden Tribe
first appeared in this galaxy.
Experience the memory,
the memory of Elysium,
known as the coffin of wisdom.
DHIANEILA:
I can feel something far away.
It's very faint.
It is a memory,
passed down
from a long time ago.
‐ It appears that I was correct
in selecting you, Dhianeila.
It's as though
I've held onto these memories
and emotions for you alone.
Perhaps my sole purpose
of existence is to aid you
in finding your future.
It appears our conversation
continues to garner
support from my kind.
‐ So that means‐‐
‐ While we are still in need
of further negotiations,
you and your people have
escaped destruction for now.
But know, the only reason we are
being lenient with your people
is to see if you can
in fact
recover the power
of the Golden Tribe.
Keep in mind, a faction exists
within our tribe
which does not believe
you can accomplish this task,
and they will try
to stop you.
I am certain that Rom Ror
will give chase
as you head
to the planet Elysium,
along with the Nodos
he has under his control.
And understand that if you fail
to find your way to Elysium,
or if you make it there
only to find that the power
of the Golden Tribe
no longer exists,
it is possible that my kind may
once again turn against you
and renew their desire
to destroy the Iron Tribe.
‐ I understand, however,
I honestly believe
that the power
of the Golden Tribe does exist
somewhere in this universe,
and I believe we can find it.
‐ I wish I could share your
certainty, Princess Dhianeila.
I truly do,
but the prophesies that tell
of the existence
of the Golden Tribe's power
are dishearteningly vague.
‐ And are not the Labors
of the Nodos a path
for all of the inhabitants
of this universe?
We must have faith and follow
that path into the future.
There lies hope for us all.
That is what I have
always believed.
‐ A path?
The future?
I've always wondered
if that could be the case,
if the Labors of the five Nodos
could tell the future.
‐ Right, and if we give up now,
we'll never get to see it.
We won't have a future
if we don't do something.
‐ We should attempt to find it,
the best possible future.
‐ That's what I believe.
Don't you agree?
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
‐ I am so glad that I met
with you, Dhianeila.
‐ I feel the same.
Thank you, Prome.
After meeting you
everything seems so clear.
It all makes sense to me now.
The power to find a path
and to create Starways
exists within everyone.
‐ I don't understand.
‐ You alone have carried
the burden of the Silver Tribe
all this time.
You have shown your people
the way
by holding your ground and
doing what you feel is right.
I do the same.
I lead my people
along what I feel is
the right path.
I think it's possible
that eventually,
my people will awaken
to the same power that I have
within themselves, and if that
were to happen, maybe‐‐
‐ Our lives would be
connected
and we'll be able to interact
even between the planets.
‐ That will become the power
to create Starways.
‐ And this universe will be
filled with Starways.
‐ I think that was
the true intention
of the Golden Tribe.
That is what they wanted
this universe to become.
♪ ♪
‐ We have been betrayed.
That girl knows nothing
of the Golden Tribe.
How could they possibly
believe her?
PROME O:
Deep in distance memories
I recall an action
called "pray."
Though I have attempted it,
I have yet to find
what it is I have been
praying for.
However,
I have not given up.
If I were to express how I feel
about the situation,
I think "praying" would be
the appropriate word.
Dhianeila, I pray that you will
safely guide your people
to the planet Elysium,
and I pray that once there,
you will find the power
of the Golden Tribe.
‐ I thank you
from the bottom of my heart.
Thank you for your kindness
and sharing your ages
of wisdom with me.
And most of all,
I thank you for believing
in the power
of possibilities.
‐ Look, it's Dhianeila.
‐ We're so glad you came back.
‐ Oh, thank goodness.
‐ Did everything go smoothly,
Princess?
‐ Thanks to Iolaous, yes.
Um, Iolaous.
‐ [grunts]
‐ I'm sure the princess
is exhausted.
Do you mind giving her a break
for a little while?
‐ Uh, excuse me, Princess.
‐ [chuckles]
‐ And Iolaous?
‐ Huh?
‐ Thanks for your help.
‐ Ah.
‐ I need to start
my meditation now.
‐ But don't you think you should
get some rest first?
‐ I appreciate you concern,
but no.
There isn't any time.
I must find the path
to Planet Elysium soon.
I don't have a choice.
This could well be
our only chance to end this war,
to make the Silver Tribe
our allies.
MOBEEDO: Eventually,
the princess will begin
to lead us
towards the home planet
of the Golden Tribe,
a place called Elysium.
I have no way of knowing
how long
this journey's going to take,
but I hope we make it back.
I hate to leave you
with this
on top of reorganizing
the fleet,
but my hands are tied.
Please take care of the fleet
in my absence.
Thanks, Nilval.
We recorded
her entire conversation
with the Silver Tribe, right?
‐ Yes, of course, master.
‐ I want you to transmit it
to the fleet,
then send it to Nilval
along with the message
I just recorded.
‐ Understood, sir.
‐ Elysium.
An ancient planet that has
lost its Starway.
Could it really hold
the lost power
of the Golden Tribe?
Please show us the way,
Princess.
Guide us towards our future
at the end of this journey.
LECTY:
They're searching for Elysium?
Does that mean their
conversation was a success?
I don't understand it.
Is the Iron Tribe
actually going to try and find
the Planet of the Dawn?
Prome O, you've always believed
there was a possibility,
and now it may become reality.
I should have faith in you,
yet I can't help by question.
How can we ever hope
to put an end to this war?
‐ [roars]
[military music]
♪ ♪
‐ Age, I can sense you.
I can feel how hard you're
fighting to win this battle.
I'm focusing all of my energy
on moving forward,
just like you told me to.
I know that you'll come
back to us eventually.
MOBEEDO: The princess has found
our projected path.
It may take several cycles
to get there.
We will now leave the Starway
and follow
the princess's guidance.
Our final destination is
the planet Elysium.
Let's go. While Age is
distracting the enemy,
we have the perfect opportunity
to follow the princess
without being detected.
Now, men! Go!
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
‐ Artemia has managed
to escape the frenzy,
thanks to the exhaustion
of its own power,
but at this rate,
both Kervius and Belcross
are in danger
of falling victim.
Time is running out.
This has to be settled soon.
Lernaea.
‐ [roars]
‐ No, Karkinos!
She won't help.
But why?
Yuty.
Does she not see that Karkinos
is right there with her?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ [roars]
‐ [screams]
‐ The frenzy.
At this rate,
Kervius will do down first.
Erymanthos, let's go!
‐ [roars]
[dramatic music]
‐ One more time.
♪ ♪
‐ [screeches]
‐ Mehitak!
Please forgive me.
‐ [roars]
[roars]
‐ Karkinos.
‐ [grunts]
[roars]
[roar echoes]
‐ Yuty.
[dramatic music]
‐ [roars]
‐ No!
♪ ♪
‐ [roars]
‐ Let's go!
Now, Erymanthos!
‐ Age.
[sad music]
♪ ♪
‐ Everyone is gone.
They're all gone.
Karkinos.
["Azurite" by Tae Urakabe]
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
WOMAN:
Yuty continues to suffer.
What is the force
that drives such hatred?
Next time on "Heroic Age,"
episode 12, "The Four."