[gasps]
[SAKAIDO]
Huh?
[screaming]
The hell is this?
What happened to me?
[SAKAIDO (M1)] How did I
get broken into pieces?
Does this mean I'm dead?
[SAKAIDO (M2)]
Is this what death is like?
[SAKAIDO (M1)]
I feel like I'm alive, but--
[SAKAIDO (M2)]
But how can I be alive?
I've been chopped into bits.
[SAKAIDO (M1)]
Who am I?
--[SAKAIDO (M2)] Who am I?
--[SAKAIDO (M1)] Who am I?!
[SAKAIDO (M2)]
I've got no clue.
Don't even know my own name.
[SAKAIDO]
Shit!
[SAKAIDO] I'm in pieces,
but they're connected.
Was I broken just so I could
put myself back together?
Who would do that to me?
I'm making too many assumptions.
For all I know,
I came apart on my own.
I can't even be sure that
putting myself back together
is the right thing to do.
[SAKAIDO]
No, this is right.
I'm not supposed
to be in pieces.
[SAKAIDO]
Well, it isn't perfect,
but I seem to be more
or less functional.
At least for now.
[SAKAIDO]
What's with this place?
[yells]
[SAKAIDO] "I'm in pieces,
but they're connected."
There's a thought to cling to.
Hang on.
I'd better not be expected
to rebuild this whole world.
Couldn't even complete myself.
[SAKAIDO] There I go making
assumptions again.
Is it ridiculous to think
that I've been given
a role to play in this world?
[SAKAIDO]
'Scuse me!
Sorry to bother you, but could
ya tell me where we are?
Hey! D'ya hear me?
Look, I just have
some questions.
Like how did this world end up
getting smashed into pieces?
[SAKAIDO] To me, it's not right
that this world is in pieces.
Any more than it was
right when I was.
The word broken comes to mind.
[SAKAIDO]
I don't know if there's a point
to using the door
in a world like this,
but hey, why not?
That's Kaeru.
[SAKAIDO] I don't know this
girl, but I do know her name.
It's Kaeru.
And somehow, seeing her
and remembering her name
has helped me to remember
more about myself.
I know my name too now.
It's Sakaido.
[SAKAIDO]
Still don't know my full name,
but that's irrelevant.
All that matters is this:
I do have a part to
play in this world.
I'm the brilliant detective.
And I'm here to solve the
mystery of Kaeru's death.
Inspector Momoki, it looks
like Sakaido's awake now.
So he finally survived
the fall into the bedroom.
How's the id well?
[TOGO]
It's stable, sir.
Good. You'll all be
assigned as follows.
Macro analysis: Togo,
assisted by Kokufu.
Times and places: Shiratake.
Human analysis: Habutae.
And Wakashika will try
to make deductions
about the murder.
This battle's just beginning,
and it won't end until
Sakaido solves the case.
Till then, we'll scour
everything we see
for details about
the Perforator.
Remember that this is the
world of his drive to kill.
Everything has meaning.
[ALL]
Sir!
[SAKAIDO] Not only was the door
locked from the inside,
the window was as well.
She can't have stabbed
herself in the chest. Heh.
This isn't a period drama.
It's a classic
locked room mystery.
[SAKAIDO] Or it would be if
the room wasn't missing a wall.
What do I do now?
Puzzles are meant to be solved.
I can assume that much.
And something tells
me that my left arm
is still like this for a reason.
[TOGO]
Sakaido is on the move.
He's entering a room.
Let's expect a data surge.
Everyone be ready.
Well, this is interestin.
All the books appear to be real.
Any rare volumes?
A fair number of them are
out of print at least.
I can't see any rare enough
that would allow us
to track an individual.
Habutae, who's in the pictures?
[HABUTAE]
Beginning analysis.
[SAKAIDO] Is this the
family that lives here?
[HABUTAE] They're all actors
or pro tennis players.
Successful enough
to be known to most.
Odds are, the killer's
only aware of them
through TV and the internet.
That said, with a framed
picture taken in that style,
you'd assume these people
were friends or family.
In the real world,
you'd be right.
But the id well is a product
of the unconscious mind.
Anything goes in there.
Logic takes a backseat.
[TOGO]
Look at this calendar.
The dates and days of
the week match up perfectly.
That's just what March
of 2019 looked like.
Why would someone recall that?
There's a lot of variation
in human memory.
Could something significant
have happened during that month?
There's no telling as of yet.
Exactly.
When drawing information
from the id well,
we should avoid
jumping to conclusions.
All information is valuable,
but we needn't assign meaning
to everything we find.
Meaning will rise to the
surface on its own in time.
[HONDOMACHI]
The id well.
I can't believe that such
detailed knowledge and memories
can be hidden in a world formed
out of murderous impulse.
Try to focus, okay, Hondomachi?
Look at how the well-side
staff do their work.
Understood, Mr. Matsuoka.
But just to be sure
I'm following,
that image in the
center of the room
was generated by
the Mizuhanome, right?
It's the world of this
Perforator's urge to kill?
[MATSUOKA]
Yes.
As of this moment,
we've located five of
the Perforator's victims.
At the scene of
each of his crimes,
we collected his
cognition particles.
It's odd.
Trepanation is such a precise,
meticulous method of killing.
Yet his drive to kill created
this chaotic, jigsaw world.
[MATSUOKA]
There is a disconnect.
But that happens.
Method does not define motive.
The urge to kill is primal.
Conscious thought
about how to kill
comes from a whole different
part of the psyche.
I'm curious about what it would
be like to go inside a well.
You?
[MATSUOKA]
Hell no.
You can only enter an id well
if you've killed someone.
Furthermore, it takes
a special aptitude
to perform as the
brilliant detective.
Huh?
[MATSUOKA]
Think about it.
As you said, that world
is the manifestation
of a murderer's drive to kill.
For a detective to do well
in that type of setting,
they've gotta have
some loose screws.
[TOGO]
That calendar was a lucky break.
The letters are faint,
but it definitely bears
the name "Fujita's Wares."
It looks like there's
an address as well.
[MOMOKI]
Matsuoka.
[HONDOMACHI]
Got the address!
[MATSUOKA] Then it's time for us
field analysts to get to work.
Let's go.
[MOMOKI]
Heads up.
This next room
has people inside.
Hello. I'm coming in.
A visitor, huh?
Hello, sir.
You're welcome here.
Make yourself at home.
Do come in.
I believe you're
our first visitor.
[SAKAIDO]
I see.
So all of you live
here, that right?
Yeah.
We are family.
Kenta Obara. Wataru Takada.
Eiko Imanishi. Yoshito Fujita.
Masami Kitamura.
Those five match. They're
victims of the Perforator.
I'm looking up the last two!
Man, that's sick.
He's forcing all of his victims
to stay under the same roof
and make believe like
they're a family?
Don't lose your head.
This is just a product
of his psyche.
Though I do believe
it has significance.
Hey, Inspector, I got facial
matches for the last two guys
in the database
of missing persons.
Yuji Oonuki and Haruka Kazuta.
So then, are those
two already dead?
We don't know that.
She's right.
The report for Yuji Oonuki
wasn't filed until yesterday.
And from what we know
about the Perforator,
he tends to keep
his victims confined
for several days
before killing them.
So these guys may well be alive.
[HABUTAE]
Um.
Look, I didn't initially
recognize this image as a face,
and I don't think
Sakaido noticed it either,
but I see someone's reflection.
I'll send you the image now.
[gasps]
[MOMOKI]
John Walker. Can't be.
This guy had contact
with John Walker, too?
[OONUKI'S MOM crying]
Yeah, I just got confirmation.
She confirmed his
identity for us.
The young man with the missing
mouth was Yuji Oonuki.
[MATSUOKA]
That "Fujita's Wares" place
off the calendar is closed.
The building's vacant.
But we're just 15 minutes from
the Oonuki residence on foot.
We'll retrace the steps Oonuki
took on the day of his abduction
and look out for any
cognition particles.
[MOMOKI]
Good.
It's possible that
you'll be entering
the Perforator's hunting ground.
Exercise extreme caution.
You know that I can
drive, right?
Just because you
have your license
doesn't mean I'm
letting a rookie drive.
Now focus.
You need to keep your eyes
trained on the Wakumusubi.
[HONDOMACHI]
The Wakumusubi.
It's strange.
To think that this machine
can glean a person's
murderous intent.
So, uh,
you know how "ido" is the
Japanese word for well?
I was thinking, if we call
these otherworlds
the Mizuhanome
creates "id wells,"
is that like a bilingual dad
joke or just a coincidence?
It isn't just a dad
joke. It's fate.
How do you mean?
[MATSUOKA] The kanji for
"ido" can also mean
"other" and "earth."
Put those together, and...
[HONDOMACHI]
You get "otherworld."
When words intersect in
that many ways, ya use 'em.
[MAN C]
So who is this girl?
[WOMAN A]
I've never seen her before.
[MAN D] She certainly isn't
a member of our family.
She's a visitor. Barged in
the same way you did.
Is it okay to come in uninvited
just 'cause the door's unlocked?
Of course it's not okay.
[OONUKI]
That said,
you think there's something
wrong with her?
[MAN D]
Hmm. Yeah, you're right.
It's more like there's something
wrong with this freaky world,
if you ask me.
[SAKAIDO] Silly of me to
think that these people
would question the
world they live in.
But as the brilliant detective,
that's precisely my job.
I have to question
everything about this world.
It's moving.
The pieces will fall
into place soon.
What's with you, Sakaido?
You're the brilliant detective,
so why'd you leave
the damn crime scene?
That open locked room
wasn't solved yet.
The killer could've gotten
Kaeru in a number of ways.
We can't do anything if you
don't give us more material.
[WAKASHIKA]
Hey, Kokufu,
I need you to take the
part he just completed
and turn it
90 degrees clockwise.
[SAKAIDO]
Well, look at that.
No idea what it means,
but it's a start.
Seems the parts of this
world that are missing
are more significant than
the parts that are present.
But these meaningful voids
don't just make
their presence known.
Guess it's more of
an absence actually.
But the only way to find them
is to work on the puzzle
and look at the larger picture.
"Takoya," huh?
What could that mean?
We've got a font match with
Takoyaki House Pot Octopus!
There are four
locations in Chuuou
and one in Choufu as well.
That's the same neighborhood
as the address
from the calendar, right?
[MOMOKI]
Matsuoka's right next to it.
An assault team will
arrive in five minutes.
Stand by till then.
Mr. Matsuoka. Check it out.
It looks like these characters
are slightly tilted.
Oh, yeah?
[HONDOMACHI] For the sign
to look the same... hmm...
...you'd have to be
standing to the side.
What is this?
Think this is it.
I've got a reading.
It's Matsuoka.
We found our particles.
Pattern matches the Perforator.
Thanks for telling me.
The Wakumusubi link
beat you to it, though.
It's already affecting
things in the well.
[SAKAIDO] Looks like the world
is breaking apart again.
Huh.
Guess "broken" is just
the natural state
of everything in this world.
Except for Kaeru?
This reading.
Unless I'm mistaken,
it's supposed to reflect
a fresh urge to kill.
He's kidnapped two
people, hasn't he?
If this reading is correct,
then he might be about to
kill them as we speak!
What do we do?
[MATSUOKA]
Stay here. Wait for backup.
No!
Not when two people
just within our reach
are about to be murdered!
[MATSUOKA]
Pipe down.
I'm going in.
Stay put, Matsuoka.
Help is coming.
We've got information
on the house's occupant.
Name: Tamotsu Fukuda.
Age 33. No family.
That's--
Against regulations,
I'm well aware.
Just wait in the car for
the assault team, okay?
[SHIRATAKE]
The world's breaking apart.
It's less stable than ever.
He kills by drilling a precise
hole through the victim's head.
Yet his drive to kill
is a chaotic mess.
[sirens wailing]
[OONUKI]
Who are you?
What do you want with me?
[OONUKI]
Stop! Please stop!
Don't do this. Please!
No! No!
Damn it. No!
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER A]
He's still breathing, sir!
Medic! We need a
stretcher down here!
[SAKAIDO]
This is a fragmented world.
So for the locals,
it's natural to be in pieces.
I'm not even whole myself.
But... aside from
the blood she's lost,
Kaeru's all put together.
She should have missing
parts like the rest of us.
And I know why she doesn't.
Hey. I know you're there.
Get out of her body, right now!
What's he doing?
[SAKAIDO]
Huh.
He did it. Sakaido has
tracked down Kaeru's killer.
[SAKAIDO]
Now what? Do I arrest him?
Are police even a thing
in this world?
If they've got prisons here,
I hope they come with more walls
than that locked room had.
Heh. Tough luck, buddy.
You can't really catch
him from the well.
And we couldn't find
him from up here.
The brilliant detective
doesn't actually
have to arrest the
criminal himself.
He just needs to solve the case.
Inspector Momoki, would you
like me to eject Sakaido?
No. Wait.
Hey. An eighth
person showed up.
There were just seven victims
before, but there's a new one.
Once you finish
solving the case,
we would appreciate it if you'd
leave our house for good.
You're new.
We know that girl.
Yeah, she was with
the Field Analyst Unit!
So how did she
show up in there?
Matsuoka. You copy?
Hondomachi! Hey! Talk to me!
Damn it, Hondomachi!
Where the hell are you?