[EMPLOYEE B]
Huh?
Who's that?
Excuse me! You don't
have access to be here.
[EMPLOYEES gasp]
The hell?
It appears she's
melting realities
faster than I expected.
Not good.
Huh?
A leak?
[ENGINEER A gasps]
[ENGINEER A]
Are those sharks?
[EMPLOYEES yell]
[gasps]
[EMPLOYEE C]
Uh, where are we--?
This is...
[BOTH gasp]
[INAMI]
Wait. What is this place?
[GUARD B]
I don't know.
Just stay close to me for now.
[HONDOMACHI] Assistant
Director Togo! Do you copy?
Something's very wrong.
Sit down! Who gave you
permission to stand?
[HONDOMACHI gasps]
[HONDOMACHI]
Chief Hayaseura!
Bastard!
Mister Narihisago!
What's going on here sir?
Everything's fine. Remain calm.
[HONDOMACHI]
No! Don't!
None of this makes sense, sir.
He's John Walker!
Arrest him, you idiot!
Sorry for shooting you.
You may not believe this,
but I do sincerely regret
having to involve you
and ruin your life.
And while you have every
right to kill me,
sadly, I must do it myself.
[gunshots]
[chuckles]
[HAYASEURA] It's a bit
awkward confessing this
to the three of you,
but the truth is,
I've never in my life
actually killed anyone.
[HAYASEURA]
I am an officer of the law.
Although you may
not be convinced,
I possess my own
sense of justice.
In accordance with that,
I'm turning the Kura
into a giant Mizuhanome.
That way we'll be
able to investigate
on a much larger scale.
Then I plan to retire.
Momoki will be my successor.
[NARIHISAGO]
You call any of this justice?
I made the Kura, used it to
catch numerous serial killers,
and yes, I'm responsible
for creating some.
But look what it's accomplished.
The world will realize
it was the moral choice,
and the benefits far
outweighed the costs.
Only one thing left.
Some may see this as
drastic, but to me...
...it's my atonement.
[HONDOMACHI, NARIHISAGO gasp]
[NARIHISAGO]
Dammit.
Some atonement!
He's going to live on in his
well as a brilliant detective.
I don't think you should be
doing this after getting shot.
It's fine. I'll stop
him if it kills me.
[HONDOMACHI]
Fukuda, come with us!
What?
I think I'll pass.
[NARIHISAGO] Move him outta
the way and dive in.
[FUKUDA]
Okay, fine.
[FUKUDA sighs]
You know, I'm getting
real tired of all the--
[URAIDO]
This is Kaeru.
And my name is Uraido.
I'm the brilliant detective
who will solve the
mystery of her death.
Seems I was the one who
killed her. Hilarious!
[laughing]
[URAIDO]
Obviously the little bitch
made it easy to solve her murder
because she wanted me to be free
to uncover the larger
secret of this world.
[URAIDO] Upon seeing this face,
I remember who I am.
My real name is
Takuhiko Hayaseura.
Under any other circumstance,
that revelation would
cause a well storm
to erupt and trap me.
Unfortunately for her
I'm already dead,
therefore, my id well
won't be updating.
[chuckles]
[URAIDO]
Ah. Exactly as I predicted.
After countless forays
into Kiki Asukai's mind,
she and I practically share
the same unconsciousness.
My id well, the wells I created,
and the ones I've never seen
from serial killers
across the world.
They're all on display
for me to explore.
Great. So now that he's
already solved Kaeru's murder,
what are we s'posed to do?
We surprise him.
No reason to be coy,
brilliant detectives.
Enough with the
cloak and dagger.
[HIJIRIIDO]
He saw us?
[SAKAIDO] More like he expected
we'd be here all along.
[chuckles]
[BOTH gasp]
He's gone.
You sure it's safe?
Not really. I don't
want to do this, but...
[gasps]
[SAKAIDO]
Found you.
Just the two of you? Hm.
Fukuda chose not to dive in.
Heh. As though it matters.
No mask. How'd he--?
If that's one of the
rules of this world,
then any brilliant
detective can do it, too.
Hold on!
[TOGO] Everyone all
right? Any injuries?
[HABUTAE] I'm fine,
but is this even reality?
[TOGO]
It doesn't feel like it.
Then an id well?
I've never seen an id
well like this before.
Not to mention only killers
can go into an id well.
From our clothes, I don't
think that we've been
turned into
brilliant detectives.
And our memories.
There's no sign of Kaeru.
[WAKASHIKA]
You mean Kiki Asukai.
Last we saw her, she was
walking the halls of the Kura.
So if we assume that's the
Mizuhanome's true form...
...then she is the Mizuhanome.
Which explains the
well within the well.
Of course it belonged to her.
[TOGO gasps]
My theory is this is happening
because she was released
from the machine.
Think back to the
hospital incident.
She vanished, then what?
Thirteen nurses
fell into a coma.
Exactly.
What if we're still in wellside,
unconscious and sharing
the same dream,
just like what happened
with the nurses?
[SHIRATAKE]
Uh. Look!
[KOKUFU]
Boulders?
[SHIRATAKE]
I can't tell how close they are!
Close!
We just couldn't really see it
without any point of reference!
Run!
So if we get killed
while we're in here,
do we just wake up
back in the real world?
You got a theory on that?
Excellent question!
So if 4 out of the 13
nurses are still in a coma,
that comes out to a 69% chance
of us exiting this nightmare,
practically 70%!
Wanna test it out?
Think I'll pass! I'm not
too keen on those odds!
[KOKUFU yelling]
[TOGO]
Where are you, Momoki?
Any word from wellside?
Right now, we still don't know
what's really going on in there.
All we have to go by is
this security footage.
Look.
[MOMOKI]
No.
It's happening again.
Again? What do you mean?
Asukai.
Who?
Are you taking about
the missing victims
from the Challenger case?
I had suspicions that she
was kidnapped and used
to develop the Mizuhanome.
I never imagined all this time
she was under our noses.
[MATSUOKA]
This gets stranger and stranger.
You said it.
The Kura has turned into
one giant Mizuhanome.
[MOMOKI]
There's Chief Hayaseura.
Yeah.
He was busy while we were in
shock over the arrest warrant.
Must've entered his own well.
And he intends to live there.
It's pretty obvious
that's his escape plan.
Our options are limited.
We've no choice.
If this phenomenon is being
caused by Kiki Asukai,
we're going to have
to contain her.
Contain? You mean put
her back in a hospital?
No. Inside the Mizuhanome.
Huh?
If I'm being honest,
I don't think there's any
other place she can go.
And how do we do
that? See them?
If we storm the Kura or
get anywhere near her,
we'll end up the same.
[MOMOKI] Simple.
We'll take countermeasures.
The last time this happened,
someone was able to
get in and abduct her.
We'll use the same
method they did.
What is this place?
Stay alert, Hijiriido!
We're gonna need more than
our brilliant detective
skills for this!
[gasps]
[laughs]
An astute observation, indeed.
However, no matter
how brilliant you are,
this place holds a secret
that's beyond you!
[gasps]
[URAIDO]
So I'll ruin the mystery!
Your name is Koharu Hondomachi.
And if you're curious where
we are, this is your id well!
[gasps]
[laughing]
Hijiriido!
Quick, before you're
caught in the storm!
Whatever you do,
don't let him get away!
Go to the lightning well!
Find it and remember
who you are!
What you have to do for
the world, then find me!
[HIJIRIIDO]
I'm not dead.
[FUKUDA chuckles]
Hey, good catch, huh?
I knew you'd make it, Fukuda
[MATSUOKA]
That it?
[MOMOKI]
Yes.
This is the same helmet used
during the hospital incident.
Sort of a prototype Mizuhanome.
'Fraid we're gonna need
to seize this as evidence.
But you can't!
Sir, we should go.
Especially since we don't
have a court order.
Not just yet. Confiscate
their med supply.
Fukuda?
Right here.
[HIJIRIIDO]
Thanks for saving me.
But how'd you remember
the exact number of steps
it took to reach Kaeru?
[FUKUDA] What can I say?
I love and hate numbers.
So, what's the plan?
I'm going after him, of course.
You coming?
Perhaps if I was a
brilliant detective,
but I can't keep up with you
and have no reason to follow.
Plus, I found your drive
to kill quite stunning.
I think I'd enjoy spending
some more time there.
Well, that sounds
a little creepy.
Oh, real quick:
I wanted to get your expert
opinion on something.
How do you feel about seven?
It's not that bad of a number,
though I don't like the
people who're into it.
So pretentious.
What do you mean?
[FUKUDA]
For just a prime number,
it has all this societal and
storytelling weight attached.
People have fallen in love
with it for the wrong reason.
I see. Good to know.
Well, later!
[FUKUDA] Come on!
How could you be so cruel?
Just one hole... and no more.
[HIJIRIIDO]
Fukuda!
[FUKUDA chuckles]
Funny.
I meant to shout out,
"Here's my chance!" just now,
but for some reason,
it all came out wrong.
[HIJIRIIDO]
One hole?
It's my one-track mind. Sorry.
[HIJIRIIDO]
Mind outta the gutter.
What?
Oh, I, uh... wasn't being
crass just now.
[HIJIRIIDO]
Nahoshi Inami.
[FUKUDA chuckles]
It's my turn to give
you my thanks.
I'm so happy that I was
able to save you.
"Here's my chance" to have
two wishes granted.
[HIJIRIIDO]
I'm gonna tell you a secret.
Your scar? I stopped seeing it.
Whenever something's missing,
removed, fragmented,
it doesn't look that way to me.
I see it as complete.
[HIJIRIIDO] That's how...
I managed to find Nahoshi Inami.
It was no coincidence.
[chuckles]
Oh, yeah?
Never got the opportunity
to visit myself,
but I'm sure you would've
liked my id well.
So, you no longer see my hole.
That makes three wishes granted.
And three... is beautiful.
[INAMI chuckles]
[INAMI] You killed my man,
and I killed yours.
Guess we're even now.
[HIJIRIIDO]
He wasn't "my man."
[INAMI] After all this, I think
my wish'll be granted, too.
This mask, it'll let me
see Kazuta, right?
No, don't!
Kazuta.
Hey, Inami. I missed
you so much.
But you really need
to hide right now.
There's a super scary
monster here.
[INAMI chokes]
K... Kazuta...
I always... I loved...
[SAKAIDO]
Hondomachi.
[HIJIRIIDO] You remembered,
didn't you, Narihisago?
I did. Are you okay?
Yeah.
Once we find a way
out of the well,
everyone who lost their life,
do you think their deaths
will be undone?
[SAKAIDO]
Who knows?
But I have a feeling the people
who still have a reason
to come back will.
I really hope that's true.
Me, too.
I'll live. How about you?
For sure.
Hear that, ya
cane-toting bastard?
The brilliant detectives
that you created
are gonna send you
straight to hell!
[HIJIRIIDO]
That's way too dark.
I say we hit him with the
spark of life, instead!
[SAKAIDO]
What?
Fine, we'll go with that then.
[HIJIRIIDO]
All right!
I'm sorry, sir. It'll be a
little tight in the chest.
We couldn't get the size
right on such short notice.
It'll work.
We'll be observing
you the whole time,
monitoring your vitals
from in here.
If you want to track them,
just use the helmet display.
[MOMOKI]
Got it.
It's time.
[MATSUOKA]
Momoki.
What if she refuses to go
back in the Mizuhanome?
So be it. The lives of my
subordinates come first.
[MOMOKI]
You're in charge, Matsuoka.
Right. Good luck in there.
I'll see you soon.