[NARIHISAGO] I've never
seen this building before,
but... must be my apartment.
[NARIHISAGO]
Because my wife, she's here.
--[SAKAIDO chuckles]
--[NARIHISAGO'S WIFE laughs]
[NARIHISAGO]
My wife is laughing.
[NARIHISAGO] Back then we didn't
even need a reason to laugh.
[MUKU] Dad, you've made
outstanding contributions
at work several times, right?
Do you think that's
probably because
you were just cut out
to be a police officer?
I think it's more likely
I've been really lucky.
Am I cut out for it,
though? Can't say.
You're lucky, huh?
Then, uh, can you
say if you think
I might be cut out
to be an officer?
Huh... Hmm...
[NARIHISAGO]
This never happened.
From the moment I became
a homicide detective,
I was always busy with work.
And I doubt Muku would've
ever wanted to be an officer.
Truth is, I was never cut
out to be on the force.
I couldn't even protect
my own family.
[MEDICAL EXAMINER A] She and
the killer had a fistfight.
She must have defended
herself bravely.
She's perfect.
[NARIHISAGO]
It didn't look like this.
She had nearly all
her bones broken.
Her lungs, liver, spleen,
and heart demolished.
Half her brain splattered
out of her skull.
That is how my daughter died.
A serial killer called the
Challenger forced her to fight
until she was injured
from head to toe.
She suffered excruciating agony,
and then she was killed.
[gasps]
[CROWD murmuring]
[CROWD screams]
[knocking]
It's open.
Are you feeling better?
[HONDOMACHI]
It's good to see you.
I still get light-headed
and dizzy some.
But today seems to
be going pretty well.
My rehab is smooth, too.
That's good. Just try
to take it slow.
Don't need to push
yourself too hard.
Matsuoka, sir.
I have a question about
the Perforator case.
What did I just say? Don't push.
[HONDOMACHI] The Mizuhanome
created an id well
from me, right?
Can you tell me
what it was like?
[MATSUOKA]
It's better you not know.
[HONDOMACHI]
Sakaido entered it, didn't he?
Lucky. I wish I could.
[MATSUOKA]
You can't.
Entering your own
id well is prohibited.
Your well comes from
your unconscious.
To dive inside it is
to become conscious
of the unconscious.
Now this is all theoretical,
but in an attempt to avoid an
invasion of consciousness,
the id well would likely render
itself invisible and expand.
Like a rising storm.
Soon the storm swallows
the conscious self,
and the brilliant
detective would be left
wandering their well forever.
Apparently, they call this
"falling into dogma."
Dogma? What's that
supposed to mean?
Hell if I know.
They say the pilot location
data becomes lost.
The pilot's retrieval will
be impossible then.
The pilot doesn't just die?
The body in the
cockpit, you mean?
I'm sure it might
struggle to maintain
its functions eventually.
However, even if the body dies,
the mind will live on
inside the Mizuhanome.
[HONDOMACHI]
Oh.
The pilot losing their
memories inside the well
and becoming the brilliant
detective is no accident.
Most likely it's
a safety feature
in case a pilot decides to
enter their own id well.
Are you listening?
[gasps]
Yeah, sure, you must be right.
[chuckles]
[HONDOMACHI] To think
other people are looking
at a part of my mind
that I don't know,
and going in and out of it.
That sounds fun.
Where's your mother?
[HONDOMACHI] Oh, yeah,
she's didn't show up today.
My mom doesn't exactly take
too much of an interest in me.
Hey, now.
[HONDOMACHI] You're gonna catch
the Pyrotechnician, right?
Lucky. I wish I could
participate, too.
[MATSUOKA]
You barely got through
the last operation alive.
Aren't you scared?
[HONDOMACHI]
Hmm.
I wouldn't say I'm
necessarily scared.
It's difficult to describe,
but it's more like I'm angry.
And not just...
...not just at the Perforator,
Tamotsu Fukuda.
I think I'm angry with
all serial killers.
Oh. From what I understand,
I did end up losing a little
bit of my frontal lobe,
but it seems there's no damage
to the limbic system,
which is located farther back.
So emotions like anger or
pleasure shouldn't be affected.
Anger or pleasure.
Interesting.
You know, now you might
be like Narihisago.
Oh, like Sakaido?
The brilliant detective!
No, not the brilliant detective.
I mean the real-world pilot.
He didn't say it in those words,
but the same thing
happened to him, too.
He talked about it.
Said it was like a
strange combination
of pleasure and anger.
Right. I forgot.
You and Narihisago were
once colleagues.
That's so cool.
Do you think I could be
a brilliant detective?
[MATSUOKA] You formed a well,
so you're probably eligible.
But whether you can
actually do it
is a question of capabilities.
That's true.
I guess someone's capabilities
depend on how much of a boost
the Mizuhanome's
adjustments provide.
[MATSUOKA]
Give up on this.
Huh?
Becoming a pilot is too
dangerous. It's suicidal.
Thankfully, you
survived your first.
There is no reason to
attempt it a second time.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say it sounds like you're
a worried about me.
[MATSUOKA] I didn't much
care for Narihisago
when we were both detectives.
And now, I truly hate the man.
If I'm being honest,
I think he's hopeless trash.
Anyway, try to rest.
Leave this guy to us, okay?
I can let you in on one bit
of good news, though.
The cognition particles were
not blown away this time.
We found some at the scene.
[NISHIMURA]
No mistake about it.
We collected samples
from the remnants
of some unexploded gunpowder.
They are the Pyrotechnician's.
I authorize construction
of a well.
Roger that. Go call
Narihisago, now.
Hey, there.
What's up? Where're you off to?
[PEOPLE murmuring]
[SAKAIDO]
Where am I?
[CROW gasping]
[CROWD screaming]
[gasps]
[SAKAIDO]
I know her.
I remember. Her name is Kaeru.
And by remembering her,
I remember who I am, too.
My name is Sakaido,
the brilliant detective.
I don't know my full name,
but that's not
important right now.
I must solve the mystery
of Kaeru's death.
[MAN A] What is this? Does
anyone know what's going on?
[gasps]
[SAKAIDO]
A sniper?
Hey! Don't stand in the open!
You need to take cover!
[MAN D screams]
What are you doing over there?
You have to get down!
Whatever. Let him stand there
and die if he wants!
[SAKAIDO]
Huh? Oh, yeah. I might die.
Can't have that.
[WOMAN A screams]
[SAKAIDO]
The shooting stopped.
Is it because everyone hid
in the shadow of the wall?
If there's a blind spot,
there's only one sniper.
Where is he?
It appears as though the bullets
are coming from
inside the waterfall,
but the water's spray
is obscuring everything.
I can't even spot
the muzzle flash.
Water on the round has
washed away the blood,
so I can't follow the
trajectory of the bullet.
I won't be able to
locate the sniper.
That's all right.
Focus on observing.
Damn.
[SAKAIDO]
I didn't come here to die.
But my job is not
survival, either.
What I'm supposed to do
is solve the mystery
of Kaeru's death.
Something here is wrong.
But I can't quite grasp it yet.
Yes, something is wrong.
What though?
[HABUTAE] A total of 75
people are on the tower.
None have been recognized.
[SHIRATAKE] The tower doesn't
appear to be a real place.
Time cannot be narrowed
down beyond midday.
But, Habutae, identifying those
people will prove impossible.
Look.
Oh, that's why.
They're no one. It doesn't
matter who they are.
Are they just generic "others"?
Basically, they're like dolls
that have been produced
from mixing together features
of multiple different people.
Fitting, given how
indiscriminate
this guy has been.
The clothing is
haphazard, as well.
We can't determine any brands.
That's okay.
Let's keep identifying
what we can't determine.
Most people tend to hide
things unconsciously.
If the Pyrotechnician is
a meticulous individual,
then they might also hide
things meticulously.
This person not only made bombs,
but they arranged
gunpowder and fireworks
in order to create
pleasing displays.
Wouldn't they have
to be meticulous?
That's a good point.
I had been imagining a thrill
seeker, but maybe...
I wish I knew what was
causing this feeling.
Extract him, now!
Reinject Sakaido. Can you?
[NARIHISAGO]
Of course.
[SAKAIDO]
My name is Sakaido.
[MOMOKI]
Extract him!
What feels wrong
about Kaeru's body?
[CROWD screaming]
More than one sniper?
The bullets do seem to be
coming from everywhere.
I don't get it.
What did we do wrong?
Why do we have to be killed?
[SAKAIDO]
That I don't know.
But if this is a senseless
slaughter to the victims,
then there might not be
a reason in the first place.
The number of victims
excluding Kaeru and Sakaido
keeps changing every time.
So far, it appears anywhere
between 71 and 83.
Continue analyzing.
I can't take it! Anything is
better than getting shot!
I can't stay here! I can't!
[screaming]
[thud]
[SAKAIDO] Is it better
to be shot or to jump?
I wonder.
Keep moving! Get away!
[FUYUKAWA]
Ah! Dammit!
Dammit!
[SAKAIDO]
Compared to staying put,
how much of a difference is
all that effort going to make?
Either way, death
will come for you.
[SAKAIDO]
Remember though,
my purpose here
is not to survive.
Don't be afraid.
I am a brilliant detective.
My purpose here is to solve
the mystery of Kaeru's death.
Please help me! Can you
do something? Anything?
Hey, wait!
[WAKASHIKA] There's something
about Kaeru's body!
Come on, think! Look close!
[SAKAIDO]
What is it?
What's wrong with this picture?
Please help!
I can't. I don't wanna die here!
Feel free to, though.
At least it'll be
a little quieter.
Stop it! Let go!
I won't.
Please, I can't take this!
I want it--I need
it all to stop!
[SAKAIDO]
Guess it pays to get involved.
The mystery is solved.
What? What is he talking about?
[SHIRATAKE]
Yes, of course.
We couldn't tell because
the sun is directly overhead.
[HABUTAE] Right, you can't tell
if you're always moving.
Well, that's great. You guys're
making me look like an idiot!
[screaming]
[thud]
[SAKAIDO] The guy who jumped
from the other side earlier
is now directly below me.
How would that happen?
[screams]
[SAKAIDO]
The tower is what's moving.
That's how the sniper
repositioned so quickly.
Or rather, how they made
it appear that way.
[SAKAIDO]
It started off with rapid fire,
but the aim was precise.
That's not a feat you can
accomplish while moving.
The sniper must have
been sniping us
from the same location
as we ran around.
What happened was this...
[SAKAIDO]
Kaeru was shot in the chest.
She went down.
However, she was still conscious
and spotted the sniper.
[SAKAIDO] To help the rest of
us, she indicated the direction.
The tower was moving then, too.
So Kaeru's finger deviated from
the trajectory of the bullet.
[SAKAIDO] That deviation is what
made things look wrong to me.
Oh, what's this?
Are you still alive?
[FUYUKAWA]
Everyone, run randomly
so you're harder to target!
I see.
That way you're the only one
going at a steady pace.
Please, don't give up yet!
We can find the sniper!
[chuckles]
Yes.
Well, he's having fun.
The sniper wasn't actually
the one moving, after all.
We're okay! Just don't
stop moving! Keep running!
Huh?
[SAKAIDO] What happens when
this guy is eventually
the last man standing?
Will another group of casualties
be brought up, then?
New victims arrive to
experience a new slaughter?
Ah, figured me out?
Yes. I'm a brilliant detective.
[FUYUKAWA] Careful. You might
be holding your head too high.
No, it's fine.
Life and death aren't the issue.
[MOMOKI]
Extract Sakaido.
The puzzle is solved.
Of the 75 victims
present this time,
74 had faces and body parts
broken down and reassembled.
It looks like they
were soldiers.
All 74 were victims of a bombing
in the Middle East
four years ago.
[alarm blaring]
It's a political alert.
What do we do?
There are ways for us to
obtain the information.
Leave it for now.
We don't want this
to be a pretext
for political interference.
They'd love to learn the
secrets of the Mizuhanome,
but we operate the thing,
and we don't even know that.
[MOMOKI] You said 74 were
soldiers. Who was 75?
[HABUTAE]
My apologies, sir.
The last one is the
man Sakaido found.
Then he's the Pyrotechnician.
Strangely, he's had his
face changed, too.
Plastic surgery.
Cross reference all plastic
surgery records, piece by piece.
Right.
[MOMOKI]
There's one more thing.
In the well, the killer also
made an appearance
at the scene of the massacre.
[HABUTAE] Then could the
Pyrotechnician be a soldier?
[TOGO] Suppose he was at the
scene of the bombing, too.
[KOKUFU]
A firefighter?
Or police.
Or maybe he was among
the crowd of bystanders.
He could be...
He pretended to be a
freelance news photographer
who rushed to the scene, huh?
[OFFICER A]
Suspect captured.
[MATSUOKA]
Good. Bring him to me.
So seven procedures
in four years.
Makes for quite a
different appearance.
Well, I guess it was worth it
to become so handsome.
To be honest, I don't
really care how I look.
But if you say that to
a plastic surgeon,
they might get suspicious and
ask unnecessary questions.
Yes, I see.
[OFFICIER B]
Matsuoka, sir,
these are the photographs
you asked for.
Thanks.
I've been wondering how
clean the images he took
of his own firework
bombs would be.
[FUYUKAWA] Can you believe
the people in this world?
They're dead long
before I kill them.
[NARIHISAGO] You like that
photograph that much.
[FUYUKAWA]
It isn't a matter of liking it.
It's just real.
[NARIHISAGO]
I suppose that's true.
All humans do love
beautiful things.
Even if they're terrifying.
[FUYUKAWA]
I believe what it captures
is the empty soul of modern man.
"Empty" seems a pretty strong
term, if you ask me.
Those people are simply trying
to preserve a record
of the fact they were present to
witness something incredible.
That's what most
onlookers do, isn't it?
[FUYUKAWA] They're obviously
lacking in empathy.
But people only died
because of your bombs.
Certainly can't deny that,
can you, Mr. Pyrotechnician?
All I did was expose the
emptiness of modern humanity.
We're all insignificant.
Whether anyone happens to be
alive or dead doesn't matter,
and that even includes you.
Doesn't matter whether
you're alive or dead.
Fair enough.
[FUYUKAWA] There's no inherent
value in life or death.
[chuckles]
What, do you think I'm wrong?
[NARIHISAGO] I think deep down,
you don't actually believe that.
At my core,
I believe and know it.
People's lives have no value.
My life doesn't matter,
neither does yours,
and neither does the life of
your dearly departed daughter.
Whether someone
is alive or dead,
either way, it's meaningless.
[NARIHISAGO]
People die.
They do it all on their
own all the time.
They die of old age.
They die of disease.
They die in accidents.
But the death you brought about
was always mass murder.
Unless a bunch of people die,
unless it's a massacre,
to you, it doesn't
count as death.
What are you saying?
That grand bombing
four years ago.
Seems it must've really
struck your fancy.
[gasps]
[NARIHISAGO] An onlooker
just enjoys the scene.
But not you. You wanted to
savor that vision of hell.
So badly that you had to
find a way to recreate it.
And then, you made sure
it happened over and over.
You bask in the center
of your handmade hell,
and you become ecstatic.
That is who you are. Truly.
You're wrong. I expose
the reality of the wo--!
[NARIHISAGO]
I'm not wrong.
Your photographs are certainly
the reality of the world,
but it's your reality.
Shallow humans, sure.
But their shallowness is nothing
more than a reflection of you.
You don't know me!
[NARIHISAGO]
Don't I?
Between setting off the bomb
and taking photos
of the onlookers,
or perhaps while
taking the photos,
what were you looking at
as you snapped the camera?
We know you weren't just
gazing at the onlookers.
What was genuinely
capturing your attention?
You were stunned and moved
by the dreadful beauty
of hell, weren't you?
That's ridiculous.
[NARIHISAGO]
I agree, but your words
will not convince me otherwise.
I know the truth.
Well, then you're wrong.
[NARIHISAGO]
It makes no difference
whether someone's alive
or dead, correct?
But the reality is,
you want other people to die.
That way you can gaze upon them
as the last man standing.
No!
[NARIHISAGO]
Oh, deny it all you want.
I already told you,
I know my words are true.
Nothing you can say
will make them less so.
Surely you must realize
your fun is all over now.
You'll never see
your hell again.
Well, except for
in your memories.
Aww. Haven't you had enough yet?
[FUYUKAWA choking]
That's right.
It's all the same, whether
you're alive or you're dead.
This is what you meant.
Don't give up.
Just a little longer
and you'll prove your
worldview to everyone.
[CROWD screaming]
Get down!
[SAKAIDO]
Kaeru!
I'm sorry. I meant to save you.
I know that.
I know that's the real reason
you've returned here
so many times.
I had to, because it seemed
like I'd have enough time
before the first shot
would kill you.
[KAERU] Yeah. The investigation
was never that important.
If your job was never that
important to begin with...
...then why couldn't
you have found a way
to be there with me
and mom before we died?
[gasps]
[GUARD A]
Everyone up!
Kaeru is not my Muku.