[gasps]
[NARIHISAGO]
The ceiling looks different.
Three years now
I've been staring at the exact
same one inside my cell.
So where...?
[AYAKO]
Good morning.
You're up early today.
[MUKU]
You're supposed to knock first.
[AYAKO giggles]
I'm talking in my sleep.
It's time to get up.
That's some serious bedhead.
[MUKU] Shh. Just gimme,
like, five more minutes.
You're so mean!
Is something wrong?
[NARIHISAGO] That's not Kaeru.
It's our daughter.
Which means... Wait!
[AYAKO]
Uh.
[NARIHISAGO] I'm not Sakaido.
I'm Akihito Narihisago.
But I remember.
Kaeru. The Mizuhanome. The Kura.
All the cases and
serial killers.
Those I've killed.
And how I got here...
[NARIHISAGO]
I remember everything.
[chuckles]
[SAKAIDO] Wait ten
minutes, then hit eject.
Only two minutes?
Aki?
Why're you running around
the house like a crazy person?
What's gotten into
you this morning?
[grunts]
Get a room, and just let
me go back to sleep!
[AYAKO] Did you have a
bad dream or something?
[NARIHISAGO] When I piloted the
bogus Mizuhanome in the id well,
this must've been the
world it constructed.
That's why it's different
from what I usually find
when I dive into a well.
There's no Kaeru,
and this place,
it's an undistorted
version of the past.
Could ya do me a favor
and stop staring at me?
It's creeping me out.
It's only because he
loves you, sweetheart.
Now stop being a little drama
queen and finish your breakfast.
[MUKU]
Fine.
[NARIHISAGO] For some reason,
I retained my memory.
I'm not some brilliant
detective. Just me.
Yeah, they found the body of
some person beaten to death.
Definitely sounds like the case
you've been working on.
[NARIHISAGO] In this reality,
my family's still alive.
I've got no idea how long this
time with them is gonna last,
but if this is the past,
I have an advantage.
I remember everything.
This guy sounds messed up.
[INVESTIGATOR A]
Tests on chemical traces
found on the body
came back positive
as a finish used
in boxing gloves,
or other similar protective
athletic hand gear.
As before, blood, brain
tissue, vomit and diarrhea,
vitreous humor
from prior victims--
[DIRECTOR]
Shut that door!
Take a seat or leave.
Who was that guy?
One of mine, Narihisago.
He's acting strange.
All right, spill.
It's really good
to see you, Momoki.
Then why haven't you
been answering my calls?
[NARIHISAGO] Just didn't
wanna get you involved.
What do you mean by "involved"?
What're you up to now?
[NARIHISAGO] Something with
no effect on reality.
Could you be more specific?
[MOMOKI]
Where are we?
Denshin Katsuyama's house.
Or should I say,
it's the home of the killer
we call the Challenger.
What?
I need you to go to
the rear of the house
and wait for my signal.
Don't walk away!
Do you have any evidence?
[NARIHISAGO]
I've been here before.
[doorbell rings]
[CHALLENGER]
Yes?
[NARIHISAGO]
Good morning to you.
[CHALLENGER]
Who're you?
Mister Katsuyama,
I mean, Mister Challenger.
Well, I'm a police officer and
I would like to speak with you.
Just one-on-one.
[CHALLENGER]
Enter.
[NARIHISAGO]
Thanks for your cooperation.
I hope I'm not disturbing you.
[CHALLENGER]
Of course not.
Now, what business
might you and I have?
It doesn't appear friendly.
Yeah, last time I was
racing the SWAT team,
so I had to come
in guns blazing.
Thought I'd take the
liberty of a redo.
We're lucky.
We can take our time,
and not have to rush.
In short, I'm here to
challenge the Challenger
to a fair and square
fight, like a man.
[CHALLENGER]
Hmm.
We've never met. What do
you mean by "last time"?
As for "lucky," I'm not sure
I would agree with you.
[NARIHISAGO] What I'm saying is,
this time, we'll do it your way.
I'm assuming by "my way,"
you mean this? Correct?
Here or inside that little
basement arena you've got,
wherever you prefer.
That venue is
currently occupied.
[NARIHISAGO] How's this work?
You bang a gong?
True combat only begins
the moment both fighters
acknowledge it's inevitable.
[NARIHISAGO]
Heh. "Combat."
As if what you're doing has
any level of dignity to it.
What you are is
a fucking pervert
who got off by beating a
14-year-old girl to death.
[CHALLENGER]
Hm.
Is that another event
I should remember?
[NARIHISAGO]
That's right.
And I won't let you
form a memory of it.
You've had your last match
in that arena of yours.
Not to brag, but I
am fairly strong.
[NARIHISAGO] Save it until
after you defeat an adult.
Oh, but I have.
[NARIHISAGO]
Oh, that's right.
You did kill a pro wrestler
and a martial artist.
So what?
A guy who gets off
on beating the shit
outta women and children
is the weakest kinda
scumbag there is!
Seriously, are you going to tell
me what you're going on about?
[NARIHISAGO]
I don't know about you,
but I'm done with the chit-chat!
[NARIHISAGO groaning]
[NARIHISAGO]
You won't make me scream.
You and I are just
getting started.
Are you sure you're
really a police officer?
You fight like a child.
[chuckles]
What happened to fighting
fair and square, like a man?
I said we'd fight your
way, and we are.
Only this time, you're the one
who was caught by surprise.
Dammit!
Good. You've still got
some fight in you.
[screams]
[CHALLENGER laughing]
[gunshots]
[NARIHISAGO]
Get up.
We're not finished!
Are you gonna let
a child beat you?
[CHALLENGER groans]
Not so tough when your
brains are bashed in!
The legendary Challenger? Ha!
I won!
[MOMOKI]
Narihisago!
What happened?
You just killed a man.
Don't die on me. I'll get help.
[NARIHISAGO]
Momoki.
Stairs behind the curtain...
There's a victim
still down there.
[music playing]
Damn!
You're safe!
I'm with the police!
[MOMOKI]
You poor thing.
If you can hear me,
tell me your name.
Help's on the way. Hold on.
[GIRL]
My name's Asukai.
My name's Kiki... Asukai.
I... Please, just let me die.
[NARIHISAGO]
Can't be her.
Look at this.
[KIKI ASUKAI]
Who is it?
[NARIHISAGO]
Detective Akihito Narihisago
with the First
Investigative Division.
You can come in.
Looks like the firework
festival's happening tonight.
You're Kaeru.
What are you?
Part of the Mizuhanome?
And what is a Mizuhanome?
[NARIHISAGO]
Never mind. Sorry for intruding.
It's nice to meet you,
Miss Kiki Asukai.
[KIKI ASUKAI] That man with
the gray hair, where is he?
You mean the Challenger?
"Challenger"? So... that's
what people were calling him.
[CHALLENGER] I want you to
hit me as hard as you can.
You understand? This isn't
part of your dreams anymore.
If you don't fight back this
time, you'll actually die.
Die already!
The Challenger,
he was right here.
If you don't mind,
I'd appreciate it if you would
refrain from speaking his name.
Hearing it aloud forces
me to think about him,
and in turn, you receive
those memories, too.
Receive those memories?
I'm not sure I...
What's going on here?
It's hard for me to explain.
As long as I can remember,
my inner thoughts have broadcast
themselves to those around me.
Whether they're words, memories,
or whatever I imagine.
Including your dreams.
Wait just a minute.
How did I know that?
[KIKI ASUKAI] There's someone
else here with us.
[whirring]
[FACE-LIFTER whistling]
Who is that whistling?
The person who's going
to kill me tonight.
What do you mean?
[FACE-LIFTER]
You there, Kiki?
The hell?
Man, what was that for?
[NARIHISAGO]
Hitoshi Sonoda!
Face-lifter? There's no way!
[FACE-LIFTER] Huh? How the
hell do you know my name?
Because he's a police detective.
A cop? That ain't right.
If you can get inside
her dreams like me,
that means you're just
like the rest of us.
Tonight's supposed
to be my turn!
You'd better explain
yourself right now!
I'm the one who's
in the dark here!
[NARIHISAGO]
He disappeared.
He woke up because you
made him experience pain.
It's different for me.
I always have to die before
I'm able to wake up.
What do you mean?
What's with this id well?
Also, why do you
look like Kaeru?
I told you, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Then tell me where I am.
[KIKI ASUKAI]
I thought I was clear.
You're asleep in your room,
and you entered my dream.
Mom, look! Dad's awake!
Don't scare us like
that ever again!
Oh, thank goodness.
We've been waiting for you
to regain consciousness
since the incident.
Since what?
Don't you remember
stopping the Challenger?
[AYAKO]
You were crying in your sleep.
Was it a bad dream?
A dream.
[MUKU]
I'm so happy you're okay!
Sorry if I had you
worried, kiddo.
[MUKU]
I gotta ask.
Was the reason you were
acting so weird that morning
because of what happened?
Did you go to the
Challenger ready to die?
Of course not, Muku.
Don't be ridiculous.
[MUKU]
You're right.
Just don't die. Okay, Dad?
Are you kidding?
You think I would die and
leave you two behind? Never.
[MOMOKI] Narihisago,
there are several matters
we need to discuss,
but I suppose they can wait.
In the meantime,
looks like the incident will
be labeled as self-defense.
Thank you, Momoki.
I'm still alive because of you.
[KIKI ASUKAI]
Come in.
It's Narihisago, isn't it?
First Investigative Division.
You wanted to make
sure, didn't you?
It was real.
A dream, yeah,
but that would mean...
...you and I really
did share it.
Making it a reality.
At least, whatever the
definition of that word means
in a place like this.
If you'll allow me
a minute to explain,
I want to share
my interpretation
of what's going on.
I noticed two things happening.
First, like I said, we were
having the same dream.
And second, I could read your
mind while it was happening.
[KIKI ASUKAI] To be more
precise, you entered my dream,
and you weren't reading my mind.
More like it was
broadcasting itself to you.
I can't explain why.
The only thing I do know
is that I've never had
a secret all my own.
[NARIHISAGO] There's one more
thing we haven't talked about.
Why there was a serial killer
there with us out to murder you.
They're the only kind
of people who appear.
Like the man who wanted
to peel off my face.
And you, as well.
I'm not like him!
At least, not in this world.
Miss Asukai, what is this world?
I need to know what it is
I'm dealing with here
if this is real.
[KIKI ASUKAI]
Yes. It isn't a dream.
I don't mean whether
it's imaginary,
but then again,
someone from this world
wouldn't know the difference.
Sonoda said--the Face-lifter--
he mentioned something like,
"tonight was supposed
to be his turn"?
What did he mean?
He meant that particular dream.
So if I understand
this correctly,
you're saying other serial
killers appear to you
on different nights?
[KIKI ASUKAI]
Yes.
If that's the truth, how can
you be so calm about it?
Because for a long time now,
these people have been coming
to murder me in my dreams.
I get it. People like the
Challenger and his buddies.
And when you fall asleep,
the bastards slink outta
the shadows to murder you.
Over and over and over again.
They have the perfect victim;
one they can torture
endlessly in dreams.
That's enough!
Please stop it.
Are you all right?
Forgive me.
I don't know why,
but I can't seem to stop it
from broadcasting to you.
All I see are flashes,
but you... you keep
experiencing it in full
with no way out except dying.
[KIKI ASUKAI] At first,
there was only one killer.
But later on, he began calling
others into my dreams.
[NARIHISAGO]
This man--
he wouldn't happen to have
a top hat and cane.
[KIKI ASUKAI]
Yes.
[NARIHISAGO]
Makes my stomach turn.
[KIKI ASUKAI]
Real quick.
Could you talk to the doctors
and make them stop
giving me sedatives?
Sleep's just part
of the problem.
Not only do I see
myself being killed
and reliving previous
deaths after I pass out,
the medicines also make
it hard to concentrate.
I'll see what I can do.
Why do you think the Challenger
tried to kill you?
In real life, I mean.
He couldn't murder you
in dreams if he did.
Dreams may be
similar to reality,
but they're no substitute.
That man wasn't only interested
in hurting other people.
He enjoyed being hit himself.
You don't get physically
injured in a dream.
I think he kidnapped me
because he needed to
actually feel that pain.
Not anymore.
Now that the
Challenger's is gone,
does it ease your pain at all?
[NARIHISAGO] I promise,
I'll find a way to end it.
I hope so, Detective.
Uh.
[FACE-LIFTER] The cop? How the
hell'd you find this place?
You told me about it
back when we met in prison.
Prison? I ain't never
been to prison!
'Cause I never had a reason to
be arrested in the first place!
[NARIHISAGO] No, at least,
not at this stage.
Yeah! That's right!
I'm innocnt.
All I did was mess
around in a dream
and there's no law against that!
Wait, you said "at this stage."
There's no point worrying
yourself about it.
Hey, who are you?
You're one of us, right?
With you-know-who?
You mean, the guy with the cane?
No, and I'm not one of you.
[FACE-LIFTER] You killed
the Challenger, didn't you?
Here to kill me, too?
[NARIHISAGO] I'm in no shape
for that. Just here to visit.
You and I are going to
have a nice long talk.
First, you're going to tell me
what you know about
this Kiki girl,
and the man who showed you
how to get inside her dreams.
And afterwards,
we can focus on you.
The reason why you like
to remove people's faces,
but you're too much of a
coward to rip off your own.
Oh, we're gonna
have a lovely time.
[inaudible]
You don't have to die anymore!
[AYAKO]
Morning.
Sorry, I didn't mean
to startle you.
[NARIHISAGO crying]
[AYAKO]
Another bad dream, huh?
So, who died?
Was it me?
I promise, I'm not gonna die,
you hear me?
Never in a million years would
I leave you or Muku behind.
Where is Muku?
She was still tired from
the firework festival,
but should be stopping by
sometime around noon.
Ah.
Are you sleeping well?
Tell me the truth.
Me? I haven't slept well.
Not for a long time.
[AYAKO]
Since when?
Oh, hard to say.
Aki! You should've told me!
Heh. I really wish
that I could have.
I'm serious! Do you realize
how important sleep is?
If you're not getting enough,
it's like chipping away
years of your life.
Ah.
[chuckles]
In that case, I guess
it's only right
to try and help her get
a good night's rest.
Who do you mean?
You're the one who
needs rest, Aki.
I'm sorry I didn't
realize it sooner.
[AYAKO]
What is it?
Honey, I'm not sure why you're
afraid to close your eyes.
But if I die, you'll
know it's just a dream,
and all you have
to do is wake up.