[MATSUOKA]
Same photo.
[gasps] Matsuoka!
[MATSUOKA]
Hm?
Stop playing games with us, now!
Tell us where he's hiding!
Awfully kind of you to
just give us the evidence.
Hm?
Hondomachi!
[gasps]
On the second floor!
Don't move a muscle.
It's Hondomachi.
Gravedigger located.
Two suspects.
The perpetrator Haruka Kazuta
and the mastermind
directing him.
Name: Nahoshi Inami.
Arrest met with resistance.
On scene officer
has been injured.
Kazuta is armed and
still remains at large.
Send back-up immediately.
[SAKAIDO]
Hmm...
What?
Nothing, you just have
an interesting face.
Oh?
I haven't had the opportunity
to look at myself yet,
since there are no mirrors here.
Ah. Good point.
[UNKNOWN VOICES] This isn't how
I'm supposed to look, anyway.
He says it's to protect
me from the monster.
Yeah?
[KAZUTA]
Excuse me.
Would you mind stepping outside?
[MATSUOKA]
Think he ran for it?
[HONDOMACHI]
Seems unlikely.
Considering how
the princess here
has him wrapped
around her finger.
[MATSUOKA]
She's one cool customer.
Toying with someone's emotions
so they kill for you...
How else could you
describe her except cold?
You know what? Just shoot her.
What?
[HONDOMACHI] You heard me.
She doesn't deserve to live.
Fine then. I'll do it myself.
[gunshot]
What'd you do?!
[KAZUTA groans]
[KAZUTA]
Huh?
Look at that. You do feel.
So what's your deal anyway?
This goes way beyond
having pride.
Not proud. Just being childish.
Sounds like he's asking for you.
Which is why I'm ignoring him.
Do you know how this works?
[SAKAIDO grunts]
Isn't there anybody
you have a crush on?
[SAKAIDO grunts]
Hey, man. Do you need a hand?
No, don't worry about it.
I appreciate the offer,
but she still should be able
to hear me, so it's fine.
Don't worry about it? You sure?
[KAZUTA]
Yeah.
[SAKAIDO]
Whatever you say.
[TOGO]
Shall I extract Sakaido, sir?
[MOMOKI]
Yes. He's through.
So including Kazuta,
John Walker's manifested
in a total of six serial
killers' id wells.
Did you find any connection
linking him to
the previous five?
I've run several queries
using different conditions,
but so far, we've got nothing.
Let's put aside the issue
of how he finds them a sec.
Just how does he turn
them into murderers?
Controlling someone's
emotions sounds unreal,
yet that seem to be
what he's doing.
Maybe we should look
into psychiatrists.
[HABUTAE] But none of them
had treatment records.
Also, he's not just ingrained
in the subjects' memories,
he exists within
their unconscious.
And what's up with that coat
and hat he's always wearing?
I don't get it,
some kind of cosplay?
I see.
While the mind's
capable of conjuring
all sorts of strange images,
all six share the same vision.
In other words, they must
have actually seen someone
dressed like John
Walker in person.
Right.
The other frustrating aspect
is that he never leaves
any witnesses,
he only appears to
whoever he's targeting.
It's nearly impossible--
No, I'd say completely
impossible.
[WAKASHIKA]
I was thinking...
It's a long shot,
but what if John Walker
has a machine like
the Mizuhanome?
Imagine if he... instead of
exploring data like the well,
he could invade a person's
unconscious mind.
Once he dove in,
he could wreak whatever
havoc he wanted.
There's the one we operate,
but maybe there's another,
like an original.
Despite working
with a Mizuhanome,
we're still being
kept in the dark.
Even we don't know
all of its secrets.
Its creator, Nishio Shirakoma,
isn't he missing,
Assistant Director?
Yes, and because of that,
no one can gain access to the
main unit's central component.
Is there anything we can do
to get some more information?
[TOGO sighs]
I'll reach out to Chief
Hayaseura about it,
but any details concerning the
project are intentionally kept
under lock and key to
prevent political pressure.
Or worse, using it for
military applications.
Don't any of you think about
getting your hands on it.
If you were discovered,
the punishment would be severe.
I won't deny more intel would
help with the investigation.
Wait a minute.
Considering the power
of Mizuhanome
we have at the wellside,
another unit may not
even be necessary.
What if this individual is
closer than we suspect?
Like a member of
the wellside staff.
It's irresponsible to make
waves without proof.
But still, it'd certainly
explain a few things,
like why he's
obscuring his face.
If it's one of our colleagues,
they don't want us to know.
The Mizuhanome was
introduced a year ago.
However, we know for a
fact Fukuda's first kill
goes back at least three.
With that timeline,
the Mizuhanome would've
been in the prototype phase.
An early version of it.
It's possible.
We're working off
too many hypotheticals.
Then let's back up.
First, we need to find
out how John Walker
chooses candidates to
turn into serial killers.
Based on our data,
variation in geography
and timing means this,
there's no pattern.
Yet, there's no
denying a connection
between some of the killers.
Kazuta was the Gravedigger,
as well as a victim of
Fukuda, the Perforator.
I mean, it's hard to believe he
randomly selected two candidates
that just happened to
have a prior connection.
[HABUTAE]
Yeah, good point.
So, that means John Walker
arrived at Kazuta from Fukuda
by using some unknown method.
But Fukuda's only
contact with Kazuta
was when he was drilling
a hole in his head.
So did John Walker
just happen to be
at that exact same location
at that exact time?
Everything is all
too convenient.
[humming]
[WAKASHIKA]
Hidden cameras and microphones.
Seems John Walker was keeping
Fukuda under surveillance.
Then, do you suppose...?
If Kazuta was being
closely watched,
it's not hard to make the leap
and assume Inami was as well.
I want Narihisago prepped and
ready to dive into the well
as soon as I return.
[MATSUOKA]
Evening.
[MOMOKI]
Matsuoka. My condolences.
There's no need for that
when it's just the three of us.
Did you meet with
the officers' families?
[HAYASEURA]
We just finished.
How's your shoulder by the way?
It's nothing serious,
but that's not the
reason I stopped you.
Tomatsu Fukuda.
When he dives into the well,
I heard brilliant detective
Anaido's useless.
In order to be a
fit for the job,
you don't necessarily have
to be a criminal, right?
If having killed
somebody's a requirement,
as well as an aptitude
for investigation,
then I might know someone.
[SAKAIDO]
Kaeru.
[SAKAIDO] The moment her name
passed my lips, I remembered.
I'm Sakaido,
the brilliant detective.
I must solve the mystery
of Kaeru's death.
[SAKAIDO]
Killer walked to the next car.
After being covered
in her blood.
Guess I'm not getting
much outta you.
Still, when did they die?
And how long have they
been on this train?
Got a match on the train.
According to this,
Kazuta and Inami took this
line back in high school.
I recognize them. Those are
the Gravedigger's victims.
Minami Ayase, Shiki Kouda,
Toshiki Yamashita,
Kaori Shiina, Kazuyuki Masuda,
and Kana Mishima.
They're standing in
the order they died.
[TOGO]
We have more info.
Apparently, when Inami was 14,
her mother committed suicide
by jumping in front
of a moving train.
From what we've gathered,
it appears Sakaido is riding
the same one that ran her over.
Moreover, it was this very train
that her daughter was aboard
the moment it happened.
See that?
[SAKAIDO]
Hmm...?
If the first and last car
are connected like this,
then the train must form a ring.
[INAMI]
Hello there.
And hello to you.
I was wondering
when you'd show up.
Did you kill that gir--?
You know anything about that?
You mean her? No clue.
Looks pretty dead to me.
I suppose you're gonna
tell me it wasn't you.
What do you think?
[SAKAIDO]
I'm leaning towards "no."
Your hands are bloody
from that handkerchief,
but there's no sign
of blood spatter on you.
If you did it, you would
have disposed of the cloth
and those bloody shoes by now.
Looking at the scene,
I'm noticing there's
not very much blood.
And the footsteps could
well be Kaeru's shoe size.
So that used to be
her name, huh? Kaeru.
Additionally, it seems you two
were complete strangers.
Meaning, you didn't have
a motive to kill her.
Still, what does it matter?
[gasps]
Are you dense?
Stop staring at him.
Boyfriend?
[INAMI]
Yeah, right.
[SAKAIDO]
Okay, let me get this straight.
Based on the clues,
Kaeru circled the train,
covered in her own blood,
and when she saw you,
asked if you could
wipe her feet off.
That's right.
I've no idea why, though.
[SAKAIDO]
But I do.
Kaeru did it to lead me here.
In order to lead
me to this girl.
Or possibly...
to bring me to this boy.
Oh, yeah.
The next station--do you know
if it's coming up soon?
My mom's probably
waiting for me there.
The train will never
reach the station.
Because it's in a loop, there's
a chance she won't be run over.
What's your take on this?
Do you think she's
protecting her mother?
I don't.
It was at the crossing
they passed earlier.
That's the location
her mother jumped.
The time of day
also fits perfectly.
Which means...
She's trapped forever.
Stuck on a train as it endlessly
runs over her mother.
[WAKASHIKA]
There. See that?
Our guy. Walker.
It makes you wonder.
Did Kazuta and Inami
commit these murders
they otherwise wouldn't
because of John Walker?
Impulses don't decide actions.
While that's the assumption,
how do we know?
It's the same as
saying that people
are fundamentally good or evil.
Or, when it comes to reason,
logic contains some
primal aspect
that's strong enough
to subdue impulse.
That idea.
Huh?
You sure I'm not interrupting?
C'mon, I thought we
went over this already.
Sorry.
[INAMI]
I hate it.
I hate the thought of
staring at a dead body.
When her mother died,
it must've completely
warped those feelings.
[DETECTIVE A] Nahoshi Inami
revealed the location
of a barrel.
You're being
awfully cooperative.
Well, sure.
Now that I can't watch the
camera feed any longer,
there's no reason
to keep them hidden.
Would you like to know where
the rest of them are buried?
Care to join us?
Could you not do that?
I want it to be
this way forever.
What now, sir?
Being that we have the location
of the remaining victims,
I'd say this case is closed.
I think we let Sakaido do what
he wants... a while longer.
Also...
...for some reason, I don't
wanna leave this world just yet.
Is that strange?
[DETECTIVE A]
Copy that.
We've recovered all the bodies.
That's good to hear.
Real quick.
That cute detective
who arrested me--
I believe her name
is Miss Hondomachi--
do you think I could meet her?
[DETECTIVE A]
It depends.
What did you need to tell her?
I know this is going
to sound strange,
but she has an injury near
her temple, like a hole.
Kazuta had one in the same place
and I was just curious if maybe
there was a connection.
[DETECTIVE A]
I'm not sure I understand.
Maybe not, but I know she will.
Call it intuition.
[HONDOMACHI]
Uh. Are you sure?
You want me to be
a brilliant detective?
Correct. Your deductive powers
make you a great fit.
Thanks, Matsuoka, for
bringing it to my attention.
[gasps]
[HAYASEURA]
Hondomachi.
Yes, sir?
Will you lend us your talents
to unmask John Walker
so we can bring him to justice?
Of course, sir!
I'm delighted to hear that.
We're all expecting
great things from you.
[HONDOMACHI]
I'll try my best!
[SAKAIDO] Kaeru killed herself
just to pass along a message.
This train isn't
headed anywhere.
It goes in circles, endlessly.
But why would she do
something like that?
Is Kaeru's death--is anyone's
death worth something like that?
I don't understand.
[SAKAIDO]
Where are we headed?
If we never reach our
destination, what's the point?
You don't have to die!
I don't want you to die.
Kaeru, I swear. I was
just trying to save you.
[HONDOMACHI]
Matsuoka!
Thank you for recommending me!
[MATSUOKA]
There's no need for that.
[HONDOMACHI]
Hm?
You're right.
I guess you were just
doing your job, after all.
[MATSUOKA] No. I meant
it's not worth celebrating.
Huh?
Honestly, this is the last
thing that I wanted for you.
[sighs] I wish you didn't
have what it takes
to be a brilliant detective.
Why not?
I'm entrusted with
important cases
that're difficult to solve.
[MATSUOKA] Do you know what the
criteria is for becoming one?
Um. Deductive powers?
There's that,
but before you can even
dive into an id well,
the pilot needs to be a killer.
On top of that, a single
death isn't good enough.
To be successful, you need
to have a thirst for killing.
I don't fault you for
your attempted suicide
when you were captured
by Fukuda, but I wonder.
At Genpei Oono's house,
why'd you go to the
basement on your own?
When did you know it
was Nahoshi Inami?
That she was the Gravedigger?
No.
When you sent that photo,
just how high did you think
the probability was?
I didn't know!
And when you used
cognition particles
to justify killing Kazuta,
how good did it make you feel?
No. Wait!
It's fine. I'm not
condemning you.
This organization values
those traits, and in its eyes,
your actions were no
different than justice.
All I did was get
you transferred
to protect me and my colleagues.
Listen, about the
cameras and microphones
we found inside Fukuda's place.
Turns out they matched evidence
from a previous case.
Which one was it?
Involved a serial killer.
The Challenger.
The one who murdered
Narihisago's daughter.
The equipment we found hidden
in his house is the exact same.