[FUKUDA]
Here's what I've concluded.
Somehow, you've created a system
that can detect
the intent to kill,
which you use to catch
people like me.
To help solve these cases,
you've allied yourself with
at least one murderer.
And that's the reason
you now have
a dead prisoner on your hands.
In one night, the inmate
in the opposite cell
was able to talk him
into killing himself.
He referenced memories,
secrets he should have
no way of knowing.
I've noticed every time
this Narihisago
is led away by the guards,
he comes back
slightly different.
Like his already grim
expression was darkened
by some new layer.
That doesn't happen
after an interrogation
regarding your own crimes.
And one other thing.
His voice was barely a whisper,
but like a deafening scream.
I wish you'd been there
to hear it in person.
I'd say lucky guess, but we
know that's not the case.
Fukuda's IQ exceeds 150.
At least, it did before
he decided to drill a hole
into his brain.
[MOMOKI]
Sir, I must object.
We still haven't ascertained
whether his last victim
is alive or dead.
I'm aware of what
the report says,
but the fact is, with Narihisago
in solitary confinement,
this entire organization
is at a standstill.
[gunshot]
[PEOPLE screaming]
[ANAIDO]
This is Kaeru.
And I am Anaido.
I don't know my full name, but
I am the brilliant detective.
[TOGO]
Anaido has died.
[MOMOKI]
Three days in a row.
He's failed seven wells.
Ten attempts on each of them.
His operation time isn't
nearly long enough.
It's putting unnecessary
strain on the pilot.
He's not a suitable substitute.
Extract him.
That's enough for today.
We're used to working
with Narihisago
only hunting serial killers,
but now we find ourselves
collaborating with a murderer
who we've incarcerated
for taking innocent lives.
Maybe we're resisting
and it's our performance
that's suffering.
Regardless, that's no excuse.
The bottom line is,
he's dying way too much.
[chuckles]
Apparently, someone who'd
willingly drill a hole
through their brain has a
remarkably low survival rate.
Who in their right mind
would've ever predicted that?
[gasps]
[KEIKO]
Oxygen. Light sticks.
I guess this means I've been
captured by the Gravedigger.
And people all over
the world are watching.
Well, sorry to disappoint
anyone who came here
just to see me die!
'Cause I'm gonna survive
this! I'll show you!
I'll hang on until someone
comes and saves me!
So just you watch!
Wait! I can't waste air.
What was the record for the
person who survived the longest?
I think it was something
like 52 hours.
Right! Then I'll just have to
leave that record in the dust
and give all of you plenty
of time to find me!
The Gravedigger has now
buried seven people alive,
and yet the police
still have zero leads
as to the killer's identity or
the location of the victims.
Something else that's
quite troubling.
Despite the public's curiosity,
I don't believe anyone
except for the investigators
should watch the
Gravedigger's broadcasts
since it gives
the killer attention.
Not only does the stream
attract numerous viewers,
but the signal travels through
multiple foreign servers,
making the source
difficult to trace.
It's beyond cruel to
continuously film
the victim as they languish.
The public's essentially
watching a snuff film.
A beautiful morning, isn't it?
Sorry to interrupt.
It takes more than that
to distract us from our jobs.
Please, you'll have
to forgive me
if I came across as being
condescending just now.
We're all professionals here
and I have the utmost respect
for you and your team.
Now then, if I
understand correctly,
this is the spot where Keiko
Kikuchi was taken, isn't it?
Right.
From what it looks like
she was kidnapped
while on her way to school.
The perp left the
girl's phone behind.
But considering this is
a Gravedigger crime scene,
I doubt you're going to
be very much use here.
[FORENSICS A]
Hey!
Would you guys stop
antagonizing the kid?
The Kura have a dedicated unit
searching every square
inch of the city.
Sooner or later they'll find
the Gravedigger and the victims.
Thanks, but I'm sure
the entire police force
is doing their part.
Heh.
Your organization hasn't been
pulling its weight lately.
The whole office on vacation?
Whoa! We finally got a hit!
Right when you were kidding
about us slacking!
I owe you one!
[TOGO] Cognition particles
have been gleaned.
We can construct an id well.
First time since dealing
with the Gravedigger.
Pull Narihisago out of solitary.
Hey. Welcome back.
[SAKAIDO] Corpse has
been burnt to a crisp,
making identification
near impossible.
Yet, I know who they are.
It's Kaeru.
And I am Sakaido,
the brilliant detective.
I'll solve the mystery behind
her death without fail.
[SAKAIDO]
No visible wounds,
but given the condition
of the body,
any signs of cuts or stabbing
might not be apparent
to the naked eye.
What a mess.
[SAKAIDO] How could Kaeru
burn to death in a room
when there's no sign of a fire?
[gasps]
Curious.
A girl?
[screams]
[TOGO]
Sakaido has died.
[MOMOKI]
Extract him.
Then I want him
put right back in.
Looks like I'm
still good on air.
I'll admit it's tough not having
anything to eat in here,
but it's even tougher
not being able to know
what time of day it is.
Seems like it's been
quite a while.
Maybe even around 24 hours?
[gasps]
Curious.
All right! He made it this time!
[SAKAIDO]
Kaeru!
No. She's already dead.
There's no point in worrying.
[WAKASHIKA]
There you go!
Our responsibilities don't
include cheering for Sakaido.
Guess you're right.
That may be true, but
the longer he stays alive,
the more information
we're able to acquire.
[HABUTAE]
The only thing we know
is that she's the girl Saikaido
saw on the top floor.
She's the victim Keiko Kikuchi,
except she appears to be
around ten years old.
This well, it's
overrun with fire,
but based on everything
that we've learned,
that's not the
Gravedigger's M.O.
True, but maybe the
flames aren't literal,
and they symbolize
something else entirely.
What do you think?
[WAKASHIKA]
Uh. Not again.
Third death caused by backdraft.
[MOMOKI] Extract Sakaido and
re-inject him immediately.
After dying in the id well for
more than six hours straight,
you are aware he's on
the verge of exhaustion.
He got plenty of rest
in solitary. Inject him.
[TOGO]
Yes, sir.
[gasps]
How did--?
He doesn't remember the
previous runs, right?
Correct.
It's thanks to his skills
as the brilliant detective.
Regardless, we've still
got a lotta work to do.
Sit tight! I'm coming
up to save you!
[MOMOKI] Do you need
a break, Narihisago?
[NARIHISAGO] I used the
bathroom a while back.
Bad news is, you're gonna
need to clean the cockpit.
[MOMOKI]
Noted. Inject him.
[screams]
That makes another death.
And in the same spot.
Extract him.
Give him the chance
to eat something first,
and then we'll resume.
Yes, sir.
I'll have personnel clean
the cockpit in the meantime.
We have no idea if
Narihisago's environment
is having an effect on
Sakaido's performance.
[MOMOKI]
Do that.
[KEIKO]
Why hasn't anyone saved me?
Don't they care?
Hey, we found cognition
particles this time, right?
So how come there weren't any
in the first six abductions?
[SHIRATAKE]
The Gravedigger's victims
are still buried somewhere,
and none have been
recovered yet.
We might not be able
to scan the bodies,
but even so, the drive to kill
should've been at the
point of kidnapping.
[SHIRATAKE]
You're right.
But if there were
a minimal amount
of cognition particles
at the scene,
they could've been dispersed
by a gust of wind.
I find it hard to
believe someone
who buried six people alive
gives off such a faint reading.
Besides, the killer livestreamed
the victim's deaths,
left oxygen canisters to
prolong their suffering,
and then after they died,
continued broadcasting as
the bodies slowly decayed.
You wouldn't think an
individual that sadistic
would have a weak drive to kill.
What I'm getting at is,
the readings should've
been off the chart.
[SHIRATAKE]
Well, we found some this time.
After we catch the killer,
we'll have our answers.
My point is, this
abduction was different
from all the previous ones.
Why?
[SAKAIDO]
I want to save that girl.
But that isn't my task.
My only job here
is to shed light
on the mystery
behind Kaeru's death.
How was she rendered a
burnt corpse in a room
without any sign of fire?
Sakaido has died.
Extract him.
Give Narihisago a
five-minute break.
Understood, sir.
[door opens]
Speaking of which, you
all should get some rest.
[MOMOKI]
Really, it's no problem.
But that's where you're wrong.
If you're fatigued, you risk
missing a vital clue.
Keiko Kikuchi doesn't have
time for us to sleep.
Two nights is nothing.
Narihisago's good, too.
If he were still
a police officer,
that certainly might
be the case.
However, these days we're
dealing with Akihito Narihisago,
the serial killer.
You mustn't think of
him as a colleague.
The desire to save people
may not be enough
to motivate him any longer.
[yells]
He did it! Uh.
[explosion]
Huh?
[gasps]
[SAKAIDO grunts]
Waiting long?
Yes!
You were scared, huh?
Everything's fine now.
This place, it's on fire
and full of dead people.
[SAKAIDO] That's what
so strange about this.
The building's ablaze, littered
with victims from the fire.
Yet this girl's the only
person I've seen alive.
Everyone else has
burnt to death.
[SAKAIDO] Furthermore, Kaeru's
the other anomaly here.
She was located in a room
that showed no signs of damage.
In other words, she
didn't die in the fire.
She was killed elsewhere,
and then was transported
to this location.
But why?
Because the killer
tried to conceal her
among the bodies
in this inferno.
They were trying to use a fire
started by someone else
to cover up the fact that
she died in a separate one.
Reminds me of that
G.K. Chesterton quote.
Where does a wise
man hide a leaf?
In a forest, or in this
instance, a pile of corpses!
We've been chasing after
the wrong killer
for this entire time.
It's the work of a copycat that
wanted everyone to think
the Gravedigger was behind this!
That explains why we found
the cognition particles.
Then who's actually responsible?
Thanks, kid. I solved this
mystery thanks to you.
I don't understand
what you mean.
No need to worry about it.
Come on. I say we
get outta here.
But how're we supposed
to do that?
[grunts]
Since I'm the
brilliant detective,
you'll just have to trust me.
Whoa. Mr. Oono's house
is really on fire.
What did she just say?
[KEIKO] Mr. Oono's a failure,
so to start all over again,
he lit his house on fire.
Even though his family
was sleeping inside.
Oh, wait.
I imagine he probably thinks
that I've been spying on him.
[HABUTAE] Suspect confirmed.
Genpei Oono.
They lived in the
same neighborhood,
at least until Kikuchi
was about five.
The face is a match!
Let's go, Hondomachi.
Right!
[bang]
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER A]
Freeze! Hands up!
On your knees! Suspect secured!
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER B]
The victim's not here.
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER A]
Tell us where Keiko Kikuchi is!
Why does that rug pattern
look so familiar?
[MOMOKI gasps]
Check underneath the rug!
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER A]
Roger that!
There're stairs leading down!
We're moving in!
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER B]
Where's that medical unit?
[KOKUFU]
The victim is still alive!
We made it in time! She's safe!
[grunts]
[HABUTAE]
What's wrong?
The video isn't a live feed.
Take a look.
The barrel's still nailed
shut on the broadcast.
It was a recording.
The cell phone was a ruse.
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER A]
I'd say the victim's been dead
for several days.
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER B]
You piece of trash!
Let me go! I'll kill him!
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER A]
Calm down.
[OONO laughing]
[KEIKO]
I don't remember Mr. Oono.
I kept telling him
I didn't see anything.
[SAKAIDO] But he decided
to burn it anyway.
Because Mr. Oono is a failure.
Now that I've got you,
he can't hurt you.
Let's get outta here.
[OONO screaming]
[KEIKO]
Why'd you do that?
You've seen enough scary
things for one lifetime.
Thank you for coming to save me.
Thank you.
Without your help, I wouldn't
have found the truth.
[KEIKO] By the way, are you ever
gonna tell me your name?
[MOMOKI]
We got our guy.
That's a relief.
Have to wonder why
he chose a victim
that knew him, though,
and why he left cognition
particles behind this one time.
Was it actually the Gravedigger?
Unfortunately not.
A copycat.
Hide a leaf in the forest.
[MOMOKI]
Yeah.
So were you able to
locate the victim in time?
There was nothing we could do.
The broadcast was
a video recording.
She was dead when we got there.
Do you wanna kill
him, Narihisago?
[NARIHISAGO]
Is that an offer?
[MOMOKI]
I'm asking whether you want to.
--So that's a yes.
--[NARIHISAGO] Momoki.
[NARIHISAGO] Since I was brought
on as part of Kura, I've killed,
driven, five people to suicide.
I fully admit it.
I acted of my own will
and gave into my urges.
But there's something
else you should know.
I didn't particularly
want them dead.
I had no malice
towards any of them,
but this overwhelming
urge to kill
just welled up inside me,
and that's when I realized,
I could take this person's life.
So I did. There's
no other reason.
What're you telling me?
You're just gonna keep
killing from now on?
[NARIHISAGO]
No.
Honestly, I'd like to think
I'm still a person,
but people don't decide to act
based on their impulse alone.
I can guarantee you, Narihisago,
you're still a person.
Though, one with
a horrid weakness.
There's one more thing
I wanted to ask.
After all this, do you still
consider me your friend?
[NARIHISAGO]
Hm.
Truth is, you're probably
the one lifeline I have left,
tethering me to reason.
That was one hell
of a resolution.
For this case,
but the Gravedigger is still
out there somewhere,
and we don't have
any idea where.
Yeah, well, that investigation
can resume tomorrow.
It's early, but
let's close shop.
[HONDOMACHI]
Hm?
Wait. I recognize him.
Guess that's that.
[HONDOMACHI gasps]
Uh. Hey, aren't you--?
[HONDOMACHI]
Mr. Kazuta!
Haruka Kazuta, right?
The missing person!
Oh, wait till everyone
hears you're still alive!