[HONDOMACHI gasps]
[HONDOMACHI] It's picking up
more cognition particles.
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER A]
That's odd.
Are you sure they're coming
from inside the house?
[HONDOMACHI] There have been
instances of Wakumusubi
detecting windborne particles
from distant crime scenes.
But since we haven't
heard reports
of any murders occurring
elsewhere,
I think this reading
must be from the house.
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER A] Could
it be sensing our willingness
to gun down the killer?
[HONDOMACHI]
Your willingness to kill
is tied to your
sense of morality.
It's derived from
higher thought.
This device only
detects base impulses.
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER D]
Freeze! You're under arrest!
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER B] Drop the
drill and put your hands up!
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER C]
Comply or we'll shoot!
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER B]
Drop the weapon right now!
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER D] Stop
right there! Get on your knees!
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER C] Stop
moving or we will open fire!
Damn it.
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER D]
He's down!
[gasps]
That head wound isn't bleeding.
[MEDICAL UNIT MEMBER B]
You're right.
It looks like it's healed.
[gasps]
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER D]
Suspect captured.
He's the only other
person down here.
Wait a minute.
Yuji Oonuki.
He's outside!
[gasps]
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER A]
Hey! You all right?
Huh?
The hell? What's going on?
The Perforator
kidnapped Hondomachi
and fled through the sewers.
But how was he able
to pull this off?
I get it.
The man posed as a victim,
just as he did
within the id well.
Interesting.
It seems there's a hole
in his head, too.
He gives people wounds
that match his own.
Question is why.
Once you finish
solving the case,
we would appreciate it if you'd
leave our house for good.
You're new.
[SAKAIDO] But yeah,
of course I'm gonna leave.
Just as soon as I've
caught the bad guy.
You've got nowhere to run.
[yelling]
[gasps]
[SAKAIDO] How is he able
to move like that?
He's ignoring the
structure of this world.
There must be a reason.
Hey. Don't guess you
have any clues.
[HONDOMACHI gasps]
[SAKAIDO]
Hm?
Have we met before?
What are you after exactly?
It's John Walker!
I want everyone but Togo and
Kokufu to shift their focus
onto John Walker.
Let's move. We'll take in all
the information we can.
[ALL]
Sir!
[MATSUOKA]
Hey! What about Hondomachi?
Focus on finding her!
We haven't abandoned the search
by any means, Matsuoka.
But this demands our attention.
[MATSUOKA]
Why?
Because it's him. John Walker.
It looks like the Perforator
knew him, too.
Shit. She's got the Wakamusubi.
We should've put a GPS on it!
I would have.
[HAYASEURA]
But that's not an option.
As it would be antithetical
to our goal
of keeping this tool secret.
Hello, Chief Hayaseura.
[MATSUOKA]
I blame you for this, Chief.
Hondomachi was kidnapped
because you don't think
enough of your field officers.
I assure you,
I think quite highly
of our field officers.
You do very important work.
[MATSUOKA]
I'm not talking about our work.
I know you value that--
it's our lives you
don't care about!
We step into dangerous
situations every day.
We should all have clearance
to carry side-arms!
I've been telling you
that for months now!
[HAYASEURA] Your request
hasn't been rejected,
but these things take time.
As I think you must be aware,
the Kura and the Wellside
already receive
preferential treatment over
other police organizations.
My apologies,
but for the time being,
we should focus on finding
Ms. Hondomachi and the suspect.
Yeah, no shit!
Dammit!
[SAKAIDO] This tells me
something else about myself.
I'm not the fighting type, but
I'll still do it if I have to.
So what are you?
Are we enemies?
[SAKAIDO]
Hm?
That went well. Too well.
Okay. Well, let's just say
I'm overpowered and move on.
Go me!
[SAKAIDO chuckles]
Now then.
[gasps]
[FUKUDA]
So you're awake.
You located my house,
but I also built hideouts
throughout the city.
It always pays to
be prepared, right?
So you've been confining
your victims here as well.
I don't get it though.
Why not kill them right away?
Let's just say I've got
a whole lot on my mind.
[FUKUDA]
Hey.
This odd device of
yours, how's it work?
[FUKUDA]
Listen.
I'm about to drill a hole
in your head to match mine,
but few people have
been able to answer
my questions afterwards,
so it would be best if you
and I talked now, understand?
"Few people"? You mean they
don't all die instantly?
No one I drill dies instantly.
All of us linger for a time.
There's a chance that
the guy I left in my house
could live as long as I have.
Assuming he hasn't been
shot in my place yet.
It sounds like you're saying
you drilled a hole
in your own head first,
and then started
doing it to others.
So what, are you trying
to start a club?
First wind comes in this hole,
then it goes out of the other,
and it makes the world
a little bit clearer.
Wait a sec.
Do you think that these holes
are somehow helping people?
However things may appear
in that scrambled head of yours,
you're dead wrong.
You're nothing more
than a killer,
and hide though you might,
you will be found again.
My colleagues are gonna put
you behind bars, understand?
If you really wanna help people,
then you can save them some
trouble and turn yourself in!
Right, so, are you gonna tell me
how this thing works or not?
I can start drilling now,
or you can buy some
time by explaining
how you managed to find me.
[SAKAIDO] Of all places,
why did the killer decide
to hide inside Kaeru?
And why didn't he
try to run for it
once the coast was clear?
I was outta the
room for a while.
Could've escaped easily...
With that wall missing,
he wouldn't even need to
open the door or window.
[SAKAIDO] Wait...
what if from his perspective
there were four walls
in this room?
This disjointed world is
a product of his mind.
So maybe to him it seems like
everything's connected normally.
If so, then maybe to his eyes,
this room is as good as sealed.
But what about the guy who
was freaking out the residents?
How does he play into this?
Now there's an idea.
It could be that the killer was
afraid of this guy as well.
So he locked himself up in here
and used Kaeru's corpse
to play possum.
I get it now.
For our serial killer,
Tamotsu Fukuda,
that broken world seems
perfectly normal
because it matches
his broken mind.
The guy doesn't seem to realize
how messed up he is.
That does seem to be the case.
I think it might have something
to do with the gaping hole
he has in his right
frontal cortex.
The profile we've built
so far would suggest
that he thinks people are
fundamentally broken.
If he believes the hole
in his head fixed him,
then he might wanna fix us now.
And he's got the rookie.
So it's a matter of time... Oh.
[MATSUOKA]
Momoki.
We still haven't
found Fukuda yet.
But if things get desperate,
Hondomachi does have a way to
alert us... and guide us to her.
Not that it's pleasant
to consider.
Right. We'll be ready for that.
[SAKAIDO]
Hm?
[MATSUOKA]
Hondomachi.
Just don't do
anything too crazy.
[HONDOMACHI] Okay. I'll tell
you about the device.
It's called a Wakumusubi.
It was named after the son of
the well goddess, Mizuhanome.
He's a harvest god.
In a way, the Wakumusubi
is a harvesting tool.
[HONDOMACHI]
Hey.
Don't just stand there spinning
your drill while I talk.
Do wanna know how to use it?
All right, then I'll show you!
It looks like another id
well's beginning to form.
Checking our field
officers' Wakumusubis.
Let's see what we've got.
Crap, the new id well's coming
from the rookie's device, sir!
Extract Sakaido! He needs
to switch wells at once.
This isn't my home! Let me go!
[SAKAIDO yelling]
[MOMOKI]
Sorry, Narihisago,
but I need you to dive
into a different well.
[NARIHISAGO sighs]
[NARIHISAGO]
Understood.
You okay?
[NARIHISAGO]
Livin' the dream.
Go ahead and drop him in.
[SAKAIDO]
I've got no idea where I am.
Or what the hell's
going on here.
What I do know is that
dead girl's name.
She's Kaeru. And I'm Sakaido.
I can't remember my full name,
but I know I'm the
brilliant detective.
Which means it's my job to solve
the mystery of her murder.
Wait. Was she murdered?
It doesn't look like
there's an actual mystery
for me to solve here.
[SAKAIDO]
But if that's the case,
what's the point
of my existence?
Odd that her feet are bound.
Why would she tie them together?
Did she think she'd look
more composed that way, or--?
Sakaido was just killed!
He was in the well
for 68.25 seconds.
Now beginning analysis.
I found Koharu Hondomachi.
There's a reflection of her
face on the tip of the drill.
Then there should be other
things reflected on it, too.
Find them!
It appears she's tied to
a stainless-steel table.
The kind used in restaurants.
There's a nearby industrial
refrigerator, too.
[TOGO]
I found her Wakumusubi.
Based on the angle that the
light it emits was reflected,
we can put the room's size
at roughly six by six meters.
There's an abandoned restaurant
just about three kilometers
from Fukuda's house.
Blueprints are downloaded!
Our projection is a match for
the restaurant's basement.
Did you hear that, Matsuoka?
Yeah. I'm on my way now.
That's what it detects?
The intent to kill?
You told the truth.
It really didn't
kill me right away.
Thank you.
What for?
[FUKUDA] I drilled into
quite a few people's heads,
but it never helped.
And now, thanks to you,
I see why that is.
I wasn't doing it right.
People have to fix themselves.
Drill their own holes.
Did you really drill
through your own head?
[FUKUDA]
Yeah. I felt like I had to.
What does that mean?
[FUKUDA]
How's the breeze?
Right now,
everything is just cold.
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER D]
Freeze!
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER B]
Get away from the girl and drop
to your knees,
you hear me, dirtbag?
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER C]
Move in!
Hondomachi!
[ASSAULT TEAM MEMBER D]
Her head's bleeding.
But she has a pulse!
Get her outta here! Now!
You'll come and pay me a visit
if you manage to pull
through, won't you?
[TOGO]
Subject has been apprehended.
En route to HQ now.
[MOMOKI] Got it. Let me
know when they arrive.
How's the rookie?
[TOGO]
We just heard from the hospital.
She's holding on,
so far at least.
What are you--?
Thank you, everybody,
for your help.
Now I need to thank him.
[MOMOKI]
Good work in there.
Thank you for saying so.
Well, we did it.
The killer's in our custody.
[NARIHISAGO]
Oh. That's good.
That was a close encounter
with John Walker.
Your thoughts?
I dunno.
He was all blurry n' hollow--
there wasn't much to see.
Do you know why he
was like that?
This was the killer's
unconscious mind.
There are countless
interpretations.
For now at least.
Even with a team of analysts?
Ya must've found
at least one clue.
[MOMOKI]
No.
When it comes to John Walker,
we're at square one.
[NARIHISAGO]
I could dive again.
Yeah. I'm sure.
I feel just fine, I swear.
I've kicked the bucket in the
well plenty, ya get used to it.
[MOMOKI] You're still
experiencing death each time.
That takes a toll on you.
I'm sure of it.
[NARIHISAGO]
Are you now?
Then I won't bother arguing.
I can dive again.
[NARIHISAGO] Is that girl
from your unit okay?
I know the killer had
her for a while,
but she fought back, right?
How did you know?
A switch flipped somewhere,
and she went from
a docile little drone
to a determined rebel.
Since no one else changed,
I figured the real
girl did something
to shake up the
killer's view of her.
Yeah. She fought and
paid the price.
But it's thanks to her
that we got the guy.
[NARIHISAGO]
I get it now.
So the second id well
I dove into today was hers.
That's pretty damn impressive.
A determined suicide.
This was a single incident,
but as a result of it,
I bet there'll be new elements
in the killer's well now.
I really look forward
to seeing them.
[MOMOKI]
Whenever you dive,
you forget who you are
and everything you know.
I'm surprised that
doesn't bother you.
[NARIHISAGO] Oh, that's
part of the fun for me.
Plus, I get to see Kaeru,
which is almost like
seeing my daughter.
In that both of them
are always dead.
It's been about two
years, right?
[NARIHISAGO] Noticed something
funny about the killer.
The way he hid with Kaeru
showed that he knew
they were both broken.
But he wasn't able to
see that the same thing
was true for his world.
Self-deception works
in strange ways, huh?
We all wanna think we see
the world for what it is.
It's just that simple, right?
It might be. I'm not sure.
You okay?
I mean, you saw the killer
hide inside Kaeru's body.
Seeing her corpse get
used like that,
it must've bothered you.
Kaeru isn't Muku.
You need to insulate your psyche
from the worlds
you're diving into.
Also, remember that you dive
in order to assist
our investigation,
not to root out the killer's
mental weaknesses.
You've driven some to suicide.
We can't have a repeat.
[NARIHISAGO]
A repeat?
Think at this point it'd
be more like a five-peat.
I'm just teasing.
I never intend to
do that again.
But for me to stop completely,
I think I'd probably have to
stop going into wells at all.
And let's be real,
that isn't much of an
option for either of us.
[HAYASEURA]
Tamotsu Fukuda makes five.
Five serial killers that
appear to have dealt
with this John Walker.
[TOGO] Do you think it's
possible that this guy's
manipulating their
unconscious minds?
[HAYASEURA sighs]
It's hard to say.
Kura has been in operation
for about six months now.
A brief time, but you've
used it to peer into
a great number of serial
killers' wells already.
So I'd be curious to hear
what you think is possible.
[TOGO] In the past, I doubted
that John Walker was real.
I believed he was meant to
embody some characteristics
shared by a number of
different serial killers.
I thought he was a symbol
made by the Mizuhanome.
I see.
Like how it always creates Kaeru
as a freshly murdered corpse.
Right.
I thought he might be a
default setting of the wells
that the Mizuhanome generates,
one with a function
that we hadn't
fully come to understand yet.
Well, I haven't
seen any evidence
that would contradict
that line of thinking,
so far at least.
And furthermore,
there's the Mizuhanome.
It remains a mystery
with all of us
still trying to interpret
how it works.
Perhaps Momoki is
overly concerned
with this John Walker fellow.
[TOGO]
I think he has a natural desire
to understand the tool
he's using, sir.
In any case, seeing
the residents' reaction
to John Walker when he appeared,
and how it seemed to
frighten all of them,
was enough to convince me.
They were completely
unfazed by Kaeru's corpse.
Because that was created
by the Mizuhanome.
The fear they displayed
was a reflection
of the feelings
of the well's owner.
We know John Walker is real
because we know the
Perforator remembers him.
Moreover...
...we know he can leave
quite the impression,
one that can be felt in the id.
This is more theory than fact,
but I think he can affect
a person's urge to kill.
As for how or why someone
would go about doing
that, I can't say.
I've already done a great
deal more speculating
than I'm comfortable with, sir.
I see.
Then we have no choice
except to consider
the matter in earnest.
If someone is making
serial killers,
then we need to stop them.
[NARIHISAGO] You chose
to die, but by hanging.
You never wanted to be
torn apart by a drill.
[NARIHISAGO]
I'm sorry, Kaeru.
I should've moved you to safety.
Next time I dive into that
well, if there's time,
I'm sure Sakaido will find
a way to do that for you.
He's the brilliant detective.
He'll know.