[SAKAIDO]
A well storm?
Because I remembered
who I am? My real self?
This well, it belongs to me!
If that's true,
then this entire time...
...John Walker was
manipulating me, too!
[screams]
[KOKUFU] Not only is
the storm getting bigger,
the well itself seems
to be expanding!
[HABUTAE]
We've lost Sakaido's position!
It's impossible to track him!
Cut the Mizuhanome's power!
But that's unheard of!
[TOGO] So is the formation
of a well storm.
Hurry up and do it!
[grunts]
I can't! No response!
The Mizuhanome's protecting
itself from termination.
[TOGO growls]
[WAKASHIKA] This id well
wasn't from our repository.
It was created from cognition
particles gleaned at Momoki's.
That rules out the Kura
making an error.
The Wakumusubi-Mizuhanome
link wouldn't allow it.
There's no mistake.
Which means, the switch
happened at the scene.
Either Mr. Matsuoka set us up,
or somebody else is
trying to set him up
and he fell into the trap.
I need a review on
Matsuoka's movements now!
[WAKASHIKA]
Ma'am!
I'm already on it.
What?
[SHIRATAKE]
When you think aloud,
you forget about all
your other duties.
Heh. That's what I call backup!
[SHIRATAKE]
What are you so proud of?
Huh. Got it.
Between entering the bedroom
and the Wakumusubi scan,
Matsuoka did nothing suspicious.
I need you to run a check to
see if any other investigators
entered the bedroom.
Yes, Ma'am.
Get Matsuoka on the
phone, right now!
[MATSUOKA]
I'm headed back to the scene.
Whoever did this...
they're gonna pay!
[SAKAIDO]
Why? What was your motive?
What the hell are
you playing at?
[chuckles]
Answer me, dammit!
[ANAIDO]
Something wrong?
[SAKAIDO]
You want me to kill you. Why?
[ANAIDO]
I deserve it, don't I?
After what I did, purposely
trapping you in the well
after dreaming about it...
That's pre-meditation.
When the opportunity arose,
something drove me forward,
and I embraced it, despite
knowing the consequences.
What are you waiting for?
Take your anger out on me.
[SAKAIDO]
No.
I reject your little offer.
[gasps]
Gotta clear my head and think!
Same goes for you!
Giving in to my anger
and beating you to death
would be playing right
into John Walker's hands.
If I fulfilled the role
he designed for me,
you'd be dead.
The fact you're
somehow still alive
is an inconvenience for him.
I want to know why.
Why you went along with him.
Of course. You want to die.
Is your life so unbearable?
I mean, you survived drilling
a damn hole into your head.
Tell me, why did you drill a
hole in your head like that?
What was so awful back then?
You don't have that scar
as a brilliant detective,
and you still want out
of this existence?
Say something.
What are you looking at?
[SAKAIDO]
The numbers?
Hey, what's all this?
[ANAIDO] Got kinda bored
so I started counting sand.
[SAKAIDO]
And who are you?
[ANAIDO chuckles]
My name? I couldn't tell you.
Wow! So cool!
Incredibly brutal,
but also pragmatic!
Could you not point at me?
[ANAIDO laughs]
Your favorite number.
It's three, right?
[ANAIDO chuckles]
[ANAIDO]
Guess I'll have to pass up
another opportunity to die.
Ah, and regarding the number
three, what an elegant number.
If things worked out the way
John Walker had planned,
you'd already be dead.
Because once the sand is gone,
this is a world of numbers.
They captivate you.
You can't help but be
a prisoner to them.
That's why. Why you
used the drill.
You have arithmomania and
wanted to escape the agony.
Thing is, every time you
dived into an id well,
the hole would seal up
and your condition
would start to plague you again.
Must be a curse, paired with a
brilliant detective's intellect.
Death is your only way out.
[ANAIDO laughs]
You nailed it!
I sympathize,
but unfortunately,
I can't grant you
the death you seek.
Because there's an important job
that John Walker
doesn't want you to do,
but you're the only
one who's capable.
Though I find it hard to
believe, you have my attention.
What is this job?
[SAKAIDO]
You haven't noticed?
The cockpit that used to be
here completely disappeared.
[ANAIDO]
It was huge. How could it--?
[SAKAIDO] My other well,
you dove into it, right?
It was a world of numbers with
the same layout as this one.
Kaeru was also there
at the starting point.
When you woke up,
I imagine you found yourself
next to her dead body,
attached at the wrist.
With handcuffs.
Likely a remnant from the days
when you were a police officer.
[SAKAIDO]
I suppose.
As for Hondomachi's cockpit,
did you stumble upon it?
[ANAIDO]
Inevitably.
Your well didn't
exactly provide me
with an efficient way
of killing myself.
Sure, there was lightning,
but it was hell having to wait
forever to be electrocuted.
Regardless, you still
located the cockpit.
Are you able to remember
the exact sequence of numbers
to retrace your steps?
Yes.
[ANAIDO]
Not only for that path.
I can recall every last number
that entered my field of vision.
Naturally, the more
numbers that are present,
the more compelled I am
to take them all in.
I see. Guess that means
you can navigate.
Since you have the map of the
entire well inside your head.
[ANAIDO]
Easily.
However, the thing
you're searching for...
I wonder if you'll find it.
[SAKAIDO]
The storm is expanding,
so the Mizuhanome
and this id well
are most likely
continuing to update.
Which must be the reason why
the cockpit disappeared.
What the--?
Assistant Director!
[TOGO]
Yes?
I looked away from
Narihisago's first well,
and when I went
check on it again...
...the cockpit's not there!
Where did it go?
[KOKUFU]
Standby, looking for it.
It seems the moment the storm
appeared in the desert,
the cockpit disappeared
from the lightning id well.
Keep monitoring the situation.
I know our brilliant detectives
will find a way back.
[SAKAIDO] When the Mizuhanome
automatically updated,
I bet it brought the
cockpit to our location,
and Hondomachi along with it.
This well's huge.
Where do we look?
In the same spot.
The well's not different,
only the time is.
[ANAIDO]
Holy hell.
Why does your subconscious
always have to be so brutal?
Guess what.
If it were any more forgiving,
we'd have to worry about someone
above observing our actions.
Now we stand a chance.
[ANAIDO gasps]
[SAKAIDO] Sometimes you fall
asleep for only a short time,
but it feels like the dreams
last much longer.
You know what I'm talking about?
Why does that matter?
[SAKAIDO] The very same
thing happened to me
when I entered the well
within this well.
You were in there ten minutes.
By the time I was extracted,
over a year had passed
in that reality.
[ANAIDO] Over a year!
Incredible! Lucky you!
[SAKAIDO]
Yeah, actually.
Only thing is,
that's never happened before
in a normal id well.
When you dive in,
time is synchronized with
the outside world.
So what made it different?
Or more importantly,
how does it relate to dreams?
Perhaps the temporal factor
is dependent on whether
a third party is observing you.
Your actions.
If someone else is witnessing
the events occur,
time is synchronized.
Otherwise, it's free
to dilate or contract.
Don't you see?
Five minutes in the outside
world is 300 seconds,
but in this well, there's no
telling how long we have.
[SAKAIDO] And the same
situation would be true
in the well within the well.
To Hondomachi.
[HONDOMACHI]
Amazing.
Mr. Narihisago
accomplished all this
despite forgetting
he was in a well.
Now I have to pick up
where he left off,
starting with examining
each killers'
preferred method of taking life.
Their calling card.
The Challenger pummels
his opponents to death.
As for the Face-lifter,
Tongue-tearer,
Thigh-severer, and Arm-twister,
their M.O.s are pretty
self-explanatory.
Whether John Walker assigned
these preferences
to these killers, or whether
they surfaced on their own,
I can't say right now.
That aside, if you
consider the various
serial killers
throughout history,
there's a clear tendency to use
a particular method of killing.
Which means, John
Walker's no different,
and he also operates
using a particular system.
Narihisago reached
the same conclusion.
[HONDOMACHI]
And I can see the answer.
You mean they don't
all die instantly?
No one I drill dies instantly.
All of us linger for a time.
[HONDOMACHI]
We linger.
Tamotsu Fukuda and all
the other serial killers
John Walker created,
their victims didn't
always die right away.
The Face-lifter.
Thigh-severer. Arm-twister.
They all had victims
that ended up surviving,
which ultimately led to
their capture or death.
Is John Walker's M.O.
creating killers
whose targets don't
necessarily die?
Well, it's a start, but I still
need to explore this further.
Let's see. What else might
they have in common?
In every case, the maximum
number of victims
is always seven.
Now, assuming John Walker
works at the Kura,
he either has a
victim found alive,
then police arrest the
murderer he created,
or he gets an officer
to kill them
before an eighth person dies.
Never more than seven deaths.
Seven.
If the acceleration of
John Walker's plans
by having Director
Momoki arrested
is a precursor to him
ceasing his activity
or moving to new methods.
Then how does it relate
to the number seven?
I get it.
The timeline of the victims
only appears to be random
because it's based
on body discovery
and estimated time of death.
Those dates taken by
themselves are irregular,
without commonalities,
but by reordering each one
based on the killing
blow, they line up.
Thigh-severer on Mondays.
Tuesdays, the Face-lifter.
Wednesdays, Tongue-tearer.
Thursdays, the Gravedigger.
Arm-twister on Fridays.
Saturdays, the Perforator.
Yuji Oonuki was killed
on a Saturday,
on the exact same Saturday that
I ended up getting injured.
Also, the Challenger's killings
and Muku Narihisago's death
both occurred on Sunday.
That's his pattern. John Walker.
He's been manipulating
their drive to kill
on certain days of the week.
Almost like it's his job.
Or as if he were God creating
the world in seven days.
[phone buzzing]
Hey, Hondomachi! Where are you?
You disappeared without
saying a word!
[HONDOMACHI] I-I'm sorry, but
I had to look into something.
[MATSUOKA]
Next time, tell me!
[HONDOMACHI] So what happened
to Tamotsu Fukuda?
What? He's gone!
Posed as the victim
and flew the coop!
[HONDOMACHI]
Is that right?
Sorry, but I have to go.
Where the hell are you?
I better hurry.
Found it! And the
little lady, too.
[HONDOMACHI]
Tamotsu Fukuda. Don't move.
[FUKUDA]
How'd you find this place?
And who are you?
Forgive me, but I don't
have enough time to explain.
You're just gonna
have to believe me.
For reasons I won't get into,
I know about you and
where I'd find you.
Come on, what could you
possibly know about me?
[HONDOMACHI] I know that
what you really want to do
is take that drill and run
it though your head again.
Come on, admit it.
I'm right, aren't I?
I can tell you no longer
have any intention
of trying to hurt me.
Therefore, I don't have any
reason to hurt you either.
As for how I know all of this...
It's hard to believe,
but a while back,
I made the choice to put
a hole in my head
using that very same drill
you're holding now.
[chuckles]
I don't have any idea
what you're talking about,
but I can't deny that
you're right about me.
So I have to assume
you're telling the truth.
So tell me, did you like it?
[HONDOMACHI] Now it's gone,
I feel incomplete.
Then it suited you.
[HONDOMACHI]
Not really.
More like, it's a part
of who I am now.
Funny.
Who would've thought one
needs to lose something
in order to feel complete.
[HONDOMACHI]
You said it.
[FUKUDA]
So? What brings you here?
[HONDOMACHI]
I wanna know about your dreams.
[gasps]
Look at this sketch.
Do you see him when you sleep?
[FUKUDA]
Sure.
It was August 15th,
three years ago.
And September,
the 7th and the 10th.
Uh. You can remember
the exact dates?
I used to be very
good with numbers.
However, not so much anymore.
Then how good are
you with times?
[FUKUDA]
On August 15th,
it would've been
two to three p.m.
September 7th would've been
from eleven p.m. to three a.m.
September 10th, the same
times mentioned for the 7th.
You wake up early.
Was the 15th a nap?
I wouldn't say that.
I drilled the hole
into my head then,
which made me lose
consciousness and collapse.
But instead of dying, I had
a vision of that old dude.
[HONDOMACHI] I see. And what
happened in the dream?
Not a lot. There was
a girl in a hospital room.
That man was there and invited
me to drill a hole in her head.
To which I said,
"Thanks, but no thanks."
He offered again the
two days in September
and I gave him the
exact same response.
I told him dream holes
don't interest me.
So he knew you,
but not the reason you
have the need to drill.
No luck.
I checked employee records
for the afternoon of August
15th, three years ago.
Everyone with access to the well
data was present that day.
Maybe, but who's to say
they didn't just fall asleep
while on the clock?
I doubt that.
All right.
How 'bout someone who
took their job seriously,
but was sleeping during
that afternoon?
[HONDOMACHI]
Hm?
You never said that they
had to be located in Japan.
[gasps]
A work trip overseas.
What are you, a cop?
[HONDOMACHI]
Yeah.
Will we get to meet again?
[HONDOMACHI]
I don't know.
But getting caught by the police
will open a new door,
I can tell you
that much for sure.
[FUKUDA]
Hm.
No reason to stop
believing you now.
[MATSUOKA] I'm here. In Momoki's
bedroom, as instructed.
I copy that.
Give me detailed
visual information
of everything in the room.
[MATSUOKA]
Roger.
[TOGO] Look for traces
of anything being moved,
or signs of something
being brought in
that doesn't belong there.
[MATSUOKA]
Huh?
I've known Momoki for years,
but I've never been
inside his room.
I'll look around
and try my best.
[gasps]
[MATSUOKA]
Hm?
[TOGO]
Straight ahead.
The picture on the left
side of the shelf.
[MATSUOKA]
This one?
[TOGO]
Run a scan on it.
[gasps]
Now return to the bedroom
and try running another scan.
[MATSUOKA]
All right.
You did it, Togo.
How'd you know? Tell me.
[TOGO] That picture wasn't
there the last time I visited.
[gasps]
Knew it.
Two pictures.
The second one is Narihisago's.
[MATSUOKA] When he drove
Fuyukawa to suicide,
it must've retained
cognition particles.
Find out who had access
to his cell's photos.
[ANAIDO]
Well, time to wake her up
so she can join the party.
On August 15th, three years ago,
a high-ranking officer
traveled to New York
to receive training.
[MAN]
Who is this?
Oh. John Walker,
glad I could catch you.
[gasps]
[HONDOMACHI]
Huh? Talk about perfect timing.
Goodbye! And thank you!
[sirens wailing]
[FUKUDA]
Don't mention it.
Hang on, what is this?
[ANAIDO] We're in "brilliant
detective" Sakaido's well.
A.K.A. Akihito Narihisago.
And you're Hondomachi.
[gasps]
Whoa! You are rocking that hole!
Well, it's just a
part of who I am.
This place, it changed.
After three years,
the lightning abated.
Isn't that good?
I guess.
Now, it's empty.
Oh. I nearly forgot. Thank you.
[ANAIDO]
What I'd do?
Well, not you you.
Mr. Narihisago, with your help,
I finished the investigation
and figured out the
identity of John Walker.
It's Chief Hayaseura.
[SAKAIDO] That right?
Let's head back to Kaeru.
[ANAIDO] What makes you think
finding her will save us?
Because she's a murder victim,
and a victim of this world
more specifically,
and we're the
brilliant detectives.
If we end up
solving her mystery,
she won't harbor any
resentments against us,
even though she told us from
the start not to leave her side.
Hey, just who is Kaeru anyway?
And why does she need your help?
[SAKAIDO]
The more important question is,
who is Kiki Asukai and why
does she look like Kaeru?
[NARIHISAGO] Why was there a
serial killer in there with us
out to murder you?
They're the only kind
of people who appear.
[SAKAIDO]
What does is it mean?
Miss Asukai's telepathy.
The different serial killers'
entering her dreams.
Their drives to kill.
[MOMOKI]
Sorry for calling so late,
but Miss Asukai disappeared
from the hospital.
I thought I'd ask if she
said anything to you
that could help us
figure this out.
As a matter of fact, she did.
[SHIRATAKE]
Huh?
I found them! All three!
The only reason
we found the solution
was because they
couldn't watch us.
But now it's time to be seen.
Extract them!
[gasps]
[TOGO]
Koharu, are you all right?
I'm feeling fine.
Listen, we know his identity.
John Walker--
it's Chief Hayaseura!
[BOTH gasp]
[growls]
Contact metro police!
And me get a warrant!
Detain him, now!
[TOGO]
Find out what's going on.
[KOKUFU]
It's the Mizuhanome!
The main power's been cut!
[HAYASEURA] It's as if I put
you here only yesterday.
[HAYASEURA]
But it's your turn. Kiki Asukai.