[HABUTAE]
Kiki Asukai.
Family resided in
Fukui Prefecture.
Rarely attended elementary
and middle school.
Expelled from boarding school.
Sent to an institution after
her parents disowned her.
First suicide attempt was at 18.
Hospitalized, released,
becomes an artist.
Repeatedly institutionalized
after three more attempts.
At 21, she's kidnapped
by the Challenger.
Rescued by Momoki after
Narihisago went rogue
and shot her abductor.
She disappeared
three months later
while recovering
in the hospital.
Has never been found.
The night she vanished, several
nurses experienced comas.
Connection is unclear.
That's all the relevant
information Director Momoki
had stored on the cloud.
The director was independently
investigating what happened
to this Kiki Asukai person?
What for?
Unknown.
[WAKASHIKA] For 13 nurses
all to lose consciousness
at the same time...
Was some drug responsible?
[HABUTAE]
Also unknown.
The only files here are
on the Challenger
and articles about
the coma incident.
Everything else is gone--
school, institution records,
hospitalization charts for
Asukai and the nurses.
They were wiped?
[HABUTAE] However, we do know
the person who scrubbed it.
It'd have to be
someone with access.
From the wellside... Momoki.
Bingo.
[TOGO]
Notify the Metropolitan Police.
[HABUTAE]
Ma'am.
As for now, let's continue
with Hondomachi's extraction.
Numbers, numbers,
and more numbers
as far as the eye can see.
This lightning feels like
it goes on forever, too.
That's what I'm workin' with.
Do they share some connection?
Could this seemingly random
arrangement of digits
hold any meaning?
Or are they just merely random?
Yeah. That's it.
There is no meaning whatsoever.
Deriving any sort of sequence
the lightning makes
is humanly impossible.
Too many numbers, and the
strikes are too far away.
In other words, you don't need
to ascertain the sequence
to survive this world.
Which is perfect. Since there's
no way with so many numbers.
[gasps]
[TOGO]
That run lasted 137 seconds.
The third one that's
gone over two minutes.
You're improving.
That makes over 20 times
I've been struck by lightning.
You'd think I'd be used to it.
[TOGO] We're keeping a
close eye on your vitals.
Though we've noticed your
heartbeats become irregular.
There's no need to pretend
you're concerned about my life.
I realize I'm not the most
important one here.
[TOGO]
You saw the cockpit?
[FUKUDA]
Yeah.
[TOGO]
Good.
Seems it was no more
than 89 meters away.
Can you reach it?
I'm not sure. Shall we find out?
[TOGO]
No, that's not necessary.
Great news.
We've got another well
for you to dive into.
[FUKUDA sighs]
[FUKUDA]
Of course you do.
[humming]
We scanned the body
and the outfit,
but particles show up
in the bedroom?
Damn!
[TOGO] We're entering
Director Momoki's id well?
That's right. Akihito
Narihisago's had a cockpit,
so I imagine we'll also
find one inside Momoki's.
If there is and if it happens to
have Kiki Asukai's well loaded,
we might be able to bring
Miss Hondomachi back home.
But in order for this to work,
there needs to be a third
party to eject the pilot.
What a thought. Having serial
killers working together.
[FUKUDA]
Good to see you, partner.
Tell me, how's it feel
having someone wandering
around your unconscious?
Whatever goes on in the id
well doesn't affect my mind.
[FUKUDA]
True,
it's merely a drive to kill
gleaned from the past.
It couldn't possibly contain
your entire psyche.
And you of all people
must know
that's the core for
serial killers like us.
The kind of thing one could use
to drive a person to suicide,
if they were so inclined.
[GUARD A]
Cut the chit-chat.
Surely a courteous greeting
between colleagues
is allowed, right?
[TOGO]
It's Togo.
Fukuda and Mister Narihisago
will dive into the same well.
Why'd she address you as
"mister"? Do you know her?
[TOGO] Once inside,
you'll be strangers.
Try your best to work together.
[FUKUDA]
Permission to ask a question.
Granted.
[FUKUDA]
If there're two detectives,
will there be two Kaerus?
We can't say for certain.
It's never been
attempted before,
but if there's any danger,
we'll extract you.
[FUKUDA]
Right. Right. One more thing.
I'm curious if you've
ever read a mystery.
What?
[FUKUDA]
A mystery. A detective story.
A few back when I was a student.
[FUKUDA] The classics,
with a brilliant detective?
Yes, of course.
[FUKUDA]
Then you'll understand.
You see, generally
speaking, two aren't able
to simultaneously exist
within a single novel.
If there's only one solution,
it stands to reason one of
the detective's theories
has to be incorrect.
The first detective
reveals the initial mystery
to the audience, only for
the second detective
to peel back the layers,
revealing an even deeper one.
Thus, turning the
story on its head.
You can't reasonably be
considered a brilliant detective
if you come to the
wrong conclusion.
Though I could see the first
detective being correct
if they only pretended their
initial findings were flawed.
In short, one of us will
inevitably lose their status
as "brilliant detective."
Then what will the
repercussions be?
Will this cause the fabricated
world to unravel?
[TOGO] I see no point in
debating the issue further.
[chuckles]
Well, if anything goes wrong
down there, then who cares?
You'll only be short
two serial killers.
You can't deny that's a
pretty fundamental problem
with this scenario.
[TOGO]
Injecting Sakaido and Anaido.
[KOKUFU]
Anaido's opened his eyes.
[HABUTAE] We aren't
receiving information yet.
Every aspect of this
is untested.
Be sure to make observations
with ample documentation.
Note anything out
of the ordinary.
Ma'am, Sakaido's waking up, too.
Data stream received.
[ANAIDO]
So, you're finally awake.
[SAKAIDO]
And who are you?
My name? I couldn't tell you.
Same here. I don't
know who I am either.
Heh. Well, that's
certainly inconvenient.
I wonder if that girl's
suffering from amnesia as well.
Wait, what girl?
[SAKAIDO]
Oh, crap!
It's Kaeru.
Kaeru, huh?
Seems they've awakened
and synced up.
Any warning signs so far?
None I see.
Good.
As of now they're both operating
successfully in the same well.
I'm not seeing anything but
sand for miles and miles.
Momoki's well is an
utter wasteland.
Sakaido.
I suddenly remembered my name,
and one other thing,
I'm a brilliant detective.
No last name though.
I know my name is Anaido.
I guess I don't have
a last name either,
but I'm a brilliant detective.
A pleasure.
Yeah.
Wow! So cool!
I'm trying to focus on the job.
Hey, same here.
Your job is to solve the mystery
of Kaeru's death? Really?
Regardless of how we got here,
it seems we share a common goal.
All right, so Kaeru doesn't
have any external wounds.
But... the hole indicates
she was looking for water.
We were unconscious
and buried in sand,
but she was awake,
exposed to the elements.
Which wore out her stamina.
Dehydration set in and
she died of organ failure.
Her cause of death doesn't
seem to be a mystery.
[SAKAIDO] Were we wearing
watches or something?
They're missing.
Seems someone stole them.
Whaddya say you and I track
down this watch thief?
His footprints
are still visible.
We can catch up to him
by following them
and see what he knows.
[SAKAIDO] Before we do,
let me ask you something.
Do you have any belongings?
Not a thing.
We have neither food nor water,
and if we move
around in this heat,
then chances are,
we'll end up dehydrated
and might even die ourselves.
Incredibly brutal,
but also pragmatic!
Could you not point at me?
[ANAIDO laughs]
[ANAIDO]
My turn to deduce.
Kaeru's body is here so
we can drink the blood
and eat the meat,
and thereby survive.
What the hell's wrong with you?
Blood has a fairly high amount
of salt concentration.
If we drink it, we'll only
end up being thirstier.
Besides, now's not the time
for us to be eating anything,
seeing how water is used
in the digestion process.
[ANAIDO]
Oh.
You sure you're a
brilliant detective?
[ANAIDO chuckles]
There's not a doubt in my mind.
[SAKAIDO]
Great.
We have to conserve
our hydration.
You know how?
Take your coat off.
I suppose I could
leave it behind.
It is rather warm.
No. Look.
You're still going to need
it to protect your body
from direct sunlight.
Why remove it then?
So you can soak it in urine.
[trickling]
[ANAIDO] Isn't this a waste
of perfectly good urine?
[SAKAIDO
"A waste"?
[ANAIDO]
It's our only source of water.
[SAKAIDO] You may as well
be drinking from the ocean.
Consuming it will just cause us
to dehydrate in the long run.
There are better uses.
Well, my clothes are
thoroughly drenched.
Good.
This way, we should prevent some
water loss through our skin.
Hurry and wrap your coat
around your head.
This stinks.
But at least we don't have
to worry about heatstroke
and dehydration for a while.
Now, we can focus
on other matters.
Right. We're properly equipped
to track down our watch thief.
[SAKAIDO]
Not yet.
We haven't finished
processing the scene here.
And after we leave, the sand
will cover our footprints,
making it nearly impossible to
find our way back to her body.
Which means the thief's trail
will also get buried
if we don't follow it soon.
Maybe we should split up.
It's best not to act rashly.
We don't know anything
about our situation,
and we might not even
catch up to whoever was here.
The trail might disappear
partway, or more likely,
we both might run out of
steam before locating him.
"Might." That word seems
to keep coming up.
I counted four times.
You mean three?
[ANAIDO]
I wish.
But I'll remind you of what
you said to me earlier.
"If we move around in this heat,
then chances are,
we'll end up dehydrated
and might even die, too."
Right, but that
still remains fact,
and I'm not saying we should
ignore the footsteps,
just that our deductions
should be prioritized.
What's left to deduce?
There's nothing suspicious
about her cause of death.
Meanwhile, we have prints
leading us to an actual mystery.
But not for long.
[SAKAIDO]
Just hold on.
[ANAIDO] The way I see it,
there are two of us here,
so maybe we're supposed
to split up.
Listen, I'll go on ahead,
and after you're through
solving this head-scratcher,
you can follow my trail.
Finish before the
wind erases mine.
Why is he in such a big rush?
I just want to assure you
not all brilliant detectives
act the same way as him.
Trust me.
[KOKUFU] No sign of
a single insect so far.
[SHIRATAKE]
And no plant life either.
One more observation.
As of yet, the sun hasn't
moved from its zenith
Time's frozen in place.
I'm impressed with
how long Anaido's
been able to survive out there.
Hopefully he'll be able to reach
whoever made those footprints.
Sakaido's on the move.
[SAKAIDO grunts]
I wondered when you'd catch up.
You all right?
Just peachy.
Your legs are wobbling.
You're low on energy.
Do you think we'll be able to
find a way outta this desert?
Not likely.
[ANAIDO laughs]
What makes you so
sure, detective?
[SAKAIDO]
This place isn't normal.
The sun hasn't moved.
[ANAIDO]
Yeah. I was curious about that.
Could Earth's revolutions
have suddenly increased?
Or the speed of rotation slowed?
I don't think either
is the issue.
This place, I get the feeling
it's an endless desert world
and nothing else exists
except more dunes.
Even if there was
something out of sight,
I doubt it's possible
for us to reach it.
So this planet's comprised
of five things.
There's a ton of sand,
Kaeru's body,
the wristwatch thief
who may hold the truth
about what happened to her,
and of course, us,
the brilliant detectives.
[chuckles]
Sounds like once we've
wrapped up this case,
the world will lose
its raison d'être.
You forgot him.
[yelps]
[ANAIDO laughs]
Who's the one unsteady
on his feet now?
[SAKAIDO]
The sand gave way. Not me.
Dammit!
That's quicksand. This I know.
Don't panic.
The more you struggle and flail,
the faster it'll suck you in.
And here I was thinkin' you were
well-versed in desert survival,
but it looks as though
you're only an expert
when it comes to piss and blood.
You think this is funny?
[ANAIDO]
All pits are the same.
The more you struggle to escape,
the stronger its hold becomes.
[SAKAIDO]
Ugh. Spare me.
I'm not finished yet.
Hell is a sinkhole,
but it takes time before
completely swallowing someone.
Before that happens, you can
gradually crawl your way out.
I'll be damned. Guess he really
is a brilliant detective.
Hey, I heard that!
I told you, didn't I?
Heh.
I don't know if you'll be
more or less impressed
when I tell you I know how to
avoid sinking in quicksand,
but not the way to escape.
I just applied general theory
concerning hell
to the situation.
Glad it worked out for you,
though. Brother.
Brother, huh? Heh.
You're a strange one.
[DETECTIVE A] Not gonna
give us anything, huh?
Come on. Help out
a fellow officer.
I would if I was
in your position.
Fine then.
Guess we'll just have to
depend on your friends.
Why get a confession
when they can deliver
the missing pieces, right?
[DETECTIVE A laughs]
So how does it feel knowing
the people you once led
are busy trying
to take you down?
They're inside a well?
[DETECTIVE B] That's right,
pal. Guess which one.
Not mine.
[gasps] Get them out!
[thud]
[COLLEAGUE C]
Huh?
[MOMOKI grunts]
They need to extract, now!
[SAKAIDO]
Are you okay?
Yeah. Don't pretend you are.
I could still carry you.
Don't expect you'd
make it too far if you did.
[ANAIDO]
Only one of us needs to survive.
But if we go down
at the same time...
[SAKAIDO]
You bring up a good point.
Then I volunteer to die. I kinda
get the feeling I should.
[SAKAIDO]
Hold on before you do.
I mean it.
I'm sure, but I don't think
you need to just yet. Look.
[ANAIDO]
Hm?
Something tells me the
wind didn't cause this.
That is brilliant.
[SAKAIDO laughs]
[BOTH laugh]
I solved the mystery!
[SAKAIDO]
He made it all this way
only to drown in the quicksand.
Talk about unlucky.
[ANAIDO chuckles]
What do you say we get a look
at this watch thief of ours?
Sure.
We made it here together, huh?
[WAKASHIKA] Give us a break
and just dig him up.
Quicksand alone didn't
do that to his face.
Run a facial reconstruction.
[HABUTAE]
Ma'am.
Hey. What's that?
[gasps]
[WAKASHIKA]
A Mizuhanome.
Some kind of chair?
The quicksand may
have taken his life,
but since his footprints
lead right up to this,
he must've wanted us to find it.
[ANAIDO]
Mh-hm.
Maybe that was the whole point,
since stealing a watch in the
desert seems a little peculiar.
Don't tell me you're
just realizing that.
I thought you called
him the "watch thief"
because we needed
a moniker for him.
[ANAIDO]
What?
Well, regardless, this
machine was waiting for us.
[ANAIDO]
Hmm...
Look at this.
[gasps]
Kiki Asukai.
Name doesn't ring a bell.
And I've no idea
what this means.
But for now, we'll hit "enter"
and see what happens.
Wait ten minutes,
then hit eject.
Well, that's not very long.
We may even be alive by then.
And finally close this case.
I guess so. Best of
luck, Detective.
Yeah.
Are you sure, Director?
No extraction?
I'm acting director.
Nothing has been finalized.
Yes. We're letting
Sakaido do this.
It seems like the Mizuhanome
wanted them to find it.
Not to mention this
is why we dispatched
two brilliant detectives
in the first place.
Best case scenario, it leads
to a well within a well,
and diving in will help us
find where Hondomachi is.
And it could provide
more info on Kiki Asukai.
It'd help to know
more about her.
[ANAIDO] My sixth sense is
telling me something's wrong,
but oh, well.
Then trust me. Let's do this.
"Let's" do this.
[SAKAIDO] You and I are
brilliant detectives.
We were right about everything.
All the events were
carefully arranged
so we would arrive
at this point...
...this conclusion.
They need to extract!
It was all a trap!