What?
[screams]
[URAIDO]
How very cruel.
This id well must derive from
the killer's first memory.
One that was equally as cruel.
[SAKAIDO]
Take this!
[cries]
[URAIDO] I'd suggest not
shouting beforehand--
ruins the element of surprise.
Hm?
Plus, it seems you woke him up.
Bastard! You're in no
position to lecture anyone!
[SAKAIDO yells]
[URAIDO]
I'm disappointed.
Such speech is unbefitting
a brilliant detective.
I take it you remember
who you are, Narihisago.
Well, yeah.
If you don't remember
your own tragic past,
you can't take revenge on
the person who's responsible.
That's a terrible notion.
What's all this talk
about revenge?
You and I are both brilliant
detectives and serial killers.
Why can't we get along?
[SAKAIDO] We're not alike,
you fucking psychopath.
[URAIDO] I'm astonished
to hear you say that.
Precisely what
distinguishes you from me?
A brilliant detective is one
who inquires. I'm doing that.
Making inquiries for
the sake of justice,
although in my own way.
Still, I can't help it if you
don't appreciate my methods.
Ha.
Yes!
Nice, Hondomachi.
[HIJIRIIDO]
Glad to help, Mr. Sakaido,
but please, call me Hijiriido
when we're in the well.
[SAKAIDO]
Okay.
But your real name is...
Never mind. You got it.
[chuckles]
[URAIDO]
That wasn't very nice of you.
Though it does illustrate
my point. Yes?
You and I are no different.
The three of us are driven
to ensnare and kill.
As for justice, that depends
on the criteria used to judge.
Even if my version can't
be found in this world,
outside is another
story, is it not?
I simply must do what
I can from within here.
Unfortunately,
I'm unable to leave.
So the Mizuhanome has no choice
but to repair my data.
And, Miss Hondomachi-- Oh.
Excuse me, you prefer to
be called Miss Hijiriido.
I applaud your creativity,
but you're dealing with
a brilliant detective.
I recall you were trapped in
a storm within your well--
till you exploited Fukuda's
abilities to escape.
[HIJIRIIDO] I wouldn't
have made it without him.
But still, that doesn't
mean I used him.
The way I understand it,
a gentleman's hat
is important to him.
[URAIDO]
Hm?
[sighs] I suppose that
was meant to provoke me.
Guess I'll play along.
[gunshot]
[MATSUOKA]
You okay, Momoki?
[MOMOKI] My head was spinning
as soon as I entered.
Also nauseous.
Seems Kiki Asukai's
powers have grown
and the suit can't keep up.
[MATSUOKA]
Unfortunately, it's all we got.
I'll hurry.
[yells]
Boom! Down you go!
Quick, put it on!
You truly think playing hide and
seek will accomplish anything?
Are you joking?
You don't have brains!
I'm the smart one!
There it is!
Just past the house.
[SAKAIDO]
You!
[groans]
My friend, I believe revenge
should be executed
more elegantly.
No one asked.
Can you stand?
[URAIDO] Please, don't strain
yourself on my account.
Remain seated.
Now let's all calm down and
talk like civilized people.
So, where is Fukuda?
You went through all the trouble
of luring me into his well.
Let me guess, he's waiting for
your signal to spring a trap.
Of course, it's doubtful whether
you can depend on him
to be a third pillar.
The man's an insult to
brilliant detectives like us.
Well, I think you're gonna
be in for a nasty shock.
Just you wait.
Not another unsophisticated
surprise attack, I hope.
Come on. You don't know?
[URAIDO]
Hm?
[SAKAIDO chuckles]
[BOTH chuckle]
He still hasn't noticed.
It must've slipped his mind
that he's dealing with
a couple of brilliant
detectives.
[URAIDO]
Hmm.
[SAKAIDO]
Hold on.
What's wrong?
I thought we were gonna be
civilized and discuss this.
Now, that's more like it.
Narihisago, I wanna
do the honors.
But before I start,
I have a question.
It's about the number seven.
What it's mean to
you, Mr. Uraido?
Sorry, I mean, Chief Hayaseura.
It is a divine number.
The Bible aside, it's--
[HIJIRIIDO laughs]
[HIJIRIIDO]
That's what I thought.
So this was all about
your God complex.
What you said earlier,
about justice,
how you had your own sense
of the word, I believe you.
Look at the facts.
Not only did you
limit the number
of serial killers you created,
but you extended the same
rule to their victims.
Never more than seven.
And once you hit your goal...
...you intended
to kill yourself.
Clever.
Except, you're only counting
the Challenger, the
Gravedigger, et cetera.
It seems I ended up
creating an eighth. Him.
Huh?
[URAIDO]
"The Cornerer." You like it?
You can't be serious. That's
even worse than the others.
You're wrong, because he's
not a serial killer.
His victims, all of
those murderers,
were pushed into suicide.
In other words, to make sure
you'd be apprehended in the end,
you created the Cornerer.
[gasps]
That's absurd!
What you're saying is the serial
killer rules he invented
apply directly to himself.
And once you reach your
limit of seven victims,
it's either death or arrest.
With zero exceptions made.
[URAIDO] You're wrong!
I did no such thing.
[HIJIRIIDO] You can deny it,
but there's always
the possibility you
acted unconsciously.
You're a detective, too.
I guess you have some
sense of justice.
But I have a job to
stop people like you
from carrying out their plots.
I won't let Mr. Narihisago play
out the role you assigned him.
You manipulated people's lives
as if you were a god.
No one else will ever
have that misfortune.
What?!
[URAIDO]
This isn't the plan.
Hey. You were right.
If you really do want a
surprise attack to work,
it's best to keep
your mouth shut.
It's over.
Oh. One more thing.
They say management's
biggest failure
is that they don't
know the work.
Or maybe, I have
a slight advantage
since the hole in my head
does affect my perception
when it comes to missing pieces.
Take you for example.
You're not sitting in a chair.
What I can see is the
Mizuhanome cockpit
that the brilliant detective
Anaido brought into this well.
And, Chief, we had
a little help.
From Fukuda.
Now that's what'd I
call elegant revenge.
Stop. Don't do this!
So he's in the well,
and it should be collapsing.
Where do you think
that he'll appear?
Let's see... You showed up
before you went to Fukuda's.
And I--
Yeah, I suppose he'll arrive
before making his first kill.
[NARIHISAGO] Arrest him!
This bastard is John Walker!
[SAKAIDO]
Good thinking.
Now no one can press the eject
button, even by accident.
[HIJIRIIDO]
And thus, peace and order
returned to the world at last.
Now we just have to get out.
About that, do you have
some genius plan?
[SAKAIDO] Nope. Just hope
and anticipation.
[HIJIRIIDO]
You don't mean that.
We're brilliant detectives
who can solve any mystery,
especially together.
This shouldn't be any different.
I am using the entirety
of my knowledge
and it's telling me
we should embrace hope.
Sometimes it's important
to put your faith
in a stranger
outside your world.
All this time I've spent
as a brilliant detective,
what's kept me alive is hope.
[SQUAD MEMBER B]
Brain function at 70%.
He's losing consciousness!
Give him 150 cc's now.
His body can't take
that much, sir.
[MATSUOKA]
Just do it!
Look, if you won't
do it, I will.
[groans]
[SQUAD MEMBER B]
Cardiac arrest.
His airway is filling
with fluid.
Start chest compressions!
Right now! Hit the defib!
He's still in asystole!
So do it again!
Defibrillate!
Give him more adrenaline!
[SQUAD MEMBER B] Lung contusions
from rib fracture.
[MATSUOKA]
Just keep going!
Comminuted rib fracture!
Still no pulse!
We're losing him.
Give him more adrenaline!
Keep defibrillating!
It looks like we got a pulse.
You there?
[MOMOKI retching]
[MATSUOKA]
Momoki, are you okay?
Can you clear your helmet?
[MOMOKI]
I'll manage.
But... Matsuoka.
[MATSUOKA]
Huh?
[MOMOKI]
Stop yelling.
[MATSUOKA]
Sorry.
It's fine. Thanks for
bringing me back.
[gasps]
Got a visual.
[MATSUOKA]
Yeah. We see her, too.
Continue dosing.
We can't lose him.
[groans]
[gasps]
It's you.
Miss Asukai.
Hey, what's your name?
You... You came
to save me again.
Thank you so mu--
I know... that I'm completely
broken at this point...
...and putting everyone
around me to sleep.
[KIKI ASUKAI] They're probably
having horrific dreams.
I know they are.
[breathing heavily]
[KIKI ASUKAI]
It's just like before.
Please know I never gave up.
You were looking for me?
[MOMOKI]
All this time.
Miss Asukai, do you
want to leave here?
Momoki! Hey!
Damn it!
[MOMOKI]
You could go someplace.
Far away from here with
no one else around.
Where dreams are safe.
You could live without
hurting anyone,
and without them hurting you.
It can happen.
[KIKI ASUKAI]
If there is a place like that,
somewhere that I could have
a life without any pain,
then I wonder if there'd be
a way for you to use that suit
and come visit me
every now and again.
It's impossible.
For either of us, really.
Besides, lately, I've started
getting terrible nightmares
from people in countries that
are far, far away from here.
My dream world is growing.
Always just getting bigger and
bigger with each passing day.
Please, take this.
I want you to shoot me.
Put an end to my suffering.
It's what I asked
when we first met.
Just let me die.
[gun clicks]
[gasps]
[MOMOKI]
I can't. I'm a police officer.
[KIKI ASUKAI]
I should've known.
No one can do it.
But it's what I want more
than anything else.
Everybody keeps telling me
they want to save me,
but this is the only way.
Death will end my misery.
I'm so sorry.
[KIKI ASUKAI]
You don't have to apologize.
It's not your fault.
I know what happens next.
I have to go back in, don't I?
If I do, at least...
At least I can be useful.
[KIKI ASUKAI] Even though my
suffering has gotten worse,
and all this has happened,
there's a part of me,
like a little corner of my soul,
where I feel more at
peace than before.
Where I can find greater
and greater relief.
Floating in a sea of darkness.
In sleep so deep that
I forget who I am.
[KIKI ASUKAI] Besides, I know
there's nothing for me here.
Not in the outside world.
It's just true.
[MOMOKI]
Miss Asukai.
I understand you'd have a hard
time believing anything I say.
Please listen to me.
It breaks my heart that we
can't set you free right now.
Truly.
But... it'll happen.
I know it will.
Someday.
There'll be somebody
who'll come along
who can save you from this.
So please, hang on
till that day comes.
Please don't lose hope.
Okay? Someday, all this
suffering will end.
I promise!
[SAKAIDO]
Hey.
[gasps]
I'm so happy I get to
find you alive this time.
Kaeru.
[KIKI ASUKAI]
Yes. I believe you.
So I'll be waiting.
As long as it takes.
Right here.
Huh?
What happened?
We're okay.
Yeah. Guess we are.
So... is it safe to talk now?
[gasps]
Sakaido and Hijiriido.
They're alive inside the well!
Extract!
[GUARD A gasps]
[HONDOMACHI] Calm down.
Just go get the medics.
[NARIHISAGO]
Hondomachi.
[HONDOMACHI]
Mh-mh.
[NARIHISAGO]
It's okay.
You're allowed to cry, you know.
Yeah. That's really
all I needed.
One tear is perfect for him.
All right.
[MUKU] You are coming back
home, aren't you, Dad?
I am.
One day, I'll be
with them again.
But not today.
Sometimes it's good
to run out of tears.
[HONDOMACHI] And so,
the curtain has been closed
on the John Walker case.
Hayaseura's death was
labeled a suicide
caused by mental breakdown.
Once again, the truth about the
Mizuhanome has been concealed.
And, as always, the facts
surrounding the case,
the victims, and the
existence of personnel
who remain comatose
will never be made public.
All staff involved knew
the Kura Organization
requires absolute
confidentiality.
Whatever happens here,
be it a life-changing event
or just a workplace
secret, stays hidden.
[MOMOKI]
Narihisago. Hondomachi.
You ready?
Let's do this!
[groans]
[MOMOKI]
Are you up to this physically?
I can handle it.
[MOMOKI] This is a new id well.
Don't lose your head.
I know.
But once we dive inside,
we won't be ourselves.
Will that make a difference?
We're counting on you to make
a difference, Hondomachi.
[HONDOMACHI]
Roger! I'll do my best!
I'm actually pretty excited to
see a new killer's id well.
Good luck to you guys!
She might be a little too happy.
Heh.
This is perfect
for her. No doubt.
C'mon, rookie!
[KOKUFU]
Sorry I'm late.
We have authorization
for the well.
[MOMOKI]
Copy that.
I imagine we'll have some
confusion about the new system.
But I know you can
handle it, acting chief.
Sir!
[NARIHISAGO] I thought we'd
be working in shifts.
[MOMOKI]
Not this time.
The real-world investigation
takes priority
over the mystery in the id well.
We'll need quantity
and quality information,
plus analysis gathered
from the well.
Roger that.
Now, ready to inject.
[NARIHISAGO]
Across this expanse,
their voices don't reach me.
Even if I could hear them,
I would have no idea
who was speaking.
I have no idea who I truly am.
My old self waits
on the outside.
And when I open my eyes,
ready to face death,
what I see out before me
is a strange new world.
The only familiar thing here,
the one constant,
is the lifeless face of a girl.
She's been murdered.
I'm here to solve her mystery.
I learn my new name.
Then, I understand.
Everything in this world
holds some meaning.
My life and her death
are intertwined.
There's a job that can only
be done in this world
and I'm the only one who can
see it through to the end.
My name is Sakaido.
The brilliant detective.