Damn you whoever you are!
I'm sorry.
Hold on Koneko.
I just wanted...
I just wanted to
serve Rias well.
It's all right...
We'll get you to Asia, and
she'll heal you up in no time.
No, don't go...!
Stay with me!
One of Lady Rias'
rooks... retired.
Damn it...!
You killed Koneko!
Get down here and see
how you do against me!
Calm down, Issei...
When someone can longer fight,
they're transferred to a
more appropriate location,
where they're treated
for their injuries...
Koneko is not dead.
You need to try and focus.
But Rias!
It's time to give up
the fight, little boy.
No matter how hard you
struggle, you won't win.
You can't win.
Well this is exciting.
Akeno!
Issei...
I can take care of this trash;
you go on ahead, okay?
Oh... and don't worry,
I'll make sure she pays.
"Make me pay"; how exciting!
I'll be fine, Issei, just go!
Whatever you say; just get her!
I've been wanting to fight you
for what seems like ages...
Priestess of Thunder.
Oh, have you...?
That's sweet, but the
pleasure is truly mine...
Bomb Queen.
Three of Lord Riser's
pawns... retired.
Whoa, three of them?
That's crazy!
Hey!
Kiba, you're okay!
Wait...!
Those three outs, was that you?
Yeah, thanks to Akeno's barrier.
She made it pretty easy for me.
Currently, the remaining
pieces on Lord Riser's side
have the advantage at nine...
Lady Rias has
only five players left.
They cannot afford to
get careless, though.
Did you hear that
we lost Koneko?
Yeah, I heard...
None of us knew how close
she was to her limit...
She was really on fire today...
I'm sure she was
disappointed, though.
I don't care how,
but we're gonna win this!
Yeah...
You're damn right we are!
Kiba, Issei, do you read me?
I'm launching a sneak attack
on their base with Asia.
I want you to draw as
many of the enemy away
from the entrance as
you can to buy us time.
Is that safe?
I'm left with no choice;
I was planning to give
Akeno time to recover
so she could blast them
one by one, but now...
Riser sent his queen,
so I need her focus there.
Yes, of course...
but don't you think
it's too risky to have
the king leave the base?
With any luck, Riser will be
thinking along the same lines...
Here's hoping I can
take him by surprise.
If we can strike him
strong and hard enough,
we might just be able to take
the fight out of him and win.
His body may be immortal,
but his heart is not...
And trust me, I will have
no problem whatsoever
breaking that
devil's black heart.
Well, since that's decided...
Let's show them what the
Occult Research Club can do!
Balls to the wall, my friend.
Hey...! We know
you're hiding out there...
Quit acting like a bunch of
pansies and come fight us!
I am Karlamine, a knight in
the service of Lord Riser!
To be perfectly honest,
requesting to be attacked
by us makes me
question your sanity.
Although... far be it from me to
refuse an idiot his reckoning!
I am Kiba Yuto, a knight in
the service of Lady Rias...
I sure hope you're ready...
I've been looking forward
to battling another knight...
Can't wait to get started.
Very well said...
En Garde, knight
of Rias Gremory!
Awesome...!
Guess it'd be rude to
get in the middle of it.
Plus you'll be busy.
Oh, that Karlamine...
Her head is filled with nothing
but swords, swords, swords,
it's freaking ridiculous.
She was way too bothered
by those other pieces
we sacrificed, too...
You ask me, she needs
to get it together.
And now, right when I think
I've found a cute boy...
Turns out he's a
sword freak, too.
Guess this just isn't
my lucky day, now is it?
Looks like they've brought out
all of their remaining pieces...
Way to go, Rias;
you guessed right.
And what am I even looking at?
Lady Rias has the
worst taste in boys.
Cute girl with a bad attitude;
you're so cliché...!
Boosted Gear!
Boost!
Please, don't point
that thing at me;
I have no intention
of fighting you.
What?
Isabela.
My name is Isabela,
and I am a rook in service
of the honorable
Lord Riser Phoenix.
Prepare yourself to fight...
Pawn of Rias Gremory!
Hey, hold on!
What's wrong with that one?
What do you mean you have
no intention of fighting, huh?
She is serving in this
battle as a bishop...
But for the most part,
she likes to watch.
Why?
Because the lady
is Ravel Phoenix.
Phoenix?
Ravel is one of the
Phoenix household devils,
but she is also
Lord Riser's sister.
His sister?
Oh?
You think it's creepy that
I have my sister in my harem...?
You're just jealous of Riser.
Fear not.
She's part of my team because
she needed something to do.
I don't have a
thing for my sister.
At least that's what he says.
That bastard is a sicko
on top of being a tool!
Although, to be fair,
I get why he'd want her
in his harem, sister or not.
You're better than I expected.
Well, I didn't just train
with Koneko and Kiba
for the fun of it!
All I have to do is power up...
Just a few more times.
Boost!
That's my fifth time boosting...
Might be enough against a pawn,
but this D-cup is a rook.
You know...
You're no me,
but you've improved
since Mira knocked
you to the floor.
My congratulations to Rias;
it looks like she
trained you well.
First off...
It was the ceiling
not the floor...
And... Thank you
for the compliment!
I trained like crazy for her...
so you'll understand
when I kick your ass!
Riser's been expecting you...
Hello, my beloved Rias.
My Holy Eraser!
Unfortunately for you,
that attack doesn't work
against someone like me.
Oh really, what
about this one...?
Freeze!
You've gotta be kidding;
there's no way you
have two Sacred Gears!
No matter,
I still control flame!
And wind, and life...!
As do all from the
House of Phoenix!.
No way!
How many Sacred Gears
do you actually have?
Oh, no, it's not that
I have multiple Sacred Gears,
I simply have the ability
to make them at my will.
I possess Sword Birth,
have you ever heard of it?
In other words...
I make swords...
Magical swords.
Impossible.
That is freakin' tight...
I had no idea he had
that kind of power.
Moron!
Never turn away during a fight!
Damn... it should
be any second now.
Boost!
Finally!
Explosion!
Un-Dragon-Wavy...
Dragon Shot!
'Kay, that was crazy.
And I thought I'd held back
a lot of power on it, too.
I can't afford for
him to boost again...
I've gotta take out
his Gear... now!
Gotcha!
Oh, was that supposed to hurt ?
Fly apart!
Dress break!
What did you do?
Save to mental folder, gazonga.
Ooh, saving complete...!
Here, have some more!
Isabela!
One of Lord Riser's
rooks... retired.
I beat her!
What an atrocious
technique, though.
Wow... That's perversion
at its basest level.
This is the first time
I've witnessed it myself...
I really don't
know what to say...
I'm sorry my friend
Issei is such a pig.
Hey! Why are you
apologizing to her?
She's one of the bad guys!
Kiba!!!
Yeah, but...
You there, foot soldier!
Just a heads up.
You may want to watch this.
Rias!
Is that Riser up there with her?
What the hell??
I bet he anticipated our move.
So, I'm assuming you knew
I was planning to
attack you directly?
A virgin should never
underestimate one
with this much experience.
How comforting;
you're as vulgar as ever.
The Princess of Ruin...
Twilight Healing...
Priestess of Thunder...
Sword Birth...
And Boosted Gear...
Such grand sounding names
when they're all together.
However, we are Phoenixes...
Immortal Birds... and
you cannot defeat us!
Are you beginning
to understand...?
Your situation here
is so completely
and pathetically hopeless...
Oh Ni?
And Li?
It's time he met
a couple of pawns
who actually know
what they're doing.
Boosted Gear!
Boost!
You're like so gross.
What kind of freak
attacks like that?
Here, maybe
this'll help you think!
Go ahead and get him, Siris!
Hey, Kiba!
You can do this!
He's so strong!
I wish you would make this
a little more entertaining...
This is the worst
foreplay I've ever had.
Play with this!
Rias, no!
I'm fine, Issei.
Don't worry about me;
focus on the battle at hand.
But!
Don't doubt yourself;
I believe in you...
Fight!
Introduce them to the
power you truly possess!
You are a servant
of Rias Gremory!
That's right!
I'm her servant, and
I'm not gonna let her down!
He blocked Siris' sword!
With his arm!
You're damn right I did...!
It's a matter of time,
so get ready because I'm
taking you all out, one by one!
For Rias Gremory!
It broke!
Red Dragon Emperor,
if you can hear me at all,
respond by lending
me your power!
Dragon Booster!
I need more!.
I ask you to fully
connect with my emotions!
Boosted... Gear!
Dragon Booster,
Second Liberation!
What?!
Whoa...!
It changed again!
I didn't expect the Priestess
of Thunder to be this strong.
Your magic must
be almost depleted.
Never fear...
All I need is a little rest,
and I'll recover just fine.
Well... That does
sound like a good plan,
but I don't think
I want to wait.
And what's in that?
Oh just your trap.
I did it...
I reached a new level...
I can feel more power!
Kiba!
Unleash your Sacred Gear
with all the power you've got!
Do what?
Just do it!
Right...
Sword Birth!
Transfer!
I don't understand...
How could we lose?
Two of Lord Riser's Pawns...
Two of his Knights...
And one of his
Bishops... retired.
Somehow he enhanced the knight's
ability with his Boosted Gear.
A new power, granted to him
by the Red Dragon Emperor.
That was so awesome...!
Boosted Gear Gift!
Lady Rias...
One Queen...
Retired.
Akeno, no.
Akeno...
How did they get to her?
Looks like you've lost
your vaunted right hand.
Maybe, but I still
have Issei and Kiba!
Not for long, my beloved.
Damn...
Akeno's the most
powerful evil piece we had.
Kiba! Kiba!!!
Give up?
Never!
One of Lady Rias'
knights... retired.
Kiba's gone now?
You might as
well resign, darling.
Resign, this!
You don't get it yet, do you?
What a lovely bishop you have...
Refuse to resign and she
and your precious
pawn will only get hurt.
What're you gonna do?
That took you long
enough, Yubelluna.
Their queen was every bit as
strong as we heard she was...
Believe it or not, I had to use
these on her in order to win.
A win is a win, as they say...
Out of all our pieces,
you're still the one we
can depend on the most.
Thank you.
What is that?
Our family's hidden treasure...
Tears of the Phoenix...
which completely heal
any injury instantly.
And how is that fair?
Oh, take a chillaxative,
we're only allowed to
use them twice per game.
Besides, you guys have a Bishop
who uses Twilight Healing,
so what're you whining about?
Luckily, these drops can
only be produced by our family,
so we've made quite a
profit off them over the years.
Face it, with our money, tears,
and immortality the House
of Phoenix was destined
to win every Rating
Game we compete in.
Um, I was in the
middle of laughing at you!
Might as well try...
Promotion give me
the power of a queen.
Just a little further...
If it's the last thing I do,
I swear I'm gonna make
sure Rias Gremory wins!
Lady Rias!.
Issei Hyodo...
Reporting for butt kicking duty!
Issei!
You're okay!
I can take care of pawn boy
and the good bishop...
Shall I?
Do not...
Riser would prefer to
take them all on together...
I enjoy being as
persuasive as possible.
Don't get ahead of yourself...
You'll have to go through me
before you get to them!
Resign; you're
about to be mated...
I can't help but
anticipate your moves...
Riser knows you better
than you think he does...
Checkmate, my love.
You know nothing if
you think I'll give up...!
Try as you might,
you will not intimidate me.
I am a king, and
I am ready for war!
You leave me no choice, then...
Do it.
Gladly, sir.
Asia, hey!
I can't believe
you're still standing after
everything they've done...
You're so brave, Issei,
you never give up, do you?
Well, I did promise,
now didn't I?
Yeah.
Thank you for that...
You're our lifeline now, so you
need to protect yourself...
better take a step back.
No!
Damn you, Riser!
You okay?
I'm good, but...
She's alright...
She most likely just collapsed
from the shock of the attack.
I apologize...
I didn't expect the boy
to take that attack so well.
Perfectly fine...
For now, you've
stopped their Bishop
from any Twilight Healing.
You dick!
He survived a direct
hit from me, though.
It's the queen's
defensive strength...
His promotion saved him.
Alright...
Can we start beating
him down now?
Yeah.
I may not know much about
putting someone in check
or anticipating
their next move...
But I'm stronger than ever
and I'm not giving up...!
As long as I can stand,
I won't stop fighting!
I couldn't have
said it better myself.
Why don't we take
him out together?
Hell yeah!.
I'm in!
Sit tight for me, Asia...
We've got a game to win...
After that, I swear we
can go home, okay?
Dragon Boost...
Boost!
One more time!
Let's go!
Boost!
Boost!!
Again!
Dragon Boost!
Burst!
Issei!
Unlike any of the
other Sacred Gears,
the Boosted Gear
has a way of taxing
its host's physical
strength without warning.
To be honest, I think
the fact that he was able
to fight at all after
enhancing himself
that many times is
practically a miracle.
His magical power was
almost completely exhausted
by the time he took that
direct hit from Yubelluna.
His body has already
exceeded its limit.
This is over.
Never!
Rias...
You barely have any magical
power left, yourself...
Why not admit defeat...?
Riser won't think
any less of you.
Not a chance!
I'm fine!.
I can still fight!
I don't care how bad it hurts;
we can still win, I swear!
I'm gonna be
the mightiest pawn...
I promised...
I told you I would...
After all, I was
trained by the best.
What?
You don't know when to die!
I can fight.
A pawn of Rias Gremory
never gives up!
Stop it!
I will fight...
I will keep my promise...
Nothing can make me stop...
or back down.
Nothing!
Issei, get back...!
Get away from him...!
That is a direct order!
You'll see.
Because...
I won't... ever give up, on her.
Whatever!
I like you and I don't care
what your name is!
I like you for who you are!
Look at everything that
you've done for me...
I just hope someday
I can pay you back.
I can't...
It's too much.
Now I'm pissed!
You're just a pathetic,
lowly servant!
You don't even have the right
to challenge Riser Phoenix!
Riser, what do you
think you're doing?
I'm sending this loser to
hell where he belongs.
No amount of healing will save
this boy when Riser's done...
Any deaths that occur
during a Rating Game
are considered accidents anyway!
Bastard.
Die!
Issei!
Riser, please stop!
Let him go!
I resign, okay?
I resign...
Please, just let him go.
Checkmate...
Riser wins again.
Rias...
Why?
Lady Rias' resignation
is recognized.
Lord Riser Phoenix is
the winner of the Game.
This is an engagement party...
So then why the hell am
I in a wedding dress?
I could've worked harder,
but it's too late now.
She deserves so
much better than me.
My bride.
Rias Gremory!
Yeah, screw those d-bags.