Last time when I almost died...
This must be what
she did to bring me back.
All set.
Thanks a lot.
You need to relax, at least till
you get your full strength back.
The light power that stray
exorcist used on you was strong,
you're lucky we
showed up when we did.
A stray exorcist?
I'm not even sure I know
what that term means.
A ton of them got the
boot from the Church,
and for lack of options,
many became servants
of fallen angels.
Wait...!
You can't actually
be saying Asia's in
the same camp
as that Freed dick?
We're not saying anything,
other than you're a devil.
And for whatever reason, she's
the servant of a fallen one.
Those are the facts, Issei.
But...
Asia.
I'm nothing but a big loser...
A stupid pawn...
I can't save my friend...
Can't protect myself.
Trust me, Issei.
No, to hell with all that!
I'm weak right now...!
But I won't be after I pump
some iron and get jacked!
That blew.
I'm a sissy boy.
No...
I'm not gonna bitch out
and throw in the towel...
I've gotta save Asia
from that angel douche!
Issei, it's you.
Asia?
Trust me...
There's no other way.
There isn't?
This is how you're
supposed to eat a hamburger.
Well if that's the way
you're supposed to do it...
Here goes!
Oh my.
It's so yummy!
Hey, Asia, what made you
decide to go to the park?
Oh well...
The weather was perfect,
and I thought it might be nice
to get out and enjoy the day.
But then...
I saw you there and my
fun day got even better...
So yay.
You know what?
Huh uh.
Since you're free...!
Why don't we hang out together?
Yeah, sure!
You all right?
Oh... Yeah, I'm
totally fine, no big deal.
So, you dig stuffed animals.
Oh...!
Not at all... Well, sort of...
Yes.
I'm kinda outing myself
as a big nerd here,
but I've spent hundreds
of hours in arcades...
Yeah!
Thanks for winning
this little guy for me...!
From now on,
every time I look at it,
I'll remember how
much of a blessing
it's been to get to know you.
Come on, there's plenty
of stuff left to see.
Thank you...
This is special...
Even if it is only for today.
You know what?
I can't remember the last
time I had this much fun!
Yeah? Good, I'm glad;
I had a pretty great time, too.
Oww, that hurt!
It's your wound
from the other day.
Yeah...
It stings.
Man, she sure is pretty.
Does your leg hurt too?
Oh.
Yeah.
Is that good?
Uh...
Yeah...
That already feels like a
thousand times better.Wow...
And check out these
bad ass moves I got now!
Awesome...
Thank you so much, Asia.
When I was a baby,
I was abandoned
by my real parents.
They left me in
front of a church
in a small town in Europe...
I was told when they found
me I wouldn't stop crying...
The sweet nuns
there brought me up.
One day, when
I was about eight...
A sad little puppy
who was hurt real bad,
found its way into the
church where I lived...
I prayed as hard as I could
that God would spare him...
And when I did...
A miracle happened.
Because of my power...
I was immediately taken
to a larger church...
Men and women
from all over the world
would visit when they
were injured or sick
and I was told to
heal all of them...
The idea that
I possessed this thing
that could actually help
other people made me so happy.
I finally felt
like I had purpose.
But then one day...
I came across someone who had
fallen and was in bad shape.
I was able to heal him,
but he wasn't a man.
This girl has the
power to heal devils!
Demon!
She's a witch!
Burn her!
They said anyone who had
my kind of power was a heretic,
so I had no choice
but to run away.
That's awful...
So after you took off,
is that when you decided
to join the fallen ones?
Yes...
But I'll never
forget who I am...
I say my prayers and try
my best to live a good life.
They're awful...
They do such
horrible, evil things
and all in the name of God.
This suffering has to
be a test of my faith.
But If I can
overcome these trials...
Someday, I know...
My hopes and dreams
will come true...
That's what I believe anyway.
What are your dreams?
To make lots of
life-long friends...
To get to know them well,
and do cool things...
To be able to
have fun together...
And care for each other.
It's kinda silly.
Honestly...
I'd be happy to
have any friends.
Hey, is something wrong?
I don't care what other
people say; I'm your friend.
I mean, after what
we've been through,
how could we not be?
It's true...!
I'd say we've gotten
to know each other
pretty well, wouldn't you...?
And... I won you that stuffed
animal so that happened.
And I definitely care about you.
We can't...
I care about you,
too, but we can't...
Issei... No...
It's forbidden, and I don't
want to cause you any trouble!
I'm sick and tired of people
telling me what I can't do...
We're friends and
that's the way it is!
Really?
Alright.
Thank you, Issei.
Isn't that sweet?
Crap...
It's Yuma.
Lady Raynare.
Right.
She's a fallen angel.
So the rumors about
your downward spiral
into the wickedness
of devildom are true...
And I had such high hopes.
Don't even try to run, Asia.
Be gone...
I want no part of the evil you
and the other
angels are up to...!
I ran away...
I'm sorry, but I couldn't stand
to be around them anymore!
Don't apologize; I'm glad!
You're too good for them...
You don't belong
around that bunch of
good-for-nothing-has-been-
wanna-be bastards anyway!
Whaddaya want from me, Yuma?!
Oh, don't worry,
my business here
has nothing to do
with you, little boy,
though, I guess we could finish
what we started, couldn't we?
Let's... have... fun.
A spear of light...
Oh shit.
I always hate to see
someone die a virgin.
Sacred Gear!
It worked!
Is that really
all you've got...?!
It's nothing but
a 'twice critical'...
Coming up short, as usual!
Wait. A twice what?!
It's also called
a 'dragon's hand'...
That thing only doubles
your power temporarily.
You might as well be fighting
me with sticks and stones.
Man, that's all it does?
Word upstairs is you're
a devil to watch out for.
They said your Sacred Gear was
a force to be reckoned with,
that's why I put on
that dumb little girl act.
'Please, Issei...
Be my boyfriend'...
Ridiculous...
You sure bought it though.
Hook, line, and sinker!
Shut your face... and fight!
You're an idiot if you
think you can take me on
with that tiny thing!
Give me the girl, take what's
left of your dignity, and go.
Not happening!
Please be careful!
If I can't take care of my
friends, then what good am I?!
Double my power...!
Come on now, show me
what you're made of Gear!
Boost!
It's working!.
I feel the power!
Issei, no!
You're hurt!
Nice catch.
Looks like your equipment
can't get the job done.
If I were you
I'd get used to that.
Damn.
What are you doing?
I'm healing you, silly.
Wow...
That's handy.
This is awesome...
The pain's almost
gone away completely.
Now, Asia, be a good little
girl and come with me...
Your healing power is far
more rare and infinitely
more valuable to our kind than
his Sacred Gear ever could be.
I knew it...
You're only interested in
me because of my power!
How about you and
I make a deal...?
If you agree to come with me
then I won't murder your friend.
Screw you, lady...!
No way she's going with you!
Look out!
Issei, no!
That sucked.
I've never seen
a spear that strong.
I spared his life on purpose.
If I had wanted to, I could've
delivered a fatal blow...
Your friend would've shattered
into a million pieces.
I'll go with you.
Good girl...
No need to fret--after
the big ritual tonight,
all your worries and troubles
will be gone forever...
I'll see you soon, Issei.
No, stop!
Asia!
Goodbye, friend.
I'll miss you.
No.
Why couldn't I save her?
Let me try one more time:
if I say 'don't,' you don't!
You have to forget
about, Asia...
You are a member of
the Gremory Family now!
Fine...
Then maybe it's
time you released me
from your household...
Cause I refuse to
just let her go!
I'm sorry, but I can't do that.
Of course not,
I'm your precious pawn...
Can't do without your most
important piece, can you?!
That's enough, Issei!
Pawns are important...
They're not the weakest piece
in the game by any means.
Do you remember when
I told you my 'evil pieces'
have the same attributes
as their chess characters?
Yeah, but so what,
what can a stupid pawn do?
In this chess game...
Quite a bit...
If a pawn advances deep enough
into the enemy's territory,
it can be promoted to any
other piece besides the King.
So does that mean
eventually I can have
all the same powers
as everyone else?
Yes, but only if
the master declares
the place enemy territory...
Say, for example,
the fallen one's church.
Now let's talk about
your Sacred Gear.
Oh yeah, it doubles my
power, is that right...?!
Yuma said, uh...
I mean the fallen angel told me.
Just feel.
Any Sacred Gear works
in direct correlation
to the current
feelings of its owner...
Or, to put it another way,
the stronger those feelings are,
the more powerful
your Sacred Gear will be.
I didn't know...
That's cool.
Something has come up...
Akeno and I have to
step out for a moment.
Wait a minute, I have
more questions for you!
Remember, even
if you're promoted...
no matter their rank,
a single devil cannot
stand up to a fallen one.
I guess we'll have to
see about that, won't we?
You going?
Yep...
And there's no point
trying to stop me.
You're gonna get killed.
Well I can deal with that,
as long as I can
get her out of there.
That's very brave...
Very stupid, too...
This is suicide.
It's none of your business!
I'm coming with you.
Wait, what?
Weren't you listening...?
The President basically
said you get in that church
and you're promoted.
But she also said you wouldn't
be able to do it on your own.
Yeah...
So we're gonna back you up,
and there's no way in hell
we're gonna let you go in there
without us so you might as
well save your breath, dude.
Koneko too?
There's nothing else goin' on.
Ugh, this is the worst!
Standing guard is the
most boring thing ever!
Oooooh...
Ask and ye shall
freakin' receive.
Hi, there...
I'm Mittelt, and I'm totally
the most awesome fallen angel
in the history of ever!
This little girl's really
into herself, isn't she?
My servant sensed
that you were nearby...
Since you're out
here standing guard,
your people must be
worried about an attack.
Worried...?
No, we're just in the middle of
a super-duper-top-secret ritual
and we don't want
you devils interfering.
Not to burst your bubble...
But unfortunately, a couple
of the younger members
of our team are on
their way there right now.
They're what...?!
Are you flippin' kidding me?
Nope...
And they're not
being discreet about it.
Ooooh! I hate devils...!
I just wanna squish their
ugly, stupid, devil faces...!
Ugh, whatever!
Let them do their worst...
Not like they can stop us.
There are way more of us
than there are of them!
So why are you here...?
I hope it's not for some
sort of rescue operation,
cause if so, you'll have
to deal with me first...
I may be little, but
I promise you this much:
I can pack a mean punch!
They're on their own.
We won't be making
any attempt to rescue them.
So what?
You're just gonna
sit back and watch?
Oh, man, can you feel that?
No kidding, there must be
a ton of priests inside there.
Seriously...
I think I'm glad
you guys are here.
Well, hey, you and
I are buddies, right?
Besides...
Fallen angels aren't exactly my
favorite things in the world...
The truth is, I hate them.
Oh yeah?
Hold on...!
Don't just go in!
No need to be sneaky;
they know we're here.
This place is creepy.
So we meet again!
Glad you could make it...
I bet I'm a sight
for sore eyes, huh?
Yeah, right!
Here's the thing,
I pride myself on the fact
that I never have to battle
any devil more than once...
And yet here you are...
Just rubbing it in...!
If there's one thing
I won't abide,
its being mocked by maggot
devils in the house of God...
So, whaddaya say...?
Let's finish this!
The thought of
tearing away your flesh
and eating it piece by piece
makes my mouth water!
Tell me where she is!
Oh right...
You mean that dirty devil-loving
whore of a Sister...
All you have to do is
go down to the basement;
she's right beneath the altar
we're currently standing on.
Downstairs.
Right...
But first you have
to go through me.
Sacred Gear!
Here.
You're pretty strong
for a runt, aren't you?!
Suck it.
Come on...!
That all you've got...?!
Show me something interesting!
You're quick.
Well you're not
so bad yourself...
Of course that only makes
me wanna kill you even more.
Whoa! Kiba's like
a total bad ass, huh?
Alright...
If you wanna get serious
about this, I can too.
Hey, what the hell is this?!
The 'Holy Eraser'...
It's a sword of darkness
that devours light.
Please!
You think I'm afraid of you?!
I didn't know he
had a Sacred Gear!
Issei!
Boost!
All right...
No more of this bullshit!
Rescue or not,
I can't let you go.
You're like, totally the
captain of your loser squad,
and if we take you out they're
on a trip to useless town.
Sorry...
But I'm bringing
friends to this tea party!
Good work, Mittelt.
Sad to say we meet
again, Lady Gremory.
You should've kept
your servant in line.
He stuck his nose where
it doesn't belong again.
Well, well, the gang's all here.
Time for a promotion!
The rook is a tank...
Its power is an unparalleled
defensive strength.
Yeah, I'm fucked.
Did I mention it kicks
some serious ass?!
That's for Asia...
For what you did to her...!
Hey, that felt
pretty good actually!
You bastard!
Ouchie!
I'll be damned if
a bunch of devils
are gonna get the best
of Freed Sellzen...!
You won the battle...
But not the war, scum!
Ha!
Damn, he got away.
Forget him, let's keep moving!
Guys!
It seems very clear to us
that your intention here
is to obstruct our ritual.
And that we can't allow.
You'll pay for
it with your lives!
Akeno.
Already on it.
No fair...!
I wasn't told we could
wear costumes to this fight!
It's a barrier!
Uh-oh...
We're totes screwed!
Catching my prey in
a cage gets me so hot!
This was your
plan the whole time!
Yep...
And I'm gonna take
a whole lot of pleasure
out of watching
you three in pain...
Hope you're into S and M.
That's totally gross!
End of the line for you.
Go ahead and act as
confident as you want.
The ritual's almost done...
And once it's over...
Not even you will have the power
to stand against
us, Lady Gremory.
Come on in, devils.
Welcome to the party...
Though I'm afraid
you're too late.
Asia!
Issei...
You came.
I'm here...
Hold on!
No, wait!
Asia!
This really is an incredibly
touching reunion...
Unfortunately,
the ritual's over.
What are you doing to her...?
You let Asia go right now!
That's it...
They're after her Sacred Gear.
I see now.
You're out to steal the
Sister's Sacred Gear
and use it for your
own evil purposes.
Hold on a second,
I don't understand...
What's going to happen to her?!
I'm sorry.
Taking that from her
is taking her life.
Wait.
She's dying?
Twilight healing...
At last it's in my hands.
You deserve a reward
for making it this far.
You won't get away, bitch!
If I were you I wouldn't
underestimate him.
Let's just say...
He's the most powerful
pawn I've ever seen.