Okey-dokie, I'm all set!
Asia and I are gonna go
hand out some flyers...!
How bout it?
You ready to go?
Hold on.
I think you'll be glad to
know your flyer days are over.
They are?
Relax, it's not a punishment.
You've both done great work,
but normally the hassle
of running around,
handing out flyers is
the job of a familiar.
Hell yeah!
So what, is this sorta
like a promotion?
Yeah, I guess you could
look at it that way,
but first thing's first: we need
to find you two familiars.
This is my familiar, Issei...
I believe you two
have met each other?
Hot flyer girl's your familiar?
And I've got one too, of course.
Whoa, is that an imp?
This is Shiro.
Mine's badass.
I don't care about
your tiny dancer.
Why you gotta hate, man?
Don't be jealous,
Issei, you'll get one...
Familiars are a major
part of being a devil;
when you're in need, they're
always there to back you up.
That's great...
only problem is, we have no idea
how we're supposed to get one.
That's the next step.
Yeah?
Sorry to interrupt.
Whoa, what the heck
is she doing here?!
Issei...
Who are these people?
The one in the middle
is Sona Shitori, the student
body president...
And the girl with the glasses
right behind her
is Tsubaki Shira.
It looks like they brought the
rest of the council with them.
Hello, Sona, what
can I do for you?
Nothing, I just wanted
to congratulate you
on increasing the
number of your servants.
Hold on, how does
she know about that?
Her real name's Sona Sitri,
and she's not just the
student council president,
she's the next head of the House
of Sitri, a big devil family.
Are you saying there are
other devils at our school?
Rias, I'm hurt to
find out you didn't
tell your little
boyfriend about us,
but I suppose if you don't
trust him with inside info,
then he must not be
worth much to you huh?
It's considered bad form
to get involved in the affairs
of other households, Saji...
It's only natural that
Rias held this back.
I know you.
You're the guy from 2-C
who was just elected student
council clerk, right...?
I think I mighta
voted for this guy.
Saji Genshiro...
My pawn.
This is my pawn Issei Hyodo...
And my bishop Asia Argento.
Whoa, so you're
a pawn too, dude...?
Then that totally
means we're twinsies!
Can it d-bag...
You and your gaggle of
slutty-sluts don't deserve
to be in the same
room as a group
of distinguished
devils like the Sitri's.
You take that back!
Aww... He's mad...
Not even gay prince
charming over there
could protect you from me,
I took up four pawn pieces, bro.
He took up eight pieces...
It's always better
to check your facts
before you make a
complete fool of yourself.
Wait... what...
You're freaking
kidding me, right...?!
How did this lame-ass,
butt-munch manage that?
Shut up!
My apologies...
He's young...
I hope you'll forgive him
his youthful naiveté...
Newbies don't always appreciate
the finer points of civility...
Do they?
Oh... Right.
My pleasure.
No, the pleasure is all mine.
Hey...
You sure you're not an angel,
cause I'm pretty sure you
just fell down from Heaven?
Saji, I just want you
to know if you even think
of putting the moves on Asia,
I'll slice off your nuts and
feed them to you through a tube!
Oh, you think you've got that
shit on lock-down, well...!
You ain't the only bull in
this rodeo anymore, dick face!
This is embarrassing.
I know, isn't it?
How's flyer duty treating
you, Captain Whack-it?
I don't do lame shit like that,
cause I'm an actual
member of the team!
Getting' a familiar
and everything, bitch.
Guess what, tool?
I just got promoted from flyers
and I'm getting a
familiar too, so suck it!
Oh...!
Is that your plan, Rias?
Yes...
I was thinking of going
next week, actually.
Well, that's a bit of
a problem for us
as he only takes
people once a month.
In that case, why don't we have
a friendly little contest
to sort this whole thing out.
A contest?
Whoever wins earns the right
to make their request first.
Surely you're not talking
about a Rating Game.
Oh, no.
We'd never get permission
to do something like that.
Yes, you're right.
Besides, this isn't the time
to call attention to
yourself, now is it?
Don't go there.
I know!
We should settle this
the good ole' fashioned
high school way: with sports!
Damn!
Let's go, Rias...!
Show these uptight
losers who's boss!
Come on, Sona...!
Stick it to those jackwagons!
Akeno...
We're in it to win it.
Got it.
No mercy!
Everyone ready...?
Good.
Heh... May the best devil win.
Oh man, tennis balls ain't the
only things bouncin' today...
This game freakin' rules!
I'd let her smack
my tennis balls.
Why're you here?
This is the bomb!
I'm beefin' up my spank
bank material, dawg,
I'll be whackin' it
for weeks offa this!
I wish I had a camera
so I could preserve those
jiggily jugglies for posterity!
They're so athletic,
can you imagine
the moves they could
pull off in the sack?!
I'd like to see them play a
little two on two on my junk!
Camel toe!
I don't think I've ever seen
this many people at
a tennis match before.
Give 'em hell, Sona!
Whoa! Akeno, you are the tits!
Is it just me or is this
getting a little out of control?
Let's see how you like a magic
attack, Sona Sitri-style?!
Oh really...?
Let's see how you handle
the Gremory counter strike!
One point... to Sitri.
Aww, man!
Suck on that, Issei!
Hey, we did agree to no magic...
Didn't we?
Yep, but that doesn't
seem to be stopping them.
Did you see the curve on that!
Well I guess we've pretty much
kissed the rulebook
goodbye, huh?
It's cool, Rias is about
to lay the smack down.
Look, Sitri...
You can cheat all you want to,
but in the end it's not going
to make a bit of
difference in this game...!
You want a magic show...?
Well, I've got a few tricks!
Do your worst Gremory...!
You think I'm afraid of you?
Bring it on!
Too bad it was a draw.
Since nobody won,
they're suggesting we all
compete in a team match.
Are you serious?
Serious as a heart
attack, my friend,
they're all out there right now,
deciding what we should play.
We've chosen dodge ball
as the game to play.
We meet the Sitri's
tomorrow night in the gym...
So... Let's win this.
Right!
Thanks for playing for us, guys.
Yeah, for real.
Hey, Asia, are you still awake?
Issei...
Hi. Come on in.
Oh... I can't...
It's really late!
I'm... sorry to bother you,
but do you have a needle
and thread I can borrow?
Yeah...?
They outnumber us by two people
so we've asked the
extras to be referees.
I'm like the worst at sports;
I don't even know if
I remember how to play.
Oh... You'll be fine,
just grab a ball,
aim it at the Sitri team,
and hit 'em right in the face!
Asia picked it up in no time;
I'm sure you can do it too!
My legs are on fire!
Stretch it a little bit farther;
come on, you can do it.
I'll... Try...
I've had wet dreams that
started exactly like this!
Only there were
way less clothes.
Join us, Issei.
Team headbands?
Nice.
Yeah, we're gonna
look totally badass.
Thanks, I stayed up all night
making em.
You didn't sleep?
I just wanted to
make something cool
as a way of saying thank you
for everything you
guys are doing for us...
I'm lucky to have friends
as awesome as you...
Plus, I suck at sports,
so this way I'll remember not to
throw the ball at my own team.
What's wrong...?
Are they lame?
Maybe I should've gone
with t-shirts instead.
Oh, no, I think
they're perfect, Issei...
It was nice of you to do that.
I don't know, it's not
a big deal or anything.
You're a pervert,
but you're sweet.
Let's put these on,
go out there,
and do our best to
kick some Sitri butt!
Yeah!
Ready to rock and roll?!
That's a point!
Aw, right in the tit.
I need a drink anyway.
Ready or not here I come!
Well, catching Tsubaki's spike
head-on is pretty impressive.
Don't forget Sona,
I'm a Gremory,
that's just how we roll!
Behind you!
Got it!
You need to keep your
head in the game, sweetie!
Whoa...
I just saw your bra!
Let's see how you handle this!
I had no idea that dodge ball
was so terrifying!
This isn't dodge ball anymore,
it's like a fight to the death!
Want me to go ahead and
take out that sissy ass pawn?!
No, I got it!
Here comes the pain!
Shit!
Oh, whoa! What the
hell's up with this thing?
Issei! Look out!
My... Frank and Beans...
I think they're squished.
I can use my twilight
healing to make you better,
but first you have to show
me where it hurts, Issei.
Oh, no...
I'm fine, thanks!
You're in pain, I think it'd be
best if I took a quick look--
Uh, I don't want you using
your weird other worldly
twilight thingie on my junk...
My twig and
berries are off limits!
If it'll make you
more comfortable...
I can just do it over the pants.
Tell me, how does that feel?
Tingly.
You better not be
getting a chub right now.
It's got a mind of its own.
Take good care of him, Asia,
we've got a game to finish!
Will do.
Come on, you guys,
let's win this one for Issei!
Yeah...!
For his man-bits!
For his one-eyed snake!
For his sack.
Does that feel good...?
Oh, boy...
Thank you for the
support everybody.
Bring it!
Come on, let's
end this thing, Sitri.
Right here, right now!
Oh, I'm just getting
warmed up, Rias!
Game over!
All right...!
We did it...! We won!
A deal's a deal, Sona...
Since we beat you, we get
first pick of the familiars.
As much as I hate to
lose, I have to admit:
that was still a
whole lotta fun.
Although, if this had
been a Rating Game,
and not just us fooling around,
there's no way you
could've beat me.
You really think so...?
Well, I guess we won't know
for sure until we
actually play the Game...
But it'll be a while 'til we
have to worry about that.
Don't be so sure, Rias, you
never know what's coming up.
Huh...?
What's a Rating Game?
Victory!
I want you to know,
I'm thankful to each
and every one of
you for going out there
and doing what needed to be
done to beat those devils...
I hope you guys feel very proud.
Hell, all I did was get
knocked in the love spuds.
Sure, you got
nailed in the nads,
but you also made
these headbands...
They're pretty rad, man.
Totes.
Yeah...!
They really brought
our team together!
Thanks, bro...
I don't wanna sound
gay or anything,
but if you were a hot chick,
I'd totally make out
with you right now!
Okay...?
I hate to break up
the celebration,
but I think it's time we go get
these two a couple of familiars.
Wait, you mean we're
getting them right now?
Full moon tonight, this
is our best shot to see him.
See who?
The Familiar Master.
Uh, where are we?
Duh, a magical forest
where all the familiars live.
Don't be scared;
this is where we
came to get ours too.
Oh, I'm cool...
I mean, besides the fact
that I just pissed myself.
Yeah... It's really freaky.
Who wants me?!
Hey! Who's there?!
The master of the
familiar, aka 'The Towji!'
That's the guy?
Oh, wow.
If you're goal is to
find familiars galore,
you've come at the
right time, that's for sure!
The full moon is out
to help you decide,
and I'll be the one
to act as your guide.
If you can't tell,
The Towji's way obsessed
with making things rhyme.
Uh-huh.
Now, how can I help you?
Tell me all your
wants and desires...
A strong one?
A fast one, one that
likes to set fires?
Yeah... Cool...
Do you have any hot
familiars with big tig-o's...?
Who really like
nerdy white guys?!
This is why amateurs
always annoy...
If you're seeking
something more than a toy,
utilize your other head, my boy.
To find the familiar
who will be the best fit,
look for best personality,
don't look for best tit.
Makes sense,
but I'd like one that's really
cute and fun to be around.
Fun...?
Done and done!
Oh! Thank you so much!
Hey, no fair, dude!
This lake is awesome,
righteous and right,
at the bottom, you'll
find magical sprites.
Yeah...!
Sprites are sexy...!
We just hit the
familiar jackpot!
She'll emerge from the
water wearing nothing
but a soaking wet
see-through dress
with hair long
enough to tie me up.
Then she'll pull me below
and we'll make sweet,
sweet, soggy love.
Whoa! Check out the lake!
Here we go...
Looks like a sprite
is about to show.
Take a look.
That's off the hook!
But clearly not off the 'roids!
What is it, a
competitive body builder?!
Undine are rare water sprites
with mega watt power...
A familiar like that would
make your enemies cower.
Screw that...!
He looks like he could pick me
up and break me in half!
Not he...
Sorry, but this he's a she.
A she...?
I think I just threw
up in my mouth.
That sprite back there,
she had really kind eyes...
Even though she's
tough on the outside,
I could tell she
has a good heart.
Oh yeah...
And pecs the size of my head.
Oh my... Look, high!
Okay. What is that?
Aw...! It's really cute!
Cute but dangerous, too...
When they get angry,
they have the power to
shoot a lightning that's blue.
Hey, that type of dragon
is pretty rare, isn't it?
I think this is the first
time I've ever seen one.
Do it now, if you
want this one claimed...
Once these dragons grow up,
they can no longer be tamed.
Issei, since you possess the
power of the Red Dragon Emperor,
that sprite might turn out
to be a pretty good fit.
Yeah, that makes sense...
Right...! Dragon...!
I choose y--!
Asia!
Oh my!
Its green slime!
It's burning my clothes!
How naughty!
I'm so slimy and wet!
No!
Oh...
My skirt!
It's so grody...
Vomit town.
Damn!
Dude...
This is the best thing
that has ever happened!
Suck on that, perv-pants.
It's not my fault
you guys got slimed outta
your skivvies by goo!
My hands are tied, I can't
use my magic like this!
Me neither, how are we
gonna get out of this mess?
I'll save you... but...
First I have to save this image
to the spank bank for later.
Eating off clothes is the random
power of this weird slime...
Fun for a while,
but in the end, a complete
and utter waste of time.
Hey...!
That's really the
only thing it does...?!
I found mine...!
I want the slime to be
my familiar right now!
The pain hurts so good,
I might just have
to fight you for it!
Yes!
Every hot girl
I meet will instantly
be naked with this by my side!
No, Issei you can't!
Picking a familiar is one of
the most important
decisions you'll ever make...
Please! You have to
think it through first!
I've thought about it enough!
This is the one I want for sure!
Sorry, slime...
We coulda had some fun!
Just back away, Issei...
The only thing to do with a
monster like that is burn it.
No, don't!
I won't have to
undress every single girl
I meet with my eyes anymore
if I have slimey by my side!
Meeting this thing
was my destiny...!
Don't take that
away from me, please!
I can't believe Issei's
actually hugging me!
It's perfect!
Oh, yucky slime...!
We were meant to be!
Seriously too into this stuff.
I've never seen a
devil come to the forest
for one of its biggest pests...
I don't think this one
knows there's more
to life than breasts!
He's usually such a good boy...
But I guess in the end,
the pervert inside of
him finally took over.
Come on...!
You really blame me
for wanting something
that makes chicks naked...?
How am I supposed
to turn down pure
unadulterated jubbly action?
That sucked.
Aw, the sprite dragon
used his blue lightning.
Yucky slime, no...!
This is your fault!
Are you all right?!
That was dope.
Sprite dragons
don't attack unless
they believe their loved
ones are in trouble...
Which, in the familiar
world means that dragon
and lovely lady should
be together on the double!
You mean Asia and that
thing are bonded now?
He's so cute!
Well, isn't that sweet.
Now, I gotta take a shit,
so you guys need to beat feet.
In the name of Asia Argento
and devils everywhere.
I command you to accept this
pact to be my familiar forever.
Well... Looks to me
like you got a friend...!
I think you two will
be very happy together!
Hey! That tickles...
Rassei...
Stop it.
Rassei?
For some reason that
name popped in my head...
I love him!
And every time I hold him,
I'll think of you.
That's a really sweet
thing to say, Asia...
I'm glad to meet
you Mister Rassei.
Oh, something you should
know about these creatures.
They hate other males--that's
just one of their features.
What a naughty boy Rassei is.
Oh, yucky slime...!
Why did you have to leave me?!
I wanted your gazonga exposing
powers to be mine forever!
Quit your whining, lech balls.
They say sprite dragons
only give themselves
to the most worthy and
pure-hearted of masters...
And normally, they would
never choose to serve a devil.
Asia used to be a holy sister,
so who knows, maybe
that had some sway
over the little guy?
Hey! Bad Dragon!
That chest isn't yours
to nuzzle in, bud!
Now, Rassei, you have to be
nice to Uncle Issei, okay?
All right then, sweet boy,
it's time to say goodnight.
I know I should
be happy for her,
but now that Asia
has a leg up on me...
I guess I'm kinda jealous!
You know what, though,
soon I'll get a kick
ass familiar of my own,
and I'll be right back
on top again, bitches!
I can't wait, man...
Well...
See you tomorrow, everyone.
Good night guys!
Night.
Issei's got a long way to go.
He's a newbie, give him time.
You're right.
That he is.
She gonna strip, too...?
Oh please turn around,
please turn around.
You like seeing people naked,
and I could be
one of those people.
He's fiancé to the next
head of the House of Gremory.
I need you to
take my virginity...
And I need you to do it now.