Asia!
Yes!
I've been lusting after
this power for years!
Those miserable hearts
are in the palm of my hand...
perfect.
I'll be beloved.
I'll be the most powerful
fallen angel there is!
All those pricks
who screwed me over
are going to regret it!
Oh screw you!
All right, let's go!
You asked for it!
I don't have time for this!
Move it!
No you don't!
Kiba!
And Koneko!
Thank you!
Asia!
Oh no.
You deserve a reward
for making it this far.
I got you!
It's me...
Are you okay?
Issei... you came.
Yeah, and we're not out
yet... so stay with me.
Kay
Go ahead and take the girl.
I got what I needed.
You crazy bitch...!
Put her Sacred Gear back
where you found it, right now!
Soooo tough...
Sorry.
I had to betray my superiors
to snag that little gem.
Unfortunately for you, you're
about to become my dénouement.
But the good news is...
...you get to die together.
Issei!
'Fraid they've got
the upper hand!
You know I can't believe...
I ever wanted to be with you.
As if I couldn't tell you were a
virgin the first time I saw you.
Made my job easier,
you pansies will
believe anything
if you think you'll
get your pole greased.
I actually liked you... or Yuma.
Sweetie!
That was the point!
I needed you to play super hero
to my damsel in distress.
Poor thing.
You wanted to believe it so
badly you never even caught on.
I wish you could see your face!
It makes the torture of spending
so much time with you worth it!
Why...?
Why would you even
let it go that far...?
You had to've known it was
pointless from the start...
why let me worry so much
about that stupid date?
Don't worry...
That date was everything
a girl like me could want...
I was so bored the whole time
I couldn't wait to kill you.
What's wrong with you?
That's gonna get old real fast.
And exactly how long do they
intend to hold their shield?
Not a very
well-thought-out tool, is it?
That's gotta be draining.
Tell ya what...
Put those barrier things
down and we'll let you go.
So kidding...
Get comfy 'cause you're
gonna be here awhile.
Man, I bet your minions think
you've dropped 'em
like a bad facelift.
Omigod...
Especially that horn-ball
who thought Raynare
wanted his corn nuts...
I bet she's crunched
his ass by now!
If I were you, I wouldn't
underestimate him.
Let's just say...
He's the most powerful
pawn I've ever seen.
Yuma.
Meaning 'Evening Daze.'
I found it appropriate since my
plan was to kill you at sunset.
Let's talk inappropriate...
First you refuse to die,
then you replace me with
some pious, platinum, nun-slut.
Ugh. Issei...
I'm hurt...
Weren't we... special?
You're makin' me jealous.
I bet you took her on one of
your yawn-athon dates, too.
But I guess for a
sheltered little prude,
a night with you is a hoot!
Oh Issei, how do
you expect to get laid
if you keep putting
your victims to sleep?!
Shut up, Raynare!
I love a man who takes control!
Where was this when
we were dating?!
You might've gotten some!
I may be a devil...
but this bitch is just evil!
Kiba!
Koneko?!
We got this!
Get out of here, now!
Hurry!
Koneko and I will
keep them here!
Run!
We'll be fine...
I promise!
Come on...
Leave already.
I can't.
You standing there
isn't helping anyone.
Go!
Thank you... my friends...
I swear when this is all over
you'll never have
to bail me out again.
I promise you!
I'm gonna get stronger...
and fight for myself next time!
A pawn?
Well isn't that nifty,
you nerds name your servants
after chess pieces...?
The pawns are the dopes
who line up in the
front, is that right?
Yeah, they're the
sacrificial players.
Nonsense...
We would never sacrifice
any of our members.
We're family.
Hang in there...
Come on...
Once we get out
of here, you're free.
Stay with me...!
You have to fight!
That's it... be strong!
I know it wasn't a
very long time, but...
I'm so blessed to have
made a friend like you.
Stop!
It isn't over, okay...?
We're going to be friends
for a lot longer than
this; you hear me?!
When you feel better,
we'll go do some karaoke or...
I'll teach you how to bowl...
so you can't give, up, damn it!
You'd be letting my buddies
down, too ya know...
You still have to meet them.
I know they'll love you.
They may come off
like a couple of pervs,
but I swear they're
actually great guys
once you warm up to
them--and you will...
Man, are we gonna have a
story to tell them after this!
We'll all need a
crazy night soon, huh...?
Where should we go, you think?
I wish it could be different...
It would've been great to
have grown up in this country,
gone to your school.
You still can...
...and school will be a lot
more fun... with you there.
I never wanted to make you cry.
Oh, Issei...
I'm... sorry.
Good bye.
No...
Why...?
Why does she have
to be the one to die?
She's a healer.
She could've helped people!
If her gift is to
heal those in need,
doesn't that mean you
have a purpose for her?
It makes no sense...!
Damn you!
Asia didn't do
anything to deserve this!
Please give her back!
Please!
All she wanted was
to make friends!
She had one in me
and would have made
so many more...!
Is that it?
Is this my fault...?
Are you punishing her because
she made friends with a devil?
I'm sorry, okay?!
Just give her back!
A demon asking for
forgiveness in church?
What an insidious
sense of humor.
What are you doing here?!
It doesn't matter what
that moron's abilities are;
he doesn't stand a chance
against Lady Raynare.
Even if she is
his ex-girlfriend!
Oh, we heard all the
tragically lame details
of their little fling!
Now, stop!
Mittelt...!
You're evil!
What a joke!
Watch out!
She deflected it!
He's not a joke...
No one laughs at my servants.
Look what you did, now...
Maybe it wasn't such a good
idea to taunt her like that.
Whoopsie on you.
Ugh, how tacky is this?
Some rabid knight did it
to me on the way up here.
Where are Kiba and Koneko?!
Wonderful, huh...?
No matter the injury,
I heal instantly...
A perfect gift for those
of us who no longer
have the benefit of divine
protection, wouldn't you say?
And now I'll never risk losing
my rank in the underworld.
Oh...!
Great Azazel and Shemhazai,
I am prepared and
ready to do your works!
What does that matter?
What does that have
to do with Asia...?!
She wasn't a threat.
She didn't care about power!
Unfortunately for those
with the Sacred Gear,
this is their destiny.
That is such bullshit...!
She never would have used it!
She just wanted
to live in peace!
Out of the question.
Why?
Humans don't have the ability
to survive in their world
with the Sacred Gear...
Even if they choose to
use the power for 'good,'
they are seen as different and
would be tortured out of fear.
They said anyone
who had my kind of
power was a heretic,
so I had no choice
but to run away.
Honestly...
I'd be happy to
have any friends.
Have you ever heard
anything more absurd...?
That's just how humans operate.
Such an unfortunate
waste of power.
That wouldn't have happened...!
I was her friend
and I could have
protected her from all that...!
I wouldn't have let
anyone hurt her--ever!
She's dead!
Stone cold dead
and you're whining
about protecting her--
you realize how
psychotic you sound?!
You wouldn't have been able
to save her back then anyway!
And you can't save her now!
Will you shut up?
I'll never forgive
you for this...
I'll never forgive myself.
Why couldn't it have been you?
Any Sacred Gear works
in direct correlation
to the current feelings
of its owner...
I want her back!
To put it another way, the
stronger those feelings are...
I want Asia back!
The more powerful your
Sacred Gear will be...
Dragon Boost!
You don't pay attention, do you?
There's nothing
you can do to win--
even if you tripled
the power you have.
And you're still
trying to test me.
Light is toxic to devils.
Just touching it
scorches your bodies.
It's said... to be
the most intense
and worst pain a
devil can endure.
So what do you think?
Is it true?
What do I care if it is?
This is nothing...
Nothing compared to
what Asia went through!
I'll put up with
anything for her!
You know I really
am impressed...
A lower class-devil
making it this far?
That power is something
to be reckoned with.
What's happening?
Not that it's gonna do
you any good, though.
I just wanted to make
sure you got your kudos
for doing so much
better than expected
from a devil of your class.
That's it.
God isn't going to help me.
I'm a demon now--what
was I thinking...?
I need to call Satan.
I'm a devil now, too,
so what do you say?
Just this once,
I need a little help.
What are you mumbling
about over there...?
Is all the pain driving you mad?
I'm begging you.
I won't ask you for
anything else after this.
What's he doing?
Turn this around on her...
Let me destroy her ass!
How are you able to stand?
This is impossible.
That light should be burning
you from the inside, out!
Tell me how you're doing that.
You don't have the
power to temper light...!
You are nothing!
Don't get me wrong...
it doesn't tickle.
Even with this strength I feel
like I'm about to pass out.
But I don't care.
I'll fight through it if it
means I can take you down!
Explosion!
That energy wave is
at least second level.
His Sacred Gear should be
nowhere near this strong...!
It's... It's just
a Double Critical!
You won't get away... bitch!
No! I have the supreme power!
This one's for Asia!
That felt good.
Look at you handling
that on your own!
Yeah, thanks...
what held you up?
I was instructed to stay back...
Rias's orders, sorry.
Seriously?
Seriously.
I believe in you.
I knew you would defeat her.
You did?
Once my business was finished,
I found my way to the basement
and arrived just in time
to see Kiba and Koneko
having a free-for-all
with a bevy of fallen angels.
I don't know that we would've
gotten out without you.
Aw man...
I'm sorry I missed it.
Did someone order this?
You must be Raynare.
Lovely entrance.
I am Rias Gremory...
Also known as the next head
of the House of Gremory.
Gremory...?
You gotta be kidding.
It's wonderful to meet you...
What a shame we don't
have time to chat...
But sadly...
It's time for you to join your
friends I disposed of earlier.
They were rather rude to me.
So you killed them?
Rias's fuse is long,
but when pushed,
she lives up to her title as
Empress of Annihilation.
Damn...
Didn't know I was part of
such a hardcore group...
Neat.
So many feathers!
It looks like the
forest is molting!
Why would the heiress of
Gremory dare such a thing?
Well, since you ask...
After Dohnaseek attacked Issei,
I discovered multiple fallen
angels had plans
to attack this town...
Normally, I would
have stayed out of it,
but they seemed insistent
on targeting my team.
So... You did it to defend me?
Look at you...!
I didn't see your Sacred Gear?
Yeah...
I don't know what happened,
it just freaked out
and turned red.
It's called a Red Dragon...
Which... explains
a lot, actually.
Did you see this, Raynare?
You weren't defeated by a Dual
Critical Sacred Gear after all.
No need to feel too embarrassed.
What?
The one Issei uses automatically
doubles its owner's power
every ten seconds--allowing
him to transcend
both God and Satan at will...
It's one of the thirteen
varieties of Longinus.
The strongest level of
the Red Dragon Emperor
is called Boosted Gear!
So this sacred tool
with the ability
to destroy God is in
the hands of a child?
The one downfall is that it
requires a decent amount
of time to start due to
it's immense power...
The only reason he was able
to beat you was because
you let your guard down.
If only you'd learned
that lesson earlier.
Issei, please...
I'm sorry, I know I said
some mean things to you
but I didn't have a choice--
I had to fulfill my role
as a fallen angel!
Yuma!
I mean...
If I really didn't care...
would I still be
wearing your gift?
Please don't tell
me you forgot...
You bought it for me,
don't you remember?
No way.
Why do you still
have that thing?
How could I possibly
get rid of this?
It reminds me of you.
Koneko...
You ready?
You wouldn't let them hurt me...
would you, Issei?
Shut up...
I don't buy it.
Rias. Please...
I can't do this.
You've toyed with
my servant's emotions
for the last time.
Be gone!
Uh... In that case...
Since you're single...
Do you think you'd
like to go out with me?
I'd like for you
to be my boyfriend!
These are beautiful.
Shall we return them?
Yeah.
I'm sorry...
You all came to help me...
I fought as hard as
I could and still...
I failed...
She's gone...
Asia, please forgive me.
You have nothing
to apologize for.
This world is still new to you.
Nobody here is placing blame,
least of all, Asia.
But... But... I...
Now, this may not
make any sense,
but I'd like to show
you something.
Have you ever seen
one of these before?
A chess piece.
Uh huh.
That one...
is called the bishop.
What does that mean?
The bishop's position
of power is to protect
and heal the other devils
in the household.
Perhaps the timing is perfect.
We could use a good clergyman.
Wait... are you saying...?
Our good Sister is about to be
born again into the underworld.
In the name of Rias Gremory
I call to Asia Argento...
Hear my command.
Return thy soul from
the shadows of death
to the human realm...
Rise once more as
my demon servant.
Rejoice!
For you have been
given new life!
Wake as my healer and clergyman!
So what now...?
Is she gonna wake up?
Just wait.
You're alive!
Huh?
Wait...
is that...
really her?
It is.
I don't make a habit
of reviving the deceased
but her power may be useful...
From here on,
you are her protector...
You are the
senior devil, after all.
Issei...?
Uh... Am... Am I here?
Yes, and I'm so happy...!
You're home.
You are so damn sexy
in the morning...
What do I do to get
you up... huh?
Hit it.
Hit it hard.
What's up?
It's your favorite
devil servant!
Hi!
I'm surprised you're here today.
How you feeling?
Great!
Thanks to Asia's power,
it's like it never happened.
Fantastic, she's already
proving how useful she can be.
It's no wonder all
those fallen angels
were so threatened by her power.
So, question.
If you don't mind...
If... we're named
after chess pieces,
does that mean all the
positions are represented?
It does.
Then if I'm a pawn,
that would mean that you have
or can have like, seven
more of me on your board?
Which is totally cool.
I understand if I'm
not enough for you.
That was a joke!
I'm completely
stable and secure!
You're the only pawn
I'll ever need, Issei.
That's awesome.
When a human becomes a devil,
the number of Evil Pieces
they consume varies.
It just depends on
what special abilities
that person has to contribute.
Consumed?
For you, the pieces
I had remaining,
were one knight, one rook,
one bishop, and eight pawns...
So that is what
I had to choose from...
After I knew I wanted to
bring you back as my servant...
I decided to use all eight of
my pawns in order to save you.
So...
You sacrificed seven
others to have me?
It was a gamble...
I had a feeling your power alone
was strong enough to replace
every one of the others.
Humans with that
potential are hard to find
so I considered the sacrifice
to be well worth the risk.
Now that we know you posses
the Boosted Gear of Longinus,
I'd say it was worth it.
You are worth it.
Boosted Gear...
The highest level of the
Red Dragon Emperor.
The crimson haired
Princess of Ruin
and the user of
the Red Dragon...
I don't know if we could
be more perfectly matched.
Yeah...
Go, Team Red!
Strive to become
the mightiest pawn...
I have complete faith in
your ability to achieve this...
Consider it an order,
my dear servant.
I can totally do that!
And now I'm closer to my goal!
Oh wow, what are you doing?!
Just a little spell to
strengthen your stamina.
Sweetness...!
I've always wanted
porn star stamina!
You'll need your strength
to better fulfill my orders,
and I'm going to have
to stop coddling you
or our newest member
will become jealous.
Jealous?
Um...
What's going on?
We're just talking!
That's how it always starts.
It's okay.
I know she's prettier than me.
And she'll probably
do things I won't,
so it makes sense
that you like her more...
Oh!
I shouldn't say
things like that!
I swear I'm not jealous!
I'm just insecure!
Dear Lord, please forgive
my sins of lust and envy--
Asia! Are you okay?!
I feel like a knife just
ran through my head.
God's not very receptive
to the prayers of demons.
I forgot.
He's probably angry that
I became a devil, huh?
How do you feel about it?
Oh me?
I don't have any regrets at all!
The best part is that Issei and
I can be together forever now,
and that's all
I ever really wanted.
Uh huh, that's nice,
now about that
outfit you've got on.
What do you think?
It's great, but...
does it mean you
go to our school?
It does.
My father is on the school
board so getting her enrolled
as a transfer student
wasn't a problem.
That's cool.
I didn't know that.
Good morning, everyone!
I'm almost glad to
see you're not dead.
Oh perfect!
You're all here!
I brought cake
so we could officially
welcome our new member!
Issei?
Yeah?
Great job today.
I was very impressed.
Oh...
Thanks for your impressed-ness.
Wasn't that a sweet ending?
Gag me.
Oh snap...
Nipple contact.
Look here, Tiny Tim,
Miltan wants you
to turn her into a
magical fairy princess!
Did ya see anything
you like, you big pervert?