Who's there?
The power you currently possess
is not of your own making.
Wait a minute.
I know that voice.
No measure of hard work
and training could give
someone that amount of strength.
Oh yeah, I remember,
you were in my dream before.
What makes you extraordinary
is the dragon
inside your soul...
Do not humble yourself
with weakness or the
White One will laugh.
The White One?
In time, he will appear...
It is your destiny to stand on
that field of battle and fight.
But you must get stronger...
If a sacrifice is made, a
boon will be given in return.
A gift of shared strength
in your moment of need...
But first, show them
what a dragon is.
What does that mean?
I am the Welsh Dragon...
The Red Dragon Emperor, Ddraig.
Ddraig?
I am what lives
in your left hand.
Rias.
I'm surprised you're awake.
Miss Grayfia...
Hey...
What the hell happened,
how did I get here?
The battle ended shortly
after Lady Rias surrendered.
We lost?
I'm afraid so.
Lord Riser was
declared the victor.
No way.
Are you sure?
Yes.
But how...?
There's no way Rias would
just give up like that...
She'd keep fighting
no matter what!
Lord Riser was
going to kill you;
she surrendered
to save your life.
The game...
The whole thing's one big blur.
You didn't give up.
Every time he knocked you
down, you got right back up.
It's fine...
Don't worry...
I'm okay...
You did your best.
You made me proud...
Thanks, Issei.
It's me...
She did it because of me.
This whole thing is my fault...
I tried so hard to beat him,
but I wasn't strong enough...
I failed and now Rias
might be Riser's forever.
Wait...
Where is everyone from my team?
Lady Rias instructed Miss Asia
to stay here and
take care of you.
After all, you were
hurt pretty badly.
The rest of them are
in the Underworld...
Lady Rias wanted them with
her for what comes next.
Underworld?
Yes.
The engagement party
will be starting soon.
Oh no.
I understand that history
is not in my favor,
and the idea of love
may just remain a dream...
But it's a dream that
I'd like to try to keep.
I'm sorry, Rias...
I failed.
Strive to become
the mightiest pawn...
I have complete
faith in your ability.
Consider it an order,
my dear servant.
Now go get stronger, Issei...
You can do it.
I could've worked
harder, but it's too late.
I'm weak...
I'm so pathetic.
She deserved better than me.
Listen, Issei...
It's not your fault.
Rias is abiding by the decisions
of the Gremory household...
Sadly...
The outcome of the battle is the
way it was always meant to be.
Even so...
The thought of it...
It makes me sick...
I can't just sit here
and watch Rias suffer...
She shouldn't be forced
to accept a horrible life
she doesn't wanna live...!
It's wrong!
I can't let that
bastard take her!
You really are a
fascinating boy, Issei.
You're an open book and
a gentle soul, to be sure...
I've met a lot of
devils over the years,
but never one quite like you...
When your mind's made up,
there's nothing that
can slow you down.
And I'm not the only
one who thinks so.
Sir Zechs feels
the exact same way.
What's that?
If you want, this can transport
you to the engagement party.
Are you saying I should
go there and stop them?
Sir Zechs gave me an
important message for you.
'If you want my
sister back, Issei,
you'd better be
prepared to fight.'
Yeah?
Remember his warning.
If you decide to
stage a rescue attempt,
it's your only option.
I guess there's only
one thing to do then.
Issei, you're up!
Asia... What's the
matter you okay?
Sorry...!
I was just so
worried about you...!
You were out so long...
I didn't know if you'd
ever open your eyes again!
I was scared, Issei!
I'm sorry...
I never meant to make you
worry about me like that.
No... Don't apologize.
You're safe, and that's the only
thing that matters to me now.
Asia, listen to me.
Okay.
I have to try and rescue Rias.
Are you sure...?
You think that's
that a good idea?
Well...
I know she'd try to rescue me.
Then I'll come with you.
You can't do that...
Please... I need you
to stay here for me.
No, I won't...
Let me come with you, I can
help you out if you get injured!
I've gotten much better
at using my magic...!
Don't make me
stay behind, Issei!
Don't worry.
I won't do anything stupid.
Trust me, everything
will be all right.
Don't make a promise
you can't keep!
If something horrible
happens to you
while you're away,
what am I supposed to do...?
I can't stand to
see you hurt again...
Oh, Issei, I don't know how
I could bear it if
I wasn't there to help!
I'm gonna be alright...
This is no big deal...
I mean hey.
After everything
I've been through,
I'm still in one
piece, aren't I?
If I let you go, you have
to promise me something.
Anything.
No matter what...
Promise me you'll bring
Rias back home with you.
You know I will...
But first...
I need you to do me the
favor we talked about before.
It's something no one else can
help me with but you... 'member?
Yes, I remember...
If it's important to you,
I'm happy to do it.
Thanks, Asia.
Hey...
You can hear me right?
Are you there...?
I need a word with you.
Come on...
Show yourself, Dragon!
I am here...
What is it you ask of me?
You and me...?
Need to make a deal.
This is an engagement party...?
So then why the hell
am I in a wedding dress?
Because Riser wanted it.
No, Lord Riser, you mustn't...
Men aren't allowed in here.
Just a word with his lady
and Riser will
be out momentarily.
Look at that dress.
You really are a
beautiful bride, my love.
I'm not a bride yet;
sorry to disappoint you.
So what's with the dress?
'What's with the dress?'...
I just want you to
make a good impression
on our esteemed
guests, my dear...
After all...
We need to
demonstrate to the world
that our two houses
have joined together...
Right?
And don't worry,
you'll have a dress
even more stunning than that
one when the time comes...
Lord Riser's bride
will be adorned
in a gown made
of flaming feathers.
It's only fitting for a
lady of the House of Phoenix
A dress made of
flaming feathers...?
I think I'd be better
off killing myself.
Issei. Issei!
Rias...
Please... Will you forgive me?
If it's the last thing I do,
I swear I'm gonna make
sure Rias Gremory wins!
You haven't learned how
to use your magic correctly...
And you have virtually
no combat experience at all.
And yet you still risk
your life to rescue me...
Issei...
Such a silly boy.
I'm so sorry...
It's my fault...
How could I let things
end up this way?
You're so brave...
So strong...
And sweet...
Thank you for everything.
Issei.
Lady Rias...
It's time.
My incredibly
talented brother won
himself a bride by
demolishing the Gremorys.
Of course I had
no doubt he was going
to win from the beginning.
But he had to keep it close
so it wasn't a complete bore.
She's delightful.
Yes, the girl's got quite
a mouth on her, doesn't she?
Sona, what's up?
The outcome not withstanding,
I thought it was a good match.
Though...
I wouldn't have complained
if the end result had
been a bit different.
Thanks for the support,
but I promise this thing
isn't even close to being over.
We'll get another shot
at them, I'm sure...
Only next time, we'll
be ready for their tricks.
Yeah screw those d-bags.
Greetings renowned
devils of the underworld!
On behalf of the
House of Phoenix...
Riser would like
to thank each and every
one of you for coming today!
This is an historic moment
for the world of devils...
And I want our dear guests
to be the first to know.
Two great dynasties
are about to become one...
Lord Riser of the distinguished
House of Phoenix,
shall wed Lady Rias of the
illustrious House of Gremory!
And now...
I present to you.
My bride.
Rias Gremory!
Issei!
Rias!
Who do you think you are, boy?
I'm Issei Hyodo, and I'm here
to bring Rias Gremory
back where she belongs...!
No one is going to take anything
from her that she
doesn't want to give.
How dare you?!
Seriously is this guy mental?!
Seize him!
Guess that's our cue to get
involved, so whaddaya say guys?
Yeah.
Let's do this.
We're here, Issei...
And we got your
back all the way!
Suck on that, douche.
Thanks you guys!
You're awesome.
Mmmm!
That was like super hot.
Akeno?
Go save Rias, Issei.
All right!
Is this your doing?
Lord Riser, what is
the meaning of this?
It's just a little
entertainment I prepared.
Who's that?
My brother's here?
That guy's your brother?!
It's the Great Devil, Lucifer!
Whoa, he looks hard-core!
What exactly do you
mean by entertainment?
I watched the Game, Riser.
And honestly, I was
underwhelmed by you.
My sister lacks your
gaming experience and yet,
against your considerably
larger forces,
she nearly had you beat.
It's the final result
that counts, my Lord.
In the past...
But the Games don't
mean what they used to...
Besides, Riser, you
were nearly brought
to your knees by a
first time competitor...
I can't imagine
your family's proud
of the way you performed...
I think you should be
given another chance.
Besides, we don't
have a celebration
like this every day...
This party could use
some flair I think...
You there.
They say you possess
the power of the Dragon...
And I, for one, would like
to see what you're made of,
which is why I had Grayfia
bring you here this evening.
I see...
You want a fight.
Dragon versus Phoenix, yes...
I believe your guests
would quite enjoy
a head to head match between
two powers such as yours.
No...
Please don't!
An excellent idea, my Lord...
I'd be more than
happy to oblige you.
And you... Dragon?
Sorry, what?
There are many here
who have quite an interest
in seeing your abilities...
Would you be kind enough
to show them what
you're capable of?
Hell yes.
Issei, don't do it.
Relax, Rias.
Mister Hyodo is a big boy...
Riser is certain
he can handle himself.
So tell me, Dragon,
if you're the victor,
what would you like
to have as your reward?
You can't be serious!
A reward for a
lower-class devil?
Your king has spoken.
Lower-class or not,
he'll get his prize.
I'm the one that's
requested this of him...
I must give him compensation
for his trouble...
What would you
like to receive...?
A title...?
Or perhaps a woman
of great beauty...?
Ask, and if you win,
you shall receive.
Here goes.
Fine...
There's only one thing I want.
Rias Gremory!
All right.
It's time to get started.
Good...
I'm ready if you are, Riser!
You messed with the wrong
family this time, Hyodo!
My brother's about
to tear you a new one!
Yes...
He's quite the confident one,
but I'll take him
down a few pegs...!
Come, boy...
Fight me!
Alright, it's time
to upgrade...!
Only one more chance!
Issei...
Please be careful out there.
Promotion...
Queen!
It's no use!
Die!
I don't have any talent
with swords like Kiba...
And I don't have
Akeno's gift with magic...
I'm nowhere near
as strong as Koneko...
And I don't know the first thing
about being a healer like Asia.
I may not be like them
but there's one thing
I've got plenty of... heart...!
And I promise you this much...
Nothing will stop
me from saving her...!
Shine forth...!
Over Booster!
Welsh Dragon...
This is the Dragon
Emperor's power...!
Balance breaker...!
Boosted Gear...
Scale Mail!
The balance breaker...?
Where did that come from?
Fascinating.
The forbidden, infernal form.
I want you to make
a deal with me.
Sounds interesting.
You sure you're ready for this?
Are you in or are you out?
Like I said...
I will grant you a power
worthy of your sacrifice...
But you have only
to the count of ten...
Anything beyond and
your body will not survive.
Fine by me...
That's plenty of time.
Rias doesn't
belong to you, jerk!
Ten!
Over here!
Nine!
I've never seen speed
and power like this...!
Who do you think
you are, Hyodo?!
You're nothing compared
to Riser, you understand?
Nothing!
I am a Phoenix nobleman...!
The flame of the immortal
bird burns within me...
The hellfire of my clan will
scorch you to dust!
You think I'm scared
of you, Riser...?!
I'm gonna make you sorry
you ever messed with us!
I'm glad I've got
this Scale Mail on.
Riser's hellfire
attack is no joke.
Seven!
If you weren't hiding
behind that armor, pawn...
There'd be nothing left of you
but a pile of smoking ashes!
Six!
You're done...
This pain...
It burns!
What have you done?!
Is that a cross?!
Five!
Where'd you get that?
Our bishop used to be
a member of the Church...
I borrowed this from her
and added a boost
from my Sacred Gear.
No matter how powerful
you think you are,
you're nothing compared
to the cross I'm holding
in my hand, Riser!
Four!
Impossible...!
A devil can't hold a cross!
Even wearing your
dragon armor shouldn't stop
that thing from destroying you!
It can't be...
Wait...
You offered that dragon
your own arm, didn't you?!
Three!
You're damn right I did,
and now I'm gonna take
you down, you son of a bitch!
This arm is no longer mine.
Understand?
What?
Just watch.
See, it doesn't hurt me...
I'm okay.
Have you lost your mind?!
After what you've done,
you'll never be the same again!
Two!
You think I care?!
He gave up his
own arm for this...
Issei's going to win,
I just know it!
He'll defeat Riser...
And he'll bring
Rias back home to us.
One!
It doesn't matter
what happens to me!
If it saves Rias
that's all I care about!
Because she's worth it!
Count is up!
Unfortunately,
you are out of time.
Come on, you gotta
be kidding me?!
I was so close!
What am I gonna have
to pay you this time?
An eye...? A leg?
I'll give you whatever you want!
Sorry, but with
your current abilities,
there's nothing else I can do.
Of course...
I'm not strong enough, it always
ends this way, doesn't it?
When I took back the armor,
I released a very small
amount of power to the gem...
You'll only have
it temporarily...
However, I'm not
sure it will be enough
to counter Phoenix's
regenerative capabilities.
I still have to try...
I'll fight.
I won't...
Give up.
That's too bad.
Looks like someone
lost their armor.
Riser believes it's time
to end this pathetic charade.
I'm not done.
If you're gonna
put out a fire...
Well...
You're gonna need water.
Holy Water?
Will Holy Water
even work against
a devil as strong as Riser?
Try this on for size, asshole!
Transfer!
Look at Riser!
The holy water is draining his
mental and physical strength.
It's preventing him
from regenerating!
Not even the Lord of the
House of Phoenix can rise
from the ashes when his mind's
under this kind of attack.
His mind?
Indeed...
His body's immortal but
his mind is far from it.
How's that feel, Riser...?
Asia taught me that
devils are vulnerable
to crosses and Holy Water.
Use both in tandem
and not even a devil
like you stands a chance!
Kiba taught me to
widen my field of vision
whenever I'm
battling an opponent!
Transfer!
Akeno taught me to use magic...!
To take the power
of my body's aura
and release it on
a single point...!
And to amplify my attack by
increasing my mental focus!
And Koneko taught me to aim
for the center of the body...
To strike with precision,
right at the heart of my enemy!
No...
Stop it...
Don't...
This engagement's important
to the future of all devils...
You fool!
A mere servant like
you has no business
getting involved with
the affairs of your betters!
Don't you understand?
I don't care!
Rias...
She's the only thing
that matters to me!
And the fact that you'd
force her to be with you...
...when she
obviously hates you...
Well that's reason enough
for me to take you out!
Suck on this, scum-bag!
Bastard.
Don't hurt him!
If I were you, I would
step aside little girl.
Unless you want to be next!
Issei...
You did it.
You really did it.
This battle is done.
Whoa, good catch, dude.
Way to rock the house.
You... Totally nailed it!
Yep.
Hey, wait.
See ya.
Hey there, Rias.
Issei...
You just saved my life.
Thank you.
Jeez, what's that?
He's a griffon.
Isn't he cute?
Well, Issei, since
you saved the day,
I think it's only fair
you ride back with Rias.
Uh. On that?
Yes, please...
Unless you don't want to.
Are you kidding me,
of course I do!
If I don't die on this thing,
I'll see ya at the club!
Beautiful, isn't it?
I had that griffon ready
in case they needed
to make a last minute escape.
Thank goodness
it didn't come to that...
We would've had quite
a mess to clean up.
I wouldn't worry too much;
my father and Sir Phoenix
have found some common ground...
Such a shame though...
For an engagement
to fall apart like this.
Yes, you're right...
It's very sad.
You look devastated.
It's truly a miracle...
I never dreamed it was possible
the great red dragon
would come over to our side.
It seems likely
that the encounter
with the Vanishing One...
the White Dragon...
could be upon us soon.
You okay?
Silly boy.
To give up your arm just for me.
Hey, it was worth it...
Totally...
I would have done anything
to get you back safely.
Issei, look...
The engagement
may be over now...
But I promise you
this isn't the last
we'll hear of it,
not by any means.
Then I'll give up
my other arm...
And then my eyes if I have to.
Issei.
I'll do whatever it takes...
Nothing is gonna stop me.
I'll always save you.
I'm your pawn, after all...
It's my job, right?
Hey...!
It's time to wake up,
sleepy head!
Pinky's here!
Is that morning wood?
Oh my, you're a
naughty boy, aren't you?!
That was my first kiss.
It's a bit of a
monumental moment
for a young woman, isn't it?
Uh, I guess it kinda is, huh...?
Wait, that was
your first kiss...!
Man, I hope
I didn't screw it up!
Well, since it is my first,
I guess I have no way
of knowing, do I...?
I liked it, though.
She liked it!
Oh, Issei?
Uh huh?
I almost forgot, I've decided
I'm going to live at your place.
What?!
Unless you have an
objection, of course.
Come on, you stupid arm, heal!
Please heal...!
Guys run!
"Get back here right
now, you perverts!
I'll teach you to spy on
helpless, innocent girls!
You guys are a
bunch of jack wagons!
You're never gonna get laid,
you understand me?
Never!"
Dude, I saw some tit,
I swear I did!
Yeah, tig' o' biddies!
That was awesome!
More than anything...
I wanted to protect her.
Not cause it's my duty or
cause it's expected of me,
or anything like that...
I wanted to protect her
because of how amazing she is...
Because I believe
she's totally worth it.
It's always been her.
And it always will be.
Forever.