Red.
The same color as her hair...
Darker than any
red hair I've ever seen...
Just like the color
running down my hand.
Long, beautiful crimson hair...
Just... like this.
Not today...
I will not let you die.
I gotta say, boobs
are the best thing ever.
Trust me, my man, you
and I are on the same page!
Me too...
But it's all pointless.
Matsuda...? Motohama?
Can you guys
tell me why the hell
we enrolled in
this school again?
Like you don't know...
We're in a place that
up until a few years ago
was nuthin' but chicks...
We had to take advantage
of this male to female ratio.
Also, the foreign exchange
students here are ridiculous.
Poon as far as
the eye could see!
We figured hos'd be linin'
up to get on our jocks,
and we wouldn't have
to do a damn thing!
We'd be drowning in that stank!
Like our very own harem!
Hell yeah! We were
gonna have casual,
unprotected sex with hot chicks
and then never call them again!
One, two! One, two! One, two!
That was the plan anyway.
But here we are,
up against the spring
semester of our second year,
and between the three of us, we
don't even have one girlfriend.
What's the point?
It'll never happen.
No, we can't give up now!
It's not too late for us!
Kiba, wait up...!
What are you doing right now?
Yeah... you maybe wanna
go sing karaoke with us?
Thanks...
But I've gotta
meeting with my club.
Aww...
That sucks.
I really do wish
I could go, though;
it's very cool of you
ladies to invite me.
Kiba Yuto. Class 2-C...
Basically every girl in this
school wants to sex him up.
And every guy wants
to mess him up!
That tool...!
I don't get it...
Just cause he's hot,
sexy, really smart,
and the coolest guy in school,
they all wanna rub up on Kiba?!
He sucks so much
less than we do.
Life really does blow sometimes.
Oh shit...
I'm gonna be late!
Huh...? Gonna be late for what?
Murayama's jugs.
They're frickin' huge!
36... 22... 34.
And Katase's
legs are crazy sexy!
34... 22... 36.
Found this yesterday.
I call it the 'tit hole.'
Good job, Matsuda!
I have to admit,
your scouting...
Guys, my turn...!
Come on, no fair!
Ooo, check that out!
She's so hot!
What was that?
Dude, run!
Can't believe those
two idiots left me here!
Guys!
Well, well, what a surprise.
No...
Wait.
Please... Don't hurt me.
Issei, you perv!
I still think attacking me
with bamboo swords
was a little extreme.
Did you at least
get to see some nip?
No, I didn't get
to see any nip...!
I was too busy getting
my ass handed to me
for looking through a tit hole
I didn't even get to look
through cause of you a-holes!
Did you guys see that honey...?
Her sugar has got to be sweet.
True that...
What is it about red hair...?
Her name's Rias Gremory.
36... 24... 36...
She's President of the
Occult Research Club...
Word around the school is
she's from Northern Europe.
Who was that boy?
What boy?
The kid who was
sitting in the middle.
Well... I think
he's in Class 2-B...
If I remember right,
his name's Issei Hyodo...
Why, what makes
you ask about him?
Oh, nothing...
I just wondered if you knew
who he was, that's all...
Ah. Checkmate.
Your trap was very
easy to see through.
Sorry, I did my best
to make it harder on you.
Thanks.
I look forward to next time.
Being a teenager's the worst...
At this rate, jerking off
to porn is the closest
I'll ever get to 'doing it'
before I go off to college,
which means I'll be a
virgin forever and die alone.
Excuse me?
You're Issei Hyodo
from Kuo Academy, right?
Or am I wrong?
Yeah.
I don't recognize that uniform.
What school's she from...?
Who cares?! She's fine!
Hi! I uh--
Um...
Hey, if there's anything
I can help you with...
Sort of.
I just wanted to ask
you a quick question:
Are you seeing anyone right now?
Now? No...
That's wonderful!
It is?
Uh... In that case...
Since you're single...
Do you think you'd
like to go out with me?
Go out with you...? Um, I...
I've been watching...
You pass by here a lot
and you seem so...
I don't know...
Gentle...
And very handsome and I--
This cannot be
happening to me right now.
See...
The thing is--
I'd like for you
to be my boyfriend!
I...
Whoa!
Is this for real?!
Wake up, please, would
you please wake up now?
Or...
You could just stay in bed...
But...
I'm not going down on you.
Wake up, mister!
No... Please God...
But--
Guys, this is Yumo
Amano my girlfriend...
And these are my good buds
Matsuda and Motohama.
It's nice to meet you.
And here's the best part, dudes.
She... Asked... Me.
Hey... Stop whackin' it,
and you'll find one, too!
Come on... Let's go, Yuma!
Kay!
Dude... He betrayed us!
Go out?
Yeah...
Next Sunday afternoon...
Can you do it?!
Sure...!
That sounds great...!
I can do it anytime you want!
It's a date then... Night.
Yeah... You too!
I really am happy
you're my boyfriend!
Ditto...
Bye, bye.
A date, a date!
This is bad ass!
I am so gonna see lady parts!
I am the man!
I see.
You were right,
one hundred percent.
Yeah, you totally called it.
I'm just glad I asked you two
to keep a close eye on him.
Yep.
What's next...?
What do we do with him now?
We need to make our
preparations immediately...
That's all we can do...
Everything else depends on him.
She should have gotten here
by now. Shouldn't she?
Here, take a flyer.
Oh goody, wonder
what this about?
'Your wish will be granted', eh?
Yeah right...
If only that were true.
Issei... Hey!
Oh, cool! You made it!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No... Please.
I'm just glad you came.
I've always wanted
to say that to a chick!
Are you all right?
Take this!
I sure had fun today.
Yeah...
This was the best date ever!
Dude...
I think this is my
chance to make a move!
I'm touching her!
Can I ask you a question?
In honor of our first
date there's something
I'd like you to do... to
commemorate this special moment.
I'm gonna get to kiss her.
I'm totally gonna
get to kiss her.
This rocks!
Sure...
You can ask me
for anything at all.
Would you die for me?
What'd you say...?
Sorry...
Something must be
wrong with my ears;
I don't think
I heard you correctly.
Could you maybe say
that one more time please?
I want you to die for me.
Breasticles!
Those are boobs...
I am looking at boobs.
My little boy eyes have
finally grown into manhood!
And she's a super
hot chick too...!
What's that old saying?
'This is a sight
for sore eyes'...
This is totally a sight
for--wait, no it's not...
She looks like a demon.
Are those wings?
Well, I have to admit...
I did have some fun today...
Considering how naive
and childish you are,
things could have
been much, much worse...
Thanks a lot for the gift too...
Very sweet...
But... even so.
Yuma, wait...
Please--
It's time to die.
I'm sorry.
But the fact is, you were
far too great a risk to us...
I had no choice
but to dispose of you.
If you're looking
for someone to blame,
why not blame Him?
He gave you the Sacred Gear.
What in the hell
is she talking about?
Oh... Thanks again
for the lovely date...
It was fun.
What a bitch.
Am I really about
to die like this?.
Alone and pathetic...
And a giant virgin...?
If you were gonna kill me...
Couldn't you have let me squeeze
your jiggle-y jugs first?
I only got to look at
them for a second...
But I could see how
bouncy they were...
Oh, Yuma...
Red.
The same color as her hair.
Darker than any red
hair I've ever seen...
Just like the color
running down my hand.
Long, beautiful crimson hair...
Just... like this.
Wait, why the crap am
I talking like this...?
I'm about to freakin' die.
It's over... Damn...
I can't even move anymore...
Trying to touch
a pair of orbs...
What a stupid way
for a person to die .
To be honest, I know
I've lived a shallow life...
Next time around I'm gonna try
real hard to be a better person.
The only thing
I can think about is Rias.
With her pretty red hair...
And huge kazongas...
If I'm going to die,
then why can't
I do it motor-boating
those glorious fun bags.
I have come...
You're the one who
summoned me, are you not?
Wh-Who is that?
Since death is upon you...
I will gladly take you in.
Whoa, she has wings too.
From this moment forward...
You will live your
life for my sake.
Wake up or
I shall kill you dead.
Wake up, bitch...
Or I'll chop off your balls.
I'm so tired...
Man...
This stupid thing...
Gives me the weirdest dreams.
Hold on.
Stop screwing with me, guys;
you seriously don't
remember meeting Yuma?
Naw dude name's
not ringin' any bells.
I'll say it again:
you never introduced us
to a chick and it's impossible
that you have a girlfriend.
But that doesn't
make any sense...
Her email address
is right here--
No way...
Yuma's contact
information's not in my phone.
What in the hell...?
Big boobies, twelve o'clock.
Rias?
She's so awesome!
Like, totally gorgeous!
Filing that image
away for later.
There's just
something about her,
she's like a naughty,
red-headed princess you know?
Hey, maybe you've been
watching too much porn
and it's making you cray-cray!
Look, I'm not crazy;
I know what happened, okay?!
Relax.
Just come by my place after
school today and we'll hang out
and watch my treasured
collection-Of DVD porn!
They're so gross.
Losers.
Anyway, I just got
a new disc called
'Double Ds and the
Nerds who love them'
That sounds awesome!
Didn't you say you also got the
latest Gentlemen's Disc release?
So weird...
Transform!
Ooo...! This is Momo's latest
video Kaben Rider Pinky!
Sure is...
I had to pull
some major strings.
Man, this is so weird...
How could it have been a dream
when the memories feel so real,
like they just
happened yesterday?
Plus, if it never happened,
where did my memories
of the real two days go?
Yo!
What the hell's wrong
with you, Issei...?
You are a Momozono
Momo fan, aren't you?!
Uh.
Heeeey, uhh...
Let's turn off the lights,
it's way too bright in
here, I can't concentrate!
Yeah, that's way better!
I know!
Dude, look at that mount!
Guys, the lights are still on.
Wait.
What'd you just say?
The lights in the room,
I thought you were
gonna turn 'em off.
Huh?
What are you talking
about, broseph?!
No, I'm wrong...
They are off.
I don't see any light...
But I know I sense it...
I do.
Sorry.
I'm going home.
Hey!
What's wrong, are you all right?
I'm not nuts...
My eyes are freaking out on me.
This is weird...
I feel so different...
Like there's something
inside me that's changing.
No, Mommy, buy it!
If you don't stop acting like a
spoiled brat, you're grounded!
No! No!
It doesn't make sense,
how can I hear them
from so far away?!
What's happening to me...?
Why is my body doing this?!
I've been here before.
Yes...
This is it.
This is the park
where I took Yuma
when we went on our first date.
It was real...
It couldn't have been a dream...
I remember every
single thing about it.
What the hell was that?
Well, this really
is unfortunate.
Me running into you, that is...
Oh man...
Why won't my body stop shaking?
I meant to back up
a little, not jump!
Looking for a way out?
I don't understand
what's happening to me?!
Feathers?
Yuma?!
Such cowardice.
I can't abide
lower-class beings.
No...
How can this be real!
So let's see...
It appears as
though your friends
and master are
nowhere to be found...
You show no signs
of disappearing,
nor are any magic
circles being deployed...
Therefore I will assume
that you are nothing
but a 'stray,' is that correct?
And that would mean...
Killing you won't be a problem!
If I'm gonna die in a dream,
I'd rather be killed by
a hot chick than a dude!
Not cool!
Man, this blows...!
Big time...!
This is the worst
pain I've ever felt!.
It didn't hurt near this bad
when Yuma murdered
me in my last dream.
Hurts, doesn't it...?
Light is a deadly
poison to your kind;
it burns you from within...
I thought I'd finished you off,
but it seems you're
quite the tough one.
Don't worry though...
I'll put you out of
your misery shortly.
I'm done for...
Someone...
Help me, please!
What did you just do,
you little shit...?!
and what the hell is that?
Keep your hands off of him.
That red hair.
Did...
Rias... come to save me.
I'll teach you not to meddle
where you don't belong.
I'm done with you!
That hair...
You're from the
house of Gremory.
My name's Rias Gremory...
And who are you...
...other than a fallen angel?
Well, well, who knew...?
This town is currently
under the control
of the next head of
the great Gremory Family.
So he's a part of your
household, I take it.
If you bring any harm to him,
you will get no mercy from me.
I apologize for the
misunderstanding.
Though it's unwise to let your
servants run loose like this...
The next time he's
out for a stroll,
he might run into someone
less cordial than myself.
I appreciate the
friendly advice...
Bear in mind, if anything
like this happens again...
I'll make you regret
the day you crossed paths
with the house of
Gremory, my friend.
No offense to your noble
household, but you should
bear in mind that the same
thing could be said to you.
My name is Dohnaseek.
I pray that you and
I never again cross paths.
That was a close call...
I can't believe he actually
ran into a fallen one!
If we don't do
something, he'll die.
That won't happen.
He'll live...
I'll see to that myself.
Master, wake up, won't you...
Master, wake up, won't you.
Master, wake up,
won't you please.
So tired...
That was the
weirdest dream yet...
Why does this keep
happening every night?
Hold on a sec, what happened
to all my clothes...?
Why the hell am I naked?
No way...
No way!
This is awesome!
Issei?
Hey.
Whoa, I can see your tits!
Good morning.
Uh, what are you
doing in my bed...?
Is this really happening?
Cause this feels like
it could be a porno,
or some kind of a wet dream.
No, this is real.
And so is everything
else you've experienced,
as a matter of fact.
My name is Rias Gremory...
And I'm a devil.
A devil?
Not only that, but
I'm your Master, too...
You're mine now...
Nice to meet you, Issei Hyodo.
Close your eyes and think
of the part of your body
you feel is strongest.
Then focus on it.
I'm gonna have a harem!
They'll be naked all the time!
I rule!
But...
I will say it kinda
feels as though
I've adopted a little brother.