You're almost there!
Just a few more feet!
Visualize, Issei!
Coming!
Rias.
Should I go get some
of those bags for him?
He'll be okay...
He needs to learn to
carry that much on his own.
On your right!
Seriously...?!
Did they give you a bag
of feathers or something?
Move it.
I hate this!
Ten days.
I think we can all
agree that's fair.
You sure?
Considering your youth
and lack of experience...
And Lord Riser's prowess...
I've decided that assigning a
handicap would be appropriate.
As much as it pains
me to admit it...
I think you may be right.
Extra time to train
would be very useful...
For all of us...
Thanks, I accept the offer.
You ready, Issei?
The purpose of this training
camp is to build your strength.
Soon... you will be stronger
than we ever imagined.
Wow...!
How beautiful!
All right, you guys.
Let's head inside and
get going on this training!
But we just got here!
That's evil and nowhere
even close to fair!
Why, thank you!
I have a question.
Y'know when you said ...
that stuff about
hating fallen angels...?
You never really
explained what happened
to make you feel that way,
and I've kinda been wondering.
Fallen angels aren't exactly my
favorite things in the world...
The truth is, I hate them.
Are you seriously asking
me about that right now?
It shouldn't matter...
All that matters is
winning this Rating Game...
We need to focus our energy
on the present--not
worry about the past...
'kay?
You're right!
Let's do this!
I am so with you.
Lesson One.
Yup. Bring it, blondie bear.
You're a little off.
Don't limit your focus
to just the sword.
Keep an eye on your opponent!
I meant to do that.
Come on, you gotta focus!
Lesson Two, it's time you both
became aware of the aura
and magic surrounding you
and tried to stream it
to a focal point.
Let the image of
light flow through you
and be released
as magical power.
I think I did it!
Awesome!
Look at you go with your
little green light...!
I think you have a lot of
natural talent for this, Asia!
Well...
She's uh... She's getting
better, that's for sure...
But she's not the only one.
Whoa...! You're quick!
And you will be too.
Once you grasp the technique,
you can control fire,
water, lightning,
and any of the other elements...
Asia, I bet this one
would be easy for you.
Wanna try?
Sure!
You, on the other hand, need
to spend a little more time
on those
concentration exercises.
I know.
Visualization is the
essence of all magic.
Think about whatever
it is you want
and see it happening
in your mind.
Kay?
Are there any rules
about what I can imagine?
Not at all.
Anything you want.
Just concentrate.
Yeah!
There ya go!
No...!
Please don't be able
to read my mind,
that's not what
I meant to think of!
What's the matter, you okay...?
Issei?
I'm fine!
I'm just focused
on magical things!
Lesson Three.
That was lame.
I wasn't finished!
You gotta aim more towards
the body's central axis
and learn to strike with
precision at your victim's core.
Screw this!
Asia's like the
manifestation queen
and I can't even control
my own imagination...!
Ugh! I suck at life!
We all have powers
that are unique to us.
Yeah, whatever...
Name one thing that I'm
better at than other people.
You're a pervert.
Thanks a lot.
But wait there's more.
You can also be a
really hard worker.
Hey, you think so...?
That's not so bad.
Thanks, Koneko!
Suck it.
Now, Lesson Four!
Can I use my powers to change?
Can we use them for cooking?
Absolutely...!
Magic comes in
handy anywhere...!
Have fun and good luck.
Okay, water... will
you please boil?
During Akeno's lesson,
the only thing I could summon
was a tiny ball of light, what'm
I supposed to do with this...?
Ahhhh, Akeno.
Now there's some ripe ones
just begging to bust free.
Sweet...!
It works on potatoes too!
Wow!
Look how good you're getting!
Yeah...
That wasn't too shabby, was it?
Maybe I was just
having a bad day earlier.
I'm so proud of you!
Wait a second...
This feels familiar...
It seems like
I've done this before?
I remember...!
With Raynare...!
The first time my
Sacred Gear deployed!
That was easy!
I can do this!
Check it out!
I'm like a Sacred
Gear Super Freak!
I think that's enough!
Oh my goodness...!
What are we gonna
do with all of these?
Visualization is the
essence of all magic.
Let the image of
light flow through you
and be released
as magical power.
You can also be a
really hard worker.
You're a pervert
Don't you dare try to peel me.
I would never!
I'm just picturing you naked!
So how was it?
Too small.
No, I mean today.
How do you think it went...?
Did you learn anything new?
I did...
I learned I'm the
weakest link on this team.
Knowing is half the
battle, as they say.
You shouldn't feel
entirely useless, though...
Between Asia's healing powers
and your Boosted Gear, the two
of you have become assets.
Your opponent will
always be aware of this...
So I need you both to
gain at least enough power
to escape from any situation,
so that you won't slow
the rest of the team down.
Yup...
That makes sense.
Besides...
I'm the one who brought
Asia into this mess...
All I want to do is learn enough
so that I can at least protect
her if we get into trouble.
That was delicious
and filling...
I think we should
head to the baths now.
You're all going together?!
That would be the plan...
You're such a silly goose.
Would you like to come along...?
You want to see us
naked together, don't you?
I don't mind.
You, Akeno?
No, I think it sounds like fun!
We could bathe him, too!
Would you mind if he came, Asia?
I wouldn't want any of us
to feel uncomfortable.
Sure!
What about you?
I'd rather die.
Oh well, sorry!
Well that's just melodramatic.
If you peek, I'll kill you.
This was such a good idea.
We haven't done this in forever!
I hope it melts away some of the
fatigue of training at least.
You've all been so working hard.
I have no doubt
this will do the trick.
Sad you're not on
the Double D team?
Yeah...
I guess, a little.
Should I leave you two alone...?
You and that wall look
like you need your privacy.
Whatever!
This is part of my
training, you Idiot!
They teaching you X-ray
vision or something,
I didn't know that
was part of the routine.
Name one thing that I'm
better at than other people.
You're a pervert.
If that's what my power
is, then so be it...!
It was given to me
for a damn good reason!
That's quite a story.
Indeed.
Sounds just like Rias.
Honestly, I don't think
she has any chance of winning.
No...
That, she does not.
But you let her go through
with the training anyway?
I let her make
her own decision...
She's next in line to be head of
the house of Gremory, after all.
I seriously hope she's
capable of at least that.
As do I.
Asia...
Hey!
Issei!
What are you--
I'm sorry.
I hate to wake you up like this.
It's just that...
I need you...
You're the only one
who can help me do this.
What?
What's going on?
Just focus...
You can do this, Issei!
Oh, Issei!
I have an idea.
But I'm gonna need to
borrow some of your clothes.
I know you need this!
I just hope we have enough time!
Good question.
The answer dates
back quite a bit...
Some would say close
to an eternity ago.
Devils, Fallen Angels,
and Heavenly Angels
were at war...
It was a massive,
destructive three-sided battle,
which ultimately ended in
neither victory nor defeat...
Every single battle fought ended
with several of our
members wiped out or missing.
Our life spans--since devils
have very low birth rates--
are nearly eternal to
insure our population...
Yet our existence as
a species is at risk due
to the impact of that war.
Most of the family
lines consisted
of pureblood, upper-class devils
that made up what is
known as the 72 Pillars.
The war then
claimed all but three.
Mine, which is the
House of Gremory.
Sona's, the House of Sitri.
And Riser's, the
House of Phoenix.
Out of 72 Pillars,
we are the only survivors.
It was then that devils
first began recruiting humans
to replace the numbers
in their houses.
After that, The Rating
Game came about.
This allowed devils
that were the masters
of their households to provide
recently converted humans
with combat experience--as well
as show off their own abilities.
Nowadays it still
has quite an impact,
one's record in the Rating
Game has a huge influence
on their nobility and status.
Okay I think that's it.
You guys look pretty tired...
What do you say we take
a break and have some tea?
Sounds good.
I'll go make it.
Oh! Wait a minute.
I'll come help you!
Hang on, Asia.
I'm sorry about last night.
Oh, that's okay!
You're getting so much stronger!
The way that you--
I wanna keep this
just between us...
Is that cool?
Like a secret?
Yeah, I think I just
need a little more time
to perfect it on my own...
Ya know, to make
it battle ready?
Absolutely...
This new move is definitely
worth waiting for,
so you shouldn't rush...
Let me know if you need my help!
What new move?
We can't tell you yet.
I almost forgot, Asia.
I'd love to learn more
about your former
life as a Holy Sister.
You mean right now?
Let's see...
I did a lot of exorcisms
so I guess we could
talk about that...
There are two things you need.
The most important one...
is holy water...
But Devils need to be careful...
It's vital that you
never actually touch it.
Is it gonna make us melt?!
It will do something bad.
I figured that much...
I don't know why
you're leaving out
all the cool parts
of this story.
It isn't just us...
This goes for you, too.
You're a devil now, remember?
Yeah, I know...
I guess there's no point
talking about how to make it...
So let's just move on
to something else...
The second item is...
The Holy Bible...
I used to read it constantly
when I was a little girl...
It was my favorite...
but now every time
I start a verse,
I get a terrible headache
and I can't get through it!
Because you're a devil.
You're one of us now, Asia.
You should write it down.
Probably not a good idea.
I just want to read one verse!
It was always my favorite...!
Okay, here it is.
I didn't start yet!
Dear Lord, forgive me
for not reading Your words.
I promise I've tried, uh...
Why do you hate me...?!
Ow-ow-ow!
If it was anyone else,
I'd think she was doing
a bit right now, but
I guess probably not.
And Asia's stronger than I am.
If it hurts her this much,
I wonder what it'd do to me.
Issei?
Oh hey, Rias...
Why are you still up...?
Getting kinda late, isn't it?
What perfect timing...
I need to chat with you
about something anyway.
Wow.
So that's the attack plan?
It is...
But it's not a very
good one, I'm afraid...
According to this manual,
we still have a lot
to be worried about.
But it's gotta work, right?
You've been busting
your ass on all this.
I mean, you don't
even sleep anymore!
Doesn't matter...
We can't control what
the opponent will do...
You realize we're up
against Phoenix, right?
And let me assure you,
the name is most appropriate.
A devil...
But he is also a marquis
counted among the 72 Pillars...
We've got our
work cut out for us.
His ability is the same as the
beast his family's named after.
Immortality.
Is that allowed...?!
How is it even possible?
It just is...
He's indestructible...
He regenerates immediately
following an attack
Riser's win-lose
ratio is eight to two...
However, those two
losses were accepted out
of respect for a
family he's close to...
He lost on purpose.
Ever since the Rating Game
was put into effect,
the House of Phoenix has
dominated the playing field.
They've always had
the highest score.
Can't say I'm surprised.
How are you supposed to
lose if you're immortal.
I'm so sorry, Rias!
About what?
I'm the one who told Riser
where to stick it and
now he wants to fight...
Should've kept
my fat mouth shut!
Not at all.
In fact, thanks to you, I'll
get a chance to tell my father
and the others
where to 'stick it.'
They set up this Game because
they all anticipate me losing.
And now I'll be able to change
the score and prove them wrong.
In our chess, this is
called a swindle...
or a trap-maneuver.
Yeah, well...
I'm just glad you're
not going along
with this bullshit
marriage proposal.
That takes balls.
The proposal was to the
heiress of the House of Gremory.
Because of my title, I am
not ever recognized as Rias.
The House of Gremory will
always come before me...
I've learned to adjust to it;
and make personal
decisions accordingly.
Make no mistake,
my title is something
I will always take pride in.
But when it comes to
the subject of marriage,
I want to share that with
someone who loves me as Rias--
not for how my status
can improve their life.
Otherwise, they may as
well marry the House.
I understand that history
is not in my favor,
and the idea of love
may just remain a dream.
But it's one I'd like to keep.
Whatever!
I like you and I don't care
what your name is!
I like you for who you are!
The Gremory name
doesn't define you...
It's just an empty
title and anyone
who thinks otherwise
doesn't know you.
You're incredible...
I mean, come on...
Look at everything
that you've done for me...
I just hope someday
I can pay you back.
What...?
What happened...?
Did I say something wrong again?
Of course not.
It's nothing.
Anyway, the point is:
If we're going to fight,
we're going to win.
I know you're called
the Princess of Ruin
and the Empress
of Annihilation...
Nobody earns themselves
nicknames like that
if they're easy to
beat, am I right...?
There's no way a guy named after
a bird can stand up to you.
Not true.
My powers are strong
but I can't heal
myself the way he can.
My strength lies
in my entire team
and our ability
to fight together...
which means I need
never battle alone.
When I fight,
Gremory fights with me...
but if I lose,
Gremory does as well.
Winning is the only option.
You're amazing.
I can't imagine
that kind of strength.
I keep trying to make
you proud, but I'm just...
a failure!
No, you're not.
It's really okay.
I need to start accepting it...
The signs have always been
there, I just refused to see.
Even with the Sacred Gear,
I've been the least
useful to you...
That says a lot,
don't you think?
I keep throwing myself into
things as if I can help...
and I end up making
everything worse.
You don't need me...
I mean I'm just...
a freaking loser!
That's not true, Issei.
You just lack confidence.
But don't worry...
that's something I'll be more
than happy to help you with.
What are you saying?
You'll know soon.
But for now, go get some rest...
Both your body and mind have
been through a lot today...
I'll stay by your side
until you fall asleep.
It's going to be okay, Issei...
You have my word...
You will come to
believe in yourself.
You're gonna need to
use your Boosted Gear...
Can you handle it?
Of course, but you said not to
use it during training camp...
You change your mind?
You weren't supposed to use
it without my permission...
Kiba, would you mind
partnering with him?
No. Not at all.
I'm not going easy on you.
Neither am I...!
Boosted Gear!
Go!
Boost!
Good, now again!
Go!
Boost!
You can do better!
More!
Boost!
Great!
Keep it going!
Boosted Gear!
Boost!
Keep it up, Issei!
Again!
Boosted Gear, Go!
Give me more!
We can do this!
Boost!
Twelve power-ups in a row
that's a record, isn't it?
Alright, stop...!
Can you see how
far you've come...?
You've never been able
to endure this much power
for this long in the past.
The results of your training
were abundantly clear just then.
Holy crap!
Let's keep moving!
All right...
Boosted Gear!
Explosion!
What's he doing?
Perfecting a new
call, it seems...
This should allow him
to gather all the
power in his body
and unleash it in
one massive blow.
You're up, Kiba!
Okay, Issei, try using
it all on him, now!
What? That's all I have?
Trust yourself!
Looks like it worked.
You broke the mountain.
I can't believe that
came out of Issei.
Woah...
That did a lot more
than I thought it would.
Issei...!
Are you okay?
Looks like he used up all of
his strength on that last one...
So what do you think...?
He's improving, isn't he?
I'll say...
I didn't expect him
to be that strong.
That last move was way better
than anything he's
ever thrown at me.
Issei!
You have become the
linchpin of this Game.
Your attack will critically
affect the direction
in which this
competition moves...
Trust in us...
and more importantly,
you must trust in yourself.
I trust you...
And I know I can handle this!
He can do this.
You're incredible...
I mean, come on...
Look at everything that
you've done for me...
I just hope I can pay you back.
Rias...
I want you to know
I could die happy right now...
This is one of the
top ten moments of my life.
Why on Earth are you crying?
I did it!
Rise and shine and
go kick some ass!