Only one more hour before
the Rating game starts.
The House of Phoenix
has no respect for us...
Let's give 'em a taste
of how strong the
House of Gremory truly is.
They will receive
no mercy from us!
I've been training for this
like my life depended on it...
There's no way in
hell I'll let them win!
Issei, are you there?
Do you mind if I come in?
No, please do.
Wow.
Uh...
Haven't seen you
wear that in a while.
I thought my habit might make
me feel more confident...
Rias said she was okay with it,
as long as I felt comfortable...
So I just wanted to
know what you thought.
I think you look pretty
incredible, actually;
but then I've always
liked you in that outfit.
You're sweet...
I'd like to stay
here with you...
Do you mind?
No...
Not at all.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing, I'm just a little
bit nervous about the battle.
Still, as long I have
you here next to me...
I know everything'll be fine.
Yeah.
Is it all right
with you, Issei...?
If I just stay here
like this for a while?
You kidding...?
I think it's perfect.
Rise and shine and
go kick some ass!
Let's go... It's time.
Unbelievable!
Our fearless leader doesn't
even look worried about
the game today, does she?
Sorry if I'm interrupting.
No, please, come on in, Sona.
I'm glad you could make it.
Wow, I sure didn't expect
to see those two here...
What gives?
There's a live broadcast
of the competition
so family members can watch...
Sona and Tsubaki are here
to help out with that.
Awesome.
And besides, it's her
first Rating Game...
I wouldn't miss an event
like this for anything.
Well, I promise to do
everything in my power
to make it interesting for you.
It's almost time...
I hope you're ready
for this, my lady.
Yes...
We're ready whenever you are.
In a few moments,
we'll use this magic circle
to transport you and the rest of
your team to the battlefield.
And where exactly
is the battlefield?
In a neutral alternate space,
created just for the game...
Because it's not real,
we have full license
to do some damage, even burn
it to the ground if we want.
Great, that doesn't
sound scary at all.
I'll be in the Student
Council broadcast
booth calling the game...
We'll be cheering you on...
Good luck.
Thanks a lot...
Just try to keep the
play-by-play fair.
Oh, I'll keep it clean.
Though if I was
a betting girl...
I'd say you're going
to beat that scumbag
seven ways from Sunday.
There's something
I forgot to tell you.
I thought you'd like to
know the Great Devil Lucifer,
will be watching the Game.
Oh... brother dearest.
Whoa...
Are you telling me that your
older brother is The Devil...?
Or am I just hearing
things wrong?
No, Rias's brother is Lucifer,
the King of the Devils.
The Lucifer...?
The King of the entire
underworld is your big bro?!
That's right.
His name is Sir Zechs...
Although historically he has
been known by many names...
During the great war,
our leader died...
Sir Zechs took over the throne
and lead us
through a dark time...
He saved the devil
kingdom from ruin.
Well, that explains
why Rias is the next heir
to the house of Gremory.
I had no idea.
The House of Gremory will
always come before me...
I've learned to adjust to it;
and make personal
decisions accordingly.
It's time, everyone.
Then let's go.
That's weird!
I think our magic
circle's broken.
Yeah, we're still here...
Did I screw it up again?
Your attention, please.
Welcome everyone,
my name is Grayfia...
I am a servant of
the house of Gremory.
I will be your referee
during today's match.
To create the battlefield you'll
be competing in,
I took suggestions from both
Lady Rias and Lord Riser...
You may recognize this place,
as it's an exact replica
of Kuo Academy,
an educational institution
in the human world.
What does that mean?
Just take a look outside.
The sky!
This is an alternate space.
It might look like it,
but trust me, we're
not at school anymore.
Okay, I'm totally
having one of those
'I just peed my pants'
moments right now.
Each team has been given an area
that will serve
as its home base.
Lady Rias, your crew will be
in the Occult Research Club
headquarters in
the old schoolhouse.
Show me Phoenix.
Yes, ma'am.
Lord Riser's home
base will be located
in the principal's office in the
new schoolhouse.
Pawns will be promoted if they
can make
their way to the home base of
the opposing team.
Good luck to all.
I'm gonna fight my way
to their home base
right out of the gate,
get promoted to
something awesome,
and beat the crap out
of Lord Douche-nozzle!
I wouldn't do that...
Unless you wanna get
your ass handed to you.
Be smart, dude...
Odds are Riser's gonna
want to move his pawns
into our territory right away...
We need to keep
enough players nearby
to make sure
that doesn't happen.
So not as badass as my plan.
Uh... Thanks?
These'll help us
communicate during the battle.
Alright, that's some
secret agent shit.
All right devils...
Let the game begin!
Those failures don't deserve to
stand on the same field as us...
Show no mercy!
Break their spirits,
shatter their pride,
and force them
into submission...
If I don't crush her,
this is meaningless.
The enemy base is
just across the way.
Cutting through the school
grounds might be quick,
but it's not an option.
They'll see us
coming a mile away.
Correct...
And we might as
well be sitting ducks.
If we go through the track field
and sneak in the back,
then we might have the
element of surprise on our side.
That's the most obvious
entry-point available...
And Riser knows it.
My guess is he'll station
a group of knights or rooks
with strong mobility right
behind the athletic clubhouse.
That doesn't leave us with
very many options then, does it?
First things first.
I think we should
secure the gymnasium
before we do anything else.
Its adjacent to their home base
and not too far from us...
but most importantly,
it will serve as a
diversion to the other side.
The gymnasium's basically in
the center of the battlefield...
Whoever gets to it first is
gonna have a leg up for sure.
Good call...
Given the options we have,
that's our best chance...
Koneko, do you
think you can handle
getting in the gym
and locking it down?
All this talk of fighting
is starting to scare me.
Relax, we've got
Rias, all we have
to do is trust her
and we'll be just fine.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
To do that, we need to secure
a defensive perimeter...
Kiba and Koneko...
Get out there and set some
traps in the woods, a-sap.
Got it.
Cool.
Let's do this, Shiro.
Well, wish us luck, you guys!
Akeno...
Next we'll need
your expertise...
When they're done
setting the traps,
your illusion magic is going to
come in handy, so be prepared.
I'll be waiting.
What about me and Asia;
is there anything we
can do to help you out?
Asia, you're my healing
support, so in order
to keep you safe, you need
to stay close to base...
Because if we lose you,
we're going to be in
big trouble out there.
Okay!
Issei, come here.
For what?
I want you to put
your head in my lap.
Really?
I'm trying to focus
on this game thing,
and I'm pretty sure that if
I do that I'll be focusing on--
Will you get over here?
Your wish is my command.
It's like I'm floating on a
cloud made of juicy thighs
and the scent of a woman.
Rias...
I want you to know
I could die happy right now...
This is one of the top
ten moments of my life.
Why in the world are you crying?
Cause...
I'm just so overwhelmed that
you're actually letting me
lie with my head
buried in your business,
this is, hands down, the nicest
thing anyone's ever done for me!
You are such a drama queen...
If you like it that much,
you can do it again sometime.
Are you serious?
Wipe your nose,
you're snotting on me.
Issei...
I cast a little spell on you...
It's time to unlock it.
Nice...
Onto the next one.
All right, off you go.
What is this...?
What's happening to me?
When you became a foot soldier,
I told you it used
eight of my pawn pieces,
but what I didn't tell you was
how much power you'd received.
Wait, what?
If I had unleashed
everything all at once,
your body wouldn't have
been able to take it...
So I cast a spell to
keep your power at bay...
Because of the spell,
your abilities come to you in
small, manageable stages...
What I just did was release
another portion of your power.
Uh, okay, so does that explain
the weird feeling
I'm having right now?
This is just the beginning
of what you can do, Issei...
But in order for
your body to be able
to handle your Boosted Gear
on top of the full
extent of your power,
we had to get you in shape,
and make sure you
were strong enough...
There's a good portion in there
that you're just
not ready for yet.
So this whole time you
were running me ragged
and busting my balls,
it was for my own good?
And I thought I was being
punished for sucking so hard!
This is awesome!
She doesn't hate me!
Yaaaay!
There I was being jealous,
when all along Rias was
just trying to help him...
Dear God...
Please forgive me
for being so stupid
and letting my awful
jealousy get the best of me.
Do your best out there...
Don't go easy on them just cause
your opponents are girls...
Take those pawns out...
Given the opportunity, they'll
do the same thing to you.
I won't let you down...
Those devil hotties'll be sorry
they messed with Team Gremory!
I can't wait to see
what you do out there...
I just know you're
going to make me proud.
Rias... Do you copy?
I hear you loud and clear.
We're ready when you are,
just say the word.
All right you guys,
here's the game plan.
Gremory might be about
to make her first move.
With as many pieces
as she's missing,
Rias won't be able
to protect her home base
and launch a full assault.
Because of that...
She'll have to force her way
in with tertiary attacks.
Okay...
Once you're in the gym,
there's no way you can
avoid a confrontation...
Be sure to follow our plan.
Got it.
Kiba...
You all set?
Yep. I'm in position now.
Akeno, stand by to move.
I'm counting on you.
We totally got this!
Let's go, team...
Commence operation
'Phoenix Ashes!'
Your opponent is Lord Riser,
a gifted warrior even among
the house of the Phoenix.
Show no mercy, because
none will be shown to you!
Good luck, guys...
I'll be praying for each
and every one of you.
I can't believe how good
of a copy this place is.
They're here.
Smells like Gremory filth...
Come out, come out
wherever you are!
Well, I guess the
stealth approach
isn't gonna work, is it?
Look what we have here...
She sent us a pawn and a rook...
Lil' Issei needed some help.
Who're they?
I'm Mira...
And I'm a Phoenix pawn.
I'm Shueran, a Phoenix Rook.
I'm Ile, and I'm a pawn!
My name is Nel,
and I'm a also a pawn!
The rook chick...
She could be a
big problem for us.
You really think so?
Based on her power level,
she's got the skills of a Queen.
That's no good.
Oh, what the hell,
we knew we were underdogs
from the beginning...
Let's just do this.
Power-up... boost!
Boost!
Those pawns are all you...
I'll try my luck
with the rook...
Watch my back out there...
At least keep those
chicken heads off me.
Don't worry, I'm not
gonna go easy on 'em
cause they're girls.
I'll choke a chicken.
Let's rock this!
So she decided to attack
from the center, after all...
How are things on
the other front?
My Lord.
Your pawns Shulyer,
Marion, and Byurent
are moving in on
the enemy as we speak.
Damn, this fog is so thick;
we won't be able
to see anything.
A trap...?
Did they really think something
that lame would work?
The Gremorys are
dumber than I thought.
A cute trick from a
Rating Game virgin.
Hey, are you okay?!
Nice one.
Who the hell are you...?
Tell me!
I'm Koneko...
Suck it.
Why are you running, pansy boy?!
What's the matter, you
not a fan of chainsaws?!
I love chainsaws, almost
as much as I love twins,
but you're ruining em both.
Psychos!
No way!
Those girls are bat-shit!
Slice him up, slice
him up, slice him up!
Hey... I got this!
You bastard...
Quit running!
Come on, we just
wanna slice you!
I've been working my butt off
to try and get stronger...!
All so when a moment
like one this came along,
I'd be ready to kick some ass!
Boost!
I'm gonna make Rias
proud of me today!
Explosion!
Guess what...?
You're first!
One!
And two!
And here's three!
My staff... It's broken.
Oww...
Stupid hand...!
That was awesome!
I'm so freakin' hard core!
We can't lose to this dweeb!
If we do, Lord Riser's
gonna be pissed off!
It's time to die!
Let's slice off his balls!
Want some?
Bring it on!
Here's my special move!
Time to geeeeeeeet...!
Naked.
You ladies like that...?
Since the first moment my tiny,
baby man-balls dropped,
all I ever did was
undress girls with my eyes.
But now, thanks
to lots of hard-work
and my perverted powers,
I just have to imagine you naked
and my vision comes true...!
Try and mess with me...?
Tops are comin' off!
What a freak.
Who knows, maybe his
special move will work...
Nothing will stop
a girl in her tracks
like having her clothes
magically ripped off.
But you're right,
it's a little rapey.
Dirt-bag!
Slime-bucket!
You make me sick!
Thanks, Asia!
Yes...!
It's working!
Oh, Issei.
Try again.
I did it!
Once more?
Sure...! Let me go
put some clothes on!
You're doing so well!
Crap...!
You've still got
your underwear on...
It's all gotta come off!
Don't worry...
I've got plenty of clothes
for you to strip away...!
Don't give up...!
Make me naked!
This is all thanks to you, Asia!
Dude, you're such a loser.
I thought you'd be proud!
Nice job, you totally
took out the rook chick!
Koneko, Issei,
what's your status?
We're good...
No great...
The gym is now
under our control...
And...
The girls.
I made their clothes rip off.
Good work, Issei...
Akeno is in position
and she's ready to go...
You need to get out
of there immediately.
Hey, come back here!
This fight isn't over yet!
Who runs away in
the middle of a battle?
Boom.
Three of Lord Riser's pawns
and one of Lord Riser's rooks...
Retired.
That was badass.
Yeah, 'badass' is
one way to put it...
She's the real deal.
It's why her nickname's
The Priestess of Thunder.
She knows how to
bring the boom...
And she likes it.
If she's the Priestess
of anything it's pain.
I'm just glad the
hardcore dominatrix
isn't on the other team!
I must say, I'm impressed...
Rias used an important
strategic position
to lure them into a trap,
and then blew it sky-high...
That was a bold move.
You're right...
Although, now
Lord Riser has no choice
but to unleash everything.
True.
This battle's just begun.
The Phoenixes still
have us outnumbered...
We'll need to buy Akeno
a little bit of time
so she can be fully ready
for her second attack...
Once her power is replenished,
we'll start to make
preparations for our next move.
Until then, stick to the
plan and I promise you,
we will win this thing.
So?
We need to get to the athletic
field as soon as we can...
Kiba's waiting for us there...
If we see any
bad guys, we own them...
Sound good?
I just hope Kiba's doing okay.
He's all alone.
Do you think the
Gremorys really believe
these stupid traps are
going to slow us down at all?
That's their
home base, isn't it?
What is this?
Hello, ladies.
You gals looking
for some company?
Cause if you're feeling
lonely this evening,
I might be the man for you.
Damn...!
We walked right into
that one, didn't we?
What we lack in
man-power, girls,
we make up for in brains.
I hate to burst your bubble,
cause you're kinda
my type, blondie...
But as cute as you are,
do you think you can take
all three of us on at once?
Why don't we find out?
Eh, knowing him,
he's probably taking on
their whole team without
even messing up his hair...
But hey...
We might as well
give him a hand.
Touch me and I puke.
Oh, come on, relax...
I'm not gonna make
your clothes disappear.
I wish I could
make you disappear.
She hates me...
But then again, I guess
that's nothing new, is it...?
Hey, Koneko,
wait up just a second!
Koneko!
Issei...!
What happened to Koneko?!
Issei, talk to me!
Koneko!
Give up, Rias...
No matter what you try.
Victory will be Riser's.
That's one.
The Princess of Ruin...
Twilight Healing...
Priestess of Thunder...
Sword Birth...
And Booster Gear...
Such grand sounding names
when they're all together.
But we are Phoenixes!
And you cannot defeat us!