♪
Hiroshi here.
Sunako is a great cook
and in my opinion,
I think that makes her
girlie enough already.
What's more, I think
she's going to be
a good mom.
What, a good mom?
Well, when you
think about it,
I suppose he actually does
have a good point there.
Hey, wait a second...
Remember, we're trying
to make her into a lady,
not a mother.
(gong bonging)
The Role to Motherhood.
Please don't be born!
♪
Oh, right there.
It feels so good, oh!
Anyway, I was saying
it should be okay
if the field investigation
doesn't find any problems.
But if that investigator‐‐
hey, hold on a second...
Listen, I have an
idea that might work.
Yo ho!
(giggling)
Isn't this great?
Mm‐hmm, taking an
off‐season vacation
isn't too bad.
Uh‐huh, Auntie
really gave us
a cool and
fabulous present.
Yar ain't kidding.
(laughing)
Well, yeah,
this probably is
a cool and fabulous
present for you!
"I bought an
uninhabited island
and I want you
to come visit."
‐Huh.
‐Visit an uninhabited island?
Yeah, that sounds boring.
You really think so?
‐Uh‐hum.
‐Is something wrong, Takenaga?
Well, it's just the
name of the island.
The name?
Yeah, Neptune Island.
I remember reading
about it in some book
and if I
recall correctly,
the legend
tells of a pirate
named Captain Wing who
died on that very island.
A pirate!
It's so romantic.
To rescue the
beautiful princess
who's been captured
by foul pirates.
I'll sail
the rough seas
and embark on an
adventurous journey alone.
And amid the
looming big waves,
a huge squid
starts attacking me.
Hang in there princess,
‐I'm coming to save you!
‐So you were saying
that a pirate captain used to
live on the island, right?
Does that mean there's tons
of buried treasure there?
Tons of treasure?
Who knows,
even if there is,
I'm sure buried treasure
isn't all you'd find.
You might find
pirate's weapons
and even their skeletons.
Skeletons?
Tons and tons of them.
Tons and tons of them!
Tons and tons
of skeletons!
I don't like scary stuff.
What are you
talking about, Yuki,
if we find the
pirate's treasure
we'll never have to worry
about our rent again.
Well, buried
treasure or not,
I think it's a
pretty sweet offer,
so let's go.
Yeah, let's go,
everyone, let's go!
All right,
it's decided!
We're gonna go to
a South Seas island!
A South Seas island?
A sunny South Seas island?
Soooo greaaaat.
Be sure to bring me
back some souvenirs.
Thanks, I
don't want much,
just skeleton or two,
maybe three or four.
Or maybe 27 or 28‐‐
(evil laughter)
And this is
how you treat me?
Hey, Kyohei, is
this your luggage?
You really think
you'll find treasure?
Why not, I'll take gold,
silver, pearls, anything.
Personally, I'll be
happy if I can find
some old dinosaur fossils.
Fossils?
Dude, you sound
like an old geezer.
Uninhabited island
means marooned hotties.
Huh, I'd rather find
some unusual animals
while we're there.
Some rare, elusive critters.
Fine with me as long
as they're edible.
Hey, I can see
the island now!
Whaa!
A pirate ship!
Whoo!
What they hay?
No way?
Hello there, folks,
I'm the captain.
That ship is actually
a floating hotel
which Miss
Nakahara had built
especially for
you to stay in.
It's already stocked with
everything you'll need
during your stay.
This way, please.
Wow, Auntie's
so prepared.
You're not a
little suspicious?
Why would
you say that?
All right then,
I'll let you guys
take care of the rest.
I'm the captain!
And he's gone.
This is suspicious.
Why would he be telling us
to take care of the rest?
Oh!
Come on, stop worrying
about all that stuff.
First we better
get ourselves
something to eat
for dinner tonight.
Sunako Nakahara,
you're coming with me.
No way, you've got
to be kidding me.
(gong bonging)
(screaming)
The Road to Womanhood!
Protecting your
skin from sun damage.
Doing this will
keep you fair skinned
all year long.
Wrong!
In fact, it's
much more effective
to apply a little
sunblock frequently
than a lot all at once.
And getting plenty
vitamin C at the same time
will prevent you
from getting freckles.
But if you forget
to apply sunblock,
all you'll
get is tragedy.
Oh no, oh no!
Waaaaaa!
Oh, don't be
like that, Sunako.
This is a vacation, you're
supposed to enjoy it.
Aaah!
Okay, Sunako?
We don't get to
do this very often.
Aaah!
Are you even listening
to us, Sunako?
Aaah, don't worry
about me, I'm fine!
(laughing)
You'll probably say
you can't stand sunshine.
But I'll bet that
you're scared of water.
No, that's not true!
Jeez, what
a crying shame.
I mean, just have
a look for yourself,
I can see so many fish
swimming around in the water
and I even spotted some
fresh skeletons down there.
Fresh?
Did you say fresh?
Fresh, fresh, fresh,
fresh, fresh, fresh
skeletons!
I'm coming!
And I won't share
them with anyone!
Whoa, Sunako
actually stood up!
Let's go!
Aaah!
Kyohei's sure
has gotten better
‐at manipulating Sunako.
‐Oh, he probably
just wants to have
some fun with her.
(laughing)
(blowing bubbles)
Wee!
‐Race me!
‐What for?
Are you afraid
you'll lose?
You're pissing me off!
(laughing)
♪
Whoa, nay!
The signal's Yukinojo
and the others
are gone from
the mainland, nay.
This is a grave
problem indeed, nay.
That means
they've most likely
gone down south, nay.
I don't know
what's going on but...
let's just get out
there and follow them!
Goth‐goth, loli‐loli.
For some reason
goth‐goth‐‐
The boat's heavy,
loli‐loli!
Get a move on ladies!!
What the heck, nay?
"Noi, I'm heading
out for a bit."
Of course I'm
gonna follow him
when he leaves a
note like this!
You've got a
point with a P.
Oh, be quiet,
just shut it!
I said row now!
To the south, goth‐goth.
Yeah, yeah, loli‐loli.
‐Come on!
‐(shouting)
‐Put some muscles into it!
‐Don't push me!
Ooh, that
was so much fun.
Hey, where are
Kyohei and Sunako?
They looked like
they were having
a lot of fun together.
Actually, they're
over that way.
♪
Treasure, treasure,
treasure, treasure!
(laughing)
She thinks
she's gonna have
all the
treasure to herself,
but that's
not gonna happen!
Bones, bones,
empty shells of light!
Tragic, lovely calcium!
Hey, what are you
doing lounging around?
We're gonna dig
up some treasure!
Oh, boy, I guess I'd
better go over there.
Treasure, treasure, treasure,
treasure, treasure, treasure!
Whooo!
♪
Huh, hey,
that sounded like‐‐
(giggling)
Yeahhhhhh!
I found it, I found it,
I found a skull!
I found a skull,
a skull, a skull!
♪
Hello, Mr. Skull.
(screaming)
♪
Um, Sunako?
I guess she's gonna
look in the woods.
(grunting)
Aaah!
♪
(screeching)
(rumbling)
♪
Hey, what was that noise?
The treasure!
I just heard something
coming from over there!
♪
Boulder!
Boulder, boulder,
boulder, boulder,
boulder,
boulder, boulder, boulder!
That was close!
If this weren't a comedy,
we'd be dead for sure!
Uh?
(growling)
Who's there?
Um, Sunako?
♪
Wait up!
What's she doing now?
She's fast.
(growling)
Where did she go?
Why did she
run away from us?
Huh?
Aaagh!
Waaa!
Aaah!
Ranmaru!
You saved me.
Whatever you do,
don't look down, okay?
Great, now you
made me want to look.
You've got to be
frickin' kidding me!
Ha!
Sunako Nakahara!
I ought to...
Where ye fools
will seek me treasure.
♪
Uh, aaah crap!
Let me down
right now, dammit!
Kyohei!
Why are you
doing this?
Aaaah!
What's wrong, Sunako?
My name be Captain Wing.
The soul of this woman
who loves the
skull and crossbones
has awakened me
from me slumber.
Therefore, I will
come back to life
right here and right now.
(ghostly moaning)
♪
Aaahhhahahh!
Sunako, wait!
Oh, you son of‐‐I mean...
Kyohei!
I can't believe
this is happening!
(evil laughter)
♪
(yelling)
(cackling)
♪
Captain Wing ahoy!
Wing, Wing, Wing, Wing.
♪
A ghost.
Who would have thought
this would happen?
Has Sunako been
possessed by this ghost?
Who the heck are you
sparkling for, anyway?
More importantly, what
are we gonna do now?
I'm not sure,
but let's be careful.
It appears as
though there are traps
set up all
over the island.
Hey, cut that out.
♪
Oh, crap!
Honestly, he just
told you to be careful.
Aah!
We were just
talking about this!
Ranmaru, Yuki!
Right, now I really need
to be careful, mmm‐hmm.
Aah, whoa!
We're falling!
♪
How long are you
planning to take a break?
You can yell, nay.
But we have, nay.
Reached our, nay.
Limits, nay.
While you're
sitting here talking
we could get attacked
by a shark or something.
Like that.
Yeah, yeah.
Unbelievable, nay!
♪
A shark, nay!
(yelling)
♪
Oh, it's a baby.
We all freaked out
for nothing, nay.
Let's get back to it.
It's the real thing!
Nobody panic, nay.
It's times like
this where we must ask
for the mercy of hell.
Goth‐goth, loli‐loli.
♪
Ah, we're melting!
Melting, melting.
♪
(crashing)
Ow!
How reckless.
All part of my
youthful charm.
Now where
is Takenaga anyway?
Takenaga?
Noi has come to see you.
Poopy, poopy, poo.
I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
Would you stop crying!
Takenaga should
be here any time now
with a rope and
a ladder truck.
Quit yelling, you meanie.
Uh.
If only he were a
beautiful girl instead,
then I wouldn't
mind it so much.
♪
I'm here for you, baby.
Ooh, you're so dependable.
‐Ah, yes, so dependable!
‐I wish...
I had a cute little
animal with me right now.
(mewling)
Wow, this
is so comforting.
(sighing)
Anyway, we just
have to hang in there
a little while longer.
At least I hope so.
Huh?
♪
Uh‐huh.
I never would
have thought I'd find
such luscious delicacy
on an uninhabited
island like this.
Huh, what's that?
What the hay?
(mewling)
♪
Ah, a panda!
A real one!
I can't resist anymore!
Who'd have thought
I'd find you here?
Let me hold you tight.
Ropes or a ladder truck.
We don't have either.
Ointment,
good luck charm,
‐and there's some salt‐‐
‐Is anyone there?
(door creaking)
♪
(cooing)
Wow, a dinosaur!
Takenaga, I found you!
♪
Noi, darling,
it's almost done.
So just make
yourself comfortable
and it'll be
ready in a minute.
Takenaga is naked
under that apron!
(heavy breathing)
It's a dinosaur, it's
a real life dinosaur!
Not only that it's‐‐
(blubbering)
Hee hee hee hee!
Please don't
stare at me that way.
(yelling)
This is too much.
I just can't
take it anymore!
That dinosaur, oh no,
please don't eat me.
Please let me eat you!
(laughing)
(insects chirping)
What is this place?
Sunako Nakahara, hello?
Argh, so you found me.
It's been far too long,
for the time has
come to raise the flag
of Captain Wing once more.
After then ye shall die!
Huh, crap!
You are possessed!
Aaah!
The time for our
departure has arrived now!
Come on, me lads!
(ghostly moaning)
♪
Arrgh.
The captain
is calling for us.
Aaah, I love you!
‐Arrgh, it's the captain.
(flag flapping)
♪
(ghostly moaning)
Captain Wing.
I'm glad you made it
here to join me, mateys.
And after we've
made an offering
of this beautiful lad,
all our lives will
be fully restored!
Hail, Captain Wing!
Hey, why the hell
are you morons
siding with those
freakin' ghosts?
Go, Wing!
Listen, Sunako Nakahara,
get that ghost
out of your tiny
skull and let me down!
(laughter)
What a feisty
sacrifice you are!
But in order for us
to be resurrected...
(gasps)
Skeletons, skeletons
skeletons, skeletons!
Skeletons!
Skeletons,
skeletons, skeletons.
So many of them!
Uh, captain?
Aaah!
♪
(indistinct grumbling)
Aaaah!
What the...Sunako?
Noi, what on earth
are you doing here?
I...you did leave
me behind after all
and that was so mean.
I'm sorry, Noi,
but I didn't want to risk
putting you in any danger.
Waaaah, this is no time
for that lovey dovey crap!
Excuse me, but what
are you guys doing?
Go, get them!
Aaaargh!
Go get them, lads!
(ghostly moaning)
You've got to be
freakin' kidding me,
this whole thing is nuts!
Damn it, untie me
this instant, you coward!
Shut up, you're not going
to live long anyway.
What did you say?
I can handle
the pirate crap,
but dressing
me up like this
while I was unconscious
is totally creepy,
you pervert.
What a noisy sacrifice.
Do you really
want to be eaten
by sharks that badly?
(yelling)
♪
Even if I must
fight skeletons,
I will protect you, Noi.
You're so awesome.
Ahh!
Still awesome.
I'm not scared,
I'm not scared!
Being surrounded by
mannequins every single day
hasn't been in vain.
Now what say ye?
This is the end!
Grrr.
Come on, pretty boy,
I want to see you jump!
And if you won't, wahhahaha!
(gasps)
♪
Gaaaah!
Aaah!
Why, why do I
have a nose bleed?
Sunako, please wake up!
Don't let a
ghost beat you!
Sunako!
(groaning)
♪
Gaaaahh!
How dare ye, I will
not give into ye fools!
Listen up!
This girl is
100 times stronger
than your candy ass.
So leave Sunako Nakahara
right the hell down!
Aaah, it's so radiant!
♪
Aaaaah!
Take on, you
creature of light!
Go, go, go!
Sunako Naka‐‐
Aaah, this really sucks!
Why, why is she
going against my will?
Shut the hell up!
Step aside you
unasleep fool!
Do you hear me?
I will kill the
creature of light!
Waaaah!
♪
Aaaah, Captain!
(ghostly wailing)
♪
No, that girl is
really freakin' weird!
♪
(gasping)
Aaah, the
radiant skeletons‐‐
Sunako!
Oh, Sunako!
Snap out of it.
‐Sunako.
Blaaaah!
Is she done now?
I guess her desire
to kill Kyohei herself
was enough to
overcome that ghost.
Wasn't it?
I don't know whether
to be happy or not.
Bonehead.
(laughing)
♪
Hi there, so
what did you think?
I got a really good
price on the island
because it
has some history,
but did you all like it?
How'd you like the
pirate's island theme?
Pretty good, right?
Looks like
you had a blast,
so I think I'll turn it
into an amusement park.
Stop blabbing
that nonsense!
But this whole island
is cursed, Auntie!
You come down and
take responsibility
for what happened.
(speaking foreign language)
(laughing)
What language did
she use this time?
More importantly, how
are we gonna get home?
Waa‐haa‐haa.
♪
Don't pull the rope.
Pull the rope?
It's the Sports Festival.
Toss the balls!
Balls?
Like I said, it's
a Sports Festival!
Put your blood
on the line, Sunako.
Put my blood on the line?
It's the Sports Festival!
Not again.
Next time on
The Wallflower,
Dream Comes True.
Do you like gym outfits?
Hey, don't pull that.