Hiroshi here, although the
kidnapping incident came
to an end, everyone seems
to be acting a little funny.
I wonder, where did Kyohei go?
Well, he's not a little kid,
so I think he'll be okay.
It still worries me though.
I just can't believe he lied
to us and left like that.
I wonder what he was thinking.
I am going to go look for him.
You should look for your own
organs before you do that!
Although elementary,
that mystery is unsolved.
♪
(horns honking)
Well, hello there, pretty boy.
Yo, gimme some money!
Hey, punk, are you
listening to us?
I'm talking to you!
I just asked if you were
listening to us or not!
♪
This is pretty nice
not to have someone
storm into the kitchen yelling‐‐
Let's eat!
It's nice and quiet.
(humming)
Sunako.
Sunako, did you hear me?
It looks like you've
got an extra serving.
Geez, where do you
think he went off to?
Something might've happened
at his parents' house.
You don't know of
anything, Sunako?
Uh, well, uh...
It's the truth.
You hate being around
me too, don't you?
‐Um, Sunako?
‐Who, me?
I don't know, why would I
know, I don't know anything!
I know nothing whatsoever,
please believe me!
I really don't know
anything at all!
Didn't I just tell you
I don't know anything?
‐Why don't we just watch TV?
‐Good idea.
You've just gotta watch
TV when you eat, you know?
‐What's the matter, Sunako?
‐It's nothing.
Extremely beautiful
single young man,
and this young man is also
a big eater who managed to eat
more than four pounds of
curry after polishing‐‐
‐Beautiful?
‐Big eater?
Here's some footage of
the beautiful young man
we have been talking about.
‐Look, it's Kyohei!
(screaming)
Please pay attention,
this is how a lady
should eat four pounds of curry.
Wrong, no lady eats that much!
♪
He's been going from place
to place breaking all kinds
of eating records
wherever he goes!
Excuse me, would you please
turn and face the camera?
(chewing noisily)
It would appear this young
man doesn't like cameras.
However, we remain
determined to keep following
this beautiful big eater.
‐We've been worried for nothing.
‐He's been on some eating tour?
Well, in any case, Sunako,
it looks like you aren't going
to have to save any
more food for Kyohei.
He has no idea what he
put us through, darn it!
Man, I can't believe
he's been traveling
with his winnings from
those eating contests!
Traveling alone, huh, must
be nice to be so carefree.
Don't you think so, Sunako?
(sighing)
Sunako?
‐Well.
‐Well, what?
♪
You know, no one is ever born
with the face that they want.
Oh, I agree, dear.
I don't wanna be around a
radiant creature like you,
so just let me leave!
You sure said some
harsh things to him.
Josephine.
(sighing)
I for one do not think
you were wrong, Sunako.
I think the blame lies
with the radiant creature.
It is his fault
for being radiant.
Does that make it okay for you
to say whatever you want to him?
‐I was‐‐
‐The truth is,
Sunako has always
been the first to say
she does not like
her radiant creatures.
That's right!
‐Is that so?
‐Yes it is.
That's your problem,
hollow stomach.
What did you say, boney butt?
Now, now, guys, can't
we all just get along?
You're quite right, Akira.
But Sunako did nothing wrong.
You're right too, Hiroshi.
That's right, Hiroshi's right!
‐Honey?
‐That's right, dear.
But you know what, Sunako, I
don't understand how you could
do that to someone who's been
rejected by his own parents.
See what I mean?
(yelling)
Hey there, Sunako, I‐‐
Wow, she looks more
depressed than usual.
I agree, hey, what...
‐What did you say?
‐You shut up!
‐You're mounted on a stand!
‐She is right!
‐You shouldn't discriminate.
‐Everyone stop it!
‐I can hear things!
‐I don't!
‐I refuse to hear!
‐Sunako.
What happened between
you and Kyohei?
‐Happened?
‐Sunako!
Ahhh, it was no
big deal, honestly!
Ahhh, no, Hiroshi, Hiroshi, no!
♪ Pain, pain, go away ♪
So tell us what happened.
Ordinarily you'd be pretty
happy with Kyohei not around.
Something's just not right here.
I'm so happy, happy, happy!
Happy!
She's creeping me out again!
Hey, this is serious.
Apparently, the beautiful
big eater everyone's
been talking about
is in a biker gang!
‐What the hell?
‐Let's go, guys.
‐Right, you got it, boss!
Yes, sir, Mr. Takano, yes, sir!
Can that actually be Kyohei?
What do they mean
by free‐wheeling?
And what's even more surprising
is that this biker gang
is very actively involved
in community service.
They are?
Mr. Takano told us
we should do this.
He also told us we should take
care of our parents and stuff.
Right, Mr. Takano?
Hang on, where'd he go?
He stole the TV camera
and took off running.
Mr. Takano, what a
beautiful biker kid he is.
Please contact our TV station
once you get home, okay?
That ain't never gonna
happen, 'cause he said
that he ain't got
no home to go to.
(shouting)
♪
(panting)
No home to go to?
‐What the heck's that mean?
(stammering)
‐That's what?
I don't wanna be around a
radiant creature like you,
so please just let me leave!
How mean, did you
really say such a thing?
I'll bet that really
hurt Kyohei a lot!
It's true that you two always
seemed like you could talk
to each other about anything and
say whatever was on your minds.
However, wasn't it bad timing
to say something like that?
(grunting)
‐Sunako.
‐What is it?
Is there anything else to say?
I know you blame me for this.
‐I don't like ugly girls.
‐Ahhh!
(explosive noises)
♪
(screaming)
T‐T‐T‐Takenaga!
That's what he said to
you, isn't it, Sunako?
You said those taboo
words so casually.
♪
Maybe the words, "I don't
wanna be around you,"
should've been
off limits for Kyohei.
You're aware of how many
bad experiences he's had
in the past simply
because of his appearance.
No matter what you might think,
he was comfortable enough
around you to say
whatever he wanted.
‐That's how much he trusted you.
‐Trusted me?
And because Kyohei did
feel that way about you,
I think your words are even
more wounding to him than when
that guy you had a crush on
said those hurtful words to you.
That's all I have to say.
♪
But I...
Get out of my room,
you radiant creature!
Come on, just let me
borrow your Jason DVD.
‐No!
‐It's so dark in here
I can't find anything!
Get out!
Who would ever come visit
your room, you dumb loser!
Well look, it's
fried shrimp today.
Whoa, tasty, it's just
so good Sunako Nakahara!
Hey, those are mine!
You really like
that, huh, Kyohei?
These are Nakahara's
famous fried shrimp.
Once you have 'em,
you'll never go back
to restaurant fried shrimp.
♪
It's the truth, you hate being
around me too, don't you?
But I don't know what
I'm supposed to do.
♪
What if there was a way
of making a radiant creature
no longer radiant?
A way to make him not radiant?
‐Do you think I went overboard?
‐For sure.
You went way over
the line in there.
But the thing is‐‐
hey, what's that sound?
(growling)
(indistinct shouting)
Radiant creature!
Ahhh!
♪
What's the matter, kitten?
(yelling)
(panting)
‐She's thinking.
‐About weird stuff again.
That was very
radiant, but still,
he's even more radiant!
(whimpering)
♪
(together)
Sunako!
He's so radiant, no matter what,
I can't control the radiance.
I have no idea what
she wants to do.
She's too creepy.
Huh, that's my phone.
Um, hello?
It's Auntie!
But that's impossible.
We're just not any good at that
kind of stuff, and you know it.
‐What's wrong?
‐She said there's going to be
a TV interview at a restaurant
where we used to work,
so she wants us to be there,
and it's going to be
a live broadcast.
‐What?
‐Please, allow me.
‐Huh?
‐Auntie?
Yes, we would like to
accept your request.
‐Takenaga!
‐Calm down.
‐Are you plotting something?
‐Sunako, you get some rest
in a place with
no sunlight, okay?
A place with no sunlight.
♪
Well, I've heard it all!
When you're going to
appear on television‐‐
What kind of clothes
should you wear?
How about something
sparkly so I stand out?
Wrong, although,
I wanna stand out too!
Sparkly clothes reflect too
much light, and similarly,
clothes with detailed patterns
are too busy for on camera.
Those things are disturbing
to viewers' eyes.
‐Is that so?
‐TV adds a couple pounds
to your appearance, so try to
avoid especially loud colors
in your clothing and makeup.
Hey, what's Noi doing
in this segment anyway?
Here I am!
One more time!
Check out those waiters.
I wonder if they're from
the entertainment business.
‐They're super hot.
‐Well, you see,
I decided that I really ought
to be standing next to you
if you were going
to be on television.
‐Oh, I see.
‐Now that it's come to this
I'm going to help
you guys out, so relax,
Noi will take care of you.
Since we're here,
let's make this flashy.
‐This Takenaga is so cool.
‐Thanks.
‐Go ahead, you two, go on.
Excuse me, but will everybody
please get ready now?
I'm counting on you,
don't let me down.
(together)
Right!
♪
Thank you for helping
me clean up around here,
young man, I appreciate it.
Now have some tea before you go.
Thanks very much.
♪
Now, where should I go to next?
Welcome to a special
gourmet report.
Today we're here at a very
popular French eatery in Tokyo,
Restaurant Noble,
thanks for joining us.
‐I used to work part‐time there.
‐What?
♪
Ahhh!
Wow, we have three
very good‐looking guys
and a lovely young lady here.
A restaurant is all about
the taste, so let's sample
their cuisine now, shall we?
‐May I help you?
‐Huh, Kyohei?
Please select something to
drink from this wine list.
‐Hurry up and‐‐
‐And I brought you an ash tray.
‐Come?
‐Brought you water!
Home?
What're they doing?
Hey, what's with
this blinding light?
‐What is it?
‐What's that?
‐Is that‐‐
‐It's shaking!
(heavy footsteps)
♪
You're incredibly
bright, Sunako!
What's going on, some special
entertainment or what?
‐No, no!
‐Stop the camera!
Oh crap, I forgot this
was a live broadcast.
♪
Camera guy, the mic's
picking up your voice.
(shouting)
Listen, radiant creature.
♪
Please come back home.
Come back for this
primo fried shrimp!
(screaming)
Oh, what the‐‐ahhh!
Ouch!
♪
‐Sunako!
What did you do this for?
♪
I thought that‐‐
I thought I would
be able to see him
if I made myself very bright.
I thought he wouldn't
look so radiant if I
became the light myself.
But Sunako, that's not‐‐
I understand where
you're coming from.
But I'm afraid you were‐‐
‐Absolutely wrong.
Wrong!
Where's our beloved Kyohei‐ne?
Don't try to pretend
you don't know‐ne.
Who the hell are you?
What's with the
arm‐flapping freaks?
Arm‐flapping freaks,
how insulting‐ne!
You don't know anything‐ne!
We four are the
Goth‐Loli sisters.
We are Goth‐Goth,
Loli‐Loli, but‐‐
We are no arm‐flapping
freaks‐ne.
Absolutely no freaking way‐ne.
♪
‐Goth‐Goth.
‐Loli‐Loli.
‐Goth‐Goth!
‐Loli‐Loli!
What's the deal
with these freaks?
‐Huh?
‐You're back!
‐It's Kyohei‐ne!
‐All of you.
‐Where are you going,
Mr. Takano, I'll
give you a ride.
‐Come here and hop on‐ne.
I, uh...
♪
If you are in need of a fast
ride, then come with us‐ne.
‐Hop on‐ne, yeah!
Vroom, vroom, vroom,
vroom, vroom‐ne!
Goth‐Loli‐ne!
God, finally.
‐I'll take that ride now.
‐Yes, sir.
Now this fabulous dish
is known as Sunako's Tears.
(indistinct remarks)
♪
So please come on by
and play with us
at this lovely restaurant, mwah.
‐Oh wow, he's so cute!
‐We'll come play with you.
No, don't come here to play,
come here to eat our food!
Come enjoy our food, please!
‐We'll see you next week!
The whole thing is
completely ruined!
(horns honking)
Ah, what now?
♪
‐Beautiful Biker Gang?
‐Kyohei!
♪
(stammering)
Hey, that guy's the legendary
beautiful big eater!
‐This is a scoop, a big scoop!
‐What?
‐Roll the damn camera!
‐It is rolling!
♪
I, uh...
Oh, well, so I wanted to‐‐
These are really good.
♪
I‐‐agh!
(screaming)
♪
Just what I expect
from you, Miss Nakahara.
‐What an amazing jet.
‐It's also super long.
By the way, I think
it's a fantastic idea
that you're going to have
a party to celebrate
your wedding anniversary
with your late husband.
‐Thank you very much.
‐You're welcome.
How many years has it been
since you were married?
It's been ten years
since that day.
That's right, and
it's been nine years
since he passed away, hasn't it?
‐Yes, time sure flies.
‐He's positively sinful
for leaving a beautiful
woman like you behind.
Oh, I wish I could
let him hear that.
I think that you're
more beautiful
than a banana.
‐Banana?
‐Speaking of beautiful,
I understand that
you're planning
to introduce us to your niece.
Well then, I look forward to it.
I'm sure she's a lovely
lady just like you.
Of course she is.
We should be arriving
in Japan very soon now.
I should go ahead
and check the weather.
LCD, fabulous!
More of our special
gourmet report.
‐Special gourmet report?
‐No, no more, no more!
Blagh!
Oh, it's a holy fountain!
(coughing)
It's so good, Nakahara's
famous fried shrimp rocks!
(chuckling)
(groaning)
(electricity buzzing)
♪
What the hell is this?
‐You sure about this?
‐I don't remember
ever telling you I didn't
want you to come home.
But you said you didn't
wanna be around me, remember?
You said you were gonna make
a deluxe dinner tonight, right?
‐I didn't say that!
‐I want steak,
‐and blowfish sashimi!
‐Come on, stop it!
(laughing)
They're getting
along so well now.
You're making me jealous!
♪
This is so incredibly painful.
What on earth have
those horrible beasts
done to my darling Sunako?
♪
Those four!
Those little punks,
you just wait!
You're toast!
(screaming)
♪
I have some unfortunate news,
it's the final episode!
This is so sad, ain't it, honey?
‐Quite right, dear.
‐What's gonna happen?
‐Everyone's gonna die!
‐Don't kill us!
Kneel down on the ground
and beg for mercy!
‐Auntie!
‐Final episode:
‐The Road to Womanhood!
‐I really like you!
‐Could that be?
‐Love!