I'm Akira, ha ha!
My name's Josephine.
And I'm the
new‐comer, George.
Wow, we knew it
was gonna be weird!
Hey, where's Hiroshi?
He's still recuperating
from the beating he took
in the last episode.
Beatin'?
Doesn't that sound
nice, honey?
It sure does, dear.
Boys and girls,
try to hold back
when you beat something up.
Oh, but to tell
you the truth,
it actually felt good.
Isn't that sick, honey?
Indubitably, dear.
So is everybody into
that kind of stuff?!
♪
Thank you for flying with us.
We hope to see you...
(shrieks)
♪
(passengers whimpering)
My Sunako.
I'm certain that
Sunako is getting
closer and closer
to becoming a lady.
There is nothing
to worry about‐‐nothing!
After all, she's been
living with a bunch
of cute, dazzling boys.
Dazzling!
(haughty laugh)
Did you just say "dazzling"?
In order to become
a good woman,
she must experience
great love with a good man.
Ah, love!
Are you listening to me?
Hello?
Are you still there?
It smells like
something's burning.
(crowd exclaims)
♪
Love...
Love, she said!
♪
(sighs)
(together)
More tea, please.
I'll go make
a fresh pot.
This is peaceful.
Like that incident the
other day never happened.
I wish it would be
like this every day.
Agreed.
(together)
We love peace!
(laughing)
(rustling)
What is it, Yuki?
Something's there.
It sure seems familiar.
I think I remember
a similar scene
at the beginning.
At the beginning?
(shrieks)
Oh, my, Yuki,
what's wrong?
This scene definitely
does seem familiar.
♪
(lightning crashes)
I have a feeling
something incredible
is about to appear!
(roars)
(screams)
It's Frankenstein!
No, it's a minotaur.
A giant monster!
Everyone, calm down,
it's human!
It might not look it,
but it's still
a human, I think.
(screaming)
Are you the one?
Ranmaru, don't tell me
you were messing around
with a Yakuza's wife!
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb,
it's obvious he is
in that kind of business!
He's gonna make you
pay for what you did.
But that happened
a year ago.
So you really
did do that?
Uh, sir, um...
who are you?
Sunako, are you all right?
(whimpers)
♪
Hey, Sunako!
Sunako!
(screams)
♪
Sunako!
Sunako, I've
missed you so much!
Gee, we didn't have
any idea you were
Sunako's dad.
I don't know
what to say.
We thought you were
in a certain kind
of business,
you know what I mean.
(growls)
That was quite rude, Kyohei!
Kyohei!
Hello, hello, hello!
‐Goth‐Goth.
‐Loli‐Loli‐Goth.
Loli‐Loli.
Goth‐Goth Loli‐Loli,
Goth‐Loli‐Loli.
What bizarre creatures.
So that we may
confirm the rumors
of Sunako Nakahara
and Kyohei being
lovey dovey with each other...
We shall infiltrate
the Nakahara residence...
And we'll use this item
which we put so much
effort into creating.
This item is our
pièce de résistance.
The deadly voodoo doll.
Love, love, love!
Love, love, nay, love!
Payback, Goth‐Goth.
Counterattack, Loli‐Loli.
That lovey dovey
story you just mentioned...
Huh?
(shrieks)
Tell me.
Tell me more about it!
(screaming)
Love.
Love, nay.
Love!
Love, nay!
She's been lovey
dovey with this guy?!
Apologize to him, Kyohei.
Just do it!
What am I supposed
to apologize to him about?
Drink this and
then go home, okay?
Go home?
Sunako, that's not
very nice to your dad.
You don't have
to be so rude.
It's not rude, in the least.
♪
(shrieking)
Sunako.
Wah, I'm really scared!
So, do you think
Sunako would be
just like that
if she were a guy?
Well, thank goodness
she's a girl.
Hooray for girls!
♪
Sunako.
Hey, Sunako,
I'm talking to you.
Hey, Sunako!
Oh, so this is
your room, huh?
(screams)
You may be my dad,
but I won't forgive you
if you enter my room!
(cries)
What's that?
What's going on?
‐Huh?
‐What the hell?
(screaming)
What's the matter, sir?
What's going on?
There, there,
please don't cry, sir.
I can't believe this
is how she treats me
after I came all the way
from Africa just to see her.
Africa?
No way.
Do you suppose Sunako
actually hates her dad?
He came so far to see her.
He just showed up
with no warning.
That sure sounds like
he's Auntie's brother.
Well, at least he didn't
drop out of the sky.
You know, he
resembles Sunako.
He's scary like her.
So, do you think
it's possible
that Sunako is being
cautious because she's afraid
Auntie will find
out she still hasn't
become a lady?
‐Oh.
‐To protect us?
Not possible!
(together)
We know that.
But you could let us
think it for a second.
All right.
So...
Guess I'll go
take a bath.
Hey, did you notice
that Sunako's dad
was staring at Kyohei?
That's Kyohei's fault
for being so rude to him.
♪
Whoa, that was a big one.
Sweet‐‐huh?
Hey, I already told you
I was going to take
a bath first!
(screams)
Uh, can I help...
you?
♪
Okay, it's nice to know
you have a good physique.
Huh, huh, huh?
Wash, wash, washing.
Hey, Sunako, are you
100% sure that guy
is really your father?
Uh‐huh.
If so, that means
you were born after
your mother and father
did that thing to make
a baby, right?
Uh, sure.
But the way you put it makes
it sound pretty explicit!
Oh, yeah.
I guess so.
Huh?
(groans)
Don't tell me‐‐
Tell you...?
He goes both ways?
What on earth are
you talking about?
I guess I don't
really know exactly.
Please do me a favor then.
Do not allow my father
to enter my room under
any circumstances, understand?
Uh‐huh.
(rooster crows)
(gong ringing)
‐Earthquake!
‐For goodness sake!
‐Jailbreak?
‐Dad's awake.
(together)
Oh, it's that again.
The Road to Womanhood.
When you wake up
in the morning‐‐
What's the first
thing you do?
(yawns)
Better go take
care of my business.
Wrong!
Ladies don't read
newspapers in the bathroom.
When you wake up,
drink a cup of
mineral water before
you do anything else.
Your body loses water
while you're asleep.
It's necessary to
replenish your system
through rehydration.
This flushes out the
accumulated gastric fluids
in your system, giving you
a fresh start at breakfast.
Discussing gastric
fluid with ladies?
Oh, well.
(gong ringing)
Why the hell is that
damn thing still ringing?!
Shut up!
Huh?
(screams)
Her dad's in my bedroom!
What on earth could
be going on so early
in the morning?
Run two laps
around the house,
then ten laps
of squat hopping,
then sit ups,
push ups,
and back
strengthening exercises.
A hundred times each.
Do what?
What are you talking about?
I'm in my pajamas.
Hmm.
Too hard?
(groans)
(yawns)
What was all
that noise about?
Amazing.
Totally amazing.
What's up?
Uh...what's he doing?
(shouting)
(yawn)
I'm still sleepy.
This is not cool.
Getting insufficient rest
will make my skin look dull.
Sunako, will you
make some coffee?
Just enough
for us three.
Fifty‐six,
fifty‐seven,
fifty‐eight,
fifty‐nine.
Brother!
How did this happen?
♪
I wonder how come
her dad's so hung up
on Kyohei.
Who knows why.
Apparently he heard
a rumor that Kyohei
and Sunako had been lovey
dovey with each other.
I get it.
That makes sense now.
Well then, your dad's probably
just worried about you.
Not his business.
Don't be that way.
(gasping)
Wa...ter.
Ah, you really scared me!
Holy cow, you look
awful, Kyohei.
(together)
Kyohei!
Take your clothes off
before you catch a cold!
Wipe your sweat,
wipe your sweat!
Water, rehydrate.
Here, please have
some coffee.
Thanks, guys,
you saved me.
Life is precious,
I'm telling you.
(whimpers)
You know, your dad
really does love you a lot.
Do something about it.
Not possible.
Not possible, my ass!
I'm gonna die here, you fool!
He'll actually kill me!
Well, unlike me, my dad
is extremely hardheaded.
Once he snaps,
there's nothing
that can stop him
or change his mind.
That is like you!
No, I'm not like
that at all.
(together)
Yes, you are!
Sunako, could you
make some hot tea for‐‐
(growls)
♪
(shouts)
You filthy bastard!
How dare you do something
like that to my daughter!
In front of her own father!
He is just like Sunako!
This isn't what
it looks like.
It's not like that.
No excuses.
Hah.
What do you want?
Please, don't interrupt.
(screams)
(together)
Kyohei, you idiot.
Blah!
♪
(alarm pinging)
(kettle whistles)
No mercy.
♪
Showdown.
Go outside.
(laughs)
Interesting.
Yeah, I'll take
you on, old man.
Why does it have
to turn out this way?
Why does Kyohei have
compatibility issues
with the Nakahara family?
♪
(wind blowing)
Come on, Sunako,
just tell them
they don't
really have to fight.
I don't care who's
wrong or right!
I don't really want
to fight no more,
but this is the time
for letting go!
You know...
my father once
defeated a bear
using only his two hands.
(together)
Huh?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I get it, it's just
some kind of expression
to describe how
strong he is, right?
I remember this
gang boss using
a similar name.
XXX The Bear Killer,
it's just a fluff!
But it's true.
(together)
Huh?
He really did...do it.
(together)
Hey, Kyohei!
Don't fight him,
he's a bear killer!
Let's go.
Now!
♪
Ah, you filthy scum!
Damn, he's strong.
(chuckles)
(grunting)
Huh?
(groans)
What the...
Are you okay, sir?
♪
Ba‐‐ba‐‐
Ba?
My back!
(groans)
(cries)
Up you go.
I'm not looking for any
pity from a guy like you.
Put me down!
(shouts)
(together)
Poor guy.
You shouldn't push
yourself so hard.
You're too old.
(groans)
You sure do look
out of place
in this room,
you know that?
Shut up.
If it's really bad,
we'll go to the hospital.
For now, I'll put
heating pads on your back,
so get undressed.
♪
Holy crap,
what is that?
What the hell did that?!
A bear.
Huh?
Hm?
♪
She hasn't changed at all.
Sunako really is
an adorable little girl.
I can't think of any
other kid who's as lovely
as she is.
(crying)
What's wrong, Sunako?
Why are you crying?
Oh, Daddy, Mr. Bear
promised me that
he was gonna be my friend.
But now Mr. Bear's
making a scary face at me.
(cries)
I understand.
So, my Sunako wants to be
friends with Mr. Bear?
Hmm?
♪
(growls)
Uh‐uh, are you sure you
wanna be friends with that?
Mr. Bear!
(giggles)
Look out!
♪
(groans)
Sunako.
I won't let you
lay a finger
on my darling Sunako!
(roars)
♪
Daddy, Daddy!
Oh, Daddy!
(groans)
Daddy, Daddy,
you're bleeding!
I'm all right, Sunako.
You know that Daddy
would do anything
for you, sweetie.
Just take a look.
(soft growl)
(shriek of joy)
Mr. Bear!
Thank you, Daddy!
I love you!
Daddy!
(laughs)
For you, Sunako,
Daddy will do anything.
(stifles cries)
Around the time she
was in middle school,
she started to stay in her room
most of the time by herself,
but then it got worse.
Sunako stopped speaking
to me altogether,
and she wouldn't
even let me go
inside her room anymore.
That's probably because‐‐
‐I'm very sorry.
‐Huh?
It's true that I got
worried when I heard
a rumor about
the two of you.
But to be perfectly honest,
I may simply have
been jealous of you
because you're the one who gets
to be around her all the time.
♪
To a young girl like her,
I realize a father's
probably nothing more
than a nagging annoyance,
but if I'd have known
what I feel this way,
I would've taken her with
me when I was transferred
instead of leaving her here
in Japan at my sister's house.
♪
Oh, hey, Kyohei.
So, how's her dad?
Looked like he was
in a lot of pain.
Yeah, but he seems okay now.
All right, time
to do some laundry.
Hang on, you.
Do you hate your father?
No, not at all.
Ah, that's not how
it looks to me.
(sighs)
(knock on door)
Huh?
Sunako?
(strains)
♪
Sunako?
How nice, thank you.
Hey, Dad, you know that
I don't hate you, right?
Huh?
But please, don't
come into my room, okay?
♪
Oh...
(sighs)
♪
Hey...
why is it...
why am I not able
to communicate
with him better?
Huh, Hiroshi?
♪
Oh, yeah!
(grunting)
♪
There it is!
(shouts)
(crash)
‐What's that?
‐Huh?
Huh?
Sunako!
Hey, old man, your back!
Suna...ko!
♪
Huh?
(groans)
What in the world
are you doing in there?
That was pretty loud, Sunako.
What's up?
(groans)
♪
(together)
Huh?
Didn't I say not
to push yourself
too hard, old man?!
He did anyway.
He must've really
pushed himself.
Well, it's like this.
Medical mannequins,
skeletons, dead bodies,
splattered blood,
brains, internal organs,
occult stories,
splatter flicks,
horror movies.
So, what exactly are
you getting at, Sunako?
All this scary stuff
that's in here...
he hates it so much
that it makes him faint.
(groaning)
That's precisely why
I told him not to come
into my room.
(door bell rings)
Come on, Dad.
That's probably Mom
coming to pick you up.
(together)
Huh?
Mom?
♪
(nervous chuckle)
I wonder...
♪
Everyone, I'm really sorry.
I know he caused
you a lot of trouble.
(together)
No trouble at all!
She's smokin' hot.
Honey, I just heard
from your sister.
You heard the word "love"
and you thought it
was necessary to fly
all the way to
Japan to confirm it?
Uh, love?
I can't believe
Sunako's in that room!
Oh, no, Sunako.
Did you really let
your Dad see your room?
Mm‐hmm.
I've been keeping it
secret from him
for so long,
but oh well.
Huh?
Now, listen, son.
"Listen, son"?
He said "son."
He sure did.
Just please...
make sure my daughter's
a decent girl, promise?
Stop butting into
other people's business.
You stay out of it.
She's interested
in that stuff.
(whimpers)
But...but...
Bye, Sunako.
I'll visit with
you longer next time.
Okay.
Well, goodbye,
you beautiful boys!
(together)
Goodbye!
Please come back
again soon!
All right, then.
Come on, honey,
time to go!
(together)
Gah!
Young man,
I'm counting on you!
On you!
Awesome.
They sure are
unique parents.
And there's certainly
no doubt that Sunako's
their daughter.
So, that means...
Sunako's going to look like
her mom when she grows up.
Is that all you
care about, Ranmaru?
Hmm.
♪
What a nice family.
Yeah.
Sunako, what are your
mother's measurements?
And what is her favorite food?
Knock it off already.
(chuckles)
Hmph.
♪
But if your mother
is that gorgeous,
then when you grow up,
you'll also be‐‐
Why do you sound like
you're bidding on her?
Well, I'm just‐‐
I have my heart
set on Noi.
Did you say something?
(laughs)
My love!
♪
It looks like people from
some kind of sect are coming!
I'm scared of
people like that!
I don't like those
kind of people!
What's "some kind of sect"?
‐We can't tell you.
‐I'm being kidnapped.
Save me, please rescue me
from the people of this sect!
What's "some sect"?
(together)
We can't tell you!
It's grown up business.
I'm asking you what
kind of sect it is!
Next time on The Wallflower,
"A Prince in Sheep's Clothing."
‐A sheep prince?
‐Mine isn't wearing any clothes.