Ho, ho, Hiroshi here,
I'm looking forward
to Christmas more
than anyone else.
Does that bother you?
The year's almost over but
it doesn't seem like Sunako's
going to become a lady
any time soon, does it?
Why don't we write a letter
to Santa Claus about it?
Santa, if I'm asking for
anything it's gonna be
for money, enough money
to cover the full rent.
Someone doesn't know
how to dream big.
All right then, what
would you ask Santa for?
Internal organs.
I don't think he could
give you those!
♪
♪ Don we now our gay apparel ♪
♪ Fa la la la la, la la la la ♪
You're pretty easily
amused, Yuki.
‐But it is a lot of fun.
‐What?
How could this be fun when the
wicked lord of dread is coming?
The wicked lord of dread?
The one who comes to visit
at Christmas is Santa Claus.
Yes, except in our case,
Santa is a very scary person
who only comes here
to collect the rent.
‐I see.
‐Yeah, so how the hell can you
be over here just humming
away with doom approaching?
But the thing is, Christmas Day
has a very special meaning
for the four of us, remember?
Huh, how's that?
‐Sunako.
‐Huh?
That's not Christmassy at all!
So Yuki, what did you mean by
Christmas being special for you?
Well, it was just one year ago.
I came here to live in this
boarding house by myself,
'cause my dad had to move away
from the city for his work.
I was really excited, but I was
a little nervous about it too.
Hello, I'm Yukinojo Toyama.
It's very nice to meet you.
♪
‐I'm the landlady.
‐You're the landlady?
‐What's wrong?
‐Well, when I hear landlady,
‐I picture someone like‐‐
‐Hey there!
Curfew's nine o'clock,
and when you come to dinner
ya gotta eat up
within half an hour.
Oh man, now I'm seeing things.
What's that sparkling?
♪
Hello.
I'm Ranmaru Morii.
Holy cow, he's dressed
like a prince or something.
Hello, nice to meet
you, you're cute.
Hey, wait a minute,
I'm a guy, I'm a guy!
‐A guy?
‐Ahhh!
Starting today you boys are
going to be living together,
so try to get along.
I'm expecting one more,
the same age as you,
so you should all
get along just fine.
But of course, and naturally,
that other person
‐is a young lady, correct?
‐What?
We're housemates
and the same age?
What's with the very
Japanese atmosphere?
Good afternoon.
My name is Takenaga Oda.
It's a pleasure to meet you,
and I shall forever
be in your debt, madam.
Well, I certainly
appreciate your courtesy.
Whoa, another good‐looking guy?
All right, now that everyone
has arrived, why don't you boys
go ahead and take your
things up to your rooms,
and then we'll all
have dinner together.
I understand our
landlady's a widow.
‐What?
‐Lucky for me.
Huh, huh, huh, huh?
(wailing)
Wow, awesome!
Starting today,
this is my new room!
Whoopee!
I get to live in this
huge amazing mansion
with a beautiful landlady
and cool housemates!
It feels like I've become part
of a completely different world!
All right, I'll do my best!
(screaming)
There was no Sunako in
the house back then, so‐‐
Wrong, you had no lady!
♪
So, how do you like it?
‐It all tastes incredible!
‐Let me guess, this cuisine is‐‐
Catered by the famous
French restaurant, Noble,
if my palate does
not deceive me.
‐Would you care for seconds?
‐Yes, please.
All right, but be sure
to leave enough room
for some dessert, okay?
Dessert, huh?
But wouldn't you like to
offer me a different dessert?
You know I'll eat it
all up, don't you?
‐It's been a while.
‐Was that just my imagination?
I could've sworn you
said something to me!
Let's just all try to enjoy the
meal together, right, Auntie?
What?
Surely you didn't
call me Auntie?
I'm so sorry, I really am!
‐Would you please let go of me?
‐I know, perhaps you're in need
of some speech lessons
or something like that!
‐Stop them, please!
‐What for?
(indistinct arguing)
‐Please, do something!
‐No way, why should I?
Why should you, the four of us
are gonna be living together
so why can't we just
get along and have fun?
(ticking)
(laughing)
What's so darn funny?
That was so cute, and
it really hit the spot.
And besides, having fun
isn't part of my plans,
and neither are you.
♪
Well, in any case...
(sweeping)
Those two boys were sent here
because their families
wanted them to be normal.
Ranmaru's been used to having
things his way all his life,
while the restrictions of
Takenaga's family's traditions
and upbringing have left him
far removed from the real world.
In the end, it really
isn't their fault,
but I must admit
they're a little twisted.
Look, I understand
those two are known
for some pretty bad behavior,
so please just try your best
to be patient with them, okay?
♪
Ranmaru!
So, Ranmaru, listen, I was‐‐ahh!
Who is this, he's such a cutie.
Wanna hang out
with us, little boy?
‐I am not a little boy!
‐Did you need something?
You have to come help me
clean in the dining room.
It's your fault it's
such a mess in there
so you need to
pitch in with this!
Hm, I haven't ever actually
cleaned anything before,
so I'll let you handle it.
Now where were we, ladies?
Fine!
So basically, I need you
to help me clean up.
Sorry, I'm busy.
♪
I'll bet you've never
cleaned anything
before either, have you?
I'm sorry, but have
we met before?
We certainly have, our first
meeting was at a party,
and the second time
we met each other
was at the Kendo championship.
Do you remember that?
I won the tournament.
The only reason I learned Kendo
is because I was forced to
as heir to the Oda family line.
But you did win
flower arrangement.
Yes I did, and you
would be Morii,
as in the Morii
family hotel group.
‐Hm, one in the same.
‐Wow, they're rich.
Real life richy‐riches.
Both of them are
crazy rich, unlike me.
I'm just a plain old
ordinary commoner!
(screaming)
I think I'll ask Miss Nakahara
to install a lock on my door.
And I'll need a TV in my room.
‐And a shower.
‐No way.
If I put locks on the doors
Takenaga would bolt himself in,
and Ranmaru would be
bringing girls over.
That kind of selfishness
will not be tolerated
‐in this household.
‐It's only natural to lock
oneself in when strangers
constantly surround one.
He's right, kids need
their privacy too, ya know?
Oh, so you want to be treated
like a kid when it's convenient.
Well, you have some nerve,
mister, there'll be no dinner
until you two clean
up the dining room.
And if you have
anything to say to me,
then say it after you've
cleaned everything up.
I don't have time for this crap.
Yes, we're obviously going
to have to hire a housekeeper.
You can't do that, that's
totally gonna make her more‐‐
Why hello there, how'd
you like to take me out
to an Italian restaurant
for dinner tonight?
All right, I'm going
back to my room.
Someone call up a catering
service for dinner.
‐Hey wait!
‐Ah!
‐What're you doing?
‐Not my face!
I hate you two, you
bookworm, you playboy!
You don't care about
other people's feelings!
I hate stupid rich kids,
I hate you, I hate you!
‐Okay by me!
‐Ahhh!
♪
Don't be so cocky!
Well don't you
underestimate playboys!
I mean, honestly,
fighting is so ridiculous.
Shut up!
(indistinct arguing)
(laughing)
You guys were such
morons, what idiots!
Oh sure, as if you're in any
position to talk about us.
How's that, I've always
been exactly the same.
‐No, I remember.
‐Uh‐huh.
Back then you were like a
walking broad‐bladed knife.
Broad‐bladed knife?
(giggling)
‐What now?
‐A knife, a broad‐bladed knife?
That's right.
Later on that day...
(thunder rumbling)
I'm home‐‐ahh, what is this?
Um, welcome back?
In any case, I have
some big news for you.
I just found something
very interesting outside.
Yoo‐hoo, come on in!
♪
Hold on, you mean you found him?
This is Kyohei Takano, I've
decided to let him stay here,
and that's all there is to it.
Okay, am I going
to be sold to them
or am I going to be sold
along with them perhaps?
Why would you think I'm
that kind of person?
Yeah, I don't buy or sell!
Hm, so where on earth
did you find such a thing?
I found him huddled in a
cardboard box out in the rain,
‐just like a little puppy dog.
‐That's a lie!
Takenaga, she just
made that up, right?
There's too much drama in here.
That calm attitude of yours
really pisses me off!
♪
Uh, Kyohei?
You've got a visitor already.
It's the manager from
your part‐time job.
Well, you just left the store
so suddenly without any warning,
so I got worried about you.
(screaming)
♪
Don't ever show your
face in here again.
(rain pattering)
That was really...
♪
‐Really what?
‐Nothing.
If you have something to
say to me, just say it.
Hm, I think you're
afraid of something.
(grumbling)
♪
‐Hey, Auntie.
‐Auntie?
Send them all away no
matter who comes to visit,
and I'm not taking any calls.
♪
I understand that
you've been followed,
but maybe you're also
the cause of it.
Kyohei, look this way!
What you did was
unjustifiable self‐defense!
Oh Kyohei, I know
you're inside the house.
Please, come out!
Kyohei!
Your mother is so tired.
♪
(phone ringing)
Hello, Kyohei Takano
is not here right now.
(phone ringing)
Hello, Kyohei Takano
is not here right now.
He's not here, geez Louise!
‐Where should I put this stack?
‐Huh, what's that?
Kyohei's part of today's mail.
Ew, that's blood!
How about this bulky envelope?
♪
That's human hair!
"I hope you will think of this
memento as me and cherish it."
My.
Why are you crying?
Because this is just terrible,
how can he feel safe anywhere
where they do this
to him all the time?
(doorbell ringing)
Be quiet out there!
‐Are you Kyohei's friend?
‐Yeah, I'm his friend.
Well, I'm his girlfriend so you
better let me see him right now!
‐I'm his girlfriend!
‐Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What makes you so
sure he's even here?
‐I hired a private detective.
‐Police would be guarding him
on his way to and from school,
and whenever I went to his house
his mother always turned me
away, it's just not fair!
Wait, why on earth do they
do such things anyway?
Because there's always
some stupid woman
‐who's trying to kidnap him.
‐That's right,
there was, so you can butt out!
Things are really
terrible for Kyohei!
He's sexually harassed,
even at work!
Harassed, sexually?
(indistinct shouting)
♪
Damn it.
I, Yukinojo Toyama,
swear to protect Kyohei
in the name of my grandmother!
Thanks, but no thanks.
You might stop being stubborn
and accept his offer.
Listen up, Kyohei Takano
is not in this house!
Attention everyone!
Kyohei Takano is
not inside this house!
Oh ladies, I have
finally located
our beautiful Kyohei, nay.
And now we're going on a rescue!
‐Our beloved prince!
‐Locked in the castle!
(together)
It's so romantic!
Get away from the windows,
they're coming!
(screaming)
♪
Isn't there any way we can
get those girls to go away?
Who knows, all they really care
about is their own fixations.
For that matter, I imagine
any cute guy will do.
Right, it's your turn
to be on stage now!
With that silky hair and
flawlessly smooth skin of yours,
your incredible sexy body
overflowing with pheromones,
you're the only one who can
satisfy them, so go do it!
Well, if you insist I guess
I simply have no choice.
Hey, someone's coming out now!
But that's definitely
not Kyohei.
Well, hello there,
beautiful young ladies.
Whoa, hold on a second.
(together)
He's so handsome!
I'll hang out with
you if that's okay.
(shrill screaming)
Wait, everyone calm
down, wait your turn!
Heavens, cease this
violence at once.
(growling)
I'm Kyohei's fiancée.
Now ladies, I'd like to ask you
to leave this place immediately.
‐That's a guy.
‐I'm busted!
That's okay, this actually
works for us too, nay.
Let's take him home!
(cheering)
They took my clothes!
(crying)
Looks like I have no choice.
What's that?
Something a lot faster than
punching them out individually.
Toss it quick, okay?
(shouting)
♪
(laughing)
That was hilarious!
You're so pathetic.
Can't you see the kid's
trying to protect you?
Just what is your damage?
Could the truth be that
you're simply unable
to do anything by yourself?
Or is that you just lash out
at anyone, even those girls,
like you did last night.
♪
If that's the case, I'm sure
you can find some place
to stay that's more
to your liking.
So why don't you go there?
Miss Nakahara,
this is the police!
There's been a report that
Kyohei Takano has been kidnapped
and confined here
at your residence!
Oh, this is great, so now
we're criminals, huh?
It'll be fine, really.
You must open the
door immediately!
Miss Nakahara,
this is the police!
‐We mean it!
‐Someone's coming out!
♪
Kyohei's coming outside,
it's really him!
What's wrong, what's happening?
Kyohei!
♪
‐Poor Kyohei!
‐Aw, look at him!
Please lift your head!
Oh Kyohei, please
stop doing that!
Oh no, this is not
like him at all!
Please stand up now, sir.
Is it true that
you've been kidnapped
and confined here
against your will?
‐Go check inside the house.
‐Right.
(indistinct conversations)
Hold it, who said you
could go in this house?
(gasping and shouting)
♪
No one goes in there,
I won't allow it.
‐What the hell?
‐Kyohei, Kyohei!
We'll have to force
our way in, sir!
Hold it right there!
You've got some nerve having
a party outside my house.
She's the kidnapper, arrest her!
I have a phone call
for you, detective.
Huh, what the‐‐huh,
who the hell is this?
‐Superintendent General?
‐Ah!
What, you say you're
the one who requested
that Kyohei Takano be
taken into her care?
Officers and ladies, please
listen very carefully.
These boys are important
to me and they belong here.
Therefore if one of you
ever harms a single hair
on their heads I'll be sure
to send you straight to hell!
You heard her, you girls
get out of here right now!
(screaming)
Well, if you'll
excuse us now, ma'am.
‐Let's go!
‐Yes, sir!
Yo.
♪
On your hands and
knees, how cool?
‐Shut up.
‐Oh, by the way,
I've told all your parents
that they don't have
to support you
financially anymore.
‐Huh?
‐Mine too?
Of course, I'm not
one to discriminate.
From now on, you boys are
responsible for everything,
including paying your own share
of the rent, among other things.
(together)
What?
And that, dear boys, is my
Christmas present to you all!
What kind of gift is that?
(laughing)
♪
I see, I had no idea
that's what happened.
Uh‐huh, and that's why Christmas
Day is so important to me.
That was the very first time
we all laughed together.
Okay, enough with all
the emotional stuff.
So was that your first time
cross‐dressing, Miss Yuki?
Hey, you know I don't
like doing that!
I only did it because I didn't
have any other choice!
Huh, look, in the
snow, is that‐‐
‐Most likely.
‐She's here.
Merry Christmas!
(together)
Merry Christmas to you!
Hey, Takenaga, how much
do you have right now?
That's a question
to ask Ranmaru.
‐Hey, Yuki.
‐I don't have it!
‐How about Kyohei?
‐Takenaga, how much do you have?
Merry Christmas!
What happened to the
broad‐bladed knife?
♪
A lady needs a personal color
to express her individuality.
To make sure it's a bright
one I would take some
of those red
polka‐dot mushrooms.
‐Sunako's being weird!
‐Someone stop her!
Next time on The Wallflower:
Oui, Monsieur.
I love shiitake‐‐
I mean, mushrooms!
I like how you just blushed!