(indistinct chattering)
Funimation.
Hello, Hiroshi here.
I'm not sure why,
but lately, I get the feeling
that college girls
understand me
much better than
housewives do.
Anyway, here's what
happened in the last episode.
Oh, what's going on here?
I don't know, I saw
Ranmaru running away,
then I heard someone scream!
The manager is dead!
The manager, th‐‐that's
Sayuri's husband, right?
Wait, are you saying
that Ranmaru might have‐‐
(laughing)
What are you laughing about?
That's not polite, Sunako.
Neither are you!
Oh well.
♪
(indistinct chattering)
All right, move along, folks.
Nothing to see here.
It's a real murder case.
(gasping)
Yes, it's a murder case!
Was he stabbed to
death or choked?
Or maybe he was beaten.
Oh, wait, he could
have been poisoned!
Oh, maybe his head was
smashed with an ax.
Oh, oh, maybe they chopped
off his head with a hatchet!
Ah!
What's with that grin?
Were you thinking
about something
completely unrelated
to what's going on here?
Me, why would I be thinking
about anything inappropriate?
A person died here,
you inhuman wretch!
Excuse me, I'd like to ask you
a few questions, all right?
‐Sure.
‐A real detective.
I need to know
where each of you was
when the incident took place.
A real investigation!
Yes, sir, the three of us
were in the karaoke room
on the first floor.
‐Mmhmm.
‐I see.
A real alibi!
How about you?
I was in the back room
with that thing.
That thing?
‐Hm?
‐It's real!
I see.
That thing, huh?
Detective!
Oh, I saw him!
I saw the culprit,
the murderer!
A real witness,
a real witness!
Calm down, try to
compose yourself.
He had such a beautiful face,
and he was tall,
sexy, with silky hair.
Uh, ma'am,
we're not interested
in hearing what your
ideal man would be like.
That's not what
I'm talking about!
I told you I saw him!
She saw it!
A real serving lady saw it!
Hey, do you guys
think it's possible
she's talking about Ranmaru?
Now that you mention it,
where the hell is he anyway?
I don't know, but maybe
we better go look for him.
...patient stabilized!
We're taking him
to the hospital!
‐Clear the way!
‐Hang in there, honey.
Please hang on.
Oh, I can't believe they
were able to save him.
Hey!
(siren wailing)
Thank goodness, I'm so glad
the boss is still alive.
Me too, but I can't
believe you were screaming
like he was actually dead.
My bad.
Oh, my beautiful dead
body isn't really dead!
Well, too bad for you.
You guys are so rude.
(crying)
So what did you observe
at the crime scene?
His blood was splattered
all over in there.
And have you found
the weapon yet?
Yeah, a real weapon!
Don't you know when to stop?
So the blood on
the weapon was...
Well, the blood would have
been the victim's, of course.
And how much blood
loss was there?
A six‐tatami room was
covered with blood.
I see, and what
type of weapon?
Like I said before,
a broad‐bladed kitchen knife.
(laughing)
Huh?
Stop interfering!
The weapon was,
the weapon was‐‐
it was a broad‐bladed
kitchen knife!
(laughing)
As a lady, I'd use my
broad‐bladed kitchen knife
to cut the throats‐‐
You ain't no lady, toots!
(gong resonating)
I want to see it!
For once in my life
I want to see a murder
scene covered in blood!
I'll see it with
my own two eyes.
Yoo‐hoo, wait for me, guys!
You can't come in here.
Authorized personnel only.
(groaning)
I think I'll go try
the other side.
Sorry, miss, you'll
have to stay back.
(grunting)
I can't accept this,
I am unhappy.
This is‐‐ooh, sorry.
(gasping)
Oh, blood!
(laughing)
How lovely!
This is so
incredibly wonderful!
(grunting)
Damn, you realize that
since you've seen this
I can't let you live.
Don't take it personally.
You‐‐ah!
Oh, that guy just
fell out of the sky!
I'm sorry, I didn't
mean to do that.
It just happened before I‐‐
Ah, a ghost!
No, no, she's with us.
She's human, I think.
Um, sorry, sorry,
I'm the one who did that.
I didn't mean to throw him,
but I did, and I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry, mister,
and I apologize to you
from the bottom of my heart,
so will you please just do
me this one little favor?
Now what's she babbling about?
Please listen to me!
Would you mind
letting me have
these bloody
clothes of yours?
(screaming)
I'm a chef.
I got blood on me when I
was cutting up some tuna!
‐You gotta believe me!
‐Shut your rice hole.
You're going downtown.
My bloody clothes.
This isn't funny.
(sighing)
My lovely, bloody,
wretchedly stained clothes.
You did a good job,
you know that?
You're so cool, Sunako.
So it was her.
Hm.
♪
(roaring)
Sayuri.
This must be difficult.
Are you all right?
That detective asked me
lots of questions.
Really?
I was wondering about
last night, about what‐‐
I'm sorry.
You must be tired.
It's so awful that you
had to deal with this.
It really is so unfortunate.
Uh‐‐
(sighing)
♪
Oh, that's a relief
for right now, huh?
Yeah, the owner ended up
surviving the attack
and the police caught
the guy who did it,
so that's case closed, right?
As illogical as it seems,
that's basically correct.
I have to admit
that after I saw
Ranmaru running last night,
I was starting to wonder
about what was going on here.
Yes, about that.
Ah, holy crap!
Watch how you're sitting!
Yeah, there are
plenty of reasons
we should be banned from
broadcast TV already.
...the most awful thing.
I'm gonna be sick.
Now that's just rude.
So, anyway, what were
you just saying?
Oh, I almost forgot.
Remember how I told you
Sayuri asked me to
meet her last night?
I'll be getting off shortly,
so wait for me
in the back room.
(sighing)
Oh, Sayuri.
So, naturally, I was
busy making preparations
so I could go to work
when she was finished
for the evening.
‐Preparations?
‐Well, of course, silly.
I had to go into town to
get some roses and wine
to set the mood.
I really look up to you
when it comes to
that kind of stuff.
Of course, anyway, I took
the tools of my trade
and went over to her room
when it was almost time
for her to get off
work, however...
Ah!
Yeah, the whole
dead body thing.
He's not dead.
Oh, yeah!
Well, to make a
long story short,
I got a little freaked out
and took off running.
I have to tell you,
after living with Sunako,
I thought I'd gotten
used to the scary stuff,
but the real
thing is no joke.
Hold on, she asked
you to meet her?
You don't mean that‐‐
Ranmaru, were you‐‐
(cracking)
♪
Hey, what's that noise?
Uh...
(screaming)
(gong resonating)
How to keep peep on
the men's bath correctly.
Wrong!
Ladies don't peep on
men's baths, period.
(gong resonating)
Uh...
(screaming)
Hey, no screaming,
collapsing,
and nose bleeding
on our side.
And speaking of
screaming at an onsen,
I seem to recall you
trying to shoot some video
at the bath yesterday.
Where did that camera go?
My camera?
Actually, Sunako asked me
if she could borrow it.
Sunako did?
This is the hotel where
the murder took place.
No, let me rephrase that.
It's where the real murder
that should have
happened took place.
And these are the real
rocks and the real trees
located outside the
real murder hotel.
Hm.
Did you hear that the weapon
was a broad‐bladed
kitchen knife?
What if it's the one that the
head chef was always using?
It's so disturbing.
But they said they haven't
been able to find it yet.
How disturbing!
Attention, studio audience!
Sunako Nakahara is going
to find the real weapon!
Like, what do you
want to drink?
I'd like a soda.
Okay.
Huh?
(laughs)
(screaming)
(sighing)
All that commotion this
morning has worn me out.
Do you want to lay down?
Why don't I set up
a futon for you?
(gasping)
(screaming)
Oh, so busy.
So busy, oh.
♪
(screaming)
Please, please!
What seems to be the
problem, everyone?
In there, I saw it!
I saw a ghost!
I saw it too!
It was the real thing‐‐
First, there was a
murder investigation,
and now there's a ghost,
give me a break, will ya?
But that's not possible.
I saw it too, ma'am!
I'm telling you, it was real!
We want our money back!
We're going home!
So far, the weapon has
yet to be discovered,
but I'll be sure
to update you
as soon as new information
becomes available.
‐Aha.
‐Huh?
Ah!
Why should I be surprised?
Well, did you want something?
I don't want to say
the wrong thing
since she's
Ranmaru's girl, but...
You'd better watch
out for Sayuri.
Ah?
♪
And could you please stop
being so freaky already?
(sighing)
Hm.
Oh.
Ooh.
Ha!
(screaming and laughing)
Finally!
I actually discovered
a real pool of blood!
Ah?
Oh!
It looks like this was
the site of a major brawl.
It's difficult to believe
that a simple
broad‐bladed kitchen knife
is responsible for
this amount of blood.
This carnage seems
to be more indicative
of an ax or a hatchet.
Maybe he could've
even used a chainsaw!
Whatever it is, I know
I'm going to take it
back home with me and
display it on the shelf
next to where I keep my
boiled and pickled frog!
Excuse me, what are
you doing over here?
Well, I just found
some bloodstains
and thought that
they might help me find
the weapon used
in the assault.
‐Bloodstains?
‐Uh‐huh, right here.
(gasping)
So you're searching
for the weapon, are you?
Uh‐huh!
Oh, my goodness.
I would never dream of letting
one of my valued guests
attempt something like
that all by herself.
Please, won't you allow
me to assist you?
Oh, would you really?
Sure, hm.
As a matter of fact,
we happen to have a
large storage facility
where someone could
have hid something.
Awesome!
‐Can you show me?
‐Of course.
‐Shall we look there now?
‐Sounds good to me.
(laughing)
♪
Mwah‐ha‐ha‐ha‐ha.
I don't know.
You think we ought
to go home now?
Go home?
That's a good idea,
especially after what happened
with Ranmaru's girlfriend's
husband and everything.
Yeah, when you consider that
our room was on the house.
Staying here does
feel a bit odd.
Oh well, what can we do?
I suppose that only
makes sense, doesn't it?
♪
What's the matter, Noi?
Did you really want to
stay for dinner that much?
I can buy you a delicious
bento to make up for it.
Thank you very much, Yuki.
(crying)
Ah!
You were right!
This is the
absolute perfect place
for someone to hide
a bloody weapon!
You really think so?
Uh‐huh, you bet!
So why are you
looking for it?
Because it's fun.
You're a strange girl.
But you know what?
You're not going to find
that weapon in here.
Ah?
But, earlier, you said that‐‐
Earlier I was lying.
What‐‐lying?
No honor among killers.
(laughing)
(screaming and grunting)
This is how a lady
strangles someone properly.
First, you take a length
of non‐stretch hemp rope,
‐and then you...
‐Wrong!
Don't tell people
how to do that!
(gong resonating)
(crying)
Why are you doing this?
What an incredibly stupid
and clueless girl you are.
The police have already
confiscated the weapon.
I can't believe the plan
that I worked so hard on
was ruined by you.
First, that little puppy
I planted at the scene
took off running, and
then the police caught
the idiot I brought in
for the knife work.
Are you saying that you're
the real criminal mastermind?
That's correct, and
I'll tell you this now
since you're
already done for.
After having my pathetic,
incompetent husband
taken care of, I was
planning to collect
his life insurance policy
and get rid of
this miserable hotel
so I could travel abroad.
But now everything
I've worked so hard on
is totally ruined thanks to
you and your meddling friends.
I can't believe it.
I'm actually going to witness
the end of the real culprit!
From the moment I
first set eyes on you,
I never liked you at all.
Being constantly surrounded
by all those beautiful boys
in spite of your ugly face!
(screaming)
For an ugly girl
who looks like you,
a grudge is much more
suitable than a hot spring!
(laughing)
An ugly girl should
just rot to death
like she's supposed to!
Ugly face, ugly, ugly, ugly!
(laughing)
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry for being ugly.
That certainly is a shame.
Some of the other guests are
leaving early today as well.
Excuse me, miss, but
do you have any idea
what they're
burning over there?
Huh?
I wonder what that could be.
Hm, I seem to
remember something
about burning about the
unused things in storage.
But they're not supposed
to do that until next week.
Oh, that's right.
Miss Sayuri must
be burning garbage
or something like that.
I saw her walking towards
the shed not long ago.
Oh, that's right!
One of our guests
was with her too.
That scary girl.
(gasping)
(crackling)
Ugly, ugly, ugly, ugly!
(laughing)
(coughing)
Rot to death like
an ugly girl should!
An ugly girl should
just rot to death
like she's supposed to!
(laughing)
Ugly, ugly, ugly!
(laughs)
Ugly, ugly, ugly.
(gasping)
(grunting)
♪
You were here.
Damn.
(screaming)
There's no time for this!
Ah.
Let's get out of
here, you idiot!
(grunting)
Didn't I say you needed to
watch out for that woman?
Uh‐huh.
(indistinct chattering)
♪
It's Kyohei.
Sunako!
♪
I can't believe it!
One of our guests
was actually in there!
Oh, no!
This is just horrible.
I want you to go inside
and call for an
ambulance right away.
You're not fooling
anyone, hot kimono.
You're the one
behind all this.
Kyohei.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I don't deserve to
be treated this way.
You know what happened
to my poor dear husband
only this morning.
After having my pathetic,
incompetent husband
taken care of, I was
planning to collect
his life insurance policy
and get rid of
this miserable hotel
so I could travel abroad.
I never liked you at all.
Being constantly surrounded
by all those beautiful boys
in spite of your ugly face!
Did she really say "ugly"?
What did she just call her?
(laughing)
An ugly girl should
just rot to death
like she's supposed to!
(grunting)
So you got the head chef
to kill your husband,
and you tricked Ranmaru
into coming to see you
so you'd have a patsy.
You thought you had
everything covered, didn't you?
That's absurd.
It's not true, is it, Sayuri?
You told me that you
really wanted to see me.
You said you'd feel better
if you could see my face.
Shut up, you useless
little bastard!
No, no way.
♪
Just what kind of
woman are you?
(laughs)
Why, was I wrong?
Someone like her could
never understand.
My beauty has
always enabled me
to get anything I've
ever wanted in my life.
Besides, those men
should have been happy
even if they were fooled
because at least they got
to believe they had me
if only for a moment.
You bitch.
Huh?
It's still winter, but
those are cherry blossoms.
The shell of a saint
harbors a she‐demon inside,
a creature of greed
who stomps on the
kindness of others.
Wait, you're‐‐
But, you see, I know
what a woman like you
should really be
called, and that's...
...ugly.
Oh!
Sunako, you are so awesome!
Aren't you one to talk?
That's quite an accusation
coming from a girl that
no man would ever want.
But that's not true.
♪
In fact, the two of us
have kissed each other.
We've kissed big‐time.
‐Sayuri.
‐Oh, what now?
It seems no matter what
awful things you say
I just can't bring
myself to hate you.
I still think
you're a good woman,
but even so,
I will never tolerate
you calling Sunako "ugly."
Do I make myself
perfectly clear?
(crying)
♪
(siren wailing)
Poor Ranmaru.
♪
(siren wailing)
Sunako, how long are you
planning to be frozen?
It must have been
such a shock for her
that now she's mentally
blocking it out.
You mean the kiss?
Uh‐huh.
And if you want, I could
kiss you again too.
Ah!
(laughing)
Oh, no, Sunako!
Oh, Sunako!
Oh, no, she's not breathing!
Somebody call an ambulance!
Thanks for doing
the hard part, Sunako.
(horn blaring)
We welcome you all back, nay.
Salutations!
Goodbye again, nay!
♪
I shouldn't have
gone to karaoke.
We never got to take a stroll
together wearing our yukatas.
I can't stand it.
You have to make her
shut up somehow.
Hey, Noi.
Uh‐huh?
(gasping)
What was that noise just now?
Whoa, look at Noi!
She's passed out!
Takenaga, what the heck
did you just do to her?
N‐‐nothing.
(giggling)
♪
We do not give up, woo‐woo!
Peking Duck.
No kissing words!
‐French fries?
‐That counts!
They're neck and neck.
No, no!
‐Smack in the middle.
‐Stop it!
That intern gave
her boss lip.
Enough with the kissing!
Isn't mono called
the "kissing disease"?
Oh, stop it!
Next on The Wallflower,
I'm up to my
kisser with books.
I told you not to
say it, you weasel!
(laughing)