It happened two years ago.
How I wish I could
burn it from my memory.
I've always had a
big crush on you.
Since my first year, actually.
♪
Listen, kid...
I hate ugly girls.
(whimpering)
♪
Wahoo!
You bastard!
♪
Hey, keep it down, Kyohei!
‐What's up?
‐"What's up?"
What's up with you?
Why are you acting so
calm when today's the day?
It is the day that girl's
supposed to come, isn't it?
Oh, yeah!
Was that today?
♪
Now, there's a little thing I
need to ask of you gentlemen.
"Gentlemen"‐‐why so formal?
Actually, it's because
I've decided to have my niece
move into this mansion.
‐A girl, huh?
‐Lucky us!
‐And then?
‐And then I'll be expecting
you gentlemen to
train her to be a lady
‐of the respectable kind.
‐Oh, this is bullpucky!
Why should we train your niece?
Because if you boys do turn
my niece Sunako into a lady,
there'll be a reward.
All your living expenses
here will be free!
‐Free?
‐Free‐‐for real?
Please say you're
not yankin' our‐‐
Hold that thought.
If you fail, your
rent will triple.
What do you say?
(indistinct yelling)
We accept your challenge.
I'm so relieved.
Now I can take off
without worries!
Huh‐‐take off?
Can we get a bit more
clarification on that?
♪
Oh, sweet adventure!
A woman can't live in
a place without love!
That wasn't an answer.
I'm off around the world
on a quest for the one love
great enough to fill
this heaving bosom!
You boys take care of the rest!
Adios, amigos!
(laughing)
She's something else.
Yeah, and you know
what that something is?
Oh, don't worry, it's covered!
Have you forgotten we have
the great Ranmaru on our side!
Exactly.
That sweet flower of womanhood.
Once we've welcomed her to
our modestly endowed abode
in the proper fashion, what
could possibly go amiss?
I don't know, how
about food, dammit?
‐Um, food?
‐Yeah,
like what if this Sunako
girl can't even cook?
In case you morons
haven't noticed,
we haven't had anything edible
to eat since Auntie left!
I'm frickin' ravenous starving!
So that's why you've
been so bad tempered.
‐Pathetic.
‐It is not pathetic!
Food is the basis
for all human life!
‐Sure, sure.
‐Stop condescending me!
I'll "sure, sure" your ass!
‐There he goes again.
‐No kidding!
I think I'm going
to gather a few roses
before our princess arrives.
‐Will you join me, Yuki?
‐Sure!
Huh?
‐Hey, something's in there!
‐Really?
Oh, it's probably
just a cat or something.
That's true.
Here, pussy, pussy!
(meowing)
What's wrong?
Hey, Yuki?
Oh, enough already!
(yelling)
♪
‐Ah, it's a ghost!
Wait, calm down,
it's a human, I think.
‐You're sure?
‐You know,
she does look kinda human.
‐It does, but the more I look‐‐
‐The less human she looks!
Look at that unkempt
and overgrown hair!
And that 500 yen sweatshirt
with mysterious
stains is bad enough,
but add that
amoeba‐patterned skirt
and shoes that
don't even deserve
to be called sneakers
and‐‐can it be?
I don't wanna say it,
but is it possible
your name is Sunako?
(grunting and gasping)
How can it be?
How can this be the
girl we bet our rent on?
Welcome, Miss Sunako.
Please let me show
you to your room.
It's right this way.
♪
Uh, excuse me.
Your stuff got here earlier,
so I put it in your room.
(grunting)
What's with the hair?
How can you stand having
those bangs in your eyes?
Cut them off!
(whimpering)
(yelling)
‐That's enough!
‐Say what?
It's none of your
business anyway,
so just shut up
and leave me alone!
(whimpering)
Did you hear that?
‐What's her damn problem?
‐Stop it‐‐behave yourself!
‐I'm scared, I'm scared!
‐How can Auntie's niece
be so abnormal?
(indistinct shouting)
♪
If I were to cut my bangs, I‐‐
(rooster crowing)
Oh, my God!
Are they celebrities
or something?
(laughing)
Okay, so what do we do now?
We certainly didn't
sign up for that.
I don't like horror stuff.
That hell spawn princess
is too much to handle
even for me.
I mean, if she
were a normal girl,
she'd eventually open
up with a little charm,
but I hate having to put on a
fake smile more than anything!
And when I think about
having to do it with her,
‐I get all‐‐
‐Wait.
When have you done this before?
Well, we've gotta try!
Otherwise, our rent will‐‐
(sighing)
Excuse me‐‐may I
take your order?
What a normal girl!
(screaming)
How about me, how about me?
I'm totally normal!
I won a normal girl contest!
Okay, enough of that scene.
♪
Hmm‐‐farewell, my
sweet young kittens.
♪
(screaming)
You're such a man slut.
What's wrong with wanting
a little take out to go?
(screaming)
I don't wanna do this.
Why, Hiroshi, why?
Why do I have to live here?
Oh, Sunako?
I thought you might be hungry.
We brought some yummy take out!
Would you dine with us?
♪
(door slamming)
That was scary‐‐I
think I wet myself!
Hey, Kyohei, get
your butt over here!
If you want her to cook,
come ask her yourself!
It's too scary!
Your acting cute is scarier!
Damn.
♪
I hate things that are bright!
(panting)
The darkness is
my only sanctuary!
(crying)
Has anyone had a brainstorm yet?
No, my prospects
are all crumbling.
‐Your prospects?
‐Yeah.
Like in one scenario, I'd
help her unpack and notice
that a lot of her
things are pink.
"Sunako, I see you
like the color pink."
And then she'd say, "What
girl doesn't like pink?"
Then I'd say, "I'd love
to turn your skin pink!"
"Oh, Ranmaru!" "Oh, Sunako!"
Then we'd reach for each other,
gaze into each
other's eyes and say‐‐
‐That's way too long.
‐Too long?
And where's Kyohei, by the way?
‐Who knows?
‐Can it be too long?
(shower hissing)
(ticking)
(crashing and gasping)
Hey!
♪
Now see here.
(screaming)
That's Sunako!
‐Miss Sunako!
‐Go away!
‐Leave me alone!
‐What just happened?
Kyohei, did you just
hit her, you brute?
(yelling)
What in the hell
is wrong with you?
One look at me and
you start screaming?
Ordering me to leave?
Can't you see I'm just
trying to be nice to you
in exchange for the free rent?
‐The rent?
‐Uh‐oh, he told her!
That's right, free rent.
Why else would anyone
in their right mind
try to talk to you?
Why else would anyone wanna
be in this scary ass room?
What scary ass room?
♪
(screaming)
(whimpering)
(yelling)
Hey, wait a second!
‐Are you afraid of men?
‐Huh?
Did you have a bad
experience or something?
He is half naked.
Now we understand‐‐
I'm so sorry, Sunako,
but we'll try to be
more careful from now on!
‐You're wrong!
‐Huh?
‐That's not why‐‐just leave!
‐No, wait.
‐We were just trying to help!
‐Well, you'd best
get out of here already!
♪
Okay, fine.
‐If you hate us that much.
‐Just do whatever you want!
(crying)
♪
I can't believe a man
that beautiful actually exists.
How am I supposed to
live with those beautiful,
shiny creatures?
Run‐‐hurry up and run!
♪
You idiot!
I can't believe you
told her about the rent.
Yeah, and if she tells Auntie,
we'll be getting
triple rent for sure!
Yeah, well, you guys
snapped on her, too!
Only because she's
so unreasonable.
I'm still in a state of shock
over learning that there
are girls in this world
‐who aren't princesses.
‐So what now?
Are we stuck paying
the rent or what?
‐Hmm.
Huh?
‐Kyohei?
‐What's up?
It's nothing.
Nothing.
♪
(crickets chirping)
(sighing)
If I can't stay in town
or live in the sewers,
I'll just sleep here.
‐Hey, girly!
‐Wanna party with us?
♪
(indistinct yelling)
‐Ghost!
‐Huh‐‐a ghost?
‐Yeah, right!
‐It's for real!
She's right there, just look!
Why?
Why is there no
place in this world
for an ugly girl?
(indistinct shouting)
I wanna see the ghost!
Wait up, little ghost girl!
(yelling)
♪
Look, she fell!
Are you gonna help her?
Hell no‐‐not unless she's cute!
Did the poor little ghost
girl fall down and go boom?
(laughing)
♪
Why‐‐why is this
happening to me?
Why?
♪
If this is how it will be,
I wanna melt into the darkness.
(gasping)
(panting)
Geez, what kind of lame‐brained
idiot runs away from home
just because somebody
told her off a little?
(panting)
Please don't worry
about the rent!
(screaming)
(laughing)
Oh, for crying out loud.
Come on, we need to go.
Don't you know girls
shouldn't be out by
themselves this late?
Are they shooting a
movie or something?
‐They're weird.
‐Go home!
There's nothing to see here!
And don't say anything, okay?
‐Huh?
‐To the others, I mean,
about me coming after you.
Who knows what they'd
say if they found out.
♪
(yelling and shattering)
Are you sure you can cook?
Can't we just go out and eat?
With whose money, you moron?
We can't even pay the rent!
Let's just call some girls.
No way, they're way too noisy.
Just shut up!
I said I'd cook, dammit!
It's just dinner,
so what's the big‐‐
(screaming)
Someone seems to be making a
big deal over "just dinner."
Well, this was already
bound to be a disaster
given that we don't even
know if Sunako can cook.
Don't speak of that anymore!
Since it's come to this,
we'll have to live with the idea
of paying rent and
cooking for ourselves!
I guess you're right.
After all, how can
we ever establish
a line of
communication with someone
who holes up in her room
and won't even talk to us?
Yeah, Auntie sure set us up!
Kyohei, I'll help out,
so hurry and cut the vegetables!
Cut your own damn‐‐
(screaming)
I thought you might be hungry.
Did you have a bad experience?
We'll try to be more
careful from now on.
Don't you know girls
shouldn't be out by
themselves this late?
(yelling)
You‐‐what are you doing here?
You, sit.
♪
Shudder.
Who do you think's gonna
get eviscerated first?
Kyohei‐‐he'll
definitely be the first.
♪
(laughing)
(screaming)
For the love of God,
someone call 911!
(crying)
Huh?
(scraping)
‐Huh?
♪
(gulping)
(yelling)
Oh, my God, this is so good!
Unbelievably awesome!
(indistinct yelling)
Look, I'm sorry
about earlier, okay?
(gasping)
♪
‐Bye.
‐No, wait!
I do believe you
just lit my fire.
You're a good cook and don't
look so bad from the back.
This could have some potential.
Aw, man, for a minute
I thought you meant
the oven was on fire again.
‐You go, player!
‐He's working it!
Now let's see what's under
that bird's nest, ma cherie.
‐No, anything but that!
‐Wait just a second!
You got to scream
when you saw my face,
and now you don't
wanna show us yours?
Sorry, it's ponytail time!
‐Does this seem sadistic?
‐In spades!
You mean he's a spadist?
I showed you mine,
you show me yours!
Bind up those natty bangs,
and show me how ugly you are!
Will you shut up and
stop moving, dammit?
In a strange way,
it's kinda erotic.
And yet not erotic at all!
I haven't even seen my
own face in two years!
Stop doing this!
Why can't you stop struggling?
‐Turn left!
‐Fuck you!
(yelling)
So‐‐sorry!
(coughing)
(gasping)
♪
(crying)
Oh, no, they saw it!
They saw my ugly face!
♪
What the hell‐‐it's normal.
‐How boring.
‐We're sorry, Sunako.
I think we all got a
little carried away.
Don't cry, Sunako.
‐You're really very cute!
‐Don't say anything!
(gasping)
Those...those are their faces!
‐Sunako!
(whimpering)
♪
(screaming)
She's got a unibrow!
Her lips were cracked!
And her skin‐‐awful!
How could a girl
be okay with that?
‐It's not okay at all!
‐That treacherous flower!
It fooled us.
But you know, it's no fun
unless she's a little
uglier than that.
Man, was that all?
That was nothing‐‐nothing!
And actually, don't you think
her skin problems
are manageable?
Oh, leave it to moi!
♪
The Road to Womanhood!
For the heartbreak of
dry skin and psoriasis...
Take a lavish amount
of skin toner in hand
and apply it to your skin,
gently patting it on.
Repeat the moisturizing
process several times
until your skin
feels fully hydrated,
then apply another
layer of toner
and gently massage
it into your pores.
(yelling)
Scrubbing too hard will
aggravate the condition!
So always use a
nonabrasive cream or lotion!
Hey, do you guys
actually do that?
‐Do we do what?
The lights‐‐I'm melting!
♪
(phone ringing)
Telephone.
Too much work to
pick this up, huh?
Well, hello there‐‐ah, Auntie!
‐Auntie!
Well, hello, Auntie dear.
(yelling)
(breathing heavily)
You wanna know
how Sunako's doing?
She's changing into
a wonderful lady!
‐What?
Sure, just leave it to‐‐ahh!
She looks even more
suspicious than before!
It's as if she's detached
herself from all humanity!
We're supposed to
make that into a lady?
‐Impossible!
♪
‐And yet‐‐
‐There it is.
The rent!
‐We have no choice!
We will change Sunako
into the perfect lady!
We'll do it or die trying!
(slurping and laughing)
‐I love slimy seaweed tea!
‐We've gotta do it!
We've got to!
♪
What do we do, what do we do?
Sunako's about to make
her high school debut!
‐Sunako, let's got to school!
‐No!
‐Sunako, put your uniform on!
‐No, no!
‐Sunako, pull up your bangs!
‐No, no, no!
Geez, do you think you're
in a "no" play or something?
‐No!
‐Next time,
Pull Down the Iron Curtain!
‐Be sure to watch it!
‐No, don't look!