Hiroshi here.
The production of my new show,
Hiroshi the Wallflower,
has kept me so busy I could
even use the cat's help.
What can a cat do?
And that show's not
on the TV schedule.
We've got to achieve
our primary objective
which means we've got to ‐‐
Turn Sunako into
a respectable lady.
Yeah, we definitely need to get
this rent problem off our backs.
Aah, thank goodness, it looks
like we made it to air on time.
You really didn't have
to make that happen!
♪
(evil cackling)
Here, young lady,
eat this mushroom.
The mushroom she offered
the princess looked
so irresistibly delicious that
the princess couldn't help
eating it without ever
giving it a second thought.
But then, all of a sudden,
her round, rosy cheeks turned
blue, and her once glossy red
lips looked pale and lifeless.
What?!
(screaming)
Um, I, uh, brought mushrooms!
You saw!
(screaming)
I'm so sorry!
Oh, I forgot all about them!
Mushrooms, mushrooms, mushrooms!
Once again, I apologize!
(grumbling)
♪
Yes, ah ha ha ha!
(maniacal laughing)
You shouldn't go in
her room right now.
Yeah, I think she's
gotten a hold of some
banned video from somewhere.
But I heard her laughing,
so I thought‐‐so I thought
she was in a good mood.
(crying)
Honestly, Yuki,
you're such an idiot.
Haven't you figured out by now
that Sunako laughs at things
normal people
would be afraid of?
What about dinner?
They were eating
other's‐‐aaah!!
Anyway, where's dinner?
The video did look scary,
but Sunako looked even scarier.
Why does she have
to be like that?
You mean, why can't
she be normal?
"Normal" meaning girls who
say, "My favorite hobby is
baking cookies," correct?
Yeah, that's right.
Where's dinner?
So what do you think
about something like this?
Every morning the sunlight
is coming through the window
and you see her smile.
Good morning, sleepyhead.
She stands in the backyard
in her frilly, white apron
where she hangs the
laundry out to dry.
How are you doing,
little birdies?
She pours me a cup of tea while
I relax out on the terrace.
I just made some
homemade pudding.
Would you like to have some?
Oh, I'd like some sweet
pudding, but I'd rather taste
those much sweeter
lips of yours.
Oh!
Please stop it, Ranmaru,
the birdie is watching us!
‐So what?
‐No, we shouldn't!
Come on!
Silly bunny, we shouldn't.
Who cares about silly bunnies?
I'm after dinner!
Sometimes I'm more scared of
Ranmaru than I am of Kyohei.
You're so cold.
Hey, Yuki, I was wondering,
what on Earth made you want
to go into Sunako's
room in the first place?
Oh, I almost forgot.
Earlier today, I got a whole
bunch of free mushrooms.
So I was gonna ask her to use
them for our dinner tonight.
Oh, mushrooms, huh?
Hmm, I had a delicious
French dish just last week
that used mushrooms.
All right, I'm
going to prepare it.
Did you hear what he said, Miss?
He was talking about
some French dish.
Pretty snooty for a
high school kid, huh?
Amen to that, brother.
So what was it, was
it really that good?
Make it, make it now,
right now, quickly, instantly!
Oui, monsieur.
Yeah, ha ha!
(growling)
(eating noises)
Hee, hee, hee.
Sunako, I made dinner tonight,
and I brought some for you.
I'll leave it here,
so eat some, okay?
Eat it, eat it with me,
ha ha ha ha, yeah!
Oh.
‐Uh?
I did my best on this, you guys.
Hmm.
(biting noise)
Hey, this stuff actually tastes
okay, believe it or not.
Well, Ranmaru made it, so
let's all try to enjoy it.
Thank you for the food!
By the way, Yuki, I meant
to ask, exactly who gave you
all these mushrooms anyway?
Well, what happened was I was
taking a walk this afternoon.
(chanting)
Hmm?
♪
Okay, now that we're drenched
in platinum‐colored sweat
from that vigorous
dancing, let us bring
forth the treasured items we
obtained before Christmas!
Behold, the maid
and mushroom's day!
Ah ha ha!
Just by making a meal of
these succulent mushrooms‐‐
The four of us will be able to
instantly metamorph our bodies‐‐
(laughing)
Into the kind of girls that
men have fantasies about.
With power granted from hell!
‐Now we shall eat‐‐
‐some mushrooms, and head‐‐
‐to the castle today‐‐
‐where our princes await us‐‐
‐neh.
(growling)
‐Huh?
(barking)
(screaming)
Hey, you forgot your mushrooms!
‐Oh, you can have them, neh!
And that's exactly
what happened.
(retching noises)
We need to purge!
Jam your finger down
your throat and throw up!
Hey, you're wasting them!
You'd better barf, too!
Why would you feed us
such freaky‐ass things?
But those girls gave
them to me for free!
(barfing noises)
Thank you, I'm done.
‐Sunako, did you‐‐
‐eat it‐‐
‐... all?
Yeah, shouldn't I have?
(moaning)
(screaming)
Sunako!
She's still breathing for now!
Snap out of it, Nakahara!
You'd better live, dammit!
♪
(gasping)
Ah, what the...?
Huh?
♪
Ah!
Uh?
Ah, this is so embarrassing!
Would you please let me down?
Ah!
Ow.
‐No way!
Was I really that heavy?
I'm terribly sorry about that.
Please, forgive me, achoo!
That's creepy.
Although she is kind
of cute that way.
‐Hey, Ranmaru.
‐Huh?
About those mushrooms,
was this one of them?
Oh, yeah, yeah, it was.
I remember it because
that part was pink.
Ah, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
‐Dude, chill!
Just hold on there.
Huh, Ranmaru?
♪
Ah?
(screaming)
So cheesy!
It's burning my eyes!
It's burning my nose!
Thank you very much, sir.
This way.
(chuckling)
Ranmaru?
That was scary.
But she‐‐but she‐‐
she looked like a‐‐
‐A lady!
Yahoo, free rent, baby!
Banzai, banzai, banzai!
I put her to sleep
in Auntie's room.
‐Attaboy!
Wait, what?
You mean she's in that
frilly, glittering room?
And she seemed very happy.
(sobbing)
You big moron, stop crying!
I'm sorry, I'm not
gonna cry anymore, wah!
Okay, but what do we do if
she reverts back tomorrow?
‐Huh?
Always so negative,
forget about it.
Banzai, Sunako!
She's a lady, banzai!
♪
(gasping)
Good morning, gentlemen.
‐Thank you,
‐and a very good morning
‐to you as well, Sunako!
I'll bring your
breakfast out right away.
Oh, yeah!
(laughing)
Please, don't mind us.
Hurry up, will ya?!
This is kind of
embarrassing, huh?
‐Uh‐huh.
‐Ow!
‐Uh?
Ah?
Huh, just a mirage.
Yeah.
Whatever, just
bring out the food!
♪
Whoa, check out
the new, girly menu!
Not that our old
Japanese menu was bad.
It all looks great,
thank you for the food!
‐Yum!
‐Um!
♪
(yelling)
And here comes
the first question.
You're at a restaurant, and you
want to remove some fish bones
or fruit seeds from your mouth.
How would you handle
this correctly?
Your answer, Kyohei?
(spitting)
Wrong!
Aaah!
(dinging)
Yes, Sunako?
Put them on either a fork or
a spoon and discreetly place
them on the edge of your plate.
Bingo, bingo, bingo, bingo!
That's correct.
But sometimes that's a
little difficult to do.
In that case, you would
simply make a fist like so,
and put the item inside your
fist while you hide your mouth,
then put it down on
the side of the plate.
Uh‐huh, you should never take
it directly from your mouth
and put it on the plate.
You're exactly right.
Would you shut up?
We'll see you next
week, everyone, bye‐bye!
Ah, it tastes like crap!
‐What is that?
‐Why is this bitter?
And what is that?
Ah, it's happening to the
salad, yogurt, and the pasta!
Oh, no, it seems
you didn't like it.
Go back!
Huh?
That's right, I demand
that you go back
to your old self this instant.
We haven't eaten anything
decent since yesterday!
(crying)
‐Aah!
♪
I‐‐I'm so sorry.
(crying)
Huh?
How come she's not
taking a swing at me?
She's just reacting the
way a normal girl would!
Please stop crying, Sunako!
I'll go back and recook
it all right away.
It's okay, you don't have to.
Really, I can eat
this if I try hard.
Oh, that makes me happy.
(sighing)
That was close.
Well then, I'll go
do the laundry now.
Hey, what about our food?
I still want something good!
Isn't it nice to have a
real girl around, though?
Uh‐huh, Auntie and old
Sunako are both women,
but when it comes
to being a lady,
it's a whole different
story, you know?
‐Huh?
Uh, is something wrong?
Stupid mirage.
Kyohei, you really need
to stop picking on Sunako.
She's a young lady now.
Yeah, that young lady
is about to encounter
your dirty underwear.
‐Huh?
(screaming)
It's just as I thought,
young lady, my ass!
♪
Oh!
‐No, stop right where you are!
I'll do this by myself.
All right, then I
guess I'll just go
clean up your rooms instead.
Oh, thanks a lot‐‐
(screaming)
All of my bad books
are lying out!
I have all kinds
of things in there!
Uh?
I think I'll do that
by myself, too, okay?
‐Uh?
Ah.
♪
‐Schwing!
‐Oh, God, what was I doing
‐just now!
I'd better get back
to doing the laundry.
Oh, I'm all wet.
Oh, dear!
Sorry about that.
No, it's okay.
Where's breakfast?
I'm still hungry.
Kyohei?
Yeah?
I need your lips.
♪
What the hell did
you just ask me?
Do you mean you've been eyeing
me that way all this time?
I can't believe it!
No, this is so indecent
I can't stand it!
It's just that having an actual
lady here in our home made me
feel as though I were
somehow betraying Noi.
Uh?
If I have to be so
sensitive all the time,
I'd rather have the old Sunako.
I agree.
Kyohei, if you kiss her the
shock might cause her to go
back to her old self!
Why didn't you just say
so instead of beating
around the bush?
Not that I want to do
it, because free rent is
more important than all that.
But you just told
her to change back!
Yeah, well, I changed
my mind, so there!
You're a cruel, perverse,
and heartless bastard!
Rant, rant, rant!
Please, you mustn't argue!
Please, try to get along!
You know, our Sunako would
never say anything like that.
Ah?
In fact, the Sunako we know
is always stirring up trouble
and making things horrifying
regardless of what's
going on around her.
Not only that, our Sunako
randomly gushes blood
from her nose and
causes us all to panic!
Ah, that's just horrible!
(screaming)
Normally, she would get
a nosebleed if she got
that close to us.
Hold on, nosebleeds?
Maybe we should
fight sex with sex.
You know what to do, Ranmaru!
Gotcha!
Man, you're fast, and that
stuff smells dangerous.
Why don't you do it, Takenaga?
Huh, me?
No, I can't.
There's nothing to worry about.
You'll have a leading authority
in these matters writing
the script for you, okay?
Aah, ha, ha, ha, I'm starving.
Um, did you call me?
Ah?
Ah, come closer.
Uh, um, yes, sir.
What now, what now?
The second page of the script,
gently take her hand,
and slowly pull her toward you.
Come.
And begin glowing now.
Ah, so bright!
Now take hold of her, then
lay her down, yes, do it!
Do it now, go on, yeah!
Idiots.
He sounds like a porn director.
Yes!
(gasping)
♪
(groaning)
Yah, forgive me, Noi!
I've been unfaithful, I'm sorry!
Takenaga, please stop crying.
I can't stay here anymore.
I'm leaving!
Don't do anything stupid!
Don't stop me, I can't do this.
Then I'm gonna go, too!
Shaddup, what you need to do
right now is feed me, dammit!
Hey, how can you
be so self‐centered
at a time like this?
I've had enough of this.
I'm gonna go take a bath.
No, wait a minute.
(growling)
He's serious, he must be
practically starving to death!
Geez, this is what makes
girls such a pain in the ass!
♪
What the hell are
you looking at??
Please, Kyohei.
Come on, you want to eat decent
food again, too, don't you?
Just give her a
little kiss, please?
Just one little
kiss, pretty please?
‐Please, please?
‐Please??
Will you stop bothering
me when I'm in the bath?
I could shampoo your hair.
I could wash your
back for you, okay?
(screaming)
Stop touching me!!
And don't come back.
Uh, geez!
Um, I brought a
change of clothes, oh!
♪
I'm very sorry!
Would you just go back, or
do you plan to stay this way?
I don't understand.
I don't know what
you're talking about,
but please, please, let me go!
Please, Kyohei, if you kiss her
the shock might cause her to go
back to her old self.
Ah, it hurts.
Oh!
(gasping)
(slapping noise)
(screaming)
♪
Get the food on now, hurry!
Damn.
It didn't even hurt.
(crying)
Huh?
♪
(stomach growling)
Sunako?
Ah, yes, I'll be right‐‐oh.
(stomach growling)
♪
What the hell happened?
(crying)
So what am I supposed
to do from now on?
Uh, hey, wait,
that smells like...
Thank you for your
patience, gentlemen.
‐Oh!
♪
I'm afraid it looks a little
plain since everything's
sort of a brownish tone.
(drooling)
♪
(gasping)
‐Now that's what we're
‐talking about!
Japanese food!
This is it, this is it!
Is this the best or what?
‐Absolutely!
Um, excuse me, would
you like seconds?
Uh!
Ah!
♪
Um, I, um...
It tastes so good!
You did it, you
really did a good job.
(laughing)
(gasping)
(screaming)
♪
‐Hey, hey!
‐Is she breathing?
Sunako!
Look, look, Sunako's back!
It is Sunako!
(laughing and crying)
She's back!
Aah.
♪
Uh, um.... uh, uh?
Hiroshi, Akira, Josephine, Sean.
(laughing)
Ow.
Oh, you're awake.
♪
For you.
Uh.
(snarling)
♪
Come to think of it, I guess
you're really better this way.
What are you talking about?
Ah, nothing.
Oh.
Hey, Kyohei, is Sunako awake?
(screaming)
(maniacal laughter)
♪
(crying)
Maybe we should try feeding
her those mushrooms again.
♪
A preppy girl, huh?
Get up, you preppy girl!
That's from tomorrow's‐‐
oh, I can't say it!
Young lady?
That's my famous scar.
That's Saotome's line,
I can't say that!
Big sister!
My little sister‐‐
I can't say it!
This review is all messed up!
‐Whose fault is that?
Next time: Sleeping
Well‐Bred Beauty.
Another new character.
‐Is this payback?