Hiroshi here, I'm extremely
health conscious,
which has resulted in my
having a minimum of body fat.
But more importantly,
up until the last episode,
‐Sunako has been‐‐
‐If we don't hurry up
and turn Sunako into
a respectable lady,
we'll be responsible for
the full amount of the rent.
But that's a lot
easier said than done.
‐You don't have any good ideas?
‐How about keeping everything
‐creepy away from her?
‐That's a good idea.
Damn straight, buddy!
♪
How much longer do I have
to keep living like this?
I just want to live a quiet life
and not have to deal with
those radiant creatures.
Hey, you're making hamburgers!
Be sure to put
fried eggs on 'em!
What, you mean tomatoes,
and you have to put cheese
and tomato sauce on a hamburger.
It must be green (indistinct)
ponzu sauce, and grated radish.
Well I say a sunny‐side‐up
egg and lots of ketchup.
(indistinct arguing)
How could they be so dazzling
arguing over hamburgers?
Soy sauce, garlic butter.
(screaming)
(indistinct remarks)
For the love of God, I
can't take this anymore!
‐Yeah!
‐Ah, I almost forgot
to mention it, but I do have
some good news from Auntie.
So, tell us what it is!
Right, her friend's
restaurant is shorthanded,
so they're looking for help,
just some part‐timers.
We'd be kitchen staff and
it pays 2,000 yen an hour.
Two thousand yen, are you
sure you heard that right?
Yes, and meals are
provided as well,
so that'd give
Sunako a break too.
That's perfect.
I can finally have
a little time alone.
Those are two very
different issues.
How is that?
What's two very
different issues?
I'm saying that you
should continue to cook
all of our meals
like you always have!
Hey, Sunako!
Kyohei, that was really
nasty to say that.
Yeah, I mean Sunako
isn't our maid, you know.
Given the fact you
always eat like a pig,
why should it matter
where you eat your meals?
Well, it does matter.
‐Nothing like a good nabe.
‐I agree.
(mixed remarks)
Let's have nabe,
tomorrow we're having nabe
‐around a kotatsu table!
‐What'd you say?
‐We're having nabe at a kotatsu!
‐But we don't have a kotatsu!
It wouldn't really go
with the mansion's decor.
No, no, we have to
have a kotatsu table!
‐Nabe, nabe!
‐Fine, nabe, tomorrow.
And go buy a kotatsu
too while you're at it.
You know which kind
I'm talking about, right?
Go get one big enough
for all of us!
‐You go get it!
‐No, it's cold outside.
You're the one who suggested it.
Are you seriously trying
to make me go buy it?
You've got some nerve.
It's only fair to warn you that
you better prepare yourselves!
‐Prepare ourselves?
‐That's right,
because I've always
wanted to be known as...
Nabe King!
Sunako Nakahara, we're
having nabe tomorrow.
I already said I'd make it.
He seems amused.
♪
(shouting)
It's freezing.
I think it's
probably gonna snow.
So radiant.
I'm gonna melt, I'm
gonna melt or liquefy.
You know, everywhere
you go, shopping arcades
always have the same atmosphere.
‐Yeah.
‐Exactly!
Oh, good afternoon, Miss.
Honey, turn on
the lights for me.
It's the creepy girl,
she's come back again.
So what vegetables are
we gonna put in the nabe?
Wow, whoa, whoa, are you Kyohei
Takano from Mori High School?
‐Yes, I am.
‐My, my.
It's so bright we won't need
to turn on any lights today.
Come over here, honey, we
have a celebrity in our shop!
‐So, can we just go now?
‐No, they have the best prices.
‐Oh my God, they're together!
‐Oh creepy girl,
I'm so happy, I'm so
truly happy for you!
Who would've ever thought
that a creepy girl like you
would find such a
handsome boyfriend!
‐He's not!
‐Listen, son.
What's in a girl's heart
matters more than her looks,
but I can see you must
understand that all to well.
‐We should celebrate!
‐Here, here, just take 'em!
Have you done
something here before?
I just shop here all
the time, that's all.
Oh, hey, creepy
lady, guess what!
The haunted house I
was telling you about‐‐
the haunted...
Mommy, Mommy, look!
The creepy lady is walking
with a super cool looking guy!
‐Oh my!
‐Have you heard?
‐The creepy girl is‐‐
The guy known as
Mr. Mori High School‐‐
Hey, lady, have
you heard about it?
Oh my, oh my, oh my!
(stammering)
(cheering)
♪
It's become a festival?
It's such a blessing, oh my,
I never did think I would live
long enough to see you marry.
I wanna die!
‐Tofu, and all for you!
‐On the house!
(indistinct remarks)
Wow, you're pretty
popular, aren't you?
‐This is all your fault!
‐Creepy girl, I just heard!
Cooking up an
intimate nabe, huh?
We're having nabe,
but not intimately!
Crabs, hey pretty boy,
you got crabs?
‐Like this?
‐I love crabs!
Then try this, I'll
even give you a discount.
♪
(screaming)
We can't afford
something so expensive!
I don't care if they do
give us a special price!
‐Yum, here!
‐What?
You really should try it.
‐Special, special.
‐Hey, the creepy girl's
hemorrhaging all
over the sidewalk!
Ah, don't worry, she
does that all the time.
Okay, let's go, Sunako Nakahara,
and pick up your feet, geez.
(indistinct conversations)
♪
‐You scared me!
‐What?
What did you just buy, what
did you just buy, you moron?
Huh, crabs, shrimp,
and matsutake mushrooms.
♪
‐Let's go home.
‐Hey, my kotatsu.
‐Huh?
‐This sucks.
It's pointless to do
this without a kotatsu.
‐Kotatsu, kotatsu!
‐Do you even realize
whose fault this is?
Oh, it started snowing,
Kenny, so let's hurry home.
Okay, Mom!
We'll have sukiyaki
around the kotatsu.
Oh boy, let's have it now!
We have to wait for Daddy
to come home before we eat.
Then I hope Daddy
comes home really soon.
Oh yeah, that's nice.
What's nice?
♪
‐He's really here, Kyohei!
‐Yeah, in the flesh!
(screaming)
(indistinct chanting)
‐Receive, nay!
‐Toss, nay!
‐Here we go, nay!
‐Ready, nay!
(together)
Attack!
(shouting)
(together)
Kyohei!
(groaning)
♪
Remember, you must not ever
let good food go to waste.
(shrill screaming)
Hey, calm down!
I thought as much.
I suspected that
this might happen.
‐I'm so terribly sorry.
‐We'll pick it up.
Forget it, just go home.
I said go home!
(crying)
♪
Hey, what on earth
happened here?
‐Are you all right, young man?
‐I'm fine, thanks.
So did all those young
ladies get the better of ya?
By the way, what happened
to the creepy girl?
‐She got fed up and left.
‐What're you gonna do
‐about the groceries?
‐I'm totally broke.
Ohhh.
♪
Splendid, there
simply no other words
to describe it
better than très bien.
Um, sir, I thought you said
we were supposed to be
working in the kitchen?
No, no, not at all.
Do you think I'd actually let
you boys work in the kitchen?
Just smile pretty and carry
the dishes to the tables.
That's all you
need to do to make
your salaries go
higher and higher.
I'm not cut out
for customer service.
Hey, come on now,
Kyohei, just smile.
You wanna pay Sunako back the
money you owe her, don't you?
Huh, that's not it, I just
want us to have nabe.
Well, either way, remember
a job's still a job,
so you better not
screw this one up.
‐Hello, I have a reservation.
‐Go get 'em, Kyohei.
‐Welcome to our restaurant.
‐No, no, no.
‐Morii, help.
‐Welcome ladies.
Allow me the honor of
showing you to your table.
Come right this way please.
Thatta boy.
(screaming)
Today let's learn
some table manners.
First you must know
how to eat your soup.
When partaking
in French cuisine,
draw the spoon towards
you as you eat.
However, with any other type of
cuisine, one should always draw
the spoon away from
oneself as one eats.
If your soup is too hot‐‐
wrong again!
One should never blow on
one's soup, nor should one
take several sips
from the same spoonful.
Instead, stir the soup
gently with the spoon.
‐Do this silently.
‐I can't remember all that!
♪
(together)
Whoa!
Thank you for the food!
Eat all you like, s'il
vous plait, I'd expect
no less from anyone referred
to me by Madame Takahara.
C'est manifique,
wouldn't you agree?
Hey, you oughta take some
of that food home for Sunako.
Give me a break, why
would I wanna do that?
You're the one who wanted to
have nabe for dinner tonight,
and you're also the reason
we had to cancel it.
You should feel bad for pushing
her around all the time.
‐But I don't.
‐Well you ought to, a little.
‐Here, take this.
‐Huh?
Don't "huh" me.
♪
Thank you for the food.
Crispy, crispy, crispy.
It's good.
We have to wait for Daddy
to come home before we eat.
Then I hope Daddy
comes home really soon.
Oh yeah, that's nice.
Crispy, crispy, crispy.
‐You seem to be eating well.
‐Ah!
‐Mmm.
‐Hey!
I don't have enough food
here for the both of us!
I've already had
an excellent meal.
Therefore, I don't have any
need for crap like this.
Here, it's foie gras
whatchamacallit
and boiled something or
other, all right?
‐Eat up.
‐No thank you!
Say what, after I came all the
way into this scary ass room
to deliver it directly to you?
Isn't there anything
else you'd like to say?
(chewing noisily)
Honestly, do you really enjoy
eating by yourself
in a room like this?
‐Just leave me alone.
‐That's fine with me!
Good for you then!
No one said you had to go out of
your way and cook a meal for us!
♪
(chuckling)
Get out of my room!
(rumbling)
So, did Sunako like it?
Who cares?
He said something to her again.
♪
Oh brother, I've
got indigestion.
‐I ate too much yesterday.
‐Wait, where's Kyohei?
Who knows, he went out
somewhere this morning.
Oh hi, Sunako, we don't
have to work tonight,
so could you please
cook dinner for us?
We don't have much here,
what did you want?
‐Well, could we have nabe?
‐Nabe, what for?
Well, I think Kyohei
would like it a lot.
‐He would, huh?
‐Yeah, Kyohei's family
had certain issues that kept
them from ever having a chance
to do things like sitting down
together and enjoying nabe.
‐I'm the same way.
‐What, seriously?
Look, I know that it must
be a pain for you Sunako,
but to tell you the truth,
I really do enjoy it,
having dinner with
all of us here.
Actually, I do too.
So I can kind of understand
how he feels about it.
It's more than just nabe,
I'm not sure if Kyohei
ever got the chance to have
any meals with his family.
♪
I'm going to buy some groceries.
Young man, that's enough
for the potatoes.
Now get the die cart,
do this whole row here.
That old fart, I never
would've thought
‐the guy was a slave driver.
‐Did ya say something?
‐Nothing.
‐Boy, I'm telling ya,
you've sure been a
big help harvesting
all these vegetables
for me today.
My back's been
killing me, you know?
I'll help you out here,
but don't forget
I'm getting some
free veggies in return.
(laughing)
Say, young man,
I have a question.
‐You don't like carrots, do you?
‐Not at all.
Well that creepy girl
is extremely careful
when it comes to picking
out carrots, and I'll bet
she acts that way when she goes
shopping because she considers
the preferences of the
people she's feeding.
At least that what
I always assumed
whenever I saw her doing that.
Though the first time I ever
met her I actually thought
‐that she was a ghost!
‐Me too!
(laughing)
♪
Ingredients for the nabe,
ingredients for the nabe.
Kotatsu, kotatsu,
ingredients for‐‐
Hey, creepy girl, aren't
you stopping by today?
‐No thanks.
‐By the way, I heard
that you were never able to have
your nabe together last night.
‐What, is that right, creepy?
‐I'm afraid so.
I'm sure sorry to hear that.
Hey, tell you what, I'll
give you some scraps.
Yeah, same here, you can
have some of mine too.
Thanks to you and
that handsome guy,
the number of our customers
tripled yesterday.
Hey, tofu guy, you oughta give
old creepy something too.
Sure, you want one piece or two?
Oh, one will be
just fine, thank you!
Don't worry about a thing.
(humming)
♪
(phone ringing)
Hello, Karahara resid‐‐
is this Takenaga?
What's going on?
Huh, you wanna borrow my what?
(indistinct conversations)
So you wanna tell me something?
Just who the heck are
ya, hell, what are ya?
Who I am is of no
importance here.
Okay, whatever.
‐You swing a mean hammer, lady.
‐Thank you.
Tell you what, since those
materials were going out
for recycling, I'll give you
everything you need as long
as you'll come back to bash
things for me sometimes.
It's a deal.
♪
We have to wait for Daddy
to come home before we eat.
Then I hope Daddy
comes home really soon.
‐Oh yeah, that's nice.
‐They had certain issues
that kept them from ever
having a chance to do things
like sitting down together
and enjoying nabe.
(hammer banging)
Excuse me, boss, does she look
like she's putting the final
nail in someone's coffin?
Looks like it
snowed a lot today.
Hey, stop that, you
can't eat only the meat!
‐But Dad!
‐Veggies, veggies, meat!
Yeah, and veggies, veggies, yay,
the enoki mushrooms
aren't gone yet.
Oh honey, you really are
the nabe king around here.
(laughing)
Oy vey, look at that.
Yeah, I can't believe that kind
of trash was left in the road.
‐I should report this?
‐Do they usually charge
‐recycling taxes on a kotatsu?
‐I should know.
It's a k‐k‐k‐kotatsu!
♪
‐Urgh!
‐Urgh?
(groaning and yelling)
Oh my God, oh my God,
you scared me to death!
But, check it out.
That's one good‐looking kotatsu.
So where'd you buy it?
Don't tell me.
You actually made this yourself?
Uh...
I think that sometimes
you do go overboard.
Yeah, I really don't wanna
hear that coming from you!
And what's that you have there?
For the record, I promise
I didn't steal them.
♪
Hey.
Allow me.
♪
‐It is fun, you know.
‐Huh?
Nabe at a kotatsu.
‐Yeah?
‐Yeah.
So where'd those two go?
I mean, I brought this
big earthen pot over here.
‐I am so hungry!
‐Yeah, you're right.
It's taking 'em way too long.
Okay, I guess we're gonna have
to split up and find 'em.
‐Right.
‐It's snowing,
so be careful out there.
♪
(screaming)
‐My blanket!
‐Cocoa!
Make it super hot!
‐So are you awake now?
‐What do you think?
The restaurant gave
us an advance loan,
so we got sliding doors put in.
And padded kimono!
Kotatsu!
Hey, you guys bought
a really nice one.
Check this out, this kotatsu
was made by Sunako Nakahara.
‐Whoa!
‐No way!
Wow, you're a genius!
Awesome, you're a
super genius, Sunako!
Oh, guess what, earlier today,
a year‐end gift was delivered
here addressed to your aunt.
♪
Let's eat it, let's eat it!
‐Come on, serve the fish!
‐Kyohei!
Don't feel obligated
to force yourself, Sunako.
It must have been
an awful lot of work
cooking so long for all of us.
I'll be glad to come help
you out as much as I can.
And we can start learning how
to cook at work too, okay?
‐Even Kyohei.
‐What?
I believe you all
have the wrong idea.
Because I actually love...
cooking!
(together)
You're awesome!
♪
Oh yeah!
You gotta have nabe
in the winter.
Hey, forget the fancy foie
gras, there's nothing better
than eating nabe with
your friends, am I right?
‐I agree.
‐Mhm.
Kyohei, aren't you
gonna be the nabe king?
That's right, back off everyone!
The meat and the fish
in the nabe belong to me!
And the rest of you can
have the lowly vegetables.
A real nabe king
wouldn't talk that way.
He wouldn't, hey, don't
put those carrots in there!
Flower shaped carrots are
an essential part of nabe.
(indistinct screaming)
(chewing noisily)
‐What's so funny?
‐They look cute together,
‐don't they?
‐Yeah, they do.
Hey, stop that, don't touch my‐‐
The mushrooms are
done already, right?
Pass me the soy sauce!
The edible chrysanthemum
is ready!
♪
I finally get to spend
the night with Takenaga!
‐Everyone else will be there!
‐Let's play paintball!
What're you looking forward
to the most, Sunako?
‐Corpses.
‐Corpses?
Next time on The Wallflower:
Murder at the Hot Springs.
What kind of title is that?