This is the story
of my friend, Sunako.
From what I've heard, those
nasty creatures of light
are trying to turn her
into an elegant lady.
‐Good luck to us!
We can do it if we
put our minds to it!
We're gonna turn Sunako
into a respectable young lady!
Oh, my heart hurts.
♪
(screaming)
No.
Please, don't do it.
Just close your eyes!
And hold really still!
No, no, no, no!
Oh, quit wiggling, Sunako!
Please let us cut
your bangs a little!
You don't wanna go to school
looking like this, do you?
(screaming)
Look, I'm just going
to raise your bangs‐‐
Aw, Sunako!
(crying)
Oh, just lay off.
If Sunako doesn't wanna change,
there's nothing
you can do with her,
no matter what you try.
This is no time for
nonchalance, dammit!
What do we do about the rent?
Oh, this is probably a
bad time to mention it,
but the plumbing
upstairs is broken‐‐
I don't wanna change.
I don't need to change.
You know, it would help
if you could tell us
why you don't wanna
show us your face.
‐Yeah, tell us!
‐No!
‐Say it!
‐I said say it, dammit!
‐No means no!
Then say goodbye!
He jumps on the count of three!
Three, two, one!
All right, all right, I'll tell!
There was a boy I liked,
and he said I was ugly and‐‐
And?
(crying)
‐And?
‐Is that all?
Until that day, I
worried about my acne,
went on diets and
looked in mirrors
just like any
normal teenage girl.
But after that, if all of
that had gotten me nowhere,
what was the point
in trying at all?
What was the point of
worrying about my face...
or being a girl ever again?
‐Oh, Sunako.
‐If I don't look in the mirror,
I don't have to compare
myself to all those other girls.
Once you've learned
to look at it that way,
it's so much nicer to be alone.
I don't get it.
You're talking
about one guy, right?
Once is all it
takes, so get out!
Hmm, so she used to be normal.
She shouldn't be so worried
about what other people think.
I guess it shows how
much she liked that guy.
What kind of jerk would
say something so cruel
‐to a young girl?
‐Well, he must've been ugly,
because only someone ugly
would call an ugly girl that.
Uh, guys, look at the time.
Okay, do you wanna take
your bath first, Kyohei?
‐Duh!
‐I think that's a yes.
I've kept this
hideous face hidden
from the rest of the
world for two years.
Why would I ever want
to cut my hair again?
(crickets chirping)
(sighing)
Why do I have to go
through this, anyway?
And why do I hear
the shower running?
The shower?
(gasping)
(grunting)
(quacking)
(screaming)
I saw him!
Oh, my God, I saw‐‐
That beautiful creature
must've seen my disgusting‐‐
I was so horrified, I
just jumped out the window!
(crying)
Well, I did tell everyone
that we had to share
the downstairs bathroom,
but I guess Sunako
didn't hear that.
She might not have
heard, but she sure saw!
Did she?
Aw, gee‐‐but tell me.
Tell you what?
‐Did you see?
‐Hmm.
(yelling)
Put some clothes on, geez!
(screaming)
Isn't he so cute?
What's all the commotion?
Nothing you should
worry about, loser.
Ah, the sweet
welcome of princesses.
(sneezing)
Are you sick‐‐it sounds
like you're catching a cold!
It's nothing, okay?
Look, all of them
are walking together!
I heard that all four
of them live together!
That must be paradise!
That's where I wanna be!
Who's making that rackety noise?
‐Lassine!
‐Madeline!
‐Roxanne!
‐And Yvonne!
The Goth‐Loli Sisters will
worship those beautiful boys!
At night, I'll seduce
my hottie Ranmaru nai!
And I'm gonna lay
with Yukinojoh nai!
Takenaga and I will soak
in the bathtub all day!
And I'm gonna put handcuffs
on my beloved Kyohei nai!
We are the ultimate
groupie gropies!
We'll make those boys
our shining trophies!
‐Oh, yeah!
‐The Goth‐Loli Sisters‐‐
why are they here?
How dare you lecherously ogle
my Kyohei nai and the others?
It pisses me off nai!
She's right‐‐royally‐‐
‐Pissed off nai!
‐Nai!
(yelling)
(grunting)
(barking)
(crying)
Who is that sloppy
looking female?
And why is she walking
so close to them
and disregarding our presence?
Who does she think she is‐‐nai?
If you want this
spot, it's yours.
‐Nai?
For some reason,
an evil‐sounding voice
suddenly echo‐echo‐echoing
around inside my head, nai!
Oh, great beautiful
angel of darkness
who waits in the deep
dark underground of hell!
‐Goth‐Goth, Loli‐Loli!
Good morning, hello, boys!
(gasping)
Hey, it's Noi!
♪
Another radiant creature!
Why don't you
handle this, Kyohei?
‐We've gotta get to class!
‐See you later, Sunako!
Man, there's no chance for
us now that Noi is here!
I don't wanna stay here
and be compared to her!
The only way to
avoid comparisons
is not to look at yourself.
So, you're name's Sunako, right?
...but I doubt
they'll even understand.
Hi, I'm Noi Kasahara‐‐
nice to meet you!
Ahh‐‐oh, my God, are you okay?
Yeah, sort of.
Happens when I run
into beautiful people.
Beautiful!
Takenaga, did you hear that?
‐She said I'm‐‐
‐You're too late‐‐he's gone.
Hey, what's with your attitude?
It's exactly the same
attitude I always have.
Well, it's a lousy one.
And I didn't ask for
your expert opinion!
And what does that mean,
you big grumpy poo head?
It's blinding!
He and she creatures
of the light!
♪
Come on, let's go.
So I'll see you
later, Sunako, okay?
Did you see that?
Kyohei put her in bondage nai!
Unforgivable!
‐May she be stricken with‐‐
‐A burning box in hell!
‐Goth‐Goth, Loli‐Loli!
Now class, this
is Sunako Nakahara,
our new transfer student.
She's so creepy!
Is it just me or did it
just get really cold in here?
And, like, check out the dark
aura of malice around her!
Hey, who turned down the lights!
You‐‐you don't think?
(screaming)
♪
Our paper's running a spotlight
on the much talked
about transfer student
who came to school with
the four beautiful boys!
‐Say brie!
‐No‐‐no pictures!
Oh, come on, you
must be really cute
if they'll let
you walk with them!
‐Give us a peek, huh?
‐Let's see your face!
‐Hey, wait!
Photo Club, follow her!
I want that face on the front
page of tomorrow's newspaper!
Reporters attack!
(yelling)
(sighing)
Finally, a place
I feel comfortable.
Greetings, my new
fellow classmates.
My name is Sunako Nakahara.
It's very nice
to meet all of you!
Really, I'm so happy.
I couldn't share a class
with those creatures of light,
but this place rocks!
(laughing)
‐What?
‐What do you mean "what"?
Haven't you seen this?
It's the Sunako Derby‐‐
bring in a photo
of this mysterious
transfer student's face
‐and win 100,000 yen!
‐Get out!
Does that mean I can
enter the contest too?
‐No!
‐And that's not funny, Kyohei.
And I'm sure things
will settle down later.
‐Hi, Ranmaru!
‐Wanna have lunch with us?
Oh, sure, I love eating!
Muah!
(indistinct yelling)
No!
Hey, that was Nakahara!
‐After her!
‐Yeah!
Nuts.
Just one shot!
Why can't you leave me alone?
I don't understand!
(panting)
This looks like a safe place.
Hey, you‐‐think you're popular
with the boys, don't you nai?
Uh, no, nai?
You think you're so in
with our sweet princes!
And now all the
other boys in school
are chasing after you too!
Must be nice to get
all that attention!
‐Right, nai?
‐No, it's not nice at all!
‐Yeah, right, whatever!
You're seriously
pissing me off, new girl!
Oh, the Immoral Ganguro Girls!
Hiding your face on purpose
so you'll get
attention from the boys!
You're trying to stand
out, aren't you, you bitch?
But I'm not‐‐I'm not!
Stop lying, ugly girl!
We're gonna cut
those nasty bangs,
so show us some gratitude!
(gasping and laughing)
This'll be good.
Watch out, that bitch is weird!
Just shut up!
Let's teach her a lesson!
(laughing)
How can I stand out
when I'm not even trying?
Could it be that, by hiding,
I stand out?
♪
(laughing)
I told you, that bitch is weird!
Hey, I said to shut up!
Yeah, but look.
♪
Am I interrupting something?
‐It's Kyohei!
Uh, this is...
What is he doing?
You know, I think it's time
for an end to this crap!
Kyohei is holding the ugly girl!
Melting, melting.
♪
Hmm?
Hey, you're looking kinda‐‐
(yelling)
Where did these
scissors come from?
I don't know how they got there!
(laughing)
No more scissors!
Oh, pretty please, Kyohei,
we were just joking!
(gasping)
No, what have you done?
Keep your skirts on,
it's just a scratch.
♪
(yelling)
They got me!
(whimpering)
Wow, that's just so...
bad.
‐Sunako!
‐Kyohei!
What's going on?
(groaning)
What happened here?
(whimpering)
(yelling)
All right, now I
don't stand out, okay?
(gasping)
How dare you threaten me?
How dare you?
Now apologize to this
creature of light!
Creature of light?
Sunako is just so commanding!
‐Oh, she's awesome!
‐Oh, God.
(groaning)
Kyohei, are you okay?
Your face is really red!
Do you think you're
getting a fever?
You need to put your jacket on.
Sunako, I want you to
take him home right now
and put him in bed.
After all, you are
partially responsible
for his condition, aren't you?
Besides, I have a test.
He's really heavy.
(grumbling)
Wait, why is Sunako
Nakahara taking Kyohei home?
She's taking him home
because she lives with us!
(yelling)
This is a nightmare.
All alone with that
creature of light.
(screaming)
Can I get you something?
Are you hungry‐‐would
you like something to eat?
Some strawberries.
Wah‐‐his light's even
more brilliant than before!
‐You got it.
‐And I want 'em in 30 seconds!
But I can't even walk to the
refrigerator in 30 seconds!
Hurry up!
Here's your strawberries!
Now I want an
energy drink instead.
Here's a nice sports drink!
No, make it some ice cream‐‐
strawberry ice cream!
Here's your ice cream‐‐it
says Yukinojoh on the label!
Nope, now I want yogurt,
strawberry flavored.
I found some yogurt, but
it said Takenaga on the box!
Maybe jam‐‐no, cancel that.
Clean up the room, it's messy!
Yeah, sure, whatever.
‐But don't touch anything!
‐Do I have psychic powers?
‐Bring me my pajamas!
‐Okay!
Those clothes on
there need to be washed!
‐Okay!
‐Now I want those strawberries!
What unspeakable evil!
This creature of
light must be a demon!
Okay, this time I brought
strawberries, a sports drink,
ice cream, yogurt, and jelly!
How about some porridge instead?
(screaming)
Should I just go ahead
and strangle him to death?
Sorry.
I said I'm sorry.
Don't worry about last night.
I couldn't see anything
through all the steam.
(grumbling)
(screaming)
Wait, I want soup!
(doorbell ringing)
Hi, Sunako, how's it going?
Takenaga said Kyohei was sick,
so I brought some
get well gifts!
I hope he likes them‐‐
strawberries, his favorite!
Would it be possible if you
could do this instead of me,
‐Miss beautiful Noi?
‐No way!
‐Why?
‐But since I'm here,
how about a little girl talk?
Okay, to sum up, you feel dizzy,
can't stop getting nose bleeds,
and think you're going to melt,
because Kyohei is so radiant,
‐is that right?
‐Uh‐huh.
Not to change the subject,
but why are all the
flowers dead right there?
That has nothing to do
with this conversation.
I can't do this anymore.
I can't be near him.
I don't wanna go
near him ever again!
Oh, I get it, so
what you're saying
is that you actually
like him, huh?
‐No, that's not it at all!
‐Oh, bummer, you're no fun!
All of this that damned
creature of light's fault.
That's right‐‐my life's
becoming a living hell,
and it's all because of
those radiant creatures!
You're so interesting!
I have no idea what you're
talking about right now!
(indistinct screaming)
Now, I'm admittedly
not an expert,
but it seems to me
that if the problem
is that they seem
so full of light,
maybe you should try
not being so gloomy
and perk up a little!
♪
Well, that's easy for you to say
since you're one of the
creatures of light as well.
I'm one of them, too?
‐How lucky!
‐Not when you consider it
from the non‐creature
of light point of view,
to which I belong and you don't.
To be honest it makes me wonder
if you know your place as
a beautiful person at all.
Excuse me‐‐as someone who isn't
even trying to make an effort,
who are you to criticize?
(screaming)
Do you have any
idea how hard it was
to get Takenaga
to even notice me?
I have to work at it harder
than any other girl in school!
Work at it?
(screaming)
The Road to Womanhood!
To perfect that flawless smile
befitting an elegant lady...
Put your lips together like
an octopus and say, "Oooh!"
Follow that by opening your
sweet little mouth sideways...
And saying, "Eee!"
Oooh, eee, oooh, eee, oooh, eee!
Wrong!
It's pointless unless you do
it very slowly and ladylike.
And, if it really starts
to hurt, take a break.
Hey, Takenaga, what do
you think about my smile?
I can't take this anymore!
Oooh, eee!
(gong booming)
It might sound strange,
but I actually envy you.
You're so lucky to get to
see Takenaga's beautiful face
every single day!
I've only seen him at
school where he puts on
that cool and serious front.
So what's he like when
he's just hanging out?
I have no idea.
He's so radiant
that it blinds me.
‐Oh, I see.
‐Am I correct in assuming
that you like Takenaga?
Uh‐huh‐‐I love him!
Take my word for it,
you can change Sunako.
All it takes is
making a little effort.
Stop living in the darkness
and come into the light!
‐Good luck!
‐Right,
that's what a person who
was born pretty would say.
What the hell?
Is this a fried
soy sauce bottle top?
No kidding, my
whole plate's fried!
Is it my fault for
not making the effort,
or is it the fault of
the creatures of light?
Actually, God's
responsible, but‐‐
Not to interrupt your
rambling, but did Noi come by?
Yes, and thanks to her, I've
gained so much enlightenment.
And all that just by
delivering strawberries!
‐That Noi's amazing.
‐What I think is amazing
is you Takenaga, and
the way you play Noi,
so when are you
gonna give her some?
She wants to date, so are
you out or in, out or in?
Shut up, Yuki, that's not nice!
I guess it must be nice
to have been born
pretty like Noi was.
Look, you've got
it wrong, Sunako.
Noi wasn't like
that from day one,
she had to work
to be that pretty!
Just look!
This is a picture of Noi back
when she was in junior high!
‐No way!
‐And yet somehow
she's become as pretty as
she is without plastic surgery.
Yeah, pretty is as pretty
does‐‐you can do it!
So hang in there, and we'll
help you however we can!
And you'll never let
someone call you ugly again!
Hello‐‐Sunako?
But can someone
defy the will of God?
Should you defy the will of God?
Defy the will of God,
defy the will of God...
Oh, she still creeps me out!
And I still can't get
over this picture of Noi!
It's like a completely
different person!
It is a different person.
Yeah, that's some weird girl
who gave me a love letter
on the street earlier.
That photo was stuck
inside the envelope.
‐Ooh, female fraud!
‐And this one might go postal!
I can defy the will of God
or melt in their radiance.
I have to.
Those are the
only choices I have
if I wanna live
through this situation.
♪
It's blinding!
How could he possibly be
so radiant when he's sick!
(groaning)
Are you okay?
‐I need to change.
‐Do you have to?
♪
(grumbling)
(screaming)
♪
My bangs are gone,
how can I live in a world
with such beautiful creatures?
How can I survive when I can
see them and they can see me?
Just be yourself, and
you'll be fine, idiot.
(screaming)
(grunting)
I have to stop this
before I rot to death!
(indistinct yelling)
Before I melt,
I'm gonna kill him!
Give it back!
Give back my dark
assets, you demon!
Is that a black hole!
Ah, we're being sucked
into the darkness!
‐I can't take this anymore!
‐I'm so scared!
It's mine!
♪
We've gotta take
Sunako to a fancy party?
‐Get a dress!
‐Keep your manners!
‐We've got no time!
‐Will you please try
‐to be a lady?
‐Why should I help you
with that attitude?
Outta my way, you plebeians!
She's not a princess,
she's the Queen!
Next on The Wallflower,
oh, my sweet, dark youth.
‐I'm sleepy!
‐Don't fall asleep, dammit!