♪
Hello, Hiroshi speaking.
May I help
you with something?
My friend, Sunako,
they've tried to
turn her into a lady,
but I'm not sure
she's going to be okay.
Dammit, quit stealing
our screen time!
Sorry, I'm at
that age, you know.
(together)
No, we don't!
♪
Okay, are you ready?
I'll do my best,
how about this?
Good, good, I like that,
can you look a
little more this way?
Yeah, just
like that, uh‐huh.
Grrr.
Uh, hi, Mr. Kinoyama,
something wrong?
Wow, you've got
beautiful hair.
Aaah!
Oh, Mr. Kinoyama.
♪
Geez, what's the matter
with Mr. Kinoyama?
It looks like
he's in a slump.
He told me he hasn't found
any good models lately.
(sigh)
Hmm?
♪
This is it,
I can feel it!
My inspiration!
The muse I've
been searching for!
(lightning cracking)
(cooing)
♪
(crows cawing)
Uh, Sunako?
Sunako, sweetie?
Uh?
This is your kind
of place, isn't it?
Yeah, everybody says this
place is really haunted.
Really!
I'm kidding, I'm kidding,
it's just a rumor, sorry.
I think I'm dead.
(heartbeat thumping)
Where is my head?
Aaah!
I love to suck
fresh meat and blood.
(cackling)
(laughing)
She looks way too happy.
I think we've successfully
cleared level one.
Yeah, whatever.
The weird thing is how she
ended up in this magazine.
You're blowing
the exposition.
You see, a world
famous photographer
happened to
see that picture
and asked Sunako
to model for him.
It looks like things
are looking up for us.
‐Really.
‐Well...
(giggling)
You're Sunako Nakahara,
aren't you?
Come this way, please.
Ah, thank you for
the invitation, ha ha.
She's going to model.
When hell freezes over.
(bats screeching)
Aaaah!
Stay still, I can't apply
foundation like this!
Aaah!
Hurry up and take
your clothes off!
(screaming)
♪
Mr. Kinoyama, please,
sir, a girl like that
can't handle being a model.
For that matter, sir,
are you completely sure
that she's even human?
Could you be saying
you doubt my judgment?
‐No, not at all, sir.
When it comes to shooting
beautiful women,
none can compare to Kinoyama,
international photographer.
Aaah!
And now the flame
of my eagle eye
has been sparked
by this girl.
As soon as I
saw her, I felt it.
Bada bing!
Did you just say
bada bing, sir?
Hmmm.
And here's the juicy part.
It seems that this
delectable little morsel
is also the niece
of Miss Nakahara,
the mysterious Marie
Antoinette of the East,
or so they say.
Buenos dias.
For really?
And considering Miss
Nakahara's great beauty,
isn't it possible that
the allure of her niece
has been ignored,
sacrificed at the alter
of her aunt's
monstrous pulchritude?
Uh, I'm not sure.
Mr. Kinoyama?
She's ready now,
go take her, please.
Aah!
She's ready for me,
my new Claudia.
♪
Aahh!
Dear God, what in
the hell is that thing?
Well, you see, sir‐‐
‐‐not even
a vampire would go
for something like that!
Now what are you going
to do about it?
And by do something,
I mean do it in
the next ten minutes!
You accept the responsibility
and not just in writing
to commit harikari
someone fall on a sword!
Uh, sir, she's
doing it again.
Stop that‐‐don't
change the subject!
But Mr. Kinoyama,
Mr. Kinoyama
for God's sake look!
Hey, hey,
come on vampires,
ghosties, ghoulies,
headless horsemen,
banshees, zombies,
werewolves, incubi, succubi,
and while I occupy,
I've got a yummy
sacrifice for you.
Aaaah!
There's something
so wrong with that girl.
So very wrong with her.
I don't care,
let's just get on
with the damn shoot
and wing it.
For all I know, she might
turn out to be photogenic.
Might be‐‐he's a
photographer for God's sake!
Start the test shoot!
‐Yes, sir!
And push those
lights to maximum.
With enough over exposure,
we might get away with it.
(camera clicking)
The part I don't get
is why she came at all.
You know how she is.
Well, there's an
interesting story there.
You lied to her,
didn't you?
No, but I
might have hinted
that a supernatural
research group
might have been wondering
if she'd be interested
in a ghost hunt.
Takenaga, you're a sneaky
bastard after my own heart.
And best of all,
they'll pay her 500,000.
She'd be crazy
not to do it.
Now wait, when
they start shooting,
don't you think they'll
discover she's‐‐
Crazy, wah wah!
Hmm.
Well, maybe we should
go check it out.
Waaah!!!
Aaaah!
♪
Okay, that may be
a little problem.
Kyohei, time
to go after her.
Uh‐‐got it!
(gasping)
I'm sorry, ladies.
That's right, don't worry.
We promise we'll fix
everything, okay.
And it'll all
be fine, really.
(gasping)
Oh, my God, these
guys are so cute!
It's as if my eyes
have been cleansed.
(yelling)
Where's my model,
where is she?
Got her!
Let me go, let me go,
let me go, ahhhh!
Jeez, it's like
catching rabid ferrets.
You wouldn't believe
how fast she is.
♪
He's fabulous!
That face, that skin,
that physique!
And oh, those long legs.
It's as if he was born
to be the ultimate subject
of the great Kinoyama,
international photographer.
How about it, do you
want to be a model, kid?
Sign with me and I'm
gonna make you a star.
He's gone, sir.
Grrrrr.
♪
Make me a model, will he?
Give me a break.
I'll give him
this, though,
he sure picked a location
Sunako would love.
I'll be that no one
would ever find me here.
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
This is garbage,
it's absolute trash!
(gong bonging)
(screaming)
The Road to Womanhood!
When you want
to look your best
during a photo session...
On what should you
keep your eyes focused?
♪
You suck!
Do you know what
your good side is?
Assuming you have one,
that's the side you should
always try to incline
slightly towards the camera.
Co‐‐correct!
When taking an I. D. photo,
place a white
hankie on your lap
and the bouncing light will
enhance your skin tone.
And what happens if
I put a blue one there?
Aaaah!
(gong bonging)
No, no, no, no, no!
Mr. Kinoyama,
just calm down.
Why don't you just use
those guys as models,
Mr. Kinoyama, sir?
You don't get it, do you?
The theme of this project
is about vanity girls,
you buffoons!
How can I use
male models for that?
Kinoyama is the
best in the world
at photographing
young girls,
not people with testicles!
‐(cooing)
‐Hmm?
You look like you're
really tired, Sunako.
Are you feeling all right?
I want to go home,
but I want to stay, too.
Well, it'll be over soon,
so hang in there.
What would you like,
some water?
Uh, Mr. Kinoyama?
You!
Do you mean me?
Eureka.
You know, I knew a
real hottie named Eureka.
Actually,
it's a Greek word
that was first
shouted by Archimedes
while in the bathroom.
Translated, it
means I found it.
Make him up, girls.
(together)
Yes, sir!
Hubba!
I thought he'd never ask!
Aaaaah!
It's coming,
it's finally coming.
My historic moment
when Kinoyama,
great international
photographer,
overcomes the wall that
he himself has created
is upon us!
(screaming)
Come on,
take it all off.
In fact, let me help
you do that, 'kay?
Ooh, your hair
is so silky.
It's such a waste
to put a wig over it.
But I, um...
Oh, Yugi,
you're so cute!
Do you think we
ought to rescue him?
Not yet, I'd like
to see what happens.
Aaah!
No, Yuki, wait!
♪
(crying)
Jeez, it was just a joke.
I can't take it,
I can't handle it anymore.
Why am I always
the one who ends up
dressed like this?
It's not so bad, sweetie.
After all, how many
girls get hand picked
by a world
famous photographer?
Isn't she lucky, Takenaga?
You think so?
He's right, Yuki,
you look very lovely.
(sobbing)
Why did you have
to play that card?
Yeah, my bad.
♪
Not like that, sexier,
more vain, allure.
Allure, I can't
do that, I can't.
Look me in the eyes,
right there‐‐
and more feminine.
‐Amazing!
‐You're amazing, Mr. Kinoyama.
‐You sure know your ladies.
Not enough, it still
needs more sex appeal.
I got it, get those
two into make up.
‐Huh?
Huh, hi, tarantula.
Do you have any friends?
This isn't bad.
I guess I was
worried over nothing.
Gorgeous, gorgeous!
Oooh, can I wear some
of those fangy teeth?
Oh, yeah, you'd look
so good with them.
You look great
with blonde hair.
All right, shoot 'em!
Why in the hell aren't
they dressed in drag, too?
Good, good, good,
just like that.
Pose it, work it,
that's right.
Put your hand on his
shoulder‐‐not that one!
Twist your hips, oh yeah,
now move your face closer.
There, work it, baby!
Great, let's take a break.
So, do you want
to come visit me
at my place sometime?
‐(squeaking)
‐Oh.
Uh.
Here, Sunako, I
brought you some cocoa.
Uh?
Thank you very much, Yuki.
♪
Being a supermodel
seriously sucks.
I hate the fact
that I'm the only one
they dress like this.
But look, I ditched
the fishnet hose
and got my jeans back.
So tell me,
do you honestly think
that I look that
much like a girl?
(blowing)
It's at times like
this I wish I was Kyohei
and say stuff like,
"Don't give me that crap!"
and "Take your gosh
darn bra and stuff it."
But that's not me.
And in the end, it's
just not who I am inside.
The thing is,
Takenega and Runmaru
always seem to
be having fun.
And it would just
be nicer if I could be
more like them,
too, sometimes.
Actually, sometimes
I feel that way, too.
But you're so
incredibly cool, Sunako.
I really admire
how you can always say
what's on your mind.
In fact, I envy you.
Huh?
But that's not
really how it is.
‐Huh?
‐(footsteps approaching)
Oh, there you are.
Let's have a little chat
while they touch you up.
Uh, okay.
(slurping)
Let me tell you, you sure
saved my bacon this time.
Thanks to you,
my next exhibition
is going to be
a big success.
Uh, that's good, I guess.
Yeah, but about
that other girl,
that Sunako
what's her name,
was something else,
badder than bad.
I mean, what
a complete rip off.
I've never seen
such an ugly model.
As I recall, you
asked her to be a model
without even meeting her.
I really don't
think she deserves
to be talked
about like that.
But that's why
she's a rip off.
Those photos
in that magazine
completely fooled me.
Who could have know
she was that ugly?
She's so unpleasant
I can't even concentrate.
You know what I mean?
(laughing)
But that's okay,
now I've got you.
And once we're done here,
I've got a new concept.
We'll keep the
momentum and snap away.
Uh, what's wrong?
I quit.
You what?
Now wait a second.
What's that all about?
Geez, what am I
gonna do with you?
Hey, Yuki, you'll never
guess what we just did.
Huh?
Sunako, look,
they just told me
this place isn't
haunted anymore.
Since that's the case,
would it be okay with you
if we went home now?
Now just hold on there.
What do you
think you're doing?
I demand an explanation.
Grrr.
Are you implying that my
trash talking that goth chick
ticked you off?
That's ridiculous.
Uh.
Oh, fine, whatever then!
Now we're all pissed.
Mr. Kinoyama,
what's going on?
What the hell is
your problem, anyway?
You're a man but you
look like a freakin' doll!
And not only do you not
know how to act like a lady,
you're also really rude!
Aah, he's talking
like a woman again!
His anger meter must
have reached its max!
What are you, some kind
of half‐assed girlie boy?
♪
Half‐assed girlie boy.
Girlie boy?
For God's sake, Yuki,
get a hold of yourself.
♪
Grrr.
‐Huh?
♪
Aaah!
My camera,
my expensive camera!
You horrid little thing!
Mr. Kinoyama, please
keep your composure.
Y‐y‐y‐y‐you're
gonna pay for that!
♪
Huh?
Pay for it,
pay for what?
I don't care, I'm not
paying for anything!
I'm getting out of here!
(screaming)
(crashing)
Oh, what was that?
Ah, there
really is a ghost!
A ghost?
♪
How exciting!
Sunako, wait, it could
be dangerous up there!
It's too late now,
she's on cloud nine.
(mumbling)
Aaah!
Kyohei, you jerk!
You tried to bail
on us, didn't you,
well you're
gonna pay for it!
I'm not paying for anything!
Aaah!
Oh, my gosh, Kyohei!
There's no ghost‐‐
well, that sucks.
Come on, Sunako,
let's get out of here.
Hold it right there.
Do you have any idea
what a privilege it is
to be photographed by me?
My eye is your
gate to the dream
of stepping
into the limelight,
beautifully exposed
to the whole wide world.
Huh.
♪
Well, we're not interested.
Ah!
♪
(fabric tearing)
Aaah!
♪
Mr. Kinoyama,
what do we do?
They're all running away!
Hmm.
Yes, sir.
♪
I had no idea
that's what happened.
Geez, if I hadn't
been unconscious
I'd have kicked that
photographer's ass.
Huh, actually I'm
glad you got hurt.
Oh, thanks, and why
aren't you angry, too?
Oh, I was, but I think
Sunako got more than angry
enough for all of us.
Says you.
If you say
it's all right.
Guys, they just
sent us the money!
They gave us
the entire thing,
all 500,000!
Huh, you're kidding.
Oh, Yuki, your
girlie ass saved us!
Stop it!
And they even
sent an invitation
to his next exhibition.
Well, that's really weird.
Should we go
and check it out?
No way, I don't
like that guy.
But we can't just take
the money and do nothing.
Let's go, are
they serving snacks?
There are a lot more
people than I expected.
I guess he is popular.
(murmuring)
Excuse me, you're the guys
in the photos, right?
All four of you
look so totally cool.
Uh, we looked cool?
All four of us?
♪
When did he take that one?
I don't know, but
it sure looks like
he nailed us to a T.
Hey, wait a second!
They're saying I'm dinner
and I never signed
a model release
for that sneaky
little bastard!
Calm down, Kyohei,
at least I've got the money
he paid us right here.
Oh, good for you.
(together)
Huh, Auntie?
I got an invitation
so I thought I'd drop by.
Isn't it fabulous?
They're saying
that this will be
one of his
greatest works ever.
An absolute masterpiece.
Hey, you give that back!
Your rent's behind
and your in arrears.
I got hurt doing this.
I got seven stitches,
a tetanus shot!
Doctor bills‐‐
Sayonara, sucker.
(together)
Sayonara money.
(counting in Japanese)
Now you listen
to me, lady!
Why, look, it comes
to 500,000 even.
Ugh.
She's a demon.
I see a demon
in front of me.
I've got an
akasuri body scrub
appointment in Korea.
I trust that you'll
keep taking care
of Sunako for me.
(speaking foreign language)
Ta‐ta, ciao, bye‐bye!
Darlings, you made it.
I am forever truly
in your debt.
Thanks to you, this exhibition
has been a huge success.
The reputation of Kinoyama,
great international
photographer,
remains unblemished.
Would anyone care if
I fit my anger
on this
sleaze ball's carcass?
I'm not gonna stop you.
And by the way,
about your captivatingly
beautiful friend,
where is that
darling Sunako?
These members
of the foreign press
have been asking for her.
No, très bien, Sunako.
Beautiful, Sunako.
Da da, kurasho, Sunako.
Actually, now that
I think about it,
we did force her to get
in the cab with us, but...
Aahh!
Aaahhh!
She's not here, she
didn't come with us, really.
Yeah, she said she didn't
feel good or something.
Yeah, that's it.
(evil laughter)
I want it.
Oh, baby, I want
I want it bad.
(laughing)
♪
I pledge no
more housework!
No don't!
I need a button sewn.
I'll do that.
My shirt's wrinkled.
I'm hungry!
I'll do that.
He's like a robot!
I'm so scared!
Next time on
The Wallflower,
Dreamy Halloween.
I'll do, do, do, do.
She's such a weirdo!