Hiroshi here, as a star
who has beautiful skin,
I cannot live without sunscreen.
Do you have a problem with that?
Sunako's from
Hokkaido isn't she?
Now that you mention it,
she does have fair skin.
Is that necessarily because
she's from a snowy region?
I don't think that's the case
for everyone from there.
I forgot to apply
sunscreen on my stomach.
We always knew you
had a darker side.
Honestly, are you telling
me I'm the only one here
who's bothered by
those tan lines?
Why do you stare at me?
♪
My business has been in the
red for quite some time.
‐I might have to close.
‐My shop is at its limits too.
If customers don't
start coming here soon
our shopping arcade
will be finished.
It wasn't like this before,
it was different when he was‐‐
‐That guy.
‐Well, sitting here
and doing nothing
won't fix the problem.
‐Ah, aren't you‐‐
‐Let's get going.
So, you're really
going to help us?
Do you mean it?
(wind howling)
(groaning)
♪
Hey, Sunako, if you
strain too much, you...
(indistinct shouting)
Let me see that.
♪
So radiant!
Please get dressed!
Incredible, contestant
Kyohei is just amazing.
His muscles are
really bulging now.
What an awesome sight!
Oh yeah, his muscles
are totally pumped up.
Kyohei for the win.
(shouting)
There!
I really appreciate your help.
There hasn't been a jar
made that I can't open.
Yeah, whatever.
He sure lets it go to his head.
‐What's the matter, Yuki?
‐He's so cool.
‐Huh?
‐My turn.
Please, bring me a
different jar, Sunako.
Huh?
(grunting)
Sunako, do you have any
jars with looser lids?
(groaning)
Do you have any with lids
that are almost open?
(straining)
I'm going to wash the dishes.
Give me that.
‐Whoa.
Why is it, why do
I have to be so lame?
Don't worry, you're cute and
look good, in girl's clothes.
‐You are not helping.
‐I wanna be cool, not cute!
What's your problem, Yuki,
you have your own charm.
‐Huh?
‐That's right.
With that cute smile of yours,
you can pretty much
get away with anything.
Your friendly personality
makes old people and children
love you, and animals
love you too.
And remember, you were the
only one who got a discount
at the takoyaki
shop the other day.
♪
‐What's up?
Yuki, on top of all that, your
family loves you too, you know?
You're the only one
of us who gets letters
‐from his family every month.
‐But that isn't cool at all.
What're you saying?
That's so much better
than it is to be cool.
‐Kyohei?
‐Stop making fun of me!
‐Oh, but I wasn't,
my adorable little Yuki!
See, you are making fun of me!
What's that?
‐Huh?
Ahhh!
(bell ringing)
♪
(together)
Hey, what the hell is going on?
(giggling)
Hang on, are those
people friends of yours?
They're not my friends,
but I, but I...
♪
I would certainly love
to be one of them.
(together)
Hey, you, snap out of it!
Don't do anything else to
distance yourself from humanity!
‐Let me go, let me go!
‐Can you not understand?
Those weirdos you so
admire are trespassing.
(shouting)
‐Kyohei!
‐Sunako!
(grunting)
♪
‐They're getting away!
‐Have you noticed that we have
a lot of kidnappings
in this show?
‐Let's go after them!
‐All right!
‐Hey, taxi!
‐That's a tractor!
‐Taxi, please stop!
‐That's a motorcycle.
Taxi, but I don't wanna
pay the night rate!
This isn't the time
to complain about that!
(choir singing)
Incredible, his skin
is like porcelain.
His hair is like silken threads.
So this is Kyohei Takano.
This is my first time
seeing him this close up.
By the way, what is this?
I don't know, it's like
dolphin bycatch in tuna fish.
Or some kind of accident.
‐Should I just throw it away?
‐Hold on.
It's pretty obvious this girl
is a secondary character,
an inconspicuous figure.
I think we have a use for her.
♪
If you don't have
money, get out!
♪
That's why I was concerned
about money, you guys.
We didn't have time
to worry about that.
And now is definitely not the
time to be thinking about it.
‐So, uh, let's see, um...
‐So what should we do?
‐Nay!
(crying and cooing)
The proper way for a lady
to travel at night, nay.
Remember that there are
always evil perpetrators
targeting young maidens, nay.
Consequently, it becomes
apparent that it is necessary
for us to attack them before
they can get to us, nay.
So if you're afraid of
perverts, the best thing to do
is act like a pervert
yourself, nay.
Let's start, make your
eyeballs gleam, nay.
‐Gleaming, nay.
Second, you must
also drool, nay.
‐Drool, nay.
And thirdly, sway your
body back and forth,
and slouch while walking, nay.
‐Slouch, nay, and sway, nay.
Wrong, nay, you guys are
way too dangerous, nay.
♪
(maniacal laughter)
I've always wondered‐‐
‐Why do they show up so often?
‐It gets old.
(together)
Let's pretend we didn't see 'em.
Okay, now we're out in
the middle of nowhere,
but don't you think
Kyohei will find
some way out of this himself?
I guess so, after all,
he's with Sunako.
Yeah, but what would you do
if something happens to them?
Something happens, that's
right, since it's Sunako,
she'll probably
get excited and...
(evil laughter)
♪
Anyway, we'd better
call someone for help.
Uh‐oh, I didn't bring
my cell phone.
‐Neither did I.
‐Me either, we left so fast.
(crickets chirping)
All right, I'll go
find a house nearby.
I'll call my kittens,
and have them come rescue us.
‐Your kittens, huh?
‐Right, see ya later.
‐Be careful.
‐Don't take any side trips.
I should probably be fine!
‐Honeys!
‐Not too reassuring.
Let's just keep moving
forward for now.
(birds chirping)
♪
(screaming)
Ow, my head!
Ahhhh!
Relax, it's a guardian
deity statue.
You sure you wouldn't
have been better off
looking for a house
with Ranmaru?
‐No, I'm fine!
‐Hey.
There's a suspicious
abandoned building.
‐No!
‐I'm gonna check it out.
Then I wanna come
along with you!
I wanna go check out
that place too, okay?
Yuki, listen to me carefully.
You should stay down here
and try to stop a passing car.
Ask 'em for a ride home.
We oughta be just
fine without you.
Nuh‐uh, I'm not going back home!
Okay, I understand,
if I don't find anything
up there I'll catch up
with you soon, sound good?
Good luck.
♪
(leaves rustling)
I'm not scared, I'm not scared.
I'm not, I'm not...
I'm not...
(screaming)
♪
I'm not, I'm not,
I'm not scared.
(barking and whimpering)
Ahhh, help!
Please, Kyohei, please help me.
(tires screeching)
Oh my, if you're out in
this neck of the woods,
you must be one of the gang,
now hurry up and get in!
Huh?
♪
Which store are you from,
where's your uniform?
‐My uniform?
‐Did you forget it?
Here, you can wear
this spare one then.
What?
♪
What is this all about?
It's simple, we want you
to come back, Takano.
‐Huh?
‐When you were in middle school
you passed by our stores
on your way to class,
and the place was
packed with people.
That's right, dozens of girls
would come through here
every day because
they were chasing you.
Don't tell me, are you guys
from the neighborhood‐‐
Shopping arcade, yes,
but it's completely dead
now, and because of that
all the young people
are going elsewhere.
So now we have no choice but to
rely on either God or the devil.
What, are you guys
out of your minds?
Where did you Sunako Nakahara,
I'm taking her home!
She's right here,
she's our sacrifice.
Sacrifice?
♪
At last, the hour is upon us,
let the ceremony begin.
(together)
Hear, hear!
In order to fulfill
our cherished desire,
we hereby offer the blood
of this living creature
to the devil.
It's black magic, how wonderful.
You idiot, don't look
so happy about this!
And you guys, you should know
your method of requesting
divine intervention
is seriously wrong!
Now, it's time for us to
pray in the way we learned
through a correspondence course.
The Path to Becoming Goth:
A Correspondence Course.
‐So no matter who you are‐‐
‐Feel free to ask us‐‐
‐How you too can become goth.
‐Goth‐Goth‐Loli‐Loli!
‐Goth‐Goth!
‐Loli‐Loli!
Everyone in here
is a complete idiot!
(gasping)
Hey, what's wrong?
(giggling)
I want this chair!
Now's not the time, okay?
‐She untied the ropes so easy.
‐She's not human.
Capture her!
Wow, cool table!
Wow cool axe!
(giggling and groaning)
♪
Oh, this is truly magnificent.
I got her!
(cheering)
♪
Don't get in my way!
(rumbling)
♪
(snarling)
Oh my God, is she...
♪
(screaming)
(laughing)
And that's because you
fools attempted witchcraft.
Looks like you guys
summoned the real demon.
Just kidding!
All right then, let me try.
Young lady, I'd like to
have a word with you.
Okay.
‐Hey, wait just a second!
‐No way!
Damn it, nothing there, but
it still looks suspicious.
Now I need to catch
up with Yuki.
Hey, stop!
♪
What the hell is that up there?
Takenaga!
It's only me, I came
to pick you up.
So that means...
Hello again, and
good evening to you.
Yeah, good evening to you too.
‐Hey, did you wait long?
‐Ranmaru?
When I explained what
happened, the only one
who actually offered
to help us was‐‐
Tamao, and here we are!
You were so reckless, don't do
something so dangerous again!
I was really worried
about you, super worried!
‐You big dummy!
‐I'm really sorry,
‐but we have to find Yuki.
‐Ranmaru explained everything.
‐So let us go.
‐Thanks very much.
Of course, it's not bother at
all for my precious friends.
By the way, as far as
troops and artillery,
what do you suppose we
ought to have at the ready?
‐Driver?
‐Yes ma'am, Lady Tamao.
For starters, we
have special forces
and an army of 100
infantry soldiers
equipped with machine guns
and rocket launchers.
We have air, land, and
sea completely covered.
Is our attack satellite
operation all set?
We expect it will
take another 15 minutes
to lock on to the target.
I must apologize,
we're still new at this.
‐I think you did great.
‐You didn't have to go this far.
(cooing)
‐Sunako?
‐Wait a damn minute!
Kyohei!
Where the hell did you take her?
If you'll agree to come back
to our arcade, we'll tell you.
It'll be just like
the good old days.
Buy 10 cartons of tofu and
get a free photo of Takano.
(together)
Yes, I'll buy it!
Buy a melon and a matsutake
mushroom and you'll get
‐Takano's phone number!
‐Yes, I'll buy it!
Buy a snapper and a crab and
we'll tell you Takano's address.
(together)
Yes, I'll buy it!
If you came back to our arcade,
people would come from not only
the neighborhood, but from
all over the country as well.
Your presence will
save our businesses.
Don't give me that crap,
who's fault do you think it is
I had to leave
in the first place?
I'll never go back there!
‐Come back to us.
Kyohei, I'm coming
to save you‐‐ow.
Come back to us,
come back to us.
(shrill screaming)
(phone ringing)
(doorbell chiming)
♪
That noise, I can't
take it anymore!
Please stop, someone
please make it stop!
Come back to us.
So how can I go back
when I don't have a home?
Kyohei?
Kyohei, I'm sorry.
Your mother is tired of this.
Because the truth
is that my parents
are much happier without me.
What a nice family.
That's a lot better
than just being cool.
‐No, Kyohei!
‐What the hell?
(grunting)
Kyohei's a member of our family,
and we're not gonna
let you have him!
‐Yuki?
‐Catch that little kid!
(together)
Yes, sir!
(screaming)
Yuki, grab an axe and
come cut these ropes!
Never mind, just run!
Bakers are best at baking,
and butchers are
best at butchering.
That's true and I'm very scared.
Run for it, Yuki, I'll
be fine, don't worry!
♪
I won't let any of you
lay a finger on Kyohei!
(together)
Aw!
Calm down, it was
just a water drop!
(together)
Aw!
(whimpering)
Right, now bring it on!
So adorable.
It feels kinda
like we're bullying.
After all, we're not
really bad people.
Here's a box‐cutter,
don't cut yourself, okay?
Oh!
Come on, this way!
Yuki, slow down!
♪
(tires screeching)
There's that van!
It's the one that was
used to kidnap Kyohei!
‐Yuki!
‐Hey!
Takenaga, Ranmaru!
So what are Noi and the
rich girl doing here?
When you're in trouble,
there's real strength
‐in numbers, right?
‐Right.
Yuki, how are you, are you hurt?
You scraped the
top of your nose.
I'm just fine,
I mean, after all,
I rescued Kyohei!
‐Huh, no way!
(laughing and clapping)
Ahem!
They followed us!
So go ahead and bring it!
‐I mean, please don't.
‐They're the witchcraft users.
‐Driver?
‐Yes, Lady Tamao.
Driver launcher!
Stop, we see how
big it is, so stop!
‐Driver.
‐As you wish, Lady Tamao.
Ahem, we'll let
you go for today.
Well that's some nerve,
you kidnapped them!
We were defeated, we
lost to your cuteness.
‐To my cuteness?
‐For his sake,
we're going to let you
off this time, Takano,
but don't fool yourself.
That doesn't mean
we've given up.
Whatever, just realize what
you're doing is wrong!
(rooster crowing)
Oh, it's morning!
(mixed remarks)
♪
So anyway, what did he mean,
"lost to your cuteness"?
Did you dress up
like a girl again?
Seriously, your cuteness
works on everyone, Yuki.
‐Your cuteness is invincible.
‐That's truly amazing cuteness.
I'm so totally lame.
♪
You saved me, thanks, Yuki.
(laughing)
♪
All right then,
let's go home now.
All that worrying
made me really hungry.
Why don't we stop at
a family restaurant?
‐I agree!
‐Would it be all right
‐if I asked you a question?
‐What is it?
Do you know where
Miss Sunako went to?
(together)
What?
She isn't here?
♪
I think you oughta
ask her about Kyohei.
I don't want to ask.
I never want to deal with a life
controlled by Kyohei again.
Never again, never!
♪
‐Good day to you.
‐Lady Tamao, it appears
that your precious friend,
Miss Sunako has been kidnapped.
‐Driver!
‐In this case, I suppose
rescuing her would be
the right thing to do.
‐Driver!
‐Yes, Lady Tamao?
‐Giddy up!
‐Yes, Lady Tamao.
Next time on The Wallflower:
The Eye of the Storm Comes Home.
‐Driver bazooka!
‐Giddy up!