Hiroshi here.
Let's see, first
I was kidnapped,
and then some other
people broke in
and kidnapped Kyohei, ne.
I'm not Kyohei, ne.
At any rate,
I'm glad you were okay.
To think they'd go that far.
It's not normal, is it?
No, I guess that's how
popular Kyohei really is.
I'm a little jealous.
Jackass!
It seems Sunako is
the one who's been
kidnapped this time.
Must be nice.
(together)
It's not!
I mean, we completely
forgot about her!
(laughing)
(together)
What an evil look!
Even so, this is still
cute in its own way.
That's one scary
kindergartner.
Yeah, but he was
still cute though.
He sure was a beautiful
little boy, wasn't he?
But then right after
I took this picture he‐‐
Don't take pictures
without asking!
He ran me over
with his tricycle.
To tell you the truth,
I was hurt pretty badly.
(laughing)
(together)
You haven't changed at all!
Shut the hell up.
Yes, but more importantly,
what about Miss Sunako?
That's right, we have
to go find Sunako Nakahara!
Oh, you didn't know?
Your father took
her home with him.
They left a while ago.
Ahh!
(sighs)
Why are you sighing?
She's at your home, isn't she?
That is why.
Look, it's going to
be all right, Takano.
Things are different now
than they were back then.
And your father has returned
from his job posting
away from home.
Sir, I notice that
you've suddenly turned
into a nice person.
Not so fast, kid.
Don't think that we've
given up so easily.
(maniacal laugh)
Hey, what's your
problem anyway?
Ranmaru, I need to
switch clothes with you.
Sure, no problem.
Woo‐oo‐oo!
Yeah, yeah.
Well then, we shall be
glad to give you a ride.
I'm sorry, but...
I have to do this by myself.
Uh, what?
(sighs)
♪
(shriek)
(slurps)
(sighs)
Ah!
What am I doing being
all relaxed like this?
I was easily lured here by...
This house belongs to that
radiant creature's parents!
I mean, there's no doubt that
the whole family is guaranteed
to be radiant, right?
Dazzling.
Dazz dazzling.
Dazz, dazz, dazzling.
(together)
Dazzling, dazzling,
dazz, dazzling, ling!
(screams)
I have to run,
I have to run!
♪
Sunako Nakahara.
So bright!
All right.
Let's go home.
♪
Kyohei.
Kyohei!
No, it's way too radiant.
Huh?
I can't believe it.
Neither one of his
parents is radiant.
I just came here
to pick her up
and I'll be leaving
right away, so don't worry.
But we want to talk to you.
I have nothing
to say to you.
Wait, you haven't
slept, have you?
Why don't you
spend the night?
Your mother even set up
your futon for you.
Oh, really?
I'm surprised that you
haven't gotten rid of it yet.
Kyohei!
(cries)
They're not radiant.
♪
Fine, I'll spend the night here.
That's what you want, isn't it?
Kyohei, hold on.
Your room is...
Hmm?
(shrieks)
All right, I'll
be going home now.
Wait, you don't have
the money to go home!
Well, then I'll just hitchhike.
That statement makes
it obvious that you're
not very self‐aware,
but you should be,
you Taxi Ghost!
So what's a Taxi Ghost?
(gong sounding, screams)
The Road to Womanhood!
The Taxi Ghost is...
(ding)
Blue Sky Cemetery,
please, driver.
Right, Miss,
Blue Sky Cemetery.
Okay, Miss,
we're here now.
(grunts)
Oh!
She's not‐‐
she's not there!
(screams)
We don't want
that kind of lady!
And so, just like that,
no one's ever gonna
give you a ride.
Well, if that's the case,
then I guess I'll just
have to walk home!
You wanna die
in some gutter?
(vocalizing)
(strains)
Just come with me!
All right then,
I'll sleep over here.
You can use the futon.
(groans)
Sleep in the same room
with that radiant creature.
You've gotta be kidding me.
I'll melt for sure!
Die in the gutter or...
melt to death in this room.
Those are my only options here.
(groans)
♪
I'd rather die in the gutter!
(applause)
♪
(screams)
(gasping)
(sighs)
♪
(shrieks)
(panting)
♪
(shrieks)
Are you trying to kill me?!
I'm going home,
I'm going home!
Look, I already told
you that you can't,
but you just don't know when
to give up, do you, damn it?
Well, why should I be
forced to sleep here
in the same room with
you in the first place?
Shut up, will ya?
There is no other room,
so this is the only choice.
I don't want to stay in
a house like this either!
What the heck do you mean,
"a house like this"?
We're in your parents' house.
Just don't leave me here alone.
Huh?
(strains)
Ah, hey, wait a second!
Come back here!
Let me go!
I don't wanna be around
a radiant creature like you,
so just let me leave!
I don't wanna be around.
(echoes)
I don't wanna...
(door closes)
♪
You feel that way, too?
(panting)
I'll die...I'll die.
(water drips)
I'm surprised that you
haven't gotten rid of it yet.
How?
How did this ever happen?
I thought if I brought
his friend here,
Kyohei would come by
to pick her up, so...
Is that so?
Are you happy that
it went as you planned?
Uh...
Are you happy?
‐Well, I...
‐Huh?!
Are you happy now?
Are you, are you?!
(screams)
How on earth did we
ever end up having
such a beautiful
child like him?
Exactly.
Don't talk with
that strange voice!
Huh?
(screams)
You mean you
aren't asleep yet?
How could I
possibly go to sleep?!
It's some type
of unknown life force!
How'd it get in here?
Honey, she's Kyohei's friend,
don't you remember?
Oh, yes, you're
absolutely right.
I want to know how many
people have you sent
to the hospital?
Huh?
So...
has Kyohei been doing
well since he moved
into your aunt's place?
‐I wouldn't know.
‐Huh?
He's so radiant,
I can't ever look
directly at him.
What an unusual girl.
I really do understand.
You understand her?
It's always puzzled me.
How is it possible
for you and I
to have produced
a beautiful child
like Kyohei?
Maybe gene mutations.
Could be supernatural.
You don't have
to go that far.
Yes, I really do understand!
You understand her?
Day after day,
a huge swarm of girls
would descend upon our house.
The phone would be
ringing all day,
and Kyohei was
detained by the police
on assault charges
so many times
I've actually lost count.
But the worst part was
that only the two of us
were living here
by ourselves
in this house for
a very long time.
(maniacal laugh)
Huh?
Meanwhile, during all
that difficult time,
this man was living
elsewhere because of his job
spending his time
flirting with young girls!
Just who the hell do you
think you are, mister?
That's not true!
I swear it's not true!
I was the only one
who had to deal
with all of the
frustration and anxiety,
sitting around here
getting uglier every day!
You really piss me off!
Oh, please stop!
She's just like me!
And because of that,
I always ended up
saying awful things
to Kyohei even though
I obviously knew
that none of this
was his fault.
But back then,
I was a little bit crazy.
Oh.
Yes, dear, what's wrong?
(clears throat)
Huh?
Oh!
♪
Too bright!
Huh?
♪
What did you want
to talk to me about?
Well, you see, I...
I just wanted to apologize
to you for the way...
(whimpering)
♪
You really piss me
off, you know that?
Why the hell did you ever
come back here anyway?
‐Honey!
‐Huh?
So, is that what you
wanted to talk to me about?
No, that's not it.
Please, Kyohei!
If I piss you off so much,
then you should
never have had me.
What am I going to do now?
This is terrible!
So this must be
what it was like
when I was away from home.
Hmm?
Damn, that Ranmaru,
these shoes of his
are a pain in the ass.
(doorbell rings)
Huh?
(shrieking girls)
My perfect Kyohei's visiting!
What?!
If I should hear
"Kyohei is in the north,"
then I'll be there just so
I can see his perfect face, ne.
♪
And if I should happen
to hear that Kyohei
is in the south,
then I'll be right there
just so I can listen
to his heavenly voice, ne.
Hold everything!
As it happens, Kyohei ne
is in the east, ne.
And yet, Kyohei is
also in the west, ne.
♪
Goth‐Goth!
Loli‐Loli Goth‐Goth.
Loli‐Loli.
Sigh.
♪
Goth‐Goth Loli‐Loli.
(phone ringing)
(excited chatter)
♪
(screams)
I can't take it anymore,
I can't take it anymore!
Now, calm down, honey.
Get a hold of yourself.
You're his mother.
Uh, Mother...
Sunako, Sunako!
Hello Sunako.
♪
My goodness, what on
earth happened to your room?
What's going on
in here, Sunako?
I like it this way, Mom.
Huh?!
Sunako seems
depressed lately.
It's more like
she's scary.
Let's not hang out
with her anymore.
I do seriously wonder
how you've been raising
your daughter
at home, Mrs. Nakahara.
Honestly, ma'am,
I just don't understand
what your problem
with my daughter is.
(shrieks)
Right there.
Just look, that's her!
You know what they
say about their place?
They all say it's haunted.
I wonder if this is normal,
because her mother's so young.
♪
Don't let that
stuff get you down,
you just need to be
yourself, okay, Sunako?
You know your mother
loves you very much
no matter what.
Oh?
(chuckles)
(phone rings, doorbell chimes)
Mother.
I can't take it anymore,
I can't take it anymore!
It was so nice
and peaceful here
while he was away!
Honey, your face is looking
really scary right now.
Scary?
Well, what I really meant‐‐
I mean, I was just
trying to say...
I'm scary?
Of course not.
It was merely
a figure of speech!
Who the hell are
you calling "scary"?
Like I said, it was merely
a figure of speech, that's all!
That's exactly why I don't
want to be around Kyohei!
I become more
and more hateful
and then I get uglier
and uglier as well!
It's all!
Everything is all his fault.
It's all because of him.
And I wish that he
would just disappear!
Oh.
("Disappear" echoes)
♪
She wants me to disappear.
Is that the kind
of thing that you were
always saying to Kyohei?
It's because I just don't know
what I'm supposed to do.
Oh, God!
But he was only
a middle school student.
Hey, what was
that loud noise?
(shrieks)
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
(grunting)
What is it now?
(screams)
Hey, where are you going?
Ahh!
Wha...
(grunting)
Ah.
(gong sounding, screams)
The Road to Womanhood!
If the mirror in your bathroom
ever becomes fogged up,
what's the best way
for you to handle it?
Squeaky, squeaky?
Squeaky, squeaky!
Squeaky!
Wrong!
I mean, do you guys
even use a mirror?
Just put a few drops
of shampoo on a sponge,
and wipe!
It's like magic!
It doesn't last long,
but it works as a quick fix
for a fogged mirror!
And you know a lady must check
her entire body in the mirror.
Speaking of which, dear.
Lately you have...
I know, I've
gained some weight.
Just don't look in the
mirror and you'll be fine.
Oh!
How can you even gain weight?
(gong sounding)
♪
The thing is, if you're
really suffering that much...
(grunts)
...you'll feel better
if you don't desire
to be attractive.
Desire to be...attractive?
If there aren't
any mirrors...
then there also
aren't any chances
you will have
to see your face.
If you don't ever
see your face,
you don't have to compare
yourself to others.
I call that
a happy life indeed.
Huh, huh, huh?
Huh?!
I'm glad I was able
to share this with you.
I mean, after all,
you and I are peers,
‐aren't we?
‐Huh?
What's the matter?
But I don't wanna
be your peer!
I don't wanna be
peers with an unknown
life force like this creature!
Calm down, dear.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Forgot?
What is it now?
(shouting)
Ah!
Let's go ahead and throw
away all these nasty cosmetics
while we're at it.
Please don't do it.
Anything but that!
They're expensive!
They're luxury items!
They're important!
(girls scream)
What's that?
‐Right up there!
‐Is that Kyohei?
I guess not.
(together)
No, it's not.
It's not Kyohei, ne.
Those are really, really...
...important to me!
(strains)
Huh?
What is it,
what's the matter?
I think I just saw something
really scary for a second there.
(screams)
Anything but that!
Give it back!
♪
(together)
It can't possibly
be a ghost, ne?
You girls have
finally summoned it!
Hey, who are you guys?
We're representatives of the
Spiritual Phenomena Institute.
Really?
That's correct.
Recently, girls
who've approached Kyohei
have experienced
supernatural phenomena
in which they were possessed
by mysterious spirits!
It's been said that
those who pursue him
too tenaciously
become covered in blood,
every one of them!
Driver!
♪
What is this?
When did this get here?
That's the spiritual
phenomenon energy
measuring device!
(motor hums)
Spiritual phenomenon
energy search, switch on.
♪
Spiritual phenomenon
energy has been detected.
Everyone here will be
possessed for certain!
It's coming very soon!
It'll be here
before you know it!
It is incredibly strong.
(wails)
Help me!
We're out of here!
I'm shaking, ne.
Me too, ne.
Goose bumps, ne.
I peed, ne.
(together)
We're out of here too, ne.
We did it!
It's a good thing
we asked them
for their costumes.
Oh, yeah, I knew
something like this
was gonna happen.
Sure you did.
You sure put on a great
performance today, Tamao.
That was incredible.
I thank you very much.
That's all, driver,
you may go now.
Everything's taken
care of, Lady Tamao.
Job well done, driver.
(panting)
♪
This is my favorite
Chanel No.9.
Hey!
Honey, you need to take
a look out the window.
It's amazing!
Everyone's gone.
Uh?
You mean that
no one's there?
Huh?
(laughs)
Those guys!
They're the best!
It really has gotten
quiet out there.
Please, Sunako,
where are all the mirrors?
Kyo...
♪
Let's go home,
Sunako Nakahara.
Kyohei, just stay in the
house a little while longer.
Enough already.
All those noisy
girls are gone now,
so I'll go and make
us some tea, all right?
Forget it.
You're not ever
going to see me again.
Don't worry.
But that...
isn't what I was
going to say to you.
♪
Kyohei...
I have really wanted
to apologize to you for‐‐
for a long time, but I...
I...
(cries)
Huh?
♪
This is still
your home, darling.
(cries)
Honey...
♪
Hey, uh, Dad?
Huh?
I need money
for the train.
‐Hey.
‐Yeah?
I heard a lot of noise
in the house earlier.
What were you doing?
Busted!
I put all the mirrors
in the house in a bag.
What for?
I thought your mom
would feel better
if she gave up
being attractive too.
Brother.
Well, at least you
didn't actually break
any of them, right?
So, did you try
to be nice about it?
(growls)
That really doesn't
make any difference,
you moron.
I'm already used to it.
Besides, she really is
better off without me.
Are you serious?
But your mother is...
You are too.
Uh?
It's the truth.
You hate being around
me too, don't you?
I don't wanna be around
a radiant creature like you!
So just let me leave!
I'm sorry about that.
Huh?
Kyohei!
Sunako!
We're over here!
(chuckles)
I didn't know what
was going to happen.
I was so worried
about you two.
Thanks a lot, you guys.
I mean, you done good.
Sure, don't be
so formal.
(laughing)
Come on, Kyohei,
hurry up and get in.
I think I'm gonna
take the train.
Huh?
Why are you doing that?
Mm, no particular reason.
All right, Kyohei.
If we get back
home first,
you have to treat
us to ramen, okay?
Sure.
(engine rumbles)
So, it's going to
be a race, is it?
Driver.
Yes, of course, Lady Tamao.
Driver scramble!
(laughter)
Uh...
♪
It's the truth.
You hate being around
me too, don't you?
Forget it.
You're not ever going
to see me again.
Don't worry.
(engine revs)
♪
(beeps)
All right.
♪
So, where should I go now?
The radiant creature's
no longer around.
I should be happy
and content,
but why do I feel so‐‐
Sunako!
This is a long monologue.
What is this,
Greek tragedy?
Next time on The Wallflower,
"The Eye of the Storm Strays."
I know nothing!
I know absolutely nothing!
(together)
You definitely know something!
♪