♪
Hiroshi here.
This is Sunako.
She's a lovely girl.
She always
takes the time
to talk to
the three of us.
Okay, a lovely
girl who talks to
human anatomical
dummies, huh.
Sure, it's just like
playing with dolls.
Playing with dolls?
They are dolls
in a way, right?
That's correct.
And we eat, too.
But dolls aren't
supposed to eat
and you can't
do it either!
♪
(screaming)
(giggling)
♪
(cackling)
(chewing)
Hi there,
I'm coming in.
Oh, hiya, Noi.
Where's Takenaga?
He should be back
any time now.
So, can I wait here then?
Of course, I'll
go make some coffee.
Oh, don't
trouble yourself.
I'd like two
sugars, please.
(thumping)
(screaming)
You okay, Yuki?
What's wrong?
(screaming)
It's everywhere!
It was so scary,
she's just creepy!
What happened
to your face?
Nothing, really.
This is what happens from
locking yourself in your room
and eating junk.
And haven't you gained
a little weight, too?
I don't know.
What are you going to do
with that first aid kit?
I'm going to put
some of this medicine
on the pimples.
No way, you can't use
insect bite cream!
‐(gong ringing)
‐Ay‐ay‐ay.
The Road to Womanhood!
You have to understand
that girl's skin
is very delicate.
You need a
well‐balanced diet,
moderate exercise,
frequent face cleansing,
and a daily skin regimen.
The fact is, beauty
doesn't happen overnight.
Do you understand, Sunako?
‐She left a while ago.
Uh.
(screaming)
(giggling)
(sighs)
Pardon me, Lady Tamao,
but it's been almost an hour.
Perhaps you should go
ahead and ring the bell?
I can't do that.
You see, the last time
I saw Ranmaru,
I struck him in the face
with my schoolbag
really hard.
I'm too ashamed
to face him
after that awful incident.
So it has to look as
though I just happen to be
passing by here today.
So, are you
waiting for Ranmaru?
Who, me, I di...
I'm sorry, I
guess I should have
introduced myself.
I am Ranmaru's
housemate, Takenaga.
It's very nice
to meet you.
‐And I'm‐‐
‐You're his fiancée, right?
Please come
inside and sit down.
Oh, but I do‐‐
Hey, Noi, I didn't know
that you were here.
Uh‐huh, Takenaga and
I are going to plan
our date together.
Sounds like
you're having fun.
I was wondering
if you've ever been
to this place
before, Ranmaru?
Yeah, actually I have.
But that location's
really crowded.
If you're going
somewhere with Takenaga,
I think it'd be best
to choose a quieter place.
I see.
That's my Ranmaru.
You are the
king of dating.
Ha ha, well,
it all comes down
to the advanced
planning, you know.
The true skill comes
in how you handle
the second half of the
romantic part of the date.
The second half
of rom‐‐rom‐‐rom,
romantic part
of the date.
Ooh, look at all
the lights, Takenaga.
The night sky
is so beautiful.
Yes, Noi, it certainly
is a lovely evening.
‐But...
‐But what, go on.
You're so much more
beautiful than that,
my darling, Noi.
Oh, please stop it,
stop it, Takenaga.
‐Noi, darling.
‐Stop it, Takenaga,
‐Not in a public place!
‐Oh, come on, sweetheart.
Come on, come on, baby.
‐Come on, yeah.
‐I can't.
But there's no one
watching us, sweetie pie.
Hey, why does it
have to be like that?
I know that's
what you want.
Oh, no I don't,
you pervert, now stop it.
It's a little too‐‐
I'm home, are
you here, Ranmaru?
They look
so good together.
♪
The coffee's
ready for you.
(crashing)
Um, would you
please pardon me?
Are you just gonna
let them go like that?
That is usually how it
goes with Noi, though.
I don't care, it's
not like she and I
are actually
dating or anything.
But that girl came
all the way over here
just to see you, Ranmaru.
Right, Takenaga?
It's none of my business.
Why don't you go
ask her yourself?
What's that, you say?
You're not
jealous, are you?
Hang on a second, you
need to stop lowering me
to the same level as you.
♪
Do something, Kyohei.
You just need to
leave them alone.
(yawns)
(crying)
Help me, Sunako!
All right!
Oh, Sunako,
it's terrible!
You won't believe
what just happened!
I saw Takenaga
with some other girl!
(sobbing)
‐Um, excuse me.
‐Huh?
♪
Ah, got a beautiful
pretty girl in my room!
What?
You mean that you're
Ranmaru's fiancée?
Not really,
I just met him
as a prospective
marriage partner one time.
I'm sorry, I must have
made you uncomfortable.
Oh no, honestly, it was
extremely indecent of me
to have been
standing right next to
a man like that anyway.
Ha, shita, nou.
You'd be facing
a tough future
married to a
ladies' man like him.
Don't you think it's
best to call it off
while you still can?
But marriage is totally
out of the question.
I already know
that he wouldn't have
the slightest interest
in a girl like me.
And I'm also quite
aware of the fact
that he has
many girlfriends.
That Ranmaru's very kind,
so I suspect he's been
waiting for me to reject
the marriage
proposal officially.
And I've been taking
advantage of that fact
and prolonging
the amount of time
before I give
him my answer.
Why is that?
I'd still like us
to be connected somehow.
Even just as a would‐be
fiancée, he once met.
(grumble)
That's so sweet, but I'm
sure you're the only person
who seriously likes
that knucklehead.
All right,
if that's how it is,
then I will make him stop
being such a ladies' man.
I swear I'm going to make
Ranmaru crazy about you!
Oh no, you don't have to
do all that just for me.
Stop being so timid.
Because self‐confidence
makes a girl beautiful.
You won't be a girl
if you're not polished.
You must aim to
become the type of girl
that Ranmaru likes.
Um, okay then.
Sunako, are you
ready to do this?
‐Let's go!
‐Where are we going?
Yes, where are we going?
First we're gonna
visit a beauty salon
to achieve beautiful
skin and a great figure.
Oh, a beauty salon?
Well, if that's the case
then... driver!
Driver, I would like you
to take me and my friends
to my mother's
company right away.
Certainly, madam.
(tires screeching)
Make yourselves
at home, ladies.
Uh.
(giggling)
How fabulous,
I've always wanted
to check this place out.
And this beauty salon
is one of the
best spots in town.
This flirty bun‐mun is one
of the chestnuts you found?
No, that's not right.
Oh, I knew that.
I knew that already,
but I was...
Well, ladies,
please come this way.
Oh, that young lady's
with us as well.
What?
This is my house,
I am not outside.
I am not outside,
Now, madam,
if you'll just
take off all your
clothes and put these on.
(screaming)
What...did...you...say?
Uhhh.
I said take
off your clothes
and put on these
special undergarments.
(screaming)
Allow anyone
to see my naked body?
I'd sooner die!
(screaming)
She's a friend
of Miss Tamao's,
we're gonna do our best
and transport her
to the world of beauty.
Right.
I'd sooner die.
Please wait!
Please change.
This is a beauty salon.
Just change.
Don't touch me!
This is a beauty salon.
It's a beauty salon.
This is a mud bask, nay.
Taking care
of our skin, nay.
I'm sorry to
bother you ladies,
but will you be
paying for your services
in cash today?
If we are
able to capture
the beauty of the world
successfully, nay.
The cost will be
of no concern
to us whatsoever, nay.
And then you will
paid in full, nay.
There's nothing for
you to worry about, nay.
Okay, so what you're
really saying is...
For the four
Goth‐Loli sisters
who move seamlessly
back and forth
between the Earthly
and hellish realms,
it is unnecessary
to possesses such
unrefined things as money.
Unnecessary.
Goth‐Goth,
Loli‐Loli.
‐Goth‐Goth, Loli‐Loli.
‐While you may not need
unrefined money,
we most certainly do!
(loud crashing)
We're gonna make you
pay for this, nay.
This our original relaxing
massage oil, enjoy.
Uuhh.
♪
Fat on my thigh!
(screaming)
Fat on my stomach!
I wonder if Miss Sunako
is doing all right?
Don't worry, she's fine.
Help me!
Please help me!
♪
Someone help me!
Sunako's screaming again.
Do you really believe
she's still all right?
The truth about
her is that Sunako
is very pretty,
cool, and strong,
but she just doesn't
have much self‐confidence.
Maybe so, but I'm sure
that one of these days
she'll come to realize
her own true charm.
You're right, and I'd
better keep up with her.
Yeah, me too.
Keep your heads
held high, ladies.
Hmm, I don't understand
what you're
so excited about.
This is just
one of those times
when you're supposed
to get excited
and yell out yeah!
Yeah!
♪
Oh my, your skin
is so flawlessly
smooth and polished.
It looks just
like an eggshell.
Oh, please, I mean
look at your skin.
(giggling)
♪
On to the
next one, ladies.
(screaming)
♪
On to the next one.
Here's our next stop.
It has mirrored walls.
Would you please excuse me?
(screams)
I'm going home!
Ahh, is it this way?
(screaming)
♪
(gasping)
Oh, Miss Sunako,
are you all right?
(giggling)
Un, deux, trois.
♪
(gong ringing)
(screaming)
The Road to Womanhood!
We aspire to carry
ourselves like celebrities,
but in the end,
we can't help
reacting like commoners.
Do you really think so?
Which one would you
pick, tea or coffee?
I suppose I would
prefer to have tea.
I suppose I'd prefer
to have coffee.
Wrong!
Mimicking her won't
change a thing about you.
What kind would you like?
I get to pick what kind?
Wrong!
Well, let me think
about that a moment.
Mmm, I believe
I'd like to have
a cup of orange
pekoe, please.
It seems more elegant
if you pause and think
before giving your answer.
And you can craft your
own celebrity‐like line
while you think.
(clock ticking)
♪
You got it, baby.
Wrong!
Your answer isn't like
a celebrity at all!
(gong ringing)
One‐two, one‐two.
So are you ready
to call it a day?
Wow, we certainly did
do a lot of work today.
You have to
do this every day.
Wha?
After baking, apply
facial toner to your face
and stretch your body.
Before bed, perform
facial exercises,
then apply face cream,
moisturizer, and lip balm.
When you wake up,
wash your face
then apply toner and
moisturizer, okay?
But why on earth
would you spend
so much of your
time and energy
doing all that stuff?
Why do I do all that?
I do it so Takenaga
will say I look beautiful.
(lightning crashing)
Uh, I just don't get it.
Would you teach me
flower arrangement
and the tea ceremony?
Oh yes, gladly.
Dammit, you put sauce on
my pork cutlet, didn't you?
You always put sauce
on your pork cutlet.
Well, I felt like having
salt and lemon today instead.
Then you should have
said that before.
Would you two
stop it already?
How pathetic, I can't
believe that you two
are fighting
over some chicks.
‐We are not!
He acts like a jerk
just because he's smart.
Oh yeah, well he's
a self‐centered brat.
‐I must admit,
‐you both have a point.
What did you say to me!
(yelling)
♪
I still don't get it.
Why would any
girl make an effort
for guys who
act like they do?
(doorbell ringing)
Good evening, Miss Sunako.
I bought a little
something for you.
Huh?
This is a great product
for skin problems.
Please feel free
to give it a try
if you like.
And try to use it
every day if possible.
You didn't have to
trouble yourself like this.
Oh, would you like to
come in and have some tea?
Oh, thank you very much.
I appreciate the offer,
but I think I'd
better not today.
However, I'd certainly
like to come back
and visit with
you and Miss Noi
some other time.
Uh, would you really?
It isn't good to keep
on running away, is it?
It's bad to
keep turning away
just because I lack
self‐confidence, isn't it?
And I didn't
even realize that
until after
I met Miss Noi.
I will try to do my best.
♪
Well, you take care now.
Hey, I'll cook
a feast up for you
when you come back.
(giggle)
♪
(dishes rattling)
Whoa, why are we
having a feast?
What's going
on here, Sunako?
What, we're having a feast?
Wow, it all
looks so delicious!
Yeah, this looks great.
Oh, I get it.
Sunako must be
trying to get
Takenaga and
Ranmaru to make up.
She's so thoughtful.
Make up for what?
It's not like we were
fighting or anything.
But he has been trying
to pick a fight with me.
Huh, you're
the one who's been
trying to pick
a fight with me.
Come on, can't
you guys cut it out?
How many days has
it been, you two?
I don't have any idea...
...what you're
even talking about.
You guys!
(doorbell ringing)
I'll get it!
At least Yuki's escaping.
You're in denial.
You just can't
accept the fact
that Noi and I look good
together, now can you?
You're not
honest with yourself
so you're taking
it out on me.
You're behaving quite
childishly, Ranmaru.
Ahh, what a
pain in the ass!
Why don't you
guys just start
punching each
other already?
Because that
would hurt, duh.
We don't have any reason
to punch each other.
Ha, I can't believe
two guys your age
are bitching at
each other like this
over a couple of chicks.
It annoys me!
We're not bitching
at each other!
Besides, it's
none of my business
who Noi looks
good with anyway!
That's fine with me, I
neither like nor dislike her.
Uh?
‐Uh?
♪
Okay, okay, okay then.
We have quite a
feast here today,
so let's dig in, guys.
Come on, all together
like friends now.
Okay, all right?
♪
(growling)
(screaming)
I don't have anything to
feed the likes of you!
Now get out!
Hey, no fair, how come
you threw me out, too?
I'm hungry!
Here, this is just for you.
Me too!
Here I have some
collagen‐rich (unintelligible).
Stir fried oysters to
help improve circulation.
And then there's‐‐
All these things
are considered
good for a woman's body.
I'm extremely impressed.
I did research the topic.
I hope you like it.
Oh, Sunako!
(sobbing)
It's so delicious!
(chewing, giggling)
Thank you so much, Sunako,
it's really good.
Am I right, this is totally
delicious, isn't it?
Oh, yes, it certainly is.
(sobbing)
♪
I guess I always
knew the truth,
but the body is
really honest, isn't it?
I told myself that
I wasn't going to cry,
and yet...
Then I thought that Takenaga
and I were going steady.
But I guess...
I guess I was wrong.
(wailing)
There's no need to cry.
You see, ladies, it will
no longer be necessary
for you to keep wasting
your precious energy
on horrible men
like that anymore.
Honestly, Sunako?
Now come with me
across infinite space to
a wonderland of darkness.
♪
No, no, no, no!
It may be unrequited love,
but I do like Takenaga.
I can't go over to
the other side just yet.
‐No?
‐The truth is, I still...
I've still done nothing.
Even though Miss Noi
did teach me I
needed to have courage,
and Miss Sunako
helped to cheer me up,
I haven't done a thing.
But you know Miss‐‐
My name's Tamao.
That's my name,
I'm not Miss anybody.
I'm Tamao Kikunoi.
All right then,
Tamao and Sunako,
we can all do
this together, yeah!
Okay, Noi, yeah!
Uh, me too.
(fighting)
♪
Ranmaru?
I'm well aware
that you probably
wouldn't ever want to
deal with someone like me,
but I... but I
still like you.
♪
Aren't you gonna say
something to her, Ranmaru?
So, ladies' man,
where's your
big con artist
speech now, huh?
Well it's...complicated.
I still don't
know whether
I actually
like you or not, so.
What can I do?
You moron, what
the hell kind of thing
is that to say to her?
That's all right, Yuki.
♪
I'll let you know
when I realize
if I like you or not.
♪
(sobbing)
Grrr.
♪
You finally did it,
Tamao, congratulations.
Excuse me, I apologize.
He made me angry,
I didn't mean it.
Oh, thank you,
thank you, Takenaga!
(stomachs growling)
♪
Uh, now it
actually feels like
I'm being mean to everyone.
Go ahead and eat, everybody.
Yeah!
(giggling)
It's ridiculous.
This male and female thing
can be really hard
to understand sometimes.
More importantly...
I'm starving!
Let me at that food!
You guys, how about
going out on a double date?
‐Not ever!
How about inviting
Sunako and Kyohei
to make it a triple date?
‐I'd rather die!
Come on, you guys, I'm sure
it would be a lot of fun.
Excuse me, everybody,
but have you totally
forgotten about me?
(together)
You can stay home!
Hey, how about a
date with Josephine?
No way, that'd
be even worse!
♪
‐Josephine's getting married?
‐Congratulations!
‐Who's she marrying?
‐Bones, not bones!
Is it true love
or was it arranged?
Let's prepare
for the ceremony!
Uh, Sunako, what's that?
Is that a dress?
She's finally
wearing a dress!
Next time
on The Wallflower,
Dream: Mutual Love.
A dress, yes.
(screams)
Don't force yourself!