Hiroshi here.
I am dancing more
than usual these days.
But that's because
it feels like some sort
of overwhelmingly
incredible power
is coming closer and
closer all the time!
Expel evil spirits
and promote our welfare!
(screams)
♪
I told them not
to make it painful.
‐(doorbell chimes)
‐It's me, Noi!
I brought some cake!
Let's all fight over it
together, okay, you guys?
(engine revving)
(scream)
♪
(gasps)
It's...Auntie!
‐What's goin'‐‐
‐(scream)
(thuds)
Uh...hi, Auntie.
Emergency!
(sirens wailing)
‐What's going on?
‐I'm sleepy!
(screaming)
Are you in there, Sunako?
Open this door!
I'm not going to, I can't,
there's no friggin' way,
I can't do this...
♪
Make it extra‐large,
s'il vous plaît.
Roger.
‐(slamming thud)
‐(scream)
What...is this?
No, don't look!
Uh, um...this is...
(indistinct crosstalk)
Just...
Just look at that!
♪
(wailing)
What for?
Um...uh...
Have some cake
if you like, it's salty.
Sunako!
Why don't we go to a spa?
Huh?
I've arranged to
unveil you at a party
the day after tomorrow.
Is that okay?
Why so suddenly?
Being self‐centered, as always.
‐Do you want me to whip you?
‐No, ma'am!
Let's begin by getting
rid of stuff like this!
(screech)
♪
Su‐‐Suna‐‐
(screams)
♪
Why...why is Sunako so...
Please have some
tea if you like,
but it's not hot anymore.
Like it or not,
Sunako's much better
than she was before.
Right, now she's becoming‐‐
or getting settled closer to‐‐
becoming a lady!
Yeah, we're working two percent
faster than the leading brands.
She cleans and does
laundry better than anyone,
and she cooks like a pro!
It's funny, but I don't
recall ever having asked you
to turn my beloved niece
Sunako into a housewife.
No, ma'am, you didn't.
I had no idea!
But I must get Sunako to that
party the day after tomorrow
no matter what!
Heh, don't gimme that crap
after you suddenly show up
out of the blue.
You need to give her
a little more time.
Would she be ready in two days
if I gave her
a little more time?
Auntie, do you remember
when we first moved in here,
you told us all kinds of things,
but you were still
watching over us.
As you did with us,
you should treat Sunako
‐with patience and dignity.
‐No way.
First of all,
when I foolishly let you
degenerates move in here,
I was totally
out of my mind,
I mean, what was I...
(voice speeds up to gibberish)
No way.
No lecture for me, thank you.
♪
(whimpers)
Auntie.
If you've got
something to say to her‐‐
(screams)
‐‐then you need to say
whatever it is to her face.
(angry gibberish)
I can't stand this, I can't.
Please try to hang on, Noi.
Why am I still here?
There ya go.
(gasps)
Sunako!
Are you excited?
It'll be a beautiful
and fabulous party!
Geez, why didn't you say no
right away like you always do?
♪
Say no?
Would you say no even
if I begged you this way?
She's ultra radiant!
Another nosebleed!
It's getting worse!
Break, you have to break now!
Listen.
Don't you remember you managed
to tolerate looking pretty
a couple times before?
Maybe you can put up
with it just one more time?
Uh‐uh!
I know.
What if I could
offer you a reward
if you can do it again?
Re‐ward?
What do you want?
Some banned video?
Or perhaps some internal
organs for Hiroshi?
Uh‐uh!
No thanks.
What I want is to do
something fun with Auntie.
Huh?
Will you become a normal...
Mm‐hm!
‐Will you become a normal‐‐
‐Normal housewife?
Yes, Auntie will become
a normal house‐‐what?
Mm‐hm!
(unhinged laughter)
She was so shocked that
she completely lost it.
What, do you mean that's
really all you want?
Yes!
All right, then.
If doing that's going to
help make you into a lady,
‐then it'll be an easy task.
‐Oh, really?
‐Costume, s'il vous plaît.
‐Roger.
♪
What do you think?
Maid service!
‐(exclaims)
‐I don't get it.
I don't get it at all!
What is supposed to be
housewifey about that?
I don't look like a housewife?
Putting your
appearance aside for now,
can you actually
behave like a housewife?
Well, my maids took care
of all the housework
when I first got married.
Then I traveled the
world with my business,
so I've never done a single
chore around the house.
Jealous!
Auntie, I'll show you how.
So why don't we try doing
the housework together?
‐Together?
‐When it's nice outside,
you enjoy the sunlight
and air out the futons.
On rainy days,
you sit quietly in front
of the fireplace and knit.
You enjoy your
day‐to‐day life
and cook delicious meals.
And now we're going to indulge
in that placid
lifestyle together.
Lovely, such a lovely lifestyle!
‐Auntie!
‐Sunako!
Does this mean
they made a deal?
Now our rent's gonna be free.
I can't believe
the day's coming
when I get to clean
and do laundry with Auntie.
I mean, I just...can't wait!
I'll start down the road
to housewifeliness tomorrow.
Housewife, housewife, woo‐hoo!
Um, I know I shouldn't
say it, but...
I'm just not sure about this.
It's just that I‐‐
‐I agree.
‐Ditto.
(gong ringing)
♪
Morning comes for two women
with drastically different
images of a housewife.
You pour the detergent
here and press the switch.
The machine will do
everything else automatically.
Okay!
(applause)
‐Boys, I'm exhausted.
‐Already?
‐So next is‐‐
‐Why don't we have some tea?
Seriously?
But there're so many
things we need to do.
Huh?
I'm gonna go vacuum now,
and I want you to hang these
clothes on the line to dry.
Then when you're done with that,
I want you to do
another load of laundry.
Sure.
Well, I have
a bad feeling about‐‐
Stop right there.
Sunako's having fun.
You were right, Noi.
You know what?
Sunako must really
like Auntie a lot.
(giggling)
(humming over vacuum's roar)
Oh, we're going digital now‐‐
Sunako, do you need any help?
No, but you might
want to help Auntie.
Oh, speaking of Auntie,
I saw her put the dirty laundry
in the limousine earlier
‐and then drive off.
‐What?
‐Drive where?
‐To the shopping arcade,
‐she said.
‐You coulda told us sooner.
My bad.
Auntie!
Time it took for Auntie
to abandon housework:
Two minutes and
seventeen seconds.
I knew something like
this would happen.
My bad!
♪
Where are you, Auntie?
Ah, hello!
(scream)
‐I knew you'd slack off.
‐I'm not slacking.
I was doing laundry.
I've taken everything
to the cleaners.
Since they said it was
going to take a few days,
I bought replacement clothes,
just look at all the goodies.
Hello, madam, see our meat?
‐What's that?
‐The highest quality
domestic beef.
100 grams for 10,000 yen.
This tuna costs 500,000 yen.
Half a dozen matsutake
mushrooms, 20,000 yen each.
I'll take them all,
s'il vous plaît.
Auntie!
Today you're only
supposed to buy
some squid at the fish market
and some daikon radish
at the grocer.
That's boring.
That's entirely
beside the point.
Fine, I'll just have one daikon.
Here.
That's 180 yen.
Use this.
But, miss, we only take
cash, not phone cards.
Never mind, just forget it!
You know I haven't ever
shopped on foot before.
My goodness, Sunako.
Why, young man, you over there!
‐Yes?
‐Will you carry these groceries?
Huh?
‐With pleasure.
‐What?!
Never mind us, please don't
pay any attention to her,
have a nice day.
Housewives are not supposed
to enslave passersby, okay?
Hm...hm...hm?
Oh, never mind!
♪
(marveling)
Wow, it looks like a movie set.
Since Sunako told me we were
going to have oden today,
we set it up like this.
‐Oden?
‐You need to wear a doterra too.
Dote‐‐I do?
Kotatsu eaters
and doterra robes.
Together, they're
the embodiment of...
‐Japanese winter!
‐But it's spring right now.
Okay, I'm going to put
on a doterra robe!
♪
So what do you think?
All right.
Let's go make oden together.
‐No thanks.
‐Why not?
Because your fake nails
might come off.
(sighs)
Yoo‐hoo!
You're going to attend the party
the day after
tomorrow now, right?
Why would you go that far
to show off, I don't get it.
(screams)
I just wanted to have
fun with Sunako too,
is that so terrible?
Because I haven't been...
Huh, how come?
‐Because...
‐'Cause why?
It's simmering.
The oden's simmering
and it's ready to eat now!
Uh...
♪
(stammers)
Why so radiant?!
Sunako!
(gasping)
♪
I just can't do this.
Just as you can never
become a housewife,
I can never become
a real lady, Auntie.
I guess there's just no point
in kidding ourselves anymore.
What are you talking about?
We live in two different
worlds to begin with.
I don't care.
That world suits you
much better, Auntie.
‐What world?
‐Which one?
Suna!
Goodnight, everyone.
♪
Well, anybody could have
figured out from the beginning
that this idea was
never going to work.
Kyohei!
There's something I've
always wanted to know.
I keep wondering why
on Earth you asked us
to turn Sunako into a lady
in the first place.
What?
Yeah, I wondered about that too.
Because you'd be much better
at turning someone into a lady.
I was afraid.
(exclaiming)
♪
I don't want anyone
coming in my room!
What happened to you, Sunako?
Nothing, just go away
and leave me alone!
Sunako.
And I got really scared,
because I was watching
the Sunako that I knew
changing into someone else.
So you only wanted to see
the things that you
liked about her, huh?
‐That's convenient.
‐You're out of line,
stop it, Kyohei.
You faced up to her
for two seconds,
and already, you're
about to give up?
Listen, lady.
The road to womanhood
is long and hard.
It's a tour of hell!
Kyohei.
Tour of hell?
Sounds weird.
I was only trying to
explain what kind of hell
Sunako has to go through
in order to be able to‐‐
It's still weird.
Look.
She isn't the same little
girl you knew back then.
It's a slow process,
but she has changed.
Right.
She's completely
different than before.
Oh, well...
I guess she's happy
with herself now.
I'm so glad.
Auntie, why don't you go
ahead and pick one man
to settle down with
and be happy yourself?
Ladies need love.
Ranmaru's right.
How much longer are you
planning to date multiple guys?
You see...
the best man for me...
has already passed away.
(gasping)
(weeping)
♪
My dear.
Sunako?
♪
You see?
The person your Auntie
loves best is gone.
(weeping)
I wish you wouldn't cry.
I'm gonna cry,
I'm gonna cry!
I'm going to cry enough
tears for you too, Auntie.
I'm just‐‐I'm just a little kid,
so I can cry for you, Auntie.
♪
A good woman
shouldn't cry so easily.
♪
A lady should never let
others see her tears,
because those tears
are much more beautiful
than any jewels in this world.
Understand?
Uh‐huh.
Good girl.
Thank you.
Thank you!
(all crying)
♪
It seems like
she's gotten stronger,
like I always wished.
God might punish me
if I wish for too much.
So please continue
to look after her.
♪
I'd better get going now,
and so you'll understand,
have a nice day.
Looks like she's
in a normal limo.
No, I guess she's not.
Figures.
Was it meant to end this way?
Is this what you want?
Do you think you
won't hurt anyone
as long as you keep quiet?
Well, what else am
I supposed to do?
If I go to the party,
I know I'm only going to
end up embarrassing Auntie.
Because I'm an ugly‐‐
No one thinks that!
Don't you get it, Sunako?
I wish you'd realize that
nobody thinks you're ugly.
Okay, you're
a little scary, but...
‐I see.
‐Stop that!
‐Sunako?
(yelling)
♪
Oh, Auntie.
Jeepers!
Pouty face.
(screaming)
(yelling)
♪
‐Ne?
‐Ne‐ne‐ne?
My sisters, this is
a sign from hell‐ne!
Now it has come
to this at last.
Now, let's move!
Maiden Rocket,
only five seconds to our
pained hearts' ignition!
‐Four...
‐Three...
‐Two...
‐One...
Liftoff‐ne!
What's the matter, Sunako?
It seemed like she was trying
to live fast and die young.
I know you're young,
but don't push yourself.
Ugh...ugh...please,
please make me into a lady!
What?
She's finally ready.
Yeah, that's my Sunako!
Let's do this.
‐Yeah!
‐Yeah.
(gong sounding)
(scream)
Chest out and back straight.
Don't forget to smile.
I'm scared!
‐Climb gracefully.
‐What's the steel girder for?
Don't ask questions!
Where's the sunrise from
hell's high mountain‐ne?
Where is it‐ne?
You should use
a clear lip gloss
with just a hint of pink.
Keep your accessories minimal.
Simple is best.
(thudding kicks)
Beautiful, really!
We did everything
we possibly could.
Okay, go!
Here I come!
Ding‐dong‐ne!
Did you see‐ne?
The light of hell‐ne?
Around this area‐ne?
Oh‐ne...
♪
All right, let's go.
Yeah!
Why are you acting like
that, Sunako Nakahara?
The party will be
starting soon, let's go!
On the double!
Double‐wouble‐ne.
(insects chirring)
(indistinct conversations)
♪
Ten years, huh?
Huh?
You are‐‐
I'm here in my father's place.
My name is Tamao Kikunoi.
I want you to know
that your niece has been
such a good friend to me.
Sunako is friends with you?
Sunako is truly
an amazing person.
You mean you don't think
that she's a bit strange?
Strange...uh...
You do, right?
A little.
‐You're an honest person.
‐But...
I honestly do like Sunako
very much indeed.
Thank you.
For me, nothing could
be a better gift.
Those words are the best
present of all, truly.
Hey, check this out,
what good‐looking people!
Wow.
They must be celebrities.
(stampeding rumble)
Where the heck is Auntie?
There are so many
people, I'm scared!
You can't chicken out now‐‐
hey, that's my butt!
I can't move in here!
Hold on a minute‐ne!
What's that?
In search of hell!
We'll follow the tiniest lead!
‐No matter where it is.
‐We'll be there!
(exclaims)
Oh, it's here‐ne!
Our dream‐ne.
This is the Goth‐Loli‐ne.
Stage show‐ne!
The picture of hell‐ne!
‐Très bien!
‐That's kind of great.
Stand out!
Goth‐goth!
Be fast!
Loli‐loli!
‐Goth‐goth.
‐Loli‐loli.
This is our chance!
‐To sneak out quietly.
‐What's all the commotion?
(twinkling chime)
Auntie, we're here.
Oh, thank you.
I'm glad you guys
made it at least.
Ta‐da!
Sunako?
♪
Auntie,
I'm really sorry
that I didn't grow up
to be your ideal girl.
To be...ideal?
So even if most people
think it's gross,
and even if you
hate me because of it,
the truth is I really do
like that kind of stuff.
I'm sorry.
I really am sorry for not
being a cute girl, Auntie.
But still, I want you to know
that I've always admired you
ever since I was a little kid.
So I just wanted you to
understand the truth about me.
And so, I...
♪
Silly girl!
You forced yourself to
come all the way out here.
Please don't worry about me.
Just as long as
you're well and happy.
I'm so glad.
Auntie!
A...a good woman
shouldn't cry so easily.
Isn't that right, Auntie?
'Cause those tears
are much more beautiful
than any jewels
in this world.
That's right!
That's just right!
♪
Happy wedding anniversary.
She insisted on coming over
here to celebrate it with you.
I see.
Thank you.
But still,
I'm sorry that...
I couldn't become a lady.
I really am.
(gong sounding)
The road to becoming a...
A lady!
Someone who never
compromises her beliefs.
Someone who can be
proud of all the things
she really likes.
Someone who is able to shine
without wearing a dress
or any makeup.
That is a lady!
We're proud of you, Sunako.
You're a respectable lady.
Oh my, this is
quite emotional.
Well, you can go home now.
Let's get down from here
while that noise is still
going on inside.
Uh‐huh.
♪
(gasping)
Hey, watch out!
♪
Oh, lovely!
Yes, Lady Tamao.
Of course she is.
You have no idea how hard
Sunako worked for this.
She never got
introduced at the party.
That's all right.
Because as it turns out,
she got to say the most
important thing, right?
(blood squelching)
(group recoils)
It's just no good, huh?
That's just how
a girl should be!
Sunako should become
a classic Japanese lady
who's beautiful
both inside and out.
Don't you agree, my dear
who's a star in heaven?
This is pretty exciting.
This isn't over yet,
it's a nightmare!
‐Hey, let's leave.
‐Huh?
Hold it.
Now I want you all
to turn my Sunako
into a superlady!
‐Give us a break!
‐Give me a break too!
Then pay the rent!
We don't want to do that either!
Me either!
♪
It looks like there's
still quite a long way to go
on the road to womanhood.
(chuckling)