Hiroshi here.
I've been thinking
maybe it's time for me
to start going
to a spa so I can
transform myself beautifully.
You can polish all
you like, you bastard.
If it were that easy
to transform someone...
We wouldn't be having
this much trouble.
By the way, what are
you planning to do
once you become beautiful?
I'm entering this year's
Miss Medical Mannequin Contest.
I think I could win.
There's no such event!
And you're no "Miss."
♪
(wind blows)
The date is February 14th!
A day when men
and women are lost
in fear and anticipation.
An undeniable restlessness
has been in the air
since early this morning!
Ready?
Yeah.
Today's going to be
a hell of a long day.
I know.
And the sweet yet horrifying
day is known as‐‐that's right.
Hey, what do you
think you're doing
sneaking around
narrating like that?!
(screams)
February 14th
is St. Valentine's Day!
Huh?
(groaning)
Oh?
Why do you have to yell
about something like that
and make us depressed
all over again?
Depressed?
(doorbell rings)
Miss Nakahara,
you have a package.
A package this early?
I'll‐‐I'll go get the door.
No, we'll go together.
All right?
Huh?
Miss Nakahara!
Yes, I'm coming right now.
♪
(contained shriek)
(screaming)
(shouting)
Would you mind signing
for these, please?
Of course, thank you.
It's already bad.
♪
The smell of chocolate!
It smells so yummy!
Be courageous, Sunako.
Gather all of your
courage and ask them.
Couldn't you let me have
just a little tiny bit of it?
Please!?
Are you all right, Yuki?
Mm‐hmm, barely.
‐Um, excuse‐‐
‐All right, guys.
It's time to go to school.
‐Let's do this.
‐Right.
Hmm?
Why aren't they
using this door?
(groans)
Blockhead!
We can't go out
the front door!
Listen, don't make a sound.
Don't utter a single word.
But it's not like
I'm a ninja, you know?
What are you so‐‐
Ah!
What the?
That was close.
Who in the world
would throw‐‐
(screams)
♪
(excited chatter)
Look at all the
chocolate out there.
No matter what
happens today,
we're going to act
as a group, got it?
(groans)
We're going now!
Chocolate!
♪
Looks like we managed
to sneak out of our mansion.
Now let's see if we'll be able
to make it to the school safely.
(together)
Right.
(groans)
Come here.
Whoa!
St. Valentine's Day‐ne!
(groaning)
(screams)
My chocolate!
(excited chatter)
(groans)
(together)
Would you please
take my chocolate?
In a tour bus?
(shrieks)
We're gonna share him!
Yuki!
♪
(sighs)
Huh?
Takenaga!
Somebody please help me!
Hold it right there.
Notice, I exist
only for my Takenaga.
I am Takenaga's
heroine and only his.
I am called Masked Noi,
and I have come here
to save the day!
♪
Takenaga, don't worry.
I'm here now,
so you're going
to be safe.
(groans)
All right, Sunako, go get 'em!
(shrieks)
The radiance!
Blah!
‐Here.
‐Blah!
(screaming)
That'll show 'em.
Help 'em on your own, will ya?
Are you okay?
Did they hurt you, Takenaga?
Ranmaru!
What now?
Well, hurry up.
Right!
(screams)
Hello!
Good day, everyone.
(together)
Good day to you.
What the‐‐
(shrieks)
The emblem of the super
famous Kikunoi family
who runs a huge conglomerate!
(shrieks)
I'm so sorry
for my rudeness!
(shrieks)
(car tires screech)
Ranmaru!
Jeez, the chicks you date
are way too much, man.
Dates?
Just as I thought,
Ranmaru does have
his heart set
on another woman.
Oh, no, no.
It's always like this for him.
Driver?
You called, Lady Tamao.
Everybody?
(together)
Yes, ma'am?
Have a good day.
(cries)
Uh?
You miserable womanizer!
Hmph!
Oh, come on!
Thank God.
I can finally see the school.
(together)
Gasp.
You cannot bring
chocolate to school!
(excited chatter)
The sweetness of
the chocolate represents
our deep devotion‐ne.
While the bitterness
of the chocolate represents
our abiding love‐ne.
The shapes of the
chocolate represents
our sensitive
virgin minds‐ne.
And the packages
the chocolates
are wrapped in represent
our playful souls‐ne.
Goth‐goth.
Loli‐loli, goth‐goth.
Loli‐loli‐‐
(shrieking)
Holy crap.
Run for it.
♪
(shrieks)
Chocolate, chocolate!
(screaming)
(gasps)
(panting)
♪
Don't you touch it!
That's my chocolate!
Damn.
But I'm too scared
to go into that crowd.
Don't you think it's
impossible to give it
to them directly?
Hm?
(both)
Nakahara, you deliver
the chocolates to them.
(crazed shriek)
Oh.
I can smell them,
so wonderful.
All these delicious chocolates.
Yet, I'm not allowed
to have even one of them.
♪
Kyohei Takano,
Kyohei Takano.
Your presence is required
in the counseling room
immediately.
Huh, they called me?
That means a teacher wants
to speak with me inside!
It's not fair.
♪
There you are, Taka.
Huh?
What on earth
is happening?
♪
You saved me.
There's been a report
that you were conducting
an unauthorized film shoot
at the local shopping arcade
a few days ago.
(groans)
Hey, are you listening to us?
I am.
I'll listen to
whatever kind of sermon
you wanna give me today.
Just please let me stay here.
‐So...
‐So...?
(shrieks)
♪
That's enough!
(panting)
They're like that
everywhere I go!
Huh?
Oh, Kyohei.
What's wrong?
The infirmary's been taken
over by female students.
Be strong.
Please don't worry
about me, but...
please help Ranmaru.
Ranmaru!
Help him!
Ranmaru?
Please help me by
giving him this.
Holy crap!
Hold on a second.
Does this mean that
Ranmaru was messing
around with the
school nurse too?
(sighs)
Um, don't you think this kind
of role play is a little
too advanced for you kittens?
This could get
dangerous, you know.
So, what do you think
we should do with him?
Should we spread
chocolate all over him?
Chocolate!
Hey, spread where?
(shrieks)
The Road to Womanhood!
This is the correct way
for a lady to attack a man.
Wrong, ladies
don't attack men.
(gong ringing)
Hey, are you all right?
Kyohei!
(screams)
This is actually
a pretty disturbing scene.
Yeah, if it wasn't
all from nosebleeds,
it'd look like a homicide
had taken place in here,
wouldn't it?
Anyway, are you all right?
I'm just scared
more than anything.
I love Kyohei!
And I love Ranmaru!
Let's run for it!
Wah!
(panting)
Where can we go?
♪
Where can we find
someplace that's safe?
♪
(gasping)
(groans)
Rich and silky
Pigeon chocolate.
My Malmonds, my Pigeon!
Those wonderful little
Pennsylvanian kisses,
and the milk chocolates
that melt on your tongue
and not on your fingers!
I wanna eat 'em!
I don't care which one,
I just wanna eat 'em all up!
(sighs)
Huh?
Why's it so dark in here?
I wanna eat 'em all now!
(shrieks)
Huh?
Thank goodness
no one's here.
Sniff sniff.
Smells like chocolate.
Yuki...
So you're in here?
I'm glad you're okay.
Sniff sniff sniff sniff.
What are you doing, Sunako?
Uh, well, um...
What?
Where is it?
Beg pardon?
Where's the chocolate!
We don't have any chocolate.
(gasps)
(groans)
I believe the teachers
are keeping an eye on it
right now in one of
the vacant classrooms.
I feel bad about it,
but there's no way
we could ever eat
so much chocolate.
Vacant classroom?
Chocolate in
a vacant classroom?
‐(giggles)
‐No, you can't, Sunako!
It's too dangerous
to go out there right now!
(gasps)
(groans)
Ranmaru, Kyohei.
So you guys are okay?
♪
Ugh!
Something is poking me.
Something hard
is poking me.
Huh?
(screams)
There it is,
in your pocket...
(shrieks)
Someone must've sneaked
this into my pocket.
Do you want it?
(gasps)
You like chocolate?
Uh‐huh, uh‐huh, uh‐huh.
All right then,
you can have it.
(shrieks)
Oh, thank you so very much.
There they are!
Oh, crap!
(shrieks)
♪
Give me what's still left!
Don't run away from us!
(shrieks)
(explosion)
That scared the hell out of me.
What the heck
just happened here?
Are you all right, Kyohei?
Did you get hurt?
Are you okay?
Why don't you all get
the hell out of here.
Oh...
So, should we just ask
Nakahara to give it to them?
I guess so.
Hang on.
Where's Sunako?
(maniacal laughing)
Oh, I see.
(screaming)
Sure, you can leave
the chocolate with me.
It will be my sincere pleasure
to accept them from you.
So I can eat every
bit of it myself!
(together)
We're really sorry!
(acid fizzles)
(shudders)
Chocolate!
It was mine!
♪
(chuckles)
I didn't know her
love of chocolate
was so strong it could
take her to the other side.
We've just seen a side of Sunako
I didn't expect she'd have.
Chocolate.
(chuckles)
Stop walking around
looking like that.
It's scary!
(groans)
I want all their chocolate!
(together)
Kyohei!
This is bad.
(excited chatter)
Run for it!
(stampede)
My Malmonds, my Pigeon.
My Malmond, my Pigeon,
Pigeon chocolate.
I can't...
I can't run any further.
Guys, just go
ahead without me.
Yuki, don't be ridiculous.
How the hell could we
go ahead without you?
‐Ranmaru.
‐Yuki!
Well, they're in no hurry.
Jeez, what are
we gonna do?
Can I just punch
them already?
You can go right ahead
if your pride will let you.
(sighs)
We said beforehand we
wouldn't accept chocolate
from anyone.
Why can't they
understand that
and leave us alone?
I have an excellent idea.
Eye drops?
(excited chatter)
I really appreciate
it, ladies, but...
I already have my heart
set on someone else.
He's crying.
I just can't see myself
with anyone but her.
(together)
Wow.
Oh, Ranmaru...
we apologize.
We got carried away
without thinking
of your feelings.
We wish you both well.
I'm so sorry.
♪
(screams)
I had no idea
that was the case.
I didn't know you
had someone you were
so serious about.
No, wait,
that's not true.
I was...
‐Driver?
‐Yes, Lady Tamao?
I hope...
you'll be happy.
(cries)
What the hell?
Awesome, that's the first
time I've personally witnessed
someone receive
divine punishment.
She was wrong!
‐I‐‐I'm in.
‐Yeah.
Guys...
‐Ladies?
‐We're sorry.
(together)
But I...
have my heart set
on someone else.
(women "aww")
(together)
Bye bye.
That really worked!
You should give it
a try, Kyohei.
Um, like we were saying,
there is someone on whom we
have already set our hearts.
Thank you.
You sound like you are
reading from a script.
Which planet are
you from anyway?
Oh, what?
No, I don't think so.
Excuse me!
We already know that.
How come they only
react that way to me?!
If you really have
someone like that,
then tell us her name.
(angry chatter)
Milk chocolate,
milk chocolate.
Milk chocolate melts
on your tongue,
not on your...
Well, her name is...
(together)
Well, her name is what?
Yummy chocolate bonbons,
yummy chocolate bonbons.
Yummy chocolate.
Right.
Her name is...
(together)
Go ahead and tell us.
Almond chocolate
has the bittersweet
taste of youth.
(laughs)
Su...
(together)
Su?
Sunako Nakahara.
(women gasp)
♪
(screaming)
It worked.
And how.
How does Sunako
feel about that?
I won't break you off a piece
of my Kit‐Kat bar, sorry!
(laughs maniacally)
We finally made
it back home.
I'm starving.
I can't take it anymore.
I just wanna go to sleep.
(snoring)
(gong ringing)
Chocolate!
The Road to Womanhood!
Facts about making
homemade chocolate.
You say "homemade,"
but you only melt it
and re‐harden it, right?
Wrong!
Never underestimate
homemade food.
If you want to make
it nice and smooth,
you can add in
fresh whipped cream.
If you'd like to make
something for more
mature tastes, try adding
ingredients like instant coffee,
for example.
The real key
here is to create
an original flavor
that also accommodates
the guy's tastes.
In trying to show
him how you feel,
be sure you don't
include anything
that isn't edible.
A lighter!
A pendant!
Wrong.
You can't eat that stuff.
It's also fun to decorate
the chocolate with toppings
such as crushed almonds
or cocoa powder.
That stuff doesn't matter
once it's in your stomach.
(gong ringing)
(groans)
How come I smell chocolate?
I hope it's not some
crazy girl who snuck
into the house.
No way.
It can't...
(screams)
(Sunako hums joyfully)
♪
(groans)
Now, let's all
eat this together.
(together)
What?
Ahh!
(groaning)
It's awesome!
(screams)
Hey, that's mine!
It's mine!
Ah.
Sweet stuff really is
the best when you're tired.
Yeah, but will you
hurry up and make dinner?
But that Valentine's
chocolate was supposed
to be for me.
Oh.
Well, in any case,
at least we did manage
to make it back home safely.
Cheers!
Oh, boy.
I didn't know what was gonna
happen for a while there.
Too right.
I mean, if Noi hadn't shown up,
it really would've been bad.
Oh, no, I forgot!
Noi's chocolate!
Ah, where's the phone!
Where's the phone!
You jerk.
So, are you the pot
or the kettle?
Exactly.
You made that rich
girl cry today.
(laughs)
That stuff happens
to me all the time.
I don't care.
No, couldn't care less.
I'll be in the John.
Aww.
So, in the end,
the only Valentine
chocolate that any of us
actually ate this year
was made by Sunako.
Well, so what?
‐Tasted good.
‐Yup.
Yummy!
Noi, I'm sorry about that.
No, no, no.
It's not that
I forgot about it,
certainly not,
I could never forget‐‐
What happened today wasn't
what you were thinking.
I swear‐‐what?
No, don't call
your driver.
Hey, let me
talk to him now!
No, I mean...
forget about him!
(both)
No, Valentine's Day!
Come back!
(dial tone)
I despise you,
I curse you!
What happened?
She said someone
kidnapped Hiroshi.
Again?
Whoever did it,
please surrender at once.
Sunako has a little mercy.
I'll do this and this
to whoever took it!
(groans)
Whoever did it,
he better run now.
Next time on The Wallflower:
"Trial of Love."
Was it you?
It wasn't me!