♪
Hiroshi here.
They say human life
is short but beautiful.
And sometimes scary, too.
Our mission is to turn Sunako
into an elegant young lady.
But how are
we gonna do that?
We'll just
have to dig in
and really work at it.
Like heck, I hate it when
we have to work at it.
Don't be so pushy,
slow and steady
is the way to go.
(together)
Whatever you say.
♪
I'm broke again.
But I thought you
had a part time job.
I did.
Fired, huh?
So who did you
beat up this time?
The president.
(together)
But why?
Kyohei, why can't you just
learn to control yourself?
Because he deserved it.
He touched my ass!
Did you file
a complaint first?
File a complaint?
Do you know what being
groped by a dude is like?
No, but you still
have to learn control!
Kyohei, Takenaga,
could you calm down?
By the way, did you
hear that the winner
of the best doll
award at tomorrow's
school cultural
festival will win 500,000?
500,000!
Of course, after you divide
it with your classmates,
your cut's only 12,500.
12,500‐‐yes, and I'm
gonna beat all of you guys.
(together)
We're not participating.
Huh, why not?
Well, I'm supposed
to give a tour
to some girls
from another school.
And I'll be‐‐
Doing the naughty
with Noi Noi.
You can pick up
more than culture
at a school
cultural festival.
School girls over money.
Yeah, yeah, we know.
So, what is your
class planning to do
for the festival, Sunako?
(gasps)
(laughing)
Creepy!
(fireworks exploding)
I think we're gonna have
a lot of visitors today.
That's 'cause
the girls know
those four will be here.
Yuki!
Takenaga!
Ranmaru.
Kyohei!
(together)
So dreamy.
Aah!
♪ Rock‐a‐bye baby ♪
Aaah!
♪ On the tree top ♪
What's that?
♪ When the wind blows ♪
♪ The cradle will rock ♪
♪ When the bough breaks ♪
How the hell did
that creepy girl
end up with those
four beautiful guys?
I heard she's the
landlady's niece.
(screaming)
Aw, the girls
are running away.
All right,
time to kick tail
and win that prize money.
You sure are fired up.
You're doing a
takoyaki stand, right?
Huh?
Wow, she almost
looks happy.
‐Sunako's‐‐
‐So scary!
(indistinct grumbling)
What time do you close?
I'll buy two
if you'll kiss me.
I'll eat a hundred
if you'll give me a hug!
(gong bonging)
(screaming)
The Road To Womanhood!
In your defense
you're invited
to a formal dinner party.
What do you think you
should do with this bowl?
No, wrong!
This bowl is called
a finger bowl
because you use it
to wash your fingers.
(splashing)
Wrong again!
Washing both hands
at the same time
is beastly.
Instead, quietly wash
one hand at a time.
What a pain in the‐‐
(gong bonging)
Oh, he's so dreamy.
Okay, patient
and focus.
Think of that 12,500.
12,500‐‐
Come on, move it!
Uh, what's your problem?
Grrr.
Aaah!
Look, boys, if you
want to try my balls,
you got to get in line
behind the ladies.
I couldn't believe
mister pretty boy Takano
had sunk to
making octopus balls,
but he really is.
How cool.
I want to be
just like you.
(laughing)
Whoops, my hand slipped.
Dude, I didn't
think his nasty looking
takoyaki could
possibly look nastier.
Huh, I didn't even know
that was takoyaki.
They look more like
little balls of doggie.
‐Dude.
‐Dude what?
Got a problem, huh?
Aaaah!
Bad move, kid.
Real bad!
Right, no more
mister nice guy.
Aaaah!
(together)
Kick his ass!
(yelling and punching)
Watch out!
(gasping)
(explosion)
What was that?
I don't know.
Dude, there was
some kind of explosion
at the festival!
Really, let's
go check it out!
‐An explosion?
‐Yeah.
Who cares about
a silly explosion?
There's still so
much to see here!
Yeah, yeah.
(bird crowing)
They said it was gas!
And one of the
stalls just exploded?
Shut up!
Kyohei, would you mind
if walked around with you?
No!
(screaming)
Isn't there anyplace
quiet around here?
Huh, a haunted house?
♪
Keroshi, Akira,
Josephina‐‐
What a sweet oasis,
surrounded by stuff I like
and no stupid
people to deal with.
What bliss,
such total bliss.
I'm so happy.
(screaming)
Oh, Sunako, is that you?
Takano, you
can't come in here!
And why the hell not?
Give me a break.
Please don't come in,
don't come in,
‐you're horrible‐‐
‐The funny thing is,
I finally understand
how you feel.
‐Huh?
‐No, boo hoo, wail, sob.
Huh?
Just let me cry alone.
It's actually
quite relaxing here.
No way!
What if someone
comes in here?
Don't worry, I'm the head
of my class committee,
it's cool.
But shouldn't
you be working?
It's covered, I'm
dumping all the real work
on that creepy girl.
So come here,
give me some.
I'm all yours, babe.
‐Aah!
‐Huh?
(creepy giggling)
♪
(screaming)
Wait, it's Nakahara.
Look, you‐‐huh?
What the hell?
Just leave it alone!
Aaah!
There's something here!
On my leg,
it touched my leg!
Dumping all the work
on Sunako, huh?
That ain't gonna fly.
No, it's not like that.
I was just kidding.
Don't even
try that one, punk.
But I already
promised Takahara
that if her
haunted house wins
we'd give her
all the prize money.
Honest and for true!
All of the money‐‐you
better not be lying to me!
I'm not, but there's
no way we'll ever win!
Aaah!
Is it true you girls
prefer the pink kind?
Maybe.
Yuki!
Huh?
Aaah!
So anyway, anyway‐‐
Takenaga!
So anyway, anyway.
Now, my angels‐‐
Ranmaru!
Which is why I think
we should all work together
to make this haunted
house a success.
Does anyone else
smell greed here?
And I wanted angels.
Be honest, you're just after
the 500,000, aren't you?
I can neither
confirm nor deny.
But if we had 500,000,
we'd still have
the rent money,
even if we don't turn
Sunako into a lady, right?
Well, that's a good point.
An even split five ways,
we each get 100,000.
Before tax.
Personal benefits aside,
I suppose it
wouldn't be fair
to just sit here and
watch you deal with Sunako
all by yourself.
‐Uh‐huh.
‐I love you guys.
Okay enough,
it's just creepy.
(giggling)
(crowd murmuring)
So, what event should
we check out next?
I don't know.
If I might make a
suggestion, fair maidens...
♪
Come visit our
house of horror.
Aaah!
‐We're there!
Do we come in here?
Uh‐huh.
It's so dark.
Gee, is this
all there is?
‐(gasps)
‐Oh, my God!
That doll is so creepy!
Did you call me a doll?
How insulting.
Calling us
creepy isn't nice.
‐It can talk!
‐No way!
♪ Gok gok,
lowly lowly gok gok ♪
♪ lowly lowly gok gok ♪
(screaming)
Have a bad day, now.
♪ Gok gok, lowly lowly ♪
Aah!
♪
Oh, wow, this one's
got to be a doll.
Do you think it's
okay to touch it?
(screaming)
That was great, Kyohei.
Yeah.
Nobody can beat you
at evil glares.
Why am I the
only one in drag?
Because you're just
not very scary, duh.
It's the curse of cute.
That's a lie‐‐I can be
just as scary as you!
Hey, check her out.
She's pretty cute, huh?
Yeah, let's hit
on her after lunch.
Sounds like a plan.
♪
Hey, hey, Sunako!
Sunako Nakahara!
Where are you,
you teenage nut job?
Hello!
What gives?
We go to all this
trouble to help her out
and instead she's
still sneaking around.
Huh?
Aah!
Why are you
hiding back here?
There are people waiting
to be scared out there!
I don't want to
be around people!
I don't wanna!
A hundred thousand yen
says that you do!
Five hundred thousand!
Why don't you just get
a part time job!
Be an escort and
hang out with girls!
I'll never do that,
that's why.
And why not?
I don't know, do I have
to have a particular reason?
Maybe I just
don't want to be
one of those
phony ass kissers.
Sounds like someone's
being selfish.
Who's selfish?
This from a girl
who hides her face
so she can't deal!
I'm hiding 'cause
I don't want to melt.
I'm so fed up
with this melting crap!
You're coming!
No, no!
I'll make you come!
No means no!
(yelling)
‐Ah!
(glass breaking)
(gasp)
♪
(heart beating)
Damn, that hurt.
Can't they even
make a decent shelf?
Aaaah!
Sunako, you're bleeding.
Are you all right?
♪
(splat)
I did it again!
What the hell,
no you don't!
Get up, damn you!
There's this mega
hot mannequin in here.
Are you serious?
♪
(screaming)
‐No, don't do it,
‐don't suck my blood!
Oh, suck my blood!
No, me, too!
You can suck anything!
♪
Unbelievable!
Inexplicable.
But at any rate...
That price money's
gonna be ours!
♪
Okay, guys, it's
time for the festival's
closing party!
No way!
Will you please
stop saying that?
I don't want to do it!
Tie her up, boys.
Aaah!
You're the star,
you've got to look hot!
Come on, it's show time!
No wait, aren't we
gonna change clothes?
No, because if we changed,
how can we prove
that we were the ones
in charge of
the haunted house?
I know that but can't
I change clothes at least?
Uh‐uh, sorry.
I love wrap parties.
Girls, girls, girls.
I'm contestant number 25
and I'm going
to sing Freebird.
(boos)
Just kidding.
Boys and girls,
this is the moment
you've all
been waiting for,
the announcement
of the school festival's
most popular event contest!
(cheering)
Maestro, can I
get a drum roll?
Hey, Noi, sorry we're late.
Takenaga, where
have you guys been?
It's a long story.
Shhh, he's about
to announce it.
And first place goes to...
Class 1‐G's haunted house!
Aaaah!
(cheering)
Congratulations, guys!
So, how do you feel?
It was inevitable.
That's confidence.
And where's your
star Nakahara hiding?
Oh she's‐‐not here!
Oh, maybe she
went to the loo?
But didn't I see her
just a second ago?
Ah, too many people.
It's too many people.
And now the winners
of the Mori High School
king and queen contest!
(screaming)
Huh, there
was a contest?
We didn't
hear about that.
No, of course you didn't,
I just made it up
so it's my choice.
And my choice for
Mr. Mori High School is...
Kyohei Takano!
Like I care.
And he receives free
cafeteria tickets for a year
and 100,000 cash!
One hundred!
That's right, and boy
was it a close contest!
And the deciding factor
was that runners up
Ranmaru Morii
and Takenaga Oda
spent most of the day
hanging out with girls!
Then I suppose
I'll never win
because moi without
beautiful girls
is like a day
without sunshine.
Takenaga's mine
and mine only,
you hear me!
Ah, Noi.
A hundred thou, a hundred
thou, a hundred thou!
Well, there you have it,
the lucky Kyohei Takano
has won the title of
Mr. Mori High School!
Objection!
We object to
the person chosen.
And as class chairman,
I refuse to
accept the prize.
I refuse because
those four idiots
aren't even
members of my class!
What'd you say‐‐come up
here and we'll settle his,
(indistinct screaming)
Kyohei, calm down.
Choosing Takano
as Mr. Mori High
don't make sense.
He's the jerk who
caused that big explosion.
And he hurt
Pinky real bad,
he tried to
barbecue his face off.
We don't think
Mr. Mori High
should condone violence.
Therefore, we're all
boycotting his selection.
Stop complaining,
you jerks,
you're just jealous.
You guys could never
compete against Kyohei,
not in a million years.
That's right,
that's right,
That's right, nay.
(together)
We're still boycotting!
You're just ugly!
(together)
Who are you calling ugly?
All men are ugly
next to Kyohei
and his friends.
Especially you!
(together)
What did you say?
You're just stupid!
(yelling)
It's not my fault‐‐
this is my fault!
We're ready to do
whatever it takes
to make sure that Kyohei
gets to keep his title.
Booya!
You lousy girls will
never beat us, so there!
(yelling)
Oh, man.
Kyohei, what should we do?
Do you think
I give a damn?
Kyohei?
Let them do
whatever they want.
♪
Gee.
Aaah!
Ah, the darkness
is so relaxing.
Skully, skully,
empty heads.
‐Sunako!
‐Huh?
This is not the time
to be polishing a skull!
One of them
radiant creatures series!
All right,
just come with me!
It's not all right.
(together)
We're not ugly!
Yes, you are!
Are you all
right, my dove?
I'm fine, thanks.
Come on, Sunako, would
you stand up already?
Aaah!
Noi, are you alright, Noi?
No, I'm not!
But you can make
me feel better.
This is awkward.
‐It's very nice to meet you.
I've been wanting to do
this since I first saw you.
‐Me too.
‐Come on.
Would you please hang
out with us later?
I'm really sorry,
but I'm kind of a guy.
Aaah!
Can we get this over with
so I can get my 600,000?
(crowd rumbling)
What I don't understand
is why you're so hung up
on winning the money.
Wouldn't it be easier
to just get a job?
It's not easier for me.
It isn't?
No matter
what kind of job,
whether my boss
is male or female,
I'm always
sexually harassed
by people where I work.
Thank you for
shopping J‐Mart.
Oh, Takano,
how would you like
to make some extra money?
I think you'd enjoy it.
Uh?
Yes, I have some tubing
that needs to be laid.
I'll pay you double
what you make now.
No, triple or more
with bonuses.
Seriously?
Very seriously.
But that doesn't
mean you won't love it.
You've got to
be kidding me!
Aah!
Hey, you're one
hard working kid.
Thanks, sir.
If you want to make
some money on the side,
I might be able
to help you out.
Really?
Yeah, 'cause the more
I stare at it,
the better your ass looks.
Don't touch my ass,
you ugly‐‐
Whaaaaa!
(crash)
Takenaga keeps saying
that I have to give
everything a chance.
So every time
I get a new job,
I force myself
to hold it in.
But it's like there's
a curse following me.
There have even
been employers
who love me at first
because I brought
in customers, but‐‐
Hey, Takano
what's on sale today?
(yelling)
No, I was here first!
Um, excuse me, ladies?
Aaah!
It's none
of your business!
It always
ends up the same.
The store gets full
of annoying people
who don't buy
anything and break stuff.
So I keep getting axed.
Really.
Some things never change
and some things
aren't meant to be.
Meaning...
Meaning that the
real problem might be
that I exist at all.
I see you, Takano.
You've got some
nerve sitting there.
You're the one who
caused all of this.
Shut your pie hole,
what do you want from me?
I want your ass.
Now stand up and
fight like a man!
Sure thing, Pinky.
Bring it on!
It's your funeral.
(gasping)
♪
(lights exploding)
(confused yelling)
♪
Aah, my God, it's a ghost!
Huh?
♪
Your ass is mine!
Aaah!
Aargh!
♪
Aah!
What a fool.
Where'd she go?
Aaaah!
Let's pretend
that didn't happen
and I'll announce the winner
of Miss Mori High School!
The winner is
the sexy young lady
who played the antique doll
in the haunted house!
Me?
(cheering)
That makes 700,000!
140,000 each!
Actually, I think you
and Sunako should split it.
‐Huh?
‐He's right.
You're the one
who did all the work
and Sunako was the one who
saved your gluteus maximus
in the end.
Besides, we're
all about the love,
not the money,
don't you know.
I love you!
I don't need it either.
Uh, you, you what?
‐How sweet.
‐Sickeningly.
That is so cool.
But in exchange, I ask
that you never bother me‐‐
Yes, someone who understands!
♪
Aaah!
(together)
Oh my gosh, Sunako!
Pull yourself together!
You dummy,
you doody head!
Hello, Hot Times Hotline.
To which hottie may
I connect your call?
Uh, yes,
he's right here.
Yeah, what?
Repairs from
the gas explosion?
700,000!
‐I'm gonna die.
‐I wanna die.
Let me be dead.
(mumbling)
(sobbing)
What a‐‐
‐‐revolting development this is.
Somebody help us.
♪
Sunako, did
you say photoshoot?
Don't make me do this!
Give me a pretty smile.
I can't!
Let's see a full frontal.
I shouldn't!
Can you show more skin?
Skin, let me get my
flaying knife, okay?
Aaah!
Next time on
The Wallflower,
The Beautiful
One's Banquet.
You're in my way,
let me through.
Who do you think you are?