Hiroshi here.
On those cold nights
when you have to sleep alone,
you can stay toasty if you use
a hot water bottle in place
of internal organs.
So, what defines a lady?
She must be beautiful,
feminine, and smart.
There's no way that'll happen!
But if we aren't able
to turn Sunako into a lady‐‐
If you fail, I'll triple
your rate and make you all
pay for it all in advance.
‐That's way too harsh!
♪
I am Ranmaru Morii,
15 years old.
I see myself and am seen
by others as a philanthropist
and here I am being awoken
on yet another morning
by my little kitten's
wake‐up call.
(cell phone rings)
♪
Hey, Ranmaru,
will you keep it down!
Your cell phone's ringing!
Come on, answer it.
That's just great,
now they're calling
on the landline
because you wouldn't answer
your cell phone!
Just wake your butt up
and answer the phone already!
(cell phone ringing)
Ranmaru, why won't
you wake up, damn you!
Honestly.
This is taking way too long!
Flying Foreign Finger Flick!
(grunts)
♪
There's been no excitement
in my life lately.
That's because the goddess
who's going to knock me
off my feet hasn't shown up yet.
♪
Where are you going?
For a walk.
Cool, get me a CD!
Yeah, and get me a book!
And bring me some
snacks, will ya?
Forget it.
Who peed in his cornflakes?
Sure wasn't me.
He sure was out of it.
I wonder if everything's okay.
(girls swooning)
♪
Oh, Ranmaru, I would be honored
if you would eat this bento!
Ranmaru, this music
is totally hot!
You absolutely have
to check it out!
Ranmaru, I want you
to have this outfit.
‐Ranmaru, yay!
Won't you please
accept our fragrant
and pleasingly mellow
virginity, dear Ranmaru?
Just like the approaching light!
♪
The target we are assigned,
will will now hunt it‐nne!
♪
(sighs)
(cell phone rings)
Yes, my little kitten?
Huh, Dad?!
(gasps)
I'm home and I brought
you some souvenirs!
Oh, yeah, that's my Ranmaru!
The donuts are mine!
I get the CD!
I get to see Sau!
Listen, you guys,
we need to talk.
Huh?
What if I were in
an exclusive relationship
with just one woman?
Huh?
I mean, wouldn't that situation
be totally unacceptable?
If that were to happen,
all the girls in the world
would shed an ocean of tears!
They'd suffer
tremendous heartache
and be unable to cope.
Then, cursing the cruel fates,
they would end their own lives!
No, I could never do
such a terrible thing
to all those poor,
sweet maidens!
What's the matter with Ranmaru?
I thought you needed
to talk to us.
Well, actually, the thing is‐‐
‐A marriage meeting?!
That's right, and my old man set
it up without even asking me.
Dude, time for you
to pay your dues.
You getting married
and settling down is
a positive thing
for all womankind.
But I don't wanna;
I wanna keep on partying!
Look, the point is,
the reason I brought this up
is because I want you
to help me ruin the meeting.
So, what kind of girl
is this fiancée?
Apparently, well‐bred
and from a wealthy family.
She's attended private all‐girl
schools ever since kindergarten
and she's driven there
and back in a stretch limousine.
From what I can tell,
she's a totally pampered girl
who's never even
talked to a boy.
(groaning)
While I happen to prefer girls
who are just
a little bit slutty.
‐Let's go wreck this meeting!
Huh?
A girl like that should never
become victim of
your venomous fangs!
It'd be way too overwhelming
for her to have a guy like you
as her first!
And what's worse,
she'd end up believing
that all men are
evil jerks like you!
Huh, but you guys are still
gonna help me, aren't you?
No matter what
your reasons might be.
Yeah, but how could
we possibly help you?
I think the best thing to do
is to make this girl hate him.
(gasping)
No, no way!
Are you saying that a girl
is actually gonna hate me?
No, I won't allow it,
do you understand?
Something like that
could never happen to me,
it could never happen!
Just kidding, sorry, guys.
Speaking of guys
that classy girls hate,
you gotta mention Kyouhei.
Hey!
He's violent, foul‐mouthed,
and way too quick
to start a fight!
Girls don't like scary guys!
Oh.
Don't listen to him!
And what about you, Yuki, huh?
Aren't girl always telling you,
"I don't like wimps"?
Jerk!
So, Takenaga, are you
even aware that most girls
think you're cold and that
you're way too sensitive?
Hey, don't drag me into this!
(mixed arguing)
(cell phone ringing)
Yes, hello?
Sweetums!
Oh, really, right now?
Of course, I'd be delighted to!
We were discussing your problem!
I'm sorry, but when I get
a phone call from a hot girl,
I'm going to pick up the phone.
You really think so?
Should we just do the usual?
(gong, screams)
In order to be a super‐bad dude
who all the girls
naturally hate,
you gotta be arrogant
with an evil look in your eyes.
It could be copacetic
if you can get your parents
to hate you, too.
Like this?
Correct!
Keep up the good work!
Lesson two!
Don't you mess with me, pal!
Don't you try
to mess with me, baby.
Wrong!
That's not even close to bad!
Stop screwing around!
Yeah, stop screwing!
(gong reverberates)
I can't!
I don't get why you're
acting like such an idiot.
Instead of messing around,
why not use this time
to memorize a formula
that's sure to annoy.
What's that mean?
Impersonate Takenaga.
I'm positive girls
would hate that even more.
Why would you say that, you‐‐
It's the way you act.
Take it easy, you two!
"Please stop fighting you guys"!
That sounds just like Yuki!
So tragic, all this fuss
because I'm beautiful.
How will you find it
in your hearts
to forgive me, lovely maidens?
Come on, I've never said
anything like that!
Yes, you have!
If someone wanted to be hated,
imitating any of you would work.
(groaning)
♪
‐I wonder where Ranmaru is?
‐Would you stop pushing me?
Hey, what's that
you've got there?
I figured we'd be
out here for a while.
(mixed conversation)
Please forgive us,
I'm terribly sorry
our fool of a son is so late.
I honestly have no idea
where he could be.
That is quite all right;
I apologize for my own parents
being unable to attend.
Please, don't worry about it!
Whoa, check that out.
Yeah, Ranmaru
looks like his dad.
You're looking at him?
She's the picture‐perfect
model of a well‐bred girl.
She's so cute!
Sorry I'm late.
Ranmaru!
Ran‐chan, is that you?!
♪
(gong, scream)
The real key to being super‐bad
is to have awful
manners at all times.
That's right, now you're
terrifically detestable.
Correct!
Hey, you don't want her
to hate you, do you?
(gong reverberates)
This segment is
totally meaningless.
Sorry!
It is a great pleasure
to make your acquaintance.
My name is Tamao Kikunoi, sir.
Who cares, I'm starving!
That's perfect,
he's being Kyouhei!
Hey, I'm not really
like that, am I?
Mm‐hmm!
Ranmaru, what's with this
attitude of yours, young man?
Shut the hell up!
Oh, my child's become
a different person!
Calm down, honey; now,
you know he doesn't usually
behave this way.
I find him to be quite
manly and far superior
to all those flaky phony men.
(gasps)
Dammit, after all
the practice I did?
Ranmaru, you're coming with me!
What's going on over there?
What the hell do you
think you're doing, mister?
I was about to ask you
the same thing.
You're the one who set up this
meeting without even asking.
The thing is, I asked her
to come here and meet you
because I really like her.
Me too.
What?
You see, I've always wanted
to have a daughter like her!
It's been my dream, too!
I've always wished
I could play dress‐up
with a cute little
daughter just like her.
You're going
to manipulate my life
for selfish reasons like that?
It's like this, son,
now listen carefully...
a romance where you
can turn an innocent girl
like her into the woman
of your dreams just like
the legendary Genji Hikaru did?
Now that's
the ultimate man's fantasy.
So, why don't you
do it then, huh?
I have...Mom.
That's right, so just
do your best, okay?
(groans)
So, tell me,
what are your hobbies, Tamao?
Well, actually,
I like tea ceremonies,
flower arrangement,
and I've recently
become interested
in horseback riding.
Oh, my, that's simply wonderful!
Dammit, what am I
supposed to do if
my super‐bad dude
strategy doesn't work
like it's supposed to?
Huh?
Hey, share that
rice cake with me!
Forget about it,
that's the carbo one
I was saving for last!
It's too late, because
I'm already eating it!
Yum, yum, yum, yum.
(screams)
That roll is mine!
That's it!
There's an evil dog outside
the window, I'm scared!
Mommy, mommy, mommy,
help me, mommy, mommy!
Help, mommy, help me!
Mommy, mommy, mommy, mommy‐‐
Normally, he's really
not like this at all!
Perhaps he sees something
that we cannot.
I actually find him
to be fascinating
and very sensitive.
It's not working at all!
All right, now it's time
for a Takenaga attack!
Excuse me, I noticed
you're holding your fork
in an incorrect manner.
Oh, thank you,
I'm most grateful
that you have made
me aware of this.
What the hell?!
Why does it always
have to be this way!
♪
I'm completely exhausted.
And I really couldn't
understand that girl at all.
Nothing I did ever seemed
to upset her one bit.
I see, and you actually
did imitate all three of us
at your meeting, didn't you?
I figured she was bound
to hate at least one of you.
I can't believe you!
But she didn't hate any of us,
is that what you're saying?
Whoa, you're right, Kyouhei!
She liked all of us;
she's such a good girl.
No thanks.
I definitely can't stand
that type at all.
Anyway, after everything
I did today, I'm pretty sure
she's gonna tell me
she's not interested.
So, what did you think
of my performance?
(doorbell rings)
I'll get it.
(mixed conversation)
Yes?
(stammering)
Ranmaru, she's here.
Huh?
That girl is outside.
(screaming)
(chuckling)
Just like a moth to a flame.
Time for me to deliver
the finishing blow.
Hey, what do you mean?
I'm gonna show her Bad Ranmaru.
That'll end this
once and for all.
♪
(door opens)
What do you want?
Well, you see,
you took off this bracelet
and left it at
the table earlier,
so I though that‐‐
(chuckles)
Do you mean you actually
came all the way to my house
just for that,
when it's so late at night?
You did that for me?
(nervous tittering)
(gasps)
Well, then, now that
I've returned the bracelet
to you, please have
a lovely evening.
♪
What kind of reaction was that?
Are you kidding me?!
Will you stop yelling
like that outside
at this time of night?
Sunako.
Oh!
Blecch!
Sorry.
Ran‐chan!
Hi, hon!
You wanna go have
some lunch with me?
What, just lunch?
Well, there might be some
yummy dessert afterwards.
I'm in.
(doorbell rings)
Yes?
Pardon me, this is
Ms. Tamao Kikunoi.
I'd like to know if
Mr. Ranmaru Morii is home.
I think he'll be back soon.
Why don't you wait inside?
No, I'll just come
back later, thank you.
♪
(tires screech)
I had a great time today.
You will call me, right?
Promise me.
Okay, I gotcha.
See ya later, then.
♪
Huh?
But‐‐!
I'm sorry,
but my mother asked me
if I would deliver this to you.
You were there; you should
have said something.
Oh, you're right,
I didn't think about that.
I'm sorry, I hope you'll
forgive my rudeness.
(approaching car)
♪
Um, hey, tell your
mother I said thanks.
Mm‐hmm.
♪
(sobbing)
What?
What the hell
was that all about?
♪
What's her deal?
Degenerate!
Oh, sorry, I didn't mean to‐‐
No, I'm the one
who should be sorry.
So, did you need something?
Yeah, I can't stop
thinking about her.
She's not my type,
but I can't get her
off my mind.
So, I wonder, do I even care
who it is as long
as it's a girl?
I wanted to find out
for myself, so I‐‐
So, you're bothering me.
But it looks like
that wasn't the case,
because it turns out
you didn't excite me at all!
And I wouldn't have wanted to!
Do you think that maybe
a girl who's just fun
to be with isn't good enough?
Uh...
I'm clueless when it comes
to romantic relationships,
but if you play around on her,
she'll play around, too.
If you're serious,
she'll treat you the same.
It's called karma.
And if you're serious about her,
but she plays you for a fool,
then go straight to hell!
(screams)
Or at least I guess
that's how it goes.
(screams)
(cell phone rings)
Huh?
That's Ranmaru's cell phone:
the second most precious
thing to him after his life.
So, where the hell
has he gone to?
He went to that girl's school.
What for?
Maybe he's gone to tell her
the whole marriage setup's
not working.
Right, let's get over
there and help him!
Help him?
Mm‐hmm!
♪
Wow, what a handsome guy!
He's hot!
Did you know he's known as
the prince of Mori High School?
Oh, is he really?
Do you think it would
be shameful if we went over
to talk to him?
♪
Hey, you.
Can I help you with something?
I came to ask you on a date.
Dreamy!
How romantic!
If this is about
what happened last night,
please don't worry about it.
I simply had something
in my eye, that's all.
The meeting was arranged
by our parents without
our consent; there's no need
for you to feel obligated
in any way.
Excuse me.
♪
Just what do you
think you're doing?
After last night,
I've thought about you.
(gasping)
It's not that
my tastes have changed.
♪
And it's not as if just
any old girl will do, either.
♪
(screeching tires)
My, my, what a scene.
(screaming)
The pretty boy
and a pretty girl.
Please don't let us
bother you, okay?
You guys go ahead.
That's right.
(gasps)
They said to go ahead.
(grunts)
♪
You're such a bad boy, Ran‐chan.
Not a bad idea
to punish him.
Feel free to have
as much fun as you like now.
Bye, bye, prince.
♪
(gasps)
It's rude to laugh.
(laughter)
Lady Tamao,
please get in the car.
(sobbing)
If I may be so bold, milady,
perhaps it would be best for you
to forget about this boy.
No!
I'm going to become
a mature woman who's his type
and then perhaps I'll
be able to win his heart!
But, Lady Tamao‐‐
You don't understand!
I've never met a boy
who was that beautiful before!
He's my first love!
Well, guys, I bet
the deal is off by now.
Excellent work, gentlemen.
Hey, what's all that?
I'm gonna cook up
something special.
You are, really,
something special?
Sweet, I can't wait, woo‐hoo!
Hang on, what for?
Because I'm sure
he's feeling depressed.
Hey, are you feeling
depressed about something?
No, not at all.
Hey, I wonder how
Ranmaru's doing?
I'm sorry, Dad, I don't think
there's a chance I'll become
some kind of Genji Hikaru.
(shattering)
♪
Not anytime soon!
Kyouhei and the others
are going far away‐nne!
This is a great problem‐nne!
No matter‐nne!
We're gonna follow them‐nne!
Goth‐Goth, Loli‐Loli!
Hey, stop that‐nne!
Will you stop with
that nne‐nne thing?
Transform‐nne!
Next episode:
"Goth‐Loli‐Rangers‐nne"
"Pirates of the Tres Bien."
Goth‐Goth!
Loli‐Loli!
What the hell
kinda preview is this?