♪
Uh, Hiroshi here.
Sometimes I wonder, if Sunako
really does become a lady,
what do you suppose
is going to happen
to all of us
medical mannequins?
What's going to
happen to you guys?
Well, I hate to be
the one to say it, but‐‐
It's just not
possible that a lady
would have something
like you guys around.
Just get rid of
the damn things.
We'll curse you and
come back and haunt you.
We're all very sorry!
♪
(laughing)
Can't take it anymore!
♪
(giggling)
(birds chirping)
How peaceful.
This is too much.
Ah‐ha, my honeys,
what should I do?
I don't have enough
arms to hold you.
It's so delicious.
Tasty.
This is good, so good!
Unbelievably good!
♪
Huh?
Fried shrimp!
Um, fried shrimp
is the best!
Ah, oh, lovely.
Oh.
(giggling)
♪
Huh?
Hello there,
I'm a heart.
Nice to meet you.
Hello, heart,
you look so fresh.
This is awesome!
(giggling)
♪
(snoring)
(fireworks exploding)
♪
Hello and welcome
to the opening
of Mori High School's
Sports Festival!
We'll start with
the cavalry battle
which very easily
could be the main event!
(cheering)
♪
This is a team competition
and all classes take part.
Attendance is
way up this year
and the crowd is
really energized!
♪
Let's do this.
Here we go, guys.
Yeah, Takenaga!
Extra good luck
to you, Takenaga!
Keep your eye
to the right.
(yelling)
Mmm, mwa, keep
sending me your smiles,
you goddesses of victory.
(screaming)
We can't decide who
we should cheer for.
You should cheer
for your own class.
(exclaiming)
Yeah!
Check it out,
Takano was incredible!
He's snatching headbands
from everyone!
Dude, we've got
to get that Takano.
We can't win
if he's in the game.
(yelling)
♪
That was magnificent!
Takano just cleared
them all out!
Come on, who wants some?
Get ready to charge.
What amazing enthusiasm.
Unlike us,
he's all pumped up.
Who'd have thought someone
with no school spirit
would create
so much excitement?
Red team's spokesman
and student council VP,
the board must be happy.
We're very happy.
As a matter of fact,
I'd like to tell
you that this is‐‐
My forces will put
a stop to the red team.
Forces‐‐you must
represent the white team,
student council president.
Emerge, anti‐Kyohei
Takano secret weapon.
I'm the sumo club captain.
And I'm the captain
of the judo club.
I'm the captain
of the karate club.
That's a full‐on martial
arts cavalry team!
And the white
team's rider is...
I'm it!
Uh, what the hell kind
of secret weapon is that?
♪
I'll show you no mercy.
I'm afraid
that's my line.
It's on page 12
of the script.
♪
Charge!
(yelling)
♪
It's mine!
Not so fast!
Huh?
♪
(screams)
Oh my, this is one
truly fearsome air duel!
Kyohei, I'm rooting for you!
Oh no, don't
hurt his face.
Nakahara's awesome.
Go for it, Nakahara!
Nakahara, Nakahara!
♪
(screams)
(yells)
But, but who won?
Sunako Nakahara's
the winner!
She's the savior
of the white team!
That was great,
I was really moved.
Taking part in a
sports festival,
what great
progress you've made.
Uhh...
Why, you...
I'm gonna win this
thing no matter what.
Stay out of my way.
How unfortunate.
Because I must win
no matter what as well.
(wind howling)
Huh!
Sunako is so cool.
♪
Blecch!
Why, why do they
have to be shirtless?
(gasping)
No, Sunako, you must
win today no matter what.
You must win!
No excuses.
Oh, that's where
you are, Sunako.
What's wrong, everyone's
looking for you.
Oh, I'm coming.
I never knew you
were so athletic.
You really were
amazing out there.
So which competition are
you participating in next?
That would be...
Next up, it's
the ball toss!
(cheering)
The crowd is roaring
for this event
which usually
isn't a big deal.
I'd say it's due
to the popularity
of some new players,
wouldn't you?
Indeed, we certainly owe
lots to Kyohei Takano's
charismatic aura.
The white team will win!
Whoa, Noi Kasahara,
Mori High School's white lily,
is going to
participate this time
as a member
of white team!
♪
(cheering)
Noi, you're the best!
She looks so good
in that gym outfit.
I wonder what
I'd have to do
to get that
kind of body?
(gong bonging)
(screaming)
The Road to Womanhood!
When you're concerned
about your figure...
What should you do?
Stop eating
to lose weight...
slowly.
Wrong!
You will die!
Fasting is a big no‐no.
You'll have to make
small changes gradually.
Like when you're
waiting at the bus stop.
Tighten your buttocks
while standing on your toes.
And when you turn around,
try to twist your body
using your waist.
One two, one two,
one two, one two!
Try that every day for
the next hundred years.
(gong bonging)
Look at that,
Noi's really popular.
Are you jealous?
Just be quiet.
Let's do our best, Sunako.
You got it, Noi.
(gunshot)
(yelling)
Takano's in the air!
♪
A slam dunk!
Next batch!
Right here.
Is that allowed?
Sunako!
(grunting)
Come help us, everyone!
We'd do anything for you,
Miss Kasahara.
Sunako.
♪
Okay, let's go.
Here I come, you guys!
(screams)
Ha!
Nakahara made it too!
Are we gonna do this?
That's great, Sunako!
Keep those
balls coming, guys.
Balls, balls, balls!
We're gonna throw
those balls in!
Look at Noi.
I know.
(screams)
(yells)
Here's more!
Yaaa!
(gong bonging)
(scream)
The Road to Womanhood!
Balls, balls,
balls, balls, balls!
Wrong‐‐I don't think
you actually understand
what the word "balls"
really means.
What do you mean?
(gong bonging)
Wha‐‐what?
This isn't basketball,
it's a ball toss, okay?
(whistle blowing)
(heavy breathing)
Twenty‐two,
twenty‐three.
The blue and pink teams
are already out.
Now we're left with
a very close contest
between the red
and white teams.
One‐forty‐six,
one‐forty‐seven.
Wow, the red team
has certainly
dominated the ball toss.
Yeah, we did it!
No way.
I'm sorry, but the Sports
Festival has just started.
The score!
Oh no, we lost!
Sunako, get a
hold of yourself!
Are you hurt, young lady?
Why don't I try giving you
some tender loving care?
So bright!
Hey, monitor!
I need tender
loving care here.
Anyway, Ranmaru, why are
you dressed like that?
I'm joining the
cosplay relay race.
Looks good, huh?
What's wrong, Noi?
(giggling)
(gibberish)
Look at how
you're dressed, ahhh!
See you this evening, Noi.
See you later,
sweetie pie.
(smooching)
Aah...
Noi!
I won't lose,
I can't lose!
♪
Wow, Sunako is on fire!
For the sake of our
beloved princes, nay.
Goth‐goth, goth‐goth.
Give it to me
one more time, nay.
Loli‐loli, baby.
A burning passion that grows
stronger day by day, nay.
Let this mighty pose
carry them away, nay.
And we'll
show everyone here
who's really
number one, nay.
Let the
competition begin, nay.
♪
Oh!
Yes, tower of victory!
(wind blowing)
What you have
just witnessed,
ladies and gentlemen,
was called the Victorious
Dance of the Goddesses,
performed for you today
by the Goth‐Loli Sisters
of the purple team.
Although honestly,
it just looks like
a totem pole to me.
Uh.
♪
Oh!
Ha, totem pole
of victory!
They've corrected themselves,
but it's still the same.
Anyway let's
change the mood
and move on to the
afternoon competition!
(yelling)
♪
And now the time has come
for today's main event!
Mori High's own obstacle race!
(cheering)
This next event is a
free‐for‐all competition
and we want to know,
will Kyohei Takano and
Sunako Nakahara compete?
There is no doubt that
this critical race‐‐
‐‐will decide
the winning team.
You insist on racing?
And you don't?
It's the Sports Festival.
That's not your thing.
And it's yours?
I'm betting
absolutely everything
on this competition.
That makes two of us.
(flames roaring)
Oh, boy, things are pretty
intense between them
even before the race.
Good luck to all
the other players.
I'll do my best, Takenaga.
So watch me.
We are not going
to lose, nay.
(gunshot)
Yaaa!
Just look at that!
Takano made
a blistering sprint
away from the start line
and the first
challenge he faces
is the net‐‐oh, he's stuck.
Is it possible
his long limbs
are getting in the way?
It's pointless.
And there's not a thing‐‐
‐‐he can do about it.
And behind him are
the Goth‐Loli Sisters,
which should have been
a foregone conclusion,
considering what
they're wearing.
Damn, I'm not any good
at this kind of stuff.
Uh?
♪
What the hell?
Are you some kind
of roach or something?
Incredible!
Sunako Nakahara's on fire!
She's outdistanced Takano.
Hey, Takano,
fried shrimp platter!
♪
(screams)
Delicious fried
shrimp platter!
Quite right, if there's
an obstacle, remove it.
That's Kyohei
Takano for you.
What does fried
shrimp mean?
First you coat
shrimp with bread crumbs
then you fry them‐‐
Lucky me.
Loli, loli, loli, loli!
I just can't
do this anymore!
A few participants have already
dropped out of the race.
Now onto the next segment!
Next is the tall,
terrible, thin box!
Nakahara's height puts
her at a grave disadvantage.
See ya!
Ha!
♪
Don't stop, we'll give
you more blackout curtains!
♪
(yelling)
An outstanding
feat for Nakahara.
Her score's 10.0.
What are blackout curtains?
They're made of
thick black cloth‐‐
Now all of you jump onto
my corpse and do this.
Goth‐goth.
(gasps)
‐(crying)
‐Loli‐loli.
Aaah.
Oh, loli‐loli.
More than half
the participants
have dropped out of
the second challenge.
Next is the
deceptively difficult
Find the Candy in
the Powdered Sugar!
All the girls who don't
want to mess up their faces
won't enjoy
this next challenge.
♪
Seems a bit odd
that those two
would go to such extremes,
don't you think?
I was thinking
the same thing.
Look, it's Noi.
(coughing)
Oh, no, there
isn't any more candy.
(coughing)
Yvonne, take this, nay.
Nay?
‐Goth.
‐Loli.
‐Aaaah!
‐Hey, that's cheating.
You guys!
Goth, goth, goth.
Ahhh, that's not fair!
Don't worry, I'll buy
some candy for you, Noi!
Did Noi just ask
Takenaga for some candy?
Only three
contestants are left
and the next challenge
is the biggest one yet!
The balance beam!
(gasping)
But you'll notice this isn't
any ordinary balance beam.
It's called the evil
balance beam from hell!
Goth‐goth.
Hey, wait a minute!
I'll be sure to
dedicate my victory
to our beloved Kyohei, nay.
♪
Oh!
Japan‐nay!
A bullet‐like spike shot
at 150 kilometers per hour
just knocked down
the contestant!
Are you kidding me?
Here goes!
♪
This is endless, we've
got to slice through!
Okay.
(yells)
Huh, aah!
Are you all right?
♪
So bright!
Nakahara, watch out!
Uh!
♪
Ya!
Kyohei Takano's amazing!
He diverted a 150
kilometer per hour ball!
Hey, are you hiding
something from me?
Me, what about you?
Are you telling me they
offered you the same deal?
Wait, if you
know about that,
does that mean
you were also...
Sunako Nakahara.
You glowing
creature of light.
♪
You're much too radiant!
Nakahara has fallen!
What an unexpected ending
to today's tournament!
Sunako!
Kyohei, behind you!
(yells)
(muttering)
Takano failed
to dodge that one.
He's hunched over.
Whoa, this is unbelievable!
Sunako Nakahara's
still hanging on
to the balance beam
by her fingertips!
(groaning)
So radiant,
I can't take it.
Is this the end for you?
♪
I won't give up now.
That's right, I can't
afford to give up yet either!
(screams)
For my dream!
For my dream.
‐For my dream!
It's the final
two hundred meters!
♪
(groaning)
That's enough already.
I can't bear to watch!
It's awful,
why do they have to
push themselves this far?
For some reason, I have
a bad feeling about this.
Uh, me too.
Me three.
You can do it, Takano!
Come on, Nakahara!
‐If you collapse now,
‐then the deal is off!
♪
Holy cow, those two are
sprinting full‐out
with everything
that's left in them!
‐Go, go, go, go!
What's this deal
you mentioned?
The VP and I have bet.
We asked everyone to pitch in
and we easily
collected a million yen
in practically
no time at all.
I see.
And the bet?
We offered Takano an all day,
all you can eat pass
for the food court
at the shopping arcade.
And we offered
Nakahara a free pass
for the biology room
and a complete human
anatomy encyclopedia.
Plus some cash, but I never
thought it would bring
this much excitement
to the Sports Festival.
As a student
council member‐‐
Council members,
huh, that's a lie!
‐Sir?
Just five meters left,
who's gonna win this?
That's my microphone.
Yo, deal's off!
‐Aaah!
(cracking)
(crying)
(crashing)
They're down!
Neither can get up!
They can't do it!
Have they run
out of steam?
Oh, boy.
I'm so moved.
I don't even care who
wins or loses the race now.
Excellent job, you two.
That was awesome.
(applause)
Thank you, Takano.
Thank you, Nakahara.
We'll never forget
this emotional moment.
Thank you for allowing
us to share your dream.
A new dream.
Forever!
♪
Time for the next
episode preview, milady.
In the next episode,
Sunako, Noi, and I will‐‐
There's a lot of these!
Don't be so imperious.
No not that, but all
three of us will be naked
and get massages.
Oh, no, you
can't touch that.
I didn't know it
was that kind of story.
Like that's possible.
Next time on
The Wallflower,
Girls, Bravo!
But it is
kinda like that.
Oh no, flesh!