I'll miss you, Chihiro.
Your best friend, Rumi.
Chihiro, Chihiro, we're almost there.
This really is in the middle of nowhere.
I'm gonna have to go to the next town to shop.
We'll just have to learn to like it.
Look, Chihiro, there's your new school.
Looks great, doesn't it?
It doesn't look so bad.
It's gonna stink, I liked my old school.
Mom!
My flowers are dying.
I told you not to smother them like that.
We'll put them in water when we get to our new home.
1 finally get a bouquet, and it's a goodbye present.
That's depressing.
Daddy bought you a rose for your birthday.
Don't you remember?
Yeah, one.
Just one rose isn't a bouquet.
Hold on to your card, I'm opening the window.
And quit whining, it's fun to move to a new place.
It's an adventure.
Wait.
Did I take the wrong turn?
This can't be right.
Look, there's our house.
Huh?
It's that blue one on the end.
Oh, you're right.
I must have missed the turnoff.
This road should get us there.
Honey don't take a shortcut, you always get us lost.
Trust me, it's gonna work.
What are those stones?
They look like little houses.
They're shrines.
Some people think little spirits live there.
Dad, I think we're lost.
We're fine, I've got four-wheel drive.
Sit down, please, sweetie.
Honey, honey, honey!
Slow down! You're gonna kill us.
What's that?
What's this old building?
It looks like an entrance.
Honey, get back in the car, we're going to be late.
Chihiro.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
This building is not old. It's fake.
These stones are just made of plaster.
The wind is pulling us in.
What is it?
Come on, let's go in. I wanna
see what's on the other side.
I'm not going.
It gives me the creeps.
Don't be such a scaredy-cat, Chihiro.
Let's just take a look.
The movers will get to our house before we do.
It's all right, they've got the keys.
They can start without us.
All right just a quick look.
Forget it, I'm not going.
Come on, you guys.
Let's get out of here.
Come on, honey.
It'll be fun.
I'm not going!
Chihiro, just wait in the car then.
But, Mom!
Wait for me!
Everybody, watch your step.
Chihiro, don't cling like that, you'll make me trip.
What is this place?
Oh, do you hear that?
It sounds like a train.
We must be near a train station.
Come on. Let's go check it out.
What are those weird buildings?
I knew it.
It's an abandoned theme park.
See?
They built them everywhere in the early '90s.
Then the economy went bad, and they all went bankrupt.
This must be one of them.
Where are you going, you said just a quick look!
Now let's go back.
Hey!
Did you hear that building, it was moaning.
It's just the wind.
Oh, what a beautiful place.
We should have brought our lunch.
Then we could have had a picnic.
Look, they were planning to put a river here.
Hmm?
Hey, you smell that?
Something smells delicious.
Yeah, and I'm starving.
Maybe this theme park is still in business, let's go.
Chihiro, hurry it up.
Wait a minute.
Over there.
This way.
How strange.
They're all restaurants.
Where is everybody?
Ah, there it is.
Hey, I found it!
Hey, you gotta see this, in here.
Ah, look at this.
Hello in there, does anybody work here?
Come in, Chihiro. It looks delicious.
Mm-mmm.
Anybody?
Don't worry, honey we can pay the bill when they get back.
Good plan.
Hey, that looks great.
I wonder what this is called.
Oh, it's delicious, Chihiro, you have to taste this.
I don't want any, we're gonna get in trouble.
Let's just get out of here.
Don't worry, you've got Daddy here.
He's got credit cards and cash.
Chihiro, you have to try this it's so tender.
Mm-mmm.
Mustard?
Thank you.
Come on, you guys you can't!
That's weird.
It's a bathhouse.
There's the train.
You shouldn't be here, get out of here now!
What?
It's almost night.
Leave, before it gets dark.
They're lighting the lamps.
Get out of here.
You've gotta get across the river.
Go, I'll distract them!
What's up with him?
Mom!
Dad!
Come on!
Quit eating!
Let's get out of here!
Mom, Dad, where are you?
Mommy!
Water?
What?
I'm dreaming!
Come on wake up, wake up!
Wake up.
It's just a dream, it's just a dream, go away.
Away.
Disappear.
I'm see-through!
It's just a bad dream.
Ah!
Oh!
Don't be afraid, I just wanna help you.
No, no, no!
Open your mouth and eat this.
You have to eat some food from
this world, or else you'll disappear.
No!
Don't worry it won't turn you into a pig.
Chew it and swallow.
There you go, you're all better.
See for yourself.
I'm okay.
You see?
Now, come with me.
Where are my mom and dad?
They, didn't really turn into pigs, did they?
You can't see them now, but you will.
Don't move.
That bird's looking for you, you've gotta get out of here.
Ah! My legs! I can't stand up.
Help! What do I do?
Calm down, take a deep breath.
In the name of the wind and water within thee, unbind her.
Get up.
Welcome.
Always nice to see you, welcome back.
Welcome back!
You have to hold your breath while we cross the bridge.
Even the tiniest breath will break the spell,
and then everyone will see you.
Welcome back.
I'm scared.
Now just stay calm.
Welcome, welcome! Always nice to see you.
Welcome back, welcome, welcome.
I'm back from my mission.
Welcome.
Welcome back, Master Haku.
Take a deep breath.
Hold it.
Welcome, welcome!
Welcome back, good to see you.
Hang on.
Almost there.
Master Haku!
Where have you been?
Wha, a human?
Let's go!
Huh, hah, huh?
Master Haku!
Oh, Master Haku?
it stinks up the place!
They know you're here.
I'm sorry, I took a breath.
No, Chihiro, you did very well.
Listen carefully to what ll tell you to do.
You can't stay here, they'll find you,
and you'll never get to rescue your parents.
I'll create a diversion while you escape.
No don't leave me, I don't wanna be alone.
You don't have any choice,
if you want to help your parents.
This is what you have to do.
They did turn into pigs, I wasn't dreaming.
Don't worry.
Now, when things quiet down, go out through the back gate.
Go all the way down the stairs
until you reach the boiler room,
where they stoke the fires.
There you'll find Kamaji, the boiler man.
Kamaji?
Tell him you want to work here.
Even if he refuses, you must insist.
If you don't get a job, Yubaba
will turn you into an animal.
Yubaba.
Huh?
You'll see she's the witch who rules the bathhouse.
Kamaji will try to turn you
away or trick you into leaving,
but just keep asking for work.
It'll be hard work, but you'll be able to stay here.
Then, even Yubaba can't harm you.
Master Haku?
Master Haku, where are you?
I have to go and don't forget, Chihiro, I'm your friend.
How did you know my name's Chihiro?
I've known you since you were very small.
Good luck, and whatever you do, don't make a sound.
Master Haku?
Calm down, I'm coming.
Master Haku, Yubaba wants to see you.
I know, it's about my mission, right?
Uh, hello, excuse me.
Uh, hello?
Uh, hello are you Kamaji?
Eh?
Haku told me to come here and ask you for work.
Could you give me a job please?
Four bath tokens at once.
Come on get to work, you little runts.
Yeah, I'm Kamaji,
slave to the boiler that heats the baths.
Move it, ya stupid soot balls.
Please, I've gotta get a job here.
I don't need any help.
The place is full of soot, l'll just cast a spell on them
and I've got all the workers I need.
Oh sorry.
Wait, just a second.
Out of the way.
What should I do with this?
Should ll leave it here?
Finish what you started, human.
Hey, you runts, you wanna turn back into soot?
And you, back off, you can't just take someone else's job.
If they don't work, the spell wears off.
They turn back into soot.
There's no work for you here, got it, try somewhere else!
You soot balls got a problem, now get back to work!
Chow time, what's going on?
Are you guys fighting again?
Where's your other bowl?
From yesterday?
I keep telling you to leave it out, Kamaji.
Meal time take a break!
A human!
You're in trouble.
You're the one everyone's looking for.
She's my granddaughter.
Granddaughter?
She said she wants to work here,
but I've got all the help I need.
Would you take her to see Yubaba?
She's a tough little girl.
I think she can handle it.
No way, I'm not gonna risk my life.
What if I give you this roasted newt, hmm?
It's a good one.
If you want a job, you'll have to make a deal with Yubaba.
She's the head honcho here.
Give me that.
Come on little girl, you better follow me.
Can't you even manage a yes, ma'am or a thank you?
Yes, ma'am.
What a dope.
Hurry up.
Yes, ma'am.
You don't need your shoes or your socks. Just leave 'em.
Thank the boiler man, you idiot.
You know, he's really sticking his neck out for you.
Thank you, Mr. Boiler Man!
Good luck.
We have to go all the way to the
top floor. That's where Yubaba lives.
Get over here.
You wanna lose your nose?
More appetizers.
Not spicy enough.
We're halfway there just stay close.
Okay.
Here we go.
The Radish Spirit.
Sorry, sir this elevator doesn't go any higher.
You'll have to take another one, thank you.
He's following us.
Just don't look at him.
Step out to the right, please, gentlemen.
Your rooms are right this way.
Hmm, Lin?
What?
What's that smell?
It's human you smell just like a human.
Oh, really?
Where's it coming from, Lin, come on.
You're hiding something, aren't you?
Show it to me.
Is this what you smell?
Roasted...
newt!
No way, frog, I'm saving every last bite for myself.
Please, just a little bit, just give me a leg.
If you wanna go up, pull the lever on your right.
Gimme, gimme, gimme, how could you be so cruel?
Can't you share?
Let me please suck on the tail, please!
Let me just...
Aren't you even going to knock?
You're the most pathetic little girl I've ever seen.
Well, come in.
I said, come in.
Quiet down you're making a racket.
Excuse me, I was wondering if you could give me a job?
I don't want to hear such a stupid request.
You're just a stinking, useless weakling.
And this is certainly no place for humans.
It's a bathhouse for the spirits.
It's where they come to replenish themselves.
And you humans always make a mess of things.
Like your parents, who gobbled up
the food of the spirits like pigs.
They got what they deserved.
And you should be punished too.
You could be a piglet.
Or, maybe you'd prefer a lump of coal?
l can see you shaking.
Actually, I'm impressed you made it this far.
But I'm sure you didn't do it on your own.
Let's thank whoever helped you.
Just who was it dear, why don't you tell me?
Please! Can't you give me a job?
Don't start that again.
Please, l just want to work.
Don't say that!
Why in world do you think l should give you a job?
Anyone can see you're a lazy, spoiled
crybaby, and you have no manners.
This is a high-class place I'm running here.
So there's no job for you, now get out.
I've got all the lazy bums I need.
Or maybe I'll give you the most difficult job I've got,
and work you until you breathe your very last breath.
Oh, dear, you woke up the baby.
Mommy's here.
Be a good boy now.
Why are you still here, I told you to leave.
I want you to give me a job, please!
Quiet down you're scaring the baby!
Hi, sweetie.
Don't be angry.
That's a good boy.
I'm not leaving till you give me a job.
Okay okay, just be quiet.
Here comes Mommy, I'm coming to get you.
That's your contract.
Sign your name away, and I'll put you to work.
If ll hear one little complaint out of you,
you'll be joining your parents in the pigpen.
So I, do I sign my name here?
Just sign it, do you want the job or not?
I can't believe I took that oath.
To give a job to anyone who asks.
Ridiculous, I hate being so nice all the time!
Are you done yet?
So, your name's Chihiro?
Yes, ma'am.
What a pretty name.
And it belongs to me now.
From now on, your name is Sen, you got that?
Answer me, Sen!
Yes, ma'am.
You called for me?
This girl signed a contract.
Set her up with a job.
Right.
What's your name?
What, Chih, oh, it's Sen.
Okay, Sen.
Follow me.
Haku, uh...
Don't talk to me, and address me as Master Haku.
I don't care if Yubaba gets angry with us.
We're not taking humans.
She's already under contract.
What?
I promise to work very hard.
We are not gonna take her in our department.
She'll stink up the whole place.
We don't want her.
Three days of eating our food, and her smell will go away.
And if she doesn't work hard, roast her, boil her,
do whatever you want.
Now get back to work.
Where is Lin?
What, don't you dump her on me.
You said you wanted an assistant.
That's perfect.
Give the girl to Lin.
Oh, great.
Sen, get going.
Right.
Why are you picking on me?
You owe me one, Haku.
You hear me?
Have a nice day.
Hmm.
Come on.
I can't believe you pulled it off.
Huh?
You're such a dope, l was really worried.
Now, keep on your toes, and if you need anything, ask me.
Okay?
Okay.
Hmm? What's wrong?
I don't feel so good.
So, this is our room.
A little food and some sleep and you'll be fine.
Here's your apron.
You have to wash it yourself.
Your pants.
You're so puny.
Way too big.
Lin, you know Haku?
What about him?
There aren't two of him here, are there?
Two Hakus? I can barely stand one.
Too big.
He's Yubaba's henchman, don't trust anything he says.
Hmm..
Let's see..
Ah!
Here we go
wh-what's wrong with you?
Are you feeling okay?
Quiet down.
What's your problem?
It's the new girl, she doesn't feel so good.
Meet me at the bridge
I'll take you to your parents.
My shoes are gone.
Huh?
Thank you.
Follow me.
We don't have much time.
If you're found here, you'll
be turned into a pig yourself.
You must never come here without me.
Understand?
I understand.
Mom, Dad, are you all right?
It's me, Sen, hey, wake up!
Mom!
Dad!
What's wrong with them, are they sick?
No, they ate too much, they're sleeping it off.
They don't remember being human.
So look hard. It's up to you
to remember which ones they are.
Don't you worry, I promise I'll get you out of
here. So just don't get any fatter or they'll eat you!
Here are your clothes.
Hide them.
I thought they'd been thrown away.
You'll need them to get home.
My goodbye card's still here.
Chihiro..
Chihiro.
That's my name, isn't it?
That's how Yubaba controls you, by stealing your name.
So hold on to that card, keep it hidden.
And while you're here, you must call yourself Sen.
I can't believe I forgot my name.
She almost took it from me.
If you completely forget it,
you'll never find your way home.
I've tried everything to remember mine.
You can't remember your name?
No, but for some reason, I remember yours.
Here you go, eat this, you must be hungry.
No.
I put a spell on it so it'll give you back your strength.
Just eat it.
Have some more, you'll be all right.
I've got to go now, I'll be back to help you soon.
Just stay out of trouble.
Thank you Haku, you're a good friend.
Haku.
He's a dragon?
Where were you Sen, I was really worried.
I'm sorry.
Out of my way.
Gee, Sen!
Haven't you ever worked a day in your life?
Lin and Sen, you get the big tub today.
What?
Hey, that's frog work.
Orders from the top, so quit your complaining!
Hello, aren't you getting wet out there?
Sen, hurry up.
Coming.
I'll leave the door open for you.
Heard you got the big tub, Lin.
Leave me alone.
Those jerks, they haven't cleaned this tub in months.
We only use this tub for our really filthy guests.
Uh, Disgusting, this sludge is so
caked on, it'll take days to scrub off.
Lin, Sen, you've got some customers on the way.
Wait!
Give us a minute, this is clearly harassment.
We'll have to soak it off.
Get an herbal soak token from the foreman.
what?
An herbal soak token.
All right.
Hey, Lin, what's a foreman?
Hmm..
Something's coming, I wonder what?
What useless scum is sleeking around in the rain?
I can't waste a token on you.
Relax, good morning.
Enjoy.
Have a nice bath.
For the Radish Spirit.
One sulfur soak.
Why are you still standing here, scrub it yourself.
I'm not giving you a token.
Relax, good morning.
I said scrub it yourself.
But ll was told it has to have an herbal soak.
Well, that's too bad.
Mugwort bath?
Relax and enjoy it.
Emm?
Foreman speaking.
Oh! Yes.
What!
Thank you very much.
Get back here!
Hey!
Wait a minute.
What's going on?
Nothing, everything's fine.
We have an intruder.
Is it a human?
I'm not quite sure.
Figure it out and report back.
Wow, Sen, you got a really good one.
Clip this on, then let go.
It goes straight to Kamaji, then he sends us our water.
You pull on this to start the
water flowing, give it a try.
Uh, you're such a klutz.
Yuck!
What's in this water?
Dried worm salt, it's supposed to be good for you.
And with water this murky, you
can't see all the sludge in the tub.
Yank it again when the bath is full, it'll stop.
You can let go of the rope
now, I'll get us some breakfast.
Okay.
Uh, sir the bath's not ready yet.
There're so many.
Uh, uh, uh...
What and they're all for me?
Uh, uh...
Thanks, but I don't need any more.
Uh...
No.
I only need one.
Oh, Yubaba.
It's a stink spirit.
And apparently, it's an extra smelly one.
He, he's headed straight for the bridge.
Go away.
That's enough.
No no, we're closed, go away!
No, hey, we're not open.
Go, please, go, leave us.
Hmm.
Something's fishy. That doesn't
seem like a stink spirit to me.
But we have no choice.
Go greet him.
Just give him a bath and get
him out of here as fast as you can.
Everybody go back to your rooms.
Repeat, back to your rooms.
Sen, Yubaba wants to see you.
Yes, sir.
Sen, don't mess this up.
Take this guest to the big tub and take care of him.
But, but I...
No buts, or I'll turn you into coal.
You hear me?
Ah it's here.
Hands down, you'll insult our guest.
Look about you customer, welcome to our baths.
Oh, it's money.
Sen, take the nice customer's money.
Yes, ma'am.
Don't make him wait, get him to the bath.
This way.
Get out of my way!
Sen!
Our food!
Open the windows, all of them!
Right away.
What?
Just a minute, sir.
Disgusting
I don't think it's very funny.
Let's see what she'll do next.
Look, she wants to refill the tub.
Oh dear, she's gonna waste all our good water!
Ah.
Emm.
Hmm, who gave her all the bath tokens?
Don't look at me, I didn't do it.
Oh, no that's our best herbal formula!
Sen!
Sen, where are you?
Over here!
Don't worry, stay, stay right where you are.
I'm coming to help you.
You're gonna be fine, I won't let him hurt you.
I think he needs help, it feels
like there's a thorn in his side.
A thorn?
It won't come out!
What's that, he has a thorn, hmm...
get the step down there.
Hmm?
Step on it.
Frog, get downstairs.
You!
All of you!
Listen to me.
That's no stink spirit we have on our hands...
Grab onto this rope.
Wait!
Mmm.
Hold on tight.
Got it.
Hurry up, now.
Get in there!
Everyone get in there and help them.
We've got it tied on!
Everyone, ready on my command.
And...
Heave!
And, heave!
And heave!
A bicycle?
Thought so.
Get ready, now!
Heave!
Sen!
Sen, where are you?
Well done.
Hmm..
Gold!
Hey, wait! That's company property!
Stop!
Back off!
Our guest is still here, you idiots!
Sen, you're in our guest's way, step aside.
Yes, sir.
Open the main gates!
Make way!
Sen, you did great, we made so much money!
That spirit is rich and powerful, everyone learn from Sen.
Sake's on the house tonight.
But first, hand over all the gold you picked up.
What do you mean git it back.
How stingy, that's no fair!
Here.
I swiped a dumpling for you.
Thank you.
What a day.
Mmm.
Lin, have you seen Haku?
Not Haku again.
He just disappears sometimes.
Rumor has it he runs around doing Yubaba's dirty work.
Does he really?
Lights out, Lin.
Fine.
There's so much water, it looks like a sea.
What do you expect after all that rain?
I've gotta get out of this place.
Someday, I'm getting on that train.
Hmm?
What's wrong?
Ahh! It's gold!
Huh?
What do you think you're doing,
you're not allowed in there.
The bath's closed.
Get out, you!
Get out of there!
Oh! More gold!
Are you, are you, are you giving them to me?
Wait, you can make gold?
Gimme!
What's going on in there?
It's way past bedtime.
Come on!
Wh...
Hey, boss, up here, I'm hungry, starving!
And l want you to serve me.
I know that voice.
Here, I'll pay you up front.
And l wanna take a bath, too.
Why don't you wake everyone up?
Mom, Dad, I got a gift from the River Spirit!
Maybe if you eat it, it'll break the spell.
Which ones are you?
Mom, Dad!
Bad dream.
Lin?
Where is everybody?
Wow.
It really is a sea.
There's Mom and Dad's pigpen.
I sure hope they're doing all right over there.
Kamaji lit the boiler already?
How long was I asleep?
Hurry up, he's hungry.
Get put of my way.
Come on, he's starving, can't you cook any faster?
Serve everything you've got even leftovers if you have to.
Hurry up!
He's starving!
Hey, Sen.
Oh, Lin.
I was just coming to wake you up, look.
It's real gold, there's a new guest who's loaded.
He's giving gold away by the handfuls!
Just keep the food coming, I wanna eat everything!
Hmm.
Who is the guest?
Oh, who cares?
Come on, before Yubaba wakes up.
I'm going to go look for Haku.
Oh would you quit worrying about Haku?
Come on, Sen.
Let's go get some gold.
Come on, Lin!
Let's go get some more!
You bet!
Hey, wait for me!
Where is Haku?
He better get here before I
forget what my parents look like.
I sure hope Dad hasn't gotten too fat.
Haku?
It's Haku!
He's back!
Are birds chasing him?
Haku fight 'em.
Come on!
He's hurt!
Haku, this way!
Aah!
Huh?
It's just paper.
Haku..
You're bleeding.
Hold still, those paper things are gone now.
You're going to be all right.
He went in that top window.
I've got to get there before he bleeds to death!
Welcome the rich man.
He's hard for you to miss.
His butt keeps getting bigger.
So there's plenty there to kiss, haha.
Oh, hey, everybody, bow down.
Welcome, rich man.
Beg for tips, this is the time.
Beg for tips, make yourselves a dime.
Give me some gold.
Give me some tips!
Sir, I'll do anything for you, just give me some tips!
Hey, what are you doing?
Going upstairs.
No, you're not.
Huh..
Ah blood!
Get out of the way our guest is coming through here!
Thank you for helping me earlier.
Don't talk to him, you stinking hum...
Wow, hey!
I don't want any, but thanks.
I'm sorry, but I'm in a really big hurry.
Hey, there, hey, get back, get back now!
Everybody, out!
Oh, I'm terribly sorry, sir.
You'll have to excuse the little girl she's just a human.
Wipe that smile off your face.
What?
You're still smiling.
It's Yubaba!
You attract terrible guests.
Alright I'm on my way.
Don't let he meet anyone else till I get down there.
Er..
Haku is bleeding all over the carpet.
Get him put of here, he'll be died soon anway.
Oh..
Hi, sweetie hiding under the cushiones again.
Oh, I woke you, and you were sound asleep.
I'm sorry.
Let me give you a kiss.
Go back to sleep, now.
Ow!
Let go of me!
Wow, you're a big baby.
Would you mind letting go of me?
I'm in a really big hurry.
You came in here to make me sick.
Huh?
You're a bad germ from outside, aren't you?
I'm not a germ, I'm a human.
Now, would you please let go of me?
You'll get sick if you go outside.
So stay here and play with me.
You won't get sick.
Yes, you will.
That's why I've never left this room.
Staying in this room is what'll make you sick.
Listen, someone very important to me is terribly hurt.
I've got to go right now, so please let go of me.
If you go I'll cry, and Mama will hear me,
and Mama will come in here and kill you.
Play with me, or I'll break your arm.
That hurts!
Please, I'll play with you later, okay?
No, I wanna play now!
Germs!
I've got germs, see?
Haku!
What are you doing?
Get away!
Get back!
Haku, are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Shut your mouth!
Haku!
Get back!
Stop it!
I'm not afraid of germs.
If you don't play with me, I'll cry.
Please don't cry.
Just wait.
Right now, or I'll start crying.
Don't cry! Don't cry!
What a spoiled brat!
Shut your big mouth!
You're a bit of a porker, aren't you?
Hmm, still see-through.
Mama?
You pea-brain.
Can't you even tell me from your own mother?
There, now your body matches your brain.
Let's see, what else can we mess with?
This is our little secret.
You tell anyone else, and I'll rip your mouth out.
Who are you?
Zeniba.
I'm Yubaba's twin sister.
It was nice of you to lead me
straight to this dragon's hiding place.
Now, hand him over to me.
What do you want with Haku?
He's badly hurt.
Too bad.
He stole my solid gold seal.
It's magic and powerful. I want it back!
Haku wouldn't steal.
He's a good person.
Ha, do you know why he became my sister's apprentice?
To steal her magic secrets
and now he's stolen my magic, too.
He's a greedy little thief.
There's nothing good about him.
Step aside, little girl.
I'm going to take my seal back from him.
There's a spell on the seal,
and anyone who steals it will die.
No, you can't!
You idiots!
What's your problem?
Keep quiet, I don't want my sister coming up here.
Ow. A paper cuts.
Haku, we're falling!
Haku!
What's going on here?
Sen, be careful!
Stay back!
Are you okay, Haku!
What's wrong with you?
This looks serious.
Haku, don't give up!
What do we do?
Is he dying?
It looks like he's bleeding from the inside.
From the inside?
I think so, maybe he swallowed something.
Haku, I got this gift from the River Spirit.
Eat it.
Maybe it'll help.
Come on!
Open your mouth!
Please, Haku!
Eat it!
See?
It's okay.
Medicine from the River Spirit.
Open your mouth.
That's it.
Got it.
Now swallow.
Sen, look there!
The gold seal!
Get that black slug!
Over there!
Get it, get it, get it!
You killed it, those things are bad luck.
Hurry, before it rubs off on you!
Put your thumbs and forefingers together.
Evil, be gone!
Haku stole this seal from Yubaba's sister.
Zeniba's solid gold monogrammed seal.
That's as powerful as it gets.
Look!
He's changed back.
Help me.
What do we do?
Haku, Haku, wake up!
Zeniba put a curse on the seal.
That's strong magic, it's made him gravely ill.
That should make him more comfortable.
Poor Haku.
He's had it hard ever since he got here.
He just showed up out of nowhere, just like you did.
But he got mixed up with Yubaba.
He took a job as her apprentice.
I warned him it was too dangerous.
"Just quit, go back home!", I told him.
But he said for some reason he had no home to return to.
Once Yubaba got control over him,
his face turned pale and his eyes turned steely.
He's never been the same.
Kamaji, what if I take the gold seal back to Zeniba?
I could give back the seal and apologize to her for Haku.
Can you tell me where Zeniba lives?
You'd go to Zeniba's?
It might help, but she's one dangerous witch.
Please?
Haku helped me before, now I wanna help him.
Hmm.
I know how you can get there,
but you'll have to get back on your own.
Wait here.
Let's see now, I know it's around here somewhere.
Everyone, I need my shoes and clothes, please.
I guess my parents will have to wait.
Sen, I've looked everywhere for you.
Lin!
There's blood everywhere.
What's going on here, who are those guys?
I picked up some new friends, see?
Everyone's looking for you, Yubaba is furious.
Huh?
The guy with all the gold turned
out to be a monster called No-Face.
And he says that you let him into the bathhouse.
I did let him in.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I thought he was a customer.
What?
He's a monster, he's already swallowed three people.
Found it!
Here it is, Sen.
Hey, we're busy, boiler man.
You can use this.
You've got train tickets?
Uh, how did you get a hold of them?
I've been saving them for 40 years.
Now, listen carefully.
The train stop you want is called Swamp Bottom.
Swamp Bottom?
That's where Zeniba lives.
The sixth stop.
Sixth stop.
Make sure you get it right.
The train used to run in both directions,
but these days it's a one-way ride.
You still wanna go?
Yep, I'll walk back along the tracks.
Sen, what about No-Face?
I'll take care of that now.
Haku, I'll be back soon, just hold on.
What's going on?
Something you wouldn't recognize
it's called love.
He just keeps getting bigger!
I'm scared.
I don't wanna be eaten by it.
It's her.
Oh, Sen, thank goodness.
Yubaba can't hold him off much longer.
There's no need to get upset.
I'm sure they'll find Sen somewhere.
Where is Sen?
I want Sen!
Hurry!
This way!
Madam, Sen is here now.
Finally!
Sen has arrived, sir.
She'll be with you in just a few minutes.
He's destroying everything, it's costing us a fortune.
So suck up to him and get every last speck of gold he's...
Choo!
Eww, what's that dirty mouse doing here?
Huh?
He's your...
He doesn't look familiar?
Familiar, don't be stupid.
Now, get in there.
Here's Sen.
Will Sen be all right in there by herself?
You wanna take her place?
Huh?
Hmpf!
Try this.
It's delicious.
Want some gold, I'm not giving it to anybody else.
Come closer, Sen what would you like?
Just name it.
I would like to leave, sir.
I have some place I need to go to right away, please.
You should go back to where you came from.
Yubaba doesn't want you in the bathhouse any longer.
Where is your home, don't you have any friends or family?
No.
No!
I'm lonely.
What is it that you want?
I want Sen, I want Sen!
Take the gold.
Take it!
Are you going to eat me?
If you want to eat me, eat this first.
I was saving this for my parents,
but I think you'd better have it.
Sen!
Sen, what did you do to me?
Enough, I don't care if he's rich!
This nonsense has gotta stop!
No-Face!
Over here!
Run for your life!
Now, that's an esophagus!
I'll get you for this, Sen!
Excuse me.
Sen, this way!
Hey, over here!
Sen, don't call him over!
I think being in the bathhouse makes him crazy.
He needs to get out of there.
Yeah?
And go where?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Great.
Now he's following us.
He won't hurt us.
You'll have to walk from here.
Okay.
The station's just down the tracks.
Thanks, Lin.
You better come back, you hear me?
I will.
Sen, I'm sorry I called you a dope before!
I take it back!
No-Face, if you put even one scratch
on that girl, you're in big trouble.
There's the station.
Here comes the train come on.
Oh we'd like to go to Swamp Bottom, please.
Oh. You wanna come with us?
He'd like to come too, please.
Sit here, behave yourself, okay?
Kamaji, wake up.
Haku, you're all right.
I'm fine.
Where is Sen?
Did she go somewhere, can you tell me what's going on?
You blacked out, remember?
Yeah, l remember being in darkness.
Then I could hear Sen's voice calling out my name.
So l followed her voice, and the next thing I knew,
l was lying here feeling better than ever.
Pure love, it broke Zeniba's spell.
Sen left to return the golden seal.
She did it to save you.
This gold doesn't even come close to
covering the damage that stupid No-Face caused.
Sen didn't get nearly enough, she'll have to be punished.
Madam, you see, Sen was the
one that saved us from No-Face.
Yes, yes.
So what, this whole mess is her fault!
And now she's run away from here.
She's even abandoned her own parents!
Those pigs must be ready to eat by now.
Turn them into bacon.
Wait a minute.
Huh?
Master Haku?
You're still alive, what is it you want?
You still haven't noticed that something
precious to you has been replaced.
Don't get fresh with me, young man.
Since when do you talk that way to your master?
Huh.
My baby!
No!
It's just dirt.
Where's my baby?
Where are you, sweetie?
Come out, please, come out!
Where are you?
Sweetie, sweetie pie!
You!
Where is he?
What did you do with my baby?
He's with your sister.
Zeniba?
Very clever, Haku, I get it.
You'll get my baby back for me, but at a price.
So, what do you want?
Tear up Sen's contract.
And then I want you to return Sen and her
mother and father back to the human world.
Fine, but on one condition.
I get to give Sen one final test.
If she fails, she's mine.
I hope this is the right stop.
Let's go.
You can ride on my shoulder if you're tired.
Come in.
Hello?
Hurry up, ll don't have all day.
Come on.
So, you all made it.
Hmm?
Sit down, I'll make some tea.
Excuse me, ma'am, Haku stole this from you.
I came to give it back.
I see.
Do you have any idea what this is?
Yes it's the golden seal you were looking for.
I'm here to apologize for Haku, I'm very sorry.
He sliced me in two, you know, and I'm still angry.
What?
What!
The protective spell is gone.
I'm sorry.
You mean that black slug that was on your seal?
I think I squashed it with my foot.
Squashed it?
That wasn't my slug.
My sister put that slug into
Haku so she could control him.
You squashed it.
What happened to my spell?
Only love can break it, come now.
Can you please turn these two
back into their normal forms?
The spell on those two wore off long ago.
Change back if you want.
I don't get along with my sister. She's so obnoxious.
You saw how tacky her home is.
We're identical twins, yet exact opposites.
I'm sorry she turned your parents into pigs.
But there's nothing ll can do,
it's just the way things are.
You'll have to help your parents and Haku on your own.
Use what you remember about them.
What?
Can't you please give me more of a hint than that?
It seems like I met Haku before,
but it was a long time ago.
That's a good start.
Once you've met someone, you never really forget them.
It just takes a while for your memories to return.
While you're thinking,
the boys and I are going to make you something.
And I want you to call me Granny from now on.
Ah, come on, keep at it.
No-Face, where did you learn to spin thread?
You're really good at this.
Now let's weave the threads together.
Knit one, pearl two, knit one, pearl two.
Knit one, that's right.
Granny, ll can't remember anything at all.
Haku could be dead already,
and I'm just sitting around here.
My mom and dad could've been eaten for dinner.
Wait just a little bit longer.
Ahh. There we go.
Use it to tie back your hair.
It's beautiful.
It will protect you.
It's made from the threads your friends wove together.
Thank you.
What good timing we've got another guest.
Will you let him in?
Sure.
Haku!
Haku.
Thank goodness.
You're alive, I can't believe it, how did it happen?
Ahh.
That's love for you.
Look Granny, Haku's alive!
Haku, I will forgive you for stealing my precious seal.
But in return, you must take care of this girl.
Okay, you two, it's time to go home.
Come back soon.
No-Face, why don't you stay with me?
I could use a good helper.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Granny!
Thank you so much, I'll miss you.
Don't worry.
You'll be all right, Sen.
I want you to know my real name.
It's Chihiro.
Chihiro.
What a pretty name.
You take good care of it.
I will.
Off you go.
Okay.
Bye.
Granny, take care, thanks for everything!
Haku, listen.
I just remembered something from a long time ago.
I think it may help you.
Once, when I was little, I dropped my shoe into a river.
And when I tried to get it back, I fell in.
I thought I'd drown, but the water carried me to shore.
It finally came back to me.
The river's name was the Kohaku River.
I think that was you, and your real name is Kohaku River!
You did it, Chihiro, I remember.
I was the spirit of the Kohaku River.
A river spirit?
My name is the Kohaku River.
They filled in that river.
It's all apartments now.
That must be why I can't find my way home, Chihiro.
I remember you falling into my river,
and ll remember your little pink shoe.
So you're the one who carried me back into shallow water.
You saved me!
I knew you were good!
Hey, there they are!
I see you failed to bring my baby back.
Mama!
My baby!
Are you traumatized?
Did they do terrible things to you?
You're standing all by yourself, when did that happen?
Don't forget your promise.
You must return Chihiro and
her parents to the human world.
Hmm, not so fast, Haku.
I get to give Sen one final test.
Shut up!
Stop it, Mama, leave her alone.
Sen and I had a really good time.
But a deal is a deal, sweetie.
I have to give Sen one final test.
If you make Sen cry, I won't like you anymore.
But?
Hey, Granny!
Granny?
You're right, a deal's a deal.
Okay, I'm ready, I'll take your test.
Hmm.
You've got guts.
I've got your contract right here.
Come this way.
This will only take a minute.
Don't worry.
See if you can tell which of
these pigs is your mother and father.
You get one try.
If you get it right, you can all go home.
There must be a mistake.
None of these pigs are my mom or dad.
None of them, is that really your answer?
Mm-hmm.
Ah!
Oh, you got it!
Thank you, everyone.
All right, you win.
Get out of my sight.
Thanks for everything, Granny.
Goodbye!
Thank you!
Haku!
Let's go!
Where are my mom and dad?
When you passed the test,
they woke up on the human side of the river.
They're there now, and they're looking for you.
There's no water here.
I can walk across now.
But I can't go any farther.
Just go back the way you came, you'll be fine.
But you have to promise not to look back,
not until you've passed through the tunnel.
What about you, what'll you do?
Don't worry, I'll go back and have a talk with Yubaba.
I'll tell her I'm going to quit being her apprentice.
I'm fine, I got my name back.
Will we meet again sometime?
Sure we will.
Promise?
Promise!
Now go, and don't look back.
Chihiro!
Where have you been, hurry up!
Mom, Dad!
You shouldn't run off like that, honey.
You could get in big trouble.
Are you guys sure you're all right?
Let's go, I don't wanna miss the movers.
Chihiro, hurry up.
Everybody, watch your step.
Chihiro, don't cling like that, you'll make me trip.
We made it.
Hey what happened?
What is it?
Look at that.
It's all dusty inside too.
Is this someone's idea of a joke?
Looks like it.
l told you we shouldn't have stopped.
Come on, Chihiro, let's get to our new home.
You're not scared, are you?
Don't be afraid, honey.
Everything's gonna be okay.
A new home and a new school?
It is a bit scary.
I think I can handle it.