[TAKEZO]
Strange.
The atmosphere seems
really tense today.
Please don't worry.
Unlike you,
I'm a good judge of character.
Kurusu?
[HIRO]
Yeah, what?
[TAKEZO] I'm a little worried
about today's practice.
Are you feeling
sick by any chance?
Kurusu?
What's the matter?
[HIRO] Oh. It's nothing,
everything is hunky dory!
Come on, then!
We should start practicing!
Uh. Okay.
[CHIKA]
Crap.
I didn't think things were
gonna be this awkward.
Even though it was an accident,
it was bad enough
to make her cry.
I'm sure she'll forgive
me if I apologize.
Hozuki!
[SATOWA] Why the heck am I
avoiding him all of the sudden?
I should have
said something like:
"Oh please, it's not
that big of a deal."
Then things could have
gone back to normal!
[MITTSU] Rawr!
Are there any naughty kids?
[KOTA]
We're gonna eat you!
Just kidding, got ya!
Did you guys get scared?
You like the costumes that
we made for the haunted house?
[MITTSU] Man, we must
have done a really good job
because Chika and
Hozuki are speechless!
[KOTA]
Hooray!
It was a huge success!
[HIRO]
Uh! Shoot!
I made another mistake!
[CHIKA]
None of us are together.
Yeah. That's it.
Let's call it quits for today.
Wait, what for?
Nothing good is going to come
from poor quality practice.
If you really wanna continue,
then do it individually
and not as a group.
[HIRO] It's my fault;
I couldn't focus at all.
[SANE]
I'm sorry!
I just need to practice more
with the 17-string.
We're lacking unity because I
can't lead you like Hozuki can.
So, I'll have
to try even harder!
[HIRO] I have no
business being distracted
when everyone else
is working so hard.
Even Suzu has been
more motivated lately.
What's my problem?
Come on!
Go, again!
But he just said.
It's my fault because
I wasn't focused earlier.
Sorry!
I know Suzu told us to stop,
but we don't have much
time left til the festival,
so let's keep going!
Yes, I agree.
Hiro's right.
Yay!
Let's do this!
Right.
[SATOWA] There's no
room for error right now.
What's important is
preparing for the festival.
[HIRO, SATOWA]
For the sake of the koto club.
I need to rein
in these feelings.
Hey. Are you all right?
[HIRO]
Huh?
Why wouldn't I be?
Oh. You seemed
kinda out of it.
Y'know, back at
practice earlier.
Yeah, I'm okay.
With the school
festival coming up,
I've just been a little
more distracted than usual.
[TAKEZO]
Ah.
That makes sense.
Sorry, I didn't mean
to make you worry.
I'm sorry, Kudo.
It was an accident, I should
haven't reacted like that.
You couldn't have known
that I was going to move.
It's all my fault things felt
so weird during practice today.
That's not true.
Okay then, that should
clear everything up.
Goodnight, see you tomorrow.
Yeah. Bye.
[TETSUKI]
Oh?
Sounds like it's all good, then.
I dunno man, I have a weird
feeling about the whole thing.
We should be back
to normal, right?
Uh.
Hey.
Morning.
Huh?
Oh, so I was wondering.
Sorry, I don't want to be late.
[TETSUKI]
It's not her fault.
Yeah, it may have
been an accident,
but it still made
her cry, right?
Her head wants
things to be normal.
But the heart's more tricky.
[CHIKA]
Dammit!
This wouldn't have happened
if I had quicker reflexes.
[TETSUKI]
I doubt it.
Anyway, try to give
her some space for now.
Things will probably
go back to normal with time.
[TAKEZO]
Hozuki?
Do you have a shortlist ready
for the national qualifier yet?
[SATOWA] Yes, I brought
a few pieces with me.
So cool!
There are a lot of different
songs to choose from.
[MITTSU]
This one is interesting.
Hey, Chika, come look
at these CDs with us.
Okay.
So, what are they?
Let me see what you have, Sane.
I just have to give
her time and space.
Things will go back to normal.
Haunted house!
Please come check
out our haunted house!
Hi, Hiro!
[HIRO]
Kota!
[KOTA]
Aaww, cute costume!
You look great!
[HIRO giggles]
Thank you!
But weren't you guys
wearing different
costumes the other day?
The girls in our class
didn't like them very much.
We had to change.
Well, they look nice!
I'm so sorry I'm late!
[TAKEZO]
Huh? No!
It's fine.
I'm sorry that you
had to shop by yourself.
[HIRO]
Wow! He's so cute!
No!
Is something wrong?
[HIRO] A school festival
may seem safe,
but I can't let my guard down!
By the way, I like your costume.
You look cute!
Shut up before I hurt you!
Sorry, ma'am!
[SATOWA] Thank you for waiting,
here's your matcha latte.
[STUDENT D]
Whoa, babe alert!
Let's ditch the festival.
You wanna go somewhere with me?
Sorry, but I still
have work to do.
[STUDENT C] Hold on,
we're not done talking yet.
[SATOWA]
Please let go of me.
I will, right after you tell me
a little bit more
about yourself.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Fine, my name is Chika Kudo,
I'm a Virgo born on September
second and my blood type is O.
Anything else you wanna know?
Nope. That'll do it.
[SATOWA]
What's wrong with me?
Why can't I look
him in the eyes?
My face feels so hot.
Why?
What do I do?
I just want things
to go back to normal.
Hey, you doin' all right?
Can you shut your mouth?
I'm fine, okay?
[TETSUKI]
Which is code for "not fine."
Come to 2-A, we have waffles!
I'm kind of glad
I picked the barker role.
At least I don't have
see Kurata so much.
Hello, welcome!
[MASHIRO] Excuse me, I was
wondering if Kurata is here?
Uh, yeah, he's inside.
Who's she?
[MASHIRO]
Takezo!
[gasps]
Whoa, wait.
Is that you Mashiro?
But what are you doing here?
Well, I'm here because I
wanted to come see you, silly.
You look so cute in that.
Hey. Cut it out.
Why didn't you
reach out and tell me?
[laughs]
I wanted to surprise you.
Oh, man.
I haven't been gone that long,
but you look so grown up!
Um. Thank you?
I'm really sorry.
I'm just beyond shocked that
you're actually here right now.
I don't know what to say.
Guess what?
We have a koto
performance today.
It'll be at 12:30
in the gymnasium.
I am so there!
I can't wait
to hear you guys play!
Wait, hold on.
Were you able to get
permission to use the stage?
As I recall,
you need at least
five people to get it.
Actually, the koto club
has seven members now.
Seven?
Wow.
That's awesome.
Great job, Takezo!
You must have
worked really hard.
I'm so proud of you!
Come on, I didn't do
anything that special.
[MASHIRO]
Yes, you did.
I'll see you at the performance.
Break a leg up there, okay?
Right!
Oh, hey there, Kurusu!
I'm really sorry, I should have
thought to introduce you to her.
That girl was actually the
previous koto club president
before me.
I was the only first year
in the club last year,
but she was very nice.
[HIRO]
So?
Huh?
It's not like it has
anything to do with me!
Huh? Oh, right. Of course.
Sorry.
[HIRO inhales]
Crap.
That was really mean of me.
I can't get rid of
my feelings for him,
and now I'm acting jealous?
What's wrong with me?
I'm the worst!
When we were first years,
I was too busy tricking
and hurting people
to get to know Kurata.
I just remember that he was
very involved with his club.
Everyone made fun
of him, including me.
I acted all high and mighty.
Like I was better than him.
I don't know what they've
been through together,
or what led to
their conversation.
But, despite that, he still
wanted me to be a part of it!
Kurata!
Look. Forget what I said!
I shouldn't have
lashed out at you, okay?
I'm sorry!
That girl.
She's important to you, right?
Then I promise to do my best
in the performance today.
So you can be proud of us!
Does that sound good?
[TAKEZO]
Kurusu.
I appreciate it.
Listen up, guys!
The old koto club prez is here,
so we have to do our best!
So, she was the president
to the president, huh?
That makes her like
our grand-president.
Then we'll do an extra good job!
Yeah!
Let's rock!
It's really not a big deal.
What's important
is that we have fun.
That's what she always told me.
Everything's fine.
There's something my
upperclassman said once.
She told me,
the stage is a reward
for all the hard
work you've put in.
That's why you have to
enjoy it as much as you can.
[HIRO]
It does have to do with me.
I was already connected to her.
[TAKEZO] Back when
I was the only club member,
it was her words that
kept me from giving up.
So, today is special.
Because I can finally
show her just how much
the koto club has grown!
Thanks, everyone!
[STUDENT A]
For our next performance,
we have the school's koto club.
This is great.
There really are seven, and so
many of them are boys, too!
♪ upbeat tempo ♪
That's such a beautiful song!
Don't they look like
they're having fun up there?
[TAKINAMI]
They've been all over the place
during practice lately,
and if I were being completely
honest with myself.
I was worried they
would be distracted
during today's performance.
But I guess they're
pretty similar.
When it comes to
the important things,
they're all on the same page.
These kids are
an interesting group.
Oh, wow! Just wow.
You guys were so great!
You think so?
Do you really mean it?
[MASHIRO]
Of course!
And the way you all
managed to stay together?
I'm so impressed!
Honestly!
Yay! You're so sweet,
Miss Mashiro!
[TAKEZO]
She hasn't changed a bit.
Right, that's enough.
I'm glad you're all getting
along but stop monopolizing her.
Besides, I'm sure she and Kurata
still have a lot of
catching up to do.
Why don't you two
take some of this time
to go and chat a little?
[TAKEZO]
Oh, but--
[HIRO]
Go on.
Uh, Kurusu?
That was your name?
Yes. That's right.
Thank you for everything.
I can tell you're doing a
great job as vice president.
Takezo's so lucky.
I suppose so.
Thank you.
This girl is really cute.
Okay, I'll be back.
No problem, take
all the time you need!
--She's such a nice girl.
--Yeah!
[TAKINAMI]
Was that okay?
Um. Yeah. Of course it was.
All right.
I need to talk
to you right now!
That was weird.
And really sudden.
I was super surprised
by how good you guys are
and how many
members you have now!
I appreciate that.
I'm really glad our
hard work has paid off.
Initially, I was
a little worried
because I didn't want
to break my promise to you.
About protecting the club.
But then I made all
of these new friends.
Luckily I remembered
everything you told me.
And that's what I relied on
when things got tough.
You mean it?
To be honest, Takezo,
I was actually kinda worried.
I was afraid I'd put
too much pressure on you.
Leaving the fate of the club
in your hands and everything.
What?
I guess in my eyes,
laying those expectations on you
seemed pretty selfish, y'know?
When I saw you standing alone
at the clubroom on
our graduation day,
I couldn't help but think about
how you'd have to recruit
more club members and perform
all the activities by yourself.
I was worried
how you'd handle it
and how much work it
was for one person.
I was afraid that maybe I'd
burdened you with my words.
Backed you into a corner
that you couldn't get out of.
What if I'd made the
club your responsibility
only to have
it fall apart around you?
Isn't that terrible?
It means I didn't have
complete faith in you.
I'm really sorry.
It's fine, no big deal.
Are you serious?
Of course I am.
It's okay.
Listen, I know you feel like
you didn't have faith in me.
What you said.
Those words gave me power
when I needed it most.
[MASHIRO] Y'know, you're acting
like a real club president.
[TAKEZO]
Hey, who said it's acting?
Look. Just be honest.
You...
You know about me.
Right?
Huh? What do I know?
[HIRO]
Come on, you have to know!
Isn't that why you said
that thing earlier?
Did I say something?
[HIRO]
Stop messing with me!
I'll get rid of these
stupid feelings, okay?
I'll make sure that
I won't cause trouble
for the rest of the club.
So, please.
Is there a reason why you
have to get rid of them?
Well, yeah.
It's because... You know...
Everybody in the club
is working so hard.
I can't afford to be distracted.
It's not fair to the others
and it's selfish.
Look, you can't control what
you feel and more importantly.
There's nothing selfish
about liking someone.
I also don't understand why
you're so worried
about causing trouble.
Thing is,
we're always gonna
cause problems for others,
and they'll cause
problems for us.
There's no getting around that.
[HIRO]
So...
What exactly are you saying?
Nothing special, you know me,
I just say what's on my mind.
If a club up and fails
because another member
has a crush on someone else,
then it only speaks
to the level of that club.
If you ask me,
you should turn your
feelings into power.
[HIRO]
Turn them into power?
Is it really okay to do that?
[SANE]
Done putting the kotos away!
[KOTA] Do you think Hiro and
Mister Takinami are coming back?
Maybe.
He said he wanted to talk to us
about the piece
for the qualifier.
[MITTSU] Well then, we should
go check out the food stalls
while we still have the chance.
All right!
You guys go, I'll wait here
for them to get back.
[SANE] Don't worry, we'll bring
you back something delicious!
[SATOWA]
Thanks a lot.
[SANE]
Come on, Chika!
I'm not super hungry,
so I'll wait here with Hozuki.
[SANE] You gotta eat,
you're a growing boy!
[CHIKA]
What are you, my mom?
Just go.
[SATOWA]
Oh no. What should I do?
Actually, I think
I'll go with them.
Hozuki.
Wait.
Yes?
Um...
Tell me.
I want to make things right
again, just tell me what to do.
Look Hozuki, the last thing
I'd ever wanna do
is make you uncomfortable!
Agh! I've wanted to apologize,
but you keep avoiding me.
I don't know what to say!
So, um...
For what it's worth to ya,
I'm truly sorry.
Oh. I...
Yo, Chika!
We ran into Mister Takinami!
Wait, wait, wait!
Why'd you close the door?
'Cause.
I didn't want to
interrupt your talk.
It's too late, bcause you're
here about the piece, right?
About the shortlist you gave me.
Oh, did you listen to them?
I was thinking about
choosing one of those.
[TAKINAMI] None of them sounded
right, so that's a hard no.
Hozuki.
Bring in all the koto
recordings you have.
We need more options.
[SATOWA]
Okay.
But what specifically
was the problem?
None of those pieces
will take you to nationals.
That was all.
[SATOWA]
But, as far as difficulty goes,
any of them would be more
than good enough.
Well, it's not a
matter of difficulty.
Play this song
for the time being.
We'll just have to keep
looking for another piece.
It's for hand movements.
Sorry.
I'm sure it'll be really boring.
Tell Kurata and Kurusu about it.
The next qualifier
will be the last chance
for them to make
it to nationals.
[ALL]
Huh?
[CHIKA]
What're you talking about?
They're second years.
Why is it gonna be
their last chance?
Hold on.
So you guys don't
know how that works?
The qualifier takes place
either in the fall or winter,
and the actual
nationals take place
in the summer of
the following year.
Even if they get past
the qualifier as third years,
they can't go to nationals
because the two of them
will have already
graduated by then.
If you lose in
the next qualifier,
then Kurusu and Kurata won't
ever make it to nationals.
To them, this is
their last opportunity.
[TAKEZO] I'm really glad
you came today, thank you.
[MASHIRO] Whatever,
the pleasure was all mine!
So, are you guys
entering the qualifiers?
We are.
You've got a really
strong koto club.
The nationals don't feel
like such a pipe dream.
You're closer than
we were, that's for sure.
Maybe.
Even though you
were all third years,
you aimed for nationals for my
sake, and that made me happy.
If we had passed that round,
it's not like any of you
could have gone over
to nationals with me,
but you tried anyway.
I think it would have been
cooler if we'd actually managed
to get the tickets to the
competition before we left.
Well, for what it's worth,
the fact that you tried
was still pretty cool.
[CHIKA]
Their last chance?
Then if we fail, it's over.
They're done competing.
No way!
[TAKEZO] Oh yeah,
one of the first years is
an exceptionally skilled player.
Then you need to practice.
All the first years
practice really hard,
and Kurusu improves
more and more every day.
Everybody's doing their best.
[TAKINAMI] If you don't want it
to be the last one for them,
then you'd better practice like
crazy for the next two months.
[TAKEZO] So I don't want the
next competition to be our last.
Be efficient and work hard.
Push yourselves.
Practice so much
that you know for a fact
no one tried harder than you.
Even with all that,
it will still be difficult.
[TAKEZO]
Together.
We'll fight!
Until the very end.
[MASHIRO]
Good luck!
Hey!
[KOTA]
Chika.
[sighs]
Hozuki.
Actually, don't bring in
the pieces you have.
Huh? Why not?
I'll drive.
I'd prefer to get
them right now.
It's a festival, missing
a few hours won't hurt.
If you say so,
and I would like to know
which piece we're going
to play as soon as possible.
Here, Kudo, this practice piece
uses the hirajoshi scale,
so you'll need the tuner.
[CHIKA]
Thanks.
[SATOWA, CHIKA]
Their last chance.
Damn.
None of these really stand out.
[TAKANAMI]
I found it.
[SATOWA]
Next time: "Reunion."