Yeah. I had a pretty hard
time facing Chika back then.
At least he was able
to pick himself up.
I think it's kind of awesome
that he's so focused
on understanding the koto
and protecting the club
that his grandfather started.
And while I'm sure we're not
all that much help to Chika,
we want to at least try
and be there for him.
Oops.
Uh. Sorry if I was rambling.
Can you please keep
this just between us?
Hey. Wait! Hozuki!
[SATOWA]
No way.
[KOTA] The group of
guys he used to hang with
smashed up his
grandfather's house
and the instruments he made,
and then they pinned
it all on Chika.
Everyone pretty much
hated him after that,
and then his grandpa
died a few days later.
And even though none
of it was his fault,
Chika still decided to take
responsibility for everything.
[SATOWA] Anyone who
would damage the instruments
doesn't have what it
takes to play the koto.
What should I do?
If we are forced to disband
because we can't get new
members, it'll be your fault!
What should I do?
Back off, a Neanderthal like you
would probably just
end up damaging it!
What should I do?
And who's fault is it that
we have to perform at all?
Hey, watch where you're going!
[gasps]
Whoa. Why are you crying?
I'm not; it's just
seasonal allergies!
Whatever makes you feel better.
If you want, I'll tell Specs
that you're runnin' a bit late.
[NISHINA] He wanted
to "earn what it takes."
[CHIKA]
I'll use them well.
Look, if you can't do it,
then you should just say so.
And if you don't know something,
then you should tell us, okay?
[SATOWA]
Sorry!
Um.
I heard all about
your grandfather.
About his shop and everything.
I said so many horrible things
and without even knowing
why you joined the koto club.
I'm sorry.
You're kinda scary
when you're nice, you know?
What?
I'm trying to be serious!
Oh, now, I get it.
Is that what you've been
out here crying about?
I guess even mean little
Satowa can be cute sometimes!
[SATOWA]
You're so annoying!
Don't be late to club, Kudo!
And sounds never lie.
They always reveal
a person's true nature.
His sound.
It's...
The koto club
will be performing?
Really?
Yes, at the school's morning
assembly, the week after next.
We must ascertain whether or not
these kids are actually serious.
We'll see their true colors.
And, if that's not the case,
we can drive Kudo
out of this school,
along with his fellow
delinquent club members.
Takinami, you're the
koto club advisor.
Are you opposed to any of this?
I'm not.
So feel free to proceed.
[SATOWA]
Stop!
Try playing that part with
a more focused sound.
What?
Would it sound focused if my
fingers had tougher callouses?
[SATOWA]
That's not what I meant.
Is there any way you can play
it like you did the other day?
[CHIKA]
What are you talking about?
Don't you remember
the other day,
when you were practicing by
yourself at the music store?
[CHIKA]
No, of course not!
You're so useless!
What?
Whoa!
I definitely understand
what you're trying to say.
Maybe a little gentler though?
Playing a focused sound at will
can be difficult for a beginner.
I suppose.
I should have known better
than to expect great
things from Kudo.
[CHIKA growls]
That's it!
Girl or not, you're dead!
Uh. That might have
been a little too far.
Ah! We made it to the
end without stopping
for the first time!
[SANE, MITTSU]
All right!
We got it.
I think we can do this!
Well, unfortunately, this is
the bare minimum of standards.
Can't you ever just be happy?
We've worked hard for this.
The audience expects for us
to be able to play the
song without stopping,
so it's not an accomplishment.
Come on, now.
This is a really big deal.
For us, anyway.
[SHIZU]
I've made some tea.
Why don't you kids take a break?
So, how bout it, Granny?
What did you think
of our performance?
Ah well, if it were a test,
I suppose you would
have squeaked by.
Uh, what the heck
does that even mean?
It's not meant to be an insult,
but you want to
satisfy your whole school
with this performance, right?
Moving people's hearts through
music is not something
that's easy to accomplish.
You're all practicing very well.
And you have
the technique down.
Your sound is strong.
So, the next step is learning
how to put your feelings
into your playing.
Our feelings?
How do you mean?
[SHIZU]
Well.
Why are you playing the koto?
Who do you want
your music to reach?
Just being conscious
of those thoughts
can change your tone completely.
Try playing your song as if
you're letting out the words
that you want to
tell your loved ones.
After all, sound is just
another language for those
who can't communicate
their feelings very well.
And that's why it's
perfect for a group of kids
who are as misunderstood as you.
[SANE]
Yo, Chika!
[KOTA] What are you
standing out here for?
That hurt, jerk!
It's too early
for all your nonsense!
Whoa. Did you really
set up our instruments for us?
Wow, you're the best!
Thanks, Hozuki!
Hey. Uh.
That's enough, dude.
You can't go around hugging
whoever ya want, got it?
I don't see why
it's such a problem.
We're all friends in the
same club, aren't we?
Oh?
Everyone's early today!
[KOTA]
Hey, good morning, Takezo!
[SATOWA]
Good morning.
We just got here
a few minutes ago.
Look! Everything's
already set up!
[SANE]
Hozuki actually did it for us.
[CHIKA]
Let's start practicing.
[TAKEZO] All these
people in the koto club
probably joined
for different reasons.
But I'm sure we all play
for the same reason.
All right, it's that time.
Now then.
You guys ready?
Let's grab the instruments.
[ALL 3]
Uh‐huh.
[SATOWA]
Wait.
The 17‐string is a little
hard for me to carry.
So you take it.
And I'll grab that one.
[CHIKA]
Hmm?
Aren't you afraid I'll
damage it, though?
Well, if you do, then
you can pay me back.
The entire student
body is out there!
There's so many.
[CHIKA]
Oh damn.
What is this?
I think my heart has somehow
moved into my ears.
Am I dying?
[ALL 3] Can we play
in front of all those people?
[TEACHER]
Okay settle down,
the morning assembly
is about to begin.
[TAKEZO]
What should I do?
As the club president,
I have to say something.
But I'm drawing a total blank!
[SATOWA]
We'll be just fine.
It doesn't matter
how nervous you are
or if your mind
forgets how to play.
because your hands
will remember.
Oh, Hozuki,
do you really think so?
After all,
you do have me here,
so there's nothing for you
to really worry about.
[CHIKA]
You braggy little‐‐
[SATOWA]
I see you found your voice.
Uh, Hozuki?
Hey. I'm sorry.
And thanks.
Sometimes I don't feel like
I'm a very good president.
That might be my fault.
I'm afraid I may have
overstepped my bounds a bit.
No, it's quite all right!
Thank you.
It's still a challenge for me.
I used to think that one
person's mistake in an ensemble
meant a mistake for everyone.
But now, if someone is
struggling in a certain area,
I know that we'll all be able
to help that person out
if they really need it.
Hozuki.
Whenever it comes
to playing the koto,
I get lost in it and can't seem
to think of anything else.
Whether you believe this or not,
you've been a big help.
[TEACHER]
Next there's an announcement
from our vice principal.
Let's get ready.
[VICE PRINCIPAL] Today we have
a special performance for you.
It's a presentation from
the school's koto club.
You see, around a month ago,
the members of the koto club
and I came to an agreement.
They promised me
that if they can't perform
in a manner that satisfies
the entire school,
then they will
disband immediately.
Whether or not they continue is
riding on everyone in this room.
Now, that is all I have to say.
I do wish the koto club
the best of luck.
[MALE STUDENT I]
What does that mean?
[MALE STUDENT J] I don't
even care what happens
to the koto club!
[MALE STUDENT C]
Man, this is so annoying.
You know.
I kind of get the feeling
they don't want us here.
It's cool.
I'm used to it.
If anything it actually
makes me less nervous.
A low bar will
be easy to surpass.
Yeah, I guess you have a point.
If no one's gonna listen anyway,
we might as well have fun.
Let's go play
our hearts out, guys!
We can't be embarrassed
if we don't have any shame.
Right!
What's more.
None of us are alone.
[TAKEZO]
All right!
Let's go!
[MALE STUDENT D]
Guess it's about to start.
[MALE STUDENT E] So why does
it matter what we think?
[FEMALE STUDENT A] Honestly, I
don't really care what happens.
Kind of you to let me watch
even though I'm an outsider.
How could you ever
think such a thing?
You're as big a part of
this school as anyone,
and you've been supporting
the club for a very long time.
What's more,
I got a special request.
[SHIZU]
Hmm?
[PRINCIPAL] You want
to invite someone to watch?
Might I ask who?
The music store lady.
I promised her
that she could hear
a really amazing performance,
so please say yes, okay?
So I couldn't bear to refuse.
Oh, you're the principal,
you could have just said
you'd let the club continue
no matter what happens
and put an end
to this silly charade.
Yes, I probably could have,
but I was curious.
To be honest,
I've been wondering
just what sort of sound these
kids would produce.
[MALE STUDENT F]
Kudo?
He's seriously going
to play the koto?
[MALE STUDENT G]
You've gotta be kidding me.
[MALE STUDENT H laughs]
Is that Kudo?
[TAKEZO]
Thank you for coming.
We in the koto club‐‐
Just get on with it already!
Nobody here cares about
your stupid performance,
so you can stop
wasting our time.
[MALE STUDENT B]
We don't have all day ya know!
[SATOWA] Whether
you believe this or not,
you've been a big help.
[TAKEZO]
You're wrong.
It was me.
I was the one being helped.
Whenever I'd wanna
run away or turn my back,
it was you guys
who kept me going.
If this is funny to you,
then go ahead and laugh.
If this is boring to you,
then go ahead and complain.
No matter what.
I refuse to lose the friends
who are precious to me,
or the place where I belong.
So we're going to play now.
[snickering]
[GEN]
Hey, Chika?
I was wondering
if it's a lot of work
to be so miserable
all the time?
Don't you have any
friends to hang out with,
or maybe there's
a special girl you like?
[CHIKA]
No, not really.
This whole thing is so stupid.
For real.
[gasps]
Huh?
♪ fast tempo ♪
What?
[gasps]
♪ ♪
Oh wow.
They sound so good!
♪ ♪
Ahh!
Way to get 'em, tiger.
They ran away like
scared little dogs.
Get off me.
[DELINQUENT E]
Jeez. What's his deal?
[DELINQUENT D] Leave him be,
he's always like that.
Besides, the dude has some
major trust issues to work out.
Probably best to just use him
when we need to win a fight.
[TAKEZO]
We're up to Hozuki's solo.
So far so good.
It's the cry of a dragon.
Huh?
Nothing.
I just thought I heard a dragon.
It's crying all alone.
Because it's never
known friendship.
[TETSUKI]
What the hell?
You can't just let yourself
into my place without asking.
Come on, man, aren't you
living with your grandfather?
Go home, already.
Just shut up.
I'm serious.
How long are you gonna
keep doing this crap?
I can't look out
for you all the time.
Fine, then.
Hold on, Chika!
Dumb brat.
[GEN] One of your friends
stopped by this morning,
to pick you up.
Who?
Uh, Testuki?
I think that's what he said.
He's a good kid.
To be honest, at this rate,
I was worried you'd quit school
and become a
good‐for‐nothing bum.
Or just fight all the time.
Yeah, so what if I did?
Listen, Chika.
It's too soon
to give up on yourself.
I don't want you
to forsake who you are,
especially when there
are still a lot of people
who haven't given up on you.
Just try to have a
little faith in everyone.
If you don't,
I'm afraid you'll find
yourself all alone one day.
How is that different
from right now?
[GEN]
Hmm?
So, you don't
understand this either?
You're an idiot.
[CHIKA]
No, I don't!
I don't want a dumb
little brat like you for a son.
Do me a favor and never
show your face here again.
Hey, did you hear?
That guy's parents just up
and abandoned him.
Kinda hilarious when you
realize his name is written
with the kanji
for "love," right?
[KOTA]
Oh, no!
I'm out of sync!
Huh? Weird.
Sounds off.
[MITTSU] Crap, I started playing
out of sync because of Kota!
[SANE]
Shit, they're distracting me!
[CHIKA]
Watch your timing, you idiots!
[TAKEZO]
Huh?! Oh no!
Our timing is
starting to fall apart!
What the heck is
wrong with you, Chika?
Do you wanna die?
C'mon, your grandfather
is worried sick about you!
I'm taking you home.
[CHIKA]
I don't care.
Let go.
Come on.
[DELINQUENT F]
Move it! Go!
[CHIKA] Those guys hang
out with Tetsuki.
You picked the wrong fight.
Now, you'll pay!
Whoa. Kudo?
[TAKEZO]
That's it!
She's making the first
beat of the bar louder
so it's easier stay together!
[SANE]
I can hear it!
[TAKEZO]
Follow Hozuki.
[CHIKA]
Her playing.
[ALL 5 GUYS]
We'll match her!
♪ ♪
[SANE]
We're back on track!
[TAKEZO]
Okay, we've made it this far.
Next is Kudo's solo.
[GEN] Hey Chika, about that
scrap you were in the other day,
I heard you only
jumped in there
because you wanted to
help your buddy's friends.
I shouldn't have called
you a brat, huh?
Can you forgive me?
I guess that means
you do have a heart of gold.
Ya big softy!
Stop it!
I made you something.
Check it out, I whipped up
some cute rice balls!
Yeah, don't you youngsters
like that kind of thing?
That's what I heard.
And see?
They're even
shaped like animals.
They're beary good!
Are they now?
Huh?
Just now. I saw you smile!
A real live smile!
Yeah. So, what?
What do ya know about that?
I've always wondered
what it would look like.
You know what?
I hope you can find more people
who can help you smile.
It's okay if there's
not many of 'em.
As for your hands,
I wish you would stop using them
to hit or hurt other people.
Instead, use them to protect
something important to you
and seize your happiness.
[SATOWA] Kotos are
there in order to connect
the hearts of the players
and the audience.
[SATOWA] I believe they're
meant to fulfill that wish.
[SHIZU] Try playing your song as
if you're letting out the words
that you want to
tell your loved ones.
♪ pretty, delicate solo ♪
[CHIKA]
Grandpa.
You can hear this.
[CHIKA]
Right?
♪ pretty, delicate solo ♪
♪ kotos join in one by one ♪
♪ tempo speeds up ♪
♪ fast tempo ♪
[TAKEZO]
This is it!
The final push!
[CHIKA]
Reach them.
Reach out to them!
[silence]
[TAKEZO] Next time,
"An Invisible Boundary."