[TAKEZO] We're almost
done with all the repairs.
Soon we can get back
to normal club stuff!
[SATOWA] Even with
the instruments back,
if we don't get two more
members within the month,
we'll be disbanded, and
thanks to a certain someone,
whose name starts with a
"K" and ends with an "Udo,"
we haven't had any prospects.
[CHIKA]
How is that my fault?
Well, for starters,
you have a reputation for
being a no‐good delinquent.
If there were any potential
members interested in the club.
You probably scared
them all away.
If that's the case,
Miss Holier Than Thou,
why don't you invite some
of your girlfriends to join?
Oh, wait a sec,
that's not an option, is it?
'Cuz ya got no friends!
Very funny.
I don't have any friends because
I've yet to meet someone
my age who's on my level,
so get off my back.
Regardless!
If we're forced to disband
because we can't get new
members, it'll be your fault.
Huh?
Man. If people are afraid
to join 'cause of me,
then we're better off
without 'em, in my opinion.
Chika! Hey, buddy!
[CHIKA yells]
Get off, Kota!
What's up, Testuki? Chika?
[TETSUKI]
Sane! Mittsu!
It's been a while, Chika.
We heard a rumor that
you joined the Koto Club.
Following in your
late grandpa's footsteps.
That's fairy tale stuff, man!
Stop it, you guys
are so annoying!
Crap.
Whoa! Gorgeous! Who's she?
Good afternoon, Kudo!
Are these handsome boys
friends of yours, perhaps?
[ALL 3] Yes! We are
Kudo's handsome friends!
Well, hello!
My name's Satowa Hozuki;
I'm in the Koto Club, too.
[MITTSU]
Hi there!
Hey! Watch out, guys!
That's actually a wolf
in sheep's clothing,
and she'll eat you!
You shouldn't say mean things
about such a delicate flower.
It's rude, man.
I'm so jealous you get to be in
the same club as this cute girl.
Heck, maybe I should
join the Koto Club too.
[SATOWA]
Oh! You should!
Huh?
We're actually short
a few members.
If nothing changes soon, I'm
afraid we'll have to disband.
Plus,
it'd be great to have a couple
more handsome guys in the club.
It would make me so happy.
We'll all join!
You guys are crazy!
Please refer to us as
the Koto Club's saviors!
What the hell is your problem?
Those idiots are actually
considering joining us!
Now what?
Relax, they don't even
have to play the koto.
All I need from those
three morons are their names.
Once they're listed
on our club roster,
we lose the risk
of being disbanded.
[CHIKA]
Evil.
You know,
these stunts are the reason
why you don't have any friends.
It doesn't really matter.
After all, I'm used
to being by myself.
[SANE]
And there you have it!
We are the Koto club's Saviors:.
Saneyasu Adachi.
Michitaka Sakai.
And Kota Mizuhara!
[TAKEZO]
Our saviors?
Someone want to
tell me what's going on?
[CHIKA] Don't worry, I'm sure
they'll get bored and leave.
Damn those reprobates.
[SANE]
Whoa, awesome!
There're so many!
Perfect, the noisy
one multiplied.
Here, plectrums and their bands.
Find some that fit.
[TAKEZO]
Hozuki?
Would you mind picking
some plectrums out for Kudo?
Why can't you do it?
Because I should
help with damage control...
...for their sake.
Give me your hand.
[CHIKA]
So, hey,
I don't really know
much about koto schools.
But I guess that would mean your
folks probably play, too, huh?
Yes, what of it?
Nothing really.
I was just wondering
if you learned how to
play from your parents.
That's not something
you need to know.
Huh?!
[CHIKA] What's with
this girl's finger tips?
They're hard as rocks.
Whoa.
My own plectrums.
Are you sure we only need three
of these plectrum thingies?
[TAKEZO]
Yep.
You use your
fingers for the rest.
[SHIZU]
Is everyone finished?
Oh, yes, ma'am.
In that case,
that's 5,000 yen each.
What? For real?
We have to pay for this crap?
[TAKEZO] Shoot. I didn't
think about this part.
[CHIKA]
Look, I can bring more tomorrow.
But for right now,
will this do?
And do you have a way
of getting more money?
[CHIKA]
I'll figure it out.
Good 'cuz it's not like I have
a money tree out back.
You gotta pay.
[CHIKA]
Then...
Once I've saved up enough,
I'll come back for them.
[TAKEZO]
I'm sorry, Kudo.
I didn't really think ahead.
[CHIKA]
Yeah, obviously!
Huh?
I suppose you did
help us repair the kotos.
Since it was a
fair amount of work,
I'll consider that your payment.
So then, uh, what about us?
[SHIZU] You think I'm dumb
enough to give away equipment
to freeloaders who
don't even want to play?
Probably not.
I'll use them well.
[SHIZU]
Hmm...
I know, that's why
I'm giving them to you.
[TETSUKI]
So, how were the guys yesterday?
Useless, of course.
And they bailed early.
Ah, so the usual?
There's no way they're gonna
stick with the club, y'know?
Plus, those guys never
commit to any... thing...
Hey, man! Why're ya late?
Do you know how
to play the koto?
Why are you guys even here?
Nah. Old instruments
aren't really our thing.
But hey, you can still enter
competitions without us, right?
Now that our names on the
roster, your club is safe!
Yay! We're such geniuses!
Yeah, sure.
I can't believe they actually
fell for that banshee's trap!
I got ya! Hah! I win again!
[CHIKA]
Cut it out, idiots!
If you're gonna roughhouse,
do it somewhere else!
[VICE‐PRINCIPAL]
Well, just as I thought.
I suspected this
might be a ruse.
Uh, Vice‐Principal, sir!
[CHIKA]
Crap.
Much like this card,
this club is nothing
more than a joke!
And I'm sure
the principal will find th‐‐
No one would join the
Koto Club just to mess around!
[VICE‐PRINCIPAL]
If that's the case,
why don't you all
play me something?
But that's impossible!
We haven't even had
the chance to practice yet.
[VICE‐PRINCIPAL]
Then I'll give you a week.
If within that time you
can perform in a way
that satisfies me,
I'll approve of the club.
Whoa, that soon?
Okay, bring it on!
‐‐A week's all we need anyway‐‐
‐‐[SATOWA] One month.
Just give us that much time.
And we could do it.
[TAKEZO]
Hozuki!
Please, excuse me,
I'm so sorry to cut in,
but I'm also a member
of the Koto Club.
That so?
While we could probably
manage a simple piece
within a week.
I doubt such a low caliber song
would satisfy your curiosity.
But if we had a whole month,
we could change that.
We could perform a piece
that the entire school
would approve of.
What are you saying?
[VICE‐PRINCIPAL laughs]
Are you serious
about that request?
Yes, I am.
[VICE‐PRINCIPAL]
All right, fine then.
I'm looking forward
to hearing you in a month.
Ah... You set us up for failure!
No matter what we end up
playing for the vice‐principal.
He'll probably just write it
off, and say he isn't satisfied.
But if our club were
to put on a huge performance
for the entire school,
then at that point he'll have
no choice but to approve us.
[TAKEZO]
You make it sound easy.
But won't it be a
bit of a challenge
for our three newest members?
[CHIKA growls]
‐‐Get lost!
‐‐[ALL 3] Sorry!
You realize without
those three idiots,
we'll be short members
and still have to disband.
[KOTA sighs]
I feel like we let Chika down.
Well, whatever, it's not like
we can actually play the koto.
If anything,
we'll hold the club back.
[TEACHER] What are we
going to do about them?
[VICE‐PRINCIPAL]
I don't believe for a second
that Kudo and his friends
want to play the koto.
A month from now that pitiful
club will be disbanded.
And that's how we'll
get rid of the little punk.
Kudo should be off
in a reform school
rather than sullying our
halls with his presence.
[MITTSU]
Sane!
Question for ya.
How come you always hang out
with that Kudo kid from class C?
[TETSUKI] Huh?
We've known each other forever.
But I hear the guy's
nothing but trouble,
so shouldn't you stop
hanging around him so much?
[TETSUKI chuckles]
Maybe so.
Tetsuki's acting so weird.
What's his deal lately?
Hey!
"Hey"?
You picked the wrong fight.
Now you'll pay!
[SANE]
No!
Whoa. Kudo?
You're gonna regret that.
Bastard!
Kudo. Why'd you help us?
It's not like we're
friends or anything.
I helped you out because you
guys are friends of Tetsuki's.
[SANE]
He risked his life for us
just because we were friends
of his friend, simple as that.
[SANE] To be honest, I'd
planned on returning the favor
the next time he
got into a big fight,
but now I think there
might be another way.
[MITTSU] Well, it looks like
we all had same idea, huh?
[SANE]
Huh? You, too?
We should at
least try, you know?
We do kinda owe him, after all.
Yeah, it'll be one way
to return the favor.
Yo, Granny!
You up?
We need three sets of
those finger things, please!
[CHIKA] What the hell are
you guys doing back here?
Tch! Come on.
Did you really think we'd run
away 'cause things got hard?
It's like you
don't know us at all.
We'd never abandon a pretty girl
in her most desperate hour!
My, how chivalrous!
So does that mean you all want
to become official
members of the Koto Club?
Uh‐huh! That's right!
Yay!
I'm glad that you're even more
simple‐minded than I thought.
You stupid fools.
[ALL 3]
Huh?
[SATOWA] Now that
you're all official members,
prepare yourselves.
Because I won't go easy on you.
Is that understood?
[ALL 3] Uh. Hozuki?
What happened to you?
[CHIKA]
I told you guys!
[SATOWA] Let's start with a
basic explanation of the koto.
A typical koto has 13 strings.
When played, there are moveable
bridges underneath the strings.
Which are tuned to the
sounds needed for each piece.
Music is written in
traditional koto notation,
or in staff notation, like you
might see with the piano.
That's it.
Here, now play this simple
piece called, "Sakura, Sakura."
[ALL 3]
Huh?
That fast?
You're a terrible teacher!
I disagree.
Actually playing a song
will help you learn faster
than if I just lectured you,
Or maybe you're
afraid you can't do it?
Bring it on!
I can play it just fine,
I'll show ya!
What is this?
Just call me "teacher," punk.
[CHIKA]
Crap!
Uh, if I remember right it's...
One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven.
Oh, it's this one!
[CHIKA]
Seven, seven again, then eight.
[CHIKA laughs]
Told ya!
This is a piece of cake!
Let's see, next up...
...an eyeball?
Guys, I don't wanna
play the koto anymore,
it's too hard and no fun.
[SATOWA]
Takezo.
A month from now,
this club will probably
have to disband.
Uh. They're not that
bad, are they?
It would help if any
of them possessed
even a modicum of talent.
[CHIKA]
We're not done yet!
We're just gonna have
to keep practicing!
Wow, Kudo.
Well, I do have an idea that
may help move things along.
We could completely skip over
the basics and focus on learning
the piece that we're going
to play one month from now.
Yeah, but we haven't
even decided
what we're going to play yet.
[SATOWA] I actually have
a piece I was considering.
Huh?
Although, it might
be impossible for them.
I'll play it!
I don't care how
difficult the piece is!
I will learn it!
In that case...
...will you please
go watch this?
They'll be performing
the piece there.
Oh... They're playing
out here in the open?
[TAKEZO]
Uh, Hozuki?
Why does it seem
like you're in disguise?
Probably because I am.
I'm pretty well known when it
comes to the world of the koto.
[TAKEZO]
Oh, I see.
By the way, what's the name
of the piece you're considering?
[SATOWA]
It's called "Ryuuseigun."
"Ryuuseigun"?
Hey.
What's up with that huge koto
in the middle of the stage?
[SATOWA]
Oh, that's the bass.
It has 17 strings
and is a low‐toned koto.
It's the core of this piece.
[HOST] Next is
"Ryuuseigun" by Taki Ayase.
It will be performed by students
of Hozuki Koto school.
Did he just say "Hozuki"?
Yes.
Today's performers
are none other than
the Hozuki school's elite.
Those kids are the "elite"?
Grade schoolers?
Oh man,
I actually feel relieved.
For real.
If those twerps
can play the song,
then we'll definitely be
able to play it in a month!
♪ ♪
So there you have it.
Let's do our best to learn this
piece before the month is up.
Say what?
I'm one thing.
But these idiots will
never learn that fast!
Hey, you can't play it either!
Uh. Maybe we should just
find a different song to play.
I think we'll be okay.
And honestly, aside
from the 17‐stringed koto,
the piece is fairly simple.
I can play that part, so relax.
Look, I'm sure that we
have enough club members
to make a good impact.
And as long as we work hard,
in a month the vice‐principal
and the whole school
will be just amazed
as you are right now.
Maybe.
Then again, if you
really think it's impossible,
then I suppose we can find
something else to play.
Maybe something
on a lower level?
[CHIKA]
Of course we can do it!
We don't need anything easier!
Do we, guys?
No, sir!
[SATOWA]
Thank goodness they're dumb.
Hold on.
There's one problem, the club
doesn't have a bass koto.
It'll be all right,
I'll just bring the
one I have at home.
Oh. I guess we're all good then.
I bet it's pretty
heavy, isn't it?
Want me to stop by your
place to help you get it?
[SATOWA]
No, it's fine!
[TAKEZO] I just thought
since it was bigger
than an ordinary koto.
[SATOWA]
I can handle it myself!
Who cares?
She's rich so she can
probably get her butler
or whatever to drive it over.
[SATOWA]
No one asked you.
Hey. Look, it's those kids.
[TAKEZO] I wonder if
that's their teacher?
Which means
it's Hozuki's mom, right?
Uh, Hozuki?
Don't you wanna go talk to them?
It's all right.
[SANE]
What should we do now?
[KOTA] Let's eat somewhere;
I'm starving!
Sure! You want something
nice or fast food?
Sorry, I'll have
to pass this time. Bye.
[SATOWA pants]
[CHIKA] Oh, is this
the 17‐stringed koto?
Uh! It's you!
Looks kinda heavy.
You want some assistance?
No! A Neanderthal like you
would most likely just
end up damaging it!
Uh... I see.
[SATOWA] "Ryuuseigun" is a
song with five different parts.
Basically,
each person in the club
will be responsible
for their own part,
and everyone's playing
something different.
Which also means...
We can't look at
someone else and play.
And we can't
pretend to play either.
Yes, that's correct.
And since all of you are
responsible for your own part,
there will be no running
away from our performance.
Ever.
[ALL 3 shriek]
[CHIKA]
There's no way I can play this!
[TAKEZO]
Are you okay, Kudo?
Yeah! Better than okay.
Let's get started already.
[SATOWA]
No! You play string six here!
How many times
do I have to tell you?
Ugh! But we go way too
fast to tell which is which!
Then you need to find a way
to make your body remember them.
[MITTSU]
Hey, can we stop here for today?
Yeah, good idea!
If we do too much too fast,
we'll all burn out.
Please, today doesn't
even count as real practice.
Starting tomorrow,
we'll practice in the
morning and afternoon.
The morning?
Huh?
Hey. You need to slow down
a little; this stuff takes time.
These guys are already
trying the best that they can.
Well, their efforts
are pathetic.
Not that you could
tell the difference.
Look, I may not know as
much about the koto as you do,
but I do know
that we're all trying!
Trying is not good enough!
And it won't keep
this club together!
At this rate,
we will be disbanded.
Try to understand,
we perform in front of the whole
school in just one short month!
And you guys can't even tell
which strings are which!
But you're the one who
told the vice‐principal
we could do it.
And who's fault is it that
we have to perform at all?
Well, it's getting pretty late.
We should call it.
Right?
Come on everyone,
let's clean up.
Whoa.
She's really that strict, huh?
Well, maybe she was taught
in that same
Spartan style, you know?
What?
[TETSUKI]
What I mean is,
people tend to teach in the
same way that they were taught.
If she's the daughter
of a grandmaster,
she probably
had it pretty tough.
[CHIKA]
You need to slow down a little!
[TAKEZO]
Hozuki.
Huh?
Takezo.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
[TAKEZO]
Oh, that?
Heh. Well, it's not
as if I was acting much
like a club president.
If everyone quits the club,
it'll be my fault.
What? Hold on!
I don't think anyone's
just going to up
and leave so suddenly!
Uh, actually, on second thought,
I'm not so sure about
the three new guys.
But not Kudo.
He's another story all together.
He won't quit.
Anyone would want to quit
after the way I acted yesterday.
[BOY] Why the heck are you so
serious all the time, Satowa?
All we wanna do is have fun.
But you act like
playing is life or death.
[GIRL]
I can't keep up with you.
Just play by yourself.
[SANE]
What's up, Chika?
What'd you wanna see us about?
[CHIKA]
Took you long enough.
I have something to give you.
I made 'em myself,
so you'd better use 'em!
Got it?
[ALL 3 laugh]
What the hell are
you laughing at?
For real?
You actually made these?
Why, Chika?
Huh? It's because I wanna make
that bossy snob speechless
for once, obviously!
[SATOWA]
What's this?
Is he planning some kind
of mean‐spirited prank?
Typical delinquent.
Okay, buddy.
Don't worry, we got you.
For sure,
by the time we're done,
she won't even know what to say!
See ya!
[CHIKA growls]
[SATOWA] Just as I thought,
he's pathetic.
[gasps]
[SATOWA]
Wait. What was that?
It looked like a
koto made of cardboard?
[CHIKA]
Let's see.
Five.
Five, and...
[SATOWA chuckles lightly]
[TAKEZO]
Not Kudo.
He's another story all together.
He won't quit.
The next one.
Let's see now. Six?
You know, It's better
if you don't write the names
of the strings on the side.
You saw?
[SATOWA]
If you have them there,
then you'll get into the
habit of relying on them.
Then again, in your case, you'll
probably need the whole month
just to memorize
which strings are which.
Hey!
[SATOWA]
Although,
I'll give you this much.
The form on the hand that you
use to play is actually perfect.
You must have had
an excellent teacher.
[gasps]
[SATOWA] Next time:
"The First Resounding Note."