[AKIRA] When I was little,
my big brother would run home
from as school fast as he could.
He'd dash straight to his
koto without stopping.
He couldn't wait to play
his favorite songs.
Soon, Mom would come
in and join him.
They'd start playing and
the room would be filled
with such happy sounds.
What a simple, gentle time
that was for all of us.
I really loved it.
Keishi's performance really
puts all the adults to shame,
doesn't it?
I can only imagine how proud
your family must be
to have such a
talented young heir!
Well. Uh. Yes.
[clapping]
[giggles]
Did you like hearing your
big brother play, Akira?
[AKIRA]
Mm-hm! Yep! I loved it!
Oh, wow! When you give
a sweet review like that,
you deserve an
encore performance!
It's my own arrangement
of a song by a rock band
I'm really into right now!
[DOJIMA, AKIRA'S MOTHER gasp]
--[koto playing]
--[KEISHI] Yeah!
[CHILDREN cheer]
Aw man, when grandma gets mad,
her lectures can
go on all night!
It really was such a
great performance, though!
I know, right?
Yep! Hey, do you
think that someday
I'll be able to play
like you, Keishi?
[KEISHI gasps, giggles]
Come on, don't be silly.
You'll play lots better
than me, Akira!
--[KEISHI laughs]
--[AKIRA whines]
[FEMALE DISCIPLE A]
Keishi really is amazing!
He gets first place in
every single competition.
Whoa. On TV? For real?
That's cool!
[giggles]
I wanna compete, too!
And be a genius!
I'll get first place, and I'll
shine just like Keishi does!
I know I will!
This is bad.
[AKIRA] But Keishi always
gets first place.
Is something
wrong with Akira?
She's feeling down because
she didn't win first place.
Hey, do you wanna go
play the koto together?
[AKIRA] No. How can I?
I'm a failure as a sister.
Akira...
[AKIRA] Keishi. Will you tell
me how to win first place?
[KEISHI grunts] You know, I was
just practicing some backflips
with my friends the other day.
[AKIRA]
That sounds dangerous!
I kept failing over and over
and I even hurt myself once.
But I kept on trying
and finally did it!
[AKIRA gasps] Mom! I'll enter
the next competition, too!
And I'll keep going
'til I get first place.
[AKIRA]
Since then,
I've participated in
many competitions.
I wanted to catch
up with Keishi.
I wanted to shine.
[AKIRA] But, what I finally
began to see clearly
as I worked hard and became more
skilled was not myself shining,
but the true nature of my
brother and his talent.
[AKIRA sighs] I came to realize
that he really was a genius,
but he still practiced
and worked harder
than anyone I knew. Constantly.
So I thought, "It's okay
that I'm not a genius.
I can still work hard,
like him."
Akira's been working
hard lately, huh?
She finally got second
place the other day!
The poor dear. She wants first.
--It'll happen. She will.
--[horn hinking]
[crashing]
[KEISHI pants]
Akira! Grandma!
Keishi. Our parents are...
[gasps]
[AKIRA, KEISHI sob]
[AKIRA] Just like that,
without any sort of warning,
our parents were gone.
[KEISHI sighs]
[AKIRA] Huh? Hold on,
what did you just say?
You heard me,
I decided to quit college
and get a real job instead.
Wait, but aren't you gonna
succeed the Tsubaki School?
Look, I'm sorry, but I'm
quitting the koto.
As for the school,
it's in your hands now.
No. You can't do that.
Why would you ever quit koto,
I don't get it! Stop! Keishi!
[AKIRA]
Why?
[DOJIMA] The income from
the Tsubaki School alone
is nowhere near enough
to support both you
and your brother.
[AKIRA]
But...
...Keishi's good enough to
perform professionally!
[DOJIMA] This is not an
easy industry to be in.
It'll take him a while
to start earning money.
[AKIRA] Well then, I'll just
have to quit high school
and get a job!
Oh, stop being ridiculous!
You're the last successor in
line for the Tsubaki School!
Learn to accept that.
It's just, the thought
of Keishi quitting koto--
[DOJIMA]
Listen to me.
Keishi has entrusted the
future of the school to you.
What are you saying?
That you'd betray his wish?
[AKIRA]
I don't understand.
Why is Keishi the one
who's quitting? Why?
[AKIRA]
"Mizu no Hentai"?
[DOJIMA] That's right.
Technique, singing, expression.
It's an unsurpassed
masterpiece on all counts.
I'm going to have you
focus on this piece
for at least the next two years.
[AKIRA]
What?
[DOJIMA]
As you well know,
your current ability is
nowhere near Keishi's.
And to be honest, many of the
disciples are worried as well.
So, I plan to intensely retrain
you using this piece,
and after your ability has
improved, I'll ensure you win
first place and attract the most
attention in the koto industry.
Then no one should have
any more complaints.
First place.
Understand? All you have to do
is work hard. Do it for Keishi.
[AKIRA gasps]
[AKIRA]
On that day,
my life of devotedly
facing the koto began.
I worked frantically. All so
I could replace my brother.
So the choice he made
wouldn't be for nothing.
How strange, it seems
that Hozuki girl
will also be in the
upcoming competition.
Really? But isn't she
still in middle school?
Yes, that's right.
How very conceited of her!
[AKIRA]
Hozuki is the parent school
that the Tsubaki
School belongs to.
The Hozuki heir was a girl
who'd been called a genius,
just like Keishi.
I'd heard her before and had
to admit, she was incredible.
Her performance
was flawless. Perfect.
And, somehow, unapproachable.
[KEISHI]
Hey, Akira. It's today, right?
I really wish I could get
off work to come see
your performance,
but I just can't.
It's fine.
But, maybe next time, I--
Sorry. I have to go.
[AKIRA] If I get through today,
I'm sure something will change.
[AKIRA] The light has to be
waiting for me. It has to.
[ANNOUNCER]
Entry number five. Akira Dojima.
"Mizu no Hentai."
[AKIRA gasps]
♪
[MALE JUDGE A]
She's good.
Masterful.
She puts such care into
each note she plays.
Both her singing and koto
technique are so pure.
Every note is beautiful.
[MALE JUDGE A] How deeply
she must have devoted herself
to the koto in
order to get here.
[AKIRA] So I thought. "It's okay
that I'm not a genius.
I can still work hard,
like him."
Then, someday, I'll do it.
I'll be able to get there!
To the top!
[AKIRA pants]
[CROWD cheers]
[AKIRA]
I did it.
I was able to give my
best performance ever!
[AKIRA]
I really did it!
[DOJIMA]
Well, that performance
pretty much sealed
first place for you!
[AKIRA]
You think so?
[ANNOUNCER] Next up is
entry number 13, Satowa Hozuki.
Playing "Yaegoromo"
[AKIRA]
The Hozuki girl.
It's amazing that she can play
"Yaegoromo" at her age.
But it's okay.
I know how she plays.
Even if she is a genius...
♪
[MALE JUDGE A gasps]
[DOJIMA gasps]
[AKIRA]
Her first note was all it took.
The technique and expression
I attained in the two years
I devoted myself
entirely to koto...
That same first note
crushed it all.
What? What is
this piece, anyway?
This isn't "Yaegoromo"!
This will get her disqualified!
[AKIRA] I realized then that
no matter how hard I worked,
I would never be able
to reach that place.
Our top award goes
to Akira Dojima.
[DOJIMA gasps]
See, Akira! They called you.
Snap out of it and get up there!
[AKIRA gasps]
[FEMALE CROWD A] What?
That other girl didn't win?
[FEMALE CROWD B] You dummy.
She got disqualified, remember?
[FEMALE CROWD A]
Oh, that's right.
Wait, what kind of piece did the
first-place winner play again?
[AKIRA]
Hey, do you think that someday
I'll be able to play
like you, Keishi?
[sobs]
[AKIRA]
No way! Disqualified?
After giving a
performance like that?
Don't you dare mock me!
It's insulting!
[AKIRA] I thought the light
had been waiting for me.
But what I found, instead...
...was an even deeper darkness
with no escape in sight.
[AKIRA] A short time
after the competition,
I heard that girl
was excommunicated.
Don't you see what an
opportunity this is?
The heir of the Hozuki School is
gone and you can take her place!
Ha! That grand master of
Hozuki isn't capable anyway.
What other option does
she have at this point?
Her daughter was
their only hope,
and look at the state she's in.
The school is just
an empty shell now.
[AKIRA]
Hm. It really is.
[AKIRA] What's with her?
I wonder why she doesn't get it.
The Tsubaki School is
an empty shell, too.
It has been ever
since Keishi left.
[AKIRA] How have I been
playing the koto up until now?
How have I been facing it?
[AKIRA] When talented people
are rapidly moving away
from the koto,
why is someone like me still
hanging onto it for dear life?
[AKIRA] It hurts, so much,
and I'm exhausted.
I don't even care anymore.
The thing is,
I went and joined the koto
club that's at my high school.
Please, I'm begging you.
[AKIRA]
What? A school club?
Talent, a big house,
an outstanding future.
She threw everything away.
What's her problem?
How far will she go
to insult someone
who's actually serious about--
[AKIRA] I just wanted
to know what it was.
What on earth could you want
so badly that you would throw
everything away and ruin the
lives of those around you.
I'm interested to know
its value. That's all for now.
Just kidding. I'm sorry.
I carried the joke too far.
Please forget it.
♪
[AKIRA]
The value. Just a single note.
[AKIRA gasps]
[AKIRA] That's all it takes.
You don't need to hear it.
You don't need to know.
You no longer need the light,
because you're not capable
of handling it anyway.
Okay, then. On the 17-string
part, start at the top.
♪
[AKIRA]
That's not good at all.
[CHIKA, SANE gasp]
[AKIRA] The sound
isn't clear. Try again.
♪
[AKIRA] This boy. He's an
incredibly fast learner.
He absorbs things as fast
as I can teach them.
[AKIRA] And this one is the
typical hard-working type.
I think he's got good intuition,
but he's almost pitifully...
...ordinary.
[AKIRA] It seems almost
cruel of Mister Takinami
to have these two boys
play the same part.
Next is the second koto part.
Okay, I'll do my best.
♪
[AKIRA] Stop there...
You're not putting
the right amount of pressure
on the string. Press harder.
--[HIRO gasps]
--♪
[AKIRA] Harder. That's only
raising the note by a half step.
--[HIRO gasps]
--♪
[HIRO] But I can't press
it any harder than this!
[gasps]
Your arm is open and
your shoulder is raised.
You can't press down
properly like that.
Don't just use
your arm to press.
Put your whole weight behind it.
[HIRO] Close my arm and
put my weight on it.
And don't raise my shoulder.
♪
[gasps]
That's good. Now, let's move on.
Ah! Damn it! Ever since she
mentioned this unclear sound,
I can't stop thinking about it!
[CHIKA gasps]
Wha--?
What do you
think you're doing?
I was just trying
to remember
how hard your fingertips
were, no big deal.
Even so, don't touch me
so casually, you stupid perv!
Sorry, what?
[CHIKA] Could she still
be holding a grudge?
[SATOWA whimpers]
[CHIKA]
So, you're okay?
[SATOWA gasps]
[CHIKA]
You've been kinda quiet today.
[gasps] I just had a
sore throat, that's all.
[CHIKA]
Oh, yeah?
Here.
[gasps] You really do
like strawberries, don't you?
Shut up. Got a
problem with that?
I appreciate it.
[SHIZU]
There you are.
A teacher I know had that
DVD you were asking about.
[SATOWA gasps]
Really? Thank you so much.
[CHIKA]
Hm? What's that?
[SATOWA] Miss Dojima's
performance in the competition
where she got first place.
[ALL gasp]
I felt like I should probably
listen to it, you know?
I'll listen, too!
That's right,
we'll listen together!
So weird. I'm actually
feeling kinda nervous.
Okay, here we go!
[ANNOUNCER] Entry number five.
Akira Dojima. "Mizu no Hentai."
[grunts]
Oh, Satowa. Is there
something wrong?
[SATOWA] I listened to it,
your performance of
"Mizu no Hentai."
[SATOWA]
I need to tell you I'm sorry.
[AKIRA gasps]
You are? For what?
[SATOWA] Honestly, when you
first came here,
there was a part of me
that was afraid you might
be up to something.
But then, I listened
to your performance,
and after that I couldn't help
but feel ashamed of myself.
[SATOWA] I've never heard
a performance so sincere
towards a piece,
or towards the koto.
So I'm sorry that I
ever doubted you.
[AKIRA]
Please, stop. It's too much.
Stop bowing, already.
And please don't make me
feel any more miserable
than I already do.
[gasps]
H-Hey, wait. Hold on!
[AKIRA] Back then.
Why did you decide to do it?
[SATOWA gasps]
You were good enough
to win first place,
but got disqualified.
Did you play a different
song on purpose to stand out?
--No, I--
--After that competition,
do you know what I
had to deal with?
All I heard was,
"The poor thing, she only won
by default. "Over and over.
I don't want to hear another
word about it from you.
Not ever again.
[SATOWA] My mother...
I was trying to get her back.
See, she was under
all kinds of pressure,
and it felt like she was a
different person somehow.
The time around the competition,
I felt like I was
invisible to her.
She just couldn't hear me.
[SATOWA] And so, I used the
performance to throw a tantrum.
That song was my way
of screaming--no--
begging for her attention.
Kinda like... a child.
[gasps]
[SATOWA gasps]
But it didn't work.
In the end, all I did was hurt
her more and mess up the school.
You told me that you didn't
think I needed any lessons.
But the fact is,
there are a lot of things
I'd like to learn from you.
That's why I'm here. I came
to ask for your guidance.
[AKIRA] I knew the truth
before she ever told me.
That performance was never a
game to her, I knew that much.
Ah, that's right.
She's only a first-year
student in high school.
[AKIRA] She's about the same age
as me when our parents died,
and I could do nothing
but lean on Keishi.
[gasps]
[FEMALE VOICE A]
Oh, her long-sought-after
first place has been eclipsed.
Even after all that
time she spent.
She doesn't compare to
her brother. That's for sure.
Poor little thing.
[AKIRA] Where are you going?
Do you want to escape from here?
You might be able to
overcome the darkness.
But there's always...
...the endless series of walls
that will continue to
stand in your way.
Are you okay?
[AKIRA]
For two years,
I studied "Mizu no Hentai."
But all that work was instantly
for nothing the moment you
played your first note.
What could you ever
expect me to teach you?
[AKIRA] It's time... I put
an end to my struggling.
[TAKINAMI]
Mm. Oh, Miss Dojima.
I'm sorry if this seems sudden.
[AKIRA]
But effective immediately,
I can no longer teach
your koto club.
[SATOWA]
Next time: "Another Chance."