[SATOWA]
No!
You? But I don't understand,
why are you here, at my
apartment of all places?
Uh, to deliver a handout.
[SATOWA]
I don't believe you!
Get out of here
and don't come back!
Look. After all the trouble
I've gone through to find you,
I don't need your attitude!
Please! Just go away, already!
Whoa. Hey!
Crap.
Man, now what should I do?
[CHIKA]
This is weird.
Does she live all by herself?
She's really burning up.
Where's your bathroom stuff?
Like towels.
[SATOWA]
In the closet, bottom right.
[CHIKA]
Over here?
Okay, then.
Wrong drawer!
I saw nothing!
Nothing!
Oh, that bottom right.
[CHIKA]
It's kinda strange,
but I don't even know
that much about Hozuki.
We've been playing the
koto together for a month,
but it's not like we talk much.
Hey. Can I watch this?
Yeah? Cool.
[CHIKA] The first time
I ever heard her play,
all I could do was stand there
with my jaw on the floor.
This time I want
to really listen.
[ANNOUNCER] Next up is entry
number 13, Satowa Hozuki.
Playing "Yaegoromo"
[WOMAN A]
It was unexpected.
The illness took
him so suddenly.
[WOMAN B]
And now his wife, Chiharu,
will take over
the Hozuki school.
[WOMAN A] I'm not sure
she's fit for the job.
Uh, hey, Mommy?
What is it?
[SATOWA]
Well, the thing is,
I wrote a new
piece for the koto.
Will you listen?
[inaudible]
That was lovely.
You just might be
a musical genius.
Thank you, dear.
I feel much better
after hearing you play.
You're so sweet.
Really?
Indeed.
It makes me want
to work even harder.
That way you can always
have a smile on your face.
[CHIHARU]
What? You're quitting? Why?
I mean, the only reason we
chose the Hozuki school
was because your late husband,
Reiji, was the grand master.
A lot of students are leaving.
Well, you can't
really blame them.
The new grand master
doesn't have much skill,
and she can't compose at all.
Wrong one!
How can you not know that?
Please forgive me.
I didn't mean to snap at you.
It's okay!
I want you to be
more strict with me.
That way I can get
better even faster!
Satowa.
[SATOWA] I won't let
them say those things.
If I manage to become
a great successor.
I know it will help
mommy and the school.
[CUSTOMER] I heard rumors
about the Hozuki school's heir,
but I didn't know
she was such a prodigy.
We're doing our best.
Well, Grand Master, your
daughter is proving to be
quite the attraction
for the Hozuki School.
Do be careful not
to embarrass yourself.
You've already brought this
esteemed school down far enough,
but even someone
like you must be able
to teach your own daughter.
At least attempt to make
your successor capable.
[CHIHARU]
That's wrong!
You're very talented,
but you tend to play
too much in your own style.
As the heir to this school,
you have to lead by example.
Um. Did something
bad happen today, Mom?
You seem upset‐‐
[CHIHARU]
I am your instructor!
Once more, from the top.
Right.
What? You have koto
lessons again today?
Come on, let's go without her.
[CHIHARU]
Listen to this!
Satowa wrote her own koto piece,
isn't that amazing?
[REIJI]
It is!
You're already much
better than your old man.
[CHIHARU]
I don't know about you,
but hearing Satowa's playing
always makes me so happy.
[REIJI]
Me, too.
Honestly, I think her playing
could make anyone happy.
I'm fine.
I don't need to have friends.
I don't care what
people say about me.
Hey, Hozuki.
Have you picked a club yet?
It's the rules.
Every student is required
to join an after‐school club.
If you want, we can
go look at them together.
Uh, yeah!
Sounds good.
[CHIHARU]
A club?
Yes. It's mandatory,
everyone has to join one.
Everyone except you,
as I've already
spoken to your teachers
and asked them to grant
you special permission not to.
But why would you
do that without asking me?
I wish you would
have said something.
[CHIHARU]
It's time to practice.
Oh. All right then.
Jeez, your home life
seems really strict.
[SATOWA]
I'm fine.
It's not like I wanted to
join a club that badly anyway.
Besides, if I keep
practicing hard, maybe...
Satowa, I've decided
that you're going to attend
Ichiei High School.
It's an elite music school.
In order to earn a scholarship,
there's a competition.
[SATOWA]
Hold on.
Why would you make
that decision by yourself?
I mean, you could have at least
talked to me about it first.
Oh, and why should
I have to consult you
before making decisions?
[SATOWA]
Well, because...
Stop for a second!
Please, can you just listen
to me for one minute?
I want you to
look at me, Mother!
And listen!
[CHIHARU]
It's time to start practice.
[ANNOUNCER] Next up is entry
number 13, Satowa Hozuki.
Playing "Yaegoromo"
She's from the Hozuki school?
I've heard that girl
is a true prodigy.
She's only in middle school,
but she's playing "Yaegoromo,"
which can be quite difficult.
[SATOWA] My mother...
can no longer hear my voice.
If I mess up even a little
in practice, she stops me.
But now, on this stage
where she can't ignore me.
I will connect to her!
♪ fast, passionate playing ♪
[EXAMINER A]
What is the piece she's playing?
It isn't "Yaegoromo!"
[OLDER EXAMINER] Did she
compose this song herself?
We'll have to fail her for not
playing her designated piece.
Still, this song...
♪ koto fades out ♪
[SATOWA]
Hey, Mommy?
The koto is a dragon, right?
But what is a dragon?
[CHIHARU]
Well, I haven't seen one myself,
but I heard that dragons can
bring together heaven and earth.
They can connect the worlds
of the living and the dead,
isn't that interesting?
Oh, so if I play the koto,
does that mean my sound
will reach Daddy all
the way up in heaven?
Of course!
I'm sure that you
could reach him.
It'll connect you two.
[SATOWA]
Tell her!
All I want...
All I want is for it to be
like it was before!
[pants]
To think that girl's only 15.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
Mother.
How dare you.
What were even you thinking?
How could you do this?
[SATOWA]
Listen.
Don't touch me!
You can't possibly understand.
How heavy a burden
it is for someone
who isn't talented to
shoulder someone who is.
Your koto playing feels
like a weapon to me.
[SATOWA]
It didn't reach her.
It didn't reach her!
Am I crying?
This girl...
Wow, the Hozuki heir sure
messed up big time, didn't she?
[DOJIMA]
My goodness!
The Hozuki School's
reputation will be ruined!
[SATOWA]
I'm such an idiot.
You've skipped out
on koto practice
the last two days in a row.
What exactly has gotten
into you, young lady?
[SATOWA]
Nothing.
I just thought that maybe
it would be easier
for you this way.
Now you don't have
to shoulder me anymore.
[SATOWA] All that practicing,
but nothing changed.
Things only got worse.
There's no reason
for me to play anymore.
[DOJIMA]
What is Satowa doing?
She's missed all
of her lessons lately!
You skipped your
lessons again, didn't you?
I'm starting to think you
don't have any motivation.
Does it matter?
Wait.
Didn't Kudo come
to my place yesterday?
A dream?
[shrieks]
It wasn't a dream? Oh!
Oh, you're awake?
Can you tone down the shouting?
It's too early
for all that crap.
First tell me why
you're in my apartment!
Because you can't leave
a sick person at home
by themselves, obviously.
So you just decided to
stay the night uninvited?
[CHIKA] If you have
enough energy to protest,
you must be okay.
And your fever...
...is gone.
Well, I'm going to school.
Catch ya later.
Get back here, Kudo!
Um.
Why aren't you saying anything?
About where I live?
Huh? Oh.
I figure your school isn't
making that much money, right?
[SATOWA]
Uh... Listen.
[CHIKA] Look, if you ever
feel like talking about it,
just talk.
And restock your fridge
every once in a while.
It's like a barren
wasteland in there.
Kinda pathetic.
Uh, what were you
doing in my fridge?
What was that?
That's odd.
I don't remember
cooking yesterday.
[gasps]
Egg and rice porridge?
[TAKEZO] I wonder what
was up with Kurusu yesterday.
She was acting really strange.
Kurata!
Hey!
[shrieks]
Good morning!
So, uh, about yesterday.
Yeah, I was wondering.
You said that you thought
everyone in the koto club
were pretty close
friends, right?
But what if you found out one
of them was deceiving everyone?
Would you think differently?
Huh? Hold on.
What's that mean?
Oh, you'll find out.
I'll see you at club.
Hozuki!
I'm so happy you're here today!
[SANE]
Bad Kota, stop it!
Down boy!
Sorry, we're just
glad you're back,
you were out sick
yesterday right?
How do you feel now?
[SATOWA]
Uh, better.
Here's some food to help
you regain your strength.
[SATOWA]
Thank you.
The thing is...
I'm so sorry, you got sick
because of all of us, huh?
Come on, are you still going
on about that nonsense?
It's so stupid.
These guys actually
think you stayed home
'cause you got tired
of how bad we are.
What? But that's
just ridiculous.
I enjoy this club,
because it's fun.
[sobbing]
Really?
If that's the case, then why
won't you tell us the truth?
[SANE]
Huh? What do you mean?
I'm sorry, Hozuki.
My grandmother told me all
about your recent troubles.
Seeing as you don't have
anywhere else to play the koto.
You had no choice
but to join the club.
Meaning this place is nothing
more than an escape.
Somewhere to hide from
your shame, is that correct?
I'm guessing that's why you
haven't told anyone about it.
Hey, Kurusu.
Does this have anything to do
with what you said this morning?
Ah, sorry to be so mysterious.
It seemed like Hozuki was too
embarrassed to tell anyone,
which is why I spoke up.
[SATOWA]
Enough.
I will be the one to
tell people about myself.
[gasps]
And what's more, while I did
hide the truth from them,
it's only because
I wasn't quite ready to
acknowledge it myself yet.
But I think I'm ready
to face it now.
I'm sorry.
I should have
told you this sooner.
That's fine, then starting
today you are excommunicated.
You see.
I was excommunicated
from the school.
[HIRO]
Oh my, they look angry.
But that's to be expected.
She was keeping
a pretty big secret.
Honestly, relationships between
people fall apart so easily.
Words like "trust"
and "friendship"
are just lip service.
What's that word mean?
Big word.
Ah...!
I'm saying that I've been
cut off from the school.
I've been dismissed
as the next heir.
Now do you get it?
[CHIKA]
I was just wondering
if you learned how
to play from your parents.
[SATOWA] That's not
something you need to know.
[TAKEZO] Does that mean
her mother disowned her?
Um, well.
In that case,
thanks for sharing!
Really.
So that's how it is?
Things must have
been so hard for you!
You can have all my bread!
In the meantime, start
taking better care of yourself,
build stamina or something.
[TAKEZO] Is that really the
nicest way you could think
to phrase that sentence?
Hold on. You're serious?
She lies and you thank her?
This is the most hilarious
train wreck I've ever witnessed.
Isn't that great?
You're all such good friends.
Ridiculous!
Huh? Whoa! Kurusu!
Hold on!
Please, I just
wanna talk to you!
[HIRO]
Jeez, you're so annoying!
You guys managed
to ruin my whole plan.
In fact, instead of
breaking you apart,
I've only made you stronger.
It pisses me off!
Did you actually think
I joined the koto club
because I was moved by
your dumb performance?
Seeing you stand on that
stage and talk about how
you weren't going to lose
your precious friends
or the place you belong only
made me want to tease you.
Know what?
I hate even looking at you.
You disgust me!
Is that all you wanted to say?
I feel kinda bad.
You must have
a lot of free time.
[HIRO]
It's not fair.
I hate them all!
So hey.
Hiro.
I heard that you've
been talking about me
behind my back to
all of your friends.
Huh? What do you mean?
I haven't done
anything like that.
[HIRO'S FRIEND A]
Liar!
Minami told us how
you've been harassing her
because you're afraid
she'll steal your boyfriend!
[HIRO'S EX‐BOYFRIEND]
Unbelievable.
That's so low.
[HIRO'S FRIEND B]
You're the worst.
[HIRO]
Wait!
I never did those things!
I haven't been harassing her!
Please listen to me!
They didn't.
It was huge lie she'd made up.
All so she could go and
steal my boyfriend from me,
and everyone just believed her.
She had transferred to
my class in the second year
of middle school, so naturally
I'd already known my friends
and boyfriend for much
longer than she had.
And yet, for some reason
they didn't believe me.
Was I that untrustworthy?
I thought.
Maybe all relationships
were like that.
Excuse me.
After that, whenever I'd see
people who seemed close,
I'd find a way to befriend
them before making up a lie.
And then, as expected,
everyone would fall apart.
[HIRO] That's why I thought
this time would be the same!
I was positive everything
would crumble
once I gave them a little nudge!
[CHIKA]
Well.
I don't believe anything
unless I hear it firsthand.
[TAKEZO]
Thanks for sharing!
Really.
[HIRO]
Those idiots!
They were supposed to react
to everything differently!
[HIRO]
This is the worst.
Man!
I really hate it when
people don't make sense!
Forget about that, Specs.
Hurry up and teach me "Rokudan."
What?
I'm sorry.
[SANE]
Chika apologized?
How far did you get yesterday?
I only got through the first
column before I got lost.
I didn't understand the goal.
Because there is no goal.
Classical pieces are fluid.
So what school.
Who decides to perform it.
The sound always changes due
to different interpretations
and thoughts that
pile up over time.
It becomes quite complicated.
Just like people.
You have to face it head on
to understand it, right?
Until the sound
finally comes to you.
[TAKEZO]
Hold on.
After what you said yesterday,
I was the one who
wanted to cry, but...
...why were you crying, Kurusu?
[HIRO]
Why do you care?
Do you wanna play the hero that
comforts me when I tell you?
No, I really don't.
Still, though.
I don't know your reason.
Hence the question.
If you'll talk to me seriously,
then I'll listen.
Well... Well,
there's not one, okay?
[SATOWA]
Kurusu!
Huh?
What now?
Look. About yesterday.
You told everyone that
I joined the koto club
because I had
nowhere else to play,
and that I was using it
as an escape, right?
But you were wrong about me.
The truth is I joined the
koto club because I wanted to.
Why are you telling me that?
Are you trying to
rub it in my face?
[SATOWA]
No, it's because
I just thought maybe
we were the same.
If you want to know the real
reason why I joined the club,
then I'll tell you why.
[SATOWA]
A music performance?
A koto club.
What am I doing here?
[SATOWA] I have to admit,
they're not all that great,
but, still, they look like
they're having a lot of fun.
[HIRO, SATOWA]
I'm jealous.
Like always, the club
will meet after school.
You won't make a good impression
if you start skipping
right after joining.
See ya.
[HIRO]
What does that mean?
I'm pretty sure I've already
made a really bad impression.
Aw, man. I wonder if
Hiro is going to come today.
[TAKEZO]
I somehow doubt she will.
If you'll talk to me seriously,
then I'll listen.
You're in the way.
Oh, Chika!
If you stand there blocking
the door, nobody can get in.
Right. Sorry.
Well? You comin' or not?
[HIRO gasps]
Um. I dunno, is it okay?
For me to come in?
What? That's not really
something for me to decide.
Oh, Hiro did show up!
Good, I'm really
happy you're here.
So, listen.
Uh.
If you'll hear me out,
then I'd like to apologize.
[TAKEZO]
Okay.
[CHIKA]
Next time: "A Sign."