[STUDENTS cheering]
Wow! I didn't know the koto
could sound so awesome!
For real! I've got goosebumps!
[STUDENT C]
That was intense!
[gasps]
Whoa, crazy.
[STUDENT A, B groan]
[VICE PRINCIPAL]
That Kudo punk actually played!
[PRINCIPAL]
Well, it sounds like everyone's
reached a verdict,
eh, Vice Principal?
What? No. Not exactly.
I mean, we still don't know
if the whole school
is satisfied or not.
‐‐[SATOWA] Vice Principal.
‐‐[VICE PRINCIPAL gasps]
I'd just like to
take this moment
and give you proper
thanks for today.
We're standing on this stage
because you chose to
challenge us as a club.
It forced us to work
together and practice
and give you our absolute best.
And I'd like to add that if
it weren't for your efforts,
I might have continued to
be a lazy ne'er‐do‐well
instead of learning the value
of hard work and friendship.
[VICE PRINCIPAL gasps]
Who, me?
Cool! Kudo thanked
the vice principal!
Wow, he helped Kudo
become a better person.
It's just like a TV drama!
Hey, great going, sir!
Uh, well.
We, too, have seen the light!
It's true! You've
helped us grow!
Yeah, thanks for not
giving up on us delinquents!
[TAKEZO]
As you can see,
the koto club owes
everything we did today
to you and your
passionate leadership.
Thank you, from the
bottom of all our hearts.
[gasps, clears throat]
Uh, yes, well,
it's all part of the job.
Please keep working hard
to represent our school
in a positive light.
[laughs]
[ALL]
To the club!
Yay! We were a success!
Yeah. To be honest,
I was a little worried
that we'd fail.
But now, thanks to you guys
and all your hard work,
the club prevailed!
You know what?
That's the first time I ever
felt something so magical!
Pouring my heart and soul into
practice for a whole month,
then getting to see
all that hard work
pay off at the presentation.
The thrill that comes
right after a performance
that makes your
whole body feel numb.
I guess I'm just saying
that it felt cool, y'know?
It probably sounds dumb.
[MITTSU]
I never knew you were so poetic!
[SANE]
Shuddup!
[TAKEZO]
Hey, listen.
I wanted to run an
idea past everyone.
Uh, would you guys... wanna
aim for Nationals with me?
[ALL gasp]
Whoa! Nationals sound like fun!
You can count us in!
After today, we can do anything!
[CHIKA]
If we're doin' this,
then we'd better
make it to the top.
[SATOWA] That's always
been the intention.
[TAKEZO]
You guys know it's not that easy
to get to Nationals, right?
[ALL laughing]
[TAKEZO]
Well, I'm sure it'll be fine.
Yo, Granny! What did you think
of our performance up there?
When school is over for the day,
I need to talk to you
at my shop, alone.
[CHIKA]
Was our performance bad?
Crap, maybe she's mad at me!
[SHIZU] I have something
of your grandfather's
that I've been holding onto.
Huh?
[SHIZU] If you were a
good‐for‐nothing punk,
I wasn't going to
give it to you, but...
[gasps]
[SHIZU] This is the very
last koto that Gen made
before he passed.
Back when your grandfather's
house was broken into,
I took over the repairs and
care of his instruments.
This koto was the only one
that survived the incident.
Isn't it beautiful?
This is what we call a
straight‐grained koto,
crafted from well‐aged wood.
It's a real work of art,
made from high‐quality wood
by the most talented koto
maker I've ever known.
It's sound is gentle, but deep,
with long‐lingering tones.
The koto is actually what we
might call a consumable good.
Over time, it's sound changes
the more it's played,
and when it passes
it's peak, it withers.
In my opinion,
there's nothing more tragic
than an instrument withering
before it's ever been played.
That's why I'm glad
to pass it on to you
before that can happen.
Play it to your heart's content.
[CHIKA]
If it's such an incredible koto,
then it should probably go to
someone more reliable than me.
Oh? What kind of
person would that be?
Y'know, someone who really
gets the koto or whatever!
Someone who's good at playing!
Your playing is at
a beginner's level
and I wouldn't dare say it's
at the point of being "good."
But your sound is far
gentler than anyone else's.
I'm sure that it was
able to reach Gen.
After all, dragons can
travel between the worlds
of the living and the dead.
To be completely honest,
I never planned on giving
this to anyone but you.
You see, there's a key detail
I failed to notice at first.
Look on the ryuuzetsu,
dragon's tongue.
[CHIKA gasps]
[GEN laughs]
Chika.
[SHIZU] There's no doubt.
This is your koto.
Thank you, Granny.
Thank you.
[STUDENT D]
Hey, Kudo, what's up?
Will you tell us why you
wanted to play the koto?
It must be so much fun!
[STUDENT E]
Are you single?
[STUDENT F]
What kind of food do you like?
[MIYOSHI] Your performance was
the coolest thing ever, Hozuki!
Uh, thank you, I appreciate it.
[MIYOSHI] Hey, relax.
You don't have to be so formal!
Um, right.
Well, o‐okay.
Oh, I know!
Why don't we all walk
together to our next class?
[gasps]
[CHILDHOOD FRIEND] Being
around you is so boring, Satowa.
Uh... I'll be fine on my own.
[MIYOSHI]
Aww.
[SANE]
What's up?
[TAKEZO]
Hey, guys.
Wow, I can't believe
today turned out so good.
The girls have been gushing
about our performance. Sweet!
Huh? That sign.
Ah. Yeah, I decided to
put it up when I got here.
Why though?
Wasn't the other
one special to you?
Yes, it was. But...
...that was an old goal
between me and the
upperclassmen who graduated.
This is a brand‐new goal
for our current club.
Now I want to aim for
Nationals with you guys.
[KOTA]
It's so touching!
[TAKINAMI]
Now hold on just a minute.
You guys seriously think
you can make it to Nationals?
Give me a break.
Please stop.
Who's that?
Mister Takinami.
What's his deal?
Yeah, he's...
kind of our advisor.
[ALL]
Uhh, that guy?
The club was never
too much work.
I could always take it easy.
I'd thought it'd just fold.
But the vice principal's
all excited now.
What a pain.
"A pain"?
Look, Nationals are
nothing but a pipe dream.
It's time to be more realistic.
Give it up.
[CHIKA] Bastard!
You tryin' to pick a fight?
That's more like it, Kudo.
This suits you better than
that goody‐two‐shoes act.
Huh?!
[TAKINAMI]
While we're at it,
what's a girl like
you even doing here?
You're on a different level.
If you stay in this pathetic
club, you'll only get worse.
That's enough, Mister Takinami!
Well, I'll be checking in
on you every so often.
Try not to cause me any trouble.
What is his problem?
[KOTA, SANE, MITTSU]
Whoa! Calm down, Chika!
[TAKINAMI] How long are
you guys gonna cry for?
[ALL crying]
Don't tell me that
you actually thought
a weak performance like that
would get you all to Nationals.
Hold on!
You don't have to be
so cruel about it.
All I'm saying is it
wasn't the sound of people
truly aiming for Nationals.
That's why you failed.
It's as simple as that.
[TAKEZO] We were finally
on the same page
and the club was going well.
[sighs]
What? Are you serious, Hiro?
[HIRO]
Yep, sure am.
To be honest, I've gotten
kinda excited about the idea of
"friends" and
"a place to belong."
You're only young once, right?
I'd like to give it a chance.
Besides, I've been
super bored lately.
Sure, whatever, I guess.
Hiro's bad habits have
found a new target.
Another way to kill time.
Hey, Kurata!
Oh, hello, Kurusu. What's up?
The koto club's performance
was so moving the other day.
Here.
[TAKEZO gasps]
Huh?
[HIRO] So... I was hoping that
you'd let me join the club.
[TAKEZO]
And there you have it.
This is our new member,
Hiro Kurusu!
She's also a
second‐year student.
Nice to meet ya!
Whoa! A girl club member?!
And she's an older girl.
This is awesome!
Show me the ropes, okay?
[MITTSU, KOTA, SANE]
Sure thing, whatever you want!
[HIRO gasps, giggles]
Your name is Hozuki, right?
Yeah.
Your performance the
other day was so cool!
I heard you're the
daughter of a grand master.
That's incredible!
Uh, I guess so. [gasps]
Let's introduce ourselves.
My name is Sane.
Hi, I'm Kota!
And you can call me Mittsu!
Well, aren't you guys sweet?
[SANE]
And that guy is Chika.
Huh? [groans]
Don't look so angry,
you're gonna scare her off!
[CHIKA]
Knock it off!
I think it's amazing that
you guys get along so well.
[TAKEZO]
I haven't had the opportunity
to talk to Kurusu much,
but it seems like
she'll fit right in.
So, now that the
performance is over with,
what's our next move?
Well, we have qualifiers
in December.
But, before that, I thought
it'd be good for us to play
at as many places as possible.
I was thinking we should
sign up for this.
[CHIKA] A traditional
Japanese music festival?
Yeah. It's an event
held in August.
They pick the best high schools
from the seven prefectures
in the Kanto region
and then from those seven,
they narrow it down to
one grand prize winner.
Does that mean we get to fight
against other high schools
using the power of music?
We'll crush those guys!
[TAKEZO] Whoa. It seems
everyone's fired up.
Well then,
all that's left is to pick a
song and start practicing‐‐
[SATOWA] Actually,
can I make a suggestion?
I think it would be
best if we at least
learned a classical piece
before a newer song.
Why's that?
[SATOWA]
It's hard to explain, but...
...there's a difference
in the sound
between people who've
played classical songs
versus those who haven't.
Their sound has
more depth to it.
So what? We've got no depth?
It might be more difficult
for the beginners in the club.
Kurusu just joined.
You don't have to
worry about me.
The truth is,
I'm not a beginner.
[SANE, TAKEZO, KOTA]
Huh?
Wait, are you saying you're
an experienced koto player?
I don't have a
ton of experience,
but my grandma
taught me some things.
A classical piece
sounds like fun,
and if it's simple enough,
then I can probably
play it with no problem.
[SANE]
That's awesome!
Oh. Well then, I guess
it's all been decided.
What song should we pick?
Let me think.
Maybe "Rokudan"?
Wasn't that the piece you played
at the club presentation?
[CHIKA] Oh, that weird
song I didn't understand.
[TAKEZO whimpers]
[SATOWA]
"Rokudan no Shirabe."
It's a piece that's
representative
of the classical works
of the Edo period.
Oh? Guess it looks
simple enough.
At least easier
than "Ryuuseigun."
It might seem that way,
but classical pieces are more
difficult than you might think.
The notations are marked
completely different
from most current pieces.
It may be too hard for you.
What did you just say?
Um, I'm sure we'll
all be great. Right?
Not to be a downer,
but aren't we short two kotos?
[TAKEZO gasps]
You're right.
What should we do?
[SANE]
The school won't buy 'em for us?
[TAKEZO] It would be a
pretty expensive purchase.
It's fine, I can
bring in my own koto.
[TAKEZO]
What?
You never mentioned
that you had one before.
Yeah, Granny gave it to me.
[TAKEZO]
She gave you one?!
[SANE]
No fair! Why just you?
[CHIKA] Thing is, my grandfather
actually made me one
before he passed away.
So that's why.
Seriously?
Wow, Kudo.
[KUDO] What the hell are you
all making a scene for?
[MITTSU]
Shuddup.
[SANE]
We're just happy for you.
Uh, okay? What's up?
I don't understand, is this
like a big deal? [gasps]
[TAKEZO]
Kudo. I'm glad for you.
Well then.
If you want, I can always
bring in the other one.
What? Are you sure?
I mean, you already brought
in the 17‐string for us.
Yeah, it's fine.
In that case, thanks a lot.
Oh, at least let me
come and pick it up
from your house this time.
No, that's okay, thanks.
I can handle it.
Just let Takezo help you!
We're here to
support each other.
Oh! Or one of us could do it.
I said I'll handle it!
[SANE, KOTA]
Uh...
[HIRO]
Hmm.
[SANE] That was really cool
earlier. I'm glad for Chika.
It's weird. You almost
never hear him
talk about himself like that.
Well, guess that
means he was happy.
I suppose that's a
good thing, isn't it?
'Cause it means he must really
trust the koto club members
with his feelings.
‐‐[KOTA giggles]
‐‐Yeah, you could say that.
[HIRO]
Not Hozuki, though.
It's pretty obvious she's
still got a wall up.
[SANE]
Huh? You mean earlier?
It makes sense.
When you think about it,
the world Hozuki lives in
is so different from ours.
‐‐[KOTA] Huh?
‐‐Oh, come on.
She's the daughter
of a grand master!
And it could just be a rumor,
but I heard she's a prodigy
with a sweeping victory at
Nationals under her belt!
Ah, well that's cool.
To be honest, we don't really
think about that stuff.
I think Hozuki's just
downplaying her talent
because she doesn't
want you to feel bad.
Get this.
When she and I were
alone, she said,
"It's hard sometimes
because I have to
work with people at a
lower level than me."
Oops. Uh, that was a secret.
I'm sure it's kinda difficult
working with beginners like us.
Yeah, we must be a huge hassle.
[KOTA] Out of the three of us,
I'm probably the biggest hassle!
‐‐[KOTA, MITTSU] Whoa!
‐‐[SANE] So cool!
[SANE]
That thing is freaking awesome!
[MITTSU]
Your grandfather made this?
[KOTA]
It even looks special!
‐‐[SATOWA growls]
‐‐Uh... Say, Kudo?
That's not a straight‐
grained koto, is it?
Sure is.
Unbelievable!
You have no business
bringing a koto that
expensive to school, Kudo!
It's worth over one million yen!
I have another koto
that I can bring for us,
so please take this one home.
[CHIKA] Why? Wouldn't it be a
waste not to play it, though?
[SATOWA] Then play it at
home or at a performance!
What would you do if
someone were to steal it,
or if it got damaged?
Calm down, Hozuki.
Chika only brought it in
because he wanted to
help out the club,
so it's not very fair
to get angry with him.
You have to remember
not everyone has
an amazing home like yours.
Maybe his place doesn't
allow loud noises.
Plus, why would
anyone even wanna
steal or damage a koto
in the first place?
It's fine. I'll take it home.
Oh, no, he seems upset.
All right then.
So starting today we'll be
learning "Rokudan," okay?
I think it'd probably be best
if we listened to an
example of it first.
Yes, I agree.
Will you do the honors?
Actually, I was hoping
that you would do it.
Uh‐‐sure, I guess I could.
[TAKEZO] Okay, I'll go
ahead and play it once.
Just try to focus on the song.
[koto plays]
[ALL snoring]
[TAKEZO]
Yeah.
I was afraid this might happen.
[TAKEZO]
Shall we get to practicing?
[SATOWA]
Uh, try it this way.
[SANE]
Like this?
[SATOWA]
Not quite.
How do I explain it?
Sorry! It must be hard having
to dumb everything down.
[SATOWA]
What?
Look, I get it.
I know it's gotta suck
to have to work with
us lower level players.
‐‐[SANE] We're trying.
‐‐[gasps]
Listen, the truth is, you're
way different from us, Satowa.
You should just
play by yourself.
[HIRO] Hozuki, can you please
show me how to play this part?
Uh, sure.
[SANE gasps]
Thank you.
By the way, I was wondering,
why did you have Kurata
play the example earlier?
I mean, you're a much
better player than he is.
Were you being considerate
because he's the president?
I do kind of wonder
how that would make
Kurata feel, you know?
Maybe like you were
undermining him.
That's not what I
intended at all.
[HIRO] Why are you in the
koto club to start with?
Your playing level and
the world you live in
are completely different
from everyone else's.
So why are you here?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[TETSUKI]
Huh? Is Hozuki absent today?
Oh, Kudo. Listen, do me a favor
and deliver this handout
to Hozuki for me.
Huh? Why'd you pick me?
[TEACHER] You're
the only other kid in class
I've seen her talk to,
so it makes sense.
Besides, aren't you
guys in the same club?
So, here's the handout and
her address. Thanks a bunch!
Hey! Hold on!
Teachers can be so bossy.
Sure, but look at the
bright side of things.
At least the teachers trust you
with this kind of stuff now.
That's good! And it's a step
in the right direction.
The right direction, huh?
What? She didn't come
to school today?
Did she catch a cold?
Or maybe she's just feeling
run down with everything.
She needs a day off
'cause we suck so much!
What are you talkin'
about? That's dumb.
[SANE]
Well that's what Hiro told us!
What? Kurusu said that?
Oh, no! It's because
we're so freakin' useless!
We're sorry!
[TAKEZO]
Whoa, just calm down you guys.
I highly doubt that's the case!
[HIRO]
Huh? But, it probably is.
[TAKEZO]
What do you mean?
She told me that
the club activities
have really been
wearing her down.
[MITTSU, KOTA, SANE]
So it was because of us!
Um, I guess since I'm a girl
who has experience
with the koto,
she feels like she
can confide in me.
She also said something weird
concerning Chika the other day.
Uhh, I think it was about how
she couldn't play with someone
with a different sense of
the koto's worth, maybe?
But I doubt it was important.
After all, Hozuki lives in
a different world than us.
[HIRO gasps]
Well, I don't believe anything
unless I hear it firsthand.
[HIRO gasping]
[CHIKA] And what's up with all
this "different world" stuff?
We all play the koto in the
same club room every day.
Chika! I'm worried that I
might have said something
that hurt Hozuki's feelings!
What? So go apologize, then.
I know Hozuki would
give you a break.
She knows you aren't
that kinda guy.
Really?
[HIRO]
How stupid.
[TAKEZO gasps]
Uh‐‐hey, Kurusu?
What's up? Is something wrong?
[TAKEZO]
Um, no.
Wow, I didn't realize everyone
in the club was so buddy‐buddy.
I'm a little jealous.
Well, let's practice!
[HIRO'S GRANDMOTHER]
What brings you by today, Hiro?
[HIRO] I came to return
the plectrums I borrowed.
Oh? You don't need them?
I thought you joined
the school's koto club.
Yeah, I did, but I'm quitting.
It's not even that interesting.
Wasn't even that much
of a time killer.
Now that I think about it,
didn't you tell me the daughter
from the Hozuki school
was in that club?
I heard that she's really going
through a lot at the moment.
I feel bad for her.
[HIRO]
Huh?
[HIRO'S GRANDMOTHER]
At least's that's what
everyone's been saying.
[inaudible]
Seriously? Is that true?
Well, I don't believe anything
unless I hear it firsthand.
That's so interesting.
I wonder if his tune will change
once he finds out she's just
a wolf in sheep's clothing.
What a little liar.
Huh? Did you say something?
[HIRO]
Nope! Actually, can I hold onto
those plectrums for a bit?
[HIRO] I think it's time
I teach that girl a lesson.
Soon she'll realize how
worthless "friends" really are.
[CHIKA] I don't see a house that
looks like it could be hers.
Am I on the wrong
street or something?
Uh, "201 Tsukimotosou"?
Wonder if the house is
even around this area.
I mean, doesn't Princess
Koto live in a castle?
[CHIKA grunts]
Oh, I guess this is it.
Wait. This is where she lives?
Okay, now I'm positive
that he must have
given me the wrong address.
[CHIKA]
No nameplate, huh?
[doorbell ringing]
[CHIKA sighs]
Yes. I'm here.
[gasps]
[SATOWA]
Next time, "Unknown Sounds."