We don't even have practice.
We lost yesterday.
And what's worse,
to a school whose
performance we didn't hear.
And now I know that
you can become even better.
[CHIKA]
It isn't locked?
Why are you here?
Isn't that my line?
There isn't any practice today.
[SANE]
Yeah.
But here's the thing.
We've been practicing
the koto day in and day out.
Yeah, I guess we
don't really know
what to do with ourselves now.
You guys.
All right, so I guess it's back
to business as usual, then.
Our next competition is
the national qualifier, right?
What are we gonna play?
[TAKEZO] We could always
practice "Kuon" more.
Or maybe even learn a new song.
[TAKINAMI]
Wow.
What are all of you doing here?
Don't you have
lives outside of koto?
[TAKEZO]
Mister Takinami.
What's up?
[TAKINAMI]
Not much.
Oh. Here.
[TAKEZO]
Hm?
Sheet music?
[TAKINAMI] It's a medley
of a few different pieces
that have been popular lately.
Your next performance is the
school festival in September.
I want you to play this piece.
Huh?
The truth is,
you guys lack any real
experience performing in public,
so you need to take every
opportunity to perform.
Why the silence?
You sound like
an actual club advisor.
I am a club advisor.
I can't believe it!
Hold on, so this is an
arrangement of popular songs?
I don't get it, where'd you
find sheet music for this?
[TAKINAMI]
I had to write it.
Oh that's nice of you.
[SATOWA]
It even has koto notations.
[ALL 3]
What?
You wrote it?
Wait, like you you
or a different you?
Yeah, that doesn't
make sense, Kurata.
But this is a music piece with
a koto notation and everything!
And you said that you
didn't know the koto!
Look, I've been the club
advisor for a good two years,
even I should be able to read
and write a koto score by now.
Okay. That's kinda cool.
I agree.
Hey, if a non-koto player
can do it, maybe we can, too!
You definitely cannot!
Yeah, that's not normal!
[TAKEZO]
Mr. Takinami, I...
Please don't make this
about me, okay?
Focus.
This score has three parts:
a first and second koto,
and a part for the 17-string.
I've written the part for the
17-string so it's simpler.
This time I would like
for Adachi to play it.
Sound good?
Really? Why me?
[TAKINAMI] You have a pretty
good sense of rhythm and power,
so you're suited for it.
The school festival's
in a month.
We still have lots of time.
You can use it to pick
a piece for the qualifier.
I'll keep my eye out
for something.
But seeing as you have
a keen ear for music,
you should look
around too, Hozuki.
Right.
Make sure to practice.
Wow, okay that was super weird.
What the heck's
going on with Suzu?
Um. I don't know.
But...
[TAKINAMI]
Oh, one more thing,
make sure you guys finish up
all of your summer assignments.
If you get in trouble with
the vice principal again,
he might not let you participate
in the school festival.
What summer assignments?
Wait, we had homework?
I can understand
your nervous reaction.
But don't you worry.
When it comes to
emergencies like this one,
we've got the
ultimate secret weapon!
Huh?
[KOTA, MITTSU, SANE]
Thank you for helping us again!
[TAKEZO] Uh, I'm sorry for
tagging along too, Takaoka.
[TETSUKI]
Actually, I appreciate it.
These guys can be
a lot to handle alone,
so I could use
your help tutoring them.
[TAKEZO]
It's kinda weird,
but I didn't expect him
to be their secret weapon.
Our friend Tetsuki
is practically a genius.
He's the reason we were able
to get into Tokise
in the first place.
Yep, he got the highest score
on the entrance exam.
[TAKEZO]
What?
Okay then, we should probably
knock out the math stuff first.
[KOTA, MITTSU, SANE]
Yes, sir!
Yeah, here's the thing, Tetsuki.
I don't think my math textbook
is feeling so hot at the moment,
so maybe we should focus
on a different subject
for the time being.
Uh, I think you're the one
who's not feeling well.
I'm not gonna make it;
go on without me.
Math makes me hungry.
Jeez, already?
I mean, what's
the deal with X and Y?
Why are they
hiding their identities
instead of just living
more confidently?
Stop being so shy!
Listen up you two,
you aren't fooling us
with that dumb act, okay?
[TAKEZO]
Wow.
They certainly are a
challenging group to teach.
I wonder how Takaoka does it.
[TETSUKI]
So that's it then,
you're just gonna turn
your backs on them?
I feel bad for X amd Y.
Hold on.
What do you mean?
They've been forced
to conceal their identities
since birth and
live in solitude.
The poor things are unable
to reveal their true selves
to anyone or anything.
And to make matters worse,
now you guys are turning
your backs on them, too.
How pitiful.
They're outcasts, like us.
Living alone.
[KOTA, MITTSU, SANE]
Aw, poor X! Poor Y!
Please forgive us.
No matter what happens,
we won't ever turn
our backs on you guys!
Yeah, that's right, we're
gonna stick to you like glue!
Hey, Mister Tetsuki,
you gotta tell me how to save
X from its solitude, okay?
Mister Takezo,
teach me how to help Y!
[TAKEZO] It's kinda nice to
spend time with them like this.
[ALL sigh]
[SANE] And that
wraps up the English part!
Tetsuki.
Yeah, what?
I'm getting hungry!
Feed me.
[TAKEZO]
You need some help?
Sure, that'd be nice.
Let's see.
You think you can handle
washing those vegetables?
[TAKEZO]
Yeah, you got it.
You know what?
I think you've got a real knack
for teaching other people.
Man, you're so good at it.
You think so?
What made you wanna
go to Tokise, anyway?
Couldn't you have
gone somewhere better?
Uh...
I don't really have a reason.
It's just close to where I live
and seemed like a fun school.
That's all.
I see.
[CHIKA]
Hey, Four-Eyes!
Why are you in the kitchen?
We need someone
to come help teach us.
[TAKEZO]
Oh.
Right, sorry.
[TETSUKI] You shouldn't call an
upperclassman names, it's rude.
Shut up.
[TAKEZO]
Well.
He's respectful sometimes.
Once he even called me "sir."
Still though.
That was a while ago.
That's enough, ya twerp!
But you know what.
The truth is...
But if there's a problem
you can't solve,
then we'll work it out together.
Mizuhara.
You don't have
to rush yourself, okay?
You're actually a
pretty good club president.
Me?
Yeah, just think about it.
Like when Hozuki told us
about her home life.
You see.
I was excommunicated
from the school.
In that case,
thanks for sharing!
Really.
[CHIKA] In that moment, I feel
like that's probably the thing
she needed
to hear the most.
And you said it without
any hesitation whatsoever.
I've never been good
with stuff like that.
I'm not really sure
why you're cryin' right now.
I'm not, the onion is just
making my eyes water!
[TETSUKI]
You haven't even cut it yet.
[CHIKA] Whatever,
let's get back to studyin'.
Dumbass.
I can handle the cooking.
Go help 'em.
Okay, if you're sure.
[TETSUKI]
Kurata.
Thank you.
When Chika first told me
that he'd decided to join
the koto club at school,
I thought it would be
a big challenge for him.
I thought he might be rejected
by the other club members.
But it looks like I was wrong.
I guess.
I'm thanking you for
preserving the koto club.
That place has helped
Chika find himself again.
[TAKEZO]
If anything, he's helped me.
He was there because he's
a new member of the koto club.
Of course he'd
be in the club room!
We are members of
the same club, after all.
I refuse to lose the friends
who are precious to me,
or the place where I belong.
So we're going to play now.
But now I realize that
you deserve to know the truth.
Then what?
Would you rather quit?
Let's make this our
best performance ever!
[KOTA, MITTSU, SANE]
Whoa! It looks great!
So good!
[CHIKA] Tetsuki's curry is
the best curry in the world.
I appreciate that.
Though I wish I could
have let it stand for a day.
[CHIKA]
So make it again tomorrow!
Wait, are you guys staying over?
That's not a problem, is it?
Well, you could have
at least asked me first.
[MITTSU, CHIKA, SANE]
Seconds, please!
Already?
The son of Kaoru Takinami
and Tsukasa Yukimori?
That's what I heard.
Are they like a big deal
or something?
[TAKEZO]
What? You didn't know?
He's a world-renowned conductor,
and she's a piano prodigy!
They're famous?
That's right.
Even I know about them.
But it explains Mister Takinami,
and why he has
a good ear for music.
So when he told us
that our performance
was good the other day,
he must have really meant it,
seeing as he knows so
much about music and stuff.
Now I feel super proud of us.
[TETSUKI]
Heh.
Good for you.
[SANE]
I'm more excited than ever!
Let's hurry and get
caught up on our homework!
[CHIKA] Tetsuki, you said we
could trade assignments, right?
[TETSUKI]
Yeah, hard pass.
[CHIKA]
All healed!
Are you serious?
It's only been like two weeks.
Jealous?
Don't underestimate my skills.
You shouldn't rush it, or
you might hurt it even worse.
What's this?
It's been a long time since I've
seen you wear your hair down.
[SATOWA]
So? Is that weird or something?
[CHIKA] Nah, it doesn't
matter either way.
Oh. I see.
Why are you upset?
This is just
my resting expression.
[2-A CLASS REP]
And thanks to a majority vote,
it's decided that
we'll do a waffle booth
at the school festival!
Next we'll assign
everyone a job and a group.
[chuckles]
I can't believe we're on the
same shopping team together.
I'm really sorry.
Why? It's not
like you planned it.
No fair, why do I have
to be stuck on this team
with all these boring people?
[HIRO]
Wow, rude.
Excuse you?
Admit it, you've become
super boring lately.
Remember when you
used to make fun of Kurata
by calling him all
those girly nicknames?
Sorry.
[TAKEZO laughs]
No worries.
Huh?! Hey, why're you laughing?
[TAKEZO]
Oh, come on.
You've said way
meaner things to my face.
Girly nicknames are nothing.
Besides,
I know what you're like now.
It's all good.
So don't worry.
[HIRO]
Oh. This is bad.
I feel like... crying.
Whoa, what is going on
with your face right now?
Wait a minute,
do you actually li--
[SHIBUYA]
Saeki.
Is there a filter between
your brain and your mouth,
or is it missing?
Uh?! You're one to talk,
you big jerk!
[SHIBUYA]
Yeah, well,
at least I know when
not to talk unlike you.
[MIYU]
Would you just shut up?
[KOTA]
A traditional café?
That's what your class is
doing for the festival huh?
Will you be serving
lots of yummy food?
[CHIKA]
Yep, strawberry daifuku !
[SANE]
Are you serious?
Chika insisted and
they made it part of the menu.
So, does anyone else
here have a menu idea?
Strawberry daifuku !
[TETSUKI]
You should have seen the class.
They couldn't
believe a delinquent
would suggest such a thing.
They weren't sure how to react.
What's your class doing?
A good ol'
classic haunted house!
I'd expect you three to be
excited about participating
in the school festival,
but Chika's a surprise.
And you're performing?
That's right.
Before I played it, I thought
it was probably a lame medley,
but it actually turned out
to be a pretty cool piece.
For sure, Mister Takinami's
parents may be amazing,
but I gotta give the
guy credit where it's due.
Like the other day.
[TAKINAMI]
These are music CDs and DVDs
that I don't think
you'd normally listen to.
I want you to
listen to all of them.
[KOTA, MITTSU, SANE]
What?
But this is a mountain of music.
[TAKINAMI] It's a fraction
of my initial picks.
Fact of the matter is,
the amount of music you guys
come in contact with
is overwhelmingly small.
You need to listen to
a large variety of music
as often as possible.
Learn the different
sounds and expressions.
Absorb them into yourselves.
It'll help develop
your musicality.
I guarantee that
when you do those things,
playing the koto
will be a lot more fun.
Well, then, make sure
you listen to them.
Wait, Mister Takinami!
Aren't you going
to help us prepare?
[TAKINAMI] After you listen
to my recommendations.
And ever since that fateful day,
we've been listening to
the giant mountain of music.
Wow, it sounds like he's
keeping you guys pretty busy.
Are you jealous, Tetsuki?
If you get lonely,
we can come eat with you again!
--[TETSUKI] Please don't.
--[CHIKA] Ow!
[MIYOSHI] Okay, was
anyone else surprised
by Kudo in class today?
[STUDENT A]
For real, who knew the guy
was so crazy about strawberries?
[STUDENT B]
Did you see how cute he looked
when we all agreed to it?
[SATOWA]
Wait, "cute"?
Satowa.
Since the two of you
are in the same club,
tell us what he's like!
Uh. I don't really know.
All in all, I suppose
he's fairly normal, so...
Oh, hey, aren't there more guys
than girls in the koto club?
Any cute boys
you're crushing on?
[SATOWA gasps]
No! Of course not!
[STUDENT B]
You sure?
I'm seeing a guy
I met this summer from
a different prefecture.
He's so hot!
Aw, I'm so jealous.
[SATOWA] What is up
with this conversation?
Is this what girls
normally talk about?
I don't get it, I'm not
following this at all.
[HIRO laughs]
That's hilarious.
It's pretty normal
for the number of couples
to increase after summer,
after all we're high-schoolers
in the prime of our lives.
I didn't know
that's how girls acted.
Do you think that there's
something wrong with me?
And how I act?
I just don't understand
these girly topics.
You're beyond adorable Hozuki,
please don't ever change!
I love you exactly
the way you are!
Um, what about you, Hiro?
Since you're a high school girl,
is there maybe a boy
or someone that you like?
Uh...
Not really.
[SATOWA]
Why did she pause?
[SANE]
S'up koto lovers!
Oh, hey Sane.
Where're the others?
[SANE]
Well.
Mittsu and Kota are on cleaning
duty, so I left them behind.
I wanted to get
here to practice.
'Cause you're playing
the 17-string this time?
Yeah, there's quite
a bit of pressure.
But I'm happy, too, you know?
It's a big responsibility.
I feel like I've
been given some credit.
I hate to keep
asking you, Hozuki,
but will you help me with
the 17-string some more?
I'll show you no mercy!
[SANE]
Thanks!
[SATOWA] This is the
atmosphere I really thrive in.
I'm much more suited
for the koto than girl talk.
[SATOWA] Is there maybe
a boy or someone you like?
[HIRO]
I have to focus!
We're gonna go
to nationals for sure!
I should follow Sane's
example and practice hard!
[2-A CLASS REP]
Yo, shopping team!
Can you make a run for us?
Here. It's the list.
[HIRO]
On it.
I'm ready whenever you are.
Oh. It's just the two of us?
Yeah, the other guys
seem to be MIA.
If you'd rather stay here,
then I can take care of it.
That wasn't really my concern.
[HIRO] Man, why do I feel
so nervous right now?
This isn't like me.
I mean, come on,
what about that time we were
alone in his room together?
Shopping should be
a walk in the park.
[MINAMI]
Hmm? Hiro?
[HIRO gasps]
That voice.
Yep!
I thought that was you.
Hiro. I heard that
you've been talking
about me behind my
back to all of your friends.
[HIRO'S FRIEND]
Liar!
Minami told us how
you've been harassing her
because you're afraid
she'll steal your boyfriend!
[NAOYA]
Unbelievable.
That's so low.
[MINAMI]
What a coincidence!
It's been a while.
Yeah. I guess.
Hey, guys.
Are these some of
your friends, Kurusu?
[NAOYA] Is he who you're
seeing these days?
No, we're friends.
[NAOYA]
You know.
I still hear bad
things about you.
I hope you aren't treating
others the way you treated us.
That's not true!
I didn't do
anything to you guys!
I told you!
So please stop saying it.
[NAOYA]
Hmph.
All that trouble.
At the very least,
you should apologize
for what you did to us.
[HIRO]
Me?
But I didn't.
Not to be rude,
but we're in a bit of a hurry.
Let's go.
Listen, pal,
if you want my advice,
I wouldn't trust that
girl if I were you.
[TAKEZO]
Hmph.
Please don't worry.
Unlike you,
I'm a good judge of character.
[HIRO]
Kurata.
Hey, Kurata!
Um, my hand.
[TAKEZO]
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
Uh. Thank you.
Right.
Let's go shopping.
Come on.
[HIRO]
Crap.
It's so loud.
Why is my heart... pounding?
So, uh, what are you making?
Huh? You can't tell?
It should be fairly obvious.
It's the café menu to
put outside our classroom.
[CHIKA]
Hmm... And what's that?
[SATOWA]
A teacup drawing.
[CHIKA]
And this?
[SATOWA]
A strawberry daifuku .
[laughs]
I see.
Who knew you were
such an artist, huh?
Whoa. Did Kudo just laugh?
Do I even wanna know
what you're doing?
[SATOWA]
Uh...
Uh... Well...
Nothing!
Seriously?
What am I doing?
[CHIKA] I feel like this base
board is way too distorted.
It's the only extra
wood I could find!
I'll fix it for you.
Hand me that tool.
[SATOWA]
Watch out!
There's a nail right there!
[screams] I'm sorry,
that was my bad!
Don't get the
wrong idea or anything!
It was just an accident, okay?
No harm, no foul!
But... I was the one who
moved forward so suddenly.
Huh?
What the...?
Am I...?
Sorry!
Wait. Hozuki, stop!
I made her cry.
[SATOWA]
My face feels hot.
What should I do?
[SATOWA]
Why is it so hot?
[laughs]
Look how scary my mask is!
Let's put some
more fake blood on it!
[laughter]
[TAKEZO]
Next time: "Their Time."