[chattering]
[TAKEZO]
This is Meiryo's koto club?
Huh?
Satowa!
You made it!
I was starting to get wor‐‐
It'll be okay!
Here, I'll disinfect you!
Stop treating me
like a virus already!
[CLUB MEMBER A] Isn't that
the koto club from Tokise?
They're so uncouth.
[CLUB MEMBER B] I didn't know
animals could play the koto.
What? Have you got
somethin' to say to us?
Come and say it, then!
Please calm down.
Oh! Hey. Is that the girl you
were talking about, Kazusa?
Whoa! She's beautiful!
Wait.
Are those boys?
Uh, but.... Don't tell me.
Are you guys all in
the Tokise Koto Club, too?
[CHIKA]
Huh?
Yeah, you got a
problem with that?
[chuckles]
Fellow koto brothers!
You? You? You?
And how about you?
Do you play the koto?
That's great!
Name's Ousuke Kiryu;
I'm a first year!
This is my first time
meeting other guys
who enjoy playing the
koto as much as I do!
Man, I am so excited!
[KOU]
Ousuke.
That's enough.
Oh, please forgive me, Kou.
Are you feeling lonely now
that I've made friends
with students from
other schools?
[OUSUKE] I'm positive
we'll be great friends.
Please ignore that
good‐for‐nothing boy.
He's a real nuisance.
All right, almost time.
Are you ready
for our performance?
I'm sure you'll love it!
Aw, man.
Those girls are Kanagawa
prefecture's number one?
Not just this prefecture.
They're always in
the top at nationals.
Their school's amazing!
What? Are you serious?
Yep. You'll understand
better once you hear them play.
At the end of the day,
they just fit together.
Why does that matter?
Fitting together or
whatever doesn't mean
their music's gonna be good.
[laughs]
Yeah, maybe.
But you have to fit together.
Otherwise nationals
are out of the question.
[ALL]
Hmm?
‐‐[KOTA] Do we fit?
‐‐[CHIKA] Our group fits!
‐‐[MITTSU] Sure do!
‐‐[CHIKA] Kinda...
[CHIKA] Like a round peg
in a square hole.
Hi, can everyone
please take a seat?
Himesaka's performance
will begin in just a moment.
Huh? Hold on.
I'm confused;
I thought Meiryo
was going to do their
performance before Himesaka.
We already did our
performance, it was earlier.
[TAKEZO]
We missed it?
Probably because we were late.
The piece we'll
be performing today
is called "Two Personalities,"
and we hope you'll all enjoy it.
[SATOWA]
"Two Personalities"?
With this many people?
That will be challenging.
♪ fast, precise playing ♪
[gasps]
[CHIKA]
Their sound is so intense!
It almost hurts!
[SANE]
No way.
This piece only has two parts?
Yes.
"Two Personalities"
was originally intended
to be performed as a duet.
The duet between the
first koto and the second koto
becomes one melody.
The tempo is fast,
so if you mess up even a little,
it can throw off
the whole sound.
It's tough.
The song is challenging
with just two people.
Such a large group
playing at this speed,
and yet they play together
as if they were one person!
[gulps]
[TAKEZO]
Forming one melody as a duet.
There's a part like
that in "Kuon," too.
But we couldn't
get it to work at all.
How?
How did they manage to do this?
What is that technique?
I've never seen it.
It's impressive
how quick they are.
Whoa! They're really fast!
No way, are they gonna
play the whole melody
using that technique?
[TAKEZO] Last year,
when I heard Himesaka perform,
it was a national‐level
performance.
I was overwhelmed.
But... now the club's reborn.
We're more organized.
I'm positive that
I've grown a bit, too.
But now the differences
between us are even more clear.
[KAZUSA]
Do you get it now?
Do you see how
much better we are?
I'll make you see.
That you aren't a
good match for Satowa!
♪ playing ends ♪
[cheering]
[SATOWA]
Even at that high speed,
they managed to stay
together until the end.
Their school is
at a national level.
Perhaps I was being naïve.
[CHIKA]
Crap!
So Wavy Head
wasn't just talk after all.
See, don't they
fit great together?
Uh. Sure.
They were fine, I guess.
Are you guys also planning
to aim for nationals?
We are.
That's awesome.
Now all you need is to be better
than the performance
you just saw.
Too bad, though.
I really wish you could have
at least heard
Meiryo's performance.
Huh?
Step aside, loser!
What'd you think?
Were you completely
blown away by our playing?
It was quite amazing.
Especially with
a song so challenging.
And with such a large group.
Okay, let's get you
a transfer application!
And I'll introduce you
to everyone!
What the? What do
you think you're doing?
Take your grubby hands
off her this instant!
[CHIKA]
Put a sock in it, Shaggy.
[KAZUSA]
Shaggy?
You got wax in your ears?
She already told you no.
She said that
she likes our club.
Stop being such a pest
and just give up.
[KAZUSA]
Huh?
So even after listening
to our performance,
you still don't understand?
You're nowhere near our level!
And you guys will never
be a match for Satowa!
You're not saying anything
we don't already know!
And we're fine with it, because
we're willing to put in the work
so that we can catch up to her.
What?
[whistles]
Yeah!
What Chika said!
C'mon, you really think
we don't know that
we're not as talented as she is?
But that doesn't mean we're
gonna stop trying our hardest!
[MITTSU, SANE, KOTA]
Hozuki.
We'll keep doing our best!
I can't keep up with you.
Just play by yourself.
Thanks.
[TAKEZO]
Catch up?
How do we do that?
[OUSUKE]
So, that's the Tokise Koto Club?
They're pretty entertaining.
It is kind of a shame they
didn't get here sooner, though.
I wanted them to hear us play.
Oh, well, one day.
We're not just a
group that fits together,
but an actual ensemble.
[SANE] Man, wasn't Himesaka's
performance amazing?
[TSUDA]
It goes on sale tomorrow.
[NAKAYAMA] Sounds cool,
we should check it out.
[TSUDA]
Kurata?
[gasps]
I thought so!
How's it goin', man?
Whoa, no way!
We haven't seen you
since middle school!
Nakayama.
Tsuda.
[TSUDA]
Where've you been?
You've been MIA
ever since graduation!
We were worried.
Sorry.
Of all people here,
why'd we have to run into them?
[TSUDA] Anyway, what
brings you to Meiryo High?
Oh.
It's just club stuff.
A joint practice session.
[NAKAYAMA]
Cool! Which club?
It's the koto club.
[TSUDA]
Huh? What was that?
[TAKEZO]
I said the koto club.
Koto? Like the
traditional instrument?
[laughter]
[NAKAYAMA]
Are you kidding me? The koto?
That's so crazy, man!
I know!
What're you hyenas laughin' at?
Do you think playing
the koto is funny?
Hey, calm down, Kudo!
Kurata, who is this guy?
Shuddup!
I'll have you know this
guy's actually serious‐‐
Stop, Kudo! It's okay!
What? No, it's really not!
They made fun of you
for playin' the koto!
You can't put up with that crap!
Bye, it was good
to see you guys!
What's your problem, Specs?
None of this is fine!
Let go of me!
[SANE]
Calm down, Chika!
Come on!
Aren't you mad about the
stupid things they're saying?
[TAKEZO]
No.
If anything, I'm used to it.
[CHIKA] Well, you shouldn't get
used to people laughing at you!
Look, that's not
what I meant, Kudo.
It just doesn't bother me, okay?
[CHIKA]
Then act like it!
Be more confident about it!
And stop laughing it off!
Jeez.
[TAKEZO]
Be more confident? How, though?
If there's something
you're holding back
or wanna talk about,
then say it.
Shut up already.
You wouldn't understand.
Okay, that's enough of that.
There will be no fighting while
we're visiting another school.
Come on, let's go.
[gasps]
[TAKINAMI]
Uh‐oh.
It seems you've upset one
of your underclassmen.
Would you get off my back?
Hey. Tell me something.
Are you and the club really
aiming for nationals, Kurata?
Yeah, of course.
Something wrong with that?
[laughs]
What's with that response?
You laugh off the koto
with your old classmates,
and you can't even
look me in the eye.
The club president
is responsible
for leading
everybody around him.
But here you lack even the
most basic self‐confidence.
You'll never get
to nationals like that.
[TAKINAMI]
Well,
it's no skin off my back
if you don't succeed.
Do whatever you want.
Oh. Takezo.
Were you at Meiryo?
What on earth
were you doing there?
Uh, I was there with my club.
[TAKERU]
Huh? You can't be serious.
You're still going on
about that stuff?
[TAKERU]
So lame.
[TAKEZO]
What should I do?
How do I become confident?
[TAKEZO] Let's try it
once more from the top.
The duet still isn't
really meshing together.
So let's try it slower.
Three, four.
[CHIKA]
Damn it.
It's no use even at this speed?
Then maybe we should try
practicing on our own.
[CHIKA]
What?
Well, I was thinking
it might be best
if we learned how to
play it better individually
before we try to do
the song together again.
Are you serious?
[TAKEZO] Shut up already.
You wouldn't understand.
Hey, now, hold on a second,
where are you going?
[CHIKA]
To practice alone.
I'll visualize it.
Should we say something?
[TAKEZO]
Sorry.
But I have to leave, too.
[TAKEZO] Even at a critical time
like this, I'm still wavering.
Tetsuki! Feed me!
Cheese Hamburg steak!
We're having pork
cutlet bowls tonight.
Boo!
[TETSUKI]
I talked to Sane earlier.
He's upset.
Something about how you
haven't made up with Kurata yet.
There's nothing to make up,
Four‐Eyes and I aren't
even really fighting!
He's just being his weird,
usual, glasses wearing, self.
Ah. I see.
Look, I don't know
all the details.
But he's an
upperclassman, right?
[CHIKA]
Yeah? So?
Well, if he has a problem,
it's probably tough
for him to talk about it,
especially with
an underclassman.
Try to keep that in mind.
[CHIKA]
Sounds stupid.
You know my older brother?
He never tells me anything,
and he rarely confides in me.
What's with that?
And does that mean
there's nothing I can do?
[TAKEZO]
How do we catch up to her?
Think.
[HIRO]
Sorry to bother you.
I'm Kurusu, Takezo's classmate
and a member of the koto club.
If you don't mind,
I have something important to
discuss with the club president.
Huh? Takezo's
the club president?
Uh. Kurusu?
Good evening! Am I intruding?
Wow, your room's
so neat and tidy.
[TAKEZO] So, is there
a reason why you're here?
Jeez, you're so uptight.
Oh, what's this?
A DVD of koto performances?
That's right.
I thought I'd listen to
some national performances.
Whoa!
You're serious about
this stuff, aren't you?
You're gonna go bald, Kurata!
[TAKEZO]
Uh.
Thanks, I guess?
[HIRO]
But, you know what?
Being the club president
doesn't mean
you have to handle
everything by yourself.
So, I had a nice chat
with Suzu about it!
Starting tomorrow,
I'll be taking over as the
koto club's vice‐president!
[TAKEZO]
Huh?
Are you serious?
That's right!
The position is available,
and it must be tough doing
everything on your own.
So if you need help
with anything,
just let me know, okay?
Sorry.
Because I'm so unreliable,
I've made you worry.
But I don't wanna be
a burden to you‐‐
Cut that out, Kurata!
Listen to me. The only
burden is watching you
try to do everything
by yourself,
and then moping around the club,
acting all sad about it!
We can all feel that,
do you understand?
It really sucks!
Oh. I, uh...
Don't you get it?
The reason why
I wanted to join this club?
It's because I saw kids
who had nothing in common.
But, despite that,
they all supported each other.
And I thought...
It was really awesome, and I
wanted to be a part of that.
What?
But I thought you joined
because you were jealous
and wanted to mess with us.
[HIRO groans]
Um. Look, it doesn't matter!
I'm saying you don't
have to carry everything
on your own, okay?
Just try to have
a little more faith
in the people around
you sometimes!
You said, that if I was serious,
you'd be willing
to listen to me.
So I'm saying,
I'll listen to you!
Well! That concludes
my business here. Bye!
[TAKEZO]
Hey, wait! Kurusu!
[HIRO]
Thanks for having me!
[TAKERU]
Who was that?
Jeez, so loud.
[TAKEZO'S MOM]
Apparently, she's a friend
from Takezo's koto club.
The koto club?
Makes sense.
Everyone in that club
seems pretty uncivilized.
[TAKERU]
Takezo.
You should really choose
your friends better.
That's enough, young man.
[TAKEZO]
Takeru.
Don't ever talk about
my friends like that again.
[TAKEZO'S DAD]
Takezo.
Your mother said your
girlfriend came over today.
Uh. My what now?
[TAKEZO'S DAD]
She also told me
that you're the president
of the koto club.
Is that true?
Yeah, it is.
But I only got the position
because I was the only person
there, so it doesn't count.
Takezo.
Don't you dare ever
lessen your worth like that.
Weren't you the one
who worked hard on
your own to continue the club?
To get new members?
That alone is admirable.
It made me so happy
when I saw you stand up for
your friends against Takeru.
It's strange,
but you never got that upset
when he picks on you,
no matter what.
The moment he went
after your friends though,
you refused to take it anymore.
That's when I realized,
they must be a
wonderful group of people,
I'm so glad you have them.
[TAKEZO]
Huh?
Where's Kudo?
Uh. Well, he said he's gonna do
visualization training
alone today.
[TAKEZO]
Oh.
Look, we're
really sorry, Takezo.
We're just not sure
what we're supposed
to do in this situation.
And if I were being
completely honest,
I think that's probably
how Chika feels too.
[inaudible]
Hey, where are you going?
[TAKEZO]
I'm such an idiot!
I've been so focused on myself
that I haven't been seeing
what's going on around me!
I should have known I'm not
the only person struggling.
Up until the club,
Chika never really
bothered with other people.
And if he did get
involved with them,
it was usually because
they were hitting one another.
So him getting angry
on someone else's behalf,
or even trying to understand
where they might be coming from.
Those are all feelings
he's rarely experienced.
I think Chika's
just really frustrated.
Because he doesn't
know how to help you.
[TAKEZO]
Kudo!
Listen.
[CHIKA] Not right now, I'm
doing visualization training.
It's just I'm sorry.
Meiryo was actually the school
I failed the entrance exam to.
So, the truth is,
I didn't want to go to
the joint practice session.
But then, I ignored my own
feelings and went anyway.
I was overwhelmed by
Himesaka's performance,
and I didn't know what to do.
So I ended up lashing out.
I don't possess that
much self‐confidence.
It was hard.
Seeing you act
so confidently in front of
everyone made me feel inferior.
And I let the club down.
Sorry.
I didn't say anything because
I didn't want to be a burden.
But now I realize that you
deserve to know the truth.
It's okay.
Honestly, I don't have
a lot of faith in myself.
Still.
I know.
There are others
who do have faith in me.
My grandpa did, anyway.
And you believed in me, too.
Huh?
The day you got beat up
by those dumb jerks.
You believed in me.
You stood up for me
and told everyone I was
a member of the club.
Because of that day.
Well, we're here now, aren't we?
Aren't we?
Uh, aren't we, what?
Shuddup!
Besides, the only person
who doesn't see you
as the president is you!
You can't let yourself be
bothered by something stupid
that you can't see, like
self‐confidence, okay?
It's invisible, and if you say
you have it, you have it!
[HIRO] But, despite that,
they all supported each other.
[TAKEZO laughs]
I see.
Yeah.
I already had something much
more important
than self‐confidence.
You're right, Kudo.
Look! It's Takezo and Chika!
See? I told you guys
they would come back.
What's wrong?
[KOTA]
Nothing!
Does this mean you
two have made up?
What? But we weren't
even fighting.
[SANE]
Whatever you say, man.
Well, thanks to your
little friendship spat,
now everyone's behind
on our schedule.
Right?
[SATOWA]
Indeed.
Looks like we'll have to
reinstate morning practice.
[MITTSU]
Aw, really?
[SATOWA]
Really.
[HIRO]
What time should we be here?
[SATOWA]
Let's shoot for seven AM.
[TAKEZO]
Hey, guys?
Listen, I think it
may be impossible
for us to get to Nationals.
Himesaka, Kanagawa's number one,
is clearly better than us.
And I doubt we can
ever surpass them...
...at least, at this rate.
Even if we put in the same
amount of effort as Himesaka,
we'll never catch up to them.
No matter how much
we want it.
We might still be left crying.
Still though,
I'd like to aim for Nationals.
With everyone in this room!
More than anything else.
[CHIKA]
Hey, Specs.
I'm taking this down.
[TAKEZO]
Why?
Okay. We all write
one word each.
Huh? What's this gonna do?
Don't worry about it.
Just have a little faith.
Here, I think the
president should go first.
[TAKEZO]
I'm done hiding.
No more laughing it off.
Battles you know you're
gonna win aren't much fun.
I like a challenge.
It might feel impossible
if we were all working alone,
but we're in this together.
Hard work's not really my forte,
but I promise to do my best!
Here you go, Hiro!
[HIRO]
Thanks!
Oh, I might have forgotten
to mention this fact,
but I'm gonna be the
club's vice‐president.
Let's do this!
[SANE, KOTA, MITTSU]
Huh?
[HIRO]
Here Hozuki.
It's your turn to add
a word to the poster next.
You know it's funny,
but this used to be
what I was working towards.
Doing it alone though
would have been impossible.
But now I've got you guys.
Right?
Personally, if you ask me,
having a goal that seems
out of reach is more fun.
[CHIKA]
Okay, tell me if it's crooked.
[SANE]
Move it to the right a little.
[MITTSU]
There! That's perfect.
[CHIKA]
'Kay! It's finished!
[SATOWA]
Next time: "Near Yet Far."