[SATOWA gasps]
[CHIHARU]
Satowa?
[gasps]
[CHIKA, TAKEZO, HIRO gasp]
[CHIHARU]
Thank goodness.
I was looking for you,
hoping you might still be here.
[CHIHARU]
I heard your performance.
[gasps]
I am so sorry.
When I think about all
the things I've done,
and how those things
can never be undone,
I can only assume that it left
a deep scar on your heart.
You don't have to forgive me.
I don't deserve that.
But I want to ask.
If you can maybe see it
in your heart, would you...?
Would you give me
one more chance?
Another chance to
face you? Properly?
So, does that mean my
feelings... finally reached you?
For once. I managed
to get through to you?
You understood me?
[CHIHARU sighs]
[SATOWA sobs]
[KOTA sniffles]
Hozuki!
I'm so happy for you!
No, don't!
Whoa!
Hey! Kota!
[ALL gasp]
[HIRO] Jeez! I can't believe
you'd do something like that!
My goodness.
I'm so sorry, Hozuki.
We didn't mean to ruin your
reunion with your mom.
[SATOWA] It wasn't ruined.
I guess I'm just embarrassed.
You had to help me look for her.
And then you guys had to
see me crying, so I'm sorry.
Don't apologize!
A beautiful reunion is nothing
to be embarrassed about!
[CHIKA] Hm? You two really
resemble each other.
D'You know that?
Were you one of the boys
playing the bass koto?
[CHIKA]
Mm! Yes, I'm Kudo.
Ah. I see. So you're Kudo.
[CHIKA]
Huh?
Well, you and the other boy
played the 17-string quite well.
It was a great performance.
I want to thank you... for being
supportive of my daughter.
[gasps]
Oh. I, uh...
But if anything, Hozuki's been
the one leading us, you know?
Leading people and supporting
someone are different things.
I can see why this
club is so important.
Why she likes it,
and why she cherishes it.
[CHIKA grunts]
[CHIKA]
Mm! Thank you.
[chuckles]
Oh man, I'm super
happy for Hozuki.
Yeah, me too!
All this happy reunion
stuff made me thirsty!
Hey! We're gonna play
to see who buys drinks!
[CHIKA]
Fine.
[AKIRA]
Grand Master?
There you are, Akira.
Thank you. I'm glad that
you brought me here today.
Oh? Well, I'm sorry that
I was so forceful.
[CHIKA]
Alright, get ready!
[ALL]
Rock, paper, scissors!
They seem like such a good group
of kids. Just like you said.
[AKIRA]
They are.
[CHIKA] Man, why do I suck so
hard at rock-paper-scissors?
[CHIKA gasps]
[KAZUSA gasps] What?
Why don't you take a picture?
Do you have a problem?
What's with that dumb
look on your face?
[CHIKA] The hell?
Stop yelling at me.
I just came here to get
some drinks, ya nut.
[KAZUSA grunts]
[KAZUSA] Whatever, I bet you
think you were better than us.
[CHIKA]
Huh?
[KAZUSA] Look at you, over here
buying drinks and stuff.
If you're that relaxed you must
think you got first place.
[CHIKA]
You don't think you took first?
[KAZUSA]
I don't know.
I used to believe being in sync
was all that really mattered.
I thought it sounded so
beautiful and perfect.
It's what making music has
always meant to us as a club.
But then... I heard your
group perform together.
So now, all the focus we
spent on just being in sync,
feels kinda dumb.
[CHIKA exhales]
What're you saying?
"Just being in sync"?
Don't belittle it like that.
[KAZUSA gasps]
[CHIKA] You guys played
perfectly at that speed,
even with so many
people up there.
It doesn't mean much
coming from me,
but I thought it was awesome.
[gasps]
[CHIKA] You're right, though.
We will take first place.
[KAZUSA gasps]
[KAZUSA]
Hey! Hold on just a second!
Do you remember when I
said that you weren't worthy
to play the koto with Satowa?
I take it back.
I hate to say it.
I don't even want to admit it.
Your performance today...
was actually really good!
[chuckles]
Damn straight.
[gasps]
[CHIKA hums]
[KAZUSA grunts]
Stupid jerk.
A normal person would just
say thank you or whatever.
[buzzing]
[ANNOUNCER A]
Attention participants:
We will now announce the results
and hold the closing ceremony.
[CHIKA grunts]
[ANNOUNCER A] We request that
the participating schools
return to the hall.
[ASAHINA] Now then. Thank you
for your performances today.
To be honest, everyone sounded
amazing this year.
It felt like we were
already at Nationals.
We were all
quite impressed. Truly.
Unfortunately, it left us judges
with a rather
difficult decision.
[WADA] Oh, my. We can
only send one of these
high schools
to Nationals, right?
Himesaka, Hakuto and Tokise.
They're all good enough to
have a shot going forward.
[ASAHINA] I agree, but we
can only choose one.
[gasps]
So in my opinion, it's Tokise.
Their skill level is above
satisfactory, and what's more,
I've never been so
moved by a performance
from high school kids before.
It's very impressive.
When I heard those
kids playing,
it made me really remember
how wonderful music can be.
I disagree.
A lot of musicians these days
only play modern pieces.
They have beautiful
melodies and simple motifs,
so the music resonates more
easily with the audience.
But, that also means that the
piece isn't that difficult
to play in the grand
scheme of things.
So I would like to
recommend Hakuto.
They should get high marks for
both their selection of piece
and performance.
What do you think,
Mister Wada?
Well, it's a tough choice.
To be honest with you,
I had found Tokise's
performance quite moving.
But if I considered all
of the competition,
I'd have to say Himesaka.
I think their ability to be
perfectly in sync
is worthy of first place.
[ASAHINA grunts] Do you have
an opinion, Mister Matsunaga?
[ASAHINA]
If it were possible,
we would send every single
participant to Nationals.
We sincerely mean that.
However.
If that happened, it would no
longer be a competition.
We still had to assign a rank
to all of your performances.
Which was hard.
Because no matter what
our personal feelings are,
at the end of the day
we can only send one
school here to Nationals.
Now then, without further ado...
[MATSUNAGA] There is only
one school that qualifies.
They were obviously
in a different league
than the others.
In music and technique.
[ASAHINA gasps]
[MATSUNAGA]
Don't get me wrong,
I understand what
Miss Midoriyama means.
But their excellent performance
didn't come from the fact
that it was simply the kind of
piece that people like to hear.
When a piece is wonderful,
it goes beyond experts.
It's able to reach those who
don't know that much about
the koto and what kind
of music it can make.
Music like that can reach those
who speak a different language
and live in a different culture.
So I think it's only proper
that we shine a light on such
a brilliant performance.
[ASAHINA] For the thirty-second
Kanagawa Qualifier
for Japan High School
Music Competition.
The school that
receives first place
and goes to nationals is...
[ASAHINA] ...Kanagawa
Prefectural Tokise High School.
[ALL gasp]
--[MITTSU] No way!
--[SANE] Huh? For real?
Is he serious?
Whoa! Hozuki, you hear that?
First! He said first! Right?
Is it true? Did we really win?
We did!
No way! Isaki!
They really did it, they're
actually going to Nationals,
this is a dream come true!
Wow. Cool.
[CROWD clapping]
Really? Takezo won?
[CHIKA] It didn't end here.
We can keep going.
Hear that? We made it!
Kudo, we--!
[CHIKA sobs]
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[ALL sobbing, cheering]
[SANE] We're all going
to Nationals together!
Hey, guys! Congratulations!
Isaki. Tetsuki.
Mashiro's with them?
I'm so happy you won!
You were amazing.
The best concert
I've ever heard.
Duh. Of course we were awesome.
We snatched up that ticket to
Nationals just like you said.
[ISAKI grunts]
Way to go.
You did a great job. I'm proud.
Hey. Get off of me!
[ISAKI]
Stop playing shy!
[TETSUKI chuckles]
Way to go, tiger.
I didn't know you were gonna
be here today, Mashiro.
I wouldn't miss it!
I just happened to
sit next to Isaki,
so we got to know
each other a bit.
You're actually going
to Nationals.
That's so cool.
No, better than cool--
it's awesome!
That was such an incredible
performance. Congratulations!
Thank you, that means a lot.
At least now we can
relax a little.
What do you mean,
you've been composed this
entire time, Mister Takinami.
I was so impressed.
Are you kidding me?
If anything, I've been
a nervous wreck all day.
[AKIRA gasps]
[TAKINAMI] If for some reason
they couldn't get to Nationals
with a performance like that,
it would be because of my
arrangement of the piece.
[AKIRA]
What? No.
It's quite possible.
When a piece is
easy to listen to,
then it becomes easy for
people to dismiss it.
I'm genuinely happy
it worked out.
[chuckles] I haven't
known you for very long,
but I kind of like seeing
this side of you.
Wait, so you like
seeing me worried?
[AKIRA]
No! That's not what I meant!
[KEISHI]
Akira!
[gasps]
[AKIRA] Huh? Keishi?
He actually came?
[KEISHI]
Hm! Whoa, you did it!
You guys are really gonna go
to Nationals, that's so amazing!
Their playing moved me to tears.
But that's to be expected
with you teaching them!
[AKIRA] What do I do? I don't
know what to say right now.
Hey. You must be the
other teacher from Tokise!
I'm Akira's older brother.
Thanks for being
kind to my sister.
Oh, hi. My name's Takinami.
And your sister has
been kind to us.
Wait, you're miss
Aki's big brother?
Makes sense. Yeah!
Whoa! Your club
played wonderfully.
There's so many boys in it.
I bet you guys have tons of fun.
It's the best club ever!
But man, your sister's like a
really tough teacher, y'know?
Yeah? Well, I'd believe it.
What? My lessons
aren't that tough.
[SANE]
But...
...I'm grateful that Miss Akira
was so hard on all of us.
I don't think that we
would have got the tickets
to Nationals otherwise.
Thank you, for everything.
[KOTA] Mh-hm! We could have
never done it without you.
It's true.
[KEISHI gasps]
[SANE]
Uh. What's up, man?
[KEISHI]
I'm giving you a hug for Akira!
[KOTA, MITTSU]
What?
[KOTA]
I'd rather get the hug from her.
[KEISHI]
As if I'd ever allow that!
I liked your playing.
It was innocent and earnest.
It made me feel super warm.
I can tell you love the koto,
your sound tells me everything.
Akira. Thank you, for inviting
me to come and listen.
I'm really glad I got to
hear your current sound.
It's beautiful.
[gasps]
[BOTH giggle]
[AKIRA chuckles]
Thank you... Keishi.
[AKIRA gasps]
[KEISHI chuckles]
[KEISHI]
My little sister is the cutest!
[FUMI]
Kazusa. We need to get going.
Kazusa?
[KAZUSA]
I already knew it,
from the moment I heard
Tokise's performance.
Even in that moment,
he had complete and
total faith in their sound.
But I... I didn't.
Don't cry! Don't cry! Don't cry!
I don't have the right!
I don't deserve to feel sad.
Come on, already. How long
are you gonna stay like that?
You're not the only
one who's upset.
[HOZUMI]
Kazusa.
[KAZUSA]
We'll get there.
We'll play together
at nationals!
[KAZUSA whimpers]
[HOZUMI]
Hey. Kazu--
[KAZUSA] I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
I'm... sorry. I'm sorry!
What're you apologizing for?
There's not a single reason
for you to be sorry.
Not when you gave such a
wonderful performance up there.
Everyone really gave it their
all for us support members.
I'm grateful that you
tried so hard for us.
It's okay. You can
start again from here.
[whimpera]
[HOZUMI]
This is a new chance.
Use it to build
yourself back up.
[YAMAMOTO]
So, hey, uh, I'm sorry.
Especially since everyone has
been practicing so hard.
But I wasn't good enough.
I let you all down.
Hold on just a sec!
That's enough.
You don't have to
apologize to us.
[gasps] If anything,
we should apologize to you.
We wanted to take you to
Nationals as a farewell gift,
but we couldn't
make that happen.
[YAMAMOTO]
What're you saying? Come on.
You guys played my
piece so wonderfully.
That by itself made
me really happy.
That's why I feel
like I let you down,
because if I was just more of an
expert in music, then maybe--
Hey. Mio?
Wait, why are you crying?
Because... I just
wanted to win today.
I had to win. Because for
Mister Yamamoto, the president,
and the others,
this was their last chance.
If I were better earlier
in the year...
...if I'd improved faster...
...then maybe things
would be different.
Maybe... we'd be
celebrating right now.
[MIO]
I'm sorry.
That's not fair of you say.
We're the ones to blame here,
you're only a first year,
it's not your responsibility
to carry us.
How can we apologize to you?
[gasps, grunts]
Stop! No more apologizing!
I need to stop as well!
There's nothing for you
guys to apologize for!
It's true! Your performance
today was the best one yet!
I'll be proud of what
I heard up there today
for the rest of my life!
Um, the first time I saw
your sheet music...
...it looked like a starry sky,
and I thought it was so pretty.
I love the pieces you make.
And... playing them
made me really happy.
[whimpers]
[MIO]
Thank you.
[TAKINAMI]
Time for us to gotta get going.
You guys got everything?
[SANE]
Let's roll!
[KAZUSA grunts]
[exhales]
Tokise High School!
[ALL gasp]
[FUMI]
Hey. Kazusa?
You guys better win
at Nationals.
I expect nothing less
after beating us.
So do whatever you have
to in order to win!
Or I won't forgive you!
Yeah. That's the plan.
[CHIKA]
Hmph.
That was a weird way
to root for you guys.
[CHIKA yells]
Congrats on winning. I'm still
upset that we lost, but...
...I wish you luck
at the Nationals.
[TAKEZO] And so, it was with
much joy and heartbreak,
that the Kanagawa Qualifier
finally came to an end.
[gasps]
Hm...
[CHIKA] Aw, dammit!
I messed up again!
Hey. This is a pretty
difficult piece, huh?
Hope we don't screw it up.
Yeah, I know, I'm having trouble
trying to figure out how
my part is supposed to sound.
Jeez. You were the ones who
wanted a tougher piece to play.
Do you even remember that?
Mister Suzu is such a meanie,
a meanie! I hate him.
Should I ask him to
change the piece, then?
Tell him it's too hard?
[BOYS]
No way!
This is easy! It's a piece
of cake, you hear me?
Good. Well...
In the meantime, we can just
practice the other piece.
For the club presentation day.
Yep, I'm super stoked for it!
Are you guys ready?
[ALL]
Yeah!
[TAKEZO] On my count.
One, two...!