[MIO] When I open sheet music,
sounds glow, and rise up,
creating a path in the darkness.
All I do is move forward,
following that light.
So I don't go off course and
get swallowed by the darkness.
I follow the path faithfully.
That's the only way I know
to play the koto right now.
What? The Advisor? Me?
For the school's koto club?
Ten years ago.
One year out of college.
After landing my dream
job of math teacher.
I was made the advisor of
a club I'd never heard of.
The world of music was
completely unknown to me,
not to mention the koto.
Oh wow, interesting!
I think I'm starting to come
around on the koto.
[FEMALE MEMBER A]
What? You haven't even heard
a performance yet.
I know. But look at this!
It's so familiar!
It's a combination
of 13 numbers,
one through kin , right?
It looks like a math problem,
so I'm drawn to it!
[KOTO CLUB MEMBERS]
Huh?
[YAMAMOTO] I casually
started learning about
the world of the koto.
[YAMAMOTO] All right! First I'll
listen to the "classics".
There's a lot to learn!
[gasps]
[YAMAMOTO] What I found
there... was a delicate,
meticulous world that seemed
to be perfectly calculated.
It was indeed a world
of math, which I loved.
With infinite potential,
contained within
only 13 strings.
Unbelievable. I'm listening
to math right now!
[YAMAMOTO]
After that,
I was rapidly sucked into
the world of music,
and eventually started
creating pieces.
Though they weren't popular
among the students,
so no one played them.
[YAMAMOTO] I guess teenagers
prefer modern music after all.
But, I like the
classics the most.
The number of sounds,
how they're assembled,
and their timing.
They're beautiful and efficient.
Even after I was transferred
to a different school,
I kept creating pieces.
And then... I ended up
in Hakuto's koto club.
[YAMAMOTO] We got so many new
first-year members this year!
Maybe if I'm lucky, one of them
will play a song or two of mine!
Eh, but probably not.
[YAMAMOTO]
Wait. This is my piece!
[YAMAMOTO] My song.
My world, is coming to life?
Yes! This is just how
I wanted it played!
This is the perfected
version of my piece!
You are?
Oh! Um, hi, I'm Yamamoto,
the koto club advisor!
[YAMAMOTO] I think this is that
new member named Kanzaki.
I don't know if you
knew this or not,
but I'm actually the one
who wrote the piece
you were just playing.
Oh. I didn't.
I just found it on
the shelf there.
Should I have not played it?
No! That's not what I meant!
Truth be told, I'm really
happy you performed it!
Thank you for that.
It was great.
[gasps]
I've composed lots of other
songs if you'd like to--
[MIO]
No thanks.
[gasps]
What? Why?
My sound it's...
it's boring. So...
[gasps]
[YAMAMOTO]
Suzumori!
Am I right in remembering
Kanzaki is your cousin?
I wanted to ask you something.
[UTA] Both of Mio's
parents work a lot,
so he often spent
time at my place.
My mom was starting to learn
the koto at the time,
so we both picked it up
and learned along with her.
I think we were around
six back then.
Wow. So you two have
been playing the koto
for a long time.
No wonder you're so good.
Well I'm okay. But Mio's
really something special.
Apparently, he can "see" sounds.
[YAMAMOTO]
What?
[UTA] It's like he somehow
knows the "right answer"
for how he should play
or express any given piece.
Well that's an
incredible talent!
Uh-huh. I think so to,
but Mio seems to hate it.
He says that the "right"
sounds are boring.
That set-in-stone
music is no fun,
so he hates his own sound.
He's been searching for the
"sound beyond the right answer."
Kanzaki! I heard that you can
see sounds. Is that true?
It is. So what?
I want you to play
the pieces I compose!
When I found you playing
one the other day,
I was really impressed,
and I was very very moved.
It was like the world
I pictured started moving
exactly the way I wanted.
It was an amazing feeling!
I don't want to play exactly
the way you meant it.
That's not enough.
I want to go "beyond" that.
Or else I'll never be able...
to be moved by my own sound.
[gasps]
Okay.
Then I'll make a piece that'll
allow you to go "beyond that."
Because I want to hear your
"sound beyond the
right answer," too!
Will you trust me,
with your talent?
I can help you!
[MIO]
No.
Why?
[MIO]
You're scary.
Kanzaki!
[YAMAMOTO]
And so, here we are.
Oh, no. I'm all tingly
and nervous.
You're our advisor, why don't
you try acting like it?
By the way, I meant to ask.
You're quitting teaching
after the qualifier, right?
H-Hold on a second,
how'd you know that?
I mean, everyone knows it.
You're the only one who thinks
that it's some big secret.
Huh?
You're taking over your
family's inn right?
And we know you weren't sick.
You made that up when you
couldn't come to the traditional
music festival because
your dad collapsed.
Are you really going
to quit after this?
[sighs]
I thought it over for a while.
Right.
Grand Master.
Let's go back home.
No performance so far
has been that good.
If the competition's
anything to go by,
we can't expect much from
Satowa's school, either.
I think I'll step outside
to get some fresh air.
[DOJIMA grunts] I don't want to
even be here a minute longer.
I'm leaving too.
[AKIRA] You heard me, come on.
You need to hear them play!
Grandmother!
You've always been the one who
can't face the koto head-on.
[DOJIMA] I know what she said,
but I can no longer do that.
It's too late for me.
[KEISHI]
Oh. Grandma, you came too?
[DOJIMA]
Keishi!
Hey. We need to leave
in five. Get ready.
Guess it's time to go!
Gotta pull it together!
I'm calm, are you?
What do I do? I can't breathe.
You're gonna be fine, Kota.
Deep breaths! Calm down.
I'm not Kota.
Hozuki save me!
Uh. Hey, you guys?
After leaving this room,
we gotta be quiet.
Wanna form a circle?
One good cuddle-puddle
for the road!
I'm in!
That'll totally pump me up!
[TAKEZO] You two could
join if you'd like.
No thank you.
I'm okay.
Man, this is kinda embarrassing.
But fun!
[ALL chuckle]
[CHIKA]
Whoa, this warmth.
I can feel it from
the other guys.
It kinda calms me down.
You gonna say something, specs?
Oh, yeah sure. Of course!
I, um... I want to
keep playing with you.
I'd like to keep us together.
I don't want this to be the end.
So let's do our--
What's that for?
Stop spoutin' all that
depressing stuff!
Tell us something
to get us fired up!
If you're gonna do this,
say something you usually
couldn't and commit!
Top of your lungs!
[inhales]
We're going to nationals!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Oh. Finally, Hakuto's up next.
That's the school who
won last time, isn't it?
Yup.
[ISAKI]
If they give the "right answer"
in their performance again,
Tokise can't win.
[ISAKI] But, if it's
different from last time...
[YAMAMOTO]
Okay, give it your all, guys!
You don't have to
tell us. We will!
You know, your songs might
come off a little plain,
but we're gonna go out there and
prove they're more than that.
We'll show how amazing they are!
We're gonna get that
ticket to nationals.
It'll be a farewell present.
[YAMAMOTO]
Hm! Heh!
[CHIKA]
Mm?
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER A]
Program number 12.
Hakuto High School. "Katakago."
[MIO]
I've always hated my own sound.
It's the right answer,
but something's missing.
It's not wrong,
but it's kind of boring.
I've been searching for this
missing something but...
[MIO]
Thank you.
Thanks to all of you, I can
finally reach the other side.
♪
[gasps]
[TSUKAJI gasps]
What a deep first sound.
[koto continues]
[TSUKAJI]
A classical piece?
No, I think it was
listed as an original.
What a tranquil
space it's creating.
It's like if I exhale,
people might hear it.
[koto continues]
[TSUKAJI]
Frankly, it's very plain.
It doesn't have
the lively feeling
of high school students, but...
[CHIKA] Yet again. It's not
like it's got momentum,
nor does it have
a catchy melody,
but his sound just
flows into my head.
I can't take my eyes off him.
♪
[TAKEZO] A performance that
feels like the "right answer"
to the piece.
[TSUKAJI gasps]
This is quite incredible.
Doesn't feel like a performance
by high school students.
But that's largely thanks
to the piece itself.
♪
[TAKINAMI] Between the solo
and the three other parts,
how the sounds are placed and
intertwined is impeccable.
Though, it seems like
the guy in the center
is significantly more skilled
than the rest of them.
The piece was
carefully calculated
so that it's well-balanced,
but at the same time
makes the solo stand out.
[SATOWA] The tempo that
makes you feel comfortable.
The pauses that draw you in.
To think someone could
compose such a piece.
[TAKINAMI]
Frightening.
[TSUKAJI] I have to admit,
their skill level is high.
It's not just the piece.
It's amazing in its own right
that they can express it.
But, after hearing that
performance from Himesaka,
something is missing.
I quit. No more koto.
What do you mean you quit?
I thought you said you liked
the way the koto sounded!
[MIO] I do like it,
but when I play,
it becomes a sound I don't like.
When I'm the one playing,
the sound is all wrong. It dies.
It dies? Hm...
Hey. Listen to me, 'kay Mio?
I don't really understand what
you mean, but no one can play
exactly how they want to
when they're just starting out!
It's not just you!
[MIO grunts]
Wait, really?
[UTA]
Yeah, I think.
Then when will I be able
to play the sounds I like?
[UTA] That probably depends on
how much effort you put in.
Effort? Then should
I just play a ton?
If I play all day long, will it
become a sound I like?
A sound that's free, open,
independent from everything.
Like water, and wind.
A sound with life.
If I was able to produce
a sound like that,
it'd make me so happy.
[MIO] But, after a year,
then three, and even five.
I was never able to
play a sound like that.
[WOMAN A] Mio, you're thinking
about it too much.
[WOMAN B] You're very talented.
Have confidence.
[WOMAN A] Do you want to
play in a competition?
[MIO]
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
You know, Mio, everyone seems
to praise your sound.
They say you're
really good, so--
I don't care about "everyone."
All I want is to be able to
produce a sound
that I like, myself!
Mio...
[MIO]
I feel kind of upset.
I don't... I don't
know what to do.
I can always see the sounds,
but they never lead me
to the place I want to go.
[MIO]
I'm tired... So tired.
[YAMAMOTO]
Okay.
I'll make a piece that'll allow
you to go "beyond that."
Because I want to hear your
"sound beyond the
right answer," too!
[MIO]
That was a shock.
Like a dazzling light...
reaching out.
♪
[CHIKA, TAKEZO gasp]
[TSUKAJI]
The sound changed?
[MIO]
You made this with calculations?
Yeah.
Well. I don't like
calculated sounds.
Then I'll make it sound
uncalculated by calculating.
♪
What do you think?
How's this piece?
I guess it seems fine.
I'll redo it.
I promised you I'd make a
piece that will let you go
"beyond the right answer".
If it isn't something
you want to play,
then it's not going
to accomplish that.
♪
You can only play sound
the way you see it?
Yeah. I don't know how to
play the sounds I hear
when other people perform.
The sound I can see glows
and becomes a path.
But the area around it is
pitch-black and empty.
It feels like if I
go off the path,
I'll fall into the darkness.
[YAMAMOTO] Hm. The way I see it,
the moment you go off the path,
a new one will be
created in its place.
Right? And then you yourself
would become the path!
♪
[CHIKA gasps]
What's this unnerving feeling?
[TSUKAJI]
Hey, hey, hey!
Am I crazy or has this solo
just been him repeating
the same sound over
and over again?
Just how deep is he
going to dive with it?
[MIO] I don't understand what
Mr. Yamamoto was trying to say.
They're disorganized and messy.
If I step off the path,
I bet I'll be just like them.
[gasps]
[MIO]
Huh? What's with this sound?
Their feelings are
flowing into me,
even though I don't know the
first thing about these people.
They're all smiling.
They're happy and alive.
It's as if they themselves
are the sound!
And then you yourself
would become the path.
[gasps]
[koto plays]
[CHIKA] Clearly... something's
happening... up there.
[ALL gasp]
[UTA]
Mio...
[koto playing]
[MIO laughs]
[laughing continues]
[ARAGAKI]
Hey! What's going on?
[gasps]
[TSUKAJI]
I'm getting dragged into it!
Oh wow. Amazing. Incredible!
Within only 13 strings,
they're creating a
boundless universe.
Hang on, Mio!
This piece isn't just yours,
we're all playing it!
Don't forget that
we're here too!
Sorry, President.
I'm just having fun.
But I'll take you guys
with me, anywhere.
There are only 13 strings.
But with them, I can now
go wherever I want.
To the ends of the earth!
♪
Mr. Yamamoto. He's gonna quit
teaching after the qualifier.
I heard that his dad
collapsed the other day.
Let's make sure our
last performance for him
is a good one.
[gasps]
Hey, Kanzaki. Do you know what
kind of flower a katakago is?
No, I don't.
[YAMAMOTO] It's a flower
that can't bloom right away.
It takes more than
one year, three years,
even five years after budding.
But it keeps trying.
It grows little by little,
season after season,
and finally blooms after
almost ten years of hard work.
[YAMAMOTO]
Hey, Kanzaki.
It's been about ten years
since we came to know
the koto, hasn't it?
[SATOWA] It was like something
awakened in him at the end.
[CHIKA chuckles]
[CHIKA] So you can play the
koto like this too, huh?
[SANE] Aww man,
I'm getting nervous again
after hearing Hakuto
play so well.
[HIRO] Seriously! Why do we
have to go right after them?
[KOTA]
Rhythm. Rhythm!
Focus on staying in sync
with everyone else.
[MITTSU groans] I hope I
don't get stupid fingers!
[SATOWA] Everyone is so anxious.
I have to say something.
[SATOWA gasps]
We're gonna be fine.
We have absolutely
nothing to worry about.
We just gotta play
like we always do.
If you say so.
[TAKEZO]
Because we've practiced...
...more than any of
the other clubs here!
Heh! If our president
says so, it must be true!
I appreciate the confidence.
You guys are gonna
do a good job.
You managed to survive my
tough lessons, after all.
So get up on that
stage and play.
Play your hearts out.
Okay, Miss Aki.
Tokise, please proceed
to the stage.
Okay!
Some final words of advice.
What's important isn't going
to nationals itself,
but why you guys want
to make it there.
Don't forget that.
[BOTH gasp]
[CHIKA]
Why we...
[TAKEZO]
...want to go?
[TAKINAMI] If you lose
in the next qualifier,
then Kurusu and Kurata won't
ever make it to nationals.
To them... this is
their last opportunity.
[SATOWA]
I don't want it to end yet.
[HIRO]
I wish it could go on forever.
[CHIKA] But next year
won't work for you guys!
Next year, it'll be too late.
[TAKEZO]
We're going to nationals!
Next time: "Tenkyu."