Good morning!
I don't have time for
you to be so secretive!
You won't improve
if I just give you
the answer, though!
Um, what's going on?
What are you two arguing about?
[CHIKA]
Get this, specs.
So, my part has a section
where I have to use
my fingers to pluck, right?
But no matter how hard I try to
play it, it always sounds dull.
Hey.
How can I get a clear
sound using my fingers?
[SATOWA]
With practice, obviously.
What kind of crap advice
is that supposed to be?
One that answers
your absurd question!
Well, it sucks!
You suck.
Oh. I see.
Well, then, if it helps,
I think I might
have an answer for you.
It probably sounds dull because
your fingers are still soft.
What do you mean "soft"?
You're still new to this,
but as you practice more,
your fingers will grow
calluses and become harder.
Little by little, you'll
develop your "playing fingers."
And you'll be able
to make clearer sounds.
I'm pretty sure that's
what Hozuki meant
when she said to "practice."
That makes sense.
Was that so hard?
You should have
explained it better!
[TAKEZO]
Since she's naturally gifted,
Hozuki may not know
how to explain this stuff.
It's intuitive to her.
Right. That means
I need to step up,
so she doesn't have to
bear all the responsibility.
Hey, Four‐Eyes!
[TAKEZO]
Huh? Uh...
What's wrong?
[CHIKA] They both
have such hard fingers.
And mine are soft like a baby's!
[TETSUKI] Is that why
you're tightening the strings?
[CHIKA]
Yeah.
If I don't make them as close
as I can to the real thing,
my fingers won't toughen up.
We're not allowed to
borrow the kotos from here,
and I can't buy one.
Ah. Can ya borrow
someone else's?
It's not that simple.
Who would have an extra
koto just laying around?
Uh. Huh?
[TETSUKI]
Hmm?
[CHIKA]
And that's it.
So would it be okay if the
four of us practiced here?
You think
I'm running a daycare
for noisy teenage hoodlums?
If I decide to let you
use the instruments,
what am I gonna get in return?
Well, I don't have much money.
[smacking]
You can take that coupon
and stick it!
[CHIKA]
Then...
In one month,
we'll let you hear a really
amazing performance.
It'll be a nice memory
before you die.
[smacking]
How rude.
Now I get it.
You're the grandson
Gen mentioned.
Hold on, you knew my grandpa?
Course I did; it's not
like this is a large industry.
So... your grandson's
living with you?
I heard he's a real brat.
Must be tough to deal with.
[GEN]
Meh, it's all right.
Shizu! Listen to this!
You know my grandson?
He actually played my koto!
I only explained a little,
but he picked it up really fast!
That boy's got some
raw talent in him!
Hahahaha!
[CHIKA]
In one month,
we'll let you hear a
really amazing performance.
[SHIZU]
Gen.
I wish you were here.
Those words would
have made you so proud.
I'm going to hold you to
your word, you understand?
Okay.
It's almost eight,
so let's start tidying...
[KOTA, SANE, CHIKA, MITTSU]
See ya!
[CHIKA]
Damn.
The sound is still
coming off pretty dull.
I didn't expect plucking with
my fingers to hurt so much.
[CHIKA]
Those guys.
I wonder how long it took them?
How much work before
their fingers got hard?
♪ ♪
Yay!
[TAKEZO]
That was amazing!
You're each able to play
your individual sections
with hardly any mistakes now!
Hey, Hozuki, why don't we all
try playing the song together?
Yes, good idea.
Y'know, I don't think
I've even seen you
practice on that koto.
Can you really play your part?
Don't worry about me,
just focus on your own playing.
[TAKEZO]
Okay.
Let's start!
[TAKEZO]
Three, and...
♪ ♪
[TAKEZO]
The beginning's good.
On the fourth bar,
Hozuki's 17‐string comes in.
[SATOWA]
Huh?
What's going on?
Why did you all stop playing?
[TAKEZO]
I'm sorry!
Your performance
was just so moving.
Incredible!
She only played for a second,
but every note
was perfectly honed,
and it had a rich tone that
only comes with experience.
[CHIKA]
Shit.
How do I make a sound like that?
Come on, let's try it
again from the top.
[TAKEZO]
Right.
Then.
Three and play.
♪ ♪
[TAKEZO]
Off to a good start.
Now here's Hozuki's 17‐string.
[TAKEZO]
We split up into parts!
♪ ♪
[TAKEZO]
And we're not together at all.
The hell?
Why are you idiots making
such horrible noises?
But I'm playing it just
like I'm supposed to!
Yeah, same here!
Nothing's wrong
with the playing,
but everyone's timing is off.
Make sure you listen
to the other sounds.
[KOTA]
Um...
[SATOWA]
Hmm?
Listen to what other sounds?
I don't get it.
You don't?
If we start at the same time,
won't we be in sync?
[SATOWA] They don't know how
to listen to the other sounds?
Or does he mean they don't
understand how to stay together?
That's an intuitive ability
that I can't teach.
No, I don't want to hear
you say that you can't do it!
When you're older, it's going
to be your responsibility
to take over and run
the Hozuki School.
I will not tolerate words like
"I can't" or "I don't know."
[SATOWA]
You guys are one beat too fast.
Now you're too slow!
Please, go on without me.
Aw, man, my legs!
I'm more confused
than when we started.
I think I'll go puke now.
[SATOWA]
Why?
We're even less together
now than we were before.
Right.
Once more, from the top.
[TAKEZO]
We can't, it's closing time.
We have to clean up.
[CHIKA]
I just don't understand it.
Why is playing in sync so hard?
Here's a fun fact,
did you know that I'm the one
who started Tokise
High School's koto club?
Why would I care
about all that crap?
I'd rather play by myself.
As usual, you don't get it.
It's just different, y'know?
The sound you make when you play
with other people you've
spent a lot of time with.
Well, that's not something
you can produce by yourself.
It's nice.
[TAKEZO]
I feel bad for Hozuki.
She probably doesn't
know what to do.
[TAKEZO] What was it
like when I first started?
[MASHIRO] After this,
we should all hang out!
[TAKEZO]
Huh?
Uh. Hey, guys?
When we're done cleaning up,
do you wanna go
get something to eat?
Um. Together?
Yeah, that sounds fun.
I'm so there;
what should we eat?
[SATOWA]
Sorry, but I'll have to pass.
You should join us
every once in a while.
Come on, everybody.
Uh. Hey!
Let go of me!
[KOTA, SANE, MITTSU]
Aw yeah, time for food!
So, is this your
first time eating monja?
What do you mean?
Of course, it's not!
[TAKEZO]
Which is code for "it is."
[SERVER]
Here you go!
Cheesy mochi and
stamina monja for strength!
[KOTA, MITTSU, SANE]
All right!
Oh cool, are you gonna
cook it for us, Hozuki?
Nice!
For real!
Thanks so much!
Uh, hey.
It's okay if you
don't feel like cooking.
Yeah, we don't mind doing it.
Look, if you can't do it,
then you should just say so.
And if you don't know something,
then you should tell us, okay?
No one's gonna get mad at you.
[TAKEZO]
Right, and what's more.
That also applies to the club.
You've got talent.
That's great, and it helps.
But that doesn't mean
you have to be perfect.
And yeah, I don't always
know what to do either.
But if there's a
problem you can't solve,
then we'll work it out together.
Hey, looks like the monja
is about ready to eat.
Oh, I thought it might
take longer to cook.
[KOTA]
You eat it like this.
It's delicious.
Of course it is!
I'm the one who
cooked it, after all.
[SATOWA]
Look, the truth is...
I'm struggling because I don't
know how to teach you properly.
Learning how to play together
isn't something I can explain.
I've always been
naturally gifted.
Playing the koto
is just easy for me.
You know, you really
should have quit talking
while you were ahead!
Okay now.
Take a deep breath.
We can figure it out.
As a team.
Well, let's think about it.
So, I play the guitar in a band,
but we also have a drummer
so gauging the
tempo's pretty easy.
Maybe that's the answer.
Instead of matching everyone,
we match someone.
[KOTA]
Yeah, that makes sense.
Well, you guys should
try syncing to me!
[SANE]
Why you?
[MITTSU] If we're clapping,
I could probably do it.
[TAKEZO]
Oh, then to start,
why don't we practice
clapping to the same rhythm?
[SERVER]
Sounds like you're having fun!
Here, this one's on the house.
[MITTSU]
Meal's not done yet!
[KOTA, SANE]
Yay, free food!
[SATOWA]
One, two, three, four.
Fourth and fifth koto rest.
All together now.
[SATOWA]
Okay.
Let's take a little break.
Aw, man!
It's so fast that
I can't keep up!
But you know what.
Hozuki clapping out the cues
is making a huge difference.
We're staying together!
[CHIKA]
True.
But we shouldn't get in
the habit of relying on it.
Let's try playing
without the clapping.
Wait.
So, have you already
memorized when to come in?
Uh, yeah. Kind of.
[MITTSU] I actually think
I've figured it out, too.
I'm probably ready
to give it a whirl.
Mizuhara.
You don't have
to rush yourself, okay?
I'll try to play,
so that it's easier for
the other parts to come in.
[KOTA]
Yeah. Okay.
Hey. You'll be fine.
[KOTA]
Mm‐hmm.
[TAKEZO]
Everyone, ready?
Let's start.
Three and...
[ALL]
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three!
[ALL]
Now!
Whoa, we did it!
[SANE, MITTSU]
Yeah!
[CHIKA]
What the hell?
We were finally together,
and you just stopped.
[CHIKA]
Still though.
I gotta admit it sounded good.
[KOTA]
Praise me, Chika!
[TAKEZO] Shouldn't
we get back to practicing?
[SANE]
I can't believe we did it!
[excited chatter]
Let's just try and do
the next part, already.
[ALL 3]
Okay.
[SHIZU] Your practice
group seems larger.
Oh, uh, you noticed?
[SHIZU]
My goodness.
Well, do as you please,
I guess I don't mind
a little more noise.
[TAKEZO]
I didn't know
that they were putting in
extra practice hours here.
The club president should
know these kinds of things.
[SHIZU]
Hmm?
Granny.
He's trying to thank you.
He really is grateful.
[SATOWA]
Stop.
We're off again.
[SANE]
We've got the beginning down,
but we can't nail the rest.
[CHIKA]
Crap.
[TAKEZO]
This isn't good.
The atmosphere is
becoming tense again.
Hey, Hozuki?
Why don't we take
a little break?
Sakai, you can rest your legs.
Thanks so much,
President Four‐Eyes!
[KOTA]
I'm so sorry!
Hey, don't apologize.
Everyone in this room is putting
in hard work, and it shows.
I mean, you guys
are already playing
at a way higher level than
back when I first started.
So, don't worry.
I know we can do this!
As long as we keep
practicing consistently,
we'll be ready for the show!
Oh, that.
I guess it sounds
kinda arrogant.
I'm sorry!
I‐It's not what I meant.
It's fine.
Thank you for saying that.
Okay! Let's try again.
From the top!
But my legs still hurt.
[KOTA] What if we let Mittsu
use a koto stand instead?
[TAKEZO]
It's funny.
But this sort of takes me back.
[SANE] Okay, starting here
it gets gradually more intense.
But then after that it
gets softer, doesn't it?
[TAKEZO] I think the variation
will increase the impact.
[SATOWA]
But adding varying intensities
isn't going to be enough.
We'll have to
work out the motif,
and from there,
play it repeatedly.
Only then will we be
able to reach people.
I'm not sure what you mean.
[SATOWA] A motif is
a piece's image or theme.
You have to consider what
the piece is trying to convey,
and then you try to find a way
to put your own
feelings into it.
We have to put
our feelings into it?
We'll start by trying to
understand the piece as a whole.
"Ryuu."
[GEN]
But did you know
that the koto is actually made
to resemble a powerful dragon?
[CHIKA]
Hey, the koto is supposed
to resemble a dragon, right?
Yes, it's awesome
that you know that, Kudo.
What's that got to do with it?
I'm not sure yet.
Is there a reason why
the title replaces "ryuu"
in "meteor shower"
with the kanji for "dragon"?
Why are kotos
associated with dragons?
Well, it's a
little hard to explain,
but this is my take on it.
[SATOWA] Dragons are said
to connect heaven and earth.
The world of the living
and the dead.
They serve to join together
two unconnected things.
So, kotos, which are created to
resemble those same dragons,
are there in order to connect
the hearts of the
players and the audience.
So... I believe it's
meant to fulfill that wish.
Oh, I get it now,
that's what the dragon
kanji stands for in the title!
Yeah!
This song just wants us
to reach everyone!
It's like a dragon meteor shower
that connects hearts!
[KOTA]
Yeah, you're right!
[MITTSU] We use the sound
of a dragon to reach them all!
Through this song, the audience
will finally get the chance
to understand us poor
"delinquent" fellas!
The vice principal may be doing
his best to take us down,
but in the end,
we'll become dragon meteors
and connect with everyone!
It's like this piece was
picked specially for us!
[SANE]
Right, Hozuki?
Perhaps you're right.
Whoa! She's smiling?
[KOTA]
Hold on, are you feeling okay?
[SATOWA] I am capable
of smiling, you know!
[SANE] Yeah, but it wasn't
super evil like it normally is!
[SATOWA]
You guys are idiots.
Kotos are there in order
to connect the hearts of
the players and the audience.
I believe they're meant
to fulfill that wish.
Oh hey, Kudo.
If you're gonna practice,
do you mind if I join you?
♪ ♪
Huh? Is someone already playing?
This is the first koto
part of "Ryuuseigun."
It's rough, but I
definitely hear the core.
I've never heard
this tone before.
It's incredibly gentle and warm.
But the first koto is!
No, it can't be!
There's no way he
can produce this sound!
[TAKEZO]
What is this tone?
Its core is strong yet
still gentle somehow.
I can't believe
it's Kudo playing.
It's entrancing.
Ah. Dammit! I messed up.
[TAKEZO]
Um, Kudo?
How'd you make that sound?
Uh, with my fingers, idiot.
[TAKEZO]
Hmm?
So, he's not aware of the
sound he just made?
I believe you've played
the koto before, correct?
Will you tell me who taught you?
[CHIKA]
My grandpa.
[TAKEZO] We practiced again
afterwards, but in the end,
he only made that
sound the one time.
Was it a fluke?
I really wish we had
a proper teacher.
I'm not any help.
Hey, Kurata!
The teacher wants you to stop
by the staffroom before you go.
[TAKEZO]
Huh? Okay, got it.
I've been worried about
you lately. Are you okay?
[TAKEZO]
Yeah, why?
[STUDENT C] I heard a rumor
that the first‐year delinquents
had taken over your club and are
bossing you around or whatever.
[TAKEZO]
I see.
From the outside in,
it looks like I'm being bullied.
Everyone is trying their
hardest, but we don't even know
if anyone in the school
will listen to us perform.
What if we can't manage
to reach anyone?
Excuse me!
What the hell?
If it isn't the koto wuss.
Wanna know somethin' funny?
Rumor has it, you're the
new errand boy for Kudo,
and his little
band of delinquents.
[TAKEZO]
That's not true.
Kudo and his friends are
members of the koto club.
[laughter]
Are you so naïve
that you don't even realize
you're being used
by those punks?
[TAKEZO]
Look!
Those guys are really
serious about the koto!
[STUDENT A]
Haha okay.
You're being pushed
around by first‐years,
you're just too
embarrassed to admit it.
[CHIKA]
There you are, Takezo, sir.
Aren't you coming
to the clubroom?
We'll be starting soon.
Oh. Kudo.
Hey. What do you guys want?
You got business
with our club president?
No, we don't!
Then get outta here
already, shoo, shoo.
Jeez. Couple of losers.
Are you headed to the club?
I am; I just have to stop
at the staff room really quick.
I gotcha.
Well, I'll see you there.
Um. Kudo, wait!
Thank you so much!
[CHIKA]
For what?
[TAKEZO] If I have
time to think about
whether or not we
can reach them,
then there's time to figure
out how we will reach them.
We can do it.
And we will
protect the koto club!
[KOTA]
Hi, Hozuki!
[SATOWA]
This is unusual.
You're the first one here.
I know.
But I kinda feel like I'm
holding everyone back,
so I thought I'd get here
early and practice.
It seems like you're
trying really hard, but why?
[KOTA]
Because Chika is trying so hard.
The three of us decided
to put in our best effort
for Chika's sake.
[SATOWA]
It's odd.
I never gave much thought
to why he's playing
the koto, but now...
Is he playing the koto because
of his grandfather's influence?
[KOTA] Oh wow, I didn't
realize you knew about all that.
Oh, well, I don't.
I think we were all surprised
when Chika began
playing the koto.
I thought the incident
with his grandfather
and the instruments would have
been too traumatic, y'know?
What do you mean by that?
[KOTA]
I mean...
[SATOWA]
Huh?
[CHIKA]
Next time:
"Let Our Sound Resound
and Reach Them."