[SANE] I was wondering
why you told me to come here
at five in the morning.
So you've been starting your
practice this early every day?
That's why you're
always here first.
Must be tough, you're not
exactly a morning guy.
[CHIKA] I'm ready to collapse
any second, to be honest.
But man, Hozuki and Miss Dojima
played amazing together.
Yeah. All this time,
I've been telling myself I gotta
be able to play like Hozuki
by nationals, but I might have
been approaching it wrong.
How so?
We shouldn't just
play like she does.
We should find our own way,
so we can stand alongside her.
[SANE gasps] "Our own way"?
What do you mean?
[CHIKA] Well, Takinami told
us we should think about
the meaning and the
role of our sound, right?
And. I still don't know exactly
what he means by that.
But I do get the
feeling it goes beyond
just playing each
note with skill.
[SANE]
I didn't even think of that.
I just thought I had
to practice more.
Seriously, Chika.
Sometimes I feel like you're
leaving me in the dust.
[SANE]
But... "we," huh?
[SANE] Okay! Let's make sure
our 17-string performance
is good enough to
match Hozuki's!
Yeah! For starters...
[SANE] Hey, Chika. I wanna
make sure I get good enough
to stand alongside
you too, you know.
...your math's a little off.
Just keep it up.
The second koto section
is really coming together.
Isn't it? Kota's been
practicing really hard!
Speaking of, you and Mittsu
seem to be doing well
with your section.
He's playing the piece so
delicately and beautifully.
I know! But still...
How we play first koto
is honestly pretty plain.
[MITTSU]
What?
[TAKEZO]
It's kinda serious.
[HIRO laughs]
[TAKEZO]
Don't laugh!
The expression of the piece
comes from how you play the
first and second kotos together,
so I'm concerned, that's all!
Really, this has been
bothering me for a while.
I'm "serious and boring."
[HIRO] What?
It's not boring! It's cool!
Huh?
Being serious! It's cool!
So why not own that and
make good use out of it?
You guys on first koto
can play all serious.
And we'll liven things
up on the second!
Plus...
[sighs]
Hey, Kurata!
Are you even listening?
Heard every word! Sorry!
[SANE] Hey! It's Miss Dojima!
You're early.
Adachi.
You doing okay today?
[AKIRA]
Uh...
Well, if you get dust in your
eyes again or something,
tell us before it gets too bad.
[gasps]
[AKIRA]
I think I'll be okay.
I'm glad to hear that.
--[AKIRA] Uh...
--[door clatters]
[SANE]
Woah, I'm first here?
Then I get Miss Dojima
all to myself!
Can you train me one-on-one
until the others show?
♪
You've been working yourself
very hard, Adachi.
[SANE]
You think so?
Maybe, but Chika works
a lot harder than I do.
[AKIRA gasps]
[SANE] He's a better player
and has a better ear than me,
but that's 'cause he
practices a lot more.
Mr. Takinami told us
we should look for our
sound's meaning and role.
And I think Chika's got reason
to take that advice seriously.
[SANE] But it's probably
not worth thinking about
with my skillset.
Ah, nevermind! Can't hold
'em back! Gotta work hard!
You complement the others.
Your sound harmonizes very well.
What?
Your teacher told me
his thought process.
Why he picked you for
the 17-string part.
[TAKINAMI] I'm sure you've
noticed that each of our
club members have
different quality sounds.
So if something goes wrong,
their performance can
easily turn messy.
But, Adachi's sound harmonizes
well with each of those
different styles. It connects
everyone's sounds nicely.
[AKIRA] So. He assigned
the core of the piece,
the 17-string, to you.
His words, but I
agree with them.
[SANE] It connects...
everyone's sounds.
Thank you very much.
I'll work hard!
[CHIKA] Sane. I've noticed that
you've changed how you play.
What? You think so?
I can't say that I've
seen a difference myself.
I did figure out my
sound's meaning and role.
Maybe, that's it. Y'know?
[CHIKA stammers] What? You did?
What is it? Spill it!
Uh. Secret.
[SANE] It's embarrassing
to say it myself!
That reminds me.
Have you adjusted how
you're playing, too?
[SATOWA]
Yes.
My index finger has always
been weaker than the rest,
and while I do think that it's
getting a lot better lately,
after hearing the
way that you perform,
I realized I have
a long way to go.
so I've been struggling to give
each note the same weight.
[AKIRA] Hm. If you'd like,
you could use this.
Try playing while wearing it.
I often practice that way.
Your attention goes to your
ears and your senses
become finely honed.
Which makes it easier to
converse with your own sound.
And you don't have to worry
about returning that.
So feel free to try it
when you practice alone.
Thank you so much.
Of course.
[CHIKA] I have to hurry up
and move forward, too.
[CHIKA] Soon. So I can
stand alongside her.
I have to. Fast.
Ah, crap. I'm feelin'
kinda spacey.
Oh. Good morning!
Guess I was finally able
to get here before you.
Oh, hey specs.
[TAKEZO] You've been practicing
this early every day, huh?
[CHIKA grunts]
What of it?
I'm a morning person,
so I naturally wake up
and need omething' to do.
[TAKEZO] You know,
I might have believed that
if you didn't look
so obviously tired.
Hey, Kudo. Don't push
yourself so much, okay?
Huh? What does that mean?
I'm not pushing myself at all.
In fact, I should
practicing more.
We've only got one month
until the competition.
[TAKEZO] His fingers!
How much has he been working?
You need to take a break!
[CHIKA] I just said I
gotta practice more!
As we are now, we can't
make it to nationals.
So I can't slow down.
I understand how
you feel, trust me.
But you're still just
a first-year student!
You don't have to be
in such a rush!
You'll still have a chance
next year to make it--!
But next year won't
work for you guys!
[CHIKA] Next year,
it'll be too late.
[gasps]
Now back up a little,
will yah? I can't pra--
You're not allowed to practice!
What?
Doing it too much is
counterproductive!
Oh shut up! How am I supposed
to get better without playing!
[TAKEZO] I'm just saying,
be a little more mindful!
[CHIKA]
I don't need your advice!
--[TAKEZO] Hey! I said no!
--[CHIKA] Get off of me!
[BOTH panting]
Dammit! What are we even doing?
We wasted all that time
I coulda been working!
It was a good diversion,
don't you think?
You know what?
There's something I've been
wondering about lately.
And it has to do
with your sound.
What is it?
Well, to put it bluntly,
it sometimes shines.
Uh. Like a light?
[TAKEZO] Yeah. Sometimes.
Very gently. And warmly.
But it shines.
I've been curious why your sound
feels that way for a while now.
But I think I finally
know what it is.
[TAKEZO]
When it comes down to it,
that sound is your soul itself.
[gasps]
[GEN]
The song is their soul.
[TAKEZO gasps] Shoot! I just
spoke my mind without thinking!
[CHIKA]
What's up with you, man?
You must've hit your
head or something.
Yeah, I shouldn't
have said that.
[GEN] Listen up, Chika.
Sound is special.
It touches people's souls.
[GEN] And pieces of music
are basically the souls
of their composers
in physical form.
[CHIKA] I don't know what
this piece means to you,
but maybe we could
face it together.
[SATOWA] Well, um. Honestly,
when I played this piece,
I was hoping the people
who listened to it
would want to smile.
[TAKINAMI] Look at the
piece in its entirety.
Understand its flow.
[gasps]
[DOJIMA]
Akira. We have guests.
Do me a favor and go
prepare some tea for them.
Why do we have--?
[gasps]
[AKIRA] Mr. Takagi. The others
are all senior members
of the Hozuki School, too.
[DOJIMA] Don't miss your
chance to say hello
before they're gone.
Oh, and make enough tea
for the grand master.
[AKIRA]
Grandmother.
Excuse me, but is it okay if I
sit in on the meeting?
[DOJIMA] Hm! Certainly.
Come with me.
[DOJIMA] I don't like
the look in her eyes.
Not that she could do
anything to mess this up.
It'll be fine. She can just
sit there and watch quietly.
And since she's been taking
her time shutting down
that club, I'll be the one
to end it for good.
Let's begin.
What's this meeting about?
[DOJIMA] I have gathered
you all here today
in order to discuss the
grand master's daughter.
As you're aware,
she was excommunicated
after causing trouble for
the school in the past.
But what you don't know is she
is about to put the school
in jeopardy yet again.
And how is she going to do that?
Satowa now belongs to a
koto club at the high school
she's attending.
But I assure you, it is a
koto club in name only.
In reality, the members
are nothing but
a group of delinquents.
[AKIRA gasps]
[TAKAGI'S SON laughs]
Oh, you'll have to forgive me.
I was expecting something worse.
[AKIRA]
That's Mr. Takagi's son.
I was curious why
you called us.
But I didn't think
we'd be discussing
this girl's club activities.
This isn't exactly
something that we adults
have to meet and talk about.
Even if one of the delinquents
she's spending her time with
has gotten in trouble
with the police?
[ALL gasp]
[TETSUKI]
What? Chika?
You're not practicing
through lunch?
Specs is forcing me
to lay off playing
until my fingertips heal up.
Huh? Oh, I see you practiced
so much you hurt yourself?
Use your head
a little, ya idiot.
[CHIKA]
Shut up.
[FEMALE STUDENT A] You're gonna
go practice now, Satowa?
[SATOWA]
Yeah. I'll see you later, 'kay?
[SATOWA gasps]
Oh, Kudo.
Got a minute? I wanna talk.
[MIYOSHI yelps]
What does that mean?
[DOJIMA]
I was worried about Satowa,
so I investigated the club.
And I found out that one of
its members named Kudo
is something of a
famous criminal.
He's had several run-ins with
the police in recent years
because of his
violent tendencies.
He's dangerous?
[DOJIMA]
His grandfather builds kotos,
which explains his connection
to the instrument.
But last year, he had another
outrageous episode.
He and his delinquent friends
attacked his
grandfather's property.
He has no respect for
authority or the koto.
What do you mean
they "attacked?"
This guy sounds more
like an actual criminal
than a delinquent.
[AKIRA gasps]
[AKIRA]
Kudo did that?
I really wanna know what
kind of piece "Tenkyu" is.
"What kind of piece?"
Exactly.
I wanna know what was going
on in your life at the time,
what you were thinking about,
and who you created
the piece for.
My grandpa once said
pieces of music are
"the souls of their composers
in physical form."
[CHIKA] So, I don't
wanna play it without
knowing those things anymore.
I have been so far,
and looking back,
it feels like
something's missing.
It would only be a story about
my family and its issues.
Do you really think that
will help your performance
the slightest bit?
It would help like crazy!
[gasps]
[SATOWA]
Okay.
So your point is that Satowa
is hanging out with
this dangerous boy?
That's right. I believe
she's harbored ill will
towards the school since
her excommunication.
So she and the boy sharing the
same club had me thinking.
There's a possibility that
they're plotting some sort of
sanctimonious revenge
against the school.
[CHIHARU gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[CHIKA]
Play it one more time.
Don't worry, we're not
neglecting anything.
[SATOWA] And so, I used the
performance to throw a tantrum.
[SATOWA] I think it'd be fun
to play the koto. Together.
Satowa's behavior at
her final competition
under our roof irreparably
damaged the Hozuki name.
We all must all do everything
possible to prevent any
further damage to the
school's reputation.
We must ask that they
disband the club,
and have Satowa transfer
to another high school!
[AKIRA]
How stupid.
What?
I'm sorry, did you not
hear me? I'll speak up.
This is stupid.
My word, Akira.
What are you on about?
[AKIRA]
I was holding my tongue.
But "revenge"?
That's ridiculous.
How do you feel justified
saying things like that
when you don't know
anything about Kudo?
If anyone's plotting something,
it's you, Grandmother!
You're snooping into
high school students' lives.
And now you're just making
things up about them!
You're the only one
who's outrageous!
So then,
I take it you're familiar with
this student named Kudo?
[AKIRA] Yes. I've been giving
lessons to that koto club.
The idea they're plotting
"revenge" is absolute nonsense.
Oh, good. In that case--
[DOJIMA]
Akira! Poor thing,
you must be feeling under
the weather or something!
You clearly don't know
what you're saying.
Why don't you go
lie down for a while?
No thanks. I know exactly
what I'm saying.
But what about you?
Maybe you should take a
second look at yourself.
[DOJIMA gasps]
If I'm being honest,
because of preconceptions I had,
I assumed the students of
this club were not serious
about the koto myself.
But I was mistaken.
Kudo and Satowa, and of course
the other members too,
face the koto with
such sincerity.
They just love the instrument
and want to become better at it.
Grandmother!
You've always been the one who
can't face the koto head-on.
[gasps]
You just think of the
school's and your reputation.
You drag other people down
to look better by comparison.
Why don't you stop all that and
face the koto for a change?
[DOJIMA gasps] How can you
say that? Such disrespect!
Who do you think
you're talking to?
[TAKAGI] Ms. Dojima.
I believe that's enough.
You've put your granddaughter
in a very awkward position here.
[DOJIMA]
Mr. Takagi.
Now then, Akira.
I'd like to hear your thoughts,
having taught him.
Is the student Kudo really
someone who's going to be
harmful to Satowa or the school?
I don't know him well, or how
he may have acted in the past.
But now, his attitude
towards the koto
is deeply earnest and sincere.
[TAKAGI]
Hm. So that's how it is.
Well, how do you all feel?
In my opinion, we don't need to
be concerned as of right now.
Please, hold on a second!
Even if he's not
causing problems now,
people don't change
so quickly!
He's sure to cause trouble--
[CHIHARU]
Stop it.
No further discussion of
this subject is needed.
Ms. Dojima, please show
them out so we don't waste
more of their time.
You agree with them?
Furthermore.
I won't allow you to investigate
my daughter and her friends,
and spout ridiculous
accusations at your leisure.
It's deplorable!
It's true that I have
excommunicated her,
but she is still my daughter.
[ALL gasp]
[AKIRA]
Grand Master.
[CHIHARU] For that club, she was
willing to get down on her
hands and knees to
ask a favor of me.
For her friends.
It was worth it?
Yes, I believe so.
[CHIHARU]
Then, that's good.
[AKIRA]
The qualifier for nationals
will be held next month.
Satowa's competing.
Grand Master, why don't
you come see it?
[CHIHARU]
I'm sorry, but...
...I no longer have
the right to do that.
[gasps]
[AKIRA]
Mr. Takagi.
I'm sorry for behaving like that
in front of you and the others.
Don't be.
Truthfully, I was relieved to
find out that Hozuki still has
a young prospect with as
much backbone as you.
I look forward to hearing
of your future successes.
Thank you very much.
[DOJIMA]
"Backbone" he says?
That club is still
full of troublemakers!
Someday they're gonna cause
problems and then you'll see!
And when they do,
don't come crying to me!
[AKIRA exhales]
[SATOWA]
That about covers it, I think.
And not long after,
I composed "Tenkyu".
I understand. Got it. Thanks.
Do you think it'd be
possible to tell the others
what you just told me?
I finally feel like I
can figure out
how to approach that
piece now, y'know?
I doubt they would want to
hear about my family history!
I mean, sure, it might
be boring if it were
coming from someone
we don't care about.
But this is different.
[gasps]
Different?
We care about you.
[CHIKA] Well, it's not
like I'm gonna force you.
[SATOWA] Why? Why is Kudo
always like this? Every time.
[SATOWA gasps] Kudo. I'm
treating you to some ice cream.
What? Why would you do that?
[SATOWA]
I just feel like it.
[SATOWA] I wonder...
if someday, I could return it.
The same amount of warmth...
that you gave me.
[SATOWA]
Someday.
[TAKINAMI]
There... Did you hear that?
It's the spot where the parts
change and we enter the main
segment of the piece.
The handoffs are
a little sloppy,
can we make them smoother?
[TAKEZO]
Smoother?
So smooth the listener can't
tell when they happened.
From then on, you each
gradually build up
and show off the color
of your sounds.
So you're free to go wild.
Just make sure you
keep the tempo.
[AKIRA]
That makes sense.
[TAKINAMI] That's the
best part of the piece,
so use your own sound to play
it to your heart's content.
Oh, and Hozuki. You play the
start of the song quite softly.
But do you think you could
make it a little more tense?
Why do you want me
to make it tense?
[TAKINAMI] You're probably
doing it unconsciously,
but your sound is
pretty gentle overall.
And to me, that says you deny
your previous performance.
But that sound of yours
had incredible power.
You shouldn't throw
that away. Use it.
By putting that sound
into the piece,
the other parts will shine more.
[gasps]
Then I'll do it.
[AKIRA] It sounds like this
will be an amazing performance.
[AKIRA] I wonder when
the last time was.
That I felt excited like this.
[TAKEZO]
And so...
...with each of us showing our
emotions through our sound...
[TAKEZO] The qualifier for
nationals was about to begin.
[TAKEZO] Next time:
"Morning of the Showdown."