[MASHIRO]
I'm sorry, Takezo,
for not being able to get
us a ticket to nationals.
I know my grandson.
[TAKEZO]
It's been a whole year...
[CHIKA]
...since that day.
Good morning!
Oh, good morning!
[TAKEZO] Wow, breakfast looks
like quite the feast today.
[TAKEZO'S MOM] Well, today's the
national qualifier, isn't it?
You need your energy!
Oh, and I'm coming to
hear your performance.
What?
[TAKEZO'S MOM]
Do you not want me to?
No, it's not like that, but...
Well, I know you've been
working hard every day
from early in the morning
until late at night,
and I haven't heard even a
single one of your performances.
Your dad and I will
come root for you.
[TAKEZO]
Dad, too?
[TAKEZO'S MOM] Good thing the
qualifier's on a Sunday!
I don't have any plans today,
but I'm not coming.
[TAKEZO'S MOM]
Hey, Takeru!
But if by some chance
you make it to nationals,
then I guess I might
consider going.
[sighs]
That'd be great, thank you.
[TAKEZO]
Hm? Kurusu?
Uh. What's wrong?
Did something happen?
I thought we were all meeting up
by the station near the venue.
[HIRO]
Um. Well...
If you don't mind, do you think
we could go together?
I'm so nervous I'm afraid I
might get on the wrong train.
[gasps]
Hold on a sec.
Take this. Hey, your hands!
Jeez, they're like ice!
Were you waiting long?
Oh, no, it wasn't
that long, not really!
I mean, your hands are
pretty cold, too, aren't they?
Ah well, to tell
you the truth,
I've been a little
nervous since yesterday.
I'm actually pretty
relieved you're here.
It makes me feel better.
Let's go.
Chika. Do you have everything?
Have you got your plectrums?
Of course I do,
who would forget their
plectrums when they're
going to perform?
[ISAKI] More people
than you might think.
Oh, I'm coming to watch
with Takaoka today.
What? With Tetsuki? How come?
You know, I just heard
he was coming, too,
so I thought I'd be
extra nice and friendly
and give him a ride.
Possibly by force.
Listen, are you trying
to kill him, or what?
See you later.
Chika?
Nationals, snatch that ticket!
[CHIKA chuckles] Hey, don't
worry about us. We will!
[chuckles]
[MALE JUDGE]
The award goes to...
Kanagawa Prefectural.
Hakuto High School.
[FUMI] Kazusa seems
unusually nervous to me.
[NENE giggles]
[KAZUSA gasps]
What's wrong, Nene?
Listen! I just know you're
gonna be number one!
What?
[NENE]
Come on, ask me "why?"!
Okay, then, why?
You'll win 'cause
I'm rooting for you!
[gasps]
You're such an angel!
Thank you, Nene!
You're right. There's no
way I'm gonna lose.
I'm going to take
you to nationals
if it's the last thing I do!
[FUMI]
Don't worry, Kazusa.
Himesaka is never going to
lose again. I'm sure of it.
[UTA] Jeez, Mio! Hurry up,
the bus is already at school!
[MIO]
I can't.
What?
I don't have enough... power.
I need to charge it.
[UTA]
Mio!
Hey! Suzumori! Looks to me
like you found Kanzaki, huh?
I'm glad you did!
I suppose so! But Mio was saying
he still isn't coming yet.
[YAMAMOTO]
Aw, and why's that?
Photosynthesis.
Oh, I see! Photosynthesis!
Do you mind if I join?
[YAMAMOTO] Hm. Wow, this feels
good, doesn't it, Kanzaki?
You look... like you're
having fun again.
Yep! I sure am!
Because the national
qualifier is finally here!
I've been waiting so long,
I almost can't believe
today is the day!
I see.
[YAMAMOTO laughs]
I couldn't go
to the traditional music
festival because I got the flu.
[MIO]
Oh yeah?
[YAMAMOTO]
You don't remember?
Seriously. Thank you for
following me all this way.
[MIO] You're welcome, but I
didn't really follow you, so...
[YAMAMOTO] What?!
Oh, right, yeah, of course!
That sounded stupid, didn't it?
Wow, I feel pretty
embarrassed now.
Forget I said it!
[UTA] Hey, come on,
you guys, we'll be late!
Oh. Sorry, Suzumori! Time to
get up, Kanzaki. Let's go!
Hey, listen, Mio.
About Mister Yamamoto.
[YAMAMOTO]
Kanzaki!
If you don't hurry it up,
I'm gonna be forced to
come carry you to the bus!
[MIO] That's fine.
Carry me on your back.
[YAMAMOTO]
Huh?
Okay, guys, take deep breaths.
I heard exhaling is important.
[ALL inhale, exhales]
It's not working!
I swear, my heart is about
to pop right out of my ear!
[KOTA]
Quick! Plug it up!
[MITTSU] Calm down!
We'll try acupressure!
My mom said pressing here on
our hands relieves tension.
[KOTA] I read on the internet
that it helps if we
admit we're nervous!
[SANE]
Okay, we're doing both!
We're so nervous!
What the heck are
you guys doing?
[ALL yell]
[MITTSU]
Ch-Ch-Ch-Ch-Ch-Chika!
Hozuki! Don't scare
us like that!
Why are you already
so nervous, anyway?
It's not like this is
our first competition.
No, you're exactly right!
And that's why we're
even more nervous!
And on top of that, today,
you know, um... It's just...
We can't fail today, for sure.
Well, if you're thinking like
that, you'll definitely mess up.
[ALL yell]
Shouldn't you maybe say
something inspiring or hopeful?
It's shock therapy.
Is your mom coming today?
To hear us perform?
[gasps]
Doubtful. I sent her a
letter and mentioned
today's competition, but she
didn't write back or call me.
I see.
[SATOWA]
But... It's okay.
My personal performance and
my performance with you.
This won't be the last chance
for her to hear it.
[gasps]
Yepper!
That's right!
[TAKEZO]
Good morning, guys!
[ALL]
Good morning!
So, are we all here, then?
We sure are!
Miss Akira will join us later,
isn't that right?
[TAKINAMI]
Yeah. Let's go.
It'll take ten minutes to
get to the venue on foot.
Uh, sorry, hold on a sec!
This may not be the right
place to give these to you,
but here goes...
[SANE, MITTSU gasp]
What? What is it?
[SATOWA gasps]
Actually, it's nothing.
I'm so sorry. Never min--
Okay, will you stop
being so hesitant?
Hey!
[CHIKA]
Can I open it? Cool.
[SATOWA]
Wait!
[TAKEZO]
Are they charms?
They're in the
shape of a bridge!
And they have our names on them!
Did you make these
all by yourself, Hozuki?
Um. Yeah, but I'm sorry that
they aren't very well made,
and they're tacky.
I-I caused you trouble
because of my family stuff.
So I made these for us
in hopes that we'll
still do our best today.
[HIRO]
Hozuki. They're great!
Thank you so much
for making them!
They're filled with love,
and that makes them precious!
We'll definitely be all
right now, thanks to these!
Thank you!
[KOTA]
Here, Mister Takinami!
[TAKINAMI]
What? I've got one, too? Thanks.
[TAKEZO] Hozuki. Did you poke
your fingers with the needle?
[SATOWA]
I did, but my fingertips
are really hard now, so...
[SANE] Uh, Chika? We need to
get going or we'll be late.
Hey, what's the deal with him?
He didn't even say "thank you."
[TAKINAMI] Kudo, that's the
wrong direction.
Oh, wow. He must
be really happy.
Yeah, looks like it.
Maybe this is the first time
anyone's given him a charm.
[CHIKA] This is crazy.
I mean, it's just a charm.
Do me a favor and never
show your face here again.
[MALE DELINQUENT]
Probably best to just use him
when we need to win a fight.
[gasps]
I guess we should
get going, too.
[CHIKA]
Hey, Granddad.
The koto club you created really
is amazing! You'd be proud!
I wish these days
could go on forever.
[TSUKAJI]
Komaki! Hurry up!
We're gonna head out
to the venue now!
[KOMAKI] Mister Tsukaji!
Please, wait for me!
[KOMAKI]
I don't understand, sir.
Is there some particular reason
I have to come today, too?
Whenever I go to concerts,
I always fall asleep right in
the middle, without fail.
So I really think
it might be better
if you just watch it alone.
[TSUKAJI] Komaki! Can you
please take your job seriously?
We publish a magazine
on traditional music!
You're one of the editors,
for god's sake. Act like it!
[chuckles] I was hired
through personal connections.
Traditional Japanese music
just isn't my thing!
That's enough!
Okay, tell me something,
honestly,
don't you think koto is
kind of a tough subject?
If that's how you feel,
then today's work will
suit you very well.
Huh?
[TSUKAJI] It's Kanagawa's
qualifier for nationals.
You think the koto is tough?
Difficult to approach?
This is way beyond that.
Today a bunch of
high school students in
their prime battle it out.
[MITTSU gasps] So, all of
them are our rivals, huh?
Tons of girls, as expected.
A total of 14 schools, was it?
Right. And the number
that goes to nationals...
...is just one.
Yeah.
[CHIKA, MITSU gasp]
It's been a while.
I'm glad to see you again.
[CHIKA]
You're...?
It's me! Remember?
I made friends with you guys
during the music festival.
Yeah, I don't remember us
becoming buddies! Although...
[CHIKA]
He was the one.
You told me that my tones were
unrefined that one time!
I found out later that you were
saying I sucked, you bastard!
[MIO]
Mm.
Don't agree with me!
Let me tell you something,
we're not the same as
we were back then!
We're gonna win today!
[MIO]
Uh!
Kanzaki! You always
seem to disappear on me
when I look away for a second!
Everyone's looking
for you over--
Whoa! It's Tokise High School!
Yeah, that's us, what about it?
Er. Forgive me! Sorry!
Are you their
advisor or something?
I'm Taishin Yamamoto. I'm the
advisor for Hakuto's koto club.
I'm delighted to meet you!
Well, thanks a lot.
I'm Takinami, Tokise's advisor.
Man, oh, man. I heard your
school's performance.
The festival put out a DVD.
I can't even tell you
how moved I was!
So, what kind of guidance
do you give them?
[TAKINAMI] Nothing really.
It's all my students' doing.
[YAMAMOTO]
Wow! What a cool answer!
Unlike the music festival,
Tokise performs right after
Hakuto today, right?
I'll be rushing to
hear your performance
as soon as ours is over!
Okay...
What? We're playing
right after Hakuto?
Yeah.
[CHIKA] Huh? For real?
How come we didn't know that?
[HIRO] Why the heck didn't
you tell us that, Suzu?
[TAKEZO] You only said we'd be
the second to last performance,
not who we
were following!
What? Did you need to know?
Does the order affect your
performance somehow?
You scared? Oh. I guess
maybe you are, huh?
No, we're not scared!
Order doesn't matter at all!
[TAKINAMI]
All good, then?
You're damn right, we are!
My goodness,
what wonderful leadership!
I gotta say, my students give a
very good performance, too.
I hope you'll listen
to them from the wings.
[UTA]
Mister Yamamoto! Mio!
Oh, excuse me, but we have
to go now. See you later.
Kanzaki?
[MIO]
Hey.
I'm not gonna lose. Count on it.
[gasps]
--[CHIKA] Will she come running?
--[KAZUSA] Satowa!
[gasps]
[TAKEZO]
They're serious.
Everyone's dead set
on getting to nationals.
Thank you very much!
So, uh, Granny. You're staying
to listen to us perform, right?
Actually, I've got some
business to take care of.
Oh. Okay.
But I guess... I'll finish it
quickly and come back.
After all, you guys are already
like my grandkids, so...
Chika, hurry up! The next
school will be here soon.
Alright.
You know, it still hurts
that he won't be here.
That Grandpa won't
see my performance.
But I'm really glad
I've got you.
[SHIZU]
Hm.
We'll just take you
to nationals, too.
[SHIZU]
Chika!
Whatever happens, you guys are
gonna be okay, for sure.
Go play to your heart's content.
[STUDENTS whispering]
[HOZUMI]
Kazusa?
[KAZUSA gasps]
Oh, Hozumi!
Hey! Are you doing okay?
Is there anything
I can help with?
[KAZUSA] Ah, no, I'm okay.
Thank you, though.
It's just that I'm kinda
more nervous than usual.
Since we're playing early,
the third in line.
I see. But that's natural.
Just know that when you perform,
all of us support members
are rooting for you!
We'll be sending you all the
good energy we've got!
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Well, if you need anything,
just let me know.
[KAZUSA]
Hozumi!
We'll get there. We'll play
together at nationals!
[chuckles]
Yeah, of course!
[KAZUSA gasps]
Whoa, it's been a while since
we were in a hall like this!
This one's smaller than
the music festival, though.
Well, only about half the number
of schools are performing.
[buzzer]
[CHIKA]
It's starting.
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
We are now commencing...
...the Kanagawa Qualifier.
The thirty-second annual Japan
High School Music Competition.
Oh, wow! They're all high school
students down there! So young!
But just as I thought,
it seems there are very few
boys competing. Bummer.
And only one school can
make it to nationals, right?
I wonder which school
I wanna root for.
What do you think,
which school is going to win?
You're oversimplifying it.
I really would prefer to think
that the one who worked
the hardest will win,
but who knows?
Because even if they worked
as hard as they can,
the pressure of performing
in a competition like this
will cause some of them
to make mistakes.
Chemistry with the judges is
a significant factor, too.
[KOMAKI]
Really?
[TSUKAJI] It can't be helped.
The judges are only human.
Let's see, today's judges are...
[TSUKAJI]
One of them is pretty strict.
Well. As usual,
it's reasonable to think
that Himesaka will
take first place.
But I couldn't go to the Kanto
Japanese Music Festival.
I'm curious about Hakuto,
seeing as they beat out
Himesaka for first there.
I would have watched the DVD,
But somebody spilled coffee on
it before I had the chance!
[AKIRA] That lesson took longer
than I thought it would.
I'll have to hurry to the venue.
[AKIRA]
Guess she's still angry with me.
Not a huge surprise,
but still...
[gasps]
[AKIRA]
Excuse me. Grand Master?
What is it?
Oh, well. I'm getting
ready to head out
to the National Qualifier.
I know that I've already told
you, but Satowa's performing.
I'm driving myself there.
I could give you a ride--
I said I that can't go.
Satowa's been excommunicated.
As the grand master
of this school,
it would be improper to
watch her performance.
But it's not improper.
You're more than just a teacher,
you're also her mother.
[CHIHARU]
After everything I've done,
I'm not even sure I
can claim that much.
I had my own problems
to deal with,
so I turned my eyes
away from her feelings.
And when she was screaming
for help on that stage,
I responded to her with
nothing but contempt.
I don't have the right
to call myself her mother,
let alone hear her perform.
Okay. That's it!
Hey. Let go! What do
you think you're doing?
I don't have to time
to argue with you,
so I'm sorry, but you're going!
[CHIHARU gasps]
I know this is none of my
business and I'm being selfish,
But too bad! Enough is enough!
I refuse to let the
shackles of this school
and the hardships of the
past bind everybody!
Not anymore, I'm so tired of it!
What is all the commotion?
My goodness, Akira.
What sort of stunt
are you pulling--
Perfect timing.
I'll take you with us, too.
What?
You heard me, come on.
You need to hear them play!
[DOJIMA gasps] Can you calm
down, you're being too rough!
I just got my license.
You ladies better hold on tight!
"Kata". The hell?
Sorry, but I'm not sure
what you're trying to say.
To be honest, I don't understand
the name of the piece
that Hakuto's playing.
[TAKEZO]
What does that say? "Katagashi"?
"Katakago".
It's a type of flower.
An archaic word for katakuri.
That's stupid.
I don't know why they picked
such a difficult name.
Do you think it's
another original piece?
Most likely. It has the same
composer as last time.
[CHIKA, TAKEZO gasp]
It does? Looks like the
composer is Miyabi Tojo.
Have you heard of this person?
Well, no.
I checked around, but I
couldn't find any info on them.
[TAKINAMI] It would appear that
Hakuto has a very talented
composer in their club.
Are you doing okay?
You're awfully quiet.
It's about Himesaka.
What about them?
Well, I thought for
sure they would
play another difficult piece.
[HIMESAKA'S ADVISOR]
Everyone, it's about that time.
President?
Thank you. Listen.
Today's really special.
We worked exceptionally hard
to get to these qualifiers.
I know we've had our fair
share of disagreements.
And we weren't always
in the best of moods.
There are members who
can't perform today,
but everyone has been crucial
part of this journey,
and your support has
been priceless.
Every single person here is an
important part of this club.
And as your president,
I can proudly say
that we've practiced harder
than any other school.
Thanks to all the people here,
we will win today!
Form a circle!
[HIMESAKA MEMBERS]
We are one entity!
We are the champions
of Kanagawa!
[YAE]
Let's go!
[SATOWA] Next time,
"Champion's Resolve."