[applause]
[SATOWA]
So, this... is a Meiryo concert.
Somehow it's like,
I saw all the seasons.
Yeah, same.
It feels like a
year just passed.
[KAZUSA] I can't believe someone
like him is this skilled.
Disgusting.
Good work, everyone!
You were amazing out there!
Hey, Ousuke,
are you feeling okay?
Huh? Yeah, why?
It's just...
You used to get
so sick after performing,
and I was wondering if
it was happening again.
Nah. I'm not as
weak as I was back then.
I mean, if you gave me a kiss,
maybe I'd feel
a little better, Asa.
Will you shut up?
[OUSUKE chuckles]
I'm just kidding.
[YOSHIKI]
Asano! Ousuke! Nice work!
That was a great performance!
[ASANO]
Yoshi!
[JUDGE A] About what
I expected from Meiryo.
It's obvious why they got
second place at nationals.
I'm surprised someone beat them.
Are we sure it was
smart to let them perform
before every other school?
The rest of the students
are going to have a
hard time following that up.
Why do you guys
look so depressed?
How could we not be
after watching a
performance like that?
It's just hitting me that we may
never be able to defeat them.
Chika, do you honestly think we
have a chance of surpassing them
with our performance?
What nonsense are
you guys on about?
Comparing yourselves
to them is ridiculous.
[CHIKA]
What did you just say?
Think about it. Imagine if Kudo,
on his first day learning
the koto, heard me play
and thought
"I can't beat that."
It's nothing short of laughable.
Well, when you
put it that way,
it does sound kinda ridiculous.
Come on!
You know, to reach the goal
we hung on the clubroom wall,
we have no choice but
to surpass their performance.
If seeing how good they are
with your own two eyes makes you
think that goal is impossible,
then what?
Would you rather quit?
[SANE]
Chika?
Are you kidding me?
What do you mean,
"would you rather quit?"
I oughtta kick
your ass for that, Specs!
Any guy who quits before
he even starts has no balls!
Can you not say "balls"?
And what's with the head trauma?
[CHIKA]
It's self‐punishment!
Consider this an apology
for getting discouraged!
Sane, punch me too!
I wanna say sorry!
Yeah, me three,
but gently please?
[chuckles]
It looks like somebody's
gotten better at dealing
with everyone, haven't they?
Oh, yeah? Think so?
[CHIKA]
All right!
If you really want it,
I'll hit you all right now!
[SATOWA]
They bounce back quickly.
[HIRO]
Oh, by the way, where's Suzu?
[TAKEZO] He said
the hall was suffocating,
so he's at the café upstairs.
[HIRO] Jeez,
why'd he even bother coming?
[TAKEZO] I expected
a little more from him
after he helped Mizuhara
out the other day.
Hey, guys.
Are there any other powerhouses
like Meiryo and Himesaka
within Kanagawa?
[TAKEZO] Himesaka is always
at the very top in Kanagawa
so not really.
Wavy‐head just had
to be at the top.
What about the school
going after us, then?
Says it right here!
[TAKEZO]
Hakuto High School?
That doesn't ring a bell.
Ahh. Well. Doesn't matter, then.
They're right after us,
so we'll be too busy cleaning
up to hear them anyway.
What are you doing
on the ground, mister?
Listening to the wind.
It's beautiful.
The break'll be over soon,
so let's get going.
I don't remember any of the
performances after Meiryo's.
Me neither. That guy
said all they had to do
was outshine everyone
who played after them,
and I guess they did.
Sure, maybe, but that's
just until we perform.
We're gonna destroy them.
Then everyone'll
forget about them and‐‐
Oh, sorry.
[SENTAROU]
Where are you looking, idiot?
[CHIKA]
Hmm? Uh...
My bad, man.
I didn't see you there.
What the hell.
Are you kidding me?
Are you trying to pick a
fight with me, you bastard?
Do yourself a favor and
revaluate who you're talking to.
I don't have the time
to get into fights
with middle schoolers.
Take your own advice.
You sonnuva‐‐!
Whoa, whoa! Sen, what
are you doing? Calm down!
Let me go, Haru!
This guy insulted me
and now he's gonna pay!
[CHIKA]
What?
When did I insult you?
Don't lie!
[TAKEZO]
Hey! Kudo!
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry!
He means no ill‐will, I promise!
It's okay! Please accept
our apologies as well.
Don't apologize,
I didn't do anything!
I take it you guys will
be playing today, too?
Oh, uh, yeah!
We're the koto club from Eidai
Fuzoku High School in Ibaraki.
Sorry again.
[CHIKA]
You're high school students?
I'm, uh, sorry.
[SENTAROU]
Don't screw with me!
[CHIKA]
What? I just said I'm sorry!
That guy can't get along
with Chika at all, huh?
[SATOWA]
Honestly.
I'm very sorry that my fellow
club member caused such trouble.
I'll give him
a talking to later.
So just this once,
could you find it in
yourself to let this slide?
Whoa! Sen, are you okay, buddy?
I'm so sorry!
We go to an all‐boys school,
so we're not used to
seeing girls our own age!
Haru! Shut it
or I'll shut it for you!
[laughs]
No way, did he actually
just get a nosebleed?
He must have seen Hozuki
and let his thoughts run wild!
Hey, you should go push his
buttons a little, Hozu... ki...
Disgusting.
You have zero tact,
you know that, Chika?
Who's laughing now, ya jerk?
That's what ya get!
All right.
I'm Chika Kudo, a first year
from Tokise High School.
What's your name?
Sentarou Miya, a first year
from Eidai Fuzoku High.
I'll never lose to the
likes of you, yah hear me?
[CHIKA]
Let's go, Specs!
[SENTAROU]
Let's go, Haru!
We gotta prep!
[ISAKI] So this is
where they're playing?
Nice place.
Thanks for showing me
how to get here.
I really appreciate it!
It's no problem,
don't mention it.
Thanks for driving me.
You carsick?
That's weird,
you must be sensitive.
I was driving so safely.
[TETSUKI]
What?
Feels kinda strange, being here.
To think the day would come
when I'd get to see my nephew's
koto performance live.
[TETSUKI] I don't blame
you for being surprised.
I mean, this time last year,
he was getting into fights
almost every day.
[ISAKI]
Is that so?
I can't say I know much
about that time in his life.
When I first met him, I was
afraid of how he'd turn out.
I'm relieved.
He's finally starting
to enjoy his life.
My father would
have loved to hear this.
I wish he could be here.
Oh, he's listening.
I'm sure.
[ISAKI]
Aww, listen to yourself.
You might as well
be Chika's guardian!
[TETSUKI]
Huh?
Next up is Eidai Fuzoku.
Are those the guys from earlier?
[CHIKA]
What are they playing?
Lemme see.
It's called "Sarashi Fuutegoto."
[CHIKA]
Never heard of it.
[KOTA] I wonder if
it's harder than "Kuon."
I don't know this "Kuon" piece,
but "Sarashi" is a
difficult one for sure.
Well look who it is.
Heyo!
So, did you guys get
to hear our performance?
Yeah, we did.
It was all right,
all things considered.
I'll take that as a compliment.
So, Sarashi's a
tough piece, huh?
[OUSUKE]
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It has a lot of forms and
advanced techniques throughout.
There's a bit in the middle
that's particularly hard
to get right, too.
Huh. Interesting.
[OUSUKE] Well it kinda depends
on how fast you play it, though.
[SENTAROU]
Listen up, Haru.
Usually when people perform,
they start playing faster
because they're nervous,
or excited, or both!
So...
Right, I know.
Stay calm and‐‐
So be prepared for me
to play three times faster
than I normally would!
Aah...
Shouldn't you say,
"Stay calm and don't rush,"
or something like that?
Not tell me to speed up
and match you?
Are you stupid?
If we stay slow,
we won't be nearly as sharp!
But you don't have to worry,
I'll guide you out there.
Just follow my lead.
[HARU]
Sen looks so tall right now,
even though
he's so very tiny.
[ANNOUNCER ] Number 16,
Eidai Fuzoku High School
from Ibaraki prefecture,
performing "Sarashi Fuutegoto."
♪ melodic, steady playing ♪
♪ tempo speeds up ♪
[MITTSU, CHIKA, SANE]
So fast!
[OUSUKE]
Wow.
I've heard a lot of
people play "Sarashi,"
but this is
definitely the fastest.
Their hands are
keeping up well, too.
[HIRO] It's so quick, I can
barely see their hands moving.
[TAKEZO] I can't believe their
notes aren't getting sloppy
at this speed!
[SATOWA]
They've practiced this a lot.
Even their breathing is in sync.
Like they're two sides of the‐‐
No, wait.
They may be synchronized,
but they're not equal.
[OUSUKE]
Interesting!
It's not just fast,
it's also seriously intense.
[SENTAROU roars]
Don't underestimate me!
Does anyone else
hear him talking?
[ADVISOR]
The koto club?
Oh yeah.
Now that you mention it,
we do have one, huh?
It's scheduled to be
disbanded this year, but
maybe it won't be
if you want to join it.
[CLASSMATE A]
Little Sentarou!
[CLASSMATE B] You're tiny
and you play the koto?
You're like a girl!
How cute!
[SENTAROU]
Damn it!
Everybody's always
making fun of me!
[CHIKA]
They got even faster?
[SENTAROU]
It was my granny who started
and taught the koto club
at Eidai Fuzoku.
It used to go to nationals
proudly every year.
But some people ridicule
and mock the club.
They don't understand!
[SATOWA]
They're still speeding up?
[SENTAROU ]
I promise,
I'm gonna take your koto club
back to national stage!
So, make sure
and watch me do it.
Okay, Granny?
[SENTAROU roars]
[ALL 4]
I'm seeing things.
That was so enthusiastic
it got me sweating,
and I'm just in the audience.
They're clearly talented.
[SATOWA] Right now,
there's a difference in energy,
but if these two got
to the same level of skill,
they'd be fantastic.
There haven't been any
bad performances so far.
Not really.
Everyone's been
playing at a high level.
Hey, they're next.
[TAKEZO]
Mm. Himesaka.
[HIMESAKA'S ADVISOR]
Listen up, everyone.
First place slipped away
from us at nationals,
but here it will be
a different story.
Let's show them all that
Kanto's number one koto club
isn't Meiryo, but Himesaka!
[STUDENTS]
Yes, ma'am!
[ANNOUNCER] Himesaka Girls'
Academy from Kanagawa prefecture
performing "Two Personalities."
♪ fast, synchronized playing ♪
[CHIKA] They fit together
even more than last time!
[KOTA]
My whole body hurts!
[SANE] They sound like
military troops again.
I feel like I'm being
stabbed by a spear!
[KAZUSA]
This is how a top contestant
at nationals performs!
Meiryo isn't the Kanto
region's number one.
We are!
[HAKUTO PRESIDENT]
Ugh!
Where have you been
all this time, Mio?
President. Scary.
He was taking a nap on
the ground in a park nearby.
[HAKUTO PRESIDENT]
What?
The wind sounded nice.
So I was listening to it.
Why will you
listen to the "wind,"
but not the other schools
performing like I asked you to?
Because their sound
is always boring.
Everyone plays the
same way at these things.
With a predetermined sound.
Being surrounded by that
kind of noise is just painful.
Ms. Isaki.
Oh. I guess I fell asleep, huh?
Yeah. You were knocked out.
Are you that tired?
Well, no, not really.
It's just that the songs
have been boring.
I didn't think the
last school was bad.
It's not that
they're bad, honestly.
They just put on a
boring performance.
It's probably a problem
with their coach.
Isn't the daughter of a grand
master teaching Chika
and the members of his club?
That's gotta be pretty rough.
I wonder if there's anyone
who's not a student
who could teach them.
Actually, now that
I think about it,
they do have an
advisor, Mr. Takinami.
Takinami?
[TETSUKI]
Yeah.
What, has Chika mentioned him?
Well, no, I was just thinking
about how back in high school,
I had an upperclassman
with the same last name.
Have you ever heard of them?
That power couple, the world‐
famous conductor Kaoru Takinami
and the genius pianist,
Tsukasa Yukimori?
Their son went to my school
and was two grades above me.
[TETSUKI] I hadn't,
but the son must be talented.
You'd think so, but
actually he was considered
a disappointment
to their elite family.
Apparently,
he didn't play music at all.
But I distinctly remember
one day when I did see him.
[STUDENT]
Hey, Takinami!
So, rumor has it
that you're the son
of that famous conductor,
Kaoru Takinami.
Our usual club advisor
isn't here today.
Think you could
conduct us a little?
[TAKINAMI]
That's presumptuous.
To be frank,
I'm not interested in your sound
enough to want to conduct you.
Try again when you're better.
[STUDENT]
Huh?
What's your problem?
I'm not sure why, but I've
never forgotten that incident.
It still makes me wonder if he
really was a "disappointment."
Interesting.
See, the thing is,
there was also a rumor
that he was a prodigy that just
decided not to play music.
But I don't know whether
it was true or not.
Oh man.
His first name's on
the tip of my tongue.
Happen to be Suzuka?
Yeah, that was it!
Suzuka!
[MUSICIAN C]
Kaoru.
Is Suzuka still not
showing any interest
in learning an instrument?
Nah. Every day, all
he does is lie there
listening to music
from morning until night.
But his older sister
Kiyoka plays the piano.
Can't you just make
him play an instrument?
He'd probably love it.
It's okay.
You can't force someone to play.
If he really wants to get
involved with creating music,
he will.
Hey, buddy.
Whatcha yah up to, there?
I just finished a piece.
Wow.
Composing at such a young age.
That's amazing!
Let me see!
I knew Suzuka wanted to do
more than just listen to music.
Okay.
Seriously?
This is a score for
a whole orchestra!
Suzuka, please tell me,
where and when did you learn
to write a score like this?
I've been writing them for
as long as I can remember,
so I guess I don't know.
Not that I have any
interest in playing myself,
but I love to listen to music.
Though I've listened to most
of the stuff we have at home.
So sometimes I'll think
"I'd love to listen to this kind
of piece!" but never find it.
When that happens,
I just write it myself.
He's a genius!
I knew he'd be like
his mother and father!
Most college students
couldn't compose this,
yet he's done it at seven?
We don't have to make
such a big fuss about it.
Why don't we just
let him do his thing?
Don't be like that,
you've got a prodigy!
You have to nurture his talent!
That's it!
Let's play this song
at our next concert!
I bet he it would
be a great fit
for our next television
appearance!
[TAKINAMI]
At first, I was happy about it.
Getting to hear what I wrote
played by professionals
was exciting.
But, day by day,
as they continued to make
such a big deal about it,
the beautiful and endlessly
free world of music
suddenly became
rigid and boring.
Finally, I couldn't
take it anymore.
[KIYOKA]
I just heard.
So you're going to stay
with our uncle in Japan?
Yeah, I am.
C'mon, Kiyoka.
You know why,
it's cus everyone here wants
to suck me into the music world.
Why not get sucked into it?
You like music, don't you?
'Course I do.
That's why I don't
want to get involved.
Music is at its best when it's
just being genuinely enjoyed.
It makes no sense.
Why would I want to live
in the world of music
when there are
people like you
who look like they're suffering?
[KIYOKA]
Well, sorry for "suffering."
Unfortunately, I'm not
a genius like some people.
But I also won't quit.
[TAKINAMI]
Why not?
That's because...
[TAKEZO] All right! Let's
start unloading the instruments
during the lunch break.
I've been nervous
this whole time,
but the closer we
get the sicker I feel.
Yeah, my stomach's
starting to ache.
Just like how I felt before
we did "Ryuuseigun."
There's no reason
to be so jittery now.
We've still got a little while.
Can't help it.
I wish I could be
as confident as you are.
What, do you not
get nervous at all
before you go on stage, Hozuki?
Of course I do, a little.
That's all?
I'm impressed.
I've been on stage
plenty of times,
and my stomach's still churning.
[SATOWA]
You get used to it.
We'll see about that.
Hey, Kurusu.
You okay?
[HIRO]
Huh? What? Why?
Oh. You just seemed
a little down, is all.
What do you mean?
I'm completely normal!
In fact, I feel great!
Really? That's good, then.
Heh...
[HIRO]
It's not like me to be nervous.
I can't tell him that I am.
All the other schools were so
good that I started worrying.
And when I thought
about it I realized,
I'm the only one
who hasn't played
in front of
an audience before.
If I hold Kota back during
the performance after being
so hard on him...
I won't.
I just can't mess up!
Here.
This one's yours,
safe and sound.
Cool, you brought
your grandpa's koto?
Good idea!
What better time
to break it out?
Well, I have been using
it at home this whole time.
But this is your first time
using it on a stage, right?
That means Gen's koto is finally
going to see the light of day.
I'm sure that makes
him very happy.
I guess so.
Oh. Hozuki.
You take my koto inside instead.
I'll bring in the 17‐string.
Uh...
Leave it to me.
Kurusu, could you
do me a huge favor
and head to
the drop‐off spot
and tell everyone
there what to do?
I was gonna go register us.
Oh!
Mr. Takinami!
Perfect timing!
Could you carry this koto
the rest of the way for me?
I wanted to go
get us registered‐‐
I already registered you.
Wait, what? You did?
What's that supposed to mean?
The advisor is supposed
to be registering you guys.
[TAKEZO] I just thought
you must've forgotten.
Well, I didn't forget.
Oh. There's fine, Hiro.
I'm going to place the bridges
and quickly tune that one.
So you can just
leave it where it is.
Okay, gotcha.
Sorry about that.
[SATOWA]
The kotos!
[CHIKA]
Hozuki!
[SANE]
Hey, are you okay?
The two of you didn't
get hurt, did you?
I'm fine, don't worry about me.
Just worry about the kotos!
They both look good to me.
Oh, no.
That was all
my fault, wasn't it?
I'm so sorry!
It's okay.
Nothing was damaged.
[SATOWA]
Next time, "Kuon."