I'm gonna inspire you.
You'd better not lose to those
other lame clubs, you got it?!
You know, I don't think
the club presentations
are supposed to be
a competition or anything.
[CHIKA]
If we don't have five members,
then we'll have to disband!
We gotta win over
those naive first years!
Go out there and
crush everyone else!
That sounds violent.
You mess this up;
I'm gonna make you pay.
[STUDENT A]
And to our new first‐years,
congratulations
on entering high school!
Our first presentation
is the light music club!
Hey, man...
Did Kurata seem okay?
Yeah. My encouragement
brought the nerd to tears.
That doesn't sound good.
[CHIKA]
Hmph. Anyway, forget about him.
Don't these guys
sound freakin' awful?
Do you think so?
They're terribly out of tune.
[TAKEZO shudders]
I was so preoccupied
talking to Kudo earlier
that I just realized I've never
performed solo before.
What do I do if I play
the wrong note...?
What if one of my strings breaks
like my upperclassmen's did?
[MASHIRO]
You're such an overthinker!
Just prepare the
best that you can...
There' s no point in worrying
about what happens after that.
Don't undermine the
effort you've put in.
The stage is your reward,
so go enjoy it!
[STUDENT A] Next up, we have
the koto club's presentation.
[TAKEZO] Hi, it's really nice
to meet everyone...
Oh, and, uh, welcome
to our high school!
I'm part of the kyoto club...!
Uh! I mean, the koto club!
Nope. He's definitely not okay.
[TAKEZO]
Anyway, we play
a traditional Japanese
instrument called the koto.
Today, I'll be using one
to perform a fundamental piece
called "Rokudan no Shirabe."
Koto fundamentals, huh?
All right.
[TAKEZO]
If you're interested in joining,
we'd love to have
you in our club.
It'll be fine... Just enjoy it.
♪ ♪
Oh... Wow... Think I'll pass.
Yeah, I mean, can you
actually call that music?
I feel sorry for the guy.
Shut your damn traps.
I can't hear anything!
Yo, I'm sorry my
idiot of a friend yelled
during your
performance earlier.
Oh. Yeah...
I was more worried about
getting new people to join.
Though I was wondering what
you thought of my playing?
Meh... It didn't
make sense to me.
He means 'casue we probably
don't know the song like you do!
Oh... Of course...
I suppsoe I should've picked
a song that was more popular.
Look, I didn't get it,
but you said it was a
fundamental piece, right?
It was fine.
Cheer up, it's not like it was
the worst thing I've ever heard.
[TAKEZO]
Thanks a lot.
So pretty!
Uh... Hello!
Hi, I hope you don't mind
that I left myself in.
You see,
I came here today
because I'd
like to join your club.
Whoa, really?!
[SATOWA] Will you give me
permission to join?
Oh yes, absolutely...!
You're 100 percent approved!
[SATOWA] Thank you!
Here's my application form.
Hey, you bastard.
What's with the double standard?
You took forever
to approve mine!
Hey, maybe it's because
her introduction
was a lot less violent!
This is great!
I didn't think anyone
would join so quickly.
Let's see, your name is...
Wait... Satowa...
Hozuki... You?!
Yes.
Hozuki...? Like as
in the Hozuki school?!
I suppose that means
you've heard of it ?
[shrieks]
[CHIKA] So, do you
know her or something?
[TAKEZO]
Of course I know her!
She's the daughter of the grand
master of a famous koto school!
Not only has she won
a ton of competitions,
she's practically a prodigy!
Oh please,
it's not that big of deal.
Yeah! So why should
we even give a damn?!
It'll take more than a good
reputation to impress me.
Would you mind explaining
why someone of your caliber
would want to join
a high school koto club?
Especially a
weak club like ours.
In truth, I've been
a part of the koto world
since I was just a little girl.
But whenever I play, it's
usually by myself...
Or on occasion I might
perform with a few other adults.
I've never played
with kids my age.
But then last year,
I happened to see your koto club
playing at the
high school qualifiers.
and I thought to myself,
"Wow, these guys look like
they're really having fun.
I wonder what it'd be
like to play with them?"
That's really sweet.
As I recall,
didn't your club also have
some female upperclassmen?
Uh... Yeah... We did,
but then they all graduated,
so now it's just me and Kudo,
who joined the club yesterday.
[SATOWA]
Just a couple of dudes, huh?
Guess I can drop
this stupid act, then.
[TAKEZO]
Hmm?
You know, I thought
it was a bit strange
that there was only one boy
in the presentation.
[TAKEZO]
I'm sorry. Heh heh.
Not to be rude, but you seem
a bit defferent from earlier.
What? I just told you
that it was all an act.
I didn't want
the girls in this club
to feel threatened
by my abilities,
so I was pretending to
be the friendly new kid.
Now, did you
get all that, champ?
No, not really...
Bet you're rethinking
that club app now, huh?!
Wait... Then...
That stuff you said
before was all a lie.
Well...
I'm already on the road to
becoming a professional
but having a cool underdog story
will help me make it to the top.
[TAKEZO]
A story?
That's right!
"Genius Koto Player
Makes Her Debut After Leading
a No Name Koto Club to
First Place in the Nationals!"
You see?
Doesn't that sound interesting?
Whoa... Win nationals?
"No name"?
Unfortunately, talent and
my family's rep isn't enough...
If I want to make it big, then I
have to do something newsworthy.
So, I thought I'd take this
dumpy club to nationals...
And that, boys, is how you make
a spectacular pro debut.
[TAKEZO]
But...
Come on,
it's not like you didn't have
that goal in mind already...
As long as you get
the desired results,
the intention doesn't matter.
We'll be fine...!
Now that I've joined you, we'll
get to nationals in no time...
Let's work hard together.
Hold it, prissy pants!
Just who the hell
do you think you are?!
Just 'cause you're koto royalty
doesn't mean you can say shit.
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
I don't think I really
owe you any answers.
Like, who even are you...?
Is there a reason a delinquent
would join the koto club?
Hey! You can't treat
Kudo like that!
That goes for you, too!
Just look at the
state of this koto!
It's terrible, and there's
no way this broke naturally.
Looks like you're having
trouble managing things.
That's because...
It's my fault, okay?!
It's not...!
You weren't the one who
broke our instruments!
Well, it seems
appearances don't lie.
Look, I don't know
why you're in this club,
nor do I particularly care.
But anyone who would damage
the instruments doesn't have
what it takes to play the koto.
[CHIKA]
I don't care about the koto!
Stop, Hozuki!
Fighting amongst ourselves isn't
going to accomplish anything!
Let's all just calm down.
'Kay?
Kudo!
He's a hot‐head, let him go.
Ah, you just haven't
gotten to know him yet.
He's not bad.
None of that matters.
The only thing I care about is
how he intends to face the koto.
[CHIKA]
Hey, about the club.
Four‐eyes gave me
permission to join.
But in the end, what if
that girl was actually right
and I don't have what it takes?
[sighs]
Yeah, you probably don't.
Dumb jerk, you could
at least pretend to care!
[TAKEZO] Even for someone
from the Hozuki school.
She's pretty ambitious.
[SATOWA] We'll get
to nationals in no time.
[TAKEZO] I guess to her
it really is that easy.
[CHIKA gasps]
What the hell are
you doing here?
Well, Captain Obvious,
this has been my seat
ever since the day of
the entrance ceremony.
What are you doing here?
Seriously?
[SATOWA] But anyone who would
damage the instruments doesn't
have what it takes
to play the koto.
Hey.
About what you
were saying before.
That thing you
told me yesterday,
at the club, you know.
Yes, what about it?
[CHIKA]
How do I get what it takes?
[SATOWA]
Huh?
Come on!
I just wanna know how
to get whatever it takes!
You're the daughter of
a grand master, right?
So you've gotta know!
That question is
so exceedingly stupid,
that I'm completely
disgusted by you.
Shuddup! I refuse to sit here
and be insulted by
Miss Queen of the Koto!
[TEACHER]
Kudo, get back here!
Why do idiots
have to be so loud?
[TAKEZO] Ah, you just haven't
gotten to know him, yet.
He's not bad.
[SATOWA]
He's not going to surprise me.
That guy is just a moron
who makes crude sounds.
And sounds never lie.
They always reveal
a person's true nature.
And that's why.
[CHIKA]
Damn it!
Who cares about her?
If I say I'm doin' it,
then I'm gonna do it
whether she likes it or not!
It's not like I need her
permission or anything,
so it's settled
and that's the end of it!
[GEN]
What are you doing?
Stop straddling the instruments!
Well, you wanna give it a try?
What do you think,
it was perfect, right?
[laughs]
More like it was okay.
But I do think you've
got a knack for it.
Yeah, who cares?
It doesn't matter to me
whether I can play some
dumb instrument or not.
[GEN]
Come on, Chika, don't leave!
[COP]
It's your fault it happened!
[SATOWA] Anyone who
damages an instrument...
Damn it.
Good afternoon.
Uh, hello.
Wait, Hozuki, what is this?
Oh.
I replaced it since
the other sign was so dingy.
After all, our end goal
is a little bit higher now.
So I updated it.
You can't just do
whatever you want!
Look. I'm sorry.
To you, the goal
of winning nationals
is some sort of express ticket
to a spectacular pro debut.
To a normal guy like me, just
getting there in the first place
would be a dream come true.
I'm not going to dream beyond
my abilities, I'm not a child.
I just want you
to understand that fact.
I do understand,
but your abilities will
grow if you aim higher.
And you can't expect
to grow as a person
if you're content
with where you are.
Do you or do you not want
to make it to nationals?
You can't tell me
you don't want to.
I saw you crying at
last year's qualifiers.
You did?
[SATOWA]
You cried because it hurt.
Because you wanted
to further than that, right?
Leave it to me and
I'll take us to nationals‐‐
No! You won't!
Because nationals aren't a place
you can lead us
to singlehandedly.
[TAKEZO] To get there,
we have to do it together.
[STUDENT C]
What? The nationals?
Are you kidding?
Do you even know
what level we play on?
[MASHIRO]
Of course!
But we're still allowed
to aim higher, right?
If we set a bigger goal,
then we'll probably
improve even faster!
[SATOWA] Do you or do you not
want to make it to nationals?
You can't tell me
you don't want to.
[CHIKA]
Shit.
That girl is already here.
Oh, look,
she's gonna play a song.
Come on your majesty,
show off those "pro abilities."
Heheh.
Let's just see how good you are.
♪ ♪
[CHIKA]
Huh?
Wait, she is playing
the koto, right?
It's the same instrument
that specs played on.
But it sounds so
different from yesterday.
I don't understand it,
but each note is
resounding so beautifully.
I've never...
I've never heard koto music
like this until now.
[GEN] A brat like you
wouldn't understand.
The koto is an extremely
charming instrument.
Because you don't understand it!
That's how art is sometimes.
A... mazing.
[knock, knock]
Sir, I have a request!
Aw, jeez.
Things feel so awkward now.
I wonder if Kudo and
Hozuki will come by today?
Uh, sir?
What's going on?
[PRINCIPAL]
Oh, hello Kurata.
I was recently informed that
your instruments were damaged.
So I requested that
a music store come
and repair them for you.
Is that okay?
[PRINCIPAL]
Of course!
It's not your fault
that they were broken.
Although, that means your club
has only one instrument left.
Will that make
practice difficult?
[TAKEZO]
Well...
We'll be okay.
As it turns out, I have
my own koto at home.
So while we wait for them to be
repaired I can practice there.
That's fortunate.
Yes.
Well then,
if you run into any problems,
please let me know.
Thank you so much, sir!
[TAKEZO]
Back to the nice girl act?
[chuckles]
I guess that's the situation.
So, do me a favor and let me
know when they're all fixed.
Bye.
I wonder if she's mad at me?
And Kudo's not here either.
[TAKEZO] What do you
mean he's out today?
Does he have a cold?
Yeah, that's giving
him way too much credit,
he's probably
just skipping school.
[TAKEZO]
Oh.
I see.
Thanks, anyway.
[TETSUKI]
Get it together, Chika.
[TAKEZO]
I wonder if something happened.
Did Hozuki make him mad?
Is that it?
Do you think I'd stay here
after she said all that crap?
I quit, four‐eyes!
Nah, he'd never do that!
To be fair, though.
It's not like I know Kudo
exceptionally well or anything.
[TAKEZO]
It'll be fine!
He'll come tomorrow,
I'm sure of it!
Huh?
He went home already?
Why though?
What exactly is he sick with?
Uh.
I don't know the details.
Sorry 'bout that.
[TAKEZO]
Kudo?
Wait! We're on the third floor!
[SATOWA] I knew he was
nothing but a delinquent.
[TAKEZO] And just like that,
a whole week had passed.
Yeah. I'm sorry, I guess he
had some things to go do,
so he bailed early again today.
Hey, Takaoka?
Yes?
Are you hiding
something from me?
[TETSUKI]
Please don't be mad, Kurata.
Chika made me swear that
I wouldn't tell you anything.
But you should know.
[TAKEZO]
Hozuki!
[STUDENT F] Why don't you watch
where the heck you're going?
[TAKEZO] It's those guys
from the light music club.
Oh. I'm so sorry!
[STUDENT G] Hey, he's the guy
who gave that lame presentation.
[STUDENT F]
Wait, for real?
[STUDENT G]
Yeah, from the koto club!
[STUDENT F] Oh right, man, that
performance was super pathetic.
Totally, he probably
scared everyone away!
Is that sad or what?
Leave him alone, idiot.
[STUDENT F]
Well, good luck, loser!
[SATOWA] If anything, you're
the ones who will need the luck.
You have some nerve belittling
another person's performance
when your own show
was completely out of tune.
Perhaps that free time would be
better suited for practice.
[gasps]
Wow, that was amazing.
Hozuki!
I need you to
please come with me!
That's the place.
Hold on.
This is the music store
where we sent the instruments.
Oh, hello there.
I'm guessing you guys
are Kudo's friends?
[TAKEZO]
Do you know him? Is he here?
Yeah, he's inside. Go on in.
[CHIKA]
Ow!
[SHIZU] Idiot! That's why
I say to do it carefully!
Yeah. Got it, okay?
[SHIZU] Don't you dare raise
your voice at an old lady!
I'm only letting you
help because you're
so annoyingly stubborn,
so show some gratitude!
Learn to respect your elders,
you punk.
Yeah, well that punch didn't
feel very elderly like,
ya old hag!
[SHIZU]
Who are you calling a hag?
[CHIKA]
That hurt!
Um. Okay.
Uh?
I should probably explain.
A week ago,
when we got the repair
request for the instruments.
Kudo showed up here
without warning.
Um.
It's actually my fault
all the kotos got broken.
So please let me help fix them.
[NISHINA]
Man.
He sure took me by surprise.
But as you can see,
granny is no pushover.
[SHIZU] Tell me exactly
how you broke them.
Like I'd really let
someone who did this
to the kotos touch them again!
Get lost!
[NISHINA] But he kept
coming back day after day.
He sat outside
the store for hours
without eating or drinking.
So I kinda gave in.
Then, Granny
finally gave in, too.
But said she'd only let him help
if he told her how
the koto got broken
and why he wanted to fix them.
[TAKEZO]
So then, you know about Kudo?
Yeah, I do.
We know about everything.
I'm sure it's probably
a pretty difficult thing
for Kudo to talk about,
but he told us his whole past.
Why's he doing this?
Because he wanted
to "earn what it takes."
[NISHINA]
He said, "I may be an idiot,
and I don't know if it's okay
for a guy who
damaged one to play.
But if I'm at least
acknowledged by someone
who can make
and repair the koto,
then I can earn what it takes.
"And maybe I'd be able
to proudly face the koto."
Is something wrong?
That idiot.
Just how simple‐minded
can he be?
I'm honestly amazed.
As for the sound he produces,
I'm sure it's just
as brash as he is.
I'm not sure.
Um, hey.
I'm really sorry,
and about earlier, thank you.
You were right
about what I wanted.
About nationals.
It was just a dream,
but I wanted to make it.
But after failing
so miserably last year.
Well, I guess I was afraid of
trying to aim higher than that.
Because I couldn't
face losing again.
Well,
I suppose I did come off
as a bit arrogant at first.
It's my first time
being in a club,
so I'm not entirely sure
what attitude to have.
It's going to be a bit of
an adjustment for me.
But I'll do my best to learn,
so let's start over.
May I please have permission
to join the koto club?
Of course!
Excellent!
So then, now
we can officially aim
for first place
at nationals, right?
[TAKEZO]
Ugh.
I guess some things
aren't gonna change.
However, I'll have you know.
Even though I'm
aiming for first place,
I didn't pick just
any old school.
Huh?
I don't understand.
Hold up, what are
you guys doing here?
[SHIZU] Hey! Be more
careful with those tools!
I swear, you're a lost cause!
Oh?
These your friends from school?
Yes. We're members
of the koto club.
Ah. I suppose you must
having a hard time of it,
especially with this
moron for a member.
Might you be...?
So, uh...
Can we help with anything?
Like maybe with
repairing the instruments?
We are members of
the same club, after all.
Yes, it would our
pleasure to assist you.
[gasps]
Hey!
Are you guys kidding?
I don't need any
of your stupid help!
Besides, you can't
barge in here.
It took forever to get
her to approve of me!
[SHIZU]
Sure, the help would be nice.
Thank you so much.
You mean, wishy‐washy
old hag, why do they get in
so easy after I had
to work so freakin' hard?
And while I'm at it, remind
me to kick Tetsuki's ass
the next time I see
that stupid blabbermouth!
[SATOWA] Can you hear
how annoying you are?
Well sorry!
Didn't mean to offend little
Miss Koto Queen, just shut up!
[TAKEZO] Next time:
"The Koto Club Reborn."