[SATOWA] Mister Takinami?
About the title of the piece.
[TAKINAMI] "A bow in
the heavens". So, "Tenkyu"?
That's right. I originally
thought of the title "Rainbow",
but I was afraid it
was too obvious.
Why "Rainbow" specifically?
Well. It often comes
right after the rain stops.
I thought it was kind
of like our smiles.
And of course,
there's seven of us.
[TAKINAMI laughs] A rainbow
with seven colors, huh?
Yeah, real original.
You don't have to laugh at me!
Right, sorry. Look, I think
it's a great title.
It just needs a little tweak.
All I did was change
the character here,
but it still reads as "Tenkyu".
I see. With that change,
"The Heaven's Cry"
would be the new title.
Which sounds sad.
I can see that,
but hear me out.
Tenkyu with "cry" is like
the rain that falls
even when there're no clouds.
It's just my impression,
but to me,
it portrays the rain that
falls from a clear blue sky.
People cry for
different reasons,
it doesn't have to be
limited to sadness.
Alright. It's strange, but in
a way I think you might
understand this piece
better than I do.
Yeah. Maybe. After all,
if I don't understand it,
then I wouldn't be able
to give you guidance.
[chuckles]
[TAKINAMI]
I'm glad the piece has a title.
But, there's still something
else they really need.
Oh, Mister Takinami. Excuse me.
Do you have a minute?
[gasps]
What's this? Oh, are you
sitting behind me now?
Huh? Wait, are you in
front of me, Kurata?
[TAKEZO] I feel bad that
they moved us together.
Counting the club it doesn't
give you much time
away from me, huh?
It's okay!
If anything, I'm happy!
[TAKEZO]
Uh... um...
[HIRO gasps]
'Cause. You know...!
Uh, this makes it easier
to talk about club stuff!
Yeah. You're right.
That's a good point.
[HIRO] Man, that was close.
Good thing he's so dense.
[HIRO gasps]
[HIRO] Wow. Thank you, God!
I'll work hard on club stuff!
I'll work super hard!
[DOJIMA] I'm from Iktah Style;
Koto Hozuki School.
Nice to meet you,
I'm Ms. Dojima.
Recently it came to my
attention that Satowa Hozuki,
the daughter of our grandmaster,
attends the koto club
at this school.
Naturally, we would love
to show you our support.
If there's anything at
all we can do to help,
please don't hesitate to ask.
[HIRO] "Tenkyu"? Wow.
That title sounds kinda pretty.
The imagery of it is amazing.
[TAKEZO]
Hello there.
Well, it seems like
we're missing
a couple of club members.
Yeah. Kudo and the others
have cleaning duty... today.
Hello again, Satowa.
Good to see you.
Oh. Miss Dojima. It's you.
Do you two know each other?
Yes, you could say that.
I'm Akira Dojima from
the Hozuki school.
It's a pleasure to
meet all of you.
[HIRO, TAKEZO gasp]
Starting today. I'll be giving
you all koto lessons
as your new instructor. I look
forward to working with you.
Huh? Koto lessons?
[HIRO] And she's from
the Hozuki School?
[SATOWA gasps]
[HIRO] Okay spill it,
what's the meaning of all this?
She literally just told you,
what don't you understand?
It's not the what,
it's the why!
Move aside, buddy! Today I'll
be the first one there!
Yeah, right!
[CHIKA gasps]
[TAKINAMI grunts]
You total idiots.
So awesome,
we were like dominoes.
What the...?
So, Mister Takinami.
Why are these boys
interrupting the club?
[TAKINAMI] Sorry, they can
definitely get a bit rowdy.
They're the other
koto club members.
You're teasing me, aren't you?
Afraid not.
[KOTA] Mister Takinami,
who is this lady?
Starting immediately,
she's going to be your
new koto instructor.
[CHIKA]
Huh?
[HIRO] And get this,
she's from the Hozuki School.
[CHIKA gasps]
I don't understand,
I thought you were going to
guide us, Mister Takinami.
Yes, that's right.
I can guide you.
Well, at least on the
piece as a whole.
But right now the koto club
needs something I can't give,
to improve your technique.
No matter how outstanding
one's musicality is
or how deeply it
can touch people,
if their technique is inferior,
they can't win in a competition.
And while I understand music,
I don't have the ability
to teach you the koto.
Yeah, that's why
we've got Hozuki.
Why can't we keep everything
the way it is?
Hozuki's busy. She needs to
focus on her own practice.
[SATOWA gasps]
[TAKINAMI] Have you ever thought
about how hard it is to teach
others while you're playing?
You lose a lot of your own
practice time that way.
Or maybe you think Hozuki
doesn't need to practice.
Is that it?
Hopefully that
answers everything.
I'll let you practice.
For today I'd like to get to
know your playing abilities,
so I'll just observe you.
[SATOWA] I don't disagree that
it would be better if we had a
koto teacher, but why does
it have to be Miss Dojima?
What do I do if she's trying
to pull something on the club?
What if something bad
happens because of me?
[TAKINAMI]
Hozuki.
Look, I don't want you to
worry about anything.
It'll be fine.
Just focus on practicing.
Okay, then.
[TAKINAMI]
Right. Get to it.
Okay. Here's the sheet music
for the piece they're doing.
Let's take a quick look.
Strange, I've never
heard of this song.
Because it's an
original piece.
Oh, I see. In that case,
I'll need to take the time to
familiarize myself with it.
[gasps]
So, what do you think?
Now that you've
watched their practice?
Well, to be honest...
...I'm disappointed to
see their skill level
is lower than I expected.
[gasps]
[AKIRA] I'm guessing that
Satowa has been the one
teaching everyone,
but unfortunately her teaching
must have been quite sloppy.
[CHIKA, SATOWA grunt]
Those are some pretty
arrogant statements.
Do you have the skills
to back them up?
I'm sorry, but what
do you mean, exactly?
Like, are you a better
player than Hozuki?
Teaching the koto and
playing the koto
aren't mutually
exclusive skillsets.
However, Satowa did play
this piece once before
in the National
Koto Competition,
but she was
ultimately disqualified.
And I was the one who won first
place in that same competition.
[gasps]
Is that answer
satisfactory to you?
[HIRO] Ugh! Who does
she think she is?
"Is that answer satisfactory?"
Stuck up much?
Yeah, I don't like her, either!
I bet you anything she's
planning to mess up our club,
just like I was before!
Please calm down, Kurusu.
[SHIZU] If I remember correctly,
the winning piece for that
competition was
"Mizu no Hentai."
[SATOWA]
"Mizu no Hentai"?
[KOTA]
That sounds weird.
[SATOWA] It's a piece about how
water can change its form.
It also requires some singing.
It's very difficult.
Can you imagine playing the koto
and singing at the same time?
In that competition, if no
one is worthy of first place,
then no one wins at all.
End of story.
[SATOWA]
Her ability has been proven.
In which case, she's perfect
for improving our skills.
And Mister Takinami
has faith it'll be fine.
But... what if this
decision is wrong?
[HIRO] Listen, Hozuki! You don't
have to force yourself!
If you don't like it,
then just say so!
Don't do this just because it's
best for the club or whatever!
[SATOWA gasps] This again.
When it comes down to it,
the club has always
been there for me.
There's no longer time to
hesitate or shrink away from
Miss Dojima and her grandmother.
But for them, this is
their last opportunity.
I think we should use
her to the fullest.
[KOTA gasps]
Her abilities are
already proven,
and Mister Takinami told
me that it would be fine.
I'm sure she'll
be a good teacher.
We'll learn as much as we can
and hope that she
teaches us properly.
But if for some reason
she doesn't do that,
well, then we'll just show
Miss Dojima the door.
[ALL]
Whoa. It's dark Satowa!
Is this what you want?
Are you sure?
Yes. And if we want to win,
then we do need to
improve our technique.
Okay.
Hold on. Are you two serious?
We are. Complaining won't
get us to nationals,
so let's give her a chance.
That way our
decision's informed.
[HIRO grunts]
Maybe. I wonder what Chika's
opinion is on all this?
He's been busy practicing,
but I'll go get him.
[TAKINAMI] Have you ever
thought about how hard it is
to teach others while
you're playing?
[AKIRA] But unfortunately
her teaching must have
been quite sloppy.
I'm disappointed to see their
skill level is lower
than I expected.
Yo, Chika, do you feel like
taking a quick break?
We're trying to figure out the
whole Dojima dilemma.
Seriously. You asleep?
[SANE gasps]
Chika?
[DOJIMA] Akira. How was
the koto club today?
Most of them haven't even
mastered the basics yet.
I highly doubt there's anything
worth being concerned over.
Still, the only way to be
certain is to nip it in the bud
before it has the chance to
become a bigger problem.
We need to make sure they
understand the difference
between their abilities and
those of a more serious
koto player such as yourself.
We must make that silly
girl aware that she's
no longer welcome
in the koto world.
You understand, don't you?
I do, grandmother.
How annoying.
Today we'll focus on
going back to the basics
and learn to play a single note
both firmly, and carefully.
One note?
Come on, that stuff
is for beginners!
[AKIRA] And that's why
you need to practice it.
Now, please begin.
♪
Are you taking this lightly
because it's only a single note?
Try to understand.
Performances are a group of
notes that are connected.
♪
[CHIKA, TAKEZO gasp]
[AKIRA]
Like this. Now, do it again.
♪
Hozuki's playing?
You don't have to participate
in this part, Satowa.
It's fine. It's always good
to practice the basics.
Next, I want you to play
from the kin string
through the tenth. But play
them in a way that you give
every single note the
exact same weight.
♪
It's important to make sure
that they all sound even.
Play the notes at a fast tempo
and go down the whole scale.
♪
[CHIKA] What's this?
This should be a simple pattern,
but the notes sound kinda
messy for some reason.
Your sounds aren't clear at all,
they're running together.
Let's move on.
We'll try something else.
[AKIRA] This is a variation
of two-finger picking.
Go up the scale from strings
one and five, two and seven,
three and eight, and so on,
then back down.
After that, try playing
closer strings.
From one and three, so on and
so forth. Quicken the tempo.
Alternate the process
and repeat.
♪
That's enough. Is it possible
that none of you realize
how muddled your sounds are?
[KOTA grunts]
You're not paying attention
to what each note
sounds like by itself.
You're taking the
notes too lightly,
and play them even
if they aren't clear.
The volume of the fingers
playing has to be the same,
or the notes won't be uniform.
[CHIKA gasps]
What is that supposed to mean?
[AKIRA] You're playing each note
at a totally different volume.
That's why they're not
uniform and sound muddled.
And as a result,
your rhythm is thrown off.
♪
[gasps]
This is what it sounds like
when the notes are uniform.
Go ahead and give
it another try.
[SANE]
Chika? Uh, you good?
What is it? If you have a
problem with me, then leave.
Play it one more time.
[gasps]
I couldn't see very well
because I'm in the back,
so do it again.
I'm your teacher, so you should
address me more politely.
[CHIKA gasps]
Can you please play it again?
♪
[BOTH gasp]
[AKIRA]
When using alternate picking,
don't use just your thumb.
[TAKEZO]
These notes sound messy, too.
I've played these
patterns before
in several of our performances.
Back then I thought I
was playing them okay,
but now when I play
them separately,
none of them sound clear.
Please stop playing.
This is getting nowhere.
It's surprising that you're
aiming for nationals
with your skill level.
You don't have to be so rude.
You aren't worthy of playing
the piece, "Tenkyu" yet.
Instead, practice the basics.
That's what I want you to
do for the rest of today.
That will be more
suitable for you.
[TAKEZO] Hozuki. Would it be
okay to practice "Tenkyu"
at Miss Nishina's place?
[SATOWA]
Yes, of course.
[TAKEZO]
About what we learned.
[KOTA gasps]
Okay, what the heck's
going on with you?
How could you go along with
whatever that girl said?
Huh? Why wouldn't I?
[HERO] It's obvious Miss
Dojima looks down on Hozuki
and the club!
[KOTA]
She's right!
And normally you're the first
one to get upset! So what's up?
We're terrible players,
that's what's up.
[HIRO, KOTA]
Huh?
If we were just better,
then she'd have no reason
to look down on us.
So I wanna improve
as soon as possible.
[HIRO gasps]
Because I'm gonna go to
nationals, with everyone here.
And I'll do whatever it takes.
[SANE] I think it was Chika
who was the most frustrated.
When she insulted us.
Because in the end, this club,
and all the people in it,
are really special to him.
[HIRO gasps] Leave it to me to
say something stupid again.
I'm such a screw up.
There's still a lot of things we
need to do before we complain!
[KOTA]
Mm!
[chuckles]
[SANE]
So let's hammer out basics!
That way, we'll be worthy
of the song, "Tenkyu"!
[door clatters]
Kudo? Wow, you're really early.
[CHIKA]
Yeah.
Your hand is too flat.
Here, I'll show you.
No!
[SATOWA gasps]
[CHIKA] You don't have to worry
about me. You should practice.
[SATOWA]
You're so stupid.
What?
You're worried about what Mister
Takinami said, aren't you?
And since you're stupid,
you accepted it. So stupid.
You insulted me three times!
Look, like it or not, I'm not
going to stop helping you.
But you should be focusing
on your own stuff!
[SATOWA]
I've heard enough. Listen.
Teaching you guys in the club
has never been a burden to me.
Never, you understand?
[SATOWA]
Now, move.
The 17-string is hard because
the amount of strength
you use is different compared
to the thirteen string.
♪
[CHIKA]
Weird, it's the same basics,
but depending on the player,
it sounds completely different.
Hozuki's tones are strong,
but somehow soft.
I'm not sure how to put it.
They are very clear.
Unlike my sounds, hers have
no unwanted noise at all.
It sounds like every
single note has meaning.
I wanna play like this, too!
One more time!
[SATOWA gasps, giggles]
[SANE]
Hold it right there!
It's not fair that only
Chika knows how to do it!
[ALL] Play it again so
we can see it, too!
Ever heard of personal space?
How do you guys have so
much energy this early?
Wow, What a relief. At least
everything's back to normal.
Yeah, but I was the complaining
the most, so I should apologize.
It's okay. Besides,
you were only upset
because you're worried
about Hozuki's well-being.
[HIRO gasps]
And in then end,
I thought that's why it'd be
okay to accept the new guidance.
[gasps]
Oh. Hey, guys?
Do ya have a second?
[CHIKA]
Yeah, what's up, specs?
It's about practicing
the basics.
[ALL]
Hm?
[SATOWA] Four, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
Two, two, three, four.
Three, two, three, four.
What is this?
They said they made
their own arrangement
of the basic practice.
They're using the patterns from
"Tenkyu" containing the basics
so that'll help when they
play the song for real.
They all pitched in their ideas,
like playing the parts
in order like a relay.
They had a few, actually.
Kind of cool, huh?
[SATOWA] Two, three, four.
Two, two.
Yes, Miss Dojima?
This club still hasn't
mastered the basics, yet.
This level is far too
advanced for them.
I mean honestly, that's how
you neglect the fundamentals.
So then, let's use today to
correct your attitude
toward the koto.
♪
[KOTA, HIRO gasp]
[TAKEZO]
Oh wow.
Since when could he play
those notes so clearly?
♪
[gasps]
[HIRO] His playing is
seriously amazing!
[SATOWA]
As always, he surprises me.
Don't worry, we're not
neglecting anything.
[SANE] His sounds are completely
different from before!
But not long ago, they sounded
really similar to mine!
We don't have that much time
left before the qualifier.
So, if you don't mind, can you
start giving lessons on "Tenkyu"
while including the
basic practice?
Yes, of course. I'll work
with you each individually.
Until then, please practice on
your own until I make it to you.
[AKIRA] Satowa. I'm sure you
don't need my help, right?
Oh, it's fine. If you have
any advice, I'd happily take it.
[AKIRA] You want advice from me?
You must be joking.
No, I'm being serious.
I heard that you actually won
that competition with the piece,
"Mizu no Hentai".
I think that's incredible.
[gasps]
[AKIRA] Satowa.
Can I ask you something?
[SATOWA]
Sure.
[AKIRA]
Of all the pieces you could do,
why did you pick this one?
Mister Takinami is the
one who suggested it.
I also thought it was
a good opportunity
to face this piece head on.
[AKIRA]
"Face" it?
Oh. I see.
So then, Is it okay if
I ask you something?
What is it?
It's just that,
I heard you're not getting
paid to do the tutoring.
Doing it twice a week requires
quite a bit of your time.
So why are you doing it?
[AKIRA] All this time...
All this time.
All this time. All this time...
[AKIRA] I haven't been able to
see the light since that day.
I just wanted to
know what it was.
What on earth could you want
so badly, that you would throw
everything away and ruin the
lives of those around you.
What?
[AKIRA]
It's this club, right?
I'm interested to know
its value. That's all for now.
[AKIRA] I can't even remember
what the light looked like.
[TAKEZO]
Next time: "Confrontation."