[SATOWA] I still don't
understand this piece.
I'm not sure what kind of
musical theme we should have.
The explanation is
pretty lacking.
[TAKINAMI] I can't believe
you're still at it
when it's so hot outside.
[SATOWA]
Mister Takinami.
Uh, hold on!
[SATOWA]
When it comes to music,
do you have any
kind of experience?
No. You forget?
I said that I don't have any.
But what about the
upbeat this morning?
[CHIKA]
Yo, Teach!
[TAKINAMI]
My, I'm suddenly popular.
What is it now?
It's this!
No matter how much we practice,
we just can't get our
duet to sound right.
Why do you guys even
bother asking me for help
when you know I don't
actually care?
I've got it!
You and Kurata are kind of
like koto teammates, right?
Trust in your teammate!
[CHIKA gasps]
Jeez, let's go, Kudo.
‐‐We'll just figure it out‐‐
‐‐That makes sense!
Come on, four‐eyes!
Are you serious?
Did that make sense to you?
[TAKINAMI laughs]
Man, that Kudo kid is really
something else, isn't he?
Does "something" mean moron?
Yeah, that's what you say,
but you've basically
committed yourself
to these morons at this point.
You good with that?
I'm not following you.
It's like I said.
If you continue to
play with them,
you're bound to get
worse as a result.
And yet you're still
determined to stay?
Yes, I am.
Because the sound I'm searching
for is here in this koto club.
[SATOWA]
On top of that,
you're underestimating them.
They're all working hard
and improving quickly.
So I can't afford to
slack off either.
Right, listen up.
From here on out, I'm gonna
put my trust in you.
Okay.
I'm not gonna wait
for you to play.
[gasps]
[TAKEZO]
So that's what he meant.
Right!
[TAKEZO] Up until now, I've been
listening to Chika play,
and then I'd start
playing myself.
That's why, when the
tempo got faster,
my hand couldn't keep up and it
wouldn't sound good together.
[CHIKA] I can't listen
to his performance
before starting my own.
[BOTH]
I need to play... and believe...
...that his notes will
come right after mine!
[koto plays]
‐‐[TAKEZO] Amazing!
‐‐[CHIKA] Awesome!
[BOTH] The notes are
where I want them to be!
[BOTH gasp]
Incredible!
You hear that?
We were so in sync!
Yeah, we sounded
like one person!
[CHIKA]
I've got it!
I really feel like I understand!
This sound belongs to me now!
Man, this is so fun.
Let's do it again!
[TAKEZO]
We'll up the tempo this time!
[SATOWA] Now that the
duet is coming along,
we should try and make it
sound more like singing.
I'm not sure whether that
actually makes sense
or not, though.
What do you mean?
Let's see. Right now it's
like "taka taka taka,"
which sounds kind of
flat and has no dynamic.
♪ Talalala tilalila.
Talalila lilalila. ♪
See? Vary the levels and
it sounds like singing.
Singing, huh?
Oh. I guess I didn't
explain it well.
Nope. It would be way easier
if you just played it for us.
Yeah. And we should
probably work on
the first koto's solo
a bit more anyway.
Hey, I was wondering.
I've been struggling a bit
about what kind
of piece this is.
I'm still not sure what
kind of musical theme
we should go for with it.
[ALL gasp]
What was the introduction
for the piece?
[SATOWA]
All it says is:
"Leap through time like
the wind and wish."
Wind and wish. I see.
You know what?
It's like right now.
This amazing moment.
Yeah, how so?
Well, it's different
from a few months ago.
I never imagined that I'd being
playing the koto one day.
If I hadn't joined the club,
then I never would've
become friends with
you, Takezo, and Hozuki.
It's a lot more fun
than I expected,
but I also know that moments
like these are kinda fleeting.
So sometimes, I wish
I could find a way
to make these days last
forever, you know?
I do. Honestly.
[SATOWA] "Leap through time
like the wind and wish."
Okay, to finish things off,
let's do one final run through.
Kota.
You'll be fine!
I believe in you.
[koto playing]
[HIRO] All right,
we're almost at the part
where Kota usually
has a hard time
coming in strong on the upbeat.
[TAKINAMI] All you need
to do is burn the image
of what we did just
into your mind.
Hammer it into your head.
[KOTA]
One, two, three.
[KOTA gasps, laughs]
[ALL panting]
Wow. That was cool.
You know,
it's weird, but I think we've
all gotten a lot better!
Yeah. Me, too!
It feels different from
everything else we've played!
Hey, what do you think?
Good, right?
Our playing's improved!
[TAKEZO]
Kurusu. Thank you so much.
Huh? For what?
Uh, well, if you hadn't
asked permission
for us to use this place,
then we wouldn't be able
to practice this much!
So I'm just grateful‐‐
Oh, you can always thank me
by treating me to
something nice!
Uh, 'kay.
[TAKEZO]
Thank you so much.
[TAKEZO] Right! That
concludes the training camp!
Good work! Let's go home
and get some rest.
Aren't you goin' home, Chika?
[CHIKA] Nah, I'm gonna stay
here and practice a bit.
‐‐[SANE groans]
‐‐Hey! No fair!
I wanna practice, too!
[SANE] No way I'm gonna
let you guys surpass me!
Jeez! Guess I'll have
to stay and supervise.
[TAKEZO chuckles]
[KOTA] So sometimes,
I wish I could find a way
to make these days
last forever, you know?
I'm going home.
I've had more than enough
of your youthful, "friendship
is magic" stuff. Bye.
[TAKEZO]
Oh! Thanks for your help!
[TAKINAMI]
Whatever.
Here's a rock from
our training camp.
[GEN] The sound you make when
you play with your friends,
it's not something you can
produce by yourself.
[CHIKA] I think I understand
what you meant now.
[CHIKA]
At least a little.
[SHIZU] The festival's just
around the corner, huh?
Oh, and some of the
other high schools
have nationals right before it.
Weird, but weren't
the preliminaries
all the way back in December?
It seems like a really huge gap.
Yes, it certainly is.
I do wish they'd consider the
timing of it all a little more.
[CHIKA]
Hm?
[CHIKA] Hey, do you remember
at training camp,
when you asked us what kind of
piece we thought "Kuon" was?
Did you ever figure it out?
I'm pretty sure Mizuhara did.
He really hit the mark
with what he said.
Kota did?
Yeah, he talked about
how amazing moments
like these are quick to
sometimes fly away from us.
And that makes us wish
that it would never end.
[SATOWA] It was the same
with "Ryuuseigun."
If we can just identify
with the song somehow,
then we can put emotion
into it that way.
[SATOWA]
What is it?
[CHIKA] Nothin'. I was
thinking it looks like you're
havin' a lot of fun, is all.
[gasps]
Do you like playing the
koto with us that much?
[SATOWA] I just happen
to like it here, okay?
[gasps] Hey!
[SATOWA gasps]
[gasps]
Man, that was close.
You really need to
be more careful.
I don't know what we'd do if
you'd gotten hurt or somethin'.
[SANE]
Chika.
I can't trust you alone with
Hozuki for a minute, you dog!
I didn't do anything!
‐‐[SANE, CHIKA yelling]
‐‐Good morning! Uh, hey.
What's up with all
the shouting, guys?
[SANE yelling]
[CHIKA] I won't mention the
part where I accidentally
touched her chest
when I caught her.
[TAKEZO] Listen. I have
the performance order
for the festival.
Oh, what's our number?
It looks like we're
number 24 out of 33 groups.
At a tournament, all the
schools play one after another.
After that, the judges
give us scores,
which determine our rank.
[TAKEZO]
For right now,
we just need to focus
on what's ahead.
Let's give these last
few practices our all.
[MITTSU, SANE, KOTA]
Yeah!
[TAKEZO] Before we knew it,
it was time for the big event.
No way.
There's a crap ton of people!
[SANE]
It kind of feels like we're
the only guys here, though.
[TAKEZO] Well, koto clubs are
80 to 90 percent female.
What? Are you serious?
Isn't that obvious?
Where have you been?
[OUSUKE]
If it isn't the Tokise gang!
[MITTSU, SANE, KOTA, CHIKA gasp]
Hey, it's that dude
from Meiryo High!
Known as the koto club prince,
My name's Ousuke Kiryu!
[SANE] Hold up. You guys
are in this festival, too?
Yep, that's right!
[CHIKA]
Wait.
I thought you guys were also
participating in nationals.
How'd you do?
We lost big time!
But at least we placed
in the top four.
The club in first place
was really good.
By the way, Himesaka's also‐‐
You're here!
Satowa! Guess what,
we placed in the top four!
Isn't that impressive?
But I know if we had you,
then we could take
first place next time!
[CHIKA]
Denied.
Ew, gross, barbarian alert!
I suppose you'll be
playing today as well?
Yeah, but why do you care?
Oh, I don't.
I was only wondering
how much you suck.
As I recall at the
joint practice,
you said all you had to do was
catch up to the
mega talented Satowa.
An ape said that.
An ape said that!
Your insults are as
stupid as your hair.
Bye, Satowa! Good luck!
[CHIKA growling]
[KOU]
Ousuke.
You need to hurry.
Asano and Yoshiki
are asking for you.
Asa and Yoshi need me?
[OUSUKE]
Well, I should go.
Our group is first up
to perform, anyway.
Whoa, seriously?
[OUSUKE]
I heard going first isn't great
because you become the
standard for the judges,
so I was initially
pretty bummed about it.
But then I thought,
there's no problem as long as we
outshine everyone
who comes after us!
Ta‐dah, problem solved!
Later!
[SANE] So he says, as he
nonchalantly skips away.
[ASANO sighs] Honestly,
what is that Ousuke up to now?
Maybe he was chatting
up a cute girl?
Who knows?
I kind of miss the days
when he young and innocent.
Still, he has an amazing talent.
The way he changes
the atmosphere‐‐
A piece can shift.
And Ousuke's solos have
always been spectacular.
But I don't know
anyone more capable
of bringing out another person's
strengths in an ensemble.
[SANE]
Is this the concert hall?
[MITTSU]
Makes me kinda nervous.
[CHIKA]
No way.
Do all the people in here
really play the koto?
[TAKEZO]
Mm. It's pretty cool, isn't it?
[ANNOUNCER] Now starting:
the High School Students'
Kanto Region Traditional
Japanese Music Festival.
Hey, Hozuki.
Does the program say
what song they're playing?
"Hyakkafu."
Is it difficult?
It is. Both the rhythm
and technique are tough.
It's a piece that is supposed
to describe the four seasons,
and Winter is
especially challenging.
[SATOWA] The nationals
weren't that long ago,
which means they made it into
the top four with this song.
[SATOWA] Just what kind
of performance is it?
[MEMBER]
Is everyone ready? Here we go!
[ANNOUNCER]
First on the program.
I present Meiryo High School.
They'll be performing
"Hyakkafu."
[koto playing]
[TAKEZO]
Whoa.
What on earth?
[HIRO]
Unbelievable. These guys...
[SANE]
So this is an ensemble.
[SATOWA]
Amazing.
Even with this many
people and this rhythm,
it doesn't feel like
they're "fitting together."
They're just naturally together.
The more people in an ensemble,
the more differences you get
in tone quality and rhythm.
That's why, in order
to sound together,
most groups tend to play at a
fixed tempo with set dynamics.
They manage to sing,
even with a large group.
[SATOWA]
No. That's not it.
It's that boy.
He's leading them in a way
that allows them all to sing.
[SANE] Hozuki's notes
are close to perfect.
And ours make 'em
sound like trash.
[SATOWA]
As of a right now,
that's a skill that
I'm incapable of.
[SATOWA]
Summer. That's the first solo.
[CHIKA]
What the hell?
Is it just me, or is this
guy's sound kind of...
[TAKEZO]
At first, I thought the melody
was really beautiful,
but now it's...
[SATOWA] At this point
the sound is...
[ALL]
...piercing.
And when my mom found
out what happened,
‐‐she was so mad!
‐‐[BOY B laughs]
[OUSUKE]
Um...
Good morning.
[BOY B]
Huh? Who are you again?
[BOY A]
Oh, you're the kid who's been
hospitalized this whole time.
What do you want to do
after we get done?
Let's go outside!
[BOY A] We're gonna play some
soccer, you wanna come, too?
Huh? Oh, uh...
Um, sure!
Hey! It's comin' your way!
Huh? Kiryu?
[panting]
[OUSUKE'S MOM] You can't do
strenuous activities yet,
remember?
Yeah, it's this awesome
new game, you'd love it!
[OUSUKE]
Um, guys? Sorry for yester‐‐
Ugh, we got yelled
at by the teacher
because you couldn't keep up.
[OUSUKE]
I hate this.
Nobody's ever gonna want
to play with me again.
[OUSUKE sobbing]
[ASANO'S MOM]
Hello there.
We're the Izumi family,
we just moved in next door.
This is my daughter, Asano.
Hi, Ousuke! Wanna be friends?
[OUSUKE'S MOM]
I'm sorry, Asano, dear,
but Ousuke's been in poor
health his whole life.
[ASANO]
Ousuke, you there?
Come and play!
Guess what? I was
trying to figure out
a new place for us to
hang out and have fun,
and I found a really cool
spot not far from here!
Uh, okay, but...
Ta‐dah!
It's a koto school!
If we do this, it'll be
safe for you to play, too!
I can play, too?
[crying]
[OUSUKE]
Asa! Asa!
I love you!
[BOY C] Are you
boyfriend and girlfriend?
[BOY D]
That's so gross!
Well, you're stupid.
It's okay, Ousuke, don't even
worry about those dumb jerks.
Let's go!
I don't understand those
guys. What's the point...
[OUSUKE]
This isn't right.
She had to put up with
that, all because of me!
[OUSUKE]
I should leave her alone.
I have to‐‐
[ASANO]
Ousuke. It'll be fine.
[OUSUKE]
I don't... want to leave.
But if I'm gonna be with
Asa without hurting her,
then I need to really
think things through.
I need to watch and
understand people.
But don't get too close,
so they can't get
the best of me.
I'll come off as somebody
they shouldn't mess with,
and learn how to figure out
their thoughts and weaknesses.
Before I knew it,
I was able to read people
more than others could,
and I started to hear
all their sounds.
[SATOWA]
Summer and Autumn are over.
Here comes the ending.
[SATOWA]
It's time for Winter.
[koto playing]
[YOSHIKI]
Ousuke.
You really do know how to
bring out people's strengths.
I see that clearly now.
[YOSHIKI]
When someone plays with you,
you have this way of
making them better.
Even though I'm the coach,
I can't compare to that.
How do you do it?
[OUSUKE] I'm not really
doing anything special.
I guess I just understand
the person I'm playing with.
I listen to their sound,
and if there's something
I can do to help them,
then I'll do that.
You make it sound so simple.
You must really like
other people, huh?
[OUSUKE]
You're wrong, Yoshi.
The reason's not
as pure as that.
The truth is...
...the thought of
ending up alone again
terrifies me more
than anything else.
[OUSUKE]
All I'm trying to do is survive
and to make my way through
this colorful world we live in.
No more, no less.
[koto playing continues]
[TAKEZO]
It's so cold, it hurts.
[MITTSU]
The snowstorm is raging.
[STUDENTS applauding]
[CHIKA] This is just how I felt
when I heard Hozuki play.
[CHIKA]
Shit.
[OUSUKE]
There's no problem as long as we
outshine everyone
who comes after us!
Ta‐dah, problem solved!
[SATOWA]
So this... is a Meiryo concert.
[TAKEZO]
Next time, "Rivals."