[AKIRA]
But effective immediately,
I can no longer teach
your koto club.
Is there a reason why?
It's something we discussed
when I first started teaching.
Surely you remember. They were
the terms you proposed.
Naturally, we would love
to show you our support,
if there's anything at
all we can do to help,
please don't hesitate to ask.
I'd like to recommend
my granddaughter to you.
She'll make an excellent
koto instructor.
Koto instructor?
[DOJIMA] Yes, feel free
to look at her resume.
[TAKINAMI gasps]
Additionally, we will waive
the payment for this service.
But. We don't want to
take advantage of you.
[DOJIMA] Teaching others is a
wonderful learning experience
in itself.
I'm positive it will help Akira
grow as a performer as well.
It's your call.
I trust your judgement.
It's funny, but I was just
thinking about finding someone
who could give
them koto lessons.
If you're offering, then yes.
However. If I determine that
you're not helping them enough,
I'll ask you to resign
from teaching.
Does that sound
reasonable to you?
[DOJIMA gasps]
[TAKINAMI] I'm sorry if
that sounds rude, but the
instructor's compatibility with
the students and her quality
as a teacher will influence
their future performances.
I truly believe that our club
can go to nationals.
In fact, I know it.
My students have the potential.
And that's why if they
couldn't go to nationals
because of an inadequate
instructor, I'd be upset.
What?
That's fine. If the
time comes that,
you feel I'm no longer
qualified to teach,
then I give you
permission to fire me.
I do remember saying that,
but you haven't done anything
that would make me think you're
not qualified to teach here.
What if I think
I'm not qualified?
If I can't teach your students
the koto with confidence,
then it will only
make them worse.
I get it. Okay, then.
I can't force you to continue,
it's not as if you're
getting paid anyway.
I'm sorry to see you go.
Oh, but would you
mind continuing
until I can find
another instructor?
I'll find someone
as soon as possible.
[AKIRA]
Of course. Thanks.
[TAKINAMI] I know we didn't
have you for very long,
but I appreciate
what you've done.
I think you've helped
the kids improve
their skills quite a bit.
[TAKINAMI]
Hm.
So, thank you.
[AKIRA]
What was that? Sarcasm?
[AKIRA] It's obvious the
students all dislike me.
--[kotos playing]
--[AKIRA gasps]
[AKIRA]
What? Their sound.
[TAKEZO]
Miss Dojima?
Uh. Your tone.
It's only been a few days,
but your sound has
changed quite a bit.
It's quite impressive.
[TAKEZO]
Huh? You think so?
Why is it so different now?
[TAKEZO] Mm. 'Cause we
listened to your performance.
[AKIRA gasps]
And I know we probably
should have asked you
before doing that. We're sorry.
But, after we
finished listening
to your performance together,
we all stood up
without another word
and we started practicing
like our lives depended on it.
Watching you play
"Mizu no Hentai"
taught us something important,
and we finally understood.
Now. Because of you,
we know what it means to
treat every note with care.
Miss Dojima!
I've been practicing the
part you taught me,
I can play it now! Listen!
Say "Please".
Um, please!
[koto playing]
Done!
The rhythm isn't right at all.
[KOTA groans]
But I can see you're that
you're putting lots of care
into the notes. Nicely done.
[KOTA gasps]
Ha! Thank you!
[HIRO]
You look happy, Kota.
[KOTA]
Well, yeah!
I almost never get
compliments from teachers!
[HIRO chuckles] Oh, after you
taught me how to position
my arm correctly, pressing the
strings became much easier.
So. Thanks very much.
[AKIRA gasps]
Yeah, when I do something
that's wrong,
I can hear you saying stop,
even if you're not here.
[AKIRA gasps]
Satowa.
[SATOWA]
Miss Dojima. Um.
Could you please give us advice
on our ensemble again today?
[SATOWA]
We've been practicing a lot.
As much as we possibly can
when you're not around,
and even during our
after-club practice as well.
Still though. I'm not...
Uh. I'm not that
good at teaching!
[gasps]
[SATOWA] We tend to
stumble at the beginning
and can't play the piece
together very well.
But I don't know what to do,
I'm not sure what to tell
everyone so we can overcome it.
That's why we need your help.
Whoa. Hold on!
That sounds like you're
complaining about us!
No, I don't mean
it in a bad way!
[AKIRA] What could you ever
expect me to teach you?
[AKIRA] Even after I
pushed her away like that?
[AKIRA] I see, you're
disorganized from the start.
[grunts]
So then.
Let's practice separately.
We can start by pairing the
solo and the 17 string.
In this piece,
the 17 string serves
as the foundation and
the solo is the key.
For this to work, we must
first form a consistent
core with these
two parts together.
[BOTH]
We're the core?
You must be pretty excited, huh?
[AKIRA] Think of the
17 string and the solo as the
"root" and the
"trunk" of a tree.
Then the first and
second kotos are leaves
and blossoms that
lend color to it.
Depending on how the
first and second kotos
are played together,
the expression of the
piece changes quite a bit.
The first and second koto
parts chase each other
and have a lot of interplay,
so you should also
practice together.
After that, we'll go
back to the ensemble.
I think that will be the
best course of action.
I'll work with the 17 strings
and the solo first.
Sure, that sounds good.
♪
Hold on. You hear that?
You're being influenced
by the solo.
Sorry Chika, that was me.
If it's okay with you,
can we try again?
[SANE]
I've been practicing so much,
I thought I nailed
this part already.
♪
Sorry, can we
try one more time?
[SANE] Who knew mixing
in the solo would increase
the difficulty like this?
[AKIRA] Oh no. I was so absorbed
by the structure of this piece,
that I paired the
17 string and solo
without really
thinking about it.
Unfortunately, I might
have put this boy
into a tough situation.
This is a tricky bar with
irregular eighth notes.
Factor in the solo. Like how
it comes in with triplets,
then the piece becomes
even more difficult.
[SANE] I'm sorry,
but can we try again?
[SANE] This sucks.
I'm dragging them down.
Chika can play it with
no problem at all.
I don't want to keep
holding them back!
Am I listening to
the solo too much?
But I should listen to it
since it's an ensemble.
It won't work if I
get influenced.
I need to focus on my own sound.
I'm fine up to this point.
♪
[SANE]
Come on.
[gasps]
Dammit!
I'm sorry!
[SANE] Should I ask them to let
me practice alone for now?
No, this is all pointless if I
can't play along with the solo.
[AKIRA gasps]
[AKIRA]
I can't let this continue.
Right. Let's move on for now.
[gasps]
One more time.
We'll try one more time.
[SATOWA]
Starting from the same spot.
[SANE]
Huh?
Okay then. Miss Dojima?
Can I please keep trying
until I can do it?
[gasps]
Chika and Hozuki, will you
guys keep playing with me?
Strawberry au lait .
It's a deal.
I'm gonna charge you one drink
for every mistake you make.
For real?
[CHIKA]
Ice cream works, too.
[SANE]
Friggin' stingy!
[AKIRA] Keishi. Will you tell
me how to win first place?
[inaudible]
[KEISHI]
I kept failing over and over
and I even hurt myself once.
[gasps]
[laughs]
[AKIRA gasps]
[KEISHI] But I kept on trying,
and finally did it!
All right! Finally!
Did you guys hear me?
Looks like I won't owe you
too many drinks, Chika!
[SANE] Whoa, hey!
What's wrong, Miss Dojima?
[CHIKA]
Did something happen?
Uh. No, I'm fine. It's nothing.
Give me a minute, 'kay?
[ALL gasping, shouting]
[AKIRA sniffs]
Um.
This was a very
thoughtful gesture,
but it's too much.
[SANE] Right, yeah,
of course. He, he. Sorry!
Hey. What do you think
made her start crying?
Was it my bad playing?
Like I'd know!
Women are a mystery to me.
[AKIRA]
I promise it's nothing terrible.
I just got a little
dust in my eye.
Oh, makes sense!
I hate it when that happens,
you gotta blink like crazy!
Yeah, it's the worst.
Dust sucks.
Tell me something
I don't know!
I'm sorry if I worried you.
Let's move on, shall we?
[TAKINAMI]
So. What are you guys up to?
[TAKEZO]
We're practicing in two groups,
the 17 strings with
the solo are playing now.
I see. Hm.
♪
Aw man, I'm out of
sync again! Sorry!
We're using a metronome, but I'm
still all over the place.
[HIRO] Don't stress, Kota.
You'll be fine.
[HIRO gasps]
Hey. Why'd you stop it?
I forbid you guys to use the
metronome from here on out.
[ALL gasp]
But my sense of rhythm is
already terrible as it is!
[TAKINAMI]
If it really is that bad,
then taking away the metronome
won't make a huge difference.
How mean!
Besides,
this piece's arrangement
doesn't call for a metronome.
There's no reason to match
a sound that doesn't exist
in the first place.
Match the sounds around you.
That's the ensemble.
I've got it.
Miss Dojima... and Hozuki.
Can you show them
a good example
of what an ensemble
sounds like?
Miss Dojima can
play the bass koto,
while Hozuki
takes the solo.
[CHIKA gasps]
I wanna hear!
[HIRO]
Yeah! Me, too!
Oh. Are you sure?
[TAKINAMI]
I think they'll get it faster
if they can hear an example
instead of an explanation.
It'd be helpful.
[AKIRA sighs]
Please say yes, Miss Dojima!
I think it'd be fun to
play the koto. Together.
[AKIRA exhales]
If you insist.
[CHIKA]
Come to think of it,
I've never seen Hozuki play
with anyone besides us before.
I wonder if it'll be different
depending on who she plays with.
♪
[CHIKA gasps]
[SATOWA]
Our sounds. Expand.
[AKIRA]
They come together.
[SATOWA]
A new sound is born.
[AKIRA] We come to
know each other...
[SATOWA] ...and we accept
and improve one another.
[SATOWA, AKIRA]
Ever further and deeper.
Our sounds become one piece.
They become one world.
[AKIRA gasps]
[exhales]
[AKIRA]
Hm!
[ALL sobbing]
That was so beautiful!
I get it now, the ensemble
is all about
the interchange
of feelings!
That's something you're
all good at, right?
[BOYS gasp]
[TAKINAMI] Thanks to
Miss Dojima's lessons,
you're getting better
at facing a single note.
Your technique and
foundation are better, too.
You're now probably ready
to practice together,
but it's more than just sound.
I want you to look at the
piece in its entirety.
Understand its flow.
Think how your sound
goes together with others'
in that flow. Think about what
your sound means and its role.
I think I need a
translator to understand
what you're trying to say.
Can you dumb it down?
Analyze the piece. And think
about what it means.
Then face it head on.
Do those things, and you'll
find that your sound
will resonate deeper
than ever before.
[ALL] Okay, you got it!
We're all fired up!
Save that passion
for your practice.
[AKIRA] That's all for today.
Please put up your kotos.
[ALL]
Thank you for the lesson!
Next we've got
after-club practice, huh?
[MITTSU]
Yep.
So, uh. I can't help but wonder.
What's after-club practice?
There's a nice instrument
shop near here
that handles our repairs.
They let us use their kotos
so we can practice more.
What? So, you'll practice
more after this?
But don't you also
practice in the morning
and on your lunch break?
Yeah, I guess we're immersed in
the koto twenty-four seven.
But it's fun. We enjoy it.
You must love the koto to
dedicate yourself like that.
[TAKEZO] Hm. Sure, but you
love it too, right?
[AKIRA gasps]
[DOJIMA] Welcome home, Akira.
How are things at the club?
Do you think those
little brats are ready
to throw in the towel, yet?
I researched that
club a bit today,
and I discovered that they're
pretty low-ranked in the big
scheme of things. It's nothing
but delinquents. Shameful.
I doubt that any of
the kids in the club
are truly serious
about the koto.
[AKIRA gasps]
[DOJIMA] That Hozuki
girl hanging out with
a shady crowd like that!
She sure has hit rock bottom.
Wouldn't you agree?
Akira!
Please forgive
my weariness, Grandmother.
This day has been rather
long and exhausting,
may I please excuse
myself for the night?
Of course you may.
[DOJIMA]
Huh...
[ISAKI]
Jeez, Chika!
What have I said about
sleeping on the couch?
Can you hear me?
You're gonna get sick--
Oh, you're awake.
What are you listening to?
My own performance.
Hey, Isaki. Is there something
you think that I lack?
What? I think the bigger
question is what don't you lack?
Oh. Besides sugar,
you definitely eat
of plenty of that.
[CHIKA]
You're such a jerk.
[ISAKI laughs]
Come on, I'm teasing.
[CHIKA]
Okay, hag.
[ISAKI gasps]
How dare you call me a hag!
[CHIKA] So when Hozuki
plays with someone
on the same skill level as her,
it sounds like that, huh?
It was really good. It seemed
like she was having an easy time
playing and her performance
was better than usual.
[TAKINAMI] Think about what your
sound means and its role.
[AKIRA] You must love the koto
to dedicate yourself like that.
[TAKEZO] Sure, but you
love it too, right?
[AKIRA]
Excuse me.
[TAKINAMI]
Miss Dojima?
I thought you didn't
have a lesson today.
Oh, I don't, I just
wanted to talk to you.
What about?
Actually, before we
get into that part,
I'd like to ask you an
important question first.
Oh, and what's that?
Well, I was wondering.
Just how serious are you about
aiming for nationals this year?
[gasps]
[AKIRA] When you and I first
met, I thought you were serious.
But you don't come to
see the practices at all.
Then yesterday, you show up
and start giving them advice.
Is this all just a game to you?
Well, for the record,
I couldn't care less what
you think about me.
But I'm very serious.
There's not much I can do when
you guys are just practicing.
That's why I decided to
let you handle the basics.
[AKIRA]
Let me handle it?
Did you have any
problems teaching them
without me in the room?
Or do you need my supervision?
[AKIRA]
That's not what I meant,
but you're entrusting
your students
with a complete stranger.
And that's why I'm asking!
Two years.
[AKIRA gasps]
[TAKINAMI]
For two years,
you've seriously faced a single
piece and produced a result.
You even told me I had
permission to fire you
if I decided you
weren't good enough.
With that kind of resolution,
I felt like you
were trustworthy.
[gasps]
[TAKINAMI]
Does that answer your question?
Excuse me, I have
a class to teach.
[AKIRA] Hold on!
I want to keep helping!
[TAKINAMI grunts]
[AKIRA]
I'm sorry.
I know yesterday I said
I was going to quit,
and I don't want to cause
you any more trouble.
I'm worried I won't be good
enough to teach them.
But I promise you,
I'll do my best.
So please let me
continue to help!
[gasps]
[TAKINAMI]
Hm.
We would be honored
to have you.
[AKIRA]
It wasn't a waste of time.
[AKIRA] I spent two years
facing that piece,
and it's giving me the power
to stand here right now.
[AKIRA]
It was never a waste of time.
Oh, excuse me. Have you
seen my granddaughter?
Yes ma'am,
I saw her earlier as she was
heading out for the day.
[DOJIMA]
Oh.
[DOJIMA] What could
she possibly be doing
so early in the morning?
I suppose then,
I really must take action
before things go even further.
[CHIKA]
Next time, "Meaning and Role"