[SATOWA] All I wanted,
was to get it back.
That precious time.
[SATOWA]
I swore to myself
that I'd protect that place
with everything I had.
Nothing else mattered.
I didn't care what
people thought of me
or if they shunned me.
Mother!
I don't want to be alone!
Don't isolate yourself.
Don't push me away!
I promise that
I'll work hard with you!
[SATOWA] But, in the end,
playing the koto was all I had.
So, I staked everything.
All of it on my sound.
I wanted to fight for us,
and I thought that if
I just tried hard enough,
then my feelings would
finally get through to her.
Because I truly
believed in my sound.
[CHIHARU] Your koto playing
feels like a weapon to me.
A weapon?
[SATOWA] I haven't had
that dream in a while.
So, I don't understand.
Why now?
But, for them, this is
their last opportunity.
[SATOWA] What he said
reminded me of something.
I've avoided thinking about it,
but this life
can't last forever.
My time with the club
will eventually end.
What will I do
when that happens?
I see.
I suppose I'm still
afraid of being alone.
Pathetic.
[SATOWA]
For right now,
I just have to focus
on getting to nationals.
We have to make it
there together.
[HIRO]
Kurata?
Oh. Morning!
Here for some solo practice?
Kind of.
Yeah, that's why I'm here.
[HIRO]
I am such an idiot!
C'mon brain, we talked
about this yesterday!
Um. Are you okay?
[HIRO] It's all right
to have feelings for him,
but I won't tell him about them
until we're done with the club!
I can't let him figure it out.
I refuse to cause problems
for the club or our performance!
Those were our rules,
brain, remember?
And yet, there is one thing
I really wanna ask him.
Uh. Kurusu?
[HIRO]
Tell me something.
Do you like the old club
president, Mashiro?
[TAKEZO gasps]
What? You wanna know that, huh?
[HIRO]
Whoa. He's super rattled.
Does that mean?
I guess.
Yeah, I would say
that I do like her.
Okay. Good to know.
It's fine, don't panic.
I'll just focus on club stuff
and working hard.
I mean I like her as a person,
and I have a lot
of respect for her.
I'd say it's more admiration
than anything romantic.
I'm kinda curious
why you'd ask that, though.
Oh, I see!
[TAKEZO]
Huh?
Wait, aren't you
gonna tell me why?
[HIRO]
Huh?
You're here early, today!
[SATOWA]
Hiro. Takezo.
[CHIKA groans]
Dammit!
You guys all beat me?
[CHIKA] I was positive I'd
be the first one here, too!
What's up?
Besides your bed head?
Nothing much past that
wild mane you call hair.
Don't you make fun
of my hair, it's in style!
[SATOWA]
Huh?
I didn't know looking like a bum
was such a fashion statement.
Well, better to be a bum
than a stuck up princess!
Jeez!
Guess we're back to normal.
Oh nice, looks
like everyone's here.
[HIRO]
Good morning!
About the piece
for the qualifier.
Do "Yaegoromo."
Hold on.
Why "Yaegoromo"?
That's like a classical piece.
Is that suited for us?
Really now?
What I heard
sounded more modern.
You played it in
this performance.
[CHIKA]
No way!
I know that one,
I've actually seen it before!
You seriously think
we can play that piece?
[KOTA]
Wait, so you know this song?
[SANE]
Cool! Tell us all about it!
[SATOWA gasps]
But...
...this isn't the
real "Yaegoromo."
You'll have to pick
a different song.
[TAKINAMI]
Why?
[SATOWA]
This is a solo.
That's not a problem, I'll
change it to be an ensemble.
Listen.
A piece like this can't
reach the heart of anyone!
It won't take us to nationals.
So we can't play it!
Tell me.
Have you taken the time to
hear your own performance?
Fine, whatever.
Anyway, I'd like for all of you
to head on to the
audiovisual room.
We just got the video
for the last music festival.
We're going to listen to both
your performance
and to Hakuto's,
the school that won.
First, I'll play Hakuto's.
[MITTSU]
Whoa, what a weird formation.
[SANE] Why's he sitting up front
like he's the star of the show?
[TAKINAMI] Well, because
he is the star of the show.
[CHIKA]
That's him.
Wait, what is this?
Why?
It's not that flashy
by any means,
and yet his sound flows
right into my head.
[TAKINAMI] That's what
Hakuto's performance is like.
How interesting.
Yeah, to be honest,
classical music has
never really been my jam,
but this feels
different somehow.
[CHIKA] Of all the
performances I've ever heard,
this one is probably
the least showy.
But I can't seem to look away.
[SATOWA]
Their pauses and tempo.
It's like their sounds
build up quietly,
with just the right splash
of color at the perfect time,
as if it were all calculated.
[TAKINAMI] Hakuto may not have
the impressive togetherness
that Himesaka does, or the
flamboyant impact of Meiryo.
But their performance
basically serves as "the
right answer" to this piece.
"Right answer"?
I don't like using
that term for music,
but I do understand
what you mean.
To make a classical song
that entrancing
is quite the accomplishment.
You're wrong.
This isn't a classic piece.
The song that they
played was an original.
[SATOWA]
An original?
[TAKINAMI]
Furthermore,
I believe it was composed
in order to emphasize the
sound of the boy in the middle.
It was written so he could
be the core of this song.
Look at the structure
of the piece
and the sounds
of the other parts.
They're all carefully calculated
and arranged in a way
to make his sound
really stand out
and shine during
the performance.
It would appear that Hakuto
has a very talented
composer in their club.
[TAKEZO]
A composer.
If you guys are set
on going to nationals,
then you need to be able
to beat schools like Hakuto.
But you said that they
were the right answer.
How are we supposed
to beat that?
Easy, you have to
surpass the right answer.
Just because something is right
doesn't mean it's the best.
Next up is your performance.
At a glance,
it's pretty rough and relies
way too much on momentum.
You lack a lot of skills.
But you're capable of putting
your emotions into the music.
And that's your
biggest weapon right now.
So... if you ask me,
I think this piece
has the best potential
of bringing out that ability.
Even if it was a solo.
I can consider the
balance of your power,
as well as your sound quality,
and change the composition
to best suit each of you.
This is the piece I recommend,
but ultimately, it's up to you.
That's a tough decision.
[TAKEZO]
What should we do?
[SATOWA] Of all the pieces, why
did Mr. Takinami pick this one?
I don't get it.
[approaching footsteps]
[SATOWA]
Hm? Kudo?
I just feel like eating
my lunch over here today.
You said.
You've heard
this performance before?
[CHIKA]
Yeah.
When I was at
your place that one time.
Without asking me?
I did ask you.
You were kind of asleep.
And if I had to choose between
her tones from then and now.
I'd pick her current,
gentler sound.
In a damn heartbeat.
[SATOWA] What did you
think about this piece?
When you heard it?
Well, it hurt.
I mean.
It felt stressful.
[SATOWA]
No.
But why?
All I wanted was to be able to
make my mother smile again.
When I first heard your tone,
I thought it sounded
like screaming.
[SATOWA]
Hey.
Kudo?
I asked Takinami to export
the audio file from the DVD.
You still haven't listened
to your playing, have you?
No. I haven't had the chance.
I don't know what this
piece means to you,
or why you haven't had
the courage to face it yet.
But maybe we could
face it together.
[ANNOUNCER] Next up is entry
number 13, Satowa Hozuki.
[SATOWA]
This is what I sounded like?
Instead of making her smile,
all I managed to do
was express the pain
and suffering I was
going through at the time.
[exhales]
What a harsh sounding tone.
The feelings that I wanted to
convey aren't in this piece,
not even a little bit.
There was no way
I could have reached her.
I see.
[SATOWA]
What's wrong?
It's nothing. Thank you.
I'm fine now.
[SATOWA]
Mr. Takinami!
About what you said earlier.
Do you really think this song
can take us to nationals?
[TAKINAMI]
Hmm...
That's up to you guys.
So that will be the
basis for your next piece.
Now.
I'm sorry!
I don't know why I'm crying.
It just literally
gave me goosebumps!
[CHIKA] This was my
third time, so whatever.
[MITTSU] You guys
think we can really give
a tear-jerking
performance like this?
[SATOWA]
Well, um...
Honestly...
When I played this piece,
I was hoping the people
who listened to it
would want to smile.
Not cry.
No, I didn't mean
you have to force
yourselves to smile either.
I ended up putting the wrong
emotions into the piece
when I performed it.
But since we're going
to play it together,
I thought that maybe...
...we could make it
more positive this time.
[TAKINAMI]
Hmm...
I definitely think
that's possible.
So don't play like
what you just saw.
I'm gonna change up
the motif big time.
[KOTA]
Uh?!
Then why'd you
make us listen to it?
Yeah, that sound's engraved
into my very heart and soul!
It was necessary.
In order to be positive,
you had to hear what
it sounded like before
because the only way
to express yang is
if you can also express yin.
The more you understand a piece,
the better you can play it,
especially in this case.
[gasps]
[TAKINAMI]
Here, I wrote the score.
Make photocopies
and bind them for everyone.
Start on it after school today.
[TAKEZO] Wait, how were you
able to write it so quickly?
He must have
pulled an all-nighter.
[TAKINAMI]
Please.
You know how much I love sleep,
I'd never give it up for this.
Thanks, Mr. Takinami!
[TAKINAMI] Looks like
I've got a little time
before the teachers' meeting.
Whoa. He wrote that in a day?
Man.
He's so cool.
[SATOWA] Mind if I take
a quick look at the music?
[TAKEZO]
Go ahead.
How are the parts assigned?
What am I playing?
Dunno.
But I bet we can find out.
[CHIKA, SATOWA]
Huh?
Yeah, all right!
The 17-string!
Yo, same here!
What?
So you're both playing it?
Except.
Last I checked we
only have one 17-string.
[ALL]
Oh.
Goodness, at least now I know
where the students
get their bad habits from.
That's some nerve
you've got there, hot stuff.
But here's the 17-string
you asked to borrow.
Thank you, we appreciate it.
Wait.
When exactly
did you have the time
to ask about borrowing this?
[SATOWA] The introduction
starts with my solo.
♪ gentle melody ♪
Is this the introduction?
Wow.
So cool!
It might be the same melody
that we heard this morning.
But the new arrangement makes
it sound entirely different.
[CHIKA]
Her tone changed again.
It's become stronger.
It reverberates more.
She continues
to improve every day.
Sane.
Teach me the 17-string.
Huh?
You want me to teach you?
Yeah, you have more
experience with it than I do.
Uh...
Hozuki.
I meant to ask you before, but
what's the title of this piece?
Um.
I never chose one.
Well, at least now I know why
you lost sight of the emotions.
Hurry up and pick a title.
It's unconvincing without one.
Okay.
What do I do?
I'm really bad at
coming up with names.
[SANE]
Listen closely.
These are the strings
of the bass koto.
In my opinion, it's better
to sit closer to the middle
than you would
with a normal koto.
The sounds reverberate more.
[CHIKA]
Okay.
Now practice like
your life depends on it!
Understood!
[CHIKA]
Whoa!
Awesome!
It sounds somber!
I love the bass,
it resonates with my soul!
She made it look so easy
when she played it.
I'm not gonna let
her increase her lead.
I will catch up to her!
[CHIKA]
Hey.
Startin' today I think
we should go back
to usin' Granny's
place after school.
Hold on.
If you're planning to go to
Ms. Nishina's to practice more,
you two will have to take turns.
Huh?
Why should we?
[TAKINAMI] Well, we borrowed
one of her 17-strings.
Because of that, now she
only has one other bass koto
there that she can let us use.
So you can't practice
at the same time.
No problem.
We can just take this
one back and forth with us.
[TAKINAMI] I can't let you carry
around a borrowed instrument.
Look, it's sucks,
but you'll have to make do
with what we have
in the time we have it.
Tch! There's no choice.
Since we can't practice
together at Granny's place,
we'll just need to find
the time somewhere else.
Time to skip classes, Sane!
Right, you got it, boss!
You guys really
are idiots, aren't you?
I can't stay.
I have an important
errand I need to run,
but I'll see you tomorrow.
What?
Okay, sure.
It's weird for
Hozuki to skip out
on after school practice, huh?
[TAKEZO]
Mm.
[DOJIMA]
Oh?
What do we have here?
You're not the sort of visitor
we were expecting to see.
[SATOWA]
Ms. Dojima, and...
My granddaughter Akira.
You've actually met her before,
but it seems that
you've forgotten her.
Right, please forgive me.
So is there a reason
why you came back?
Did you also forget you
shamed the Hozuki name
and were driven out?
No, sorry, I came here
to talk to my mother.
And what about you, Ms. Dojima,
are you practicing
at this late hour?
You don't know?
After you left, Akira and I
became the grandmaster's
live-in apprentices
studying under her tutelage.
You live here?
Of course, after all,
not only did poor Chiharu
lose her husband,
but she also lost her only heir.
What your mother needs right now
is someone who will support her.
And, of course,
there's the matter of finding
a new heir for the school,
which must be
weighing on her terribly.
But never mind that for now,
you came to talk to
the grandmaster, right?
Why don't you
come inside, please?
Just a moment, Akira...
This girl...
She's the
grandmaster's daughter,
regardless of whatever happened.
She's still only a student.
It'd would be sad if she
couldn't see her mother.
Yes, that's a fair point.
You're truly such
a kind young woman.
Kindness?
No.
Hold on.
Grandmaster?
It's good to see you.
What are you doing here, Satowa?
I want you to leave.
[SATOWA]
Mother, please!
I came because
I need to ask a favor.
Oh?
Don't tell me you want
to come back to the school
after everything you've done.
You can't possibly
believe she'd accept you.
You see.
I've joined the koto club
that's at my high school.
So I'm still playing
the koto, every day.
But, for our next competition,
we're in need
of a 17-string koto.
Could you please let me
borrow one of yours?
You've been excommunicated
from the Hozuki School
and play the koto in
a club just for fun?
And now you want to borrow
one of our instruments?
I think that might be the most
shameful thing I've ever heard!
Excuse me, but I was
talking to my mother.
[DOJIMA gasps]
If I remember correctly,
you should already have
your own 17-string koto.
[SATOWA]
Yes, but I need one more.
There are no instruments in this
school that I could lend you.
Now please leave.
[TAKINAMI] To them,
this is their last opportunity.
That's what you get
for being such a rude girl.
You come here asking for favors
and that's the
attitude you have?
It's no wonder
she turned you down.
[gasps]
Please, I'm begging you.
Well,
this just keeps getting
better and better, doesn't it?
All this trouble
for a silly club.
Or could it be you're plotting
something more devious?
[AKIRA]
If you don't mind,
I'd be happy to
lend you my 17-string.
Is that all right with
you, Grandmaster?
You know.
Since it's my instrument.
[DOJIMA gasps]
Akira!
You don't mind?
It's fine.
I have one that's not
being used right now.
Plus.
Seeing you in
such a pitiful state
is just plain embarrassing.
Thank you for your kindness.
I refuse.
[gasps]
[CHIHARU] It's one thing for my
daughter to cause me trouble,
but I simply cannot allow her to
make trouble for my apprentice.
Take whatever koto you want.
But, in return, promise me that
you'll never come back here.
[SATOWA]
Thank you very much.
No matter what I'm told,
I won't ever give up on
trying to reach Mother.
I won't stop until my
true sound reaches her.
Never.
[DOJIMA]
I never imagined that Satowa
would still be playing the koto.
We have to ensure that there
isn't the slightest possibility
that she can come back
to the Hozuki school.
Right.
Akira?
[AKIRA]
Yes.
Grandmother.
No way!
[SANE]
A 17-string?
[CHIKA]
All right!
Hey, Hozuki!
Where'd you get this koto?
I borrowed it from
my mother's school.
Huh? Wait. Your mom?
[TAKEZO]
Is that okay, Hozuki?
[HIRO]
That must've been difficult.
It wasn't anything special.
I just borrowed an instrument.
I get it, but are you sure?
Look, that's enough about me,
you two need
to practice together.
I don't want you guys
holding us back.
Don't worry;
we'll make you proud.
Thanks a lot, Hozuki!
[HIRO]
Not anything special, huh?
There's no way that's true.
Especially since that's where
she was excommunicated from.
[CHIKA]
Let's start practicing!
[SANE]
Yeah!
[SATOWA] Uh, can I help you
with something, Hiro?
[HIRO]
Nope!
Let's get to work!
[AKIRA] I won't forget...
about that day.
I'll never forget...
that performance.
[AKIRA]
Never.
[CHIKA] Next time:
"Their Determination."