[police siren]
[DETECTIVE A sighs]
What a nightmare.
And they think
the grandson did it?
[DETECTIVE B]
Yes.
So we were told.
[TAKEZO]
That place...
...was invaluable and precious.
[COP C]
Hey, there he is!
It's been fun, Takezo.
The club's yours.
You've got this.
[MASHIRO]
You'll be fine!
It's you after all!
[STUDENT A]
Whoa.
Check it out, isn't
that guy over there Kudo?
Like Chika Kudo
from Nishi Middle School?
That dude's bad news.
[TAKEZO]
All right. Looks good! Next up‐‐
Ah!
[PRINCIPAL] Are these
fliers for the koto club?
[TAKEZO]
Huh? Principal!
What're you up to?
Recruitment?
[TAKEZO]
Uh, yeah.
You see, since the
upperclassmen have graduated,
I'm all that's left.
And if I can't find some new
members, we'll have to disband.
[PRINCIPAL]
Is that so?
This club's been around a while.
In fact, it was actually founded
by an old friend of mine.
I would hate
to see it get shut down.
Good luck in your endeavors.
Right. I'll do my best, sir.
I just hope it'll
be good enough.
[DELINQUENT C]
I keep dying!
Man, this sucks!
Come on, go left!
Crap!
This dumb level
is so freakin' hard.
Yo, you guys won't believe
how hot this girl is.
[DELINQUENT B]
You say that about every girl.
[DELINQUENT C]
Ugh, I shoulda saved!
[DELINQUENT B]
Ugh! Dammit!
[DELINQUENT A]
Oh? Who let the wuss in here?
Heh, so you're back again.
Ya know the room's ours.
[TAKEZO] But it's reserved
for the koto club.
I'm going to have
to ask you to please leave.
We have new students that
might be coming to look around.
And everything's a mess.
[DELINQUENT A]
A club? Who cares?
Don't touch the instruments!
[DELINQUENT A]
What's this?
You decide to man up?
Jeez, learn how to
pick your battles, bro.
Not even the teachers
care about this stupid club.
[DELINQUENT A]
Yeah, no one gives a damn
whether or not it disappears.
Hey, kinda like you!
At least ya have that in common.
No one wants in your loser club.
Just give it up already.
[TAKEZO]
I‐I won't let it disband!
I promised the upperclassmen.
That's why.
[DELINQUENT A]
Shut up.
Why'd you have to disrespect me?
Now I'm gonna hafta make
sure you never play again.
Sorry.
[TAKEZO]
No!
[TAKEZO gasps]
Whoa, what the
hell's wrong with you?
Crazy bastard!
Uh! Hold up.
I think that's Chika Kudo!
[DELINQUENT B]
Wait, you mean the dude
who got arrested last year?
Yo, morons.
Who gave you permission
to hang out in my territory?
Leave!
Move.
I've got business in that room.
Uh...
Wait a second, do you mean
in this room specifically?
[CHIKA]
Huh?
[TETSUKI]
There you are.
[CHIKA]
Tetsuki?
Please tell me you
aren't starting any crap.
I thought you were
gonna give up fighting.
Everything's fine.
I was just rescuin'
this four‐eyed wimp
from those dumbass punks.
Right?
Were you now? I see.
Where are the upperclassmen?
[TAKEZO]
Oh, well.
I'm actually the
koto club's president.
What? You for real?
This sucks!
I thought the club prez
would be a hot girl!
[TAKEZO]
Why is he so angry?
[CHIKA]
Well, whatever. Here.
Huh? Wait,
that's my club's room!
[CHIKA]
No duh.
Get it? I'm joining
the club, specs.
Uh. Um, I'm sorry.
I think you're confused.
We're the koto club.
What the hell?
This room is a disaster!
It looks like a dumpster!
I'll have you know
I clean it up every day!
Yeah, right!
I'm firing you as president!
From now on, I'm the president!
You can't just vote yourself in!
Look, I don't know
what your problem is.
But I can't accept this.
Please leave!
This room isn't a hangout
for punks like you!
Like he'd really
want to join up.
I'm not stupid!
Huh?
What is this crap?
He...
He took my sign?!
[TAKEZO]
What should I do?
I don't want to let
the upperclassmen down.
This is terrible.
[TAKERU]
Why was Takezo late?
[TAKEZO'S MOM]
He had club things.
Oh, the koto club?
So he still does that stuff.
I thought it was just
a desperate cry for help
after he bombed his exams.
[TAKEZO'S RELATIVE]
Takezo didn't get into
Meiryo High School?
[TAKEZO'S MOM]
I'm afraid not.
His stomach was
upset during the test.
[TAKEZO'S RELATIVE]
But he had the grades to pass!
[TAKERU]
No surprise,
Takezo always screws up
when it matters.
[TAKEZO]
He was right.
I hated myself for failing.
I was feeling pretty lost.
But then...
[STUDENT F]
Okay, next up.
We have the koto club.
[TAKEZO]
The koto?
I hate to say it,
but that sounds
boring even to me.
I feel bad for them.
[TAKEZO] Watching this club is
kind of like watching myself.
They probably wish they
could stop the performance
and run away.
Hello?
Hey! Wanna join?
Not exactly.
I mean...
[TAKEZO]
Yes.
I ended up joining
without even thinking.
Why?
[MASHIRO]
Thanks for signing up, Takezo.
[TAKEZO]
You wanna teach me a new song?
Really?
But it's so late in the year.
[MASHIRO] It's a song
that's been taught here
for generations.
I'm relieved.
If you know the song, you'll be
able to continue the tradition.
It's a good thing you joined.
I'm really glad you're here.
Hey. About the club sign,
please give it back!
Denied.
Just hear me out!
It's for the club, that sign
is very important to me!
Look, dude, I ain't
givin' shit back to you.
It didn't look like
you cared about it.
What a joke.
[TAKEZO]
What's his problem?
And what's the point
of even taking the sign?
He has no idea
what I care about!
[CHIKA]
What the hell, you again?
Get lost.
Where'd all their stuff go?
Dumpster.
You threw it out?
Yeah, it's trash.
Wait. Did you throw
out the instruments too?
Why do you even wear glasses
if you don't use 'em for seein'?
Ahh! My neck!
[CHIKA] Idiot, I told you
I'm joinin' the koto club.
Why would I throw out
the instruments?
Heads up.
Be a dear and
take out the trash.
Hey, why should I?
The sign!
[TAKEZO]
That jerk.
He sure likes
bossing people around.
[CHIKA] Idiot, I told you
I'm joining the koto club.
[TAKEZO]
Yeah, right.
Why would a creep like him
want to play the koto anyway?
[DELINQUENT A]
Oh look, it's the wuss!
[gasps]
[DELINQUENT A]
What?
I guess you're
Kudo's errand boy now?
What? No!
He stood up for you yesterday.
I guess you got a protector?
No. That's crazy.
I don't even really know him!
Don't talk back to me!
[CHIKA] I thought I told you
to take out the trash.
Not play with it.
[DELINQUENT A]
Kudo!
Hey. Did this loser
throw the first punch?
Um, yeah.
That's perfect.
Because now it's self‐defense!
[TAKEZO]
Don't do it!
What?! I'm just tryin' to
help you out, four‐eyes!
Well, it doesn't concern you!
[CHIKA]
That's bullshit.
It concerns everybody.
If nobody stops guys like that,
then they just do
whatever they want.
What's the difference
between you and them?
The only thing I want
is to protect the club!
That's rich.
You're not protecting anything!
Maybe protect is code
for do nothing.
That's why you get
beaten up so much.
It's not like you're any better!
You go around doing
whatever you please!
Why are you doing this?
To ruin the koto club?
[CHIKA]
You serious?
I already said I wanted to join.
I'm sorry, but I just
don't believe you.
Of course.
[TAKEZO] I don't get it.
He just did a 180.
Now I feel like the bad guy.
[TAKEZO gasps]
What... kind of
sloppiness is this?
It's not like you're any better!
[TETSUKI]
Chika?
Sorry, but I don't
think he's here yet.
I see.
[TETSUKI] Let me guess,
he did something stupid again?
Uh, no.
It wasn't Kudo.
It was me.
[TETSUKI]
Hmm...
Listen. Can we talk
for a second?
Dammit. That Kudo's
a real piece of work.
[DELINQUENT A]
So, let's get rid of 'im.
I've got a great idea
that just might work.
Heh, sounds good.
What's the plan?
He's already
been in trouble once.
It won't be hard to make him
look like the bad guy again.
Oh no. That troublesome
boy is back again.
He always comes on the same day.
Maybe he's trying to repent.
[TETSUKI]
Let's see, where do I start?
I guess you should know
it was his grandpa
who introduced him to the koto.
You see.
In his third year
of middle school,
Chika started living
with his grandpa,
and his grandfather was
a professional koto maker.
[TAKEZO gasps]
Wow, really?
[TETSUKI]
To be honest,
the Chika you know now
is actually pretty chill.
But in middle school
he was a loose cannon,
and he fought with
his grandpa constantly.
And, while I don't
know all the details,
I guess they just
had a lot goin' on.
[GEN]
Well, look at you.
Did you get into another scrap?
Heh, whatever.
With that face I can't tell
whether you won or not.
[CHIKA]
Ah shuddup.
There were nine of 'em,
you know.
High school dudes.
I still won.
[GEN] You really
are a brat, aren't you?
What?
[GEN]
How long are you gonna
keep treating
yourself like trash?
That's a terrible way
to live life.
Come on, you're
still pretty young.
If anything,
you should be out havin' fun
and living life to the fullest.
Yeah, you're one to talk.
All you do is hide in your shop
and make the same stupid
instrument every day.
[GEN] Heh. A brat like
you wouldn't understand.
The koto is an extremely
charming instrument.
[CHIKA]
Stop calling me a brat.
I don't care about the koto!
And that's why you're a brat.
Get it? Chika.
Where're you going?
Come back!
Hey!
[CHIKA]
Dammit
[NEIGHBOUR] What are
you doing out here, Gen?
Waiting on your grandson?
My goodness.
That boy brings you
nothing but trouble.
[CHIKA'S FATHER] I don't want a
little brat like you for a son.
Do me a favor and never
show your face here again.
[GEN] It doesn't matter
if he's nothing but trouble.
That boy's my grandchild.
And at the end of the day, I
still wanna be his grandfather.
What's up?
Has this "stupid instrument"
finally piqued your interest?
[CHIKA laughs]
No way.
I'm not sure I believe
that big lump of wood
can even make a sound.
[GEN]
Because you don't understand it!
That's how art is sometimes.
But did you know that
the koto is actually made
to resemble a powerful dragon?
[CHIKA]
What?
You'll see one day.
When the right piece, performer,
and koto all come
together like magic.
That performance will
absolutely change your world.
How 'bout it?
Wanna give it a try?
Are you out of your mind?
[GEN chuckles]
Don't wanna fail in front of me?
What? How hard could it be?
Just give it here!
Okay, then.
Put this on your finger.
[TETSUKI] I think that was
the moment that changed them,
and they stopped
fighting so much.
Chika quit spending time
with those punks.
But then, I guess they
thought he'd gotten boring.
Maybe that he thought
he was better than they were.
That's when they attacked
his grandpa's place.
They dressed up like Chika
and waited for
his grandfather to leave.
Everything was destroyed.
[TAKEZO] Wait, is that...
why he got arrested?
[TETSUKI] Naturally,
he was the prime suspect.
His grandpa collapsed
that same night
and then passed away
a few days later.
Oh. Sorry to hear that.
It was rough.
I think the old guy might
have been sick for a while.
Listen.
The reason he's set
on joining the koto club.
Is because his grandfather
was the one who founded it.
[TAKEZO]
Kudo was being honest.
He really did wanna
join the club.
The one that
his grandfather started.
I'm sorry, but I just
don't believe you.
I want to disappear.
I have to apologize to Kudo.
But what should I say?
[TAKEZO] I'm sorry,
but I just don't believe you.
[CHIKA]
Too bad.
Listen up, four‐eyes!
Hey, man!
What happened to you?
[TEACHER A] Hold it!
What's going on in there?
Kudo?
I heard a loud noise
and came to check it out.
It was you? Let's go!
What? You're blamin'
me for this crap?
I haven't done anything!
Shut up!
You're a criminal!
We'd never believe you!
[CHIKA]
Of course not.
No one does.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[NURSE]
Oh. You're awake!
That Kudo kid did
a number on you.
Did you say Kudo?
[NURSE] He destroyed
your club room, too.
They've detained him
in the principal's office.
Oh no.
It's like the incident
with the police last year.
Kudo isn't the one who did this!
I have to tell them!
[NURSE]
Hold on.
Look, it's probably better
if you don't associate with him.
Why though?
[NURSE]
That boy is nothing but trouble.
Kudo, please.
I need you to say something,
anything, about what happened.
The sooner we get some details,
the sooner this whole
thing gets resolved.
Unfortunately, your silence
could be mistaken for guilt.
[CHIKA]
You're wrong!
I'd never do this!
[COP A] He took care of you,
and you wrecked his house!
What a brat!
It wasn't me!
[COP B]
Yeah right, kid!
Even if you didn't do it,
you probably did something
to deserve this, right?
[gasps]
[TAKEZO]
She's right.
Ever since he tried to join,
it's caused me
nothing but trouble.
We live in completely
different worlds.
I feel bad for Kudo, but...
...I should just
stay out of this.
I need to protect the club.
[CHIKA] Maybe "protect"
is code for "do nothing."
[DELINQUENT A] Man, I can't
believe we pulled that off!
With his criminal record,
Kudo'll get expelled for sure!
[TETSUKI]
Yo. Didn't see me here?
That sucks.
Listen, all we're doing at
this point is wasting our time.
He's already done this
sort of thing once before.
It's fairly obvious.
Kudo's guilty.
So what should we do?
He needs to be punished.
‐‐Expulsion perhaps?
‐‐[TAKEZO] Hold on!
What are you doing here?
[PRINCIPAL]
Kurata!
Are you all right?
Your injuries.
I'm fine, sir.
Anyway. Uh...
Look, Kudo's isn't the
person who did this to me!
What?
Then do you know
who the culprit is?
[TAKEZO]
Well, no, but...
It had to be Kudo.
He was at the crime scene.
What other proof do you need?
That isn't why!
He was there because he's
a new member of the koto club.
Of course he'd be
in the club room!
Well, Chika.
You finally showed up.
[COP B]
Tell us the truth!
[COP A]
We don't believe you!
Wait. Are you serious?
Be honest.
Is it really true?
Why did you join that club?
Listen‐‐
Shut up, you dumb brat!
You think I don't already know?
I know my grandson.
[CHIKA]
The reason I joined
is because my grandpa
founded the club.
Most of the things
he loved are gone,
and I know that it's my fault.
I just wanna protect the
few things that are left.
And I wanna learn
more about him.
Whatever I can.
That's why I joined
the koto club.
That's ridiculous!
[PRINCIPAL]
I have to disagree.
This boy's grandfather
was my dear friend.
[gasps]
[VICE PRINCIPAL]
Wait!
What does your friendship
have to do with Kudo's guilt?
This is the same kid
who wrecked his grand‐‐
[PRINCIPAL]
That's enough, Vice Principal!
There's no proof
for that statement.
It's nothing more than
speculation born from bias.
Am I wrong?
But Kudo...
Excuse me, Principal!
We've had three
students come forward.
They've just confessed!
You're kidding.
Who were they?
[PRINCIPAL]
Kudo. Kurata.
This must have been
quite the ordeal for you.
I'm sorry you were involved.
It's fine.
So... is it true that you were
friends with my grandpa?
Yes.
Perhaps in the future we could
have a nice chat about him.
I guess we should head home!
[CHIKA]
Hey!
Uh, I just wanted
to say thank you.
That was so polite!
Shut up! No, it wasn't!
[TAKEZO shrieks]
Still though,
I don't understand
why the attackers
would give themselves up.
Who the hell knows. Huh.
Maybe an annoying guy who
doesn't know how to mind
his own business talked to 'em.
Where are you going?
The gate's that way.
[CHIKA]
To the club room.
It's still trashed.
So it's gotta be cleaned again.
[chuckles]
[MASHIRO]
You'll be fine!
It's you after all!
It'll be the best
koto club ever.
I believe in you!
[TAKEZO]
Everyone,
he's a lot to deal with.
But somehow we just gained
our strongest recruit yet.
Uh. Hey, Kudo?
Thanks for the sign.
It's great.
Huh? Whaddaya mean?
What sign?
[TAKEZO]
What are you denying it?
Wait, are you blushing?
[CHIKA]
Shut up!
I don't need your
dumb compliments, nerd!
[CHIKA] Next time,
"Havin' What it Takes."