[TAKEZO]
We're gonna be fine.
Because we've practiced...
...more than any of
the other clubs here!
You guys are gonna
do a good job.
You managed to survive my
tough lessons, after all.
[TAKINAMI]
Some final words of advice.
What's important isn't
going to nationals itself,
but why you guys want
to make it there.
To them, this is their
last opportunity.
[SATOWA]
I don't want it to end yet.
[HIRO]
I wish it could go on forever.
[CHIKA] But next year
won't work for you guys!
Next year it'll be too late.
[TAKEZO]
We're going to nationals!
[MIO exhales]
I can't believe
what I just heard.
What kind of
performance was that?
Well, it was evenly
matched with ours,
though it got there in
quite a different way.
[KAZUSA]
Hm...
[KAZUSA] The judge's votes
will probably be split.
What's with these
high-level performances?
It's absurd!
Between Himesaka and Hakuto,
only one can go to nationals?
Seriously?
That was nothing
short of incredible.
But it was incredible in a
completely different way
than Himesaka.
You're right. They're good.
The judges are gonna have
a hard time deciding.
How do they usually decide
which one is better?
Difficulty and how
well it was played?
Those are important factors,
for sure.
But when schools are playing
equally difficult pieces
at equally skillful levels,
I think it'll depend on
what each judge values.
Do they value the aesthetic
of staying together?
Or do they value the way the
sound was expressed?
[TAKEZO'S MOTHER]
Honey! Takezo's club is up next!
I wonder if he'll be okay.
He does have a history
of making big mistakes
at critical moments, you know!
He'll be fine dear,
stop worrying.
It looks like we made it
back just in time, eh, Granny?
Luckily.
[MASHIRO]
Takezo! Everyone! You got this!
This is weird. I'm feeling
sort of nervous for them.
It'll be okay, just you watch.
They've practiced like crazy.
Can you believe it, Mr. Tsukaji?
The next school up has five
boys in their club! Amazing!
I'm jealous!
Yeah, and they have
to follow up Hakuto.
Pretty rotten luck.
[TSUKAJI] Honestly, I don't
even want to hear the mundane
performances coming up.
At this point, Himesaka or
Hakuto will win, anyway.
Tokise.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Program number 13.
Tokise High School.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER
"Tenkyu."
[gasps]
[CHIHARU]
Hm.
[SATOWA] No matter how many
times I repeated those words
in my head...
[CHIHARU] Your koto playing
feels like a weapon to me.
[CHIHARU gasps]
This is pathetic.
How could I be afraid of hearing
my own daughter's performance?
[SATOWA]
...I never understood them.
I couldn't face them. But now...
♪
[AKIRA]
Ah. Yes, this is it.
But this time,
it's completely different.
♪
[CHIHARU gasps, sobs]
[AKIRA]
A single note.
It makes me want
to work harder.
That way you can always
have a smile on your face.
[TSUKAJI] How can she produce...
a sound like this?
♪
[KAZUSA]
Satowa.
[ASAHINA] She's already
in a class of her own.
[TSUKAJI]
But...
...there's no way that the
others can match her sound!
♪
[ASAHINA]
They're blending in so well!
[DOJIMA] How can these vulgar
delinquents do this?
[sobs]
[KAZUSA] You aren't worthy
enough to play the koto
with Satowa and you
proved it out there.
[gasps]
♪
[AKIRA] Think of the 17 string
and the solo as the "root"
and the "trunk" of a tree.
Then, the first and second kotos
are leaves and blossoms
that lend color to it.
♪
[WAKABA] Hold on a second.
What the heck in going on here?
This sound!
It's not just the solo part?
♪
[ASAHINA] Their sound
is completely different
from the other schools.
The care they put
into each note.
How it resonates.
The others are no match.
[koto playing continues]
[TSUKAJI] Who are these kids?
How did they become like this?
[TSUKAJI] Just how much time
did they spend practicing?
♪
You did well, guys.
I liked your performance.
It was a pretty damn good one.
And now I know that you
can become even better.
♪
[TAKEZO] So, I don't want the
next competition to be our last.
Together, we'll fight!
Until the very end.
So I wanna improve
as soon as possible.
[HIRO] There's still a lot of
things we need to do
before we complain!
♪
[TAKEZO]
When it comes down to it,
that sound is your soul itself.
[GEN]
The song is their soul.
[koto playing continues]
[CHIHARU] When I suddenly
lost someone dear to me,
I felt I had to protect
what was left behind.
I thought I could manage
my grief and overcome it,
because I had my daughter.
[CHIHARU] But... I was too weak.
Far more than I thought.
So much so,
that I took the only light
I had and let it go.
[SATOWA] Back then,
I was just going to quit.
I thought there was no point
in playing the koto anymore
if I couldn't even help Mom.
[SATOWA]
But...
[koto music continues]
[TSUKAJI] They keep switching
who plays the main theme
every two beats!
[ASAHINA] They're using
high-level techniques
for every crucial moment.
[SHIZU]
But they do it so effortlessly,
completely hiding the difficulty
of their performance.
Exactly how music
should be played.
[AKIRA] The section that
highlights each part
is starting.
♪
[TAKEZO gasps]
I'm so happy. This is so fun.
I want to play for much longer,
with everyone!
[CHIKA]
I'd rather play by myself.
[GEN] The sound you make when
you play with other people
you've spent a
lot of time with,
well, that's not something you
can produce by yourself.
[CHIKA] You were right, Grandpa.
I understand that now.
[TAKINAMI]
Good. Now, the final part.
♪
[CROWD gasps, sobs]
[gasps]
[TAKEZO]
Huh?
[HIRO]
Uh, what? We finished, but...
[SANE]
Zero applause?
[KOTA]
Did we screw something up?
[MITTSU groans]
[gasps]
[TAKEZO]
Guys!
Lights out means we
take our kotos and leave!
Uh. Okay.
[clapping]
[YAMAMOTO]
Huh?
[gasps]
Is... that for us?
[exhales]
[SANE] Was anyone else confused
by how long it took them
to clap for us?
[HIRO] Yeah, why wait
'til they cut the lights?
I wonder if our performance
was actually just that bad.
Stop it, it was fine!
Honestly, I think
our performance
up there was our best one ever.
Do you really mean that, Takezo?
There you are. Good thing
we came straight here.
I'm so glad to see you!
I'm freakin' out over here!
Miss Aki! You have to
tell us how we sounded!
Were we terrible?
We want both of your
honest opinions!
[ALL whimper]
What's with those faces?
You guys don't have
to look so worried.
[chuckles]
Just relax.
That was a wonderful
performance.
[ALL sigh]
You think so, don't you,
Mr. Takinami?
Kinda. They did
so-so, I guess.
C'mon. Let's get going.
Well that settles it! We didn't
do that good after all!
Why are you such a jerk?
Hey. Wait Mr. Takinami.
You really shouldn't
be so stubborn.
Be honest and say what you feel.
See, the thing about me
is that I'm always honest.
Having watched them
grow all this time.
That was nothing
special for them.
[gasps]
Uh. Hey, Hozuki.
Is something wrong?
[SATOWA] Oh. no. I just feel
tired now that it's over.
Oh yeah. I understand.
I feel the same.
But now, all that's left is to
wait for the results, and hope.
[gasps]
Uh-huh.
Ugh. Damn it! Tokise High
School was so damn good!
[KOMAKI] It made me cry too,
I don't get it! I'm scared.
What's going on? Why?
[YAMAMOTO] Wow. It was
a very good performance.
Not only that, but the
piece was incredible.
I composed mine to allow
Kanzaki to stand out
and balanced his role
with the others.
In contrast, Tokise's piece
was made to bring
out the characteristics
of each part.
[YAMAMOTO]
Ah, dammit.
Today's my last day doing this,
and yet, I'm already itching
to write the next piece.
[ISAKI]
Takaoka. I need more tissues.
Sorry, but mine
are all gone, too.
And are you still crying?
--[MASHIRO sobs]
--[TETSUKI gasps]
Hey, are you doing
all right over there?
[MASHIRO] Uh! I'm sorry.
I'm just so deeply moved.
Give the poor girl
some tissues!
I told you, I'm all out!
All right you kids,
I've gotta get going.
You performed well,
you should be proud.
[CHIKA]
Hey, thanks again, Granny!
[TAKEZO]
Yeah, thank you very much!
Okay, then.
All the performances are
finished now, and there's still
some time before the results
are set to be announced.
What're you guys gonna do?
Just head to the hall?
[SANE]
Uh, I dunno, maybe.
[MITTSU]
I'm pretty thirsty.
[SANE] Oh, then let's go
grab something to dri--!
[SATOWA] Excuse me, but do you
think it would it be a problem
if I stepped away for a moment?
Why?
It looks like my mother
came today, and um,
it's possible she's gone
home already, but maybe not.
[ALL gasp]
I'm sorry. I know
this is personal...
Well, why didn't you
say anything sooner?
[SATOWA gasps]
Yeah, seriously, Hozuki!
We would have taken care
of your koto for you
if you had told us
this before, you dummy!
Come on Hozuki's mom,
please still be around!
You wouldn't leave yet, right?
We're gonna help look.
But we'll be back soon!
What? Do they really all
need to go with her?
Mr. Takinami?
Let's help, too! Okay?
Huh?
Okay! Let's split
up and find her!
Wait. Do you know what
Hozuki's mom looks like?
Cus I don't.
No way. But I just
gotta find someone
who looks like
a grand-master, right?
[HIRO gasps]
[SATOWA]
She was wearing a kimono.
[BOYS]
On it!
[TAKEZO] If anyone finds her,
ask her to stay put,
then contact Hozuki.
[HIRO]
Either call her or text her!
[gasps]
[SATOWA] If I recall,
she was sitting around here.
[CHIKA gasps] Dammit!
I hope she's still close by.
[gasps]
[pants]
[SATOWA] No luck.
Maybe she really is gone.
[cell phone rings]
[pants]
[SATOWA] The only place we
haven't looked is backstage.
[SATOWA] What... am I doing?
Why would she be here?
She's got no reason to be.
[SATOWA]
What was I... expecting?
[CHIHARU]
Satowa?
[gasps]
[SATOWA]
Next time, "Starting Line."