[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR]
The Black Bulls are bound
for the Underwater Temple
and the magic stone
coveted by the Eye
of the Midnight Sun.
Unfortunately, the powerful
mana-driven currents
that surround it prevent
all from entering.
That mana weakens
during a full moon,
giving Noelle one week
in which to master the spell
that will allow
underwater travel
and help the Magic Knights
reach the temple.
Noelle was discouraged
by her inability
to control her magic, but
the mysterious girl Kahono,
Asta, and the rest of the
Black Bulls cheered her on,
until, finally...
[NOELLE]
The Black Bulls accepted me.
They relied on me.
And now... I want to do
something for them!
[NOELLE] Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Cradle!
It... It worked!
[BLACK BULLS cheering]
[NOELLE] Sea Dragon's
Cradle. A new spell!
Kahono! Did you see?
Huh? Where'd she go?
[KAHONO humming]
You've got great friends.
In the end, they're
the ones who should
be here cheering you on.
I'm glad it all worked out.
Can't wait till the
next time we meet, Noelle.
I'll see you in the Temple. Bye!
[YAMI]
Well, tonight's the full moon.
With the mana around
here at its weakest,
this is our best chance to
get to the Underwater Temple.
[YAMI]
So, you idiots ready to go?
Yeah! Just you wait,
Underwater Temple!
Just you wait, magic stone!
Just you wait, yummy seafood
I've never had before!
If I'm lucky, maybe they'll have
some rare vintages to sample.
I wonder who we'll be
up against down there.
I hope they're strong.
C'mon, let's go already!
The sooner we go,
the sooner we can return,
and the sooner I can see Marie!
And then I can get back
to the beach babes!
[GREY exhales]
[YAMI]
All right, I'm gonna go ahead
and take that as a yes, then.
Okay, it looks like you're up!
[NOELLE grunts]
What's wrong? You're not
gettin' nervous, are you?
No way!
It's not like there's anything
for me to be nervous about!
I pulled it off fine yesterday.
[VANESSA laughs]
Easy, sweetie.
Have a sip, you're
stiff as a board.
How about you not offer alcohol
to the person we're
trustin' with our lives?
[YAMI] When you're under
a lotta pressure,
things can go wrong,
even if they've gone right
100 times before.
Just remember,
ya gotta try and relax.
And if you do screw this up,
I'm gonna kill ya.
[NOELLE yelps]
Oh, yeah, no pressure at all!
[NOELLE]
Honestly. What is with them?
It almost feels silly
to be nervous now.
I mean, really.
If my spell fails,
we could all die.
But no one seems
that worried about it.
Okay. Here goes.
Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Cradle!
[BLACK BULLS]
Whoa!
I did it! I cast the spell!
Yeah, we knew you could do it!
But, uh...
[BLACK BULLS groaning]
[ASTA]
We're a little squished here.
Yer big enough without
the floaty thing!
Should I kill Grey?
[FINRAL] Come on! Transform
into someone smaller!
--[GREY] Ha!
--[BLACK BULLS sigh]
Well, peons, is this better?
[ASTA]
Now can we shrink the attitude?
[YAMI]
Not a bad job at all, Noelle.
Now you just gotta get us down
to the Underwater Temple.
Right! I've got it covered.
Everybody, hang on tight.
[NOELLE]
He complimented me!
[BLACK BULLS gasping]
[VANESSA laughing]
So cool!
It's almost like we're
flying through the ocean!
[CHARMY, GREY]
Look at all those yummy fish
begging to be turned into lunch!
Take a look, Marie.
We're travelling under
the water using magic!
Noelle, get us closer
to those fish.
Marie wants to see them!
It doesn't work
like that, moron!
[GAUCHE]
No! Come back!
I'm lost without the sight of...
I can already feel the mana
getting stronger down here.
What's that?
[ASTA yelps]
[MAGNA]
Doesn't look good!
[YAMI] I'd say we've reached
the strong magic region.
[BLACK BULLS yelling]
This is what it's like down here
when the mana's at its weakest?
Man, this strong magic
region is somethin' else!
Uh... This bubble thing
isn't gonna pop on us, is it?
You've gotta be pretty scared,
being a Flame mage and all.
Please! I don't know what
you're talkin' about.
I've never been
scared in my life!
[BLACK BULLS shouting]
[ASTA] Noelle, Noelle, she's
our man, if she can't do it...
[NOELLE]
Will you three be quiet, please?
I'm trying to concentrate, here!
[NOELLE] I'm just barely
avoiding all these currents.
It's almost like the
mana is helping me!
This'll work!
[VANESSA gags]
Feel sick. Think I'm gonna puke.
[GAUCHE] Don't even think
about it, you wino!
[NOELLE]
The currents have let up a bit!
[BLACK BULLS gasp]
[BLACK BULLS]
Whoa!
[ASTA]
Cool!
It's beautiful!
They've sure got
some funky lookin'
animals down here!
Yeah! That fish is
glowing like crazy!
[MAGNA]
Kinda looks like...
Yeah, it's magic!
That's pretty cool.
[YAMI] Guess all this
mana messed with the way
the beasties around
here evolved.
Yeah, but do they
taste any good?
Let's catch one and find out
if its flavors evolved, too!
[CHARMY, GREY]
Come here, little fishy-fish!
[MAGNA]
Not so fast!
Are you two idiots seriously
willing to die
for a little food?
And, Grey, we really don't need
another bottomless pit around.
[YAMI]
Huh?
Hey, look. Those whirlpools.
It's a magic barrier!
And an extremely powerful one!
My spell won't
get us through it.
Okay, kid, you're up.
Give that thing a nice big
slash with your sword.
[ASTA]
Captain Yami?
[YAMI]
Yeah?
[ASTA] The thing is, this was
my first trip to the beach,
and it taught me something
really important.
I don't know how to swim!
Funny, huh? You'd think I
woulda known before now.
Good thing you
won't need to swim.
[ASTA]
Eh?
[YAMI]
All right, you're probably gonna
need to hold your
breath for this.
I'm the captain here,
so that means your pace
is my pace, and my pace
is the pace, ya got that.
[shrieking] No!
[YAMI]
Ready, and...
[ASTA yelps]
[ASTA grunts]
Need air! I'm gonna drown!
Hold on. Oh, hey, I can breathe.
Thanks, kid.
I can't believe we didn't die!
See, I knew you were scared,
you even wet yourself.
Shut up, lightning boy!
That's just seawater
and you know it!
The mana's too
strong here for me
to get a hold of Marie!
[ASTA]
Gauche! Hey, Gauche!
Huh?
[ASTA]
You're kinda standing on me!
[GAUCHE]
You think I care?
Well, this is nice.
Crazy something like this exists
at the bottom of the ocean.
Whew.
[YAMI]
Hm.
[VANESSA]
Oh, my!
[CHARMY, GREY]
Wow!
[ASTA] Whoa! So that's
the Underwater Temple!
[YAMI]
Charmy. Whip us up some cotton.
Roger!
Munch, munch, munch...
Want some?
Absolutely, thank you!
[LUCK]
Well, this is a bust.
We haven't even
been attacked once!
[NOELLE]
He's right.
There don't seem
to be any trap spells.
I expected something.
[VANESSA]
Yawn! This is getting tedious.
You had better not be
lettin' your guard down,
ya hear me? There's
nothin' safe about
a strong magic region,
so get yourselves fired up!
Yes, sir!
Whoa!
[ASTA]
This is awesome!
[NOELLE]
Are these houses?
That means there are probably
oceanfolk down here!
Are they strong and scary
and super powerful?
I can't wait to fight them!
Well, that makes
one of us, at least.
[ASTA]
Look! People!
[MAGNA]
Luck was right. Oceanfolk!
They're not gonna
attack us, are they?
[NOELLE]
Shh! They'll hear you!
Whoa! Look over there.
Hey!
Oh, yeah, I think
they heard you.
Don't see that every day.
We've got real, live visitors!
And if the robes are
anything to go by,
it looks like they're
Magic Knights!
Cute ones, too!
Please, tell us about
the outside world!
So, have you been sent out
on any dangerous
missions lately?
Musta been ten years
since we've had visitors here.
Hey!
I was picturing someplace
a whole lot scarier
and more dungeon-y, with
booby traps and tricky magic.
Hate to break it to ya,
but imagination
doesn't really tend
to match reality.
We ought to look
around for someone
who knows about
that magic stone.
Right, Captain?
[YAMI]
I'm on it.
I wanna talk to whoever's
the boss of this temple, 'kay?
Maybe we should ask
a little more nicely, sir.
Yeah, no problem.
That would be the high priest
you're looking for. 'Kay?
He's way up at the
top of these stairs,
so I hope you don't mind
a bit of a hike, 'kay?
I can take you there
if you want, 'kay?
[ASTA]
He started a trend!
[FINRAL] You should join us
for a beach barbeque later.
You are such a cutie.
Isn't she, Gauche?
[GAUCHE] Please, Marie's
a billion times cuter.
Come on, Grey!
Transform into me, and we can
get some twin action going!
[muttering] I've never seen any
girls in the outside world
who are as beautiful
as the two of you.
Hitting on girls while
looking like Gordon?
Why him of all people?
[CHARMY] Crab boil, crab cakes,
crab claws, crab rangoon.
So far this has
been a lot easier
than I expected it to be.
Well, I'm not complaining.
But how will you cope without
your regularly scheduled
near-death experience?
Hey, it's not like I go
around asking people
to try and kill me!
Well, here we are.
Make sure and tell
the high priest
hello for us, okay?
We'll talk more about
the outside world
when you come back!
Yeah, and thank you!
Well, good luck.
Don't thank us yet.
[MAGNA]
Look. Someone's here.
[ASTA] Think that's the high
priest guy we're lookin' for?
Hey!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[OCEAN MONSTER growls]
[BOTH scream]
A huge fish! With teeth!
Asta! Poke it with your
sword or something!
Maybe it's actually
a kind temple guardian
that only looks
ugly and terrifying.
We should wait until it attacks!
[BOTH scream]
[MAGNA, LUCK, GAUCHE]
That oughta do it.
What was that thing, anyway?
[ASTA]
You guys didn't waste any time!
[GIFSO laughs]
Oh, this is wonderful!
I love it when we have
exciting visitors! Hah!
Yes! Welcome to the
Underwater Temple!
I'm the high priest of
this subaqueous structure.
Wait, this freaky geezer
is the one in charge here?
That wasn't the most
neighborly welcome
you gave us, ya old fart.
[laughs] I can't tell
you how much I enjoy
catching people
off guard like that!
Did you see how they
reacted? Delightful!
This guy needs a new hobby.
Fishy. Do you taste good?
Easy there, Charmy,
I'd leave the monster thing
alone if I were you.
[CHARMY, ASTA yelp]
[ASTA]
It's all sliced up!
[CHARMY]
Like it wants me to eat it!
Sorry, kids, you
can't eat magic.
[ASTA]
Huh?
[CHARMY]
I didn't even get one bite.
[VANESSA]
What kind of magic was he using?
[FINRAL] It's not easy to make
something that enormous.
This guy must be
really powerful!
You came to my temple to seek
the magic stone, didn't you?
If you want it,
you'll have to play
a game with me first.
What kinda game are
we talking about?
[FINRAL]
Here we go.
I can tell this guy is trouble.
He'll act like
it's just for fun,
right up until we lose
and he kills us all!
Well, are you ready?
The name of this
little game is...
..."Find Out How Squishy
the Boobs Are."
[GIFSO groans]
How about we play
this game instead?
[ASTA] Hey! You can't go
beatin' up the high priest.
He's some kinda big shot!
So what? I'm royalty.
It was just a joke!
[NOELLE] Well, now I'm
going to show you exactly
how not funny I think
that kind of joke is.
[ASTA] I really don't think
that's a good idea, Noelle!
All right, enough
messin' around.
We didn't drag our butts
all the way out here
to play games with you!
How'd you know we were after
the magic stone, anyway?
You'd be surprised how well
these old eyes still see.
So, what are you going to do?
Your kingdom needs
that stone. Doesn't it?
Whaddya think? Beat 'im up
and, uh, take it by force?
Yeah, that would
probably be the fastest.
It looks like the
geezer's super powerful,
so fighting him would
get my vote, for sure.
What kinda twisted stuff
are you three
plotting over here?!
Beating up old men isn't what
the Magic Knights are about!
[FINRAL] I'm telling you,
that's no ordinary old man.
We don't want to get caught up
with someone like him.
[VANESSA yawns] Do you think
we have time to take a nap?
[CHARMY] Forget napping.
I wanna know when dinner is.
And do you three
even care at all?
[GIFSO] Aw. Haven't you
made up your minds yet?
Play with me, and not only
will you get the magic stone,
but I'll round up the
temple's loveliest ladies,
finest drinks,
and tastiest food.
We'll have a
magnificent banquet.
What do ya think?
Shall we play?
[ALL]
Yeah, let's do it!
[yells] Is that seriously
what's more important to you?
I'll play the game 'cause of our
mission, not some stupid party!
That's enough outta you.
Looks like we got no choice.
All right, then, old man.
You wanna play so bad,
take on this master gambler.
Go get 'im!
No one can outplay you,
Captain Yami!
Okay, so what game
is it gonna be?
Dice? Roulette?
Woo-hoo! A brawl!
A real Temple battle royale!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah, ye-yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah-yeah!
Temple mages, come on down!
Game Magic: It's time
for Temple Shuffle!
--[BLACK BULLS gasp]
--[ASTA] What the...?
Looks like more doors.
[TEMPLE MAGES]
You summoned us, High Priest?
[TEMPLE MAGE 42A]
Finally, mages from the outside
have come to visit us!
[TEMPLE MAGE 42B]
Ooh, this is gonna be fun!
[MORAY EEL MAGE]
I'm not sure.
They don't seem as
impressive as we'd thought.
[ASTA]
A buncha talking fish!
[MAGNA]
Come on.
Those're the lamest
masks I've ever seen.
Oh, this is bad. I'm sensing
a ton of power here.
Are these mages temple warriors?
[GIFSO] All righty!
Shall we get started?
Like, now?
What exactly are we starting?
[laughs] Are you ready?
Okay! Let's go!
I'm totally not ready!
[GIFSO cackles]
[screaming]
What the heck?
Where am I?
Where's everyone else?
[GIFSO] Uh, testing, testing!
Can you all hear me?
[gasps]
[GIFSO]
As you may have noticed,
you've been separated
and placed in various spots
throughout the Temple.
[LUCK] So all this is
inside the temple? Cool!
[GIFSO]
...a short while ago.
[MAGNA]
The hell kinda game is this?
Where do they keep
the food in this place?
[GIFSO]
...battle of magic and witts!
[NOELLE] Wait, I never actually
learned any attack magic.
How is it that I'm just
realizing this now?
Hold on.
Did he say it was going
to be a nine-on-nine battle?
But, there should be ten of us.
[GIFSO]
The rules are very simple.
Knock them out, and you win.
Make them surrender,
and you win.
Well, I'm a little bit
more awake now, at least.
[GIFSO] ...or the one with
the most players left standing
when the game concludes!
[muttering] Who should
I transform into next,
little crab?
[GIFSO]
You may play any way you like.
Fight one-on-one. Hide and
hope to outlast the others.
Find your friends, band
together, and swarm the enemy!
The choice is yours!
[FINRAL] What kind of
vicious game is this?
That's it. I'm outta here.
Good luck, guys.
[GIFSO] Just make sure
you keep an eye out
for my nuisance spells.
They can be a bit startling.
[GAUCHE]
Nuisance spells?
I'll show you
a nuisance, old man.
Oh, yeah! I'm so there!
This is gonna be
a total bloodbath!
All right, I got it!
Now, let's go! I'm ready!
[OCTOPUS MAGE]
What's this?
How interesting.
I'm not sensing so much as a
scrap of magic coming from you.
Tell me. Can you even fight?
[OCTOPUS MAGE]
Too bad.
I was hoping for
a good opponent,
but it looks like I got a dud.
[ASTA]
You think I'm a dud, huh?
Just try me and find out.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[TEMPLE MAGES]
"There's 10 of Us."
You summoned us, High Priest?
[GIFSO] I'm sorry to call the
nine of you here like this.
However, there is
an urgent matter
that I needed to
discuss with you.
[TEMPLE MAGES]
Huh?
[GIFSO]
Wait a minute.
Now that you're
all standing here.
I sense that something's amiss.
There's one too many!
[TEMPLE MAGE 42A]
One too many?
[MORAY EEL MAGE]
Too many of what?
[GIFSO] Of you.
There should only be nine.
[TEMPLE MAGES]
What?
[TEMPLE MAGES chatter]
[ELEPHANT MAGE]
This is unbelievable!
There's an imposter among
the ranks of the Temple mages?
[TEMPLE MAGES]
Huh?
[ELEPHANT MAGE] Huh? What?
Is there something wrong?
[OCTOPUS MAGE]
Yeah. I'd say there is.
[KIATO] You're not
exactly a sea creature.
[ELEPHANT MAGE]
Oh, I get it.
You're messing
with me. Ha, ha, ha.
Answer me this:
what's your favorite food?
[ELEPHANT MAGE]
Peanuts, of course!
And what's your best feature?
[ELEPHANT MAGE]
My long nose, of course!
And what does that make you?
[ELEPHANT MAGE]
An elephant!
[ELEPHANT MAGE laughs]
I'm an elephant!
Have you ever tried a peanut?
No? You should,
they're delicious!
Really!
[GIFSO] Welcome to the
Underwater Temple!
I know what you're after.
If you want the magic stone,
you'd better be ready
to fight for it!
Black Clover , Page 43:
"Temple Battle Royale"!
Yeah, that's right,
I'm the high priest here.
I'm kind of a big deal.