[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] His arms now restored
by the Queen of Witches,
Asta and the others were
fighting to protect the Forest
from enemy forces when they were
suddenly confronted by Fana.
a leading member of the
Eye of the Midnight Sun
who also possesses a third eye.
[yells]
[ASTA yelps]
[ASTA]
She's got that third eye, too!
[NOELLE] Everything is riding
on this single shot!
Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Roar!
[NARRATOR] Our heroes
appeared to be helpless
as Fana's fire spirit,
Salamander, began
to lay waste to the Forest.
But, thanks to a powerful
attack generated
by Noelle's Water Magic,
they were able to subdue
the terrible beast.
Okay! Finally time
for my special move!
[NARRATOR] For the finishing
blow, Asta used Bull Thrust,
a fighting technique
he had just invented.
Here we go!
[ASTA]
Bull Thrust!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES] To think
that imperfect little rat
had this much power.
So it appears he wasn't
all bark and no bite.
And those other troops...
I dunno who this is,
but I'm guessing
he isn't a witch.
He must have guts to stand up to
this huge army all by himself.
Either that, or he's stupid.
Mars! You remember me, right?
Wait a minute now!
I might be totally
off base here,
but I think that guy
is our old teacher!
Yes, Ladros.
And it looks like
I get the honor
of tormenting you!
Lucky me!
[yells]
Ooh! Still got it, huh?
You two have changed
quite a bit,
and I can see that it's
not for the better.
You leave me no choice...
...but to atone for my mistake!
Ooh! Feel that breeze?
Nice and gentle!
I'll ask you this one time.
Any chance you'll turn back?
[LADROS laughs] Well, we're
the ones with the army,
so I'm thinkin' that's our line.
See, here's the thing.
It turns out our king isn't in
the best of health these days.
And from what we've
been hearing,
the Queen of Witches
has been around
for hundreds of years now.
The King wants to
find out her secret,
even if it means wiping out
everyone in this pitiful Forest.
So when we got word that
the Eye of the Midnight Sun
was already planning
to stir up trouble here,
we thought we might as well
take advantage of the confusion
and make this a real party!
We want something,
we take it by force!
That's always been
our philosophy
in the Diamond Kingdom, right?
Which is why I left
and never went back.
Now!
Woo-hoo-hoo! Sure is good
to see you again, Teach!
Heh.
All these soldiers, and he's
charging right for us?
Is he crazy?
[yells]
Wind Creation:
Emperor of Slashing
Winds, Winter Wind!
Here it comes!
He's fast!
[DIAMOND MAGIC
KNIGHTS screaming]
Wait. I know him!
It's that traitorous
coward, Fanzell Kruger!
He was a Diamond
Kingdom commander
and combat instructor before
he double-crossed us!
And he's got a sizable bounty
on his head, as well!
Let's take him down, now!
[yells]
[DIAMOND MAGIC KNIGHTS groan]
[DIAMOND MAGIC KNIGHTS grunt]
[yells]
[FANZELL]
They're not moving.
Must be hard to attack when your
allies are that close together.
Especially with the
powerful magic ability
that those two possess.
[FANZELL] But there's only
so much one man can do.
I'll have to depend on my
other half and my student.
[MARIELLA] I wonder if my
Master ever put clothes on.
There! I am such a genius.
Remain calm! Assume
formation number six!
Even if he is a former
commander, if you follow orders
and strike from afar,
then he will fall!
He is your only target!
[DIAMOND MAGIC KNIGHTS scream]
[gasps]
That's not exactly accurate.
No matter how many troops
your opponent has,
you should always attack
with three times as many.
That's what Master told me.
It's an ambush!
We'll be fine--we have
plenty of soldiers!
Go, Squad Two!
[DIAMOND MAGIC KNIGHTS grunt]
[DIAMOND MAGIC KNIGHTS groan]
[MOHAWQ] What? They're
pushing us into the Forest!
[DIAMOND MAGIC
KNIGHTS screaming]
[FANZELL grunting]
[MOHAWQ]
There's no way this will work
with all these trees and fog!
Let's switch to formation 13!
[MARIELLA]
Squad Four!
[DIAMOND MAGIC KNIGHTS groan]
Squad Five!
[MOHAWQ] How are they able
to predict our every move?
Easy.
Not so long ago, I was
on the Diamond Kingdom's
assassination squad.
[MOHAWQ gasps]
[MARIELLA]
You aren't even a challenge.
[ASSASSINATION TARGET
60A panting]
[gasps]
[ASSASSINATION TARGET 60A yells]
[MARIELLA] I used to kill
people who were just
doing their best to survive.
Simply so that I could
stay alive myself.
[gasps]
[MARIELLA] Maybe I'm hoping
to make up for what I've done.
Or maybe I'm just patting
myself on the back.
Huh?
[MARIELLA] But still,
I'm going to stop you!
You're a damn traitor!
True, but there's
nothing you can say
that'll make me
change my mind now.
If I back down, then the
person who saved my life
won't be very happy with me.
[WITCH HERBALIST 57A]
That girl's a fierce one!
Jumping right in there
and taking command
of so many people!
Oh, I agree!
Our Mariella sure is something!
Now for the next phase!
[DIAMOND MAGIC KNIGHT 60HH]
Oh?
[DIAMOND MAGIC KNIGHT 60II]
What's happening?
[BOTH yell]
[laughs] And there you have it!
Thanks to my superior magic
items and tinkering skills,
I was able to give
those security golems
a little upgrade!
That's marvelous!
I'm sure it must've been
expensive to pull off, though!
You won't believe this,
but the materials
only cost me about
3,000 yul each!
That much destruction
for so cheap--
what a value!
[DOMINANTE]
Now's our chance, ladies!
Don't let those lawless brutes
ransack our beautiful Forest!
Show them that these
witches mean business!
[LADROS]
Well, well!
They set a trap
down there thinking
we would barrel right into it!
It's probably better
if we tread carefully.
But it kind of looks
like fun, so here I go!
Whatever the game
is, let's play!
Now then, where could they be?
Uh-oh!
[FANZELL]
Exactly what I thought you'd do.
That's enough, Ladros!
Wind Binding Magic:
Emperor of Slashing Winds.
Whirlwind!
Oh, rats! Guess you got me!
For the last time, do you
want to turn around?
[LADROS]
Hm.
Now where would be
the fun in that?
I've got so much more
slaughtering left to do!
What's wrong with you? Huh?
You can't train us
to be killing machines,
only to expect us to behave
like upstanding citizens,
and during a big
battle like this?
I'm sorry, but I promised.
See, I told my last pupil--
someone younger than you...
[FANZELL] ...I'm done
running. I'm gonna live!
[LADROS gasps]
[yells]
[FANZELL] That's it,
feel your opponent's mana.
Calm your emotions.
Good job! Try to focus.
Listen.
Your powers are meant
for protecting people,
and nothing else.
Don't ever forget that, okay?
[CHILDREN]
Right!
[FANZELL] His strength was
physical Reinforcement spells.
I'll never win like this.
[MARS]
Don't move, or you're dead!
[FANZELL grunts]
[FANZELL]
Mars.
Of all the students I taught,
he was the most skilled.
There's no way I stand a chance
against him at this distance.
I'll have to make some room!
Wind Creation Magic:
Emperor of Slashing Winds.
Mountain Wind!
[MARS grunts]
Ooh!
[FANZELL]
Ladros.
I'm putting my all into this.
Now, Wind Creation Magic:
Emperor of Slashing Winds. Gale!
[screams]
[FANZELL] Not having
an elemental attribute
always made him
feel a little odd.
[LADROS]
Sir.
I don't need an attribute
to be strong, right?
[FANZELL] He gave himself
a complex over it.
[LADROS yelling]
[FANZELL]
But he still had greater power
than any of his peers.
If he knows a long-range
spell, I'm done for.
I'd better put him out quick.
Forgive me.
No! Stop it!
I can't, I can't, I can't,
I can't, I can't!
No more of your
magic, sir, please!
I'm downright stuffed.
[FANZELL gasps]
Heh! You surprised?
[FANZELL]
There's not a scratch on him!
[LADROS]
Yeah, I've made a few changes.
After you left, the army
gave me one of those
upgrade surgeries and I came
out with some new tricks.
Absorption and emission.
My body can suck up
any magic attack
that's thrown at it,
and I can release
that gathered force
whenever I like.
You know what
that means, right?
Not only am I about to kill
all your little buddies,
I'm gonna use your
magic to do it!
What's this power from?
It's not just Ladros.
There's so much,
it must be something else!
By the way, Teach.
You didn't happen to
bring any loved ones
into the Forest, did you?
'Cause if you did,
you might wanna go
check on them real quick.
And you'll have to
outrun my magic,
so you'd better hurry up!
On your marks.
Get set... Go!
Million Lasers!
[WITCHES yelping]
[DIAMOND MAGIC KNIGHTS groaning]
[LADROS]
Whoopsie!
I got so excited there that
I wiped out my own guys!
I wonder if Teach made it?
Ah! There you are!
[FANZELL grunting]
[DOMINANTE]
Zell. Oh, no.
Domina.
[LADROS]
Look at that.
So you did have someone
special here, after all!
But why haven't
you introduced us?
Don't you have any manners?
Wow, you didn't tell
me your lady friend
was such a looker! I'm jealous!
[LADROS]
Hey, wait.
Haven't I seen you before?
Oh, yeah! That's right.
you're the little
minx he decided
to run away with, aren't ya?
So, how've you been?
Ladros, stop! Please, I beg you.
Use your power for what's right!
Of course, I am
and I always have.
Come on, you and I both
know that combat training
was never meant to teach us
how to protect anybody.
There's nothing better
than using your power
to the absolute max and
devastating any opponent
that dares stand in your way!
My goal is to be recognized
all over this nation
and eventually the whole world!
That's why I trained hard
and rose through the ranks
to become one of the
Eight Shining Generals!
[LADROS]
Why are you always spewing
this idealistic garbage?
No wonder you were defeated
in that power struggle
and had to flee
the Diamond Kingdom
with your tail
between your legs!
You're such a coward!
Shut your mouth right now!
My Zell is no coward!
I think I'll start by killing
this noisy little witch!
[DOMINANTE yelps]
[giggles]
Domina!
[DOMINANTE gasps]
[gasps]
[MARS] My powers are
for protecting people.
Everything that you said...
Well, I guess,
it finally hit home.
[FANZELL]
Mars. I...
You're kidding. What is this?
There's no need for
all this killing.
We're all here for
the Queen, remember?
[LADROS] Oh, now you wanna
pull out the kid gloves?
Come on, they turned their
backs on the Diamond Kingdom!
If we overlook that,
then it means
we're basically traitors, too.
That's fine.
Really? You're gonna
betray your country?
That seems to be the case.
[LADROS gasps]
[sighs]
Yay for me!
[LADROS]
Now I can kill you legally!
[LADROS] You've been a thorn
in my side for too damn long!
So good at everything
and so nonchalant
about it at the same time!
It's such a pain in the neck!
I always knew that if
I kept aiming for the top,
you would end up gettin'
in my way somehow!
And today's finally my chance.
I get to kill you
and our old teacher!
This is the best!
[grunts]
Mariella?
He's my teacher, too, you know.
Don't treat him like he's
some sort of bonus kill!
[LADROS] Why don't you
and your pathetic magic
stay out of this?
That's not even
enough to snack on.
There's our little
Marsie-boy for ya!
I'll take all that power and
send it back with interest!
Flame Recovery Magic:
Phoenix Robe!
But, Mars. Why would
you help us?
Ladros is right. The two
of us are traitors!
I mean, losing your memories...
Not to worry, sir.
I've decided I'm on your side.
Unexpected though
our reunion may be.
[LADROS]
Ooh!
We can talk later.
First, we should deal with him.
Okay.
But how do we handle
somebody who can do that?
Well, he's almost invincible,
but I know of a few ways
we can defeat him.
One is to keep feeding
him more magic
than he can absorb until
he self-destructs.
We'd have to use
Spirit Magic or get
the Queen of Witches to help us.
The other way is anti-magic.
Anti-magic! Asta! That's right!
It turns out we know
just the guy,
and he happens to be waiting
at the opposite end
of the Forest as we speak!
[gasps]
[FANZELL]
Let's try to guide Ladros there.
Good idea, Master.
Hey, are you guys
talkin' about me?
Doesn't matter how
great your plan is,
it'll be useless
against my magic!
What the--?
[LADROS]
Huh?
Your power is what causes
you to be careless!
[chuckles]
I've got a knack for
Reinforcement spells myself.
[BOTH]
So say goodbye!
[yells]
It's over, we've got you
completely surrounded!
So you might as well give up!
[ASTA]
Ow, hot! Hot!
Don't bother putting up a fight!
We don't wanna hurt you,
so please don't force us to!
You're still young, right?
There's no point in you
throwing your life away!
If you do something stupid,
then your friends and family
are gonna be really sad!
You disgusting human.
Don't you dare
speak of my friends!
[gasps]
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[MARS]
"It Hit Home."
[FANZELL]
Tell me the truth, Mars!
Do you know how old I am?
You're 28.
Ah!
Ooh! There's no way
Teach is in his 20s!
He's 38!
Nobody could teach
sword-fighting like that
without a ton of experience.
I'd say he's 42.
Not that I care or anything,
but I think he's 46.
[FINRAL] You guys are
forgetting about his beautiful
and intelligent
fiancée, Dominante.
She's the kind of classy
lady you can only score
with the flirting techniques
of a middle-aged man!
Mm, 50!
[VANESSA]
He looks so tired all the time.
I guess 54.
You are younger than me,
at least, aren't you?
Guys, I'm only 28.
What you said, well,
it really hit home!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES] Salamander
is still alive and well.
So, what now, little one?
Show us what you can do.
Black Clover , Page 61:
"The Promised World."
My magic is being
of unknown age.