[VILLAGERS screaming]
[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a
lone mage stepped forward
and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was
hailed as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[CROWD cheering]
[NARRATOR] Time flowed
onward into the present.
The role of Wizard King was
passed down through the ages,
and always, he and the Magic
Knights under his command
have fought to keep
the kingdom safe.
[NARRATOR]
The Magic Knights:
nine squads of
knight-mages whose powers
are specialized for
combat, operating under
the direct control
of the Wizard King.
[NARRATOR] These heroic men
and women risk their lives
to protect their country.
For their bravery and
dedication, the Magic Knights
and the Wizard King are revered
throughout the Clover Kingdom.
[clanging]
[ASTA]
...995...
...996...
...997...
...998...
...999...
[yells]
[ASTA pants]
[ASTA]
And now for some magic-boosting
moguro-leaf juice!
So gross!
[ASTA]
Time for another round!
Still gross!
[BIRD chirping]
You want a swig, birdie?
[ASTA]
Or not.
Yeah, I got me a grimoire.
So what if I've got no magic?
I'm gonna kick butt anyway!
Okay, here we go. Back to work!
One thousand and one!
I bet Yuno's doing some
special training, too.
He won't get the best of me.
[yells]
[NARRATOR] Determined to succeed
despite his lack of magic,
Asta was training hard for the
Magic Knights Entrance Exam,
which would be held at the
Clover Kingdom's capital
in six months' time.
And indeed, so was Yuno.
That's enough for today.
Maybe... a little more.
He'll be training, too.
[YUNO]
...1,001!
Now, break!
[NARRATOR] Both young men
had their sights set
on becoming the Wizard King.
...1,503!
[HIGH PRIEST]
Now, Yuno I can understand.
But encouraging Asta
to take the exam, really?
Are you certain?
Well, why not?
Asta insists on taking it,
so what else should I do?
[TOWERMASTER] We had some
other promising youngsters.
[BOY 1A] It's impossible.
There's just no way!
We'll never be Magic Knights.
That guy was insanely powerful,
and they kicked him
out of the ranks.
We just can't!
[BOYS]
We're sorry, sir!
[TOWERMASTER]
But, unfortunately, it appears
they've had a change of heart.
Okay, Yuno I understand,
but does Asta
really have a chance?
[TOWERMASTER]
Well, he insists on taking it,
so what else should I do?
Yuno I can understand,
but I don't see the point
in Asta going, too.
Yes, well, he insists
on taking it,
so what else should I do?
Oh, I see the problem here.
You're going to be lonely
when Asta leaves for
the capital, aren't you?
That's so sweet, Father!
He's totally off the mark!
It's just, if Asta's
going to fail anyway,
wouldn't it be better for him
not to take it
in the first place?
And the little ones!
They'll miss him
terribly, I'm sure.
This isn't about me.
I'm just thinking of
the children, that's all.
[giggles]
[HIGH PRIEST]
Don't give me that look.
[giggles]
That goes for you, too.
I know I'm going
to miss Yuno and Asta
when they leave for the
city. You're not alone.
[HIGH PRIEST clears throat]
[HIGH PRIEST]
W-Well, I've raised them
since they were infants
and spent all these years
living alongside them.
It's only natural that
I'd miss them a bit.
I understand.
We've always looked out for them
and kept them safe, but now,
we must give them a chance
to make their own way.
Yes, exactly.
Look at it like this.
Yuno may well succeed,
but in all likelihood,
Asta will not, and he'll turn
right around and come back.
Yes! You're right!
He probably will.
Okay, then!
Yuno may be lost to us,
but Asta's sure to come back.
[HIGH PRIEST]
Now, about that book of Asta's.
Do you think it could
truly be a grimoire?
It seems so unlikely.
Why would he get one
if he can't use magic?
[TOWERMASTER]
No clue.
However, that book...
Go on.
[TOWERMASTER]
Nothing.
Well, what d'you think?
My very own grimoire.
I don't know how it
happened, but I got one!
[TOWERMASTER]
The five-leaf clover...
Who would have thought?
[ASTA yelling]
Training doesn't stop
till I reach the church!
Comin' through!
[ASTA yells]
[YUNO grunts]
[ASTA, YUNO grunting]
[REKKA]
Made it!
[ARLU]
Hey! Welcome back!
How's training?
--[YUNO panting]
--Well? Who got here first?
[NASH] Mm... It's a close call,
but Yuno was a tiny bit faster.
Seriously? Were you
really watching?
[ASTA growls]
All right, then.
Let's see who's first
into the church.
[ASTA yelping]
Looks like that would be me.
[ASTA grunts]
I didn't expect Yuno
to be so childish.
He musta snapped, with all
the training they're doing.
It's getting pretty
intense. Though...
We'll have firewood for years.
I'm gonna be the Wizard King.
[sighs]
[clanging]
[ASTA grunting]
[ASTA]
Hey, Yuno!
Curious about my training, huh?
Well...
Oh, Nash!
Is something up?
Nothing much.
Just bored, that's all.
Thought I'd spend some time
making fun of a dumb
dummy doing dumb stuff.
This isn't dumb, you punk!
Yeah, it really is.
I mean, you can't
even use magic,
and you're taking the
Magic Knights Exam?
There's no way you'll pass.
I wouldn't be too
sure about that.
Look!
I've got a grimoire
now and everything.
I'll get into a Magic
Knight squad, I know I will.
And then, someday,
I'll become the Wizard--
[NASH]
No, you won't!
You're poor like the rest of us.
An orphaned cast-off.
Kids like us don't
get to have dreams.
Hey, Nash...
No giving up, you hear me?!
We can dream as
much as we want to!
No, you're wrong!
We can't do anything!
We can!
Look!
I'm following my dreams.
Even if you're a poor orphan,
you can become great,
just like anyone else.
You can do anything you want,
make your dreams come true,
and make the people
you care about happy.
That's exactly what
I'm going to prove.
Come on.
[ASTA] I'll join the Magic
Knights and be the Wizard King!
Watch!
[CHILDREN]
Wow!
[HIGH PRIEST chuckles]
Well, now.
Asta and Yuno are heading
to the royal capital
tomorrow, after all.
I thought we'd send
them off in style.
It's quite a feast.
Father went to
a bunch of villages.
He got all the
pop-potatoes he could.
Oh, Father!
Don't look at me like that.
It isn't just for you.
Honestly...
I mainly did it for Yuno.
[ASTA]
Father...
It's true.
Yuno just might make it
into the Magic Knights.
But you...
Father!
Now, listen. It's a tough exam.
There's no shame
in failing, Asta.
It's not like anybody
expects you to pass.
I can't even tell if
you're cheering me on
or putting me down right now!
[HIGH PRIEST] You'll always
have a place here, all right?
No matter what,
this is your home.
Even if it is a crumbling dump,
it's still your home.
Yeah, and don't ever forget it.
We're gonna miss you so much
while you're gone, Asta,
and Yuno, too!
Yeah, 'cause we're family!
You're gonna say all that
stuff to Yuno, too, right?
About how he can
always come back.
Yes, well, uh...
He'll be fine.
Hey, now!
You may not think so,
but I'll be fine, too.
I'm gonna be the Wizard King.
Then I'll come back
for Sister Lily.
[gasps]
And when I do, I'll
ask her to marry m--
Let's all eat now, shall we?
Boiled pop-potatoes,
battered pop-potatoes,
Roasted pop-potatoes or fried.
Sautéed pop-potatoes,
and steamed, too.
Boiled pop-potatoes à la Hage,
pop-potatoe juice,
and extra-special
pop-potatoe flan.
[BOTH]
Thank you! It looks so yummy!
[ARLU]
It's only a little bit burnt!
[HORO]
So good!
[ASTA]
I call dibs on this one.
[REKKA] Don't hog it all
for yourself, you big pig!
[ASTA]
Delicious.
Take care, boys.
Yuno, you'll write
us, won't you?
Of course.
I hope you guys have fun!
But come back soon, okay?
Asta will be back soon enough.
Don't you worry.
Come on, Nash!
But listen.
If by some chance,
some very small one,
you actually manage to
join the Magic Knights...
Yeah, what?
Then I'll start believing
dreams really can come true.
That I can be anything
I want, and maybe one day
I'll become a Magic Knight, too!
Or, you know, whatever.
I'll be waiting.
Sure.
All right, Asta.
Let's get going.
Hey, hold up, Yuno.
Do you have to be such a jerk
all the time, lady-killer?
Sure, we're rivals.
That doesn't mean
we can't be friends.
Yuno!
See you later!
Wish us luck, everybody!
[GROUP]
Have a safe trip! Good luck!
So long.
[LILY]
Yuno and Asta.
So strange to watch them leave.
I can't believe how
much they've grown.
Asta's always had
that boundless energy,
from the day we met.
Everybody, I'd like you
to meet our new arrival,
Sister Lily. Let's give
her a warm welcome.
--[YUNO gasps]
--Ah... Sister Lily?
Yes?
Pretty please,
will you marry me?
[LILY gasps]
Oh, I didn't mean to! Sorry!
Sister Lily...
Oh, boy. He's lost it now.
[LILY] Yuno may not like to
admit it, but Asta changed him.
Made him stronger,
more determined.
Asta...
His injuries are very bad.
It's my fault he's hurt.
He was just trying to defend me.
From what? Yuno, what happened?
[ASTA grunting]
Asta! Stay with us!
Sister... Lily...
I'm here.
Will you... marry me?
He'll be all right.
[LILY] Good luck, boys.
We're proud of you.
[NARRATOR]
Summer.
After months of training, Asta
and Yuno have finally set out
for the royal capital to take
the Magic Knights Entrance Exam.
The capital is a far
distance from Hage,
and their journey
will be a long one.
The capital, eh?
What do ya think
it's gonna be like?
Wonder if we'll meet
the Wizard King.
First we have to pass the
Magic Knights Entrance Exam.
And then, who knows?
Aw, man, I can't wait!
You can't? Aren't you
nervous, though?
[ASTA]
Huh? About what?
[YUNO chuckles]
How very Asta.
Let's get a move on, huh?
Got a long way to go!
[YUNO]
Hey!
[ASTA] I gotta be the
Wizard King, like, yesterday.
It doesn't matter
when you get there.
It won't make you the
Wizard King any sooner.
And once I am the Wizard King...
Asta! Is that you?
How grand you've become!
Sister! I mean, my darling Lily.
I've come for you,
just as I promised I would.
I am the Wizard King now.
Hop on, my dear.
Yes!
Hold on tight for
the ride of your life.
It'll be great!
[YUNO] Can you even fly
a broom? Without any magic?
[yelps]
Yeah, sure, I'll make it work.
Will you, now?
Totally! I'm sure my trusty
grimoire will help me.
As long as you don't give up,
you can do anything.
C'mon, let's move!
Do you wanna get left behind?
We'll keep training till
we reach the capital!
[YUNO]
Sure, we will.
Betcha can't catch me! Ha, ha!
[YUNO, ASTA panting]
No, not done yet!
[ASTA yelling]
[ASTA, YUNO panting]
[YUNO] Stop this.
So much further to go.
Not yet. Still going.
[sighs]
Ow, ow, ow, ow,
ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
[ASTA yells]
I wish everybody back home
could get to try this, too.
Yeah.
This way!
Actually, this way.
Hey, wait up.
[BOTH gasp]
Stay out of my way!
Calm down. I was
just helping you.
Well, I don't need your help.
Gotcha!
[coughs]
No! My precious
moguro-leaf juice.
Why'd you stop?
[gasps]
Oh, wow! It's huge.
The capital! Finally!
[ASTA]
That's where the Wizard King is!
Here we go. Time to
do this thing!
Hope you're ready!
'Cause I'm comin'!
I will be the Wizard King! Yeah!
[NARRATOR] After a long
journey, Asta and Yuno
have finally arrived
at the royal capital
of the Clover Kingdom.
Awaiting them there
is the Magic Knights
Entrance Exam.
If they are to join
a Magic Knight squad,
they must face off against
one mighty foe after another.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[ASTA, YUNO]
"The Mystery of the Grimoires."
[gasps] What happened?
I think... we've shrunk.
Anyway, like I was saying.
My grimoire and yours
are totally different.
[YUNO]
Okay...
A grimoire's measurements.
It's size, thickness,
etcetera, are determined
based on its owner's talent.
All right then,
let's compare grimoires.
Come on, hand it over.
No way.
[ASTA]
Why not?
You're afraid you'll
lose, aren't you?
[YUNO]
Not a chance.
[ASTA]
Hey!
Don't get so cocky just 'cause
the girls kinda like you.
[YUNO]
Let it go.
[ASTA growls]
[ASTA]
C'mon, Yuno.
We've always wanted
to be Magic Knights!
This is the first
step on the road
to becoming the Wizard King!
Black Clover , Page Four:
"The Magic Knights
Entrance Exam"!
My magic is never giving up!