[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] When the Black
Bulls' hideout was attacked
by the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
Gauche, Gordon,
and Grey were aided
by an unfamiliar ally.
[HENRY] I won't let anyone
get away with hurting them.
These are my squadmates!
[HENRY]
Mana Corkscrew!
[NARRATOR] With the help of
Henry and his powerful magic,
these four Black Bulls
managed to drive away
Rades and his group
of miscreants. But...
How could we let this happen?
Whatever they stole
from our hideout,
they're long gone with it now!
Here it is.
[LICHT]
Well done.
[NARRATOR] The enemy had
run off with a magic stone
from inside the base.
Throughout all this...
Mereoleona's Royal Knights
were infiltrating
the Eye of the Midnight
Sun's fortress.
And Rhya the Disloyal,
the last of the Third Eye,
was on the move.
[RHYA] Apparently, we have a
real tricky bunch on our hands.
Seeing as Licht isn't around.
This is gonna be a pain.
Guess I'll have to suck it up.
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES groan]
[grunting]
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGE 91A]
His power--it's so intense!
Mercury Magic: Silver Bullets.
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES groan]
[yelling]
Silver Blades!
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES grunting]
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGE 91A]
Have a taste of this!
[NOZEL]
Silver Shining Regal Spear!
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES yelling]
He makes it look easy,
almost like he's up against
a bunch of novices.
I've never seen Sir Nozel
looking this determined before!
He's amazing.
[NOZEL] According to the
information I've gathered,
that Spatial Mage has
a habit of venturing
out of the fortress at
the same time every day.
That time is now.
We currently have our
own Spatial Mage outside
casting a Spatial Jamming spell.
That should prevent any other
mages from entering the base.
[NOZEL] Get ready, Licht.
I'm coming after you.
And I swear, I won't leave
until I've eliminated
you for good.
[KIRSCH]
Cherry Blossom Magic:
Raging Magic Cherry
Blossom Storm of Petals,
plus my beautiful illusion.
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGE 91E yelps]
What the hell is this?!
I was an arrogant man.
But I've cast all that aside,
along with my luscious hair.
This noble sacrifice
has allowed my already
great magic to increase
in potency, which means that
the rest of you will have room
to shine even more fully!
You've got a twisted idea
of what modesty is!
Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Waterball!
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES grunt]
[BEN]
Copper Magic: Red Shining Mace!
Ha!
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGE 91I groans]
Ben, was it?
I meant to tell you: congrats
on making the Royal Knights.
You should be proud.
Even though my team
crushed you to pieces.
Real classy, taking
the time to brag
in the middle of
a fight like this.
Besides, if I recall,
it was Yuno who defeated us.
[NOELLE]
Who cares about the details?!
[BEN]
I'm putting my all into this!
As a member of the
Crimson Lion Kings,
I know what happens
to Magic Knights
who disappoint
Captain Mereoleona!
[LUCK]
Lightning Magic: Thunder Fiend!
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES yelping]
[LUCK] Aw, man, this turned out
to be a really fun place.
Too bad Magna's not here.
Well, whatever!
I'll just have double
the fun and brag later!
Oh! Isn't that beautiful?
Ugh.
That's my Yuno!
There may be a ton of 'em,
but they're still wimps!
Piece o' cake!
We should keep moving.
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGE 91M]
I-It's no use.
The outcome's been decided.
[ALL]
Huh?
Oh, yeah? You giving up already?
We'll be reborn soon.
And then, we'll assume
our true forms.
Your "true forms"?
But I don't understand.
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGE 91M giggles]
[MIMOSA gasps]
Come to think of it,
what are all these markings?
There are more of them
the deeper we go.
How strange.
Huh? You see something, Yuno?
Listen.
[thumping]
[YUNO] Am I the only
one who hears that?
You morons need to get
some better traps.
I can see right through them.
Whatever spell you throw at us,
my anti-magic sword'll
slice it up!
[gasps]
[yelps]
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES yell]
[ZORA]
Ugh...
[BOTH]
Seriously, why are we here?
We can fight, too, y'know!
Don't you wanna
take a break soon?!
[ZORA]
Huh?
[BOTH] Whoa, there's two
of me! Is Grey here?
How'd you manage to pull
off a trick like that?
Clone spell?
[BOTH] Don't be a jerk!
You know I can't do magic!
Did I say you could
duplicate yourself?
[BOTH] Hey! It's not like
I had any choice in this!
So, How do we find out
which one is real?
They've even copied
the lack of magic.
What about you,
can you tell them apart?
Nope, sure can't.
[MEREOLEONA]
You're of no use to me.
I'm the real Asta!
No, I'm the real Asta!
Whatever! You're
obviously the fake one!
You're the fake one
and you know it!
[MEREOLEONA]
Stop yelling!
[growls]
[ASTAS yelp]
[ZORA]
That's one solution.
[ASTAS screaming]
What's wrong with you?!
You coulda killed me!
So this is the real one.
--[ASTA] Huh?
--You survived a trial by fire,
and I wouldn't have brought
anyone who couldn't.
[ASTA]
This lady is out of control!
[RHYA]
You've got that right.
[RHYA] She's a real
spitfire, isn't she?
[RHYA]
Copy Magic: Aqua Curtain.
Copy Magic: Healing
Light Particles.
You, my dear,
are downright scary.
Wait. I know you!
That's right. Call me Rhya.
And the pretty lady can call
me whatever she wants to.
Don't get too hung
up on her looks.
--She's strong, too.
--And who are you?
Seems like you would
be amusing to fight.
He's with the Third Eye,
the Eye of the Midnight
Sun's strongest fighters!
Oh?
Rhya the Disloyal.
He can copy other
people's magic abilities!
Now that you mention it,
I do know who he is.
[ASTA]
You forgot him?!
[ZORA] Hold on a second.
He's got a lot of power.
We're goin' toe-to-toe with him?
It's too bad that
you're royalty.
I was hoping you and I could
go out for a drink sometime.
Heh. I'll tell you what.
Why don't I send you to Hell,
and you can have a drink there?
Ooh, you really are scary.
No, thanks, though.
I've already tasted Hell,
and I didn't care for it.
Copy Magic: Dark
Cloaked Black Blade.
Hey, that's Captain
Yami's spell!
You can't rip him off like that!
I hate to break it to ya,
but copying people's
kinda my thing.
If he's that easy to mimic,
Yami's got a long way to go.
[RHYA]
Shall we start?
Just so ya know,
you won't be able
to dodge this one so easily!
Check out the stance.
That's the captain's, too!
Copy Magic: Dark Cloaked
Lightless Slash!
[gasps]
She burned up the
spell with a punch?
He's in trouble.
Nice impression, but
Yami's had more power.
Work on it.
Oh, yeah? Then--
[groans]
[MEREOLEONA] I'll show you
what destruction looks like!
Flame Magic: Calidos Brachium!
[RHYA grunts]
I'll burn this place down in
honor of my foolish brother!
[MEREOLEONA] I'll show you
what destruction looks like!
Flame Magic: Calidos Brachium!
[RHYA grunts]
[ZORA]
She's moving so fast. Plus,
those fiery fists are chock-
full of condensed magic.
It's a simple spell,
but it's effective.
She's a greater warrior than
any mage I've ever seen.
Awesome!
She's not fighting
him from a distance;
she's gettin' right in his face!
[gasps]
[ASTA] That gives me an idea!
I bet I can learn a lot
from how she handles
herself in close combat!
[yelps]
Copy Magic: Healing
Light Particles.
Argh! He healed up again!
[MEREOLEONA]
Hm.
Fine. I'm joining the fi--
[grunts, yelps]
Unless you wanna die,
just stand back and watch.
Aw!
[RHYA]
I see.
So this time, you're the
biggest thorn in my side.
However, I wouldn't
get too cocky
since you stole that
power from us, Royal.
Copy Magic: Light
Swords of Conviction!
[RHYA] She can't possibly
keep up at this speed.
[MEREOLEONA growls]
What's next?
[ASTA whimpering]
That was amazing,
I don't even care that
it set me on fire!
[RHYA] Her movements--
they're practically superhuman.
[RHYA]
Copy Magic: Invisible Seeker.
Jeez, talk about unoriginal.
Whose spell did he just use?
I know that one.
I think it was the former
captain of the Purple Orcas!
Copy Magic: Aqua Javelin!
[RHYA] She can change
direction in midair?
Try again!
[RHYA] She reacts almost
as quickly as Vetto!
[MEREOLEONA]
You can't escape!
Copy Magic: Tainted
Culvert Wyrm!
This is the most powerful
Water Magic we have!
How do you like it?
[roars]
[MEREOLEONA grunts]
[RHYA]
Copy Magic: Salamander's Breath!
Your move!
[RHYA] Water is her weakness
and Fire is her affinity,
but she can burn
through both of them?
You're getting on my nerves!
[MEREOLEONA]
Come on. Is that all you've got?
[RHYA grunts]
[MEREOLEONA growls]
Invisible--
[MEREOLEONA grunts]
[yelps, yells]
[RHYA grunts]
[MEREOLEONA]
Next!
[RHYA]
Copy Magic: Sticky Salamander!
[MEREOLEONA]
Next!
[RHYA]
Copy Magic: Jotunn's Ice Floe!
Calidos Brachium!
Next!
She's relentless.
Meroleona Vermillion.
She's as ferocious
as the rumors say.
I've done a little
research on her.
This beast of a woman spends
300 days a year living
in the woods and plains.
She says it's
because the capital
is too stifling and that
she prefers wild game.
Yum!
[ZORA] Because of all the
time she spent basking
in the mana of
the natural world,
word has it, she's taken
Mana Skin to the next level.
And judging by those
animalistic movements.
I'd be inclined to believe it.
This is the first I've
seen of this Rhya guy
and his Copy Magic,
but I feel like
I've got a good idea
of how it works.
It allows him to mimic
a spell from its attribute,
and that means that
he has every single
attribute at his fingertips.
Which is only possible because
of his astounding power.
[ZORA] Because of that,
any spell copied
from an average mage would be
more potent than the original.
But there's one
thing he can't do,
and that's cast a second attack
from a different attribute
while he's already
got one working.
We saw that when
he tried it before
and lost his transparency.
Most mages wouldn't
stand a chance
against a cheating
scumbag like him.
But, this is her.
[MEREOLEONA growls, yells]
[ASTA] Whoa! She keeps
gettin' cooler and cooler!
Isn't there any technique
I can steal from this fight
and use later? Anything?
[growls] You're such a pain!
Let's see how you counter this!
--What?
--[ZORA] No.
That's my sword!
[ZORA]
How did he do that?
I didn't know he could
copy antimagic, too!
[RHYA] All I need to do
to steal someone's magic
is touch their grimoire.
And when I was transformed,
I managed to make
contact with it.
Not bad, eh, Licht?
[yawns]
Copy Magic, huh? Great.
Well, I guess this is
kinda fitting for somebody
who's as empty as I am, right?
Actually, Rhya, you're
the kindest person I know.
Huh? What makes you say that?
Heh. You see people
for who they are,
and you can always
find the good in them.
I suppose that's why
you have that magic.
It's because I like people?
You can't use it
without first observing
and understanding someone.
It means you're kind.
[RHYA] You thought I was kind,
but you were wrong.
Not only am I disloyal,
I'm a lazy, worthless liar.
But Licht said so many
wonderful things about me.
He was truly the kind one.
And when you people deceived
him and killed him,
an unfathomable amount
of anger and hate
welled up inside of me!
Your time has come,
you foul humans!
I'm going to slaughter
every one of you!
[yells]
So it was just for show.
You can't copy
anti-magic after all.
[RHYA]
She thought it might be real
and she still punched me
without hesitation?
If I could use anti-magic,
it would have destroyed
that fist of hers!
And such intense mana...
This woman's incredible!
It's not just because
she's a royal.
This is a human strength
we've never known!
[MEREOLEONA]
Are you done playin' around?
[RHYA gasps]
Now then...
[RHYA] She's gone beyond
Mana Skin to control
all the mana in the area!
It's time to end this!
[MEREOLEONA] Mana Zone.
Calidos Brachium Barrage!
[MEREOLEONA yells]
[MEREOLEONA]
What's wrong, Mr. Third Eye?
Running out of spells?
Yeah, he's finished.
[RHYA] No time to use Fast
Movement or Recovery Magic.
What can I do now?
I had no idea she'd mastered
a Mana Zone attack!
[NARRATOR]
With the Mana Zone ability,
the user is able to
manipulate the mana
in the surrounding area to
suit his or her own purposes.
This means that any
mana-using techniques
activated within that zone
can be controlled, as well.
Try another attack! I dare you!
[NARRATOR] Additionally,
Mana Zone gives a massive boost
to sensitivity and
reaction speed.
Borrowing power
from nearby mana,
one can move freely
through the air.
[ZORA] She's too good,
it's gettin' ridiculous.
[ASTA] We struggled so hard
to beat the Third Eye,
and now look!
Captain Mereoleona,
you're so strong!
If that's really your best,
I'll punch you until
you're a pile of ashes!
Now, burn!
[RHYA]
Well, I guess that's it for me.
Wind Magic: Tornado
Fang, times three.
Huh?
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES groan]
Sorry, but you can't defeat me.
You don't have what it takes.
Nice one, Yuno!
[MIMOSA] His magic came
from behind them.
Could that be the ability
they call Mana Zone?
[MIMOSA]
Now that I think about it,
he cast a spell inside
another spell earlier.
And Spirit Dive...
He used Mana Zone to do it!
Yuno really is an
outstanding Magic Knight!
Do you hear that?
[gasps] I heard it before, too!
[YUNO]
A heartbeat?
The mana here feels so familiar.
[RHYA]
The Royal Knights, huh?
Eh, I might as well play
with them a little longer.
Black Clover , Page 92:
"The Wizard King vs.
the Leader of the Eye
of the Midnight Sun."
Go on, Licht. Crush that
Wizard King for good.