[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] A dungeon
surfaced near the border
between the Clover
and Diamond Kingdoms.
Asta, Noelle, and Luck of
the Black Bulls were dispatched
to explore it and
prevent the treasures
concealed within from
falling into enemy hands.
Whoa! This is like,
the most awesome place ever!
Hey, take a look at this, Asta.
Right there.
I don't see anything.
[LUCK]
Closer.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
[screams]
[NARRATOR]
The dungeon was thick with mana
and teeming with traps.
Wow, the looks on your faces!
That was fun, huh?
I could play in this
place all day!
[BOTH panting]
[ASTA, NOELLE] This guy is
totally going to get us killed.
Now, let's see what we've got.
[LUCK]
I'm just about at my limit.
I knew it.
We're not alone in here.
And the strongest
of them all is...
Sorry guys, but something
important's come up.
I gotta get going.
You two just go ahead and
get through the dungeon
on your own, and I'll
see ya soon, okay?
[LUCK laughs]
[ASTA] It's okay. We've got
nothin' to worry about.
Whatever traps are
in this place,
my sword'll slice
right through them, easy.
[NOELLE]
We're alone now.
It's just the two of us.
What's up? Is something wrong?
Uh! No, of course not! Insect!
Well? Hurry!
[gasps]
Oh, no! It's a trap!
Gimme a sec!
[NARRATOR]
Asta and Noelle found themselves
in grave danger.
But just then...
Not good.
[ASTA]
Oh, crap!
Such powerful magic.
And precision, too.
But, whose spell was that?
[YUNO]
And with that, my debt is paid.
Asta.
Hey, Yuno!
[ALECDORA]
Captain Vangeance!
[WILLIAM]
Yes, Alecdora, what is it?
Sir.
I have some concerns
regarding the exploration
of the newly discovered dungeon.
Forgive me, but why
send an untried commoner
on such a crucial mission?
Do I have your trust
as your leader and captain?
[ALECDORA]
Yes, of course.
I would follow you anywhere,
do anything you asked.
Even should it mean my death.
I trust you.
That's good.
I trust the "untried commoner,"
as you called him,
and I would ask you
to do the same.
After all, he is a
full-fledged member
of the Golden Dawn.
And for the sake of
the squad, I am certain
he will only continue
to grow stronger.
Sir.
[WILLIAM] Yes. Our new
member must grow stronger.
He must.
[ASTA chuckles]
[NOELLE]
So this is Yuno. And that's...
--Yuno.
--Sir.
[KLAUS]
Why did you go out of your way
to save these people?
We've been charged with
exploring this dungeon
and securing its
valuable contents.
Our primary objective is
to reach the treasure hall
at its heart with
all possible haste.
We have no time
to involve ourselves
with such rabble as these.
Jeez.
Who the hell is
Four-Eyes the Rude, here?
[YUNO]
My superior.
Excuse me?! And you
think that I'm rude?
Don't say that again, brat!
I am a noble, and you will
treat me with respect!
[YUNO] So much for not
involving ourselves.
Fancy running into
you here, Noelle.
Uh-huh...
We haven't seen each other
since last year's
royal banquet, isn't that right?
You know each other?
Yes, just a bit.
Actually, I'm Noelle's cousin.
[ASTA]
Uh-- Huh?
Well, this is quite a surprise.
[NOELLE]
It just had to be her.
From what I've heard,
the Black Bulls can be a rather
unrefined squad at times.
Are you doing
all right with them?
I think that's what I should
be asking you, Mimosa.
[MIMOSA]
Huh?
Can you actually keep up
with the elite members
of the Golden Dawn,
dim bulb that you are?
Sure!
Everyone is just
so incredibly kind.
I can wield my magic
with no qualms at all
knowing I have their support.
Oh! How thoughtless of me,
when you've always had
to struggle so much
with learning to
control your own magic.
Has that gotten any better?
[NOELLE] Clearly the girl
still doesn't have a filter.
Just fantastic.
Yes, it's coming
along fine, thank you.
Great! It's so wonderful
that we're both
finding our footing
as Magic Knights.
The Wizard King
even gave us a star
for our last mission!
[KLAUS]
Hmph.
[NOELLE, ASTA chuckle]
What a coincidence!
We got a star for
our last mission, too.
Huh.
You're a liar.
Brand-new members of
the slipshod Black Bulls?
It's inconceivable that you
could earn a star so easily.
Eh, heh...
Well, we did. So there!
And our total is up
to negative thirty now.
Ha! Not a chance.
Why, you're being sent on this
mission is absurd enough.
Guess the Wizard King
didn't think so,
'cause he's the one who sent me!
Yet another bald-faced lie.
It is not a lie!
[KLAUS]
Hah!
[YUNO]
Yeah, we're definitely involved.
Now that I think of it.
I was told that there were
going to be three of you.
So, where is your third member?
[BOTH]
Uh...
[KLAUS] What, did they
run away and leave you here
to explore the dungeon
on your own? Was that it?
Or perhaps they fell victim
to a trap spell? Hah!
[NOELLE]
He didn't run away,
and he didn't get
caught in some trap.
So where is he, then?
[ASTA, NOELLE]
Uh...
Almost there!
[ASTA]
He took off into the dungeon
because he's basically nuts?
[NOELLE]
Thanks, Luck.
Whatever the case,
he's a coward who left his
newest colleagues behind.
A typical Black Bull.
How disgusting.
Your whole squad brings
shame to the Magic Knights.
Okay, now you've
really done it, pal.
The Black Bulls are gonna
conquer this dungeon so fast,
you won't even
know what hit you!
Just you watch! Golden Dumb!
Uh, Golden Dim?
No, uh...
Squad with the
Weird-Haired Boss!
I've heard enough.
First you insult
our intelligence
and then our captain?
How dare you?!
Mocking our leader,
the incomparable
Captain Vangeance?
You will pay!
Besides, you're the
one whose captain
walks around in a ratty old top,
flaunting his
overinflated muscles
and smoking like a chimney!
What, are you crazy?
Or maybe you're just jealous
'cause Yami's manlier than you!
I am a senior Magic
Knight and a noble!
Show some respect, you filth!
Oh, begging your pardon,
sir. I'm so sorry !
Damn you!
[YUNO] "Involved" doesn't
even begin to cover it.
[KLAUS, ASTA panting]
All right, enough
of this idiocy.
I'll show you the
difference between
the top Magic Knight
squad in the kingdom
and the one that doesn't
deserve the name.
Mimosa!
Sure!
All right. Plant Creation Magic:
Magic Flower Guidepost.
[BOTH gasp]
[MIMOSA]
Let's see. Yes, yes, okay.
I've got the dungeon's layout.
I should be able to
find the treasure hall.
Good. Yuno?
[YUNO]
Yes, sir.
They all make it look so easy.
Do your best, poor as it is.
Good work, Yuno.
Yeah!
Let's go! You comin'?
Hey! Wait, no!
[YUNO, ASTA]
We'll fight to see
who will reach the
treasure hall first.
Whatever it takes!
Great! Now what do we do?
It's not as if either
of us are equipped
to use exploration
magic, you know!
We just check out every path
until we find the
right one. Let's do this!
What are you, insane?
Oh, yeah, that's right, you are.
This ingenious idea of yours
isn't going to get us
anywhere but lost.
[NOELLE]
Nero?
--[NOELLE gasps]
--[ASTA laughs]
[MIMOSA]
Next, we take a right.
[YUNO]
Okay.
That brat's name was Asta?
That little fool.
Does he honestly think he
can get the better of us?
He does seem a most unusual boy.
I sensed not a bit
of magic power in him.
No, neither did I.
[KLAUS] What was the
Black Bull captain thinking?
How could someone like
that be of any use
to a Magic Knight squad?
[YUNO]
Klaus, sir.
Asta's strong.
I would suggest not
underestimating him.
As far as I'm concerned,
it will be a miracle if they
make it out of here alive.
All we need to concentrate
on is capturing
this dungeon swiftly
for the good of our kingdom.
[MESSENGER 15A]
Reporting, Wizard King, sir.
Teams have been dispatched
by the Golden Dawn
and the Black Bulls.
They have begun their
exploration of the dungeon.
Also...
We have confirmed that
the Diamond Kingdom's
mage troops have
entered as well.
[OFFICIALS]
What?
[OFFICIAL 15A]
Diamond Kingdom!
[OFFICIAL 15C] They'd better
not get their hands
on the dungeon's treasure.
[OFFICIAL 15B] They've been
particularly focused
on expanding their
territory lately.
[OFFICIAL 15C]
They're always the aggressor.
[OFFICIAL 15D] If we let their
people take the ancient magic
from the dungeon, who knows
what kind of trouble
they'll cause?
These Diamond mage troops.
Who's their leader?
Sir!
The enemy troops appear
to be commanded
by Lotus of the Abyss.
--[JULIUS] Ah!
--[OFFICIALS murmuring]
[JULIUS] We met on the
battlefield once upon a time.
He was certainly tough. Crafty.
Uses the most
interesting magic, too.
Sir! This is no time
to be so nonchalant.
A graver tone, please?
All will be well, don't worry.
I believe Yami also sent
along someone interesting.
Still.
Lotus may be powerful, Marx,
but our young recruits...
They are, too.
Aw.
[LUCK]
You're all so weak.
But you're much stronger
than them, right?
Well. I don't know
about all that.
Don't like to
raise expectations.
It only leads to disappointment.
So much raw, young power.
I'm intimidated, to be honest.
You took out my underlings
with so little effort.
Truly impressive.
[laughs] Like you said,
they were underlings.
They can afford to
be weak so long as
their leader is powerful.
[LOTUS] I see that you fight
by surrounding yourself
with lightning magic.
How very resourceful of you.
Your attacks must
pack quite a punch.
You're fast, as well.
And all of that is fed
by your youthful vigor.
My, you've got this old
man scared, all right.
And what about you, then?
What magic do you fight with?
Goodness, you are an
eager one, aren't you?
[LOTUS] I'm assuming you
Clover folks came in search
of the dungeon's
treasure hall, too.
Yeah. Now, let's fight!
Oh, I don't know.
I mean, it's not like
we really need to fight.
We can just have a nice,
friendly footrace.
No violence or
bloodshed necessary.
What do ya think? It sounds
like a good idea to me.
Come on, let's go!
No way!
[LOTUS]
Fast, indeed.
[LUCK]
He dodged!
Smoke?
[LOTUS]
Oh. I'm terribly frightened.
Hm.
I can understand why your people
would be so angry with mine.
Obviously, no one likes
having their country invaded.
I don't blame you. Truly.
And we of the Diamond
Kingdom apologize
for the inconvenience.
It's just, we've found
ourselves running low
on resources, you know?
What choice do we have
if we want to live?
Living can be so very hard.
See,
I have three daughters of
my own I need to provide for.
Oh, yeah?
[laughs]
Whatever, "old man."
I'm just happy to finally be
fighting somebody powerful.
[chuckles] You're a real piece
of work. You know that, right?
You may reduce me to tears.
[screaming]
[NOELLE, ASTA yelping]
[NOELLE]
What's with this place?
The gravity's gone haywire!
Hey, birdbrain, are you sure
this is the right way?
Come on! Nero! Wake up!
Look at that! It's treasure!
It definitely is not!
[ASTA yells]
Don't go after it!
Only a complete idiot wouldn't
see that it's a trap.
[ASTA]
All right! Gotcha now!
[NOELLE]
Stop! Don't open it!
[ASTA screams]
My sweet treasure chest.
What's inside of you?
Will you let it go?
What are you going
to do if it's a trap?
[ASTA]
And, open!
[BOTH]
Uh...
[NOELLE]
Wh-What did you just
make me look at, you jerk?
--[blows landing]
--[ASTA yelping]
[ASTA]
It's not like I knew what was--
[ASTA retches]
[LUCK yells]
You're quite
a hot-blooded youth.
It's no fun if you just dodge
my attacks. Fight back!
Well?
Aw, c'mon!
[LOTUS]
Phew.
[laughs]
Ah, yes. I remember that robe.
You're a Black Bull, aren't you?
I actually had the dubious honor
of fighting your captain once.
He was a spitfire, like you.
Wow! You really
know Captain Yami?
[LOTUS] I'm not likely
to forget him, either.
Not after he left me
such a splendid memento.
Wet my pants and ran
as fast as I could.
Now, that was truly
a scary fellow.
Ah... He had a rather
unique fighting style.
He was the only person
younger than me
who I couldn't defeat.
You're totally worth fighting--
[heartbeats]
[LUCK gasping]
Oh? You don't look well.
Something wrong?
Nothing. I'm... fine.
[LOTUS]
Too slow!
[LUCK grunting]
[LOTUS]
Down you go now, nice and easy.
Down into the abyss.
[LUCK]
What's going on?
A spell? But...
I don't remember being
hit with anything.
[chuckles] You see, I have
something to confess.
The air in here's full
of my magic power.
An extremely thin smoke,
too thin for the eye to see.
Oh, and in case
you're interested,
it's called
Weakening Smoke Magic:
Garden of Plundering Smoke.
[LUCK] My body...
It's not moving right.
[LUCK gasps]
[LUCK] Magic that reduces
physical ability.
But when did he...?
Visible attacks can
only do so much.
They're easy enough for
an opponent to dodge.
I opted for a more
subtle approach.
So I used every last drop
of my magic power
and cast it stealthily.
Fighting off my
underlings provided
a more than
adequate distraction.
[gasping]
[LOTUS]
Their defeat was regrettable,
but it wasn't in vain.
Their sacrifice gave me the
opportunity to work my magic.
[LUCK pants]
You know, it truly is vital.
Teamwork.
We're almost there now.
It should be just
through this hallway.
[MIMOSA gasps]
Isn't that simply marvelous?
[KLAUS]
Hmph. Some dungeon that was.
Not much to it at all.
So what's your plan
for getting past this?
It doesn't appear
as if the Black Bulls
have managed to find it yet.
Of course they haven't.
Despite their bluster,
they never stood a chance
of beating us here.
[MIMOSA]
You're probably right.
[gasps]
[KLAUS, YUNO gasp]
[KLAUS]
Mimosa!
[KLAUS] It pierced through
her cloak of magical defense!
Such a keen mana sense,
but she never saw it coming!
She's still alive!
[KLAUS]
This is no trap magic.
So, what is it?
Who goes there?
[MARS]
You're in my way.
Now move.
[LOTUS]
See, what you really need
are friends you know
you can count on.
Well, sorry about this,
but I've got things to do.
You know how it is.
[panting]
[LUCK'S MOTHER]
Win.
[LUCK panting]
[LUCK'S MOTHER]
Keep on winning, Luck.
Hold on.
It's been too long...
...since things've gotten
this interesting.
[chuckles]
Oh, yeah!
Let's do this.
Time to fight!
So much potential.
I'm almost sorry
to extinguish it.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[LOTUS]
"A Lotus That Won't Bloom
is Just Another Water Lily!"
See.
I have three daughters of
my own I need to provide for.
[LOTUS high pitched]
"When I'm all grown up,
I'm gonna marry Daddy!"
My girls dote on me,
but of course, there's no
telling how long that will last.
Oh, yes. I can just hear it now.
[LOTUS high pitched]
"Go away!"
"We can take care
of our own laundry!"
Teenagers are truly scary.
What a sad man.
Sounds like he could really use
a good fight to cheer him up.
[LOTUS]
...forget about it!
[LUCK]
It's not over yet.
Things are finally getting good!
Let's play some more!
Let's see who dies first!
Okay, old man?
Black Clover ,
Page 16: "Friends."
My magic is never giving up!