[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR]
Finral Roulacase, member of the
Black Bulls Magic Knight squad,
had some concerns.
Some very serious concerns.
[FINRAL]
What now? What should I do?
[NARRATOR] Was it a mission
that had him so preoccupied?
[FINRAL]
The mixer tonight!
[NARRATOR]
No. He was planning a mixer,
a party meant to
help men and women
forge closer friendships.
[FINRAL] Let's see, how
do I wanna arrange this?
I have three ladies
lined up already.
Mm. A line of ladies.
No! Focus, Finral.
You have to decide which
squadmates to bring with you.
Asta's a firecracker, so he's
a must. But I need one more.
[MAGNA]
Flame Magic...
My Exploding...
...Fireball!
[MAGNA laughs]
Home run, baby!
Oh, yeah! Nice one!
[FINRAL] Maybe. Girls do like
the whole bad boy thing.
Hey, ladies. You wanna
see a real man's ride?
Check out my Crazy Cyclone here.
Just hop on and I'll treat you
to the full Magna experience.
[WOMAN 28A]
Hm...
[WOMAN 28B]
Uh...
[WOMAN 28C sighs]
[FINRAL] But Magna's more
of an "acquired taste."
--Huh?
--[tapping]
[GAUCHE pants]
Almost there.
Soon I'll have a life-size
statue of my Marie
in all her glory!
Oh, Marie. I can feel
you here beside me.
My beloved little sister.
My precious...
[FINRAL]
No. I can just see it now.
Take a look at my Marie.
Have you ever seen
anybody more angelic?
No. Because there is no one
who can compare to her.
[WOMAN 28B]
Ew. So gross.
[FINRAL]
That's one way to kill the mood.
[GORDON mumbling]
I heard about the mixer,
and I'd be happy to go
with you if you want.
It's not like
I'm not into girls...
Nobody knows what Gordon
is thinking, ever.
So, no.
A-Ah...
[GREY grunting]
[FINRAL sighs]
[sighs] Charmy might
liven things up a bit
if I brought her, like a
little mascot. Although...
Excuse me! Can I get some more?
Very sorry.
We only opened five minutes ago,
but we're already out of food.
[whines]
That would be a disaster.
Okay, no Charmy, then.
So, what about Vanessa?
[FINRAL] Assuming she's
sober. That's a no-go.
Yeah, now, that's what
I'm talkin' about.
I could see if Captain
Yami wants to go.
Some ladies have a thing
for older men, right?
Except, he is a little
rough around the edges.
What's up with those goofy
little outfits, anyway?
Huh? Not wearing any
hats or gloves, either.
You oughta cover up more.
Jeez. You wanna catch
a cold or somethin'? Well?
[WOMAN 28A]
Uh...
[WOMAN 28B]
What?
[WOMAN 28C]
Seriously?
[FINRAL]
Hard pass.
[YAMI]
Hm?
That just leaves me
with one option.
A mixer? Okay.
Excellent, I'm glad
you're on board.
[FINRAL]
Yeah. Luck at least looks sane.
He should do fine.
Hey, what is a mixer?
This'll be great.
[FINRAL]
All right! We're all set.
So, wearing our robes is okay?
We wanna make it crystal clear
that we're Magic Knights.
The people look up to us.
I see no reason not to use
that to our advantage.
Sure, I got it!
So what are mixers like, anyway?
Think we'll get to fight?
I don't know. I've never
been to one before!
Yeah, just great.
Okay, let's go.
Well? You coming?
Yes, sir!
[mumbling] Can I come, too?
I won't get in the--
Aw...
[ASTA]
Out we go!
[LUCK]
Ooh!
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
Good. Made it.
[NOELLE grunting]
[NOELLE]
What was I thinking,
skulking after them
to some silly mixer?
I got all worried
because that cretin
wants to indulge himself in
a little low-brow socializing.
[yelps]
[NOELLE]
No, I am not thinking about him!
He's a useless muscle-head,
and I couldn't care less
what he wants to do
with his free time.
Argh! Who am I making
excuses to, anyway?
[FINRAL]
Mm... Right. Let's see.
Where...
Ah! Good, there we go!
Well, looks like everybody's
got drinks now.
I'd say introductions
are in order.
I'll start, then, shall I?
I'm, Finral Roulacase.
Twenty-one-year-old Spatial
Magic user from Touda,
and a Black Bulls squad member.
Hi, there.
[BOTH]
Ooh!
[FINRAL] Have a
freshly-picked moon blossom
as a symbol of our acquaintance.
[HELENE]
Oh, wow! How nice.
These are hard to get.
They only bloom at
night on Mount Anahu.
They smell so good!
Thank you.
[FINRAL] All right,
I've got them interested!
I'll land a girlfriend
this time for sure.
I just need Asta and Luck
to pull their weight.
Now, who would like
to introduce themselves?
I guess I'll go.
[LUCK] This shouldn't be
too hard, right? Okay!
I'm Luck Voltia,
18 years old, from Ibon.
I'm a member of the
Black Bulls, too.
My favorite thing is
life or death battles
against super-strong opponents--
the bloodier the better!
And my motto is "do or die"!
[ASTA]
It's my turn.
A real man would
probably talk about
his dreams and stuff, huh?
All right!
Hi, I'm Asta.
I'm 15, from Hage Village,
and I'm a Black Bull.
And, um, my dream is
to be the Wizard King.
[ERIKA]
Uh, the Wizard King?
[HELENE]
No way. He's just a kid.
[ERIKA]
I don't know about these two.
[HELENE, ERIKA]
They look like trouble.
[ERIKA] It's great that they're
Magic Knights and all,
but did they have
to be Black Bulls?
Ugh, lowest of the low.
[HELENE]
Isn't Hage a commoner village?
In the middle of nowhere?
[ERIKA]
If he isn't taller, wealthier,
and of a higher social standing
than I am, what's the point?
[HELENE]
Just forget it.
[FINRAL]
Uh-oh.
I'm not getting an
"interested" vibe.
Okay! Well, that does it for us.
Now, let's hear all about you!
We're dying to
learn more, ladies.
You ready? Let's go!
Well. I don't know
what to say, really.
We're all friends.
I'm Erika, and I work
for a dressmaker.
I'm Helene, and I work
at a barbershop.
Rebecca, I work at a restaurant.
[FINRAL]
Nope, not interested at all.
Wow! You all work, that's great.
I'd love to hear a little bit
more about what you do.
Maybe you could
make me an outfit.
What do you think
would look good on me?
Would you give me a haircut?
I think it's time for me
to try out a new look.
Can I drop in for a bite?
[FINRAL]
Well, that didn't work.
What's a topic that
might reel them in?
So.
Wanna hear about what
we do as Magic Knights?
Yes, that would be wonderful.
Please, tell us everything.
[FINRAL]
Bingo!
I'm happy to oblige.
I get to see a lot of different
places as a Spatial Magic user.
I could tell you about
some of my recent travels.
Please do!
[FINRAL]
Ah-- Well...
Hey, I need to get
to the john quick.
Right.
Finral, it's bath time.
So, uh, I'm ready for bed.
Right.
[FINRAL] Lately, all I've been
doing is dealing with Yami.
Luck! You've been working hard.
Tell us about it.
Who, me?
Well, go on now, don't be shy.
The ladies said they
wanted to hear everything.
My work, huh? Let me think.
Oh! I was fighting these
bad guys, you know?
Bandits.
[HELENE, ERIKA]
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
And, oh, boy. Wow.
Talk about a bloodbath!
I coulda just killed
'em if I wanted,
but I decided to be
nice and let 'em go
with a few bones
still left intact.
[FINRAL]
You're not helping, Luck!
Then another time,
I was fighting this
really strong mage...
Yeah, thanks, Luck!
Now, aren't you getting hungry?
Well, I'd like to
hear from Asta.
He helped protect the royal
capital, didn't you, Asta?
Oh, yeah. That's right.
Wait!
Are you talking about
the attack the other day?
That sounded so scary.
[FINRAL]
Our Asta wasn't scared, though.
He even got a promotion.
[BOTH]
Wow!
[FINRAL]
All right, got 'em!
Now we just need to keep
the conversation on track.
That's amazing!
[ASTA]
The people we were fighting
were really tough, though.
Managed to put three
new holes in me,
and man did it hurt!
Wow, it's all squishy, too.
[ASTA] Ow! Jeez, keep
your hands to yourself!
[FINRAL]
Ah! They're useless!
What was I thinking
bringing these two?
None of my squadmates
are mixer material!
[ASTA] C'mon, stop it!
Look, they're bleeding again!
[LUCK]
Ooh, really?
[ASTA]
Well, no.
[NOELLE]
Maybe I didn't need to keep
an eye on things, after all.
The mixer doesn't look
like it's going well.
Not that I care.
Dorksta's social life has
nothing to do with me.
[CUSTOMER 28A]
Excuse me, miss! Over here!
Huh?
Another round, please.
Go get it yourself. I'm busy.
[CUSTOMER 28A]
Brr...
[SEKKE] So, you heard about
that business in the capital
the other day, right?
Well, I was there
guarding a VIP,
so I got in on the action, too.
Took out a fair number
of attackers myself,
as a matter of fact.
Ha, ha!
I didn't expect
to get a promotion
just for doing my duty, truly.
What's a boy to do, though?
I know I didn't
deserve the honor,
but they insisted, so, well...
[laughs] Oh, dear.
I may be a tad drunk.
On myself.
And what were you doing
during the attack?
Reading that dirty
book of yours?
What? Shut up.
You don't know what you're
talkin' about, Sekke.
Hey, something wrong?
Does being around us
make ya nervous?
[WOMEN sigh]
You've got nothing
to worry about, ladies.
We won't bite, I swear.
[WOMAN 28D]
He just squeezed that lemon
right on the chicken.
[WOMAN 28E] Just listening
to this guy makes me sick.
[NOELLE] Things look even
worse at that table.
Wait, haven't I met
that guy before?
I think...
Right! It's Ha, Ha!
I knew my Bronze Magic was good,
but I never suspected
it was that good.
Honestly, sometimes
I scare myself.
Hey, you there! Get me
another drink, at once!
[BOYS groan]
[gasps] So that's the magic
you use to cut hair? Cool!
Yep, this is it. Here, see?
Wow!
It doesn't take
much magic power,
but your control
has to be stellar.
Show me more!
[gasps] Well,
if you want me to.
[HELENE]
His eyes are so genuine.
How can someone that
bloodthirsty be so cute?
And why does it make
my stomach all tingly?
Oh, no!
Do I have a secret love
for dangerous men?
Hey, Luck.
Do you think I could
see your magic, too?
Yeah, sure. It's kinda
tight in here.
Let's go out front, 'kay?
[HELENE]
Great!
[FINRAL]
Nice. Well done, Luck.
Anyway, the sunrise
is so beautiful there,
you wouldn't believe it.
Wow.
I'll use my Spatial Magic
to take us there sometime.
How does that sound?
It sounds good, actually.
Oh, your mug's empty.
Excuse me, another
round, please!
[ERIKA] A little too flashy
and not really my type,
but he's the best of the three.
He looks like a noble,
and Spatial Magic
does come in handy.
Plus, he's attentive.
Well, shall we go
to the veranda?
[ERIKA]
Sure, that would be nice.
[FINRAL]
Phew.
For a while there, things
weren't looking good,
but now I think this might
just be my lucky night!
[ASTA]
Ugh. So awkward.
Why's she staring off
to the side like that?
Is she mad? Is there
something on my face?
I can't take it anymore!
I don't really know how, but
I've got to make this better.
I'm not done yet!
So, um!
[REBECCA]
Mm?
Do you have a favorite
food or anything?
Me, I like pop-potatoes.
[sighs] You don't
have to try so hard
to make conversation. It's okay.
Getting all dressed up and
coming out was Erika's idea.
She thinks I need a man
for my siblings' sake.
But I don't even
want to be here.
I've spent the whole
time worrying about
my brothers and
sisters back home.
Wow, how many
siblings do you have?
Three little brothers
and two sisters.
Hey, that sounds like me!
Huh?
Well, we're not actually
related or anything,
but I have five sorta-siblings.
They're a bunch of rascals.
I miss 'em now that
I'm gone, though.
We had fun even though
we didn't always get along.
Yeah, we slept squished
up like sardines.
When I joined the Magic Knights,
I got a room all to myself,
which was nice, but, y'know,
it's kinda lonely not havin'
a pack of restless little kids
in there with me.
Oh, yeah!
They can be so annoying,
but then you miss them
when they're not around.
I know!
Plus, they help keep
me in line sometimes
because I always want them
to think the best of me--
it's weird!
I totally understand.
Hey, wait! She's
actually laughing now?
How could this be happening?
[BAR OWNER 28A] H-Hey! What kind
of serving girl are you?
I gave you a chance since
you were begging for a job,
and then you send
customers flying
and start breaking my plates?
That's enough out of you.
[BAR OWNER 28A yelps]
I'm not surprised
you're a big sister.
You seem like the type.
I have to admit,
you don't really come across
as the oldest in your family.
There was actually
another kid there my age.
His name's Yuno.
[DRUNK MAN 28A]
Well, well!
[DRUNK MAN 28A] Havin' some
fun over here, are we?
Mister Fancy Magic Knight.
Whoa. You're a runty thing.
And you're in the
Magic Knights? Really?
Must not be too hard to get in.
Maybe I oughta give it a try.
I mean, they let you join.
Yeah, sometimes I still
don't even believe it myself.
Hey, now.
Y'gotta lotta nerve goin'
after a pretty lady like her.
What's she want
with you, anyway?
Got a thing for Magic Knights?
[REBECCA growls]
Huh? Oh. You look familiar.
I've seen you somewhere.
Ah!
Workin' in that restaurant with
a kid strapped to your back.
You're always sweatin'
your tail off,
surrounded by a buncha brats.
[laughs]
Those your kids
hangin' around, huh?
Did your man leave
ya high and dry?
No! I am not their mother!
No wonder you're tryin'
to land a Magic Knight.
That sure would make
your life easier.
Well, you're pretty enough.
You want a man that bad?
Lemme help ya, sweet cheeks.
Hey! Get off! Let me go!
Huh?
I don't know what you think
you're doing, old man,
but you better let her go.
You don't know the first
thing about that woman.
Ooh, so scary.
I'm quakin' in my boots,
Mister Magic Knight.
What kinda spell are
you gonna throw at me?
Actually, I can't use magic.
Wha...? You're a Magic Knight
who can't do magic?
Is that some kinda joke?
[laughs]
[ASTA]
Nope. But check this out.
[ASTA yells]
[groans]
[ALL]
Huh?
[BOYS groan]
Forget it. Let's get
out of here.
[WOMAN 28D]
What a waste of time.
[WOMAN 28E]
Want to go somewhere else?
What did you do to my table?
[gasps] We gotta go! Quick!
[BAR OWNER 28A]
Wait, come back!
I just remembered, there's
somewhere I need to be.
[BAR OWNER 28A]
Huh? Hey!
[NOELLE panting]
[gasps]
[REBECCA panting]
You were really
great back there.
Thank you so much.
[ASTA]
No problem.
Sorry I kinda ruined
the mixer for you.
You didn't, though.
[REBECCA]
He's on the short side,
but there's somethin'
about this kid.
[gasps] Hey, Asta?
Do... Do you have anyone
who's special to you?
Yes! I've got my heart
set on someone!
[NOELLE]
What?!
Oh, okay. She must
be pretty amazing.
[ASTA]
She is! She's from my--
I'll be rooting for you.
Yeah? Thanks!
Hey, you should
come over sometime
and meet the kids.
I think they'd like you.
[ASTA]
You got it!
"From my" what?
[gasps]
[NOELLE] From my squad?
Wait, does that mean?
Is it possible? Could he
be talking about m-m-m--?
No. No way.
And so what if he is?
It's not like it matters.
Not to me. Not at all.
Not one tiny, little bit.
[ASTA] Keep waiting
for me, Sister Lily.
One day, after I've
become the Wizard King,
I'll come back for you,
and when I do, please marry me!
[REBECCA]
I may be rooting for him,
but that doesn't
mean I'm giving up.
Oh, yeah! I never
figured it out.
What was the point of
the whole mixer thing?
[REBECCA]
What?!
[NOELLE]
[ERIKA] He threw some
drunk guy into a table.
Those Black Bull Knights
are such savages.
Yeah. Seriously.
Rejected.
[LUCK chuckles]
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[GORDON] "If Gordon, Grey,
and Sekke Went to a Mixer."
I'm Helene!
I'm Erika!
[mumbling] Hey, I'm
Gordon. You're pretty.
Will you be my friend?
That would make me happy.
--You will, really? Thank you.
--[GREY exhales]
Ha, ha!
[mumbling] Will you please
give me your address, too?
I'll send letters.
Not too often.
Ha, ha, ha!
Or maybe one a day.
[exhales]
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
[HELENE, ERIKA]
Ah! Somebody save me!
[ASTA]
I'm gonna be the Wizard King.
I won't let anybody
get in my way.
Commoners can climb to the top.
I'll show them all!
Black Clover , Page 29: "Path."
Not yet. I'm not done!
My magic is never giving up!