[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[LICHT]
Rhya. Let's go.
[NARRATOR]
Licht and the reincarnated elves
headed toward the royal capital.
Well. 'Bout that time.
Let's go pay the rest
of our friends a visit,
and then, we'll wipe
out all humankind!
All right! Go!
[NARRATOR] Asta and Yuno
were making their way there
as well to head off
the invasion.
But during their trip, they
realized that their hometown
of Hage Village
was under attack,
so they parted ways with
Nozel and the others.
[BOTH]
Stay back, it's our turn now!
Poison Plant Magic:
Zofnir's Breath.
And Zofnir's Fingers,
for good measure.
[yelling]
[NARRATOR] Asta tried
desperately to rid the priest
of Poison Plant Magic,
but even with the help
of the Demon-Slayer Sword,
the spell's effects
appeared impossible to reverse.
You're not done yet!
Ya hear me?!
Don't die. You can't die!
You were supposed to
stick around for a while
to watch over us.
To see me through!
To see all of us through!
[ASTA]
That sword... It's his!
I saw it back at the
Midnight Sun's hideout!
It must've slipped into
my grimoire somehow!
[ASTA]
Maybe if I use it, I can...!
[ASTA screams, growls]
[screaming]
[CHILDREN gasp]
I know that sword!
It's the same one that
creepy guy had earlier!
That weapon.
Why does he have it?
Oh, Asta. I'm scared!
Hey, what's going on here?
[panting]
[ASTA] This sword's got
tons more dark power
flowin' into it than
the ones I used before.
Gotta stay focused!
I can't go against the flow.
I need to take it in.
Think like it's
a part of my body!
[inhales]
[ASTA]
Now!
[yells]
[CHILDREN gasp]
What is this?
[VILLAGERS groaning]
[ALL gasp]
Look!
[LILY]
The poison's disappearing!
[ASTA]
Please, this has to work!
[gasps]
[CHILDREN crying]
[CHILDREN]
Father!
What? I'm alive?
Or am I dreaming?
I thought that this
would be the end of me.
[ARLU]
No, Asta made you all better!
[HORO]
Yeah!
I was so worried.
Wow, Asta, you really are
amazing, you know that?
He's okay!
Oh, man, and this sword
is crazy-powerful.
I can barely control the thing!
[ASTA]
Wait, that's it!
Maybe, now that I have this,
I can find a way to change
everyone back to normal!
[gasps]
[DIGIT] He managed to eradicate
all of the poison's effects!
I don't believe it!
Focus on your opponent.
[YUNO]
Mana Zone:
Crescent Moon Sickle,
Four Blades!
What? But, why? And how?
You're under the same
Reincarnation spell
as the rest of us.
So why is the will of your
human host still in control?
And you! That blade
belongs to Licht,
so how did it get
into your filthy hands?
What's more, someone
without any magic power
shouldn't be able
to wield it at all!
How is this possible?
Who are you, anyway?!
[DIGIT growls, groans]
[BOTH gasp]
You... You disgust me.
You insufferable,
putrid human garbage!
Oh, good!
Now I can make it to
Licht's wedding, after all!
Don't tell me you're
gonna give him
those freaky flowers
as a present.
That's a bad move.
What? You don't think
he would like them?
But they're pretty,
and they're not the
poisonous kind, either.
[LICHT]
They're lovely.
[RYHA, DIGIT]
Licht!
And they have a special meaning.
"Kindness dwells within."
They simply appear poisonous
so elves and birds
don't disturb them.
Since the insects
know that, to them,
these flowers are a sanctuary.
Oh.
Between elves and humanity,
it's the same thing.
We lack an understanding,
so we avoid each other.
Tetia's going to enjoy
these, too. Thank you.
Sure. Of course.
[DIGIT]
We tried to understand.
And they made it
perfectly clear.
They were all monsters!
[DIGIT]
Humans. I can never forgive you!
So stay out of our way,
or you're dead!
[screams]
[gasps]
[ASTA]
Wait, I've felt this before.
[DIGIT] Humans, humans,
humans, humans, humans,
humans, humans...
He's not even trying
to hold back his magic.
He can't control himself!
You're right.
His mana says it all.
The elf spirit inside him
is crying out in pain.
[ASTA] Is it possible?
Are the elves asking for help?
Hey, Yuno!
[YUNO]
Let's go, Asta!
He's turning into something
that's not an elf at all!
We should set him free!
[DIGIT screaming]
What's happening?
It looks like he just
blocked Yuno's attack!
Nice, Yuno!
I made you a path,
Asta. Now, strike!
[screaming]
[ASTA growling]
[DIGIT screaming]
[DIGIT]
They were all monsters!
Humans. I can never forgive you!
So stay out of our way,
or you're dead!
[screaming]
[gasps]
Humans, humans, humans,
humans, humans,
humans, humans, humans,
humans, humans...
He's not even trying
to hold back his magic.
He can't control himself!
You're right.
His mana says it all.
The elf spirit inside him
is crying out in pain.
[ASTA] Is it possible?
Are the elves asking for help?
Hey, Yuno!
[YUNO]
Let's go, Asta!
He's turning into something
that's not an elf at all!
We should set him free!
[DIGIT screaming]
I made you a path,
Asta. Now, strike!
[screaming]
[ASTA growls]
[DIGIT screaming]
[YUNO] Did he undo the
Reincarnation Magic?
[ASTA] Now that I have
this sword, I can save them!
[BELL]
Yuno's the only reason we won,
so you'd better say thank you!
Come on, I think I deserve
a little credit, too, right?
No, I definitely did
100 percent of the work.
All you did was hold the sword.
If you did 100 percent,
then I musta done 500 percent!
Yeah, that isn't how math works.
Dummy.
[ARLU, NASH]
Asta!
[REKKA, HORO]
Yuno!
I thought he was gonna kill us,
and then you showed up
just in time to stop him.
You're so brave!
You were brave, too, Nash,
protectin' the others like that!
Thank you for saving us!
[HORO]
That was scary!
[BELL]
Okay, okay!
We get it, now give
Yuno some space!
Wow, look, she's so
tiny and beautiful!
Yeah, she's like a doll!
--[ARLU] Let's play dress-up!
--[BELL] Hey, watch the outfit!
[BELL]
No!
[HIGH PRIEST]
Asta. Yuno.
[YUNO]
Father!
Are you okay?
Of course. I'm a bit
dizzy, but I'll survive.
The poison's fading from
the other villagers, as well.
We can't thank you
enough for this.
[LILY]
What a blessing.
Both of you have grown up
to be so strong!
Does that mean you wanna
marry me now, Sister Lily--?
[LILY] Water Creation Magic:
Holy Fist of Love!
Oops! I did that out of habit!
[ASTA] Agh. I didn't know
how much I missed this!
Do it again, Sister!
Again?
What an idiot.
Hey, Yuno, your ears
are all pointy now!
Yeah, they are!
That's right, which means
the two of us match!
Now that that's over with...
Do you two have any idea what's
happening to the kingdom?
It's like a new
crisis ensues before
we're able to recover
from the last.
Well, we don't
have a lot of time,
but we'd better explain.
Yeah. Who knows when
another resurrected elf
might attack this place?
Either way. No matter
what it takes...
[BOTH]
...we'll keep this kingdom safe!
[CITIZENS screaming]
[door opens]
[MAGIC KNIGHT 103A]
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
[grunts]
There's trouble. Please, sir!
[KING CLOVER]
What's all the noise about?
You'd better have a good reason
for disturbing my beauty rest!
I apologize, my liege.
But we have an emergency!
There are several
mages attacking
the royal capital as we speak!
Things of that nature tend
to be Julius's responsibility.
[MAGIC KNIGHT 103A]
Actually, sir,
the Wizard King's gone missing.
We can't locate him anywhere.
The Magic Knight
Headquarters is in chaos!
Is that true?
His timing couldn't
have been worse!
Then again, I don't really mind.
[MAGIC KNIGHT 103A]
What?
Because it's finally my turn
to have the spotlight!
It was always the same
thing with Julius.
Every time I got a chance
to shine, he'd ruin it!
But for the first time ever,
I'm calling the shots!
What a great speech,
Your Majesty!
You're the greatest ruler ever!
Send out an urgent message
to all of the
Magic Knight Captains.
I need them to
assemble immediately!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 103A]
Er, that's already done.
Although, many of them
never even responded
to the message we sent.
In fact, we've received
word that some
of the Magic Knights
have betrayed us.
What did you say?!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 103A]
Apparently, Langris has escaped
from detainment, and he
appeared to be leading
the rebellion with the rest
of the Golden Dawn at his side!
[RYHA] Seems like our other
reincarnated friends
have already gotten
the party started.
It would be nice if they'd
save some fun for us,
but I won't count on it.
Well, can you blame them?
Even someone as calm as I am
couldn't resist slaughtering
those humans.
Hah. You may act calm,
but you looked
pretty amped up
in that last fight.
[KLAUS grunts]
[RYHA] But yeah. I don't think
I can hold back, either.
We're the same. Aren't we?
So we should be able
to talk things over.
Both sides are mad because
we lost someone we loved.
[gasps]
[RYHA]
Sorry, kid, but nobody's gonna
stand in our way anymore.
Those two should be
awakening any moment.
You might as well
throw in the towel.
[MIMOSA] I felt this enormous
surge of magic power,
and then it just disappeared.
That's true, it was
really intense,
but whatever it was,
I'm sure they're okay.
They promised they'd meet
us in the royal capital,
so all we can do is trust them!
Yeah, we've gotta give it
our best shot for their sake!
Those two were sure
about their decision.
You should concentrate on
what you need to do, as well.
[BOTH]
Got it!
[ASTA gobbling]
And then we had to fight against
this super-strong
person named Licht!
Stop, no one can understand
anything you're saying.
Can't you pick between
speaking and eating,
you big dumb pig?
We don't have time for both!
Are you okay there, Asta?
He's a better fighter now,
but he still hasn't
changed that much.
Let me see.
You said some of your
fellow Magic Knights
have been possessed
by elf spirits who
want to kill humans.
Is that correct?
I couldn't've said
it better myself!
I'm surprised you
understood that.
Well, naturally,
I did raise this kiddo
from when he was just a baby.
Oh, I still can't believe
what a fine young man
our Asta's grown into!
I mean, Yuno was
always great, but...!
He sure cries a lot, doesn't he?
--Uh-huh.
--[HIGH PRIEST] These are tears
of joy, I promise.
[DIGIT]
Excuse me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Who the heck are you, wierdo?
[DIGIT]
You forgot me already?
I'm the one you just defeated.
You rescued me from the elf
who was possessing
my body, remember?
My name is Digit Taliss.
[ALL]
Oh.
[ASTA] Is this what
you're actually like?
Why would you say that?
Of course this is what
I'm actually like!
How did I get myself
into this mess?
Oh, I should probably mention,
I'm a member of
the Purple Orcas.
As some already know,
our former captain
was involved in bribery and
other kinds of corruption.
So, I was patrolling
the Forsaken Realm
looking for ways to rebuild
our squad's reputation.
Wow! Endangered
Horseface Berries.
I don't believe it!
And this carnivorous species
can't be found in
any encyclopedia!
Who knew the Forsaken Realm
was such a treasure
trove of rare plants
that you don't see
in the capital!
[DIGIT] As I wandered
through the forest,
I ended up getting lost.
[screams]
[DIGIT]
The next thing I knew,
I wasn't myself anymore.
And then I started
attacking the village!
I still don't know
what's going on.
I mean, everything
happened so quickly!
Stop panicking.
Although, there's
one thing I do know!
That elf spirit who
took over my body:
whoever it was,
he didn't want this!
He didn't approve of all
this hatred and violence.
It wasn't his choice.
Come on, Yuno.
We'll save everyone.
The elves and the humans!
Yeah.
Wait, you're leaving already?
But you just got back home!
[HORO]
Please stay with us!
[ARLU] Yeah, we wanna
hear more stories!
Now, now. Try not to be selfish.
We'll miss these two, but the
kingdom needs protection.
There are other
people in danger,
just like we were tonight.
Okay.
[ARLU] Will you write
to us again soon?
Of course.
It's a promise!
You better work on your
handwriting though, Asta!
It's way too hard to read!
And you have to swear
that you won't get killed,
no matter what!
Right! Bye, Gramps!
Sorry it was so short!
Gramps?
Where did that little
nickname come from?
[ASTA]
I dunno, I just like it!
[HIGH PRIEST]
Well, I don't, so stop it!
[DIGIT] I'm sorry, but
would it be all right
if I came along with you?
Despite my demeanor,
I am a Magic Knight.
Yeah, come on!
Let's get going.
See ya later!
We're gonna go save
the Clover Kingdom!
--[ARLU] G'bye!
--[NASH] Asta!
Take care!
Thank you for all
the letters and the money,
but nothing's better
than you coming home safe!
Be careful out there!
Sister! I love you so much!
[BOTH]
Shut up.
You're off to save
the kingdom, eh?
Our little Asta,
who's never been able
to use magic at all. And Yuno.
He's the hope of
Hage Village now.
Even though he always
used to be so timid
and burst into tears so easily.
You both grew up so quickly,
it's unbelievable!
Take care of
yourselves, you hear?
Huh? What's up with that
giant rock in the sky?
Oh boy, I think
it's finally time
for me to have
some fun for real!
[ASTA] After all that,
we're super behind!
We should hurry!
[gasps] I sense
elven magic up ahead.
It's coming from the
north and the south.
[DIGIT] I-It's just a guess,
but maybe even more
Magic Knights got possessed
and started attacking humans.
What should we do?
Aren't we supposed
to go to the capital now?
Even if they live out here,
they're still citizens
of the Clover Kingdom!
That's that, then.
Since there are
two places in danger,
perhaps we should split up?
Good idea, that way
we can protect everybody.
You go with Yuno!
No, I'll be fine on
my own. Go with Asta.
Duh, Yuno is a whole
lot more capable
than you are, sword boy!
I don't need any backup,
so why don't you just
take him with you?
--No thanks.
--[ASTA] Come on!
[DIGIT]
Um, this is awkward.
Please don't fight
over me, okay?
Look, I've got this,
which means I can turn
our friends back to
their regular selves!
And you don't have that
ability, so it'll be better
if you bring somebody
with you to help out!
[YUNO sighs]
Surprisingly, you're right.
[ASTA]
Why's it surprising?
[YUNO] I guess he can use his
poison to incapacitate them.
I'm starting to
feel like you guys
don't want me here.
[ASTA]
Ready?
[YUNO]
Of course.
[BOTH]
See you at the capital!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[YUNO, ASTA]
"Splitting Up."
Asta. Just so we're
clear, are you certain
you wanna split up
and go off on your own?
Of course I do, don't treat
me like some kinda baby!
You're completely sure?
Uh-huh!
I'll ask you one more time.
You definitely want to split up?
I told you, yes! What?
You gonna get all
lonely and cry if I do?
Don't be stupid.
Then, let's go ahead
and split up already.
I'll meet ya at the capital!
Sounds good.
Well, bye then.
So awful.
[screams] I wasn't ready!
[DIGIT]
I'm scared.
[MAGNA] I heard the
town was under attack,
so I rushed over! What's
the matter with you, Luck?
Whoa! Why are you hittin' me?
We're on the same side!
Black Clover , Page 104:
"Lightning of Rage vs. Friends."