[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR]
On orders from the Wizard King,
Asta and his fellow Black Bulls
headed for the seaside village
of Raquey and the Underwater
Temple that lay off its coast.
[NARRATOR] Their mission: to
enter the well-guarded temple,
secure its magic stone,
and prevent the
Eye of the Midnight Sun from
fulfilling their ambition
to topple the Clover Kingdom
and establish a sovereign state.
However...
What're you messin' around for?
Like you're not.
Oh, hi, Captain Yami.
Okay, you incompetent
knuckleheads, listen up.
Apparently, the Underwater
Temple is beneath
the surface of the
ocean around here.
Unfortunately, the
mana-driven currents
are too strong,
so even a skilled mage
can't normally get near it.
The only time the mana is
weak enough to even possibly
access it is during a full moon.
If ya didn't guess already,
the Underwater Temple
is on the ocean floor.
You need magic to get there.
So, Noelle.
That's where your
Water Magic comes in.
We're gonna hitch a ride on it.
[NOELLE]
But, sir.
I'd need exceptional
control over my magic
to manage something like that.
No, I can't do it!
You have to, Noelle.
The full moon's a week away.
You've got till then to learn
to control your magic.
Push past your limits.
[MARX] And where do you
think you're going?
Oh, nowhere.
I just thought the place could
use a little airing out, is all.
Of course, sir. Though...
Your foot?
[JULIUS]
Well, what do you know?
How did that get there? Feet!
They never listen.
[MARX] You were about
to abandon your work
and go goof off.
Me? But I would never do
something so irresponsible.
Just taking a
quick magic stroll.
[MARX] This is not the time
for your shenanigans!
Now, will you please
do your work, sir?
And close that window!
[JULIUS]
Fine.
Really, all the trouble
the Eye of the Midnight Sun
has been giving us lately,
and you still insist
on slacking off.
If you keep getting
worked up like that,
you're going to send yourself
to an early grave.
[MARX]
And I'll have you to thank!
Speaking of the Midnight Sun.
I wonder how Yami and
his crew are coming along.
[MARX] I only hope they've
gotten down to business.
The Underwater Temple.
I wish I could've gone.
[MARX sighs]
[FINRAL] Please, tell
me more, sweetheart!
[MAGNA, LUCK shouting, yelling]
"You are the light
of my life, Finral!"
Why, thank you, my dear.
[MAGNA]
Damn it! I told you
to stay away from my flan!
[laughs] Sorry!
I wrote my name on it
and everything!
Yeah.
But food that's not yours
just tastes better, ya know?
[MAGNA]
My flan!
Sweet dreams, my
beautiful little angel.
[CHARMY]
Munch, munch, munch...
Need more!
Jackasses! Quit screwin' around!
We're not on vacation, you know!
Now sit down and shut up!
I'm tryin' to concentrate here!
[BLACK BULLS]
Sorry, Captain Yami!
[KAHONO singing]
[NOELLE]
What a beautiful voice.
Almost like something
out of a dream.
Is she from Raquey?
Are these magical bubbles?
Is that the spirit of the sea?
[gasps]
Ah! Were you listening?
Oh, my gosh!
[ASTA, NOELLE]
Not what I was expecting.
[KAHONO]
Well, nothin' I can do about it.
Wanna be friends?
♪ Do, do, do, do, do... ♪
[ASTA, NOELLE]
She wants to be friends?
All right, I guess I
should introduce myself.
I'm Kahono, and you?
My name's Noelle,
and this guy is Dorksta
the Musclehead.
That's not my name,
and I'm not a musclehead!
[KAHONO] Huh. Noelle and
Dorksta the Musclehead.
You have such strange names.
Wait, you believe her?
Aw, come on!
Huh?
She's obviously
making fun of me.
My real name's actually Asta!
Okay! It's nice
to meet you, Asta.
So, Kahono, what are you
doing out here so late?
Just singing.
Yeah, I gathered that much.
This is the perfect place
for voice training.
The atmosphere, the acoustics--
I just love singing here!
Voice training?
That's right! You see,
I have this dream.
Between my singing, dancing,
and spellcasting...
I'm gonna become an idol!
[BOTH]
Uh, what's an idol?
[KAHONO]
What?! You're joking, right?
[ASTA, NOELLE]
No, sorry.
But they're all the rage in
the Common and Noble Realms.
Ah! C'mon, you know, idols!
[ASTA, NOELLE]
Uh...
[KAHONO] Okay, so idols are
people who are so good
at singing, dancing,
and using magic
that everyone everywhere
knows who they are.
Well, except you, I guess.
[ASTA, NOELLE]
Huh.
[KAHONO] I'm gonna work and
work and work and work
until I make it big as an
idol and get crazy rich!
That's the reason
you're doing it?
I don't see what's
so great about money.
I mean, it just gets in the way.
You're wrong there.
You royals are basically
rolling in the stuff,
so you probably can't
understand this, but money,
it's a big deal.
I mean, without it, you
can't buy pop-potatoes.
If you don't have
any pop-potatoes,
just eat steak instead.
[ASTA]
Royalty!
There, you see! Money
is totally important!
Wow, Dorksta, I feel
like you really get me!
Please don't use
that dumb nickname!
Sorry, Dorksta!
Seriously, it's Asta!
Okay, right. Sorry, I--hold on.
What's wrong?
[NOELLE]
Hm?
Your body seems to
be weakened, Dorksta.
[ASTA]
I told you, it's-- Wait. Huh?
[KAHONO] Your muscles are
holding onto a lot of fatigue.
They are?
[KAHONO] You're sore
when you move, right?
Yeah, but how could you tell?
[giggles] Because it's my gift.
[BOTH]
Your gift?
[KAHONO]
Here, I'll make it better.
[KAHONO sings]
[KAHONO] Song Recovery
Magic: Healing Lullaby.
Whoa, so cool!
She's good!
It takes an incredibly
delicate touch to direct magic
with that much accuracy.
[KAHONO giggles]
Well, how do you feel?
[ASTA]
I dunno.
Ah! Oh! Whoa!
That's awesome!
I was sore all over, and now
I don't hurt anywhere!
My body feels so light!
Bye-bye muscle fatigue!
Whatever you did really worked!
You're amazing, Kahono!
It's like I have
a whole new body!
I've never seen someone use
Song Recovery Magic before.
That's great!
I'm glad it worked out!
'Kay, that'll be
100 yul, please.
You're charging me?!
Just kidding!
Oh, good.
But not really.
Are you serious?!
Money's a big deal, you know?
Take it.
[KAHONO]
Great, thanks!
And if you ever need
another Healing Lullaby,
I'm more than happy to help.
I can't believe
I just lost 100 yul.
[NOELLE]
Please, that's nothing.
[ASTA]
"Nothing"?!
That much money would
buy ten pop-potatoes!
Like I said: nothing.
[ASTA]
Royalty!
[laughs] You two are
so funny! How old are you?
Fifteen.
Me, too.
Wow, both of you?
That's crazy, so am I!
Oh, really?
Well, now we definitely
have to be friends.
Sure, sounds great.
You're pretty funny, too.
[NOELLE] A friend who's
a girl my own age?
That's new.
Fine.
If you insist, I suppose
that would be acceptable.
I mean, I won't not
be your friend.
[KAHONO]
Yay!
Sorry, I guess I got
a little carried away.
[ASTA]
"A little"?
[KAHONO giggles]
[ASTA, NOELLE laugh]
Wow! That's so cool!
The Magic Knights are amazing!
[NOELLE]
It's not a big deal.
It stands to reason that I
would be one. I am royalty.
[ASTA]
I'm a commoner, though.
Okay, so, what brings
you here? Vacation?
Nah. Actually, we've got
an important mission
at the Underwater Temple--
Shut up, Asta!
The Underwater Temple?
[NOELLE] Please don't listen
to him. It's top-secret, so...
[KAHONO]
Hm. Okay, whatever.
So, you two are
out here pretty late.
Were you...?
Well, you know!
[squeals]
What are you talking about?
As if we would ever!
The moonlight is so
terribly romantic, though.
And the sound of the waves
is perfect mood music!
No! I'm telling you,
whatever you may
have been thinking,
it isn't like that at all, okay?
I'm out here training.
Like, with magic?
Yes, with magic, and I
have a lot of work to do.
I can't go into detail,
but I need find a way
to control my magic in a week,
before the full moon.
If I don't, then our mission...
[KAHONO]
Right, I get the jist.
Let's see. A control issue.
Very interesting.
Well, go on, Noelle,
show me what you can do.
Huh?
Come on, Noelle! You can do it!
Wow! She's really powerful!
[panting]
[KAHONO] Hm, yes, I see.
Nice job, Noelle.
Now, as your new friend,
I have a little piece
of advice for you.
I think you might be having
trouble with control
because you're trying too
hard to hold back your mana.
Stand still and listen a sec.
[waves rolling]
Hear them?
I relax by listening to the
sound of the waves and then
try to cast my spells
without letting myself
get too caught up in my own
thoughts and feelings.
Just like that?
I'm not a philosopher
or anything,
but I've always thought
that the best way
to focus was to have a serene
mind and a peaceful heart.
A serene mind? I'm not
sure I understand.
I do!
I always feel like
I do my best fighting
when my mind's clear and I'm
not thinking about anything.
[NOELLE] Oh, yeah, and what
would you know about it?
You don't even use magic,
and you're always not thinking.
Try to focus on
your fondest memory,
something comforting. Y'know?
Um, okay.
I'll try.
[KAHONO]
It's not that hard.
What about your family?
My family, huh?
[NOELLE'S FATHER] The last thing
the Steel Warrior Princess
left behind was
a useless little girl.
As if this tragedy weren't
great enough already.
[SOLID] I don't see how anyone
could ever accept a failure
like you as their sister.
I swear I'm trying, brother.
How is it possible you were
born to the same mother as us?
Pathetic wretch. You don't
belong in our House.
Please, Nebra. I do.
[NOELLE]
Nozel, will you just talk to me?
Why wasn't it you who died
instead of our mother?
You're a mistake
and an embarrassment
to the great Silva name.
[NOZEL]
You killed our mother.
[NOELLE]
I appreciate the advice, Kahono.
I'll keep practicing.
Just let me know
if you get too tired.
I heal royals such as yourself
for the low, low price
of 100--I mean 1,000 yul!
[ASTA yells]
[ASTA]
What's my fondest memory?
That's easy. Sister Lily!
I don't know what's
more blinding,
the sun or your beauty.
Seriously?
Uh--
[pants]
You got it! Yeah!
Go, Noelle!
[GAUCHE chuckles]
Immortalized in sand.
I miss you, my little goddess.
Big sculpture.
Think maybe it's for
a contest or something?
I'm not done!
[KAHONO singing]
Thank you, I needed that.
Sure. We can settle
your tab later.
All right.
[giggles]
[NOELLE]
Not yet.
No, really, I couldn't
drink another drop.
[yells] Not yet!
Aw, yeah!
[GORDON sniffling]
[whispering] Come back.
Please, everyone.
Don't leave me here all alone.
[NOELLE panting]
[NOELLE]
The full moon's tomorrow.
This is it. Tonight's
my last chance.
Hey, Noelle! Don't give up.
You can do this!
[NOELLE]
I'm running out of time,
and I still have no
semblance of control.
At this rate, our mission...
[ASTA]
I just had a great idea!
You did?
Listen!
Stop thinking about
control so much
and just let your
magic run wild!
[NOELLE]
Huh?
I've been thinking
about something.
That thing you did the first
time your magic went crazy
might be exactly what we need.
[NOELLE]
Uh--
It's like Kahono
said before, right?
You're trying too hard
to hold the mana back!
If you relax and
let it do its thing,
maybe the spell
will actually work.
No! That's just insane!
If it doesn't work, then--
It's fine!
I'll use my sword to
keep everyone safe.
So quit worryin' and go for it!
All right, but if
this goes wrong,
you better not
come crying to me!
[NOELLE]
Okay. I'm letting it go!
That's incredible!
[NOELLE] I knew it.
This isn't working at all!
I'm nowhere close to
having a serene mind.
[KAHONO]
Noelle!
Come on!
What the--
[NOELLE] I guess it's true.
I really am hopeless. A failure.
How am I supposed to
focus on a fond memory
when I don't have any?
[BLACK BULLS]
Noelle!
[NOELLE gasps]
[BLACK BULL shouting]
What the hell're
you doing up there,
Lil' Miss Royalty?
Is that really the best a
Black Bull knight can do, huh?
You're wasting all
that super-strong
magic power of yours.
The sooner you can control it,
the sooner we can spar together!
It's not like you'll
die if you mess up,
so just relax, and next time
have a little drink
to settle your nerves.
You've gotta be hungry
after all that work,
so hurry up and finish before
I eat everything myself!
Don't worry, if you
fall I'll be waiting
right here to catch you.
Fall and I'll kick
you right back up.
So make it work.
Just give it your all!
You can do it.
I know you can, Noelle!
[BLACK BULLS shouting, cheering]
[NOELLE] I was wrong.
I do have fond memories.
[YAMI] Hm. So you're Nozel's
little sister, huh?
Your brother was
talkin' about you.
Apparently, you're
a total failure
who can't even
control her magic.
He said you'd never pass the
entrance exam even if you tried.
Ya know, I've never seen
a royal failure before.
Well, if you'll excuse me.
If you really wanna fight,
you could always join us.
[YAMI] That's right.
The worst of the worst
Magic Knight squads:
the Black Bulls,
where all the best
failures hang out.
I think you'll fit right in.
[NOELLE] I spent so many
years with my family,
and I don't have a single
good memory to show for it.
I've only been with
the Black Bulls
for a few months, and yet...
[NOELLE]
I have all these memories,
and most of them are
good ones. Very good ones.
[NOELLE]
The Black Bulls accepted me.
They relied on me. And now...
I want to do something for them!
[NOELLE] Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Cradle!
It... It worked!
[BLACK BULLS cheer]
[NOELLE]
Sea Dragon's Cradle.
A new spell! I did it.
I really did it!
Hey, what're you
stoppin' now for?
Don't worry, I'll
keep the food dry!
[laughs] Actually,
it feels great
when your cheeks
are all flushed.
[GREY exhales]
[yelps]
Right. That's my cue.
I'm coming, Noe--
That was my job, no fair!
[NOELLE]
What are you doing, Dorksta?
I knew you could pull it off.
Huh?
Get your filthy hands off of me!
Why are there sheep?
Everything turned out perfectly,
and I'd say that
calls for a drink!
[NOELLE]
Kahono! Did you see?
Huh? Where'd she go?
All right, it's party time!
Oh, yeah! Let's light it up!
[MAGNA, LUCK yell, laugh]
I told you to push
past your limits,
and that's exactly what you did.
Guess we better get goin' soon.
The Temple's waitin' for us.
You've got great friends.
In the end, they're the ones who
should be here cheering you on.
I'm glad it all worked out.
Can't wait till the next
time we meet, Noelle.
I'll see you in the Temple. Bye!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[KAHONO]
"Song Recovery Magic!"
Song Recovery Magic?
That's amazing!
Will you sing for me, please?
I'd be happy to,
for 10,000,000,000 yul.
Here!
All right, let's go!
[JULIUS]
L-O-V-E Kahano!
[MARX]
What is he doing?
[KAHONO giggles]
I made some new friends!
Once Noelle can control her
magic, she'll be unstoppable!
I can't wait to see her again.
Black Clover , Page 42:
"The Underwater Temple."
My magic is Song Magic!