[CITIZENS screaming]
[gasps] Where did that
creature come from?
[CITIZEN 118B]
Run away!
[CITIZEN 118AA]
But there's nowhere to run!
[CITIZEN 118BB]
Oh, no.
[CITIZEN 118C] This must
be the end of the world!
[BABY crying]
[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR]
Until a lone mage...
[LICHT]
Lumiere. I need you to kill me!
[LUMIERE]
I see now.
I understand why I was born with
such a massive amount
of magic power.
Don't worry.
I won't let you
become a murderer!
[growling]
--[CITIZEN 118D] Who's that?
--[CITIZEN 118E] Look!
[CITIZEN 118F]
It's Prince Lumiere!
[gasps]
[LUMIERE yells]
[SECRÉ] They stole
something I helped create
and used it to take
away the elves' magic!
We built that item to make
everyone's lives better!
I'm sorry, Prince. Lady Tetia.
Is there anything
left that I can do?
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] I don't know
what you expected that to do,
but it clearly didn't work.
If you'd cooperated earlier
and given me control
of your body, you wouldn't
be suffering nearly as much.
Then again, if the situation
had played out that way,
it would have been impossible
for me to make use of
your Light Magic, anyway.
I suppose it doesn't
make much difference now.
Soon, everything
will cease to exist!
[LUMIERE] The magic stones
are strengthening him.
Can I stop him at this point?
Even if I do, the
kingdom will be crushed!
[SECRÉ]
My prince!
This item is our legacy!
We can still make it a good one!
Right, of course!
[LUMIERE] I'll use the item
we built to absorb his attack!
Will it work?
[LUMIERE grunting]
[LUMIERE] I should've known,
it couldn't withstand
that much magic!
The beam stopped.
[SECRÉ]
That evil mana's fading.
[LICHT]
Lumiere.
[gasps]
[LICHT] Once I marry Tetia,
our families will be one,
and you and I will
become brothers.
I'm sure some humans
won't approve of that.
Probably. But, still,
with your help...
...we can create a new world
of peace and equality.
I truly believe that.
I believe it, too. I know...
[LUMIERE]...that you and I were
brought together by destiny.
[LICHT]
This is your chance.
Do it now.
I can't.
[LICHT] You are the future
we all believed in.
You represent hope.
[LUMIERE]
You're right. I have to!
[growls]
[gasps]
[CITIZENS cheer]
[CITIZEN 118G] Prince Lumiere
killed the monster!
[CITIZEN 118H] The kingdom
would have been destroyed
if it weren't for him!
[CITIZEN 118I]
He's our savior!
[cackles] You may
have prevented me
from possessing him,
but you put on a good show.
For the time being, I suppose
I'll have to be satisfied
with taking his grimoire.
[SECRÉ]
Don't you dare!
What now?
Stay away! I won't
let you have it!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Magic stones.
You saw what happened
to the elf, didn't you?
You're a mere human.
If you used those,
you wouldn't be able
to keep your form
for even a tiny spell.
Give up!
[SECRÉ]
Never!
I'll use these stones
to maximize my power!
[SECRÉ]
Sealing Magic: Eternal Prison!
Wait, I know what you're doing!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Sealing Magic, eh?
She's using a forbidden spell
without concern for
the consequences.
Her seal presents
a bit of a problem,
but I can use the magic
stones for reincarnation.
In which case...
"Come here."
What's happening?
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] There's even
more despair and pain in store
for the soul who
possesses the four-leaf.
So I'll go ahead and
sow the seeds for him.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Forbidden Magic: Noad Nepesh.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] I'll be sure
to work much more slowly
and carefully
next time, in an era
where you two don't exist.
[sighs]
[LUMIERE]
Secré! Are you hurt?
[SECRÉ]
You're alive!
[LUMIERE] You managed
to seal that devil away.
I did. It should
contain him for now,
but it won't last forever.
No! Prince.
This is the way it should be.
I kept my promise
to Licht, so it's okay.
[gasps]
[SECRÉ]
Don't worry.
I'm going to use the
magic stones to seal you.
It probably won't be perfect,
but it should at least
keep you alive.
If the devil's seal is broken,
then the peaceful future
we fought so hard for
will be taken away!
But you can't, Secré.
If you use that
forbidden magic any more,
you'll lose your humanity.
That's better than letting
you die here, Your Highness.
It's just as he said.
You're our hope
for a brighter future!
[SECRÉ] So, the prince began
his long slumber as a statue.
And for some reason,
I was turned into a bird.
[SECRÉ] I've been spared,
but in this small form.
I'll need help from
the future mages.
[SECRÉ]
Five hundred years ago,
I was removed from
the natural realm.
I watched over the
five-leaf grimoire,
preparing for the day
when the devil's seal
would be broken.
And to my surprise,
the one who inherited
that grimoire, was a boy
who was born without magic.
As soon as things
were set into motion,
momentum built quickly,
and now the time has come.
Today, we will finally
put this conflict to rest!
[ASTA yells]
I knew we'd find you
eventually, you creep!
Aren't you something!
I see you found a way to
eradicate his dark elf form.
Sadly, I have no use for toys
I've grown tired
of playing with.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] It seems
my spell that saps the life
out of whatever it touches
can be counteracted
by Anti-magic.
What an unbelievable nuisance!
It's over for you, devil!
You again!
This fight is getting more
and more interesting
by the minute!
Hey. Yuno. You see that?
Yeah.
[ASTA]
Call me crazy,
but I think it's the
First Wizard King!
[gasps]
No freakin' way!
Are you the real deal?
I don't understand
what's goin' on here,
but it's the coolest thing ever!
[YUNO] Calm down, Asta.
Now isn't the time for that.
It's you.
Who are they?
[SECRÉ] He's an elf revived
by forbidden magic.
Those two are members of the
present-day Magic Knights.
They helped gather the magic
stones to bring you back.
[ASTA]
Hm?
[ASTA] There's somethin'
familiar about her ki.
[SECRÉ] Prince. We'd better
see to Licht first.
[SECRÉ] I'm not sure of the
reason, but it looks like
that forbidden spell
reincarnated him
with his soul intact.
He's still dormant, but Licht
is in there somewhere.
[LUMIERE]
That's good. Can you wake him?
[SECRÉ]
Leave it to me.
[SECREÉ] In the beginning,
my magic could only
open and close things.
But as His Highness
and I worked together,
my skill gradually
started to evolve.
He brilliantly found
ways to use my spells
to their full potential.
And now, thanks to
the prince's help,
my magic can release any seal!
Are you there?
[LICHT gasps]
[LICHT] There was something
I couldn't say to you back then,
so I'll say it now.
I'm grateful, Lumiere.
It appears your
timing has improved
in this modern era. You
must've learned your lesson
when you were late
all those years ago.
And I've learned that I should
destroy both of you at once!
Licht. I...
Patry, even though
my soul was trapped
in a deep sleep.
I saw everything.
[PATRY]
Really? So...
In our lifetime,
the elves fell prey
to this devil's dark plot.
But while I was
drowning in despair,
someone stopped me
from hurting even more
innocent people and letting
the despair grow deeper.
My precious friend, Lumiere.
Regardless of how it was done,
it's clear that someone
arrived to stop you
just in time, as well.
Dear Patry, when you
took up that blade,
you believed that it was right.
But to the ones who
were struck down by it,
what you did was
an unspeakable crime.
[LICHT] Still, even if
you can't be forgiven,
I hope this is of
some comfort to you:
I know you did your best.
[gasps]
Oh, Licht.
[LICHT] All that's left
for us to do now is combat
this next threat without letting
our past mistakes
break our spirits.
At long last, we'll put
an end to 500 years of pain.
Couldn't agree more.
The sooner I swallow up
those pitiful little feelings
of yours, the better.
[ASTA gasps]
[LUMIERE] Light Magic: Mana
Zone, Lamp of Avior-Gloria.
[LICHT] Sword Magic:
Origin Flash-Rampage.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] They managed
to blow apart my spell,
which devours the
magic of this world.
The one who used the most
forbidden spell of all,
and the one who
absorbed his power.
The only explanation is that
they've been affected
by that world.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
They're quick!
Whoa. Amazing.
[YUNO gasps]
[LUMIERE] All we have to do
is keep up this speed.
[LICHT] If we're swift, he can't
counter with his words!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL grunts]
They did it!
Douve Nuutra Edde!
[gasps]
His arm!
Lumiere!
[LICHT] That spear
can break down spells!
I commend you for
having the wherewithal
to attack me that many times,
but regardless of how
capable a pair you may be,
now that I have my own
body and grimoire,
I am unstoppable!
[ASTA]
Wanna bet?
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Anti-magic?
--[LUMIERE gasps]
--[LICHT] Right!
[SECRÉ]
That might do it!
[ASTA grunting]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] This weapon
is supposed to crumble
anything it touches!
Still, he's nothing to fear
without the other sword.
Now, "Get back."
[ASTA yelps]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
"Tempest of Blades!"
[ASTA] All right! Thanks
for the backup, guys!
[YUNO] His magic is immense,
but it doesn't feel oppressive.
It's almost like
a well-honed blade.
So this is the
leader of the elves.
But, why is there something warm
and nostalgic about
his presence?
[SECRÉ]
Let me help you!
I'll mend the wound so
you can keep fighting!
[SECRÉ]
Sealing Magic: Closed Sorrow!
That's great! Thank you!
So cool!
Are all of his friends
as awesome as you are?
Also, I know you're like
a jillion years old,
but I get the feeling
I've met you before!
Y'know. Like...
There's somethin' about
your ki and your eyes
that reminds me of
someone I know--
--Just focus on the fight.
--[ASTA] Let go!
What's the big idea?
[laughs] You did
manage to seal me,
so I'll admit that ability
of yours is convenient.
At least in terms
of this world's magic,
which is as weak
as a wilted flower
compared to the four-leaf kind.
Then again, now that
I have my body,
it's completely
ineffective against me.
Be quiet! Long ago,
His Highness found a use
for my insignificant power!
He showed me that
even I can help
make this world better!
[LUMIERE]
I have a four-leaf grimoire,
and people always tell me
my Light Magic is
something special.
But if you ask me,
everyone is unique,
which means that we're
all pretty amazing.
I don't know.
All my magic can do is
open and close things,
so I'm not that great.
What did I tell you?
I'm sure your Sealing Magic
can come in handy
in ways that you
haven't even discovered.
It doesn't matter who you are.
There are some things
that only you can do.
Things that only I can do?
That's why we're inventing
these magic items.
If every person used their
talents to help everyone else,
the world would be great!
The only way you
know how to live
is by taking from other people!
But now, the ones
you hurt, stepped on,
and brought to shame are
going to take it all back!
I suggest you get
started with that, then.
Regardless of what you do
to combat this magic,
it won't stop flowing
until you've defeated me.
The exit is here
on the top floor.
So the more time you
waste running your mouth,
the more likely it is
that your friends
in the other rooms will
get swallowed up. [laughs]
This is bad!
[PATRY] If not even Licht
and Lumiere had the power
to stop him, then,
is there anything
the rest of us can do?
[LICHT]
Very well.
My friends and I are going
to rid this fortress
of your evil magic with a spell
that combines all our might!
Careful, Licht!
[LICHT]
I need to borrow your power.
[BOTH gasp]
Crap. I probably shoulda
thought this idea
through a little more.
Yes. You should have, human.
Can't you make this
space any wider?
Did you seriously ask me that?
This is the thanks I get
for savin' your ass?
You sure you're possessed?
'Cause you sound like
the real Charlotte!
Damn, this nasty stuff
is gonna chip away
at my magic until it's gone.
If you didn't know how
to use Recovery Magic,
we'd really be up a creek
right now, wouldn't we?
You're welcome, brute--
Hey. Uh, what's the deal?
Why are you glowing?
Is that, uh, normal for elves?
Is this...?
That's what you get for
wasting my precious food!
Behold the power of hunger!
It's him! Licht!
At last, we elves
get our vengeance!
[LICHT]
Ultimate Sword Magic:
Demon-Dweller
Sword-Conquering Eon!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL screams]
[BOTH gasp]
No way!
[YUNO]
His magic's unbelievable!
It's over.
He's dead. Well done!
[PATRY gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Is that... the devil's heart?
"Heal me."
[KOTODAMA DEVIL cackles]
Weren't you listening?
I told you it would be
impossible to kill me.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] Using magic
from this world, anyway.
[PATRY] After everything
they threw at him,
he still regenerated? Now what?
[ASTA]
That sword is even more deadly
than I thought it was.
If my own sword has a power
I haven't unlocked yet,
then we still have a chance!
I couldn't erase that spear,
but I did block it!
That probably means
my Anti-magic
was too weak to break through.
But if it kinda worked,
then it's possible, right?
So if I can fight
as hard as them...
...then there's something
only I can do,
because I don't have any magic!
[ASTA] I may not have
mana, but that's why
I'm the one person
who can pull this off!
Get ready, 'cause
I'm not done yet!
Black Clover , Page 119:
"The Final Attack."
Yuno!
Let's shut this guy up together!