[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed
lost until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] The day begins
early for a Magic Knight.
There is much to be done
before the sun goes down.
[ASTA yelling]
[yelling]
[ASTA grunting, yelling]
[coughing]
[NARRATOR]
There's cleaning.
[yelling]
[NARRATOR]
Laundry.
[yelling]
[yelps]
No! My heart belongs
to Sister Lily,
and I won't betray
her for anybody!
[yells]
Next!
[yelps]
[NARRATOR]
Tending to the beasts.
Sit, beastie.
[BEAST 7A barks]
There. Good boy.
I think you've
earned a treat. Go on.
[ASTA screams]
[NARRATOR] Feeding them,
even if it turns out
you're on the menu
for breakfast, and then...
Hey, Captain Yami!
[ASTA]
Captain!
[NARRATOR]
The unenviable task of waking up
Yami Sukehiro, captain
of the Black Bulls.
Captain, sir! It's morning!
[YAMI]
Shut up now or I will kill you.
[ASTA yelps]
Yes, sir! Sorry, sir!
You were the one who told me
to wake you up every morning!
[NARRATOR] It is also a Magic
Knight's duty to put up with
the whims of their
sometimes fickle captain.
[sighs] Another day of
backbreaking manual labor.
Being in a Magic Knight squad is
a lot more work than I expected.
[gasps] How is
this any different
from what I did
back at the church?
What does a Magic
Knight squad do?
[NOELLE]
First thing in the morning:
meat, meat, and more meat.
Hey, Noelle.
How come you don't ever help out
with the cleaning and stuff?
The cleaning?
I'm royalty, you know.
And a new recruit!
I've never done any cleaning
or laundry in my life.
Why would I start now?
Are you bragging
about being lazy?
Come on, we're on
the same squad here.
Ever heard the term
"team effort"?
[NOELLE]
I am royalty .
[ASTA] Yeah, and you
won't let us forget it.
[NOELLE]
Silence, insect.
[ASTA]
We're back to that?
Hey, uh...
Just wondering, what exactly
does a Magic Knight squad do?
Huh?!
[MAGNA] Are you seriously
serious right now?
We protect the
country, you idiot!
Keep the people safe.
It's the manliest
job in the world!
Why'd you even wanna join up
if you were so
freakin' clueless, huh?!
Well, answer me!
[ASTA] I'm sorry! I just
wanted to be the Wizard King!
[MAGNA]
Why did you even take the exam
if you don't know what we do?!
Well, those two are
certainly chipper, aren't they?
[mumbling] It must be
nice to be chipper.
Maybe if I watch them,
I can learn how.
[ASTA, MAGNA yelling, bickering]
Uh...
[ASTA coughs]
Jeez.
Will someone tell him what
a Magic Knight squad does?
How 'bout you, wino?
[sighs] Well, uh...
We, like, safeguard
the citizens' safety.
Y'know, that sorta thing.
And, as a bonus,
you can get to know some
marvelous gentlemen while
you're on guard duty.
Oh, okay.
[NOELLE]
Hm.
Well, if you ask me,
the best part's all the people
you get to fight. You can spend
hours beating up a criminal
and nobody will even
think twice about it!
[ASTA laughs nervously]
More than anything,
it's an excellent career.
One that makes my sister proud.
See her? Marie.
I use my wages to
buy her nice things.
Remember, if you lay a finger
on her, then you die.
[BOTH gasp]
'Kay. And, what about you?
Saving women left and right,
making all of them want you.
What more could you ask for?
[NOELLE]
Uh...
[mumbling] I can
tell you, right?
And you won't be scared because
we're friends, aren't we?
[BOTH whimper]
[CHARMY wails]
--[ASTA] What's wrong, Charmy?
--I can't believe it.
How did this happen?
This is awful!
The food is all...
It's all gone!
I'm nowhere near full!
Cotton Creation Magic,
bring on the Sheep Cooks!
[SHEEP bleat]
[CHARMY]
All right! That's more like it!
The most important
thing is, when you're
in a Magic Knight squad,
you can eat like crazy!
Munch, munch.
[GREY growls]
[ASTA]
Grey?
Wha--?
Well, it's just a
good job, you know?
A clone?
I'm really looking forward
to our first mission together.
Uh, yeah.
[GREY exhales]
Man, there are some serious
weirdos in this place.
[NOELLE]
What am I doing?
They're insane. Should I
even be in this squad?
Watch closely.
You take this, and you do this,
and now it's yummy.
So very yummy.
[CHARMY]
Here, you take a bite. Go on.
I can't! I'm way
too full, really.
Well, runt? Are you
startin' to understand
what being a Magic
Knight is all about?
[CHARMY]
Aw, c'mon. Just one tiny bite.
[ASTA]
Nope. Not even a little bit.
[VANESSA]
Hm?
Magna. We're going.
Yes, Yami, sir.
[muffled] What's going on?
There's a mission.
A real Magic Knight
squad mission.
Hold on, I'll come, too!
[MAGNA]
No way!
Can't bring a kid along.
This is an important mission.
Only grown-up men allowed.
Okay. We'll be back. Bye.
Listen, gang!
No breakin' stuff
while we're gone.
'Kay! Have fun. Bye!
Captain.
Will ya fight me when you
get back, pretty please?
[mumbling] Don't be gone
too long, Captain.
I'll be waiting for you.
Hurry back. You don't
wanna miss dinner, do ya?
I don't know how much longer
I can wait to see Marie.
I'm going through withdrawal.
[exhales]
I'd like to hit on--
I mean, get on a mission, too.
[NOELLE]
Really.
What am I doing here?
[ASTA] Captain Yami's going
and he's taking Magna.
They both looked so serious.
What kind of mission is this?
[MAGNA sighs, growls]
[MAGNA]
Oh, man.
This is bad, all right.
[laughing]
[MAGNA]
Totally, seriously, crazy bad!
[SEIHI] From the looks
of it, the two of you...
...are done for.
[SEIHI] From the looks
of it, the two of you...
...are done for.
[SEIHI]
Flush!
[YAMI]
Two pair.
[MAGNA]
Nothin'.
[laughs]
[groans]
He got us, sir.
--[clothes rustling]
--[DEALER 8A] Mm...
[laughing] Oh.
That'll never get old.
I lost it all! That was
over half a year's wages.
It's a pleasure, Magna.
Always. You, too, Captain.
[laughs]
[SEIHI]
I'll be able to buy
a lot of nice souvenirs
for the village.
Deal us in for one more hand.
Really, sir?
Hey, now. You have
nothing left to wager.
Not even underwear.
It's true. He took
everything we had!
No, not yet. Here's my offer.
One last hand. That's all.
If we win, then you
give us back everything.
Oh? All right,
and what if you lose?
Uh...
Your prize.
You're kidding, right, sir?
Well, Gramps, what do ya say?
Please. You can't bet
that and you know it.
He's right. Come on, Captain!
Shut it! This is where
we push our limits!
I'm not so sure about this.
Hey, here's an idea.
You lose to me, and you have
to do any one thing I say.
Well?
Anything?
What, are you crazy?
Yami would never agree
to that kind of--
That works.
Yami agrees to the
terms of the wager.
Come on, Seihi, let's do this!
Say your prayers!
Hah! I don't think
I'm the one here
who needs to be praying.
[MAGNA]
Yeah. These'll do.
[sighs]
[SEIHI, YAMI, MAGNA]
Let's see 'em!
Okay. There, there.
Who's a good beastie?
Meat treat?
[ASTA yelps]
Don't just stand there. Help me!
Do I look like I feed animals?
You're lucky I even
came down here.
You should be thanking me.
Not gonna happen!
I thought I was dead for sure.
You truly are very strong.
That's because I train hard!
[YAMI, MAGNA laughing]
[MAGNA]
Man, that hand.
[ASTA]
Captain Yami and Magna.
So, then. The
mission must be--
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH laughing]
That old man!
He actually pulled
out a royal flush. Ha!
Incredible. [laughs]
Shoulda known!
[MAGNA] We didn't stand
a chance against old Seihi.
He was motivated
to beat us today,
that's for damn sure.
[laughs]
[MAGNA]
Hey, there, Rasta. No-No.
We're back.
[laughing]
[MAGNA]
Guess what?
I got some news I think
you're gonna like.
It's time for your
first mission.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Uh--
Like I said,
we've decided to put
you in the field.
All right, our first mission.
Here we go.
So, what are we doing?
I assume it's something
befitting royalty
such as myself.
Yeah, it's a real honor.
Go to Saussy Village
for some boar hunting.
Huh?
Hunting boar?
[BOAR 8A]
Oink!
Wow. That is a terrible mission.
No, it's not!
You take that back!
I can bring down a boar
with my bare hands, easy.
No, you can't!
Don't even think about trying!
Those things are pure evil.
They got beady eyes,
huge tusks,
and they charge for no reason!
[sighs]
We lost to the chief
of Saussy Village.
Now we gotta pay the price.
[NOELLE]
Huh?
[ASTA]
The two of you lost in a fight?
That doesn't even seem possible!
[NOELLE]
How powerful was this man?
[YAMI]
We lost at poker.
[BOTH]
At poker?
He literally stripped us
of everything we had.
Including half a year's wages!
[ASTA]
Really?
[NOELLE]
Why would you brag about that?
That's not all.
We also promised we'd do any
one thing he requested of us.
And that turned out to be
gettin' rid of some boar.
There's been a herd
of 'em hangin' around
near the village. Trampling
fields and causing trouble.
Well. I'll head back
and wait for you there.
[YAMI]
Uh...
Oh, here, you can have
these back at least.
[SEIHI laughs]
Ooh! Ooh!
Can you explain what
this has to do with us?
Yes, exactly.
You were the ones who lost.
It was none of our doing.
So, why--
You idiots!
Do you seriously expect Yami
to clean up his own mess?
[ASTA]
Oh, y-yeah.
[NOELLE]
It seems reasonable.
Yami doesn't deal
with these things.
That's what he's got us for.
[YAMI]
Either go or die. Your choice.
[ASTA, NOELLE]
We'll go!
So what if it's boar hunting?
We're finally
going on a mission!
I'm getting pumped now!
Yeah!
I still don't see why
he would be sending me.
[MAGNA]
Come on!
Do you ever do
anything but complain?
Actually, that wasn't
intended as a complaint.
It's just...
Given that I can't
control my magic power,
should I really be going
on a mission at a--?
[MAGNA]
Dummy!
[NOELLE gasps]
That's the whole point!
How do you expect
to get any better
if you aren't even
willing to try?
[NOELLE gasps]
Besides,
we're not sending some
wet-behind-the-ears recruits
out there alone.
I'll be around to keep
an eye on you two.
Wow! You're such
a manly man, Magna!
Aw, 'nough of that,
Rasta. I'm blushing.
Well...
If you insist, I suppose I would
be willing to accompany you.
[MAGNA]
Really? Wow, thank you!
Wait a minute! How come you're
always lookin' down on us, huh?
It isn't that I choose
to look down on you.
You just always happen to be
below me, so what else can I do?
What kind of logic is that?
Do your thing.
Use your Spatial Magic to
send us to Saussy Village.
Saussy Village?
Mm...
No can do.
Come on, it's not like
I'm asking a lot.
Now, now.
I can go to distant places,
but only if I've marked them
with my magic power before.
Huh?
In other words,
you wanna go somewhere
I've never been?
Sorry, can't do it.
[NOELLE]
Uh--
Well, that was a waste of time.
Fine, we'll have to
go by broom, then.
[ASTA]
Uh-- Um, Magna, sir.
Yeah, what is it?
[ASTA]
I... can't fly on a broom.
[NOELLE]
Um--
Yeah, what is it?
[NOELLE]
What he said.
[MAGNA groans]
[MAGNA yells]
Are you two kidding me?
You're so completely incompetent
that you can't manage
something that freakin' simple?
Flying is pretty much the
most basic skill a mage has!
I don't have any
magic power, remember?
[laughs]
Why do you look so proud? Huh?
And since I can't
control my magic power,
a broom is out of the question.
Obviously.
And why are you
being so arrogant?
Ugh. Fine.
[MAGNA] We'll just
have to ride together.
Are you ready to meet my baby?
[BOTH]
Your baby?
Here it is.
Introducing Crazy Cyclone!
Whoa. So cool!
[MAGNA laughs]
[MAGNA] I know, right?
Awesome, isn't it?
Yeah! Way awesome.
Try "lame."
[MAGNA]
Excuse me?
Are you so blind that you
can't even recognize beauty
when you're starin' right at it?
It's lame!
[MAGNA]
A-Ah...
[MAGNA growling]
Yeah!
Take us up, Magna!
You can't do it, can you?
[yells]
A man never goes
back on his word!
Let's do this thing!
Fly!
[yelps]
--[NOELLE yells]
--[ASTA] Woo-hoo!
--[ASTA laughing]
--[MAGNA yelling]
[yelling]
[ASTA]
Yeah!
[panting]
There, ya see?
Crazy Cyclone does just fine
even with three riders.
[NOELLE yelps]
Careful!
Are you certain you've
flown this thing before?
Ah-- Whoa, newbie!
Try not to get so clingy.
[NOELLE]
Silence, you mohawked punk.
Now's not the time
for name calling!
Oh, yeah!
This is amazing, Magna!
We're one with the wind!
Rasta! You trying
to die or somethin'?
Hold on!
Right!
[yelps] Hey, watch where
you put your hands, insect.
[ASTA grunts]
What the hell are you
doing back there?
[screams]
Right on time.
[BOARS growling]
[HEATH]
So it's here, is it?
The magic stone. Find it.
[UNDERLINGS]
Sir!
In the mist, be lost.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[MAGNA]
"Pleased to Meetcha!"
Yeah! That's my Crazy Cyclone.
Way cool, huh?
Actually, between you two,
I'd say your head
is the Crazy Cyclone.
[MAGNA]
Who're you callin' a cyclone?
But the "crazy" part's fine?
[ASTA] We came for some
boar hunting but wound up
facing much deadlier game.
I won't let them get away
with making everyone suffer!
Black Clover ,
Page Nine: "Beasts."
My magic is never giving up!