[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR]
And, today...
[ASTA yelling]
Now that my arms are better,
I gotta work real hard
and make up for lost time!
[NARRATOR]
It looks like peace has finally
returned to the
Black Bulls' hideout.
Kinda boring with
nothing goin' on
around here, don't you think?
I could get used to this!
[NARRATOR]
Then, a lone mage stepped in
and spoiled the tranquility.
[YAMI]
Listen up.
[ALL]
Hm?
[NARRATOR] He was known as
the captain of the Black Bulls.
And for some reason,
he wore a happi coat.
There's a big festival
goin' on today.
[BOTH]
Festival?
[ASTA]
Captain Yami!
Tell me more about
this big festival!
Well, I can tell ya
one thing, Asta.
It's pretty freakin'
awesome! Does that help?
Yeah, totally!
Wait, I still don't understand!
That doesn't help at all.
You! Tell us what
the festival is,
and be as detailed as you can.
Me? Oh right, sure!
[FINRAL]
I'm your superior.
As you know,
Magic Knight Squads
receive stars as a reward
for good performance.
And we compete with
all the usual suspects
to see who can get the most.
This festival is where they
announce the total number
of stars distributed
over the past year
and crown the winning squad.
[ASTA]
Ooh! Let's aim for the top!
Except our squad does
nothing but cause trouble,
which means we're always
in a race for dead last.
[YAMI]
No.
We're in last by a mile.
No one else has negative stars.
Really?! Come on,
how terrible can we be?
As I was saying,
the festival is attended
and enjoyed by citizens
all over the Clover Kingdom
as the largest public
event of its kind.
[YAMI]
It's called...
...the Star Festival.
[BLACK BULLS cheer]
Nice one, boss!
This is nuts!
I've never seen him
get this fired up!
[YAMI] Yeah, festival's
are fine I guess.
It's, uh, you know, whatever.
[NOELLE]
Your clothes say otherwise.
[MAGNA]
I'm with you, Captain Yami!
--[MAGNA, LUCK] Festival!
--[FINRAL] Ladies! Ladies!
[ASTA] Oh, hey, wait a second!
Before we leave...
Huh?
If it's not a problem,
do you think
we could bring a couple
friends along?
[ASTA]
So cool!
Here we are!
Now you rascals
go have some fun!
We've still got
plenty of free time
before the announcement!
Yahoo! Where's the booze?
Festival food!
I think I'll grab
a bite to eat, too!
I'll try to pick out a nice
souvenir for my sweet sister.
I wonder if there's anybody
here who wants to fight me?
[GREY growls]
[CHILD 67A]
Hey!
Where were they selling that
funny-looking mask, Mister?
[mumbling] It's my face.
--[MOTHER 67A] Let's go!
--[CHILD 67A] Hey!
Whoa, check it out!
There's so much
stuff to do here!
I wish my friends in
the village could see it!
Just try not to get distracted
and wind up lost somewhere.
Then again, I guess I could
walk around with you
if you really wanted me to.
[KIATO]
Hey!
[ASTA]
Great, they made it!
Kahono! And Kiato!
[KAHONO]
It's been so long!
Hey, Asta! Looking
good, man! Heh!
You, too!
[NOELLE]
How did you get here?
I asked Finral
to make a pit stop
and pick 'em up for me.
[FINRAL]
Just wanted to do something nice
for my adorable pal here.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have some girls to
sweep off their feet.
My work's never done!
[KIATO] So this is a
festival on land, huh?
It's amazing!
[KIATO]
You saved the Underwater Temple
from the Eye of
the Midnight Sun,
and as if that wasn't enough,
you bring us here, too?
We're really grateful, Asta.
Ah, and my gorgeous goddess!
[whispering] Look at
all the shops here!
Hey, careful! Don't
strain yourself, Kahono.
[KIATO] I'm sure she
must be dying to sing.
Poor girl.
Kiato! You brought
your foot, right?
[KIATO]
Huh? Yeah.
I preserved it with water magic,
but why did you want
me to bring it?
[ASTA]
You'll see. Here we go!
[KIATO]
It's as good as new!
That's awesome!
It's from the Forest of Witches.
All I had to do was bottle
some of the Queen's
Recovery Magic!
Oh, wow! Incredible!
Look, I can dance again!
I'm just as good
as I was before!
Am I... still...?
[gasps]
My voice. It's back!
So, wait.
Does this mean...?
Yes! I can talk!
Noelle!
[KAHONO]
Thank you!
It's amazing! How wonderful!
You can sing again!
I'm so grateful!
You're a real friend!
This is the best!
[ASTA]
Yeah, anytime.
[singing]
[KAHONO] Now everyone
can hear my song again.
Thank you, Asta!
[singing continues]
[CROWD gasping]
--[CROWD cheers]
--[CITIZEN AA] Bravo!
--[CITIZEN A] Beautiful singing!
Now we can achieve our dream
of becoming pop stars.
Yeah!
We're gonna make it big
and be filthy rich!
--[ASTA sighs]
--[NOELLE] Ugh.
That's their first thought?
Priorities, I guess.
You're always thinking
about the practical stuff.
[KAHONO]
Money's crucial!
Anyway, this star festival only
comes once a year, right?
So let's make the most of it!
--[ASTA] Okay!
--[NOELLE] Right!
[KIATO]
Watch out, my goddess.
I'm going to win
your heart today.
[NOELLE]
Huh?
Hey, There you are!
Perfect timing!
Oh, Magna, you surprised me.
What's that huge
thing you're holding?
Shouldn't that be obvious?
It's a fireworks cannon!
Did you say fireworks?
That's right. As soon as
it gets good and dark out,
we're gonna light up the
whole sky with those things!
[ASTA]
Sweet! Oh, but wait.
I was just about to
head off to check out
the sights with these three.
So ditch 'em! I outrank you!
Hold on, there's two guys
and two girls here.
I understand now.
Looks like I just walked
right in the middle
of a double-date, huh?
[NOELLE]
A what?!
Man, you've got moves,
dontcha, shorty?
[ASTA]
Uh, I guess?
What the heck is
a double-date, anyway?
Oh. It's when two
couples go out--
[MAGNA yelps]
That isn't even close
to what we're doing!
How can you be such
an idiot, Magna?
[KIATO]
A date with my goddess?
Sounds okay to me.
[KAHONO]
Poor thing.
Still can't express
her true feelings.
Maybe I can help.
Come on, you guys!
The four of us are
finally together again,
so let's have some fun!
You know what?
I think we should
make it a double-date!
[BOTH yell]
[ASTA] Uh-oh. What did
I get myself into?
[KAHONO]
'Kay! It's time to get started!
[NOELLE]
So now it is a double-date?
That's way too forward for me!
Kahono seems really
into this, though.
Does that mean she likes Asta?
[KIATO]
Kahono's trying to pair me up
with my beautiful goddess.
You're the best, sis!
I won't let you down!
[ASTA]
I still don't know what this is!
Whoa, hey there!
Stick with me, Asta!
This is gonna be a total blast!
Uh, okay! I guess
I'll give it a try.
[NOELLE shrieks]
[NOELLE]
I see what she's up to!
Getting all close
to him like that.
Shall we dance our way along?
[KAHONO]
That's more like it!
Better make a move, Noelle,
or he's gonna spend
the entire festival next to me!
You're about to learn you've
got to fight for what you want!
So yummy!
[KAHONO]
Mm-hm!
Could I trouble you to
write a special message
in mayonnaise for me?
Sure, what would you like?
"Love Goddess." For
the young lady here.
[whimpering]
[ASTA]
I can't get it to shoot!
[VENDOR 67B]
You're actually supposed
to use your magic, sir.
[KAHONO]
Here.
I'll use mine!
Oh! Thanks a lot!
[screams]
[VENDOR 67B]
Ma'am, Please don't aim that
outside the booth!
[KIATO] Look! I found
a mask fit for a goddess!
Wow!
We really showed that
gun game who's boss!
We sure did! You're so
good at that stuff!
I even got these little ball
things as a consolation prize!
[NOELLE] Those two kind of
look good together.
Wait, why do I care
about something
ridiculous like that, anyway?
[KIATO] Behold, my goddess!
I bought crepes!
[KAHONO]
Ugh.
What's it gonna take to get
Noelle to fight for her man?
At this point, I'm just
getting in the way
of their relationship!
That's it.
It's time to change tactics,
and I've got a secret weapon!
[ASTA]
What is this place?
It's a haunted house, idiot.
What's that?
Really? Wow, you don't know
anything at all, do you?
We didn't have festivals
back where I come from.
[KAHONO] All the scary stuff
in here is the perfect excuse
for couples to cozy up!
That's why they call it
the "couples factory!"
But we'll need to
bring out the big guns
if we want it to stick!
Uh, Kahono. Don't
leave me, okay?
I don't want my goddess
to see me all scared!
[KAHONO]
Do your stuff, ghosts!
Or should I say, angels of love!
Ha, ha! All right, gentlemen.
Here's the plan!
You two scare the
pants off the customers,
and that's when I step in!
Ha, ha!
Don't be frightened by
those phantoms, milady!
Oh, my, you're so wonderful!
Indeed I am, you smart girl!
I'm also the most powerful
of all the Magic Knights!
And just between us,
I'm the next captain
of the Green Praying Mantises!
Even so, without you,
I'm just alone, ha, ha.
Let us enjoy the
evening together.
Oh. Yes!
And that's how I'll get
myself a girlfriend!
There's nothing to it.
[PHATI, APHRO]
Easy for you to say.
Yes, it's showtime.
Don't let me down, you two!
When are we s'posed
to see the ghosts?
Why are you asking me?
Boo!
Rawr!
[NOELLE, ASTA scream]
[screams]
[KAHONO] That's it, now
they're good and terrified!
I bet those two are
holding onto each other
for dear life right about now!
[PHATI]
Boogedy!
[KAHONO]
Or not!
[yells] Leave us alone,
you creepy little freaks!
[panting]
Get lost!
I won't let you attack
the capital again!
[APHRO screams]
Wha- ha t?
Where did those two go?
[APHRO]
Save me!
No, let go of my leg!
Hey, stop! Look closer!
[SEKKE]
It's just me!
I get it, you're the ringleader!
--[screaming]
--[SEKKE] Ha, huh?
[SEKKE screams]
[NOELLE screams]
[ASTA]
Really?
You're sayin' they
were just fakes?
Of course they were.
I can't believe you
got us all kicked out.
Come on, you were just
as scared as I was.
I was not scared.
Me either.
[KAHONO]
Rats! Foiled again!
Noelle is enough of a problem,
but Asta is so oblivious!
I wonder how he feels about her?
[KAHONO]
Hey, Asta!
[ASTA]
Hm?
I've been meaning to ask you--
what do you think about Noelle?
Wh-What do I think?
Uh. Well, I, uh...
[EMMA crying]
Where's my mommy?
[CITIZEN 67C] Is she lost?
Where'd her mom go?
Hey, are you okay?
She's so shabby.
I guess they're commoners.
They probably came here
looking for work.
She's so loud.
Where are her manners?
How dare these filthy commoners
ruin the Star Festival
for everyone else?
[LILY]
Only those with powerful magic
can live in the upper realms.
They look down upon those
who have less magic power.
Despite the fact that
all of us are human.
Oh.
Should we--
What's the matter?
Is there something
we can do to help you?
[sobs]
Listen. I can't understand
you if you're crying!
Try to calm down!
There, there. It's not that bad.
Hey, I know!
[sobbing]
[ASTA]
Little girl! Look what I can do!
Here. See? It's
pretty neat, right?
[gasps]
This is perfect!
♪ Asta the superman ♪
♪ Yes, he can do anything ♪
♪ He may be tiny,
but he's super loud ♪
♪ So what if he's a dummy? ♪
♪ He's got the strongest body ♪
♪ Sure he may be worthless ♪
-- ♪ when it comes to magic ♪
--[ASTA] Huh?
That's not a compliment!
[KAHONO]
♪ No, he can't use magic, ♪
♪ But he's still pretty swell! ♪
♪ Asta, Asta, Asta: Superman! ♪
♪ Asta the superman ♪
♪ Yes, he can do anything ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la,
la, la, la, la, la. ♪
♪ He's got the strongest body ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la. ♪
♪ Worthless doing magic ♪
♪ But slashes any spell ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la. ♪
♪ Oh yeah, he's pretty swell! ♪
♪ Asta, Asta, Asta: Superman! ♪
[CROWD cheers]
Oh, wow!
[KIATO]
Please watch, my goddess.
This dance is dedicated to you!
Okay, can you please
tell me your name?
[EMMA]
Emma.
[NOELLE]
Kahono.
Do you think you could
use your Song Magic
to send this little girl's
name to her mother,
wherever she is?
Good idea! Leave it to me!
[inhales]
♪ Emma! ♪
[EMMA'S MOM]
Oh, how can I ever thank you?
Look at that!
You're back together!
Thank you for helping
me find my mom!
Mommy's here so she can
find work, remember?
I thought I told you not
to wander off all by yourself!
[EMMA]
I'm sorry.
But the festival just
looked like so much fun.
I really can't
express my gratitude.
[EMMA'S MOM]
That emblem.
You're a member of House Silva?
Oh! A thousand pardons!
I do hope my daughter didn't
do anything to offend you!
What? Royalty?
Look at her hair. She's a Silva!
A commoner like
that shouldn't even
be speaking to her!
[NOELLE]
You're right, I am royalty.
We're said to have
the greatest magic power
in the kingdom.
Which is why we must
use it to help others!
Vainly putting yourself
above everyone else
and looking down on
the people around you.
That's something you only
do if your heart is small!
[ALL gasp]
[NOELLE] Emma can enjoy
the Star Festival, too!
Whether someone is royalty
or a commoner, doesn't matter!
We can all have fun together!
[CROWD cheers]
You're amazing, thank you!
I've been meaning to ask you;
what do you think about Noelle?
If I had to say...
[NOELLE]
Hm?
You're pretty great.
I like you a lot, Noelle.
Hah! Right outta the park!
Huh? Now what's wrong?
[KAHONO]
Bingo! Come on, Noelle!
This is your chance!
Just say it already!
[yelps]
Where did that come from?!
I swear, you get
dumber every day!
[ASTA yelps]
What did I do?
Ow, hot!
Whoa.
He'll live, right?
She is royalty.
That's gonna hurt tomorrow.
Great.
Asta. Did you let her send
you flying just for me?
Uh...
[panting]
Sheesh.
With her stubbornness
and his foolishness,
they'll never couple up.
[ASTA yelling]
But I...
I said something nice.
[JACK cackles]
I always knew that we'd end up
settling the score eventually.
[YAMI growls]
What the--?
Hey! What's going on?
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[GAUCHE]
"The Hitman."
[GAUCHE] My angel--uh,
I mean, my client, Marie!
Your big brother's about
to finish him off,
just like you wanted.
The target is that doll.
[ALIEN DOLL 11A]
Take us to your leader, humans!
[GAUCHE] Marie really
fancies these lately,
so I plan to use all of my
magic power to take it down!
Mirror Magic!
[BOTH]
Go, Real Double!
After that comes
Reflect Refrain!
[ALIEN DOLL 11A]
Human, human...
[BOTH]
What? I can't hit it!
Oh, yeah I forgot.
Some short guy with
giant muscles was usin'
that gun earlier and
must've busted it.
[BOTH]
He's dead!
[NOELLE] Listen, Asta,
I let you take me on that,
uh, date, or whatever.
So you'd better show
me some gratitude!
After all, I am royalty!
Black Clover , Page 68:
"Battle to the Death?
Yami vs. Jack"
Huh? What's the captain up to?