[VILLAGERS screaming]
[VILLAGERS screaming, shouting]
[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[CROWD cheering]
[NARRATOR] Time flowed
onward into the present.
The role of Wizard King was
passed down through the ages,
and always, he and the
Magic Knights under his command
have fought to keep
the kingdom safe.
[NARRATOR]
The Magic Knights:
nine squads of
knight-mages whose powers
are specialized for combat,
operating under the direct
control of the Wizard King.
[NARRATOR] These heroic men
and women risk their lives
to protect their country. For
their bravery and dedication,
the Magic Knights
and the Wizard King
are revered throughout
the Clover Kingdom.
[ASTA]
...2,996...
...2,997...
...2,998...
...2,999...
[grunts]
[yelling]
[ASTA] I'll train and train
and train some more!
I'm gonna get even
stronger and faster!
[ASTA]
Yuno won't win.
I'm gonna beat him
to the finish line.
And when I'm the Wizard King,
I'll come back
for you, Sister Lily.
So, will you please marry me?
[LILY sneezes]
[TOWERMASTER] That Asta
is just full of surprises.
The boy who barely
got a grimoire
is a regular Magic Knight
success story.
I'm glad to hear
he's doing well.
They've both come so far
in their young lives.
Abandoned on the
doorstep when they were
only babies, and now
look at them!
With the money they've
sent home every month,
we've fixed up the church
and laid in enough
pop-potatoes to keep
everybody's stomachs
full this winter!
Here, use this.
Ah! Perfect, thanks.
--[HIGH PRIEST] Here you go.
--Why don't you keep it?
[HIGH PRIEST]
Huh? Are you sure?
[TOWERMASTER] In this world,
magic is everything.
So what could ever become
of a boy who has none?
[TOWERMASTER]
Now, never once has anyone
from this region
distinguished him, or herself,
by becoming a Magic Knight,
much less the Wizard King.
I pray that one among you
will have what it takes
to become the most
powerful mage in the land.
Ahem. And now to
accept your grimoires.
[CROWD gasping, chattering]
[TEEN GIRL 1A]
Finally, my very own grimoire!
[TOWERMASTER]
Yuno was given the legendary
four-leaf clover grimoire.
I will become the Wizard King.
[TOWERMASTER] But, as for
the magicless Asta...
Hey, uh...
Is my grimoire running
late or something?
[ASTA]
Whew!
Now! Time for a hearty swig
of magic-boosting moguro
leaf juice. Bottoms up!
[yelling]
[TEEN BOY 1I chuckles]
Oh, wow, you're kidding!
[TEEN BOY 1J]
That's actually kinda awesome.
[TEEN BOY 1K]
What?
[REVCHI]
You don't have any magic!
How could you get a grimoire?
And that sword?
What kind of freak
of nature are you?!
[yells]
You took my spell and turned it
into your magic power?!
[ASTA yells]
Even without traditional
magic power,
I will be the Wizard King!
My magic is never giving up!
[ASTA yells]
Well, what d'ya think?
My very own grimoire.
I don't know how it
happened, but I got one!
[TOWERMASTER] Sounds like
he's holding his own.
[HIGH PRIEST]
Yuno. Asta. My boys!
You're the pride of the village.
[LILY]
There, there, Father.
[GORDON chuckles]
[GORDON mumbling] First time
I saw Asta was on the day
of the Magic Knights
Entrance Exam.
Even then, at the very
beginning, he sparkled.
[ASTA] Ha, ha, ha! One of us
is gonna be the Wizard King.
This is where our legend
begins, right, Yuno?
I've been training for this
the last six months.
Wait'll you see what I can do--
[ASTA yelps]
Why are they trying to kill me?
[BUMODA laughs]
What the hell?
[GAYAYA]
Poor shmuck.
[AMY chuckles]
[KOZA] Not the nicest
welcome to the big city.
[ASTA screaming]
Get the hell away from me!
[EXAMINEES gasp]
Ooh!
One of them.
A real Magic Knight
squad captain.
On to the next test.
The final and most difficult.
A display of combat skill.
As knights, battle
is our business.
We wanna see everything
you're capable of!
[ASTA] The best way to
show off now is to pair off
with someone strong.
Ha, ha! What do you say
you and I pair up?
[ASTA]
You really mean it, Sekke?
You're willing to take on
a charity case like me?
We're both working
for the same goal.
So we'll have a fair fight,
but nobody pulls
any punches, okay?
Now, begin.
No pulling punches, remember?
Let's do this, Asta. Ha, ha!
Bronze Creation Magic:
Sekke Magnum Cannon ball!
Come on, don't get
shy on me now. Ha, ha!
[ASTA]
Okay. Here we go.
[ASTA grunts]
[SEKKE gasps]
[ASTA yells]
[EXAMINEES gasp]
[ASTA] Unlike you, Sekke,
I'm not joining
the Magic Knights just
so I can slack off
and have a little fun.
I've got a much bigger goal.
I'm gonna be the Wizard King.
[GORDON whispering]
So cool.
[gasps]
[ASTA] It's like magic
is coming off him in waves.
This is it. The power of
a Magic Knight captain.
What you said before.
That you took the exam
'cause you wanna become
the Wizard King.
And now, standing here
magicless and pathetic,
can you really say
you have what it takes?
That you're strong enough
to be the Wizard King?
[gasps]
Yeah, fine.
So, maybe I won't get to join
a Magic Knight squad today.
But no matter what anyone says,
and no matter how many
times I might stumble,
I won't give up!
I will become the Wizard King!
[laughs]
You know, kid. I like you.
Come join our crew.
Wha--?
Quit gapin' like a fish.
I'm sayin' I'll let you
into the Black Bulls.
[ASTA gasps]
[GORDON mumbling] I wasn't the
only one who saw the bright glow
of Asta's inner light.
The captain did, too.
And that's the story of how Asta
came to join the
Black Bulls family.
But let's not forget Asta's
childhood friend, Yuno.
[STAFF 4A]
Do we have any hands?
[EXAMINEES murmuring]
[GAYAYA]
No way.
[SHINANA]
All of them?
[BUMODA]
Impossible!
[LOUNIE]
Has that ever happened?
[TANOSO] Uh-- I guess it's not
just royalty and nobles
who can get into
the Golden Dawn.
[ASTA]
Whoa! They all want him?
Way to show 'em, Yuno!
[YUNO] I have to choose
the squad that offers me
the best path to becoming
the Wizard King.
It would be an honor
to join the Golden Dawn.
[EXAMINEES clammoring]
[GORDON mumbling] Asta and I
are basically brothers now,
so any childhood friend of his
is a childhood friend of mine.
In other words,
Yuno and I are best friends.
[GORDON]
Now, then.
Time for today's entry
in my observation diary.
[GORDON mumbling]
"Today, my dearest friend Asta
worked his very hardest,
just like he does every day."
"He washed the floors,
dusted the shelves..."
[coughing]
[yelling]
[GORDON]
"Did the laundry."
[yelling]
No! My heart belongs
to Sister Lily,
and I won't betray
her for anybody!
[yelling]
Next!
[GORDON chuckles]
[GORDON]
"And tended the beasts."
Sit, beastie.
[BEAST 7A yips]
There. Good boy.
I think you've earned a treat.
[ASTA screams] What're you
doing, ya slobbery mutt?
Lemme go! I'm not your dinner!
[GORDON chuckles]
[ASTA]
Ow, ow, ow, ow! It's so hot.
I mean, maybe it is
for a normal person,
but this heat should be
nothing to a Black Bull.
What's wrong? Do you
wanna get out already?
No, of course not.
I can stay in. I'm not done yet.
[GORDON mumbling]
I honestly wouldn't mind
adding a little cold water.
[GORDON mumbling] It sure was
nice getting some naked time
with my friends.
[GORDON chuckling]
[NOELLE] Honestly,
does he have a death wish?
You're with me on
this one, right, Nero?
He's just so, so reckless.
And he's been that way since
our very first mission.
That ridiculous boar hunt.
[ASTA yelling]
[screaming]
[NOELLE] We'd barely made
it to Saussy Village
when we were accosted
by a band of thugs.
[sighs]
Hey, Asta.
Sir!
[ASTA grunts]
[ALL gasp]
Kill them.
[ASTA yells]
Think again!
[HEATH] Do you imagine
you can still protect
your herd of beasts like this?
[ASTA yells]
[NOELLE]
Asta!
Too late.
[gasps]
[ASTA screams]
[ASTA grunting]
You stand no chance
of prevailing against me.
Why not accept that and give up?
If I gave up now, then
who would protect them?
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[ASTA]
I realized something.
[HEATH]
Hm?
Sooner or later, I'm going
to be the Wizard King.
But it's not just about
keeping a promise.
It's about keeping people safe!
[NOELLE]
Wizard King, my foot!
What does he think
would have happened
if I hadn't been there?
Well, I did mentally
cheer for him, but still.
It's not like that means
anything. Not really.
Ugh! This has to stop!
It's not like that!
I mean, me and that
idiot commoner?
There's no way. I'm royalty.
And he's basically a lunatic.
Like, back in the dungeon.
Your new opponent...
[ASTA]
...is right here!
[yelling]
One for me!
Begone, boy!
[NOELLE] Why are you just
sitting there, insect?
[ASTA gasps]
You're awake!
[NOELLE]
Now get moving.
And don't you dare give up
until you beat him.
Understand?
[gasps]
Yeah. I'll bring this guy down,
and I'll get one or two hits
in for you while I'm at it.
Give up. You can't win.
I live to destroy the weak!
Well, you're not
gonna destroy me!
I may not have any magic power,
but what I do have
are my friends!
[MARS groans]
I don't really know
how, but I did it.
[sputters]
I'm dead.
What's happening?
[NOELLE]
Asta!
Even if he was fine in the end.
I'd be dead if it
weren't for you.
Thanks a lot.
I'm so very sorry!
[ASTA, YUNO gasp]
[GROUP gasps]
[gasps]
[REBECCA panting]
You were really
great back there.
Thank you so much.
[ASTA]
No problem.
Sorry I kinda ruined
the mixer for you.
You didn't, though.
Hey, Asta.
Do... Do you have anyone
who's special to you?
Yes! I've got my heart
set on someone!
[NOELLE]
Someone special, huh?
Someone he's got
his heart set on.
If he cares so much,
he shouldn't make me worry.
[ASTA]
Who's makin' you worry?
How long have you
been there, anyway?
It isn't nice to
sneak up on people!
Not long, I just got back
from an epic training session.
What are you up to in here?
Ha!
[ASTA]
Huh? Why?
[NOELLE]
Hmph.
[KLAUS] We've been given
a mission of grave importance.
Right. We're ready.
Yuno, perhaps it would be
best if you stayed behind.
If your injuries aren't healed--
I'll be fine.
[KLAUS gasps]
[MIMOSA]
It's so sweet of you to put
Yuno's health first like that.
I am not sweet.
Bringing along an injured
man would slow us down,
that's all.
My concern is for the mission,
not Yuno's health.
Let's go.
You're not riding?
Uh. Well, uh, it's just
more of a broom sort of day,
ya know?
[KLAUS]
Don't be shy.
It doesn't use too
much magic power,
if that's what you're
worried about.
[MIMOSA]
Oh, I'm not being shy.
And I'm definitely not
thinking about how embarrassing
it would be if my friends
saw me riding in that.
[YUNO]
Yeah.
[KLAUS]
Now see here!
Are you two making
fun of my chariot?
[YUNO]
Of course not.
[KLAUS]
Ah! Hey! Come back!
You can't take off
on your own like that!
Well, I'll just be
on my way, too, then.
Uh--
[YUNO]
I can't waste any time resting.
I need to get stronger.
Much stronger!
[YUNO] You showed me it
was possible. Gave me hope.
That even though we're
poor orphans, commoners,
we can still make something
of ourselves in this world.
And to prove that...
[ASTA] To make Sister Lily
and everybody else happy...
[ASTA, YUNO] ...we'll fight
to see who will be
the Wizard King.
Whatever it takes.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[GORDON mumbling]
Clover Clips.
[KLAUS]
"It's Not Like I'm Worried."
[KLAUS] He's brushing each tooth
carefully and thoroughly,
ensuring maximum cleanliness.
[KLAUS gasps]
Don't scrub so roughly!
[KLAUS]
His eyes!
No!
Safe.
It's a chilly night.
Is he going to catch cold?
Um, Klaus, at this point,
I'm not sure if it's
sweet or just creepy.
Just creepy.
[ASTA]
No work again today?
Feels like all I do
is take time off lately.
Guess this would be
a good chance to visit
Rebecca and her family.
Black Clover , Page 30:
"The Mirror Mage."
All right! Let's see if
I play as well as I fight!