[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR]
Wizard King Julius Novachrono
had successfully shielded
the people of Clover
from an assault by Licht,
leader of the Eye
of the Midnight Sun.
But his courageous act
came at a heavy cost.
[YAMI] What happened here?
Tell me, Vangeance!
Salutations. Yami, is it?
You may call me Licht.
[NARRATOR] Yami attempted
to launch a counterattack.
[YAMI]
Dark Magic...
Now, Dark Cloaked...
Dimension Slash!
[NARRATOR] But Licht escaped.
And as for Julius...
I'm leaving the rest to you now.
Yes, sir.
[LICHT] This is where we must
bid each other farewell.
[ALL gasp]
[LICHT] The great rebirth
will start with you.
[NARRATOR] Only now is
Licht finally beginning
to reveal his true
intentions for this world.
[ELVES cheering]
[ELF VILLAGER 95A]
Wow, I can't believe it!
[ELF VILLAGER 95B]
Licht and his Sword Magic
have been chosen by the
four-leaf clover grimoire!
[PATRY]
What's so exciting, Mom?
Well, my dear, only a select few
can get a grimoire like that.
And it comes with an extra
helping of good luck!
[PATRY]
Oh.
[PATRY] Licht and his
four-leaf grimoire. Wow!
He's so cool!
[PATRY]
There you are!
[LICHT, RHYA]
Hm?
This kid again?
Look, stop comin' over here
and buggin' us every day;
it's such a pain! Get lost.
I'm not here because I wanted
to hang out with you .
What'd you say, shorty?
Oh, I don't mind
if he stays, Rhya.
This isn't a bother
to me at all.
Thank you for stopping by.
I'm glad you're here.
Whatever.
[PATRY] What do you
think about all this?
[LICHT]
Hm?
You know, there's
been a lot of talk
about humans planning
to attack us.
I'm sure it's a rumor.
It's still a possibility
though, isn't it?
I mean, think.
The human race is so
wicked and mean-spirited,
they slaughter animals
for the sport of it,
without ever giving it
a second thought.
They don't have much
power on their own,
but a big group can be dangerous
when they get carried away.
Even though we elves
helped them recover
from natural disasters
a long time ago.
They're probably afraid.
[PATRY]
What?
[LICHT]
Both sides are afraid.
We have things in common,
but we fear what we don't know.
Regardless of that, this land
blesses everyone equally
with magical grimoires.
So, why wouldn't we
understand each other?
[sighs]
--[RHYA] Hm?
--[rumbling]
What's that thing?
[LICHT] A tornado of natural
mana running wild.
It's awfully big, isn't it?
Yeah, but it should
die down on its own.
[yawns] Man, talk about a pain.
[TETIA screams]
What's that?
What's he doing?
Looks like there's someone
inside the tornado!
Yeah, it does.
[LICHT]
Sword Magic...
Now, Origin Flash!
[FIRST WIZARD KING]
Light Magic: Lamp of Avior!
He's okay!
Licht is amazing,
stopping that big thing!
But wait...
That light mage was using spells
that were just as
powerful as his are.
I wonder who that guy is.
You're not hurt, are you?
No. I'm fine!
Thank you for saving me!
[FIRST WIZARD KING] Tetia, don't
leave the castle like that!
I'm sorry.
Besides, a Wind Magic
user like you
isn't supposed to be
getting herself caught
in a mana tornado.
What were you thinking?
[FIRST WIZARD KING]
Thank you for helping my sister.
It's no--
[FIRST WIZARD KING]
Hm?
[BOTH gasp]
Hey, look at his grimoire.
It's a four-leaf, just
like yours! But he's human.
[VETTO] Licht's been
spending quite a lot of time
with those two lately.
[RHYA]
You can say that again.
Seems like he's happy
to have some human friends.
But hey, they really
are good people.
Apparently, they
have the same idea
about society that he does.
[VETTO]
Idea?
They all believe that
humans and elves
can figure out how to
live together peacefully.
Ah, is that so?
[PATRY] It's odd to see an elf
making friends with humans,
but if he's doing
it, then I guess
it must not be such a bad thing.
Besides, that Light
mage was good enough
to be chosen by the four-leaf
clover grimoire, too,
so they're not that different.
Let's foster understanding.
Your elvish mana really
is a remarkable thing!
If we combine that with our
own magic-item technology,
this land will be safer
and more prosperous!
Let's all work together,
hand in hand!
[ELVES cheer]
[VETTO]
Is it true? You're with child?
[FANA gasps] With you for
parents, it'll be a lovely baby!
Hey, congrats, Tetia!
And you, too, I guess.
[laughs] Well, thank you
for including me, Rhya.
[RHYA] What are you
pouting about, tiny?
It's nothing.
You're still little.
You'll understand one day.
Would you shut up?
Stop talking down to me
like I'm some stupid baby!
[RHYA]
Excuse me then, big man!
Oh, hey, there you are.
[RHYA hums]
[gasps]
Hello, Rhya.
Let me guess, waking up
is a pain, too, now?
You're the worst.
Aw, get off my case.
Oh, and Patry.
I can see you're still
clinging onto Licht
like nobody's business.
He's gonna belong to a human
after tomorrow's big ceremony,
so you'd better start
letting go of him.
Leave me alone, Rhya.
That's my choice
to make, not yours.
Hey, watch your tone!
[TETIA]
It's all right.
Even after we get married,
Licht will still
belong to everybody.
Man, you human princesses
are so generous.
I'd be careful of what I promise
if I were you, though, Tetia.
Before long, there
won't be any room
in his busy schedule
to spend time with you.
You don't have to be
so blunt about things.
Patry knows what to expect.
So what's it like?
Knowing that you'll be a father
in a few months' time?
I can sense that the mana has
blessed our lives, as well.
When our child arrives,
we know that your kind
will welcome it and
we're very grateful.
[TETIA giggles]
This little one here
is the key to our future.
The bridge to unite
elves and humankind!
[ELVES chattering]
[ELF VILLAGER 95AA]
Good luck!
[ELF VILLAGER 95BB]
We wish you the best!
[ELF VILLAGER 95CC]
Congratulations!
Thank you all very much.
Take care of her, okay, Licht?
[LICHT] Yes. I swear I'll keep
her safe, no matter what.
My friends. Thank you
for joining us.
Come to think of it,
aren't you receiving
your grimoire tomorrow?
[PATRY]
Oh, wow, you remembered!
Well, how could I forget
something so important?
[laughs]
[LICHT] I look forward
to seeing what kind
of grimoire chooses
you as its owner.
Me, too!
How sweet! I wanna be a bride.
I'm sure you'll
meet your soulmate
one day, too, Fana.
Yeah, and hopefully soon.
May the rest of your
days be happy ones.
[TETIA]
Thank you!
[RHYA] And you better tell me
if this guy's unfaithful.
I'll smack him around for ya.
[ELVES, TETIA laugh]
[LICHT]
Rhya, don't say that.
[RHYA]
Aw, it's all in fun.
[PATRY] He looks like
he's really happy.
But, to tell the truth, he
kind of always looked happy.
I hate to admit it,
but it seems like the ones
who've made him even happier
are her and that other human.
Let's foster understanding.
[PATRY]
I wonder.
Can we really come to
understand each other
like he said we could?
Licht believes it's possible.
Maybe they're right.
Elves and human beings,
living side by side.
[ELVES screaming]
[PATRY]
What's going on?
It's the humans!
They're attacking us!
[ELVES screaming]
Everyone, this way! Let's hurry!
My spells won't work.
Our magic... It's
been sealed away!
[VETTO]
Get down!
[VETTO grunts]
[gasps]
[VETTO groans]
You have to get away from here.
[VETTO]
Hateful humans.
[PATRY] This is Light magic.
Does that mean...?
No. This is a mistake.
It's not true!
[ELF CHILD 95A]
Mommy!
[ELF MOTHER 95A]
Run away!
Please, stay with me!
Open your eyes!
[ELF VILLAGERS panting]
[gasps, groans]
[ELF VILLAGER 95E]
What's happening?!
[ELF VILLAGER 95F]
This must be a dream!
[ELF VILLAGER 95G]
You can't die!
[PATRY]
No. I refuse to believe it!
It's not real. It's not real.
None of this is real!
No, no, no.
No way, no way, no way,
no way, no way!
I won't accept it! I'll never...
...forgive you for...
Is that you, Licht?
[LICHT whimpering]
[PATRY]
Answer me.
Licht...
[LICHT gasps]
[LICHT]
What is this place?
What happened to me?
I thought I was dead.
These hands... They're not mine.
[gasps] I look like Licht!
[PATRY] What is this?
Have I become him somehow?
Did my spirit implant
itself in his body?
That's not it.
Judging by how this mana feels,
the body I'm in is human!
A human that looks like Licht.
I see, so I really did die.
Whatever Licht unleashed
when our magic
was sealed away,
it must have been
some kind of forbidden spell.
And something extremely
powerful, too!
Like Reincarnation Magic!
This light...
[PATRY] I can sense them.
Every single one!
I can feel Rhya's soul,
and the souls
of all the other elves
in this village!
Licht must have done this
in the final few
seconds of his life!
And all for the
sake of our people.
[PATRY]
But, so far, it seems like
I'm the only one who's
been completely revived.
Oh, yeah, his grimoire!
[PATRY] It chose to bond with
Licht, the soul that truly
belongs inside this body,
so I won't be able to use it.
I'm not sure whether
or not this was meant
to happen to me.
But I am the only one
who came back to life.
Not only that, but I came
back looking like Licht!
[PATRY]
I'm the only one...
...who can save the
rest of the elves!
[PATRY]
Which means...
I have been chosen.
I'll become Licht!
No matter what it takes.
[PATRY] I'll revive all the
elves. As for the humans...
For going back on their word,
for killing the people
I loved, they must pay!
I swear, they will
all be annihilated!
[PATRY]
Forbidden Magic: Evil Eye.
[PATRY] Ah. It would appear
you're finally awake.
This human has a
similar wavelength,
so I've imbued your
soul with magic
from the other world to
support your reincarnation
into this body.
[PATRY] Gathering enough magic
power to make that possible
wasn't easy, you know.
So please don't cause
me any more trouble.
Okay, Rhya?
Wait, you're Patry.
Why're you...?
[PATRY] But your old friend
Licht can revive everyone.
That's the mission that he--
no, I must fulfil.
You get it, don't you?
Yeah, Licht. I hear ya.
You're here, too?
Rhya.
About time, sleepyhead.
Rise and shine.
[yawns] It was good to sleep in,
but five more minutes
woulda been great.
As you can see, I've also
resurrected these two.
[PATRY]
Vetto.
You were a gentle soul who
loved to befriend animals.
Yet, this world has
shown you only cruelty.
Live with me, as you once did.
[PATRY] It is not you
who should be despairing,
but those unconscionable humans.
You must remember
your true self.
What a tragedy.
To think we were once friends.
I suppose the world
never changes.
If humans are so determined
to harm each other,
then we'll just help them along.
However, you're going
to need your body, so...
Let's keep you alive.
[PATRY]
Fana.
Your appearances are so similar,
and you share the same name.
This can't be coincidence.
There is no need
for you to suffer
the same sad fate in this age.
Now, awaken!
[PATRY] So, these three
are the souls I was able
to restore at this juncture.
It's as if they never died.
But I'll need greater power
to bring back the rest.
And that means supplying
even more sacrifices!
[PATRY] To that end, we will
gather the magic stones
that were once kept
within our village
but have since been
scattered far and wide.
And we'll use humans to do it.
Smart, don't you think?
--Oh, yeah.
--[FANA] Agreed. Let's begin.
We'll get back at
those hateful scum.
I'll make sure they
suffer endless despair!
[PATRY]
Indeed.
The great rebirth will
start with the humans.
[laughs]
[ALL gasp]
[RADES] Wait, we're gonna
kick off the rebirth?
You're singin' a different
tune than you used to.
I thought this was the part
where we get a huge power boost!
I see what's goin' on!
You tricked us, didn't you?
Huh? Now what?
[BOTH gasp]
It can't be!
From the very moment
I gathered you three
to serve as my allies,
you were marked as sacrifices
for this forbidden magic.
And now, it's time that you
receive your true names.
[SALLY whimpers]
[VALTOS, RADES, SALLY scream]
Forbidden magic?
You're kiddin' me!
What makes you think I'm
gonna go by whatever random,
off-the-wall name you
throw at me, huh?
I'm Rades Spirito,
and that's that!
No, Master Licht! Please don't!
I just can't believe this.
All this time...
I thought we were your
most cherished friends!
Yes. You truly were.
Then, why?
[PATRY]
I needed you.
After all, you're
the sacrificial lambs
who will bring back
my real friends.
You're very dear to me.
[ALL whimper]
Damn you, Licht!
[screams]
[ALL screaming]
[MIMOSA gasps]
Yuno? What's wrong?
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[SALLY] "Strange Spectacled
Sally and the Letter S"!
[NARRATOR]
Sally!
That's me!
[NARRATOR]
Shimmy!
This is kind of embarrassing.
[NARRATOR]
Syringe!
Who's my bestest buddy?
[NARRATOR]
Celery!
Okay.
That starts with a C,
but the way I see it,
"slack" starts with an S,
so cut me some,
if you don't mind!
[NARRATOR]
Sled!
[SALLY]
Whee! This is so much fun!
[NARRATOR]
This has been
"Strange Spectacled Sally
and the Letter S."
Wasn't that cool?
After this, I'll be right back
to trying to dissect you.
Oh, and I'm not gonna
use an anesthetic.
[NARRATOR]
Marx and Owen attack Yami,
seemingly unprompted.
Shocked by their
change of heart,
Yami puts them to sleep.
Black Clover , Page 96:
"The Black Bulls Captain vs.
the Crimson Wild Rose."
Even the loveliest
roses have thorns.