[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR]
Asta visits the village of Nean,
home to Rebecca and
her younger siblings.
Coincidentally, Gauche's
beloved little sister Marie
lives there as well.
'Kay, come on and-- [yelps]
[gasps]
Get away from her
right now, you scum.
[NARRATOR] That night,
a strange tragedy befell Nean.
It's time...
...for you to die!
[ASTA screams]
We don't even live here!
What?
There's snow everywhere.
Where'd it all come from?
It's not even winter yet.
Hey! Stop it!
What are you doing out here?
It's the children.
They're missing!
No.
[NEIGE]
How exciting.
I just love making new friends.
[laughs]
Where are they?
Why would they
run off at this hour?
[FATHER 31A]
Basim!
[MOTHER 31A]
Helen! Where are you?
Not playing hide and
seek, I'm guessing.
Die, scum!
[yelps]
I will never allow you
to marry my sister.
Come on, Gauche,
this is so not the time.
There is nothing in this world
more important than
my Marie. Nothing!
[yelling]
[NOELLE] Can someone please
tell me what's wrong
with this village?
I mean, snow?
At this time of year?
That is just absurd.
Hey, Noelle, what are
you doing in Nean?
Uh. Just passing through,
seeing the sights,
that sort of thing, you know.
Asta, who is this?
[ASTA]
A friend from the Magic Knights.
Noelle, this is
my friend, Rebecca.
[NOELLE]
His "friend"?
[REBECCA]
[BOTH]
Uh.
[ASTA]
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
Hey, listen.
A little while ago,
I saw a bunch of kids
headed toward the mountains.
What was that about?
Is there some kind of
late-night festival?
The kids!
I have a festival
of blood planned.
[ASTA yelps]
[SISTER THERESA]
Stop that.
[gasps] The hag.
[ASTA]
Sister Granny!
[SISTER THERESA]
This snow isn't natural.
I can sense some
kind of spell in it.
One that controls people.
But only children whose
magic has not yet developed.
[ALL gasp]
Several of ours have
disappeared as well.
Why would someone be spiriting
all of these children away?
[GAUCHE] Wait, crone.
You lost some of yours?
Marie better not have
been one of them.
Unfortunately, she was.
[GAUCHE]
Damn you!
--[SISTER THERESA yelps]
--[NUN 31A gasps]
You decrepit old fool,
how could you let
this happen to her?
[NUN 31A]
Stop, please!
So quick to resort to violence.
You truly are hopeless.
You can hit me if you want to,
but that's not going
to bring them back.
It won't help Marie.
No, it won't...
...but it will make me feel
a hellava lot better!
[ASTA yelps]
Get off of him!
What do you think you're doing?
Asta. You will die.
Hey, now, why don't
we stop for a second
to take a deep breath and
cool off a little bit!
[GAUCHE groans]
[ASTA]
We're Magic Knights, after all.
--We hafta learn to remain calm.
--[FUEGOLEON] You must learn
--You got it?
--to remain calm.
Well done. I like this boy.
[GAUCHE]
Calm, huh? All right, then.
[ASTA]
I knew you'd come around!
I'll kill you very calmly.
That's not what I meant!
That's right, brat.
I'm going to make it hurt.
[ASTA] No, please, stop!
We're wasting time!
We have to start
looking for clues!
Oh, yeah! Like it's
gonna be that easy.
[GAUCHE] I told Marie to keep
her magic mirror with her
at all times.
The snow will interfere
with Transmission magic,
but if we track down
the mana in the mirror,
then we should
be able to find her!
[ASTA]
There, ya see?
Fine, you were right!
But don't think for a second
that's gonna keep me
from stomping the life
out of you, maggot!
I'll come, too.
The church's children
are my responsibility.
Thanks, Sister, but maybe you
should just let us handle it.
No, the hag is infuriating,
but she does have her uses.
Really? But isn't
she kind of... old?
Heh. I can still
teach you youngsters
a thing or two.
[REBECCA]
Asta...
Between Marco's immaturity
and Luca's stubborn streak,
I'm really worried about them.
What am I going to do?
If anything happens
to those two...
[ASTA]
Hey, get it together!
[gasps]
Ya hear me?
I promise you.
I'll bring your brother
and sister back.
[gasps]
No moping, okay?
I don't think they
would want that.
Yeah, you're right.
[yelps]
Let's go now.
You're not going to
leave me behind, are you?
[GAUCHE] You can't fly
on your own, either.
You wanna be a dangler like him?
[NOELLE]
Hm...
[SISTER THERESA] There's
always a chance the village
may be attacked again
while we're gone.
Please stay here and
look after it for me.
[ASTA] Oh, and let the
Magic Knights know what's up!
[REBECCA]
Asta! We're counting on you!
[NOELLE]
Right. I'm stuck here with her.
Oh, wow!
I can't believe how many
new friends I've made!
Now, let's play nice, 'kay?
[laughs]
What?
[MARIE]
Where am I?
This isn't the church.
How did I get here?
And why does everyone
look so strange?
--So sweet...
--[MARIE] Who is that man?
You're good little children
now, thanks to my magic.
[MARIE]
Did he cast a spell on everyone?
Then why...? Oh, right!
The mirror my brother gave me.
He said it would protect me
from magic a little bit.
Think of it as your big brother
when I'm not there.
[MARIE]
That's why I'm awake.
[NEIGE]
Hm?
[MARIE gasps]
Oh, dear.
My spell's worn off
this one. Why is that?
--[MARIE whimpers]
--It's too bad, really.
If I can't use my magic
to make you a good girl,
we can't be friends.
You want to be my friend, right?
No, not that way.
You shouldn't use spells to
make people do what you want.
If you do that, you're
not a real friend at all.
[NEIGE gasps]
You don't belong here,
you horrible little monster.
No friend of mine would ever
say something like that!
[panting]
Now, now. Don't lose
your temper, Neige.
We don't wanna damage
the merchandise.
Do I have to do all
your thinking for you?
No, please! I'm sorry!
[BARO chuckles]
This one's our star.
Lotta power for a kid.
[BARO] Any more like her
and we'll be rich men
by the time we're done.
That kid hardly has any magic.
I told you to get the
ones who were loaded,
and this is what you
bring me? Really?
I'm sorry, Baro.
We don't need this
trash. Bye, kid.
[BARO]
Hmph. Brother or not,
keep wastin' my time
and I'll kill you.
Now, then.
Time to start
extracting some magic.
[BARO cackles]
She's nearby. The mana
feels stronger here.
Okay!
Whoever's behind this
has a good deal of power.
We have to keep our guards up.
Please, Marie. Hold on!
[ASTA] We're comin',
kids. Hang in there!
Now, everyone, please stay calm.
The Magic Knights will
find your children
and bring them home safely.
[VILLAGER 31A]
Whoa!
[VILLAGER 31B]
Get a look at her robe!
Are they really going to
bring my son back to me?
Where are Marco and Luca?
What's going on?
I'm sorry, Pim.
It's all right.
Asta will bring them
back, I promise you.
Yes, they'll be home
before you know it.
'Kay. But what
happened to our house?
[NOELLE] Uh... Yeah, that's
another thing silly Asta
will be taking care of.
For now, let's just patch it up
the best we can okay?
[PIM]
It's gonna be freezing in there.
Right. I need to contact
the other knights.
[yawns]
Huh? Hello there.
Knights Headquarters here.
[NOELLE]
Hey, I recognize you.
They have you working
at Headquarters?
Ha, ha!
Captain Jack stationed me here
to help out temporarily,
but I'm not gonna be a full-time
paper pusher or anything.
I've just accomplished
so much in my short time
with the Praying Mantises
that I've earned myself
a little break from battle,
you see. Ha, ha!
We've got an emergency,
here, you babbling idiot!
Listen! There's snow
falling in Nean.
Really? How romantic!
Do you understand
the word "emergency"?
Somebody used magic to
make it snow so they could
abduct children
from the village!
Wait, huh?
You should tell the
Magic Knights right away.
What do you think
I'm doing now?
[SEKKE]
Ha, ha! Right, well don't worry.
Sekke is on the case. Ha, ha!
I don't find that
reassuring. Idiot.
I'm picking up mana over there.
Yes, that's it!
The caves would be
a perfect place
to keep all of
the children hidden.
[ASTA]
Marco!
Hang on, Gauche!
Can you set me down
over there for a sec?
Leave him.
My angel's the only
one who matters.
[ASTA]
Ah!
If you want off, then let go.
[ASTA sputters]
[yells]
Asta!
And you're a Magic Knight?
Don't they have
standards anymore?
I couldn't care less what
happens to anybody else.
As long as Marie stays safe.
[GAUCHE] Just like the captain
told me the day I cast aside
my prisoner's clothing
and joined the Black Bulls.
[YAMI]
I won't stop you.
Go on and protect whatever
you think needs protecting.
And that's just
what I'm gonna do.
Marco!
[SISTER THERESA]
Stay with us. The poor thing.
He's covered in scrapes,
and frostbitten, too.
Marco, can you hear me?
It's no use. He's in
some kind of trance.
[ASTA]
All right. Just leave it to me!
Wait, what are you going to do?
[gasps]
Hold on. What?
Asta? Sister?
Hey, kid, how ya feeling?
[SISTER THERESA]
He dispelled the magic
with a touch of his sword?
[MARCO grunts]
It hurts so much!
[SISTER THERESA]
Hold on.
Flame Healing Magic:
Sacred Healing Light.
Thank you! I'm a lot warmer now!
That's amazing, Granny!
You can use healing magic?
[SISTER THERESA]
Tell us, child, what happened?
I'm sorry, I don't really know.
[ASTA]
Someone sure roughed him up.
Marco!
We've gotta go
rescue your sister
and the rest of the kids.
Can you wait by yourself
in that cave till we get back?
What? Please, Asta!
It's scary in there!
Can't I stay with you?
Hey, what's with the tears?
You're a man now, aren't ya?
Tell ya what.
I'll lend you my
Black Bulls robe, okay?
Just wear that and you'll forget
all about being scared.
Can't tell by looking
at it, but this baby's
chock full of
Magic Knight courage.
[gasps]
[ASTA] Now you sit tight
until we come back, okay?
Okay, I will!
You get that it's just
a loan, though, don't you?
When we're done, you're
gonna give it right back.
And don't even think about
getting it all snotty!
[MARCO]
Yeah. Got it.
[SISTER THERESA]
Come on. We need to hurry.
I'm worried about the others.
[GAUCHE]
Tsk. It's a maze in here.
But the mana's getting
stronger and stronger.
Marie. I'll be there soon.
[GIRL 31A whimpering, screaming]
[BARO cackles]
Oh, yeah! There we go!
I'm gonna squeeze
every last drop of magic
outta you whiny brats!
You'll be empty shells!
And done.
Now. Let's see. Is our
little star ready?
[MARIE]
No! Please let me go!
Don't take my magic!
It's only going to get worse
if you keep fighting.
Don't struggle, girl.
We've got plans for you.
That magic power of yours
is gonna make us filthy rich!
Marie!
[gasps]
Big Brother, I knew you'd come!
My angel! You're al--
You've hurt Marie,
and for that, you will die!
[NEIGE yelps]
What do we do?
He's going to kill us!
And that robe.
He's a Magic Knight!
Damn. How did he
find us so fast?
Are you waiting for
an engraved invitation?
Attack him already!
Yes, sir!
Snow Magic: Snow Cry!
Mirror Magic: Now, Mirror Shift!
You ever seen magic
like that before?
[NEIGE grunts]
[NEIGE yells]
I can't seem to hit him at all.
You'll pay!
[gasps] Hurry! Try another
spell, you moron!
Give me a second.
I'm going to try Snow Creation
Magic: Snow Friends!
That's it! Help me, friends. Go!
[GAUCHE]
Dammit!
[laughs] Taking out a few
of these guys isn't gonna
do you any good.
Neige can make 1,000,000 of his
little friends if he needs to.
Please don't hurt him!
I'm done playing! Mirror Magic:
Reflect Refrain!
I'll slaughter you all.
No way!
He killed them all.
Every last one.
How are we supposed to
beat someone so powerful?
[BARO]
Dammit.
It wasn't supposed
to play out like this.
I only took this job
because it sounded easy,
sucking the magic out
of a bunch of kids.
I didn't plan on going up
against a guy like this!
Nothing's working. What now?
I need to think! Shut up!
[BARO] Come on. There's gotta
be something we can do.
But what?
[yelps]
[laughs] You'd better
back off, Mirror Boy,
or you won't like
what I do to her next.
Don't you dare!
[BARO] Do you really
wanna threaten me now?
If I get nervous, I might
squeeze just a little too tight
and bruise this delicate peach.
[SNOWMEN growling]
Go on, Neige.
I don't think he's gonna
give us any more trouble.
[ASTA yells]
[MARIE yelps]
Damn!
[panting]
Marie!
Everything's going to
be all right, angel.
[MARIE]
Asta, you came!
Of course I did. Are you okay?
--[ASTA yelps]
--[MARIE] Asta!
You idiot! What
were you thinking,
launching an attack like that?
Any one of those projectiles
could have hit Marie!
Take it easy!
I had to do it if
I was gonna save her.
And besides, you were
a lot more likely
to get hit with something.
Like you'd ever
be able to hit me.
[ASTA yelps]
[GAUCHE]
My love makes me invincible.
Stop, brother, that's enough.
[GAUCHE]
Move, Marie!
Nuh-uh!
These children have been
completely drained of magic.
It's been taken.
And I don't know if
they can ever regain it.
That's what they wanted?
That big, scary man.
He said something about money.
What kind of monster are you?
[BARO grunts]
[BARO]
Not good.
I don't like the way
he's looking at us.
So, what now?
[BARO] That tall, angry one
was bad enough on his own,
but now that his friends are
here, we don't stand a chance.
[BARO]
This kid...
[laughs]
Hey, he's some kinda freak.
He doesn't have a scrap
of magic power in 'im.
Can you believe it?
I didn't even know
that was possible!
And look! He's not
wearing a robe.
That's no Magic Knight.
Just some stupid kid.
Let's split up, Neige.
You take the girl's brother.
Huh?
Meanwhile, I'll see
what I can do
about this little
runt over here.
[BARO]
Huh?
[yells]
[BARO groans]
[gasping]
[ASTA]
You won't get away with this.
I will make you pay!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[NOELLE, REBECCA]
"Holding Down the Fort."
[REBECCA sighs]
Luca. Marco.
Don't you worry.
I'm sure Asta and others
will have no problem
bringing them back.
Oh! I know what would take
your mind off of it--a quiz!
[REBECCA]
Okay. I'll go first.
Where was Asta born?
Huh? In Hage Village?
[REBECCA]
That's right.
Okay, my turn now.
How old is Asta?
He's 15 years old.
[NOELLE]
Mm-hm.
[REBECCA] All right.
When is Asta's birthday?
[NOELLE]
October fourth.
Okay. What's his dream?
Let's see, it's to
become the Wizard King.
That's right, isn't it?
You sure know a lot about him.
And so do you.
[REBECCA, NOELLE
laugh nervously]
[REBECCA, NOELLE] I'm not going
to let her show me up!
[SEKKE] Ha, ha, everyone!
Feeling a bit down?
Nothing a little Sekke
action won't cure.
I'll be making quite
the showing next time.
Hu-ha, hu-ho-ha, Page 32:
"Three-Leaf Sprouts."
Get ready for maximum ha, ha!