[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] A young Yami
was out training when
he received a request
to protect a village
from a group of bandit mages.
But before he knew it,
he found himself
outnumbered and surrounded.
And, during that
fateful fight...
[WILLIAM]
Yami, I believe your name was?
Watch my back,
if you wouldn't mind.
[NARRATOR]
Yami met William Vangeance.
who was on his own
mission nearby.
I intend to become the captain
of a Magic Knight Squad.
Then it's a contest.
Let's see who gets there first.
[YAMI] After all that, a whole
bunch of stuff happened.
Years went by.
Ol' Julius was crowned
as the Wizard King.
And as for me and my
new pal Goldiguts...
..both of us ended up
getting promoted
to vice captain
of the Grey Deer.
Then, one day...
Ah, yes! It's
wonderful to see you.
How are things?
[YAMI] Let's skip the small
talk, if you don't mind.
[WILLIAM]
I agree.
By the way, William,
I was happy to hear about
your excellent work
investigating the dungeon
that was recently discovered.
Oh, that was nothing, sir.
Don't be so modest!
You valiantly used
your magic to rescue
your trapped squadmates!
Boy, I wish I
could've seen that!
Ah, and such a noble
effort is obviously
worthy of a star! Nice work!
[WILLIAM] I'm honored.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
[JULIUS] And apparently,
you fought like a man possessed
during the treacherous battle
to defend the Village of Kuka.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but I believe I heard
you sliced the enemy's
giant Stone Magic
warrior in two!
Oh, come on,
that was... amazing!
And I'm gonna get a star
for my heroics, too, right?
[JULIUS]
Of course!
Your captain must be beaming
with pride right now!
[MARX]
Wizard King? It's time, sir.
[JULIUS]
Right, I almost forgot.
I appreciate you
coming all this way
when you're so busy, but...
[YAMI, WILLIAM]
But?
It would appear that
I have a new assignment
lined up for you to do.
[YAMI, WILLIAM]
Bandits?
Indeed. They've been
making mischief all over.
Do you think you could
take care of them for us?
Certainly. We're Magic
Knights, after all.
We're here to serve the people
of the Clover Kingdom.
So we'll go, and
happily. However...
Why are you sending
us and only us?
[JULIUS] Well, we have reason
to believe that these bandits
may be receiving
help from someone
who's part of the Magic Knights.
Ah, so it'll take
a little finesse.
[JULIUS]
Hm. This isn't just
some ordinary band
of miscreants.
From what we've observed,
we understand these people
are considerably powerful,
their leadership
is unusually strong,
and they're currently
in possession of ancient
magic items. Plus...
It seems they may
have absconded with
some magic artifacts that
were found in the dungeons.
So you came to us.
Well, guess that makes sense.
[WILLIAM] If you'd addressed
the Magic Knights as a whole,
someone within the ranks
could've disposed
of evidence that might
reveal the truth.
That's why we need to
handle it discreetly.
[JULIUS]
That about covers it.
Just one thing, though, Julius.
What're you gonna do if it
turns out William and I
were the big traitors all along?
We would prob'ly turn a blind
eye to those bandits, right?
Indeed, that would be a problem.
But then...
...I like to believe I know
you fellows fairly well.
Even from the days
before you became
members of the Magic Knights.
So I'm assuming it's
safe to trust you.
Although, if you do
decide to betray me,
I guess that's
the way life goes.
Heh. You got a strange
outlook on life, Julius.
Marx, would you
please do the honors?
[MARX]
Yes, sir.
[MARX] The towns and villages
that have been attacked
by the bandits are
indicated here.
Oh, I see. They're
all over the place.
They must not want us
to figure out which area
they're gonna go
after next, huh?
[MARX] We've sent word to
local Magic Knight squads
telling them to be extra
vigilant, but even that bit
of information could
be subject to leaks.
They tend to focus on the
places with weaker defenses.
So basically, we're gonna
have to guess at what
their next target'll be
and hope we get it right.
And that will not
be an easy task.
No. I think it will be.
Huh?
[WILLIAM] We can start by
ruling out all the spots
that have already been hit.
The places that are most at
risk would be where treasure
has recently been discovered,
or anywhere a harvest
is about to take place.
Especially a large one.
That's real nice detective work,
but we're still lookin'
at one or two dozen here.
We can exclude any
location that's near
a place they've already
attacked, as well.
And they'll most likely
avoid any areas
that are on high alert.
Maybe, but--
But that's too many for just
the two of us to manage.
I'm well aware.
So...
[WILLIAM] Here and here.
This village, as well.
Could you dispatch some
squads to these three areas
to watch for bandits?
[YAMI]
What for?
If word gets out, it'll be
all for nothin' anyway y--
That's brilliant! And assuming
the information does get leaked,
we can simply use it
to our advantage.
Correct. It's safe
to assume the bandits
will avoid the regions
where Magic Knights are.
They're probably going to
appear where they believe
no one will be waiting for them.
Uh. Yeah, obviously I knew that.
I was just makin' sure you
knew it, too, that's all.
Anyway, it looks like
we've narrowed it down
to one of two spots.
The town of Aymaia
or Zocodany Village.
[WILLIAM]
How does it look there, Yami?
[YAMI]
Everything's quiet right now.
[WILLIAM] Apparently,
a very old magic item
was recently found inside
a cave near Zocodany.
It's currently being kept
inside the chief's house
and revered as a precious
village treasure.
That sounds like the
kind of info only a handful
of Magic Knights would've
gotten wind of, right?
[WILLIAM] Exactly, if the
bandits show up in Zocodany
looking for that treasure,
then they would have
received their intel
far too quickly.
In which case, there's no doubt
we have a traitor in our midst.
[YAMI]
Got it. How's Aymaia?
It seems to be
all clear, as well.
They're done reaping,
and now they're preparing
for their harvest festival.
It's sure to be a
plentiful crop this year.
[YAMI] Well, that'll give the
bandits something to steal.
[WILLIAM] Look, just so
we're on the same page,
no matter which of us
sees the thieves first,
we shouldn't do it alone.
We should contact each
other and wait to attack
until we're both
present. Agreed?
[YAMI]
Yeah, yeah.
But you better not
pull a fast one on me
and try to get all
the stars for yourself!
[laughs] I'd never!
Anyway, I'll let you know
if I notice any movement.
[YAMI]
Tch.
Guess it's that time.
Hey, Mask Boy,
they're on the move.
You there? Hey!
The hell? It was
workin' fine earlier.
There's somethin' about this ki.
[YAMI] Are those guys blockin'
the flow of mana somehow?
They gotta be doin'
somethin' to break up
our lines of communication.
These are not your
run-o'-the-mill bandits.
[YAMI]
That means there is a traitor.
Now we just have
to figure out who.
Looks like about 30 of 'em--
No, more than that.
I'm gonna say it's around 50.
No matter which of us
sees the thieves first,
we shouldn't do it alone.
We should contact each other.
[YAMI] Well, we can't
contact each other,
so I'm movin' onto Plan B.
Sorry, I'm goin' solo.
[YAMI] I'll stop 'em
before they get there.
Dark Cloaked.
Black Blade!
[BANDITS yell]
Who's back there?
[BANDITS scream]
Spread out, we've been spotted!
Who is this guy?
A Magic Knight?
You've got guts
fighting us all alone!
Yeah, big mistake, pal!
Whatever. Dark Magic:
Dark Cloaked,
Lightless Slash!
[BANDITS scream]
Heh. That got about half of 'em.
[YAMI coughs]
You must be the bossman!
Wait, I think I know you.
That's odd, you don't
look like a Magic Knight.
Huh. Hey, I recognize you.
Yeah, you're gonna
have to remind me.
[BANDIT BOSS 85A]
Years ago, you were the one
who interfered with our attack
on that pathetic village.
Who knew I'd get to
settle the score here?
I don't follow.
Oh! That was you!
I remember now.
[YAMI] He looks flashy,
but he actually doesn't have
a whole lot of magic
power to speak of.
That wand he's got is
another story, though.
I betcha anything it's
a priceless treasure
that was dug up in
one of those dungeons.
[BANDIT BOSS 85A]
I've changed quite a bit
since the last time we fought.
Who cares? I'm more interested
in who gave you that wand.
You wanna find out,
you'll have to beat me first!
It's over!
[DRAGON roars]
[yells]
[YAMI] That turned out to
be a whole lotta nothin'.
Now. Speak up, and I want
every single detail.
Who was it that gave ya
this fancy magic wand?
Five seconds. And now four...
[BANDIT BOSS 85A]
Okay, okay, I'll tell you!
Uh, the truth is...
Ah!
Get back inside!
That's it. Don't you move,
Mr. Magic Knight!
Take one step,
and the old lady dies!
Then you're gonna suffer
a hundred times worse!
What does that mean?
Your little buddies won't
do you any more good
than they did
last time we fought.
No, you're obviously capable
of defeating my men. But this...
[YAMI]
What the--?
[MOHL] That's an Earth
Magic spell by the name
of Witch Hunter Claws.
Impressive, isn't it?
And that's not all.
You're also trapped
by a Binding spell
called Sheep Horn Snag.
Wait a sec. Don't I
know you two?
[MOHL, GOHT cackle]
[YAMI] That's right,
Crimson Goht and Silver Mohl!
I never thought there'd
be two traitors among us.
You guys have been feeding
those bandits intel
and magic items
so they would go out
and attack the villages
and towns. Haven't you?
That won't help you.
You can't break those bonds
with mortal strength.
You're a damn disgrace to
Magic Knights everywhere!
[GOHT]
Ah, I remember!
You're that foreigner
the Wizard King
just promoted, aren't
you? Yami Sukehiro.
I suspected he might
be plotting something.
I guess this means
I was correct.
[MOHL] In other words,
when the Wizard King ordered
the Magic Knights to guard
these areas against
bandit invasions, it was
nothing but a simple diversion.
An attempt to narrow down
where we'd strike next
and you fell for it,
hook, line, and sinker!
I have to say, the whole
situation's terribly amusing!
Excellent, you two managed
to capture him just
in the nick of time!
I should've known you would
have no problems with traps!
[MOHL] Stop standing around
and go look for that treasure!
Oh! Right! Of course!
I'll have a look around
the chief's house!
You! Take me there!
Ah! Okay!
[BANDIT BOSS 85A]
Give me a hand, boys!
[BANDITS]
Yes, sir!
[YAMI] The Magic Knights are
supposed to protect the people,
not ransack their towns!
You're both monsters!
We'll be certain to fulfil
our duty as Magic Knights
by making the Wizard King
aware that there's been
a bandit incident in this area.
Don't go thinkin' you'll
finish me off that easily.
I'll pay you back
times a million!
[GOHT]
Oh, I'm shaking in my shoes!
[MOHL]
Anyway, we're done here.
How much longer can
you keep that up?
Might as well surrender already.
Nah, it'll take a whole
lot more than this.
I'm not done!
I'll break through!
[MOHL] Surely you've exhausted
all your strength by now.
I'm just getting started.
I'll reach my limit and
push past it! Here and now!
[BANDITS yelp]
[WILLIAM]
Dracaena Formation.
[YAMI pants]
Are you all right?
[YAMI]
'Bout time.
I got here as
quickly as I could.
I realized we'd been cut off.
And then, well, the
only logical assumption
was that the bandits must
have appeared in Zocodany.
[YAMI] Uh-huh. Guess
I owe ya one, then.
In fact, I'll pay
it off right now.
Ready for this? Those
punks are the traitors.
[WILLIAM] Goht and Mohl,
you say? Good to know.
Ah, William Vangeance.
I take it you're acting under
the Wizard King's
orders as well?
Then we'll just eliminate
you and Yami Sukehiro
in one fell swoop.
This again.
Now, Attack of the Horn!
Dark Cloaked, Lightless Slash!
[GOHT groans]
I believe I said
I'd pay you back
a million times over, didn't I?
Um. Please go easy on me,
if you don't mind!
Not bad at all, if you ask me.
Let me suggest something while
I've got your attention.
I think you should consider
coming over to our side.
Your side?
[MOHL] Sure, it's a lot
of fun working with us.
My, how tempting.
Thank you, but I refuse.
I'm afraid I've
sworn my absolute
loyalty to the Wizard King.
Yes, of course you have.
Well, that's a terrible shame.
I figure that makes
us about even.
[WILLIAM]
You're right, it is a shame.
A shame that there
were traitors hiding
among the ranks of
the Magic Knights.
[MOHL screams]
[WILLIAM]
Now then. One last thing.
Uh-huh.
Whoever that is,
go get rid of him!
[BANDITS yell]
[JULIUS] I didn't intend
to involve myself.
I mean, maybe a little bit.
[BOTH gasp]
Guess we're done.
[JULIUS]
Splendid job, you two!
Not only did you discover
the Magic Knight traitors
and capture them, but you
managed to round up
the entire bandit group!
[YAMI]
To be fair, we found the bossman
unconscious up in a tree.
[JULIUS laughs]
Sometimes, things just work out!
But, with my deepest sincerity,
you both did well.
[JULIUS]
Yami. William.
I'm so impressed with
your performance.
I'd like to invite
you to be captains
of two new Magic Knight squads.
You're kidding.
You're asking us to
lead our own squads?
I hope that you'll accept.
So if both of us made
the captain spot at once,
I guess it's a tie.
That's true. But the
real race lies ahead.
Uh-huh.
I'll win. Watch.
Keep dreamin'.
I have every confidence in you.
So, Yami, what kind of squad
would you like to form?
What kind, huh? How do I put it?
Lemme see. How about a place
for misfits to belong.
Where things like your
rank and bloodline
don't make any difference.
Where even hooligans
are welcome.
You know, like the
home you gave me.
I see! An excellent idea!
As for the name...
Gimme a second.
If I want lotsa
different people,
bringin' all their
colors to the table,
mixin' 'em up till
it's a big mess...
Hm...
Oh! If you put a buncha
different colors together,
you get black!
So I'll call us the Black,
uh, the Black Bulls!
The Black Bulls
it is! Nice choice.
It suits you well.
And your team?
If I could,
I'd like to call mine
the Golden Dawn.
[JULIUS]
Golden Dawn?
That's right.
And when it becomes
the best of all,
consider it my tribute to you.
True to its name,
my squad will bring
the shining gold of
dawn to our world,
covering it with
warmth and light.
Just as sunlight pierces
even the darkest night,
we'll serve as a
reminder to the people
that daybreak is sure to come.
[YAMI] You think really
highly of yourself.
Such a beautiful sentiment.
I'm expecting great things.
Starting today,
I hereby name you
the official captain
of the Golden Dawn.
Congratulations to you, William.
[WILLIAM]
Sir.
[JULIUS]
And, Yami, from this moment on,
you will be
recognized as founder
and leader of the Black Bulls.
Best of luck, Captain.
[YAMI]
Let's do this, Goldiguts.
And that's that.
Uh...
Neat, huh?
Well, uh, a bunch of
stuff did happen.
Um, what's the point you
were tryin' to make again?
You know! To never give up!
No matter how many times
you may fall down!
Even if you're about
to lose it all!
You can't quit on your dreams!
Always push past your limits!
So what if your rival outdid ya
this one time, that's nothin'!
If you lose 99 battles,
just win the 100th!
Um. I'll keep that in mind.
Could've said it from
the start, though--
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
I'm sorry, that was
a great story--
please don't crush my head!
You know, the captain said
some smart stuff in there.
There's no reason to be sad!
All right! Time to work
hard, catch up to Yuno,
and leave him behind!
Hey, that reminds me.
Isn't it about time we got
back the results from
the Royal Knights
Selection Exam?
Uh. Yeah, think so!
Whoo! Can't wait to see!
[laughs nervously]
Bring it on, Mr. Owl,
I'm ready for ya!
[banging]
[MAGNA]
Damn!
That's the biggest owl
I've ever heard!
Well, whoever you are,
you can quit bangin'
the door down already.
If you're lookin' for
Captain Yami's Black Bulls,
then you came to the ri--
Whoa, what just happened?
[ASTA] Hey, I recognize her!
That's Fuegoleon's sister!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[YAMI] "Goldiguts
With the Moronic Mask!"
Oh, hey. Moronic Mask Goldiguts!
I wish you would stop
calling me that name.
Then how 'bout...
Moronic Mask Baldiguts!
I'd rather you didn't
call me that name, either.
Okay, Baldiguts Longjohns!
That's not any better.
Baldiguts Longjohns
Belt Mask then!
That doesn't sound like a name.
Baldiguts Longjohns
Mustache Teacup Guy!
I think you left some out.
Moronic Mask Goldiguts--no,
Baldiguts Longjohns
Mustache Teacup.
Wait, dammit, I forgot the belt.
Just call me "William."
[MAGNA] The Selection Exam
results'll be here
any minute now! I mean,
not that it matters,
I totally made the cut! Huh?
Wh-What do you mean,
I sound like I'm panicking?
Black Clover , Page 87:
"Formation of the
Royal Knights"!
I'm on fire, baby!