[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR]
Round Two, Match One of the
Royal Knights Selection Exam.
[NARRATOR] Sol trapped
Mimosa with her magic.
Asta defended their
crystal from Magna,
who launched an all-out
solo attack. Then...
Seems you're forgetting
about this dashing mage!
[ASTA]
Yikes! Two against one?
Not good.
[NARRATOR] Asta's mysterious
teammate, Xerx,
came to his rescue.
Go after the flower
guy. Do it. Now!
This will only slow
me for a moment.
[ASTA]
That's all I need to beat you!
[KIRSCH yelps, grunts]
[NARRATOR] Mimosa deployed
a plant spell that stopped
Sol's golem in its
tracks, and Asta
and the rest of Team B
were able to claim victory.
And now, Finral and Langris
prepare to face off.
Who will win in this
battle of brothers?
[VANESSA chuckles]
That's much better.
Uh. Thank you, Vanessa.
That's great.
[ASTA]
Great? Try perfect!
You look awesome, Finral!
Yeah, you think you
could do mine next?
[VANESSA] Why would I
style a loser's hair?
You look fine to me. Like
the failure that you are.
Oh, yeah? Come over
here and say that!
Hey, take it easy, Magna.
Just try to stay calm.
Like a loser should.
Hey! You mess with me right now,
and I'm gonna kill you!
[LUCK laughs] Sounds like
someone's looking to spar.
Whoa! Whoa! It's not
the time, g--!
[yelps]
In spite of his rough
looks, that guy seems
like he knows his way
around flame magic.
The lightning mage
is skilled, as well.
[mumbling] Luck is
trying to cheer Magna up
because that's what friends do.
Hey there! You got any
more food, mister?
[HAMON] My goodness,
for someone your size,
you certainly can eat.
[GAUCHE] Marie. Angel.
How I miss you, my darling!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 80A]
What's going on?
[MAGIC KNIGHT 80B]
It's just the Black Bulls.
[MAGIC KNIGHT 80A] Still the
same idiots they've always been.
Stop, this is embarrassing!
You're making all
of us look bad!
[VANESSA laughs] You're
lookin' a little stiff there.
Worried, huh?
About the match
and who you're facing.
Well, yeah. A little. I mean...
He might be my younger brother,
but I've never beaten
him at anything.
[VANESSA]
Don't worry.
I've fought alongside
you, so I know.
You changed after meeting
Asta. Just like I did.
Thanks to him, I was
finally able to face
something I'd hidden
deep inside my heart.
You're not going to lose
to him so easily anymore.
Go show 'em how awesome you are.
And I don't just mean the hair.
[gasps] Thanks, Vanessa.
She's right, you've
totally got this!
I wanna fight you, so don't
be a big loser like Magna.
Yeah! Don't be a
big loser like m--
That's it! I'm gonna kill you!
[laughs]
[GREY] We'll all be
rooting for you, Finral.
[mumbling] You can do it!
You can do it!
You had better not
blow this match
and embarrass the
rest of the squad.
Wow. You guys. Thank you all.
I don't know what to say.
I'm so happy I joined
the Black Bulls.
You're like a family--
Feed me, feed me,
feed me, feed me,
--feed me, feed me, feed me. Ah!
--[HAMON laughs]
Hurry up and win this.
I need to return to Marie
as soon as possible.
--Uh--
--[FINRAL] I'm your superior.
[ASTA] And I'm sure Captain
Yami's cheering you on
back at the hideout, too!
That's right.
His stomach wasn't feeling well,
or else I know he would've been
here to show his support.
Even so.
I'm sure he wants
you to work hard.
With or without him.
Heh. Those morons
are probably pushin'
past their limits right now.
Just like I'm about to.
This is the biggest dump
the world's ever seen.
Damn it, kid!
I told you to restock
the toilet paper!
Give up now.
You must know you stand
no chance of defeating me.
No, you're wrong.
Thanks to my friends, I'm
stronger than I used to be.
Our team will win.
We'll see about that, Brother.
Don't blame me if you get hurt.
If it's okay with you,
I'd like to handle him myself.
[HAMON]
Hm. Seems fine.
A battle between brothers.
I hope to test
my fighting prowess
against my own brother someday.
So, yes, I agree to your request
and wish you the best of luck.
Ha, ha! I'll ride the Sekke
Shooting Star to victory.
All shall remember
my performance.
Your team won't lay a finger
on our crystal in this match.
[yells] It's finally starting!
I can't help but
feel nervous for him.
[VANESSA]
You can win this, Finral.
I know you can.
And now, Team E,
comprised of Leopold,
Hamon, and Finral,
vs Langris, Fragil,
and Sekke of Team G.
Round two, match two, begin!
You guys concentrate on
destroying their crystal.
[LEOPOLD]
We've got this.
First we need to
determine its location.
Now. Glass Magic:
Verre Détection .
[HAMON] The light will reflect
off the glass shards
scattered throughout
the battleground,
and every last inch of it
will be revealed to me.
This may take some time,
but rest assured,
I've no doubt I will find
the enemy's crystal.
Oh!
[SEKKE laughing]
I expect you to take
me all the way
to the enemy base
again, Mr. Ha, ha.
Leave it to me. And the
name's actually Sekke.
Please feel free to use it.
You can even call me
"Sek" for short, ha, ha!
Whatever you say, Mr. Ha, ha.
Ha, ha! No, I just told you.
It's Sekke. Sekke!
[LANGRIS] You brought shame
upon the House of Vaude.
There's no way I'll let
you defeat me today.
[FINRAL'S STEP MOTHER]
How could I possibly love you?
You aren't even my own
flesh and blood.
My sweet little Langris
is the only child I need.
[laughs] Come now,
Mother, don't you think
it's a bit cruel
to put it so bluntly?
[FINRAL'S FATHER] What can
you accomplish with that?
Learn to attack, like Langris!
[FINRAL'S STEP MOTHER]
What do you know.
My Langris is both more athletic
and more intelligent than you.
[FINRAL'S STEP MOTHER laughs]
You're so amazing,
darling Langris.
As I should expect from
my own flesh and blood.
[FINRAL'S FATHER]
Unlike you, Finral.
You're a disgrace
to the Vaude name.
[LANGRIS]
How pathetic.
He's the older brother,
but there's not a single
thing he can do better than me.
[FINRAL]
What? A fiancée?
[FINRAL'S FATHER]
Yes. This is Lady Finnes.
She will marry the next head
of the House of Vaude.
[FINNES coughs]
Nice to meet you.
[FINRAL'S FATHER]
Her chronic illness keeps her
housebound mostly, but the
king is her great uncle,
so she comes from
a prestigious family,
and her magic is impressive.
[LANGRIS] Ugh. This is the
woman I'm going to marry?
Couldn't Father have
chosen someone less dull?
[FINRAL'S STEP MOTHER]
Now remember, dear.
Lady Finnes is going
to be your bride someday,
so you must try to
get along with her.
Of course!
[LANGRIS] Honestly. I don't
need a wife with a fancy title.
When I'm the lord of
this house, I'll bring more
honor to the Vaude family
than anyone has before.
Ugh. I'm so bored.
I'm very sorry.
I doubt many men would
choose to marry a woman
who's both sickly and
older than they are
I... I mean.
Any man would be lucky
to have a wife
as beautiful as you,
Lady Finnes.
[laughs]
It's just that
I'm not actually the
one who will become
the next head of House Vaude.
Huh?
I'm sure my younger brother
will make you happy, though.
He's better at
everything than I am.
His magic's amazing,
and he's really brave.
Compared to him,
I'm a total failure.
[LANGRIS]
Exactly.
At least he realizes
he's inferior to me in--
[FINNES]
No, you're wrong.
I know I've only met
you a few times,
but I can tell.
You're a very kind,
considerate person.
So, if you ask me,
you're a better mage
than your brother will ever be.
[gasps] Oh! You're
joking, of course.
Please don't tease me like that.
Don't be silly. I wasn't
teasing you at all.
[LANGRIS] Who does this
sparrow think she is?
Rating me lower
than that failure.
Utterly absurd.
He left the family because he
couldn't handle the pressure.
He's not better than
me at anything.
Not a single thing!
[SEKKE]
Ha, ha! We found it!
[laughs]
[ALL gasp]
Well, I hope you're
ready, Finral,
because here he comes.
Remember what I said.
Don't blame me if you
wind up losing a limb or two.
I'll end this in a single blow!
[gasps] What?
That's right. I tested
this earlier with Cob.
Something happens when
spatial magic spells clash.
The mana currents
within them collide,
causing them to cancel
each other out.
Just like that!
Langris, you won't
win this time!
That's so cool!
So two spatial magic spells
cancel each other out?
He didn't see that coming!
It's like Finral's a totally
different person out there!
Lose at this point
and I'll kill ya!
Hurry up and finish it.
Marie's waiting.
[slurps] I can almost taste
the victory cupcakes now!
Uh. Ha... ha?
[laughs] It looks like
we made a good choice,
letting you take him on.
Hamon, any luck yet?
[HAMON] Yes! I've finally
found the enemy's crystal.
It's hidden within that tower.
Right. Now, go. Quickly!
[gasps] They're gone! Ha, ha!
You've gotten too cocky,
but I'll put you
back in your place!
[LEOPOLD yells]
[gasps]
Step aside! We're gonna
destroy that crystal!
We'll see about that.
What's this?
Snow Magic: Phantom Snow Garden.
Do you feel it yet?
This spell both deadens your
senses and induces sleep.
While it's active, you won't
be able to attack
me effectively.
[grunting]
Yeah, right. I'm
not tired at all.
This is nothing compared to
my older sister's training.
Nothing.
[HAMON] Did you honestly think
that this would be enough?
Exactly! We can take
her, no problem.
I could eat five more helpings
and still have room left.
You're talking in your sleep?
[chuckles] Why fight it?
You look like you
can use the rest.
[LEOPOLD growls, yells]
[gasps] Those flames!
[LEOPOLD] I bear the
House Vermillion symbol
of an oath made to oneself.
I swore a vow that one day
I would surpass my brother.
So I'm not about to lose
to somebody like you.
There's no way!
Mana Skin!
Go Flame Magic: Spiral Flames!
[gasps]
[FRAGIL]
His senses are still sharp.
He managed to nullify my spell
by enveloping himself in mana.
[LEOPOLD] Stay strong.
Can't lose my concentration.
[gasps] I won't last much
longer. Hurry, Langris.
[SEKKE]
Ha, ha!
Ooh! A battle between two
adept spatial magic users!
You don't see one
of those every day.
Ah, so that's the Vaude boy
Finnes is going to
marry. He's talented.
Still no match for me, though.
Keep it up, Finral!
You've got him now!
You just have to hold out until
the other two destroy
the enemy's crystal.
Who knew?
I never imagined you had what
it took to stand against me.
Do you plan on playing defense
all by yourself until
your crystal breaks?
I'm not going to make it easy.
I'm sure you won't. That's fine.
Because I came
prepared to fight.
Ha, ha! You're an even bigger
idiot than I realized
if you think a sluggish
spell like that
could ever catch
my marvelous self.
[LANGRIS]
Incoming?
[SEKKE] That's an interesting
feature, but it's still no match
for my invincible
Sekke Magnum Cannonball!
[SEKKE laughs]
What? He just disappeared?
[sighs] Even I think
it's pitiful.
I trained like crazy,
but it didn't matter.
I never managed to learn
a single attack spell.
[LANGRIS]
Wait. It's not an attack spell?
That's Spatial Magic:
Fallen Angel's Wingbeat.
It follows the enemy,
makes contact,
then transports them
to another location.
It's a battlefield application
of the spell I usually use.
[gasps] He adapted a
basic spatial magic spell
so he can get rid of his
enemies without harming them.
Clearly this is a mage who
possesses a truly gentle soul.
I knew you could do more
than just flirt with girls!
He's gone.
I wonder where the
portal took him, though.
[laughing]
[YAMI growls]
I was this close
to pinchin' it off.
You're dead meat.
[SEKKE]
Ha, ha... Not good.
[SEKKE screams]
Langris, it's only
a matter of time
before my teammates
destroy your crystal.
II don't want to hurt
my own brother.
Give up, or you'll
disappear, too.
[laughs]
[gasps]
[LANGRIS]
You're worried about hurting me?
You're as annoying as
you are incompetent.
Who would've thought our special
reserve spells would
be so similar?
[LANGRIS] How dare you force
me to use my grimoire's magic?
There isn't a single
thing you can beat me at,
and there never will be.
[ASTA] This threatening
feeling. I recognize it.
Wait. I know this mana.
[gasps]
What happened?
My goodness.
I must say, this is
quite unpleasant.
[JULIUS]
As I suspected.
[LANGRIS]
It's over, Brother.
His magic...
[FINRAL] I already knew I
didn't stand a chance against
a mage as strong as my brother,
but something else
is going on here.
Something strange.
I've felt magic
like this before.
[FINRAL]
Who are you?
Get outta there!
If that attack hits him...
Run, Finral!
[FINRAL] No. He's Langris.
He's my little brother.
You may not like it,
but we're similar.
So what if we come
from different mothers?
I never acted like
an older sibling should.
I left our family, and tried
to forget everything.
[FINRAL] But I couldn't.
No matter what you think...
No matter what
we've been through...
You're still my little brother.
[yells] Please, Langris,
stop this! Right now!
Or I don't know how much
longer you'll stay you.
Give me a break.
What could you possibly
understand about me?
You ran--abandoned your house.
You're a coward who can't even
attack somebody in battle!
You're nothing!
I'll stop you!
[FINRAL, LANGRIS yell]
Finral, no!
Crystal destroyed. Team G wins.
[LANGRIS cackles]
There. Do you understand now?
You can never beat me.
Such different boys.
Young Master Finral's so kind,
and very popular, too.
Unlike his little brother.
You can tell that boy looks down
on everybody he talks to.
Such a shame.
Well, if you ask me,
you're a much better mage.
[LANGRIS] She seemed so kind.
But even she hates me.
[FINRAL]
Langris! You can take one day
off of studying, can't you?
Come goof off with
your big brother.
I'll be at the festival
if you wanna join me!
[LANGRIS]
Why is he so nice to me?
Stop it.
Be more like Langris!
My Langris is so amazing!
[LANGRIS]
I'm better than he is.
That's why Mother and Father
are always kind to me.
I have to beat him
at everything.
Everything. Otherwise...
I'll... I'll...
See that?
He's goin' after the
guy on the ground.
Why? The match is over.
[LANGRIS]
Disappear.
[CHARMY yelps]
[NOELLE]
Finral!
[NOELLE] He won't last long
with wounds like these.
[ASTA]
Hey!
Go on. Take one more
step toward him.
But you should know that the
second you do, you're dead.
[GAUCHE]
Bastard.
You're going to pay for this.
[CAT hisses]
I can't believe
he would do that.
[mumbling] You actually
managed to piss me off.
Monster!
Huh?
There's something
wrong with you.
The match was already over.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[GORDON mumbling]
Clover Clips.
[FINRAL]
"Hairstyle."
That new spell was
totally awesome!
Fallen Angel's Weightlifting!
That was close. But not quite.
Well, sometimes you gotta
shake things up, y'know.
That's the only way
to get stronger.
Oh, yeah?
So, are you gonna
get a new hairdo
every time you need
to beef up your magic?
[BLACK BULLS]
That could be cool.
Uh, I don't know.
You should try one of those
pompadour things next.
Or maybe Captain
Yami's hairstyle.
Or a yummy soft-serve swirl.
[FINRAL]
That looks like poop--
This one looks pretty tough.
If you try Marie's
hairstyle, I'll kill you.
Or, um, maybe
something like this?
[NOELLE] Well, personally,
I think this one
would be more attractive.
For no particular
reason, of course.
[mumbling] Maybe something
a bit more mature?
This one here is for
pushing past your limits.
No, seriously.
My life would be
complete if I could
only see this hairstyle
on you, Finral!
I've got more to worry about
right now than my hair!
[KING CLOVER]
Praise me as I deserve!
For I am your benevolent
and mighty sovereign.
Next time on
Black Clover , Page 81:
"The Life of a Certain Man."
[KING CLOVER]
I said praise me!