[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] The Star Festival
is an annual event
at which the number of
stars bestowed upon each
of the Magic Knight squads
during that year
by the Wizard King is
announced to the public.
The squad whose
accomplishments were greater
than all the others is
awarded the topmost rank,
which is an unparalleled honor.
[FESTIVALGOER 69D]
The Star Ceremony's
getting ready to start!
[FESTIVALGOER 69E] All th
captains are going to be there!
[FESTIVALGOER 69AA]
Even the new captains
of the Crimson Lion Kings
and the Purple Orcas!
All of 'em? Uh-oh.
Dammit, we're late.
Eh, they'll wait for me.
[JULIUS]
Citizens!
Thank you all so much
for attending.
Hey, look! It's the Wizard King!
[CROWD cheers]
The Magic Knight
squads have done
some amazing deeds this year.
I'm here to recognize them.
The Wizard King in the flesh!
[CITIZEN 70C]
That's awesome!
[JULIUS]
And following my announcement,
King Clover himself has
a few words for you as well.
[CITIZEN 70D]
Wizard King!
That's our Wizard King!
He's so cool! Wow!
Now then.
As I assume everyone here
is aware, our nation
has suffered attacks
from both the Spade
and Diamond Kingdoms.
We're also waging a bitter
war against the relentless
terrorist organization known as
the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
When they advanced
on the Capital,
many of our people
sacrificed their lives.
At one point, I even
considered canceling
this year's festival.
But then, it occurred
to me that this event
would be the ideal
opportunity to honor
all of those who bravely
defended this country
from our enemies.
And so, the moment has come.
Please welcome the pride
of Clover Kingdom:
our Magic Knight captains!
[CROWD cheers]
[CITIZEN 70E]
It's the captains!
[JULIUS] Captain of the
Silver Eagles: Nozel Silva!
Captain of the Green Praying
Mantises: Jack the Ripper!
Captain of the Coral Peacocks:
Dorothy Unsworth!
Captain of the Aqua Deer:
Rill Boismortier!
Captain of the Crimson Lion
Kings: Mereoleona Vermillion!
[CITIZEN 70F]
Their new captain's a woman?
[CITIZEN 70G] I hear she's just
as skilled with Flame Magic
as her brother Fuegoleon--
you know, their last captain.
In fact, she might
be even better!
[JULIUS] The new captain of the
Purple Orcas: Kaiser Granvorka!
[CITIZEN 70H]
Another new captain?
[CITIZEN 70I] Yeah, that
group's been through a lot.
[CITIZEN 70AA] I'm sure
they'll do great things!
And last but not least,
the captain of the Golden Dawn:
William Vangeance!
[CITIZEN 70BB squeals]
Captain William!
[CITIZEN 70J] The Golden Dawn's
totally gonna win this thing!
[CITIZEN 70K] Wait. Aren't
we missing some people?
[CITIZEN 70CC]
I think so!
[JULIUS] I told them several
times to be punctual.
I'd expect this from Yami, but
it's not like Charlotte at all!
That's no good.
Bein' late makes
a bad impression.
[FINRAL] Yeah, you seem
really concerned about it!
Well, I suppose we
should keep moving.
It's time to announce
the standings!
In first place...
The Golden Dawn!
Their total number
of stars was 125!
That's an improvement on last
year's total of 96 stars!
[CITIZEN 70DD]
Wow!
[CITIZEN 70L]
They're really crushin' it!
[CITIZEN 70M]
That's the Golden Dawn for ya!
It would appear the
Golden Dawn has managed
to pull off an impressive
showing once again.
And now, please allow me to
introduce the highest earner
among all the Magic Knights.
Attended by the
Wind spirit Sylph,
our promising newcomer, Yuno!
[CHARMY]
Huh? Yuno?
He's dreamy!
Isn't he?
Excellent work, Yuno!
I'm so proud!
Oh, come on.
What did you expect?
Yuno. I'm gonna
catch up to you soon!
And now for the
second-place winners.
Whaddaya think?
The Crimson Lions?
Nah. I'm sure they
fell behind a lot
after Fuegoleon got injured.
My money's on the Silver Eagles!
The Blue Rose Knights
deserve to win
more than anyone else!
I do wonder why
Captain Charlotte's
not up on stage, though.
[FINRAL]
Hey there.
You wanna come walk around
the festival with me?
[CITIZEN 70GG] That robe.
You're one of the Black Bulls.
Yeah, forget it.
You'll just come in
last place again.
Our second-place team is...
No point in listening.
Might as well stay here
and goof off right?
We know we're dead last.
[JULIUS]
The Black Bulls!
[ALL gasp]
[CITIZEN 70Q]
What?
It can't be!
[JULIUS]
Their star total, 101!
No way! We got second place?
But how is that possible?
If we're second... Uh-oh.
There's no way this
is really happening.
Awesome!
Well, that's quite a surprise.
I thought they might
have raised their rank
from last year,
but this? Now I see.
[CITIZEN 70R] Those goofballs
really took second place?
[CITIZEN 70S]
There must be some mistake.
[CITIZEN 70T] Heh. I bet
they threatened somebody.
[CITIZEN 70HH]
They probably cheated somehow.
[KAHONO]
No they didn't!
The Black Bulls risked
their lives to save us
from the Midnight
Sun, so I won't
let you talk about 'em that way!
That's right, and they
would never cheat!
Wow, you guys. Thanks a lot.
Yeah, they were a big
help to us, too!
Some of them are kind of rough,
but they're all nice people!
[JULIUS] I don't blame you
all for being surprised.
If you'll recall, just
last year, the Black Bulls
ended up earning
an unprecedented total
of negative 50 stars.
But this year is different.
They've accomplished
unbelievable feats
and risen up through the
rankings to claim second-place.
Then there's the newcomer
who's especially--
Oh, their captain
is still missing.
Hello?
Are any of the Black Bulls
present tonight?
[MAGNA]
Man, this is a shock.
[GAME HOST 70A] Uh... I'm sorry
to butt in, gentlemen,
but he's askin' for you.
Trust me, we'd love
to go up there,
but this moment belongs
to a different member
of the Black Bulls.
[LUCK]
Mm-hm!
Where is that nitwit, anyway?
I'm going to let you
have this one, Asta,
so you'd better get up there
before I change my mind!
[YAMI] They're callin'
your name. Go on, kid.
[ASTA screams]
[gasps]
[ASTA]
Whew, that was scary.
Oh, hey. You made it.
Sure did. What's up?
[CROWD cheering]
Go, Asta!
[YUNO] The Black Bulls
did grow a lot more
than the rest of us
over the past year.
Good job.
Looks like you earned
your fair share
of stars for your team.
But don't get comfortable.
I'll become the
next Wizard King.
I wouldn't talk so big!
Your squad might've gotten
first place and set
a new record and everything,
but you'd better not
let that go to your head
either, 'cause I'm gonna
make sure I earn double
the number of stars
you get next time!
Okay, then I'll get twice that.
That's how you wanna play?
Then I'll do five
times that many!
Do you even know how
many times more stars
than me you're
looking at right now?
Uh, two times two times five
would be, er, nine times?
Twenty times, genius.
[ASTA]
Man!
My, that certainly was an
exciting entrance, wasn't it?
Let's all applaud for
the rookie who's done
the most for the Black
Bulls this year. Asta!
Aw. Shucks, guys! Thanks a lot!
[JULIUS] Yuno and Asta
are the top earners
among all of the novice Knights.
Which means they're two
new stars to watch!
They've produced
outstanding results,
considering the
fact they've only
been Knights for half a year.
Interestingly, these 16 years
old's are childhood friends
from the same hometown!
For being so young,
those two are doing
marvelous things!
Yeah, they're probably nobility.
[SEKKE] Actually, they're
naught but commoners!
[CROWD gasps]
It's true ha, ha!
The scrawny guy from
the Black Bulls
doesn't even have any magic.
Isn't that so sad?
[CITIZEN 70Y]
Commoners?
[CITIZEN 70Z]
Really?
[CITIZEN 70AA]
He can't use magic?
[CITIZEN 70II]
Makes you wonder if they really
earned those stars.
Sheesh!
What's the matter
with these people?
[YUNO]
Bell.
What is it, Yuno?
Let's show them.
Heh! It'd be my pleasure.
[CROWD gasps]
[gasps]
Yuno, wait. What are
you about to do?
Asta. Remember how
we used to train back
when we were little kids?
Yeah, but...
[ASTA grunts]
[CROWD screams]
Why do you always have to
pull crazy stuff like this
on me outta nowhere?
You're stronger now!
What, are you tryin'
to kill me during
my 15 seconds of fame,
ya big jerk?
[YUNO] If that'd killed you,
we'd know what your limit was.
Good thing you survived.
[ASTA]
Why, you little!
[CITIZEN 70AA] Whoa, that
magic power was devastating.
[CITIZEN 70AB]
And he blocked it!
[SEKKE]
They're sha- ha ckingly strong!
Now that you've witnessed
their abilities,
I invite anyone who still
doubts their worthiness
to please step forward.
Yes, it's true these
two are commoners,
but they've worked harder
than any of their peers
to make it where they are today.
Proud citizens of
the Clover Kingdom,
let us commend these
brave Knights!
Regardless of rank or status,
our nation's path
to victory is to
join together as one!
[CITIZEN 70AC]
Wizard King.
[CITIZEN 70AD]
Commoners aren't so bad.
[CITIZEN 70AE]
Hear, hear!
This is no time to dwell
on our differences!
[CITIZEN 70AF]
We can all fight together!
Yuno.
Yeah.
Look at us. We've
really come this far.
Now that everyone's gotten
back in a celebratory mood,
I'll go ahead and announce
the remainder of the
Magic Knight rankings!
Third place, the Silver
Eagles, with 95 stars.
Fourth place, the Blue Rose
Knights, with 83 stars.
Fifth place, the
Crimson Lion Kings,
with 76 stars.
Sixth place, the Green Praying
Mantises, with 69 stars.
Seventh place, the Coral
Peacocks, with 67 stars.
Eighth place, the Purple
Orcas, with 51 stars.
And lastly, in ninth place,
the Aqua Deer, with 49 stars.
That's all we got?
And on that note, the
Magic Knights' Star Ceremony
has come to an end.
I trust our squads
will continue doing good work
in the coming year.
We really came in dead last?
But why? How did that happen?
I don't understand
any of this at all.
Probably because all
you do is sit around
on your butt and draw stupid
pictures all day. [cackles]
[gasps]
Asta, please help me out!
How did you get so many stars?
I don't wanna end up a loser!
[ASTA]
Whoa, You are not makin' me
wanna help you, little guy!
[YUNO] This guys's a
Magic Knight Captain?
How did we lose
to the Black Bulls?
They're the band of misfits
Noelle works with!
Noelle, I'm so happy for you,
I don't know what to do!
Eh. It's not like
it's a surprise
[KIATO]
Next stop, first place!
And when that happens,
we'll dance for joy!
[CITIZEN 70AG]
We love you, Magic Knights!
[CITIZEN 70AH]
We're counting on you!
All right, now that
we're finished
with the Star
Ceremony announcements,
it is finally time!
The ruler of Clover Kingdom,
His Majesty the King.
Whoa, the king?
I just realized I've never
met the guy before,
so I don't know
what kinda person
we're dealing with, do you?
No clue.
[KING CLOVER chuckles]
They're nice and warmed up
from that opening act.
Which leaves me to bask
in their loving praise!
Now, my dear subjects...
...I will accept your cheers!
[KING CLOVER]
You're casting a shadow on me.
Move over three feet.
Oh, sorry.
Ahem! That's better.
Good evening and felicitations,
my adoring followers.
I am your beloved and
benevolent monarch,
the celebrated King Augustus
Kira Clover the Thirteenth.
[CITIZEN 70AI]
All hail the King. I guess.
You can do better than that!
Yikes, is that all it
took for him to snap?
Unbelievable.
You insolent fools,
I am the sovereign
of this great kingdom
and I demand admiration.
Am I making myself clear?
Witness this awe-inspiring
royal magic power,
handed down through
the generations!
My every single thought
and my appearance.
I am a most fitting and
proper King in all respects!
This makes me far superior
to a mere Wizard King!
[KING CLOVER laughs, coughs]
[CITIZEN 70AJ]
Man, I wish the Wizard King
could just be our king.
[CITIZEN 70AK] This guy's
a mess. Why's he in charge?
[CITIZEN 70AL] It's not like
we need two separate kings.
I think the Wizard King should
be our real king from now on!
[CROWD]
Shh!
Your Majesty.
Please calm down and
pull yourself together.
[KING CLOVER]
A curse upon you, Julius!
How easily you win the
affection of the people,
when I suffer such difficulty!
And what's more...
The Golden Dawn
is victorious again?
That featherfaced buffoon!
It's an outrage, I tell you!
Some of the other captains
have royal blood.
They're much worthier
of first place
than that pompous peacock!
[KING CLOVER] I'll just
have to make a dramatic
announcement and win
the support of my flock!
[KING CLOVER]
Citizens.
I have an important piece
of news to share with you.
We have located the
Midnight Sun's hideout.
[CROWD gasps]
Huh? We really found it?
[KING CLOVER] So far in
our battle against them,
we've consistently
been one step behind.
But those days are over!
You will be pleased to know that
we're preparing to launch
a full-scale counterattack
of our own.
And to do so, we plan
to gather the absolute
cream-of-the-crop from
our Magic Knight squads.
Allowing us to assemble the
most elite team imaginable!
And that unit will be
called the Royal Knights!
In a week's time.
I shall administer a rigorous
exam to the members
of all nine Magic Knight squads.
Only those who pass
the test will be invited
to join my Royal Knights!
And then, we will obliterate
the Eye of the Midnight Sun!
Now listen carefully,
my Magic Knights!
I ask you to offer up
your grimoires
in service to your country!
[CITIZEN 70AM]
Royal Knights!
[CITIZEN 70AN]
They can do it!
[CITIZEN 70JJ]
This is brilliant!
[KING CLOVER]
Success!
Julius came up with
the idea and took care
of all the research, but I'm
still getting the credit!
[ASTA] Why's the King
picking people, though?
Shouldn't the Wizard King
handle all that stuff?
I mean, he knows more
about the Magic Knights
than the king does, plus
everybody likes him more.
Think about it. The Wizard King
does cool stuff all the time,
and I never heard of King Clover
doin' anything that great.
What about you?
I dunno.
So he's got this
super-awesome magic power,
but he's never used it to make
life better for the kingdom?
Is that right?
[YUNO]
Yeah, I guess so.
I dunno, maybe it's 'cause
I don't have any powers,
so tell me if I'm
missin' the point here.
But I gotta say,
from where I'm standin',
it kinda seems to me
like the king
is totally pointless and dumb.
Asta, quit talking
and read the room.
No matter how right you are,
it's better to keep those
comments to yourself.
[ASTA] Huh? Sounds like
you agree with me!
[JACK chuckles] I like this kid.
He tells it like it is.
Off with their heads!
I want both of those traitors
to be executed at once,
right here at the festival!
[gasps]
Thanks for getting us killed.
Yeah, Yuno didn't
say anything bad!
[CITIZEN 70AO]
Execute them?
[CITIZEN 70AP]
Seriously?
Kill them! Kill them! Kill them!
I want them dead!
I do apologize for their
impertinence, Your Majesty.
However, for my sake,
I must implore you
to find it in your heart
to pardon this transgression.
After all, they may turn
out to be the shield
that protects you from
an attack one of these days.
Besides, this is
a trivial matter.
Best not throw
your weight around.
It'll cheapen your
royal authority.
Now, Royal Knights!
I expect great things!
I'm certain our Magic Knights
will meet this challenge
with profound strength
and courage!
[NOZEL]
Obviously.
[JACK] If he chooses
a Green Praying Mantis,
it'll raise the
squad's reputation.
Yami won't be ahead
of me for much longer.
[RILL] I gotta work hard and
make sure we don't end up
at last place again!
[YAMI]
Ugh. Sheesh.
This Royal Knights idea's got
"Julius" written all over it.
He sure comes up with
some interesting stuff.
[ASTA]
Wizard King!
I'm really, really, really sorry
for makin' the king mad! Really!
Where's my apology?
I almost got executed
because of you.
For Knights like you who
aspire to be the Wizard King,
the Royal Knights are a chance
to do even greater deeds.
[ASTA]
Right!
[JULIUS]
But, impressive though you are,
you're still newcomers.
You'll have some
stiff competition
when you take that exam.
The likes of which you
have yet to encounter.
Sounds fun to me!
Even if I don't succeed.
I'll at least be proud
to have made it that far.
You two keep working
hard and stay modest.
Well. Until next time.
[BOTH]
Sir!
I got no idea what kind of
exam they're gonna make us
take to join the Royal Knights,
but I'm ready to punch
it right in the face!
Try not to cry if I pass
and you fail, okay?
The only ones who'll
be cryin' are those
Eye of the Midnight Sun
losers when I ace this test
and kick their butts
into next week!
[ASTA] That's another reason
why I need to learn
how to handle that crazy
new power I just got.
[MEREOLEONA] Damn you!
You weak little imbecile!
[MEREOLEONA] The Crimson
Lions in fifth place?
How could you
humiliate us that way?
I have half a mind to annihilate
the whole lot of you
so I can save myself
the disappointment during
next year's Ceremony!
[ASTA]
Yikes!
What kinda crazy murder spree
did we just walk in on?
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[RILL]
"Rill the Artist"!
Oh, no.
I just can't get
that drawing right!
Hey, Rill! What are you up to?
Well, the king wanted me to draw
a caricature for him,
which is an honor and all.
But no matter what I do,
it keeps coming out all wrong!
Wow, I guess even the best
artists have bad days, huh?
I've been sitting
here forever waiting
for some inspiration
to land on me.
But even if I use
an abstract style,
his face is just so boring!
Let me see it.
[ASTA]
This is awesome.
[ASTA] Who's that scary
lady we just met?
Huh? Captain Fuegoleon's
big sister?
Black Clover , Page 71:
"The Uncrowned,
Undefeated Lioness."
I haven't said this in a while,
so I'll give it my best shot.
"My magic is never giving up!"