[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] The Royal Knights
seemed to be maintaining
the upper hand while attacking
the Eye of the Midnight
Sun's hideout.
But just as Mereoleona was about
to defeat Rhya for good...
We're the same. Aren't we?
So we should be able
to talk things over.
Both sides are mad because
we lost someone we loved.
I just want a kingdom
where all of us get along
and laugh together.
And when I'm Wizard King,
we'll have one.
You'll see!
[MEREOLEONA]
You imbecile.
Proudly proclaiming
something so outrageous.
[RHYA]
I think he's actually serious!
In fact, it reminds me of what
someone else said once before.
If only the rest
of the human race
thought about it the
way these guys do.
Then maybe...
No. It's too late to stop now.
[NARRATOR] At the same time,
the true intentions
of Licht or, rather,
Patry, were finally
beginning to come
to the surface.
Patry had once been
betrayed by humans,
forced to witness the
violent mass-murder
of his fellow elves.
And so, since assuming
the identity of Licht,
he had been working to resurrect
his fallen companions.
For going back on their word,
for killing the people
I loved, they must pay!
I swear, they will
all be annihilated!
[PATRY]
Indeed.
The great rebirth will
start with the humans.
Now what?
It can't be!
[SALLY, RADES, VALTOS scream]
[RILL] Hm. I think that profile
needs a little more work.
What's wrong with them?
We don't stand a chance.
These guys are out of control!
So, um...
You think maybe
you could tell me
where your leader is?
Well, you see, uh...!
Hurry up, spit it out.
I'm just itching to create
another masterpiece.
Master Licht
should be-- [groans]
Huh?
[yells]
[BOTH groaning]
[ALL gasp]
[groaning]
[gasps]
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES screaming]
I don't understand!
What's going on here?
I didn't even do
anything yet, I swear!
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES screaming]
[gasps]
Whoa. This is crazy!
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES groaning]
What kind of spell is that?
Ooh! This looks interesting!
Look there, at
the demon's skull.
Oh, don't be afraid.
It's all right.
There's nothing for us
to be concerned about.
After all, we've got
the Magic Knights.
They'll protect
the Clover Kingdom
from whoever dares
to threaten it!
[LILY]
Asta. Yuno!
It looks like the sun's rising,
even though it's the
middle of the night.
And those swords that
appeared in the sky...
What's happening to this place?
[gasps]
What is that? So bright!
First the whole sky
was covered with big,
shiny swords and now
this, too? I'm confused!
[mumbling] It's so bright.
Reminds me of the warmth
and friendship we share.
But... I guess I shouldn't
bring that up right now.
It might be another attack from
the Eye of the Midnight Sun!
[mumbling] It went out.
But still, our friendship
sparkles forever.
Hey, look at Gauche!
That's weird!
What's weird?
[GREY]
Um, your body is...
Yeah, what's the matter with it?
It's... all... glowy!
[gasps]
[GREY, GORDON gasp]
What is that, Marie?
It just never ends, does it?
[YAMI grunts]
What the hell?
[gasps]
Oh, wow. Where'd this come from?
Not Luck, too!
[BOTH gasp]
This is so weird.
What is it? I'm scared!
Man, it's one thing
after another!
Come on, what's with
the light show?
You owe us an explanation
before this is over,
do ya understand?
Hey! Answer me!
[RHYA]
Too bad.
What is?
Your worthless human
race is finished.
Oh, no. I have a bad feeling.
No. My friends.
What's happening?
Why do you look...
Klaus, talk to me!
[MIMOSA gasps]
Don't use such a
familiar tone with us.
You should know.
We aren't teammates or friends.
[PATRY]
Begone.
Begone. Begone.
Begone. Begone!
[PATRY chuckles]
[PATRY]
Begone, humans!
At last, the time
has come for revenge!
[YAMI] That flash of
light wasn't an attack,
but it was a giant
burst of magic power.
The kingdom is drenched in it.
[YAMI gasps]
[YAMI]
This ki. Is it...?
[MAGE 96A]
Where did that light come from?
[MAGE 96B]
You all right? What happened?
[MAGIC KNIGHT 96A] I'll call
the nearest Magic Knight Squad!
--[MAGES groan]
--[crashing]
[MAGE 96C]
What do you think you're doing?
So you finally made it here.
Once you do, you've got
the nerve to attack our guys.
I'm gonna need an
explanation for that.
It should be obvious
that we're not the ones
who once inhabited these forms.
[YAMI growls]
No, we are the elves.
A race that lived in
this world long ago
before we were slaughtered
by you humans.
[YAMI]
Is that right?
Precisely, except this
time it is humanity
that will be eliminated.
With no survivors.
The same as before.
This thing is really shapin' up
to be an inconvenience for me.
[YAMI] They did say somethin'
about bein' reborn
into their true
forms and gainin'
a whole buncha magic power.
But I thought they meant those
Eye of the Midnight Sun jerks
would be the ones comin' back.
It may be inconvenient, yes.
But I promise you, it
won't take long at all.
[YAMI] If he's able to
hit me with that spell,
my most recent memories'll
be wiped away!
And it looks like
he's boosted his range
and speed by a pretty
big margin, too.
Had enough?
[YAMI grunts]
[YAMI] Owen's Recovery
spell is different, too.
Way stronger and
twisted somehow.
Like he wants to break your
body instead of healing it.
[YAMI]
Get it together, Yami.
Just grab 'em both and end this!
I don't recognize
that corpse there.
Is it someone who
was important to you?
Not that it matters.
He was a human, so he
was a repulsive sinner
who deserved to die anyway.
Take that back.
If he's so precious
to you, feel free to pay
your respects while I
obliterate his remains,
piece by piece!
You're not Marx and Owen,
and I'm not gonna let
you spew that garbage
outta their mouths!
[MARX, OWEN gasp]
Go on, charge right in.
That's even easier.
Memory Magic:
Torment Canceller attack!
[YAMI]
Dark Magic: Black Hole!
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked,
Lightless Blade Storm!
[MARX]
What?
[BOTH gasp]
[OWEN]
How is he moving like that?
[YAMI] Dark Cloaked,
Lightless Blunt Slash!
[YAMI]
Now, Why don't you stay put?
I have to protect this country.
A promise I made to a man
both of you respected.
[YAMI]
Man, what a mess.
Those two aren't
even combat mages.
How did things get
this outta hand?
[crackling]
[YAMI]
What? Red roses?
[CHARLOTTE]
My comrades.
Letting down your guard
as soon as you awakened.
It'll serve our mission better
if you sleep within my spell.
At least, for now.
Hey, Prickly Princess.
Long time, no see, huh?
I've never known you
to cut people slack.
I don't know you at all.
You seem capable for a human.
[CITIZENS screaming]
[CITIZEN 96A]
What's that?
[CITIZEN 96B]
Powerful spells, everywhere!
The kingdom's being
attacked again already?
[CITIZENS yelp]
Get the hell outta here! Now!
If you don't escape,
I'll waste ya myself!
[YAMI] Let the buildings
crumble all over town.
As long as its people live,
a nation never dies.
But with so many of these
jokers runnin' around,
the people might not
hold out, either.
The smell of those
roses is coverin' up
her magic power. This
really isn't like her.
You know what? Heh.
I always was good
at hide-and-seek!
Dark Cloaked, Lightless Slash!
Your intuition is sharp!
That's not it.
It's 'cause of your ki.
It came through loud and clear!
[CHARLOTTE]
My "ki"?
[YAMI]
Gotta love ki!
[YAMI] She's got Charlotte's
ki and all her moves,
but the fighting
style's different.
Her signature midrange
attacks are there,
but now she's got a slew
of close-range spells,
and that smell is scramblin'
her magic power.
Not to mention her
air-tight defense.
With that workin' against me,
it won't be easy
to knock her out.
Her roses.
I heard they turned blue when
she was cursed as a little girl.
[CITIZEN 69G]
What the hell?!
[CITIZEN 69H]
It's the curse on House Roselei!
[CITIZEN 69J screams]
[ROYALS scream]
[CHARLOTTE]
Damn it!
[sword slashing]
[YAMI] You really made
a mess of things, huh?
Made me spill the pasta I was
eatin' all over the place.
[YAMI] I'm not a fan of chicks
who prance into battle
actin' all smug when they
have no reason to be.
I prefer women who are strong.
[gasps]
[YAMI]
But you can lean on someone else
every once in a while.
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
Know how you can find
lots of other strong
people to lean on?
By joinin' the Magic Knights.
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
[YAMI]
I'm a bit fuzzy on the details,
but I think the curse got
lifted back then, too.
If that's the case,
then you'd think the roses
would have changed color.
[YAMI]
Well. She is an elf inside.
Maybe the mark of
the curse went away
now that she's
not human anymore.
This must be Charlotte Roselei's
original Briar Magic!
The Charlotte I used
to know was a determined
woman who used her
curse to her advantage
and made herself stronger!
And now you let someone
take over your body
and magic for
their own purposes?
I'm disappointed in you!
[SOL]
Char, no!
This chick?
[panting] What's with you?
You attacked us.
I don't understand.
How could you?
Tell me.
You didn't mean to
hurt us, right, Char?
What's wrong?
Impudent, sniveling human.
Don't address me like a friend.
You mean nothing to me.
[gasps] But, Char.
Listen, she's bein' controlled
by some kinda magic.
It's not her.
So, what are we
supposed to do now?
You can just leave
your boss-lady to me.
What?
You showed up at
a good time, though.
[SOL]
Huh? What is that?
[YAMI]
I want you to take this orb
and go somewhere
safe, all right?
Hey! I refuse to take
orders from men, forget it!
[YAMI] Is this really
the time to be worried
about that kinda crap?
[SOL]
I said no!
[YAMI]
There's a hero inside there.
Show some respect for a--
What are you doing?
I won't let Char be
rescued by a man, either!
Hang on, you can't
just barrel in there!
[SOL] Yeah, well, it's either
that or abandon her!
Trust me, I can
snap her out of it!
Now, Earth Magic: Multi--
[gasps]
[SOL] Char's hyper-concentrated
magic field is keeping me
from casting my spells properly!
That's a tough fight,
even for a captain!
[SOL]
Does this mean...
...I'll be totally
helpless to stop her?
No! Not after all
she's done for me!
[SOL] Char was the person
who saved my life!
I'll make her wake up. Even if
I get killed in the process!
[YAMI grunts]
Forget that!
We're under orders to protect
the people and stay alive,
which means that's
what we're gonna do!
It's not that I don't understand
where you're comin' from.
Then let go--
Not until I'm finished!
You have to survive, dum-dum,
not just for her sake,
but for his, too!
Mark my words.
Nobody gets near
Char on my watch,
especially not some lowlife man!
Please save Char.
The Blue Rose Knights
need their captain.
I'm counting on you!
Then stand down. I got this.
[CHARLOTTE] You missed
your chance to run away.
I'm not plannin' to.
Dark Magic: Black Hole.
Your subordinate's cryin'!
[gasps]
You're just gonna let
them do what they want?
That's what a weakling
would do, and you're not weak!
I know you're not!
[CHARLOTTE] You're quite
strong. I respect you.
This magic power
is unbelievable.
Black Hole won't nearly be
enough to absorb it all.
One good blast from that
and half the town'll
be blown to smithereens.
takin' countless lives with it.
Hah. You have my respect.
You've had it all along.
That's why... Whatever it takes,
I'll save you.
[YAMI yells]
--[YAMI] Dark Magic:
--[CHARLOTTE] Briar Magic:
[CHARLOTTE]
Crimson Vine Spear!
[YAMI]
Dark Cloaked, Dimension Slash!
[yells]
[YAMI grunts, yells]
You guys, what's wrong?
It's just so beautiful.
[NOELLE] It's just like
with Vetto and the others.
It feels so evil.
Why's that kind of magic
power coming from you?
[giggles]
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[NOELLE] "Radiant Royal
Noelle and the Letter N"!
[NARRATOR]
Numb!
This is weird.
I can't feel my feet.
[NARRATOR]
Nutrition!
I'm boiling alive,
but at least I'm part
of a healthy diet!
[NARRATOR]
Needlework!
Look at that, my tapestry's
almost finished!
[yelps]
--Not bad!
--[NARRATOR] Nails!
My hands are still pretty sore
from all that
needlework, though.
[NARRATOR]
Noelle!
They love me!
Well, I am royalty.
[ASTA]
Whoa!
All of a sudden,
those Midnight Sun jerks
started shinin' really bright,
and now they're crazy-powerful!
Wait. Rill?
What are you attacking us for?
Black Clover , Page 97:
"Overwhelming Disadvantage."
I hope the captain
knows what to do!