[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] Asta and the
rest of the Royal Knights
were busy infiltrating
the Eye of the Midnight
Sun's hideout.
While Licht, who had just
revealed his true identity,
was in the royal capital,
engaged in a vicious battle
with Julius over possession
of the magic stones.
[LICHT]
But how? What is this strength?
He's only human.
He shouldn't be able to--
[NARRATOR]
Using his coverless grimoire
and Time Magic abilities,
Julius managed to
secure the upper hand.
And as the Wizard King,
I'll protect the people
of Clover. Come what may.
[NARRATOR]
However,
Licht released himself
from his Sealing spell
to launch a deadly attack
on every person in
the Clover Kingdom.
[YAMI] That's a big
hunk o' Light Magic.
Dammit!
Now. Here is your
punishment, humans!
Light Magic: Arrows of Judgment!
[JULIUS] Time Reversal Magic:
Chrono Anastasis!
[NARRATOR] Julius used
all the time and power
he'd been saving up to protect
the helpless civilians,
but that was exactly what
Licht wanted him to do.
[LICHT] You would've seen
this attack of mine coming.
But, unfortunately, you
weren't able to call off
that final Time Magic spell
in order to get out of the way.
Because you're the Wizard King.
[YAMI gasps]
[YAMI] What happened here?
Tell me, Vangeance!
Salutations. Yami, is it?
You may call me Licht.
You're Licht?
William is lying dormant
within this body.
[LICHT]
That's right.
You and I both watched it
through these eyes, William.
The end of the Wizard King.
[YAMI]
What? If that's the case,
then you better
say your prayers!
This can't be happening.
There's no way this is real.
Not Julius. Please, no.
Don't just stand there, Marx!
[MARX gasps]
He's injured!
Go get that quack Owen
to come and heal him!
Hurry up!
Right!
Hang tight, Julius! We--
[LICHT]
Don't bother.
He'll be gone in
mere moments now.
You protected your kingdom
to the very end.
I must commend you for that,
Julius Novachrono.
[grunts]
[LICHT]
But...
Master Licht, sir!
[YAMI]
Dark Magic...
Now, Dark Cloaked.
Elves and humankind will
never live in harmony again.
It's over.
[YAMI]
Dimension Slash!
[YAMI growls]
[YAMI]
He's gone.
[YAMI] Hold on, all right?
Don't die on me!
Ya... mi. That spell
you did was amazing.
You can cut through
space itself.
C'mon, this is no
time for that stuff!
You've turned into a superb
Magic Knight, haven't you?
Julius.
Like I keep tellin' ya,
I'm 28 years old!
I'm not some kid anymore.
[JULIUS] It's so inspiring
seeing that your generation
was raised right.
And knowing the next one
is beginning to bud as well.
My own hopes, living on through
all of the Magic
Knights to come...
[MEREOLEONA] Mana Zone:
Calidos Brachium Barrage!
[MEREOLEONA yells]
[MEREOLEONA]
What's wrong, Mr. Third Eye?
Running out of spells?
[RHYA grunts]
Yeah, he's finished.
[RHYA] No time to use Fast
Movement or Recovery Magic.
Try another attack! I dare you!
[ASTA] We struggled so hard
to beat the Third Eye,
and now look!
Captain Mereoleona,
you're so strong!
If that's really your best,
I'll punch you until
you're a pile of ashes!
[RHYA]
Well, I guess that's it for me.
[MEREOLEONA]
Now, burn!
[RHYA] I'll give you
one thing, Miss Royal.
You sure know how
to pack a fiery punch.
Which is why...
[gasps]
Before I burn up,
I'm castin' a
self-destruct spell
and takin' you down with me!
[yells]
[RHYA] Once you hit me,
we'll disappear with a bang!
[ASTA yells]
[ZORA gasps]
[growls]
[RHYA grunting]
[RHYA]
That Anti-magic brat.
He sniffed out my
self-destruct spell
and countered it before
she landed her attack!
He acted so fast--
it's incredible!
Two other people have
already tried that,
and I'm fed up with it!
You can't kill
yourself on my watch,
you three-eyed jerk! Got it?
Don't throw your life away!
[yelling] Seriously, what's
the matter with you guys?!
You're mad at humans
for takin' somethin' away
from you, right?!
I'm still fuzzy on the details!
But we're all people!
I want you to tell me
your side of the story,
and then I'm gonna
tell you mine!
And nobody's dyin' until
that happens, okay?
Uh...
Good grief.
That pipsqueak really
runs hot, doesn't he?
I don't recall
giving you permission
to butt into my fight, boy.
Should I burn you as well?
Ah--
He's part of the
Eye of the Midnight Sun.
They've plunged the
kingdom into confusion
and taken a massive
toll on its people.
They are not interested
in swapping stories.
Now, move.
[ASTA yelps]
Even if it means
killing them all,
we must stop them.
Yeah? Why is that?
Huh?
We're the same. Aren't we?
So we should be able
to talk things over.
Both sides are mad because
we lost someone we loved.
[gasps]
I've been thinkin'
a lot about this.
Everyone's fighting because
we can't forgive the other side.
So how do we get rid of
all that anger and hatred?
I know I'm not very smart,
so I can't come up
with the right answer.
But we can do it.
I mean, we have to, don't we?
[JULIUS] My goal, the future
that I worked so hard to build,
I believe it isn't that far off.
[ASTA] Whether you're
nobility, a citizen,
or just a commoner,
or even if you're not a human.
[JULIUS] It's a future that
all of you will create.
A nation that's free
of hatred and prejudice.
I just want a kingdom
where all of us
get along and laugh together.
And when I'm the Wizard
King, we'll have one.
You'll see!
Heh.
[MEREOLEONA]
You imbecile.
Proudly proclaiming
something so outrageous.
[gasps]
[RHYA]
I think he's actually serious!
In fact, it reminds me of what
someone else said once before.
This little one here
is the key to our future.
the bridge that will unite
the elves and humankind!
[RHYA] Congratulations,
Licht and Tetia!
[VETTO, FANA, PATRY, RILL]
Congratulations!
[RHYA] If only the rest of the
human race thought about it
the way these guys
do, then maybe...
No. It's too late to stop now.
Hey, welcome back!
[RADES]
Took ya long enough!
You snagged the last of
the magic stones, right?
Watch your tongue, Rades.
Everything went as we planned.
In fact, even better!
Our Master Licht has
assassinated the Wizard King!
Seriously? That's awesome!
Wow, Master Licht. Great going!
[LICHT]
The time has come.
There's not a soul who can
stand in our way anymore.
[YAMI]
Come on! Just a little longer.
When Owen gets here,
he's gonna fix ya right up!
Their leader was so powerful.
He could have easily killed
everyone in the land,
even without collecting
all of the magic stones.
That means he must be
after something else.
I fear that Clover Kingdom may
yet suffer a devastating fate.
I let him steal the stones.
I'm sorry. Such a failure
is below the Wizard King.
Forget that! You just
saved thousands of lives!
[MARX] I hope we make
it to him in time.
[JULIUS] Marx is going
to be so disappointed in me
for the way things ended.
It's a shame that
I won't be there
when Fuegoleon finally wakes up.
Yami, there are still
so many things...
Things I wanted to tell you.
Don't go talkin' like that!
You can't check out on me now!
That's somethin'
I can't forgive!
'Cause I still haven't...
[VILLAGER 39A]
Look at that freak.
He's not from here, you know.
[VILLAGER 39AA] He washed up
from some other country.
Lives alone on the coast.
[VILLAGER 39C] I wish he'd just
go back where he belongs.
[JULIUS]
Wow! Was that Dark Magic?
What the...?
[JULIUS giggles] Awesome!
I've never seen it before!
Please! You've gotta let
me get a closer look.
Yeah, no. Who are you, mister?
I, uh, well...
I'm no one to be suspicious
of, I assure you,
I'm just a Magic Knight captain
out walking in disguise.
What's a Magic Knight captain?
Huh? You don't know that?
Okay...
Why don't you come with
me and I'll show you?
I think you have real potential!
See this, Yami? It's how
you write your name here.
Oh, great. I'm never
gonna remember
a buncha squiggly
lines like that.
Well, if you practice,
you'll pick it up in no time!
I don't wanna.
Aw. But if you learn to write,
I'll buy dinner for you!
I'm on it.
[JULIUS chuckles]
You haven't been on the
squad for very long,
but I'm already astonished by
everything you've accomplished.
That said, I'd rather
you didn't run too wild.
We've had some, well--
Uh-oh, look! It's the enemy.
Then let's go. But
reel it in a little--
[YAMI yells]
Well. We'll work on that later.
[JULIUS]
And, Yami, from this moment on,
you will be
recognized as founder
and leader of the Black Bulls.
Best of luck, Captain.
Yami.
I'm leaving the rest to you now.
Yes, sir.
I got to meet so many people
and see so many spells.
[JULIUS]
It was a fun life. A good life.
Julius.
Don't you worry, friend.
We'll keep the kingdom
safe for you.
[COB] I can't help but
wonder how everyone's doing.
I've been casting my Spatial
Jamming spell for several hours.
It's getting rather difficult
to hold my arms up.
But this is no time
for complaining!
The Royal Knights
are in there battling
the Eye of the Midnight Sun
with everything they've got!
The future of the Clover Kingdom
hangs in the balance!
Please, team, do your very best!
Hey! Look up there!
[gasps] What's that?
It's an abundance of mana!
[MIMOSA] We're headed
straight for the center.
You guys, be careful!
I don't care who crosses us.
I'm not in the mood to lose.
Neither am I! Let's go
knock 'em dead, Yuno!
[heartbeats]
[gasps] This place
is so bizarre!
Yes. Is that a person?
The mana... It's so...
Yes. It's unbelievably powerful.
All it needs now is the
last of the magic stones.
We'll awaken our true might
with the Monument of the Tree
of Life to guide our every step.
[VALTOS]
Yes.
The fateful day that we've
waited for has arrived.
Yeah, since we
were lucky enough
to be chosen by the mana,
our magic powers are about
to go through the roof!
Heh. This is gonna be fun.
Those Magic Knights'll
be dead before
they even figure out
what hit 'em.
With our new power plus
my dark magic items,
we'll be unbeatable!
Oh, I can hardly wait!
Soon, I'll get my hands on Asta
and experiment to
my heart's content!
[giggling]
Enough. This newfound advantage
is to be used solely
to establish the society
Master Licht has envisioned.
You know, Master.
If we'd never become
acquainted with you,
we'd still be eking out the
same lonely, pathetic existence.
Despised by everyone.
[VALTOS]
But you...
You gladly welcomed us into
the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
changing our lives.
Master Licht.
I've been happy to serve, even
if we were but a small help.
Are you done yet?
Because I can only listen
to so much kissin' up
before I puke.
Anyway, it's lookin' like
we'll be able to wreak
even more havoc,
so you know I'm in!
[SALLY] And my research'll
be extra helpful
after we get this boost!
[chuckles]
[LICHT]
Yes, you three have done well
during our time together.
Thank you for that.
And please know that
I'm exceedingly proud
of your efforts.
At last, the time has come
to fulfill our highest goal:
the rebirth of our true forms
to create our new kingdom.
Yes, sir!
[SALLY laughs]
Since I met you all,
I have been speaking as Licht,
your humble leader.
[ALL gasp]
From now on,
I will express my
true feelings instead.
You have acted out of
greed and selfishness.
Casually harming others
while prioritizing
your own interest
above everything else.
You hate, envy,
and discriminate against
your fellow human beings for
the most fleeting of reasons.
And then, you justify
your sins and shortcomings
with your blind devotion to me.
All for the sake of your lousy,
filthy, disgusting selves!
Humans really are the
self-serving, shameful worms
I always knew you were!
You're absolutely irredeemable!
[VALTOS grunts]
Master...
[RADES]
I don't understand.
[SALLY gasps]
[LICHT] This is where we must
bid each other farewell.
The great rebirth
will start with you.
[ALL gasping]
[LICHT cackles]
[mumbling] Hey, look.
What's that glow?
That bright light...
It's from the Forsaken Realm!
Oh, no!
[heartbeats]
[BOTH grunt]
What's going on here?
Well, Look at that.
It's finally begun.
What are you talking about?
His power just shot
through the roof!
Hey. Somethin's not right.
This is it.
Today, we're going to
assume our true forms
and reclaim our old strength.
[gasps] What's happening?
Whatever power he's wielding,
it's not human mana!
Listen! Let's get out--
[gasps]
Yuno? What's wrong?
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[JULIUS]
"Lessons."
Yami, can you tell me
what this one says?
How should I know?
This one, then.
Nope, not a clue.
Okay.
I told ya, I'm never gonna
be able to learn all this stuff!
You have no idea how
crappy my memory is.
Be strong.
It isn't good to set
limits for yourself.
[gasps]
Even if it seems
hopeless to you now,
if you believe in yourself,
then you can push
beyond any obstacle.
I want to unite this
kingdom, whatever it takes.
So that everyone
can laugh together,
regardless of their magic,
status, or background.
It may sound like a lofty dream,
but I have no doubt
it can be done.
Push beyond my limits...
Okay then, how do
you write like that?
Ah. Now you're motivated!
Let's try the last
question. What's this?
[YAMI]
Left.
We're not testing your eyesight.
[LICHT] Too long have my
people and I been forced
to trod under the burden
of sadness and solitude.
But now, that, too,
has reached its end.
Black Clover , Page 95:
"Reincarnation."
I shall destroy humankind!