[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] In this world,
magic is everything.
[NARRATOR] Asta and Yuno
were abandoned together
as infants at a church in
the remote village of Hage.
Determined not to be held back
by their status as commoners,
both do their utmost to
realize their shared dream
of becoming the ultimate mage:
the Wizard King.
[NARRATOR]
In their 15th year,
the two boys receive
their grimoires:
special books that will
enhance their magic.
They then set off to take
the Magic Knights Entrance Exam
in hopes of joining one of
the Wizard King's famed squads.
[ASTA, YUNO] We'll fight to see
who will be the Wizard King.
Whatever it takes.
[NARRATOR] After an exceptional
performance on the exam,
magically-gifted Yuno has
his pick of the nine squads
and elects to join
the elite Golden Dawn.
Meanwhile, magicless
Asta is inducted
into the Black Bulls, widely
regarded as a squad of misfits.
[ASTA]
I won't give up!
I will become the Wizard King!
[NARRATOR]
And so, the two young men
have taken the first step
toward achieving their dream
of becoming the Wizard King.
[rumbling]
Shaking?
What's going on?
Is this an earthquake?
Whoa, what the--?
[FARMER 14A]
What the hell is that?!
Sorry to interrupt,
but there's urgent news, sir.
[JULIUS] We have a
situation on our hands.
Yes?
Calm down, Marx.
The timing couldn't
be more perfect.
I know just who to
give this mission to.
[MARX]
Who, sir?
[JULIUS chuckles]
--Aw, c'mon, Magna.
--[ASTA] ...982...
--Spar with me. No holding back.
[ASTA]
...983...
[MAGNA]
No way, battle freak.
Please? You know you wanna.
Let's go! I'll eat your
flan again if I have to.
You better keep your
grubby little hands
away from my food!
Okay! So, you'll fight?
Not happening.
--[LUCK] Aw, you big tease!
--...988...
[NOELLE]
How about Sylvantus Schnauzer?
Yeah, maybe a different
name would be better.
Something like... "Wine"!
That's it. This fits
him perfectly.
--Right, Wine?
--[ASTA] ...993...
[ASTA]
...994...
[GAUCHE] This is my
angelic sister, Marie.
You may use one
syllable of her name.
Thus, I dub you, "Ma."
The birdie's tough.
He needs a cooler
name than that.
Lemme think for a sec.
Huh.
Call him Magnum Fire!
[NOELLE]
That's lame.
[MAGNA] Seriously, you've
got the worst taste ever.
[NOELLE]
No, that would be you.
[exhales]
[mumbling] We're
naming the bird?
What a fun group
bonding activity.
I've got an idea if
anyone wants to hear it.
I think it's really good.
[CHARMY]
Mind if I fatten the bird up?
I've got a craving for
drumsticks, and it looks tasty.
[NOELLE gasps]
Not a chance.
You think it'll lay eggs?
Huh?
This guy's Birdyboy.
No. His name is
Sylvantus Schnauzer!
No, it's Birdyboy!
He likes Sylvantus
Schnauzer better!
[ASTA]
Birdyboy!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Hey, what's that for, Birdyboy?
See, I was right.
You prefer Sylvantus
Schnauzer, don't you?
Huh? Huh?
He likes Magnum Fire!
Ma!
No, Wine!
Huh...
How about we name him Nero?
[MAGNA]
That's dumb.
There, I think he likes it.
It means "black." Cool, huh?
[BOTH]
"Nero"?
Uh... What the...?
Okay, listen up, guys.
[MAGNA]
Yes, Yami, sir!
[ASTA, MANGNA grunt]
[FINRAL]
Hi, gang! How's it going?
Hey, welcome back.
What did they want you to
schlep over to the castle for?
[GREY exhales]
[mumbling] Is it a mission?
I really hope it's a mission.
Then we can all go together.
Well, sir? Is it a mission?
Kinda.
Pay attention, everyone,
here's what's goin' on.
I was called in because they've
discovered a new dungeon.
[ALL gasp]
A new dungeon? Seriously?
You mean it, Yami, sir?
Wow! That's awesome!
What's a dungeon?
[ALL but ASTA]
Huh?
[MAGNA]
Dude, are you kidding me?
What're you acting shocked for
when you don't even
know what it is?
[ASTA]
Everyone else was.
[MAGNA]
Typical Rasta! Listen up.
Dungeons one-oh-one.
Dungeons are like
tombs where people
from way back stored their
most valuable stuff.
Sometimes they've got powerful
ancient magic techniques
or sweet magic items inside.
What I'm sayin' is,
dungeons totally rock!
Whoa!
One thing, though.
They kinda try to kill you.
The folks who built 'em added
all sorts of crazy trap spells
to keep people from getting
to their stuff and misusing it.
So, they're seriously dangerous
and seriously fun, too.
[whimpers]
Exploring a dungeon's kinda like
going on a treasure hunt where
you could die at any second.
You can see why it's
the sort of thing
they only leave
to Magic Knights.
Yeah! Sure!
So, a new dungeon showed up.
And then Captain Yami
was called to the castle.
I'm guessing that means
the Black Bulls are being
sent to explore it.
That's right, and it's
in a dicey location.
Popped up near our border
with an enemy country.
[ASTA]
An enemy?
Yeah, the Diamond Kingdom.
[BOTH gasp]
[YAMI] This mission
has to be carried out
swiftly and thoroughly.
We wanna keep those
Diamond guys' paws
off the good stuff.
Who knows what could happen?
In the past, people have
found items in dungeons
that could change
civilization itself.
Some explorers have
even come out of them
able to use the
most powerful magic.
Ooh! Ooh! Send me!
Please send me,
Captain Yami, sir!
Maybe I'll be able to learn
how to use the
most powerful magic!
Yeah? How ya gonna do
that without any magic?
It could work!
I won't know until I try.
Magic power or not, you are
goin' on this mission, kid.
Wasn't my call this time,
so don't look at me.
The Wizard King asked for you.
Wha--
What?! The Wizard King?
There's no way!
Hey, that's awesome,
Asta. Good for you.
So, what's the deal?
You got an in with the
Wizard King or somethin'?
No, not at all!
The Wizard King
actually chose me!
I don't know why, but...
Oh, wow! Wizard King, sir!
I've got this. Count on me.
I will devote myself to
this mission, body and soul!
Well, that's one.
Noelle, you should go, too.
[NOELLE]
Uh--
It's all about gettin'
experience, isn't it?
And last but not least is Luck.
I want you to take
the lead on this one.
The newbies are all yours.
--[MAGNA] Uh--
--[LUCK] Really? Me?
Sure. You're gonna
lose your edge
if you're always here
holdin' down the fort.
Thank you, sir!
And listen, Luck.
The rookies are
your responsibility,
so look after 'em.
Yeah, don't worry.
[mumbling] I want to go, too.
It makes me sad
to be left behind.
[GREY exhales]
Be careful out there.
Do your best, you two.
Go give 'em hell.
Yes, sir!
I suppose we can do that.
I wonder how many
ladies I can pick up
while you three are
exploring the dungeon.
--[ASTA] Hm?
--[NOELLE] Huh?
[GAUCHE] Since I'm not needed,
may I visit my sister?
If you're lookin' to get
killed, then go right ahead.
[FINRAL, GAUCHE]
Uh...
We're here.
The sunset looks
lovely from this hill.
I highly recommend this spot
for date nights, by the way.
I'll have some
nummies ready for you
when you get back.
[YAMI]
Okay, get it done, you three.
[ASTA]
Thanks!
[LUCK]
Bye!
Well, let's go. This way!
[NOELLE]
Couldn't he have just taken us
right to the entrance
of the dungeon?
[LUCK laughs]
Nope, sorry.
Finral can only send people
places he's already been.
Whoa! It looks like he
dropped us off pretty close.
[ASTA, NOELLE gasp]
[ASTA, NOELLE gulp]
Right, let's do this.
[ASTA] Who asked you
to tag along, anyway?
[VANESSA yawns]
I still don't understand
how the Wizard King
even knows about Asta.
And you probably never will.
[YAMI] Fact is, the Wizard King
sees things we don't.
Also, he's weird.
[laughs]
It's so dark in here.
Could ya maybe stop
clinging like that?
I can barely walk over here.
Excuse me? I do not cling!
[ASTA]
Whoa!
[NOELLE shrieks]
[ASTA]
I can't see anything!
[LUCK laughs]
Ow, ow, ow!
Thank you. I love
having my foot stomped.
What do you want from me?
It's pitch black here.
Calm down, would ya?
Well, maybe I would be calmer
if you hadn't broken
our only lantern!
You klutz!
[ASTA] I only broke it 'cause
you tripped and ran into me!
[NOELLE]
I am royalty. Royals don't trip.
[ASTA]
Clearly, they do.
[NOELLE]
Insect.
Is this it? Let's see.
Whoa, that's bright!
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Whoa! This is, like, the
most awesome place ever!
It's all sparkly. So cool!
What's going on in here?
It looks like the
space has been warped
because of all the magic.
There's way more than
I detected outside.
The air is crazy thick.
[NOELLE]
Yes.
I don't think I've ever been
somewhere so steeped in mana.
[ASTA]
How can you tell?
Wait, you're standing in a room
full of this much mana,
and you can't feel it?
Nope, nothing.
Well, I suppose that
does make sense.
Amazing how different
people without magic are.
You don't have to rub it in!
It's not fair!
I wanna be able
to feel mana, too.
No! I want my own mana.
Do you know how lucky
you royals are?
You all seem to have
boatloads of it.
The source of all magic power,
and I don't have a single drop!
I'm empty! Just a hollow shell!
[sobs] Why? Why me? Huh?
What's that?
[ASTA screams]
Whoa! Is that trap magic?
[ASTA yels]
Whew.
Uh... Try to be more careful.
You almost got us all killed.
Heh. My bad. Sorry.
[LUCK]
Huh?
Hey, take a look at this,
Asta. Right there.
I don't see anything.
[LUCK]
Closer.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
[yelps]
What'd you do that for?
That was so much fun to watch!
What are you playing at?
Oh! Another one.
[LUCK chuckles]
[NOELLE screams]
[ASTA yells]
[LUCK]
Heads up!
[yelps]
[ASTA yells]
[LUCK]
Comin' in!
[screams]
[ASTA grunts]
Wow, you guys should see
the looks on your faces!
That was fun, huh?
I could play in
this place all day!
[BOTH panting]
[ASTA, NOELLE] This guy is
totally going to get us killed.
Dungeons are no joke.
I wonder how those
two are doing.
They know they're
out on a mission
that's both important
and dangerous.
It'll give 'em a chance to
push their limits and grow.
Probably.
"Probably"?
Aw, don't worry about it.
They're gonna be fine.
Luck's with 'em.
Ain't no one out there
who can sense mana
better than him, and that
includes the royals.
All the squads would've
been after him,
if not for that defective
personality of his.
[laughs]
[MAGNA]
It's his busted personality
that's got me worried.
[VANESSA]
I'll drink to that.
Oh, man.
Your anti-magic sword is
seriously something else, Asta.
Maybe that's why the Wizard King
specifically asked for you.
I'm lookin' forward
to taking you on
in a couple years.
All you have to do is make
sure that sword of yours
is at the ready, and we
should have it made.
This dungeon'll be
a piece of cake.
Right!
Now, let's see what we've got.
[LUCK]
I'm just about at my limit.
[LUCK] I knew it.
We're not alone in here.
And the strongest
of them all is...
[LUCK]
Lightning Creation Magic...
...Holy Lightning Boots!
Sorry guys, but something
important's come up.
I gotta get going.
[BOTH]
Huh?
You two just go ahead and
get through the dungeon
on your own, and I'll
see ya soon, okay?
[NOELLE]
Hey! Where are you--?
[NOELLE yelps]
Really?
What in the world is
that lunatic thinking?
That was beyond cool!
This can't be happening to me!
I'll hook a left up there.
Man, I can't wait to see
how tough these guys are.
I sure hope they can
give me a good fight.
[LUCK laughs]
[NOELLE]
You have got to be kidding.
This is just ridiculous.
Captain Yami tells him
to look after the newbies,
and then he leaves us
the first chance he gets?
What a jerk.
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
Whatever traps are
in this place,
my sword'll slice
right through them,
no big deal. Easy.
It must be nice being
a simpleminded optimist.
Taking on a dungeon
like this is nothing.
And do you know why?
'Cause I am gonna become
the Wizard King!
Here we go again.
That's right, Yuno.
That job is gonna go to me.
"Yuno"?
Oh, yeah. Haven't I
mentioned him before?
He's an old friend.
We grew up together
in Hage Village.
We both took the Magic Knights
Entrance Exam this year.
The Black Bulls got me,
and the Golden Dawn got Yuno.
That's pretty amazing.
They took a commoner?
That's rare, or,
maybe unheard of.
[ASTA]
Yeah.
Yuno's pretty
amazing, all right.
But he isn't gonna
beat me. Not a chance.
Huh.
[NOELLE]
I suppose even little insects
have their own aspirations.
Come on. Let's go.
[ASTA] Looks like we
can cross over there.
Ready?
[NOELLE] We're alone now.
It's just the two of us.
Sylvantus--wait, no--
Nero is here, but...
What's up? Something wrong?
Uh! No, of course not! Insect!
Well? Hurry!
[gasps]
Oh, no! It's a trap!
Noelle!
There's... such immense power.
[ASTA]
Quick, Noelle, get away!
[gasps]
Asta!
Not again!
Not good.
[ASTA]
Oh, crap!
[BOTH gasp]
[ASTA grunts]
Where'd that come from?
Such powerful magic.
And precision, too.
But, whose spell was that?
Oh, yeah. Forgot to mention.
Captain?
Luck and the rookies won't
be alone in the dungeon.
Some Golden Dawn Knights
were sent to explore it, too.
What?
The Golden Dawn's
gonna be there?
They sure will.
Think the kids can
play nice together?
[YUNO]
And with that...
...my debt is paid.
Asta.
Hey, Yuno!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[FINRAL]
"What is Mana?"
All right, Asta, let's hear it.
Can you tell me
something about mana?
Yes!
One thing I know is
this is how you write it.
See, there it is: mana.
Write it like this,
and it's "man alive."
--[MAGNA groans]
--That's right.
And mana is supernatural energy.
It's a vital force in this
world that all mages call upon.
Yeah, and everyone has it,
whether they're a
noble or a commoner.
Everyone but me!
[FINRAL]
As I was saying,
mages call upon mana
to cast spells.
If you don't have enough
mana, you're out of luck.
You can't use magic
until it's restored.
You getting all this?
Yeah, I got it.
[FINRAL]
Oh! What a lovely flower!
I think this would make
an excellent present
for some lucky lady.
I'll save you!
[FINRAL muffled]
My! How feisty.
We can pick up the lesson later.
[LUCK] Wow, you guys have
some major magic power.
C'mon, let's fight!
I'm putting everything
on the line.
Black Clover , Page 15:
"The Diamond Mage."
My magic is never giving up!