[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] The elves reborn
as Golden Dawn mages
descended upon the castle.
Meanwhile, the Eye of
the Midnight Sun's base
arrived at the capital,
carrying Licht and Rhya.
[YAMI] Who the hell thought
it'd be a good idea
to invite the giant floating
boulder to the party?
But, look, a pretty little
birdie just showed up, too.
[NARRATOR]
Nozel and Noelle met up
with Yami's group
for a brief moment,
then all the knights went
their separate ways
in order to protect the people
of the Clover Kingdom.
However, when the
Silvas returned
to their childhood residence,
they were forced to contend
with the enemy's devastating
Compass Magic.
Just when all seemed lost,
Noelle combined everything
she'd learned from her training
and experience as a
member of the Black Bulls
with her resolute desire
to rescue her siblings
and gained an awe-inspiring
new power.
[NOELLE] I'll crush you
and this world you've made!
[ALECDORA] Blow it away,
and it comes right back.
Human magic.
It's so impertinent.
They've invaded the third level
and the inner courtyard, too.
So the safest, and therefore
loveliest, route is...
...that way.
Everyone, please hurry outside!
We're so lucky you
arrived in time.
Yes, you saved us!
Well, this is the esteemed
Vermillion residence, after all.
Which means the terrain is
completely in our favor!
And look!
My beautiful Cherry Blossom
Magic confuses the enemy
while concealing our
allies' whereabouts!
Plus, the Fungus Magic secreted
by those shriveled spores
helps to muddle any
attempts to locate us.
And of course, my sister
Mimosa's using her Plant Magic
to survey the surroundings
and guide our path.
All of our enchanting techniques
are perfectly suited
to evacuation!
And with no violence necessary!
How gorgeous!
Would you please stop talking
before you blow our cover,
you loudmouthed buffoon?
[MIMOSA]
They're only our enemies because
they're possessed
by elf spirits.
Deep down, they're
still our squadmates.
I swear, we'll do
everything possible
to bring them back to normal!
Hey there. Workin' hard, huh?
[MIMOSA gasps]
[MIMOSA]
David!
Nope. Sorry, my name's Baval.
[KIRSCH] I didn't notice
his presence at all!
[EN] If he found us, that must
mean our spells aren't working.
Relax. Why do you guys
look so angry?
Sorry for bargin' in,
but all I wanted to do
was track you guys down
and say a quick hello.
If I was trying to kill you,
then you would already be dead.
So there's no reason
to get all defensive.
[MIMOSA] I don't think
that's all he wants.
Tell us what you're
really after, elf!
Oh, not much,
but I can catch you
up on the details.
If you haven't figured it out,
my friends and I have
been reincarnated
with much stronger
magic than you possess.
And now we've come here
to pay the royals a visit.
You can sense it too, right?
You know, the fact that
something even more powerful
is heading over
here as we speak.
Not much point
evacuating the castle.
Either way, you're
all going to die.
So you might as well
surrender at this point.
I'm pretty formidable, but the
rest of us are tough as well.
Man, this takes me back.
I can't wait to see everybody.
I won't let you hurt
anyone else!
We'll defeat you,
no matter what!
I do admire your determination,
but it's too late now.
Once we take care of your king,
this invasion's as
good as over with.
We sent one of our
most qualified people
to deal with him, too.
Believe me, the guy's as
stubborn as he is twisted.
King Clover's
trapped like a rat.
Oh, and...
...our guy has something
particularly nasty
up his sleeve.
Perfect magic for
killing a king.
[gasping]
[groaning]
[LEDIOR] I don't have what it
takes to stop that spell.
How's he this powerful?
Ingrate!
How dare you come in here
and disgrace this sacred hall!
[gasps] Langris, dear!
What's wrong?!
Heh. This is the current king?
He looks so seedy.
What?!
I will not abide such disrespect
in my royal presence!
You should be ashamed to have
this traitorous rebel for a son!
Please, sir!
This has to be a
misunderstanding!
Yes, something's wrong!
Our precious son Langris would
never betray the Clover Kingdom!
[KING CLOVER]
Silence!
With all of our
defenses outside,
how could that scoundrel have
weaseled his way in here?
I swear, Julius and
the other Magic Knights
are positively useless!
You have left me no choice!
Now I'll show you my magic!
[KING CLOVER laughing]
Here! Behold the magnificent
talent of a king!
I see you're too busy
trembling to escape!
My Light Magic!
Absolute Monarch
of Divine Brilliance!
What say you?! Positively
godlike, is it not?!
Bow down and grovel
before my royal visage!
[KING CLOVER]
What?! What did you do?!
How sad. That spell was
ridiculously sluggish.
I won't kill you just yet.
Let's start with your legs.
[whimpers]
No, wait! Langris!
[FINNES gasps]
You can't do this,
you know it's not right!
[coughing]
If you go through with it,
you and a lot of other
people will be hurt.
People who care
about you very much.
So, please...
Shut your mouth.
[LANGRIS]
Your kind killed the elves,
and you have the nerve
to talk about being hurt?
[FINRAL panting]
Langris, no!
[FINRAL grunts]
Please tell me he didn't
injure you, Miss Finnes.
No, I'm fine.
Finral's here.
I'm sorry, who are you?
Your brother! Wake up!
[YAMI] Stop tryin' to
act like a hero, Finral.
[FINRAL chuckles]
I wasn't, though! Really.
How'd they manage to
get past our forces?
[YAMI]
Oh, those other glowin' guys?
Yeah, we took care
of 'em already.
But it woulda gone a
lot faster if Skinny here
had been on the ball.
'Scuse me?
You were the one goofing
around the whole time.
Friggin' meathead.
[JACK cackles]
You shouldn't have
split up your forces, elf-boy.
Because you don't stand a
chance against us on your own.
[LANGRIS]
Heh. I'm not worried.
Care to explain how
you overpowered
that many by yourselves?
Why don't we show ya?
[YAMI]
You can't counter this.
[JACK]
It's too late!
Heh.
[YAMI gasps]
[JACK grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
I'm sorry. I should've
warned you before.
This spell I'm using
retaliates automatically.
Give me a challenge, would you?
I'm bored.
[BOTH]
We can do that.
[LEDIOR]
His abilities are unbelievable!
There's no Spatial mage
in the whole kingdom
who can cancel out
a spell like that.
It's an extremely
protective shield,
and he can keep it
going constantly.
[FINRAL]
Father.
Miss Finnes.
You should run away and
let us deal with this.
[BOTH gasp]
You fool!
You're merely a transport
for the Black Bulls,
you can't defeat him!
I may not be able
to do any damage,
and he may be the vice captain
of the Golden Dawn,
but all that matters
to me right now
is that Langris and
I are brothers!
[gasps]
He's lost his mind.
Don't you go underestimatin'
my wheels, mister.
Uh, what--? But I--
Look, pal, you're in the way.
I'll throw you in there myself.
[LEDIOR screams]
Oh, Langris.
My precious Langris!
[YAMI] All right, you're
goin' in there with him.
[LILIANE]
Langris!
[coughs] I'm worried, Finral.
Promise me you'll
come back alive.
[FINRAL] Sure, and I'll
bring Langris with me.
[sighs]
[KING CLOVER] Wait!
I should be first priority!
[FINRAL]
Huh? Oh...
Honestly, you're
such a useless lot.
[yelps]
What's the hurry?
You should stick around.
I was just getting ready
to mutilate His Majesty.
I won't let you.
[cackles]
This kid talks a big game.
I'll cut him down to size.
[JACK]
Severing Magic: Death Scythe.
Lunatic Slash.
[gasps]
[KING CLOVER screams]
You moronic mantis!
[FINRAL]
That's one way to save someone.
He's the king, you know!
[cackles] You interfered
with my slashes.
Not too shabby, pal.
[FINRAL] Never mind,
he's already moved on.
[LANGRIS]
Heh. Still think you can
hold a candle to my strength?
It's time for you filth
to learn your place!
[JACK growls]
[YAMI]
He can use his attack spells
without turning off
that defensive shield?
Not gonna fight fair, are ya?
If this spell hits you even
one time, you'll be dead.
[LANGRIS]
Spatial Magic...
[FINRAL]
[LANGRIS]
Archangel's Crash!
Fallen Angel's Wingbeat!
[FINRAL grunts]
[FINRAL] The difference
in our power's too great!
I can only block about
half of these things!
Avoid them however you can!
Hey, who said you could
start barkin' orders?
[YAMI]
Dark Magic: Black Hole!
[JACK cackling]
[JACK] Reinforcement Magic:
Leg Strength Boost!
[YAMI] Dark Magic:
Dark Cloaked Lightless Slash!
Yami!
Thanks for that.
[FINRAL grunts]
Huh?
[YAMI] If we want to land
even a scratch on this guy,
we're gonna have to do
somethin' about that barrier.
[YAMI] But he's constantly
throwin' his orbs at us,
and Finral's magic can only
cancel out so many of 'em.
A long battle puts us
at a disadvantage,
so we need to end this
thing nice and quick.
[YAMI grunts]
[YAMI]
Which means...
[growls]
[YAMI]
It'll take more than one of us
attackin' him at the same time.
I can cover this side myself.
[JACK] I haven't had prey
like this in a while.
Ooh. I want to slice
him up so bad!
You're mine now!
[NARRATOR]
Using his instinctual ability
to transform the very
nature of his magic,
Jack's ferocious blades
are able to cut through
practically any type of spell.
All because his desire to
slash things is so intense.
[JACK]
Here you go!
[NARRATOR] Even though Spatial
Magic has unique properties
of its own, he can cut his way
through it just the same.
[growls] But how?
Well, well. That scrawny psycho
came in handy after all.
[JACK]
Severing Magic...
Now, Dark Magic...
Dark Cloaked...
Ready, Jack?
[JACK]
Ready!
Death Scythe!
[YAMI]
Dimension Slash!
[gasping]
[JACK cackling]
Hmph.
All right!
[JACK grunts]
Damn.
[LANGRIS] I was surprised when
they eliminated my shield,
but they're still
one step behind.
[LANGRIS laughs]
[LANGRIS] Looks like your
Spatial Magic is worthless
for attacking and defending!
[FINRAL] My power can't
actually defeat anybody.
[FINRAL groans]
[FINRAL]
But...
[LANGRIS]
I'll send you to oblivion.
[FINRAL] Spatial Magic:
Fallen Angel's Wingbeat!
What the--?
[LANGRIS] He dropped his guard
so he could transport them?
[FINRAL]
My Fallen Angel's Wingbeat
can forcibly transport a person
from one location to another.
I'm gonna save my friends,
and you, too!
Heh!
Well, I hate to break it
to you, human. You're fast.
But I'm just a
little bit faster!
I'll kill all of you in one go!
[FINRAL] It's fine, these guys
are Magic Knight Captains.
If anyone can win
this fight, it's them!
[gasps]
[JACK] The more I use them,
the quicker my blades become!
[YAMI]
All right, kid.
Time for a nap.
I've got just the thing.
My Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked
Lightless Blunt Strike!
[LANGRIS gasping]
That should work!
[YAMI grunts]
[LANGRIS]
How could you beat me?
When you're just... human trash!
[LANGRIS]
I hate your kind.
All of you are so filthy,
petty, and repulsive!
[ALL gasp]
[LANGRIS]
Just disappear!
[cackles] He finally lost
the rest of his marbles.
[YAMI]
This mana.
It feels even more sinister
than it did earlier.
Great! What the hell are we
s'posed to do with him now?
[FINRAL panting]
[FINRAL] Nothing.
It's over at this point.
He's too far gone.
My magic is so insignificant
compared to his,
he won't even notice it.
[panting]
[FINRAL]
Langris.
When I think about it,
we never actually argued.
Not since we were children.
I always ran away instead.
Using my lack of
talent as an excuse.
Even though I'm
the older brother,
and I knew how lonely
you were feeling.
This is... my last chance!
Your big brother really shines
when it comes to
speed and accuracy.
So I'll stop you,
whatever it takes!
I hope you're ready.
Wake up!
[LANGRIS grunts]
[FINRAL]
Langris... Langris...
Langris!
Listen to me!
[FINRAL] For being the
gifted younger brother,
you're kind of a
handful, aren't you?
[FINRAL]
Sorry it took so long.
I'm not really good
at this stuff.
Come with me.
That's real cute.
We do all the grunt work
and you save the day
with your brotherly love.
[cackles]
Good job, Finral. You did it.
[YAMI]
But the big question is...
What's their endgame here?
Just wipe out humanity
and call it a day?
No, I think they've got
somethin' else up their sleeve.
[PATRY]
It won't be long now, Licht.
Soon, I'll get to see you awake.
[gasps]
[PATRY] Did the two of you
just get here, as well?
Who's he, Brother?
That isn't Licht.
You're Patry.
I know that you always
looked up to Licht,
but now you've copied his
appearance and everything.
What do you mean
"copied" him?
It wasn't my choice. I was
in this body when I awoke.
I suppose you could
call it my destiny.
Wow. That's creepy.
Hey!
Droit! It's been a
long time, hasn't it?
I was just awakened, actually.
So it doesn't feel like
it's been very long to me.
[laughs] Good point. And how
are you, little Eclat?
Hello, sir.
[PATRY]
Rhya, where is Licht right now?
Oh. Patry's here, too, eh?
Licht's using a fake body.
So it's either because of that,
or because he's the one
who activated the forbidden
reincarnation spell.
But his memories haven't
completely come back yet,
so he's asleep.
How unfortunate.
[RHYA]
Well, anyway,
it's good to see the gang's
all here, finally.
The others are out back.
[PATRY]
That's true.
And I'm fairly certain the
Golden Dawn has taken care
of eradicating the
humans in our absence.
Judging by that large
hole in the castle,
I'd say Latry
must've overindulged,
and I'm sure that pompous
king is long dead.
[PATRY] Now all that's left is
to fit the final magic stone
into the pedestal
within the castle
and initiate the spell that will
destroy the Clover Kingdom.
The magic stone is
already in our hands.
We'll wash away the
malice brought on
by that forbidden spell,
and then our reincarnation
will be truly complete.
After humanity is snuffed out,
we will reclaim this world,
making it a peaceful
place for elves alone.
[YAMI]
I don't know who's in there,
but I'm guessin' it won't
be an easy fight.
Wonder what my
dumbass subordinates
and the other Magic
Knights are doin'.
At this rate,
I'll have to flatten
every one o' those
elves by myself.
[JACK]
Nah, I'll slash 'em first.
[YAMI]
Keep dreamin'.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[YAMI, JACK]
Me!
At this rate,
I'll have to flatten
every one o' those
elves by myself.
[JACK]
Nah, I'll slash 'em first.
[YAMI]
Keep dreamin'.
They're mine!
Hey! I just said I'm the one
who's gonna kick their asses!
The only person
kicking ass'll be me!
[BOTH]
No, me!
Me, me, me, me, me, me,
me, me, me, me, me, me.
Me!
Tch. You sure piss me off.
Huh?!
Stop copyin' me, weirdo. Uh!
I said stop copying
me, right now! Uh!
[BOTH]
Hey. What's going on here?
We're doin' everything
the same way!
[NARRATOR]
In essence,
Yami and Jack are
basically the same person.
[BOTH]
No we're not!
[KIRSCH]
My beautiful voice.
My beautiful flowers.
Everything about me,
Kirsch "Beautiful" Vermillion,
is beautiful.
Black Clover , Page 110,
"The Raging Bull
Joins the Showdown!"
I'm not a raging bull.
I'm just ragingly beautiful.