[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy
who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world,
and to become the
next Wizard King!
[NARRATOR] The captains
held a meeting to decide
who would go to train
in the Heart Kingdom.
Five of the Black Bulls:
Asta, Nero, Luck,
Finral, and Noelle.
Mimosa from the Golden Dawn.
Leopold of the
Crimson Lion Kings.
Captain Charlotte chose
to nominate herself.
As did Captain Rill
from the Aqua Deer.
This elite group
would be learning
from the five Spirit Guardians.
Afterward, during the
decoration ceremony,
those who had performed
especially well
in the last conflict
were recognized.
Leopold,
Sol, and Mimosa
received promotions.
Then...
[MARX] You're being
promoted as well, Yuno.
To first-class
Senior Magic Knight.
[GROUP gasps]
[NARRATOR] Yuno was promoted to
the highest rank below Captain.
The king, not to be outdone,
made his own promotion.
[KING CLOVER] By my authority
as the ruler of this kingdom,
I award to Sekke the title
of first-class
Senior Magic Knight!
[GROUP gasps]
[SEKKE] Did he say "first-class
Senior Magic Knight"?
That's like the cream
of the crah- ha p!
[NARRATOR]
Surprisingly,
Sekke was given the same
prestigious title as Yuno.
Back at the Black Bulls hideout,
there was one squad member
who refused to
accept his exclusion
from training in
the Heart Kingdom.
[MAGNA]
Please, Boss!
I'm begging you here!
If I'm going to be a real man,
then I refuse to be
left behind anymore!
I'll go, even if you
tell me to stay here!
You good with that?
[MAGNA]
Yes, sir!
I can push past
the limits of my mana!
More than any
commoner has before!
All right. I'll ask Julius
if there's room for another guy.
[NARRATOR] And, at the
Golden Dawn's headquarters,
not everyone was pleased
to hear about the promotion
that the Wizard King
had awarded to Yuno.
[DAVID] A first-class Senior
Magic Knight, huh?
Now he's the same rank
as Vice Captain Langris.
Which is crazy, since he's
only been with us for a year.
I'm not exactly surprised.
Yuno's really powerful.
Come to think of it,
Langris hasn't been on a mission
since everything that happened
with the Midnight Sun.
If you ask me,
it's only a matter of time
before Yuno takes his job.
Ever since he got
that promotion,
it's all anyone talks
about around here.
For good reason!
Yuno and Langris are both
amazing mages and all,
but when it comes to
who would be a better VC,
I gotta tell you,
the answer is pretty obvious.
[gasps]
Oh, Vice Captain Langris, sir!
Hello there. Out for a stroll?
It's a wonderful day for it!
Please enjoy. I should go.
[DAVID] It's only a matter of
time before Yuno takes his job.
[WILLIAM]
Don't you think it's about time?
Time for what, sir?
To continue with your
duties as Vice Captain.
We'll be dealing
with Spade soon,
so I need you to
watch over the squa--
[LANGRIS]
I can't yet.
Please just wait
a little longer.
[door clicks]
Has my brother
contacted you recently?
Oh, yes. Look.
He writes to you?
It's funny.
He could use portals
to visit me anytime,
but he's been sending letters
through them, instead.
[LANGRIS] I'm sure he's trying
to put a little distance
between you two
because he believes
it's a part of his training.
[sneezes]
[NOELLE sighs]
Do you have a cold?
You're looking especially
lovely today, Noelle.
Let's go for some tea.
Huh?
You have to stop,
or you're never going to
break your curse, Finral!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
[LANGRIS]
What's he say in his letters?
[FINNES] That he's going to
train in the Heart Kingdom soon.
[LANGRIS]
He told you that?
[FINNES] If he has to
travel to another land,
it must be for
something serious.
Do you think there's going
to be another big battle?
Uh...
[FINNES] I tried to get him
to tell me face-to-face.
You know, since he's not
very good at keeping secrets.
[FINNES]
What's wrong, Langris?
There's no need
to concern yourself
with that, Lady Finnes.
[LANGRIS]
Why the smile?
[FINNES]
You can't hide things either.
The two of you really
are a lot alike.
[clatter]
[LANGRIS]
Don't ever compare me to him!
Please forgive me.
No, it's fine. I'm sorry.
[FINNES coughs]
[LANGRIS]
Are you all right?
Yes.
You should go
back inside and rest.
I'll take my leave now.
It's just my usual cough,
nothing too scary.
Either way, I've got
business to attend to today.
Oh, did you return to your
post as the vice captain?
[LANGRIS]
Goodbye. Thank you for the tea.
That's check.
[laughs] What a clever move!
See that? You lose, Alecdora!
Told you it was better
to bet on Shiren.
[ALECDORA]
The game's not even over yet.
Come on, Yuno, this is
amazing weather for a date!
Where should we go?
I'm good with
anything, honestly.
Hey, are you listening?
Here comes Vice Captain Langris.
What's your problem?
I know you're jealous that Yuno
and I are the perfect couple,
but that's no reason
to have such an attitude--
What's wrong?
You need something?
I'd like to spar with you.
[GROUP gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[LANGRIS] You're a first-class
Senior Magic Knight now.
So, based on that, you and I
should be equally matched.
I want to test you and determine
whether you're qualified--
[YUNO]
Let's do it.
Yuno!
Calm down, both of you!
Let's not be rash.
There's no reason for this!
No, Klaus.
You're the one who
needs to calm down.
I'm not suggesting this because
I want to pick a fight with him.
[knocking]
[WILLIAM]
Come.
[ALECDORA]
Pardon me, sir.
I had to tell you
that the vice captain
just challenged Yuno to a duel.
Did he really?
It makes me nervous.
I hope nothing terrible happens.
I'll be with you
the whole time, Yuno.
So trust me, you don't need
to worry about holding back!
[LANGRIS] A normal sparring
session is no fun.
Let's spice it up.
How about this?
The loser agrees to resign
from the Golden Dawn.
[ALL gasping]
[LANGRIS] Honestly.
What a vulgar bunch they are.
You should really choose your
friends more carefully, Yuno.
Aren't you embarrassed
to be seen
with people like that?
[YUNO]
Why would I be?
I've never felt that way once.
I'm very proud of Asta.
He's my rival.
[laughs] A simpleton
like that's your rival?
For what, anyway?
Are you two in some
kind of competition?
That's right, yes.
We're aiming to become
the Wizard King.
I don't know what your
problem is, Sir Smirky,
but I don't let
anybody mock my Yuno--!
[YUNO] There's no rule
saying that a commoner
can't be the Wizard King.
Huh?
[YUNO]
First, of course,
I'll become captain
of the Golden Dawn.
Will you?
Have you forgotten the fact
that I'm our squad's
current vice captain?
I believe you said,
before you're Wizard King,
you want to be Captain
of our squad, yes?
If you win, you'll be
forcing the vice captain
to abandon the team,
which would put you
one step closer to the top.
That's not such
a bad deal, is it?
[YUNO]
Stop talking and let's go.
He keeps adding more
and more fuel to the fire!
I don't think they can
resolve this quickly.
No.
I have a feeling this
may get quite bloody.
Let's make some bets!
Why are you like this, David?
We should stop them!
Now, are you ready, Yuno?
Let's begin!
He made the rock disappear!
Talking won't solve this.
[gasps] Please stop it,
Vice Captain!
He's out to kill. Why?
Oh, dear. Looks like
you dodged it.
[LANGRIS]
But I'll get you this time!
[YUNO] Wind Creation Magic:
Wind Blade Shower!
Perhaps I was too careless.
My goodness,
that's quite a scowl.
I don't know why you've been
holding back on me so far,
but I'd like you to stop it now.
Oh? You think I've been
holding back, do you?
[YUNO]
Of course.
If you hadn't been, you would've
dodged that last spell easily.
Langris. Fight me for real,
or you'll get hurt.
This isn't right!
Actually, I have a feeling Yuno
isn't doing that to provoke him.
[LANGRIS]
What did you say to me?
You want me to say it
slower for you?
I was giving you the
benefit of the doubt,
but now I know you're
trying to insult me.
I won't go easy on you anymore!
It's that spell again!
[MIMOSA] This is the same
spatial magic he used
during the Royal Knights
Selection Exam.
I'll go all out! Happy now?
[YUNO] Spirit Assimilation:
Spirit Dive!
[LANGRIS]
Take this!
[YUNO] Mana Zone:
Spirit's Hushed Dance.
Incredible!
Yuno's really talented!
[YUNO]
Spirit Storm!
I know this move!
It's from when that elf
was possessing him!
The auto-defense spell!
He shouldn't be able
to use it anymore,
now that he's been released
from the spirit's influence.
[LANGRIS] It's faint,
but I can still feel the mana
from the elf that was
reincarnated inside my body.
Well? You can't keep
dodging me forever!
[YUNO grunts]
He just hit Yuno's crown!
It's been destroyed!
Can't you do anything
besides run away?
It's all over!
Yuno!
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
Wha--? How--? An afterimage?
You're right. It is over.
Oh, good.
They both survived.
But this means the
vice captain's leaving.
You don't happen to
remember who I bet on?
Don't know, don't care!
So that's how it is.
[LANGRIS]
Don't just stand there.
Go ahead, laugh at me.
I gave it all I had,
and you still won.
You did get serious,
but not till it was half-done.
Before that, you were
trying to lose.
[GOLDEN DAWN gasps]
Quite an accusation,
but you're right.
I wanted to let you
take me down.
It was a plan for me to
resign with some dignity.
But this... This is shameful.
I lost, even without
holding back.
[YUNO]
That isn't shameful at all.
Do you think it was that easy
for me to win against you?
He brings up a good point.
That's right, it was
a close battle.
What makes you
think that matters?
You just defeated me.
And that's all I care about!
Which means that
I'm going to walk away
from the Golden Dawn.
That's what we agreed upon.
I never actually
agreed to those terms.
Maybe you didn't
accept them, but I did.
This is stupid!
[LANGRIS] Take good care
of the squad for me, Yuno.
You're walking away now?
Do you honestly feel like
you lost that battle?
If you'd have gone
all out from the start,
then you might've succeeded.
Someday down the road,
let's spar again.
And promise you won't hold back!
[gasps]
[LANGRIS] Forgive me for not
consulting you, Captain.
I'm not surprised.
You know, Langris,
you didn't have to
resort to theatrics
because you wanted to resign.
[LANGRIS]
You saw through me, too?
Sorry, that's the way I am.
I'm well aware.
But, then, I also know that this
isn't the end of your journey.
What happened today
doesn't change the fact
that you're part
of the Golden Dawn.
[LANGRIS]
Thank you very much.
I should go.
I'll be waiting. We all will.
[FINNES] Langris, why are
you dressed like that?
I'm about to leave on a journey.
What? So it's true then;
you really did leave
the Golden Dawn.
Well, no, not entirely.
I just made a silly promise,
and now I have to keep my word.
[FINNES]
Oh.
Good morning, Lady Finnes,
how are you? Uh, Langris?
What are you wearing
that big cloak for?
Let me guess, you wanted
to pay one final visit
to Lady Finnes before you went
away for your training, right?
Huh? Yeah. I did.
I'll be the man who
makes Lady Finnes happy.
I promise.
Once I've become worthy,
I'm gonna come back for you.
I guess I'm willing to wait,
but don't take too long.
[LANGRIS] By the way, there's
something I forgot to tell you.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[LANGRIS]
Despite how you feel,
I still haven't decided
to let you win her love.
Uh--
Come, now.
Just who do you think
you are, brother?
[LANGRIS] Wait and see.
Our battle is only beginning.
You'll need energy to train
in the Heart Kingdom,
so you gotta eat way more food!
Gladly! This is great!
I'm gonna be so sick.
[SHEEP COOKS bleet]
Is it just you three?
Yeah, Luck and Magna said
they were gonna wait
and have their dinner later on,
if that's cool, sir!
[YAMI]
Gotcha.
If you notice me, then
I'm sure you'll invite me
to go to the Heart
Kingdom with you, too.
However, I plan to
improve my Curse Magic
under my father's guidance.
So I have to go back home now.
It pains me,
but I cannot join you.
I'll just leave
without being seen.
[NOELLE]
Where does it all go?!
[MAGNA] Whoa, did someone
just walk past us?
Nah, it was the wind.
Oh, okay. Hey, Captain Yami!
Did they say they'd
let me go or not?
Don't worry, Magna,
they're all right with
you taggin' along.
[gasps] Wow,
thanks a million, boss!
[YAMI] You should thank
the Wizard King, not me.
That's badass!
I'm so happy you're
comin' with us, Magna!
I appreciate it, pal!
Whoo, I could go for
a nice cold drink.
Wait, what's that juice?
You know, the tasty one
they have in Heart?
[CHARMY]
Tasty?
Oh, are you talkin' about
the crimson orange juice?
Right, I can't
wait to try that!
I hear it gets sweeter when
you add your mana to it!
[CHARMY]
It gets sweeter?
Yeah, but if you're me,
it just stays all sour
and disgusting!
Quit crying,
at least you had me
there to fix it for you.
Anyway, you guys'll arrive
in the Heart Kingdom tomorrow.
Make the Black Bulls proud
and push past your limits!
[GROUP]
Yes, sir!
[NOELLE] I'm going to
improve my magic ability
so that I can defeat
the devil Megicula!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[LANGRIS] "If You're Going
to Quit Being Vice Captain."
[LANGRIS] Forgive me for
not consulting you, Captain.
Since you gave up your post,
you're on lunch duty.
So you're still making me work?
You don't like it?
Then clean the chalkboard.
The chalkboard?
That's just as terrible!
I can always put you
in charge of the animals.
Since when do we have these?
You suck!
[yells]
[ASTA]
Time to train!
I'm gonna work so hard, I'll
have muscles on my muscles!
[NOELLE]
Ugh, would you be quiet?
Try training your brain
for once, instead.
Black Clover , Page 155:
"The 5 Spirit Guardians."