[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] After the Magic
Knights' awards ceremony,
the grand finale of the
Star Festival, the nation's king
delivered an announcement
of monumental importance.
We have located the
Midnight Sun's hideout.
To combat this deadly foe,
we're planning to gather
the absolute cream-of-the-crop
from our Magic Knight squads.
They'll be the Royal Knights!
[NARRATOR]
And while Yuno and Asta
were making sense of the news.
[MEREOLEONA] Damn you!
You weak little imbecile!
[NARRATOR] They happened to
run into the new captain
of the Crimson Lion Kings,
Mereoleona Vermillion,
berating her squad members
in a demonic rage.
[MEREOLEONA]
Every year, the Crimson Lions
have consistently placed
first or second!
And now you have
forced me to endure
the disgrace of coming in fifth?
All because my frater stultum
is currently out of commission?
You feckless little infants!
What's a frater stultum ?
"Idiot brother."
Who is she talkin'
about, though?
Fuegoleon, of course.
Wait a second.
Are you tryin' to tell me
that this crazy lady
is related to Fuegoleon and Leo?
They're siblings?
That brother of mine
has always been a buffoon!
How could he have produced
such a pack of cowards?!
And now I have the
pleasure of looking after
you sad sacks while
he's off taking a nap!
Fuegoleon's not fit
to be your captain!
Hold on, that's not true!
My brother was
the finest captain
we ever could have asked for!
That's right!
Captain Fuegoleon was
a perfect example
of the kind of person
that every Magic Knight
should aspire to be!
He cared about every member
of this squad and
the Clover Kingdom
more than anyone else
I've met in my life.
If you ask me, that man's
the greatest Magic Knight
in this whole country!
That's why I refuse to
let you talk about him
that way, even if you are--
Well, if you feel that
strongly about it,
then you'd better give me
less talk and more action!
Show me you're
the strongest team
in the kingdom, led by
the strongest captain!
That numbskull isn't
going to die.
That would mean
abandoning his country
and the Crimson Lion Kings!
[MEREOLEONA]
So until he returns,
I want every one of you
to walk with pride
and show the world the full
glory of our mighty ranks!
It's my job to work
you to the bone
while my brother's away,
and that's exactly
what I plan to do.
Don't you dare let me down!
[ALL]
Yes, ma'am!
Did you hear that, Yuno?
Man! She is on fire!
Tell me about it.
What kinda training is
she gonna make 'em do?
Now then, off to the
hot springs training camp!
[CRIMSON LIONS murmur]
[CRIMSON LION 71C]
Hot springs? Seriously?
Hot springs, really?
Whoa, that sounds
like the funnest
training camp in the world!
And the easiest.
[MEREOLEONA]
I heard that.
You're comin' with us, kid.
How's that work?
Y'tryin' to kidnap me?
I mean, not that
I wouldn't love to,
but we're from different
squads and it's dangerous
to go places with
strangers so...
Hey! Asta!
Are you gonna join our squad
and be my official rival?
[ASTA]
No!
I'm out. This doesn't
involve me. Later.
[ASTA]
Yuno, wait! Don't leave me!
Huh?
Both of you.
[gasps]
[YUNO]
Uh-oh.
[BELL] Hey, cut it out,
you big hothead.
Yuno's not interested
in your little spa trip,
so get your hands off of him!
It's not a spa trip!
[BELL yelps]
Look, Bell. I'd rather
you stay out of this.
You'll only make
her more heated.
'Kay, if you say so.
Once my sister sinks
her claws into you,
there's no hope of escaping.
She doesn't care for war.
She's not interested
in politics.
That's why she never
really took center stage
in our family.
But when she does fight,
she's arguably stronger
than our brother.
They call her the uncrowned,
undefeated lioness:
Mereoleona Vermillion!
And I think I'll call you
Rookies One and Two.
Now let's hit the hot springs
and see what you're made of.
[ASTA] I dunno why, but I got
a bad feelin' about this!
[YAMI laughs]
Whoo, that drink
tasted like victory!
Sure feels good to outrank
every Magic Knight
in this whole bar!
Are you feeling okay, Char?
Call me, "Captain." Captain.
You got it, Char.
[CAPTAINS grunt]
[JACK] Don't get all cocky
just because you managed
to win for once after a lifetime
of bringing up
the rear, Suckyhiro!
[YAMI] Must be rough for you,
gettin' your ass handed to ya
by the squad that always
comes in dead last!
Shut your filthy mouth
or I'll shut it for you.
That's a pretty fancy hairdo
you're sportin' there,
Mr. Silver Eagles.
You must think highly
of yourself for a guy
who got beat by the Black Bulls.
Good for you.
[YAMI]
Oh, you wanna do this?
Mercury Magic: Silver Spears!
My apologies, sir.
We don't allow offensive
spells in the bar.
Here's a drink on the house
for the inconvenience.
Sorry, I wasn't aware.
[gasps] Delicious.
[KAISER]
The barkeep is right, Nozel.
This is a place for enjoying
drinks, not for fighting.
You shouldn't have
missed the event.
It was quite unbecoming.
[YAMI] Pft! Your hairdo might
even be stupider than his!
[KAISER growls] I'll make you
eat those words, you ruffian!
I'm sorry, sir.
As I told the other gentleman,
no offensive magic inside.
Please accept a free drink.
Oh, my goodness.
It must have slipped my mind.
Do forgive me.
And thank you for this.
[KAISER]
Mm! Upon my word!
Don't you clowns know how
to stand up for yourselves?
Looks like it's my turn.
Keh. On second thought,
I guess I can let it go.
Why's everybody actin'
so damn reasonable now?
This bartender's gotta
be puttin' some sketchy
happy-drugs in those
cocktails o' his.
[RILL] Captain Yami!
I really look up to you!
I mean, I only came in
last place this one time,
and look how busted up
I let myself get.
But you were in dead
last, like, forever,
and you never lost your cool!
That's like,
superhuman or something!
You really are amazing!
You're so confident!
So thick-skinned!
You don't care how much
people laugh at you!
Even though you were
always the worst,
you did everything your way!
Uh, thank you?
[DOROTHY grumbling]
[YAMI] For the last time,
I don't understand
anything you're sayin' to me!
[JACK] Keh! You just
wait until next year!
Aw, come on, you really leavin'?
What's wrong, beanpole!
Any other day you'd be beggin'
me to go drinkin' with you!
[JACK]
Shut it!
Suit yourself.
I guess that means
I'll be knockin' back
this celebratory
booze without ya!
[laughs]
[MEREOLEONA] You sure are riding
high for a one-time winner.
[YAMI]
Huh? Oh, Sisgoleon.
Where do you get that name from?
[YAMI]
You're Fuegoleon's sister,
so I assumed that was right.
You honestly believe
a lineage as proud as mine
would name their
offspring so carelessly?
You don't? I figured you just
take whatever thing you are
and slap a "goleon"
on the end of it.
You're such a simpleton.
[YUNO, ASTA grunt]
Oh, hey, how's
it goin', Captain?
[laughs] Looks like she
got a hold of you, kid!
How'd that happen anyway?
Uh, that's kind of a long story.
[MEREOLEONA]
You're coming, too.
[YAMI]
Huh?
[MEREOLEONA]
Being late's bad enough,
but you didn't even show up!
[YAMI] Hey, wait--
Wait stop it, 'goleon.
[MEREOLEONA] You need to
learn a little discipline!
[YAMI] Discipline? But I'm
already the captain!
Sorry, Yami, but it
serves you right.
[MEREOLEONA]
You, too.
You're not taking
my Char anywhere!
And who are you?
[SOL]
Don't worry, Char.
I may not know what's going on,
but I'd follow you
anywhere in the universe!
For the last time,
it's "Captain."
Asta! So this is where
you've been hiding!
Listen, it's not like
you were the reason
we came in second, so dispense
with the celebrating
and help me give Kahono
and Kiato a proper sendoff!
Uh!
Oh. Mereoleona. Uh...
Wow, it's been too long!
Well, have a nice night!
[MEREOLEONA]
Ah-ah.
Noelle.
Um, yes, ma'am?
You're comin', too.
What? Wait a minute!
You can't be serious!
I don't have anything
to do with this nonsense!
Yeah, and how many
fiery cat paws
can this lady possibly have?
[YUNO]
But why me? It's not fair.
Don't be a baby.
Got any idea where
she's taking us?
A hot spring, I think?
[NOELLE]
Uh, hot spring?
[sighs] Oh, hey there, Noelle.
Could you wash my back for me?
[NOELLE gasps]
You're such a pervert!
[ASTA]
I am?
[MEREOLEONA]
All of you, settle down!
[ALL yelping]
[BARTENDER]
Thank you for your patronage.
Well, how do you like that?
It looks like things are
about to get more interesting.
[ASTA]
What the...?
This is the hot spring?
What's the holdup?
Let's get to work!
[MEREOLEONA] Yultim Volcano
is a strong magic region.
Deep underground there's
a volcanic belt
that's laced with mana and
constantly spewing out lava.
[CRIMSON LIONS gasp]
[MEREOLEONA] Normal humans
can't set foot in this place.
But if you reach the peak,
you'll find the most fantastic
and revitalizing hot spring
you can imagine!
How's that?
Are you getting excited?
Come! Let's head for the summit!
[ASTA]
I wouldn't say "excited."
No way! This place is
a nightmare! Then again...
[CHARLOTTE]
Sol. Please wash my back.
[SOL]
A hot spring with Char? Sweet!
Look, Sol.
There was really no reason
for you to tag along with us.
What are you talking about?
I told you I'd
follow you anywhere,
so this'll be easy
as pie! Okay, Char?
Call me, "Captain."
Roger, Char!
I say we make it a race
to see which one of us
can get to the summit first!
Are you game, Asta?
Sure, I could stand
to blow off some steam!
I'm ready when you are!
Hey, golden boy!
Are you in, or what?
Knock yourselves out.
[LEOPOLD gasps]
[LEOPOLD]
Oh, right, he's Mr. Cool.
Killjoy.
Yeah, but you get used to it.
Quit wasting time and let's go!
[CRIMSON LIONS yell]
[ASTA]
All right, time to do this!
[LEOPOLD]
Our magic should do the trick--
[BOTH gasp]
[LEOPOLD]
What's the deal with this heat?
The mana in the
atmosphere is going crazy!
I'm suffocating!
[LEOPOLD]
It's hard to breathe.
I feel like my chest is
on fire and my sweat glands
are about to explode!
[LEOPOLD] And on top of that,
she expects us to climb
an erupting volcano?
There's just no way!
[BOTH gasp]
[YAMI]
If I try to duck out,
Sisgoleon's gonna
come after me again.
Guess I'm doin' this.
[CHARLOTTE] Why did she
insist on bringing me?
It's a good thing I'm
starting to sober up.
If I fail, I'll be a disgrace
to women everywhere!
Let's make this quick.
Wow, the captains
are unbelievably strong.
It's like the magma's
not even affecting them!
Yeah, but they shouldn't be able
to move like that
in this environment,
it's not humanly possible!
So cool!
I think I know! They're
both using Mana Skin!
[NARRATOR] To some extent,
all Magic Knights
use magic power to enhance
their physical abilities
in combat situations.
But the height of this skill
is a fundamental spell
known as Mana Skin.
Even in unstable
conditions such as these.
Yami and Charlotte are able
to emit a constant stream
of magic power that
encases their body
and protects them from damage.
Mana Skin? That's nothing.
Every Magic Knight
knows how to use
a basic technique like that.
Yeah, but not everybody
can sustain it
for that long in
a raging volcano--
there's no way we'll make it!
[LEOPOLD]
Of course we will!
All we have to do is
feel it out as we go,
slowly adapt to the mana here.
then make our way up
to the summit
before our magic power runs out!
[LEOPOLD] We've gone soft,
so think of this as a chance
to retrain ourselves! You ready?
[CRIMSON LIONS]
Ready!
Ugh, gross! It's so hot!
[YUNO]
Mana Skin, huh?
[sighs]
Ah, this feels much better.
[yelps]
Hey! Yuno!
[YUNO] Hurry, or I'll be
dizzy from the hot spring
before you even get there!
[LEOPOLD]
Well, I'm headin' up, see ya!
[ASTA]
Leo!
[LEOPOLD] Dammit, Yuno!
You better wait for me!
[SOL growls]
[SOL] I'm gonna be
as strong as Char is!
And then the two of us can relax
in the hot spring together!
[YAMI]
I get it now.
Sisgoleon brought us out here
so we could be examples
for the Crimson Lion Kings.
[YAMI]
Especially Charlotte.
Her magic's an awful fit
for a place like this,
but she's still holdin' her own.
[YAMI] And the little Golden
Dawn prodigy is their age,
so that'll probably get 'em
feelin' competitive.
Huh, that boss-lady of theirs
is sharper than she lets on.
[MEREOLEONA] I thought I told
you louts to quit dawdling
and move it!
[YAMI] Or maybe she's
just mean. I dunno anymore.
[NOELLE]
Mana Skin.
It's not exactly an
easy thing to pull off
if you have a hard time
controlling your magic power!
And my water magic
is practically made
for these conditions!
[NOELLE] It's been forever
since I'd seen Mereoleona.
And she drags me to this place?
She must really hate me.
You say something, Noelle?
[NOELLE yelps]
Me? No! Not a word!
[MEREOLEONA]
Are you ready to climb?
[NOELLE]
Mm...
[MEREOLEONA] I asked if
you were ready to climb!
I am!
[MEREOLEONA] You used to be
a little girl who feared
her siblings, but I can tell
from your mana, that's changed.
[gasps]
[MEREOLEONA] It's not just
your outward appearance.
You resemble her on the
inside a little, too.
[gasps]
[MEREOLEONA]
She was a powerful Magic Knight,
and possessed an incredibly
strong heart as well.
Unlike anyone I've ever met.
Thank you for the
beautiful flowers.
[MEREOLEONA] Mm. I hear you'll
be giving birth any day.
[ACIER]
Yes.
And afterwards,
are you considering
returning to the
field of battle?
This is no time to cry!
So the children have
already told you.
Lady Acier, the Magic Knights
need you to return to your
post as soon as you recover.
I honestly don't
understand why you
would put your life
in such danger.
I know I don't need
to remind you,
but once the Magic Knights
decide to enter the fray,
they will never stop fighting
in order to protect
the Clover Kingdom and
its people, even if it means
they must put their
own lives on the line.
--[MEREOLEONA gasps]
--[heartbeats]
You see, having a child
is no different.
When a woman is carrying a baby,
she'll do whatever's
necessary to prevent
any harm from befalling
that innocent life.
That's what being a
mother is, Mereoleona.
[MEREOLEONA]
There's nothing stronger than
a determined woman, and your
mother was certainly that.
[gasps]
[MEREOLEONA]
If you have the determination
to reach the top, then there's
no mountain in existence
that you can't conquer!
Yes, ma'am!
[ASTA panting]
[ASTA] They're gone.
Everyone's way up ahead.
My muscles and spirit
are just about shot.
[ASTA grunts]
The heat is too strong
for my sword to cut through.
I don't think I can
get up there after all.
[MEREOLEONA]
Then quit.
It was a fool's
errand for someone
without magic to attempt
to scale this mountain at all.
[MEREOLEONA] And here I was
thinking Rookie Number Two
might actually have
something going for him.
Now I see you've
only come this far
because fortune's
been on your side.
[MEREOLEONA]
At least you have that.
Even if you aren't able
to overcome this trial,
you might just end up being
the next the Wizard King
through nothing but
sheer luck of the draw.
Do yourself a favor, climb down.
[ASTA]
I'm not leaving.
What I want...
Just wondering.
[BOTH] How can I become
the Wizard King?
What we want most in the
world, isn't something
you can just achieve
through blind luck!
It's about results.
Yeah? Then you
better get movin'!
[JULIUS] A noble heart alone
cannot protect anyone,
and the trust of the people
is earned, not granted.
You want to know
what you need to do
to gain the title
of Wizard King?
I don't see how a
fool who doesn't even
know himself can
achieve anything great.
[JULIUS] Get results. Prove
that you're the strongest.
[ASTA] I'll reach the top!
Our dream depends on it!
You want results, you got it!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[RILL]
"A Dialogue with Dorothy!"
[RILL laughs] Hey, Dorothy,
how 'bout a little conversation?
I was wondering if
you have any hobbies
other than sleeping when
you're standing up.
Ooh, I betcha I can guess!
Uh. Maybe you like
taking dancing lessons?
And you probably
enjoy cooking meals?
[DOROTHY grumbles]
Your best dish is hamburger?
[DOROTHY grunts]
But sometimes, you prefer
to cook up dessert!
[DOROTHY grumbles]
I'd love to sample your
cooking one day, Dorothy!
Hey, how bout we play
rock-paper-scissors,
and if I win, you cook for me?
This oughtta be easy.
One, two, three!
Ah--
[screams]
[MEREOLEONA]
How dare you weaklings
call yourselves Magic
Knights? Don't give up!
And soon, we'll bask in
that glorious hot spring!
Black Clover , Page 72:
"Saint Elmo's Fire."
My magic is uninhibited
naked conversation!