[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed
lost until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King, and
his story became legend.
Only those who are
strong will survive.
The weak deserve death.
Mimosa!
[ASTA yells]
[ASTA] Your new opponent
is right here!
Begone, boy!
[ASTA] He's still got
that Recovery magic.
I can't finish
him off. What now?
[NOELLE] Why are you just
sitting there, insect?
[NOELLE]
Listen to me.
I am royalty, Asta,
and you are the first
commoner I've accepted.
Now get moving.
And don't you dare give up
until you beat him.
Understand?
Yeah. I'll bring this guy
down, and I'll get one or two
hits in for you while I'm at it.
I live to destroy the weak!
Well, you're not
gonna destroy me!
I may not have any magic power,
but what I do have
are my friends!
[MARS groans]
I don't really know
how, but, I did it.
[ASTA]
I'm dead.
He's... hit.
Asta!
I'm fine.
Forget about me for now
and go look after him!
Oh, right, sure!
[MIMOSA]
This wound.
Can I even heal it with the
magic power I have left?
[YUNO]
Asta!
[KLAUS]
Open up your eyes, brat!
Where did all that arrogance go?
[LUCK]
You can't die before we fight!
[NOELLE]
Asta!
Try to hold on. You can do it.
Do you hear me?
You're not alone!
[FANA] Mars, is our
training getting to you?
When things get tough,
just close your eyes
and think about
the people you love.
That's why we're here.
We were born so we could
become powerful enough
to protect our country.
[FANA]
Once we've gotten strong,
that's when we'll get
to leave this place.
Do you think you'll be
the first one who goes?
I do.
I mean, how could you not be?
You're the strongest.
We all know it.
If I get out... I'll wait.
I promise. I'll wait for you.
Yeah!
We'll go see the
outside world together.
[INSTRUCTOR 19A]
This is your final test:
a fight to the death.
Only the last one standing
will be permitted to
leave here as a mage
in service to our country.
Refuse and you will
all be eliminated.
[TRAINEE KIDS murmuring]
[yells]
--[TRAINEE KIDS scream]
--[TRAINEE 19A screams]
[screaming continues]
[panting]
[FANA]
Mars. I'm sorry.
[MARS]
Fana?
This is the only way.
Now, die.
[panting]
[MARS wheezing]
[MARS screams]
[INSTRUCTOR 19A]
It seems Mars is the survivor.
[INSTRUCTOR 19B]
Which means he will be the one
that gets the mage stones.
[INSTRUCTOR 19C]
As for his Compound Magic,
let's use Fana.
Both for her
abilities and because
she was the last he defeated.
And thus, from the
deaths of his peers,
the mightiest mage is born.
[INSTRUCTOR C laughs]
[MARS]
I... I don't need anyone.
As powerful as I am,
I will never need anyone.
Those who don't
have power are weak,
and the weak die.
[gasps]
Impossible!
He can still move?
[MARS]
Give up!
You're a pathetic,
helpless little child.
You never stood a chance
of defeating me!
No, Asta!
[KLAUS]
This is our chance.
Asta's last slash dispelled
his Flame Recovery Magic.
We could finish
him off right now.
[LUCK]
Almost there.
A little longer and I'll
break through this binding.
[gasps]
Now, die!
Asta!
[YUNO] No matter which spell
I pull from my grimoire,
it'll be too late.
I can't let him die!
Not like this!
[yawns]
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[KLAUS]
What happened? Is it over?
Did Yuno finish him?
The binding spell--it's broken!
[KLAUS]
Yuno! What did you do?
[LUCK] Yeah, really.
What magic was that?
I don't know.
"Don't know"... What?
There was this tiny person.
A tiny person?
I think.
You must be tired.
We can discuss this later.
There will be time.
[KLAUS]
He's down now. For good.
[gasps]
[YUNO] This writing.
Is it from that scroll?
[gasps]
Asta!
Well... That's just great.
A trap spell?
The ceiling's caving.
It's going to collapse!
Celestial Wind Ark!
Everybody, get on!
[YUNO]
Time to leave.
Now, let's go!
Mimosa. Look after Asta!
I will!
[ASTA grunts]
You... You've got to...
[MIMOSA]
Please, don't speak.
[ASTA]
You've gotta... help him, too.
[gasps] What are
you saying, Asta?
Did you forget that he's
been trying to kill us?
We were sent here.
[grunts]
Sent to protect the
dungeon's treasure.
To...
To keep the things
here safe, not to kill.
[LUCK]
He's got a point.
It would be a shame
to let such a tough guy
just die like that, you know?
[MIMOSA, NOELLE gasp]
There's no time.
Leave him! Let's go!
[YUNO]
Where's the exit?
Mimosa can't keep healing
Asta and guide us out.
Make a right now.
I can guide us out of here.
Yeah? Sure.
Left here!
Okay.
[gasps]
[NOELLE gasps]
Okay, full speed ahead.
Got it!
[NOELLE]
Hah!
I hit it!
They're still coming.
[NOELLE]
Right. On it!
But you're my friend.
You're our friend.
So let us help!
[LUCK]
We've gotta save him.
[MIMOSA]
I won't let you die.
[NOELLE]
We will get him out alive.
[KLAUS]
Keep fighting.
[YUNO]
There's our exit!
We made it out!
That was so close!
Well, that was fun, huh?
Lunatic.
Let's head that way.
[LOTUS]
Excellent! I'm saved.
Very considerate of them to
forge a path for me like that.
Of course, it helped that
nobody could see me.
Hermit's Thick Smoke is
certainly a useful spell.
Right there all the time,
and not a single one
of them noticed.
Well, anyway, good thing
you didn't die back there.
That would have
been a real shame.
[FANA]
Mars. I'm sorry.
[MARS]
Fana?
This is the only way.
Now, die.
[panting]
[MARS wheezing]
[MARS screams]
Why did you...? Why, Fana?
[MARS]
But your wounds.
[FANA]
I had to do it, Mars. I'm sorry.
[MARS sobbing]
Fana...
[MARS]
Fana!
Fana.
[LOTUS] Oh? Finally waking
up over there, Mars?
Lotus?
That was some good
work you did, kid.
Just look at all the treasure
I was able to salvage
thanks to you.
Think of all the delicious food
this'll buy our
people back home.
My daughters will be eating
well after a haul like this.
[MARS]
It's coming back. All of it.
Now go see the outside world.
You've earned it.
Live your life, Mars.
For both of us.
[MARS]
Lotus?
[LOTUS]
Hm?
You saved me. Thank you.
Well, all right.
So it appears you
can say thank you.
[ASTA grunts]
[ASTA]
Hey, gang.
Asta!
Hi!
[KLAUS]
Hmph.
Welcome back!
Hey! You made it!
[ASTA groans]
Oh, ow, that hurts.
Uh-- Yes, well.
I suppose it's a good
thing you didn't die.
It was close for a while there,
but you recovered very quickly.
[YUNO] His sturdiness is about
all he's got going for him.
Hey, be nice to the injured guy.
I may not be a
lady-killer like you,
but I've got plenty
of good qualit--
[ASTA groans]
[MIMOSA]
I'm so sorry!
I didn't have enough magic
power to heal you completely.
It was more like first-aid,
so maybe don't move?
It's not that bad, really.
I'd be dead if it
weren't for you.
Thanks a lot.
[MIMOSA]
Oh, no, it's...
Sure.
[NOELLE]
Hm?
Ya know.
I was sure you were gonne
kick it before we got to fight.
Not a chance! No dyin' for me.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Not until I become
the Wizard King.
Poor Asta. You wish.
I am going to become
the Wizard King.
[groans]
Did I give you permission
to use me as a crutch?
C'mon, I'm just leanin'
here for a sec.
[KLAUS]
You two.
[YUNO]
Klaus, sir?
[KLAUS]
I have something to say.
I'm so very sorry!
--[ASTA] Uh--
--[YUNO gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[KLAUS] I rejected you both
because you're commoners,
and for that, I am ashamed.
You two are exemplary
Magic Knights.
The order is lucky to have you!
[YUNO]
Sir.
Sir?
[gasps]
[YUNO]
A bit too tight.
[ASTA] That kinda hurts,
Sir Spectacles.
[KLAUS] That again?
After everything I said?
[ASTA] You're right, I
should start callin' you
Mr. Softy Specs.
You truly don't know when
to quit, do you? Brat.
"Too serious" is
Klaus's natural state.
Hey, Yuno! Let's fight!
Ha! You want to?
Spar with me, please!
I'll pass.
[laughs]
[ASTA]
Noelle!
Looks like I'm not the
only one with torn clothes.
[MIMOSA]
Uh...
[NOELLE]
[NOELLE screams]
[ASTA yelps]
[LUCK]
Whoops! He's dead.
Are you okay?
Oh, no! What did I do?
I'm sorry! Hang in there.
Please wake up!
[grunts]
[laughs]
[BOTH gasp]
What are you looking at? Creep!
[ASTA yelps]
[NOELLE]
Hmph.
Ah...
[laughs]
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[LOTUS]
"So You Can Say It."
You saved me. Thank you, Lotus.
Well, all right.
So it appears you
can say thank you.
Yes, I can.
Then do you think
you can say this:
Peter Piper picked a peck
of pickled peppers.
Sally sells seashells
by the seashore.
Rubber baby buggy bumpers.
Yes, I can.
Peter pepper packed a...
Sally shells...
sells by the sheshore.
Rubber bubby baby...
I guess you can't say it.
Yes, I can.
Peter Piper pecked
a pick of-- Uh, uh...
Sally shell she shells by the--
Rubber babby boggy baby bump--
Fine, I can't!
[ASTA]
Yes! Did you see that?
I did it, Sister Lily!
Wait! I did what?!
Met the Wizard King?
Black Clover , page 20:
"Assembly at the Royal Capital."
My magic is being
super loud and annoying!