[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] With elf spirits
possessing the bodies
of Magic Knights
and attacking humans,
the royal capital found
itself mired in chaos.
Inside the Eye of the
Midnight Sun's hideout,
Luck and some of the
others turned against
their fellow Royal Knights,
and Asta's words
about finding common
ground weren't enough
to convince Rhya
to stop the violence
from unfolding further.
Let's foster understanding.
[RHYA] There were no lies
in anything that he said,
and so I trusted him.
And what did it get me?
That.
[RHYA] So, you see,
I'm done with trusting.
[rumbling]
Rill, is that you?
Hey, Rhya, good to see ya!
All of them, too?
[ZORA] We won't last five
minutes against them!
[NARRATOR] After pulling Asta
and Zora from the fight
for their own safety,
Mereoleona faced
their foes alone.
You seem like a benevolent
leader, Madam Royal.
[MEREOLEONA] You don't
understand a thing, do you?
I sent those novices home
because they were
getting in my way.
Slow you down?
Don't make me laugh.
I wanted the chance
to obliterate all
of you personally!
What in the world's
happening out there?
I'm not sure. All I know
is we have to keep
Sir Fuegoleon safe!
[CRIMSON LIONS groaning]
[RANDALL sighs] That's the
best you humans can do?
You're useless, even as a group!
What's gotten into you,
Vice Captain Randall?
Please stop this!
Not going to happen.
I'll keep fighting until
every one of you humans
is destroyed. And besides,
my name's not Randall,
so stop calling me that.
His magic power
is insanely strong!
[CRIMSON LION 98B]
It's no use. We're dead.
[CRIMSON LION 98C]
There's no way we can win!
Don't give me that!
[CRIMSON LIONS gasp]
[LEOPOLD]
Did you forget?
We were trained
by the two greatest
Magic Knight Captains
who ever lived!
We are the proud
and mighty squad
known as the Crimson Lion Kings!
Giving up and losing are
two things we don't do!
[RANDALL]
Are you sure about that?
I've saturated the entire
area with Air Magic.
And, as such, you can't
even cast a proper spell!
[LEOPOLD] Randall always used
to add air to my Flame Magic
to fan the fire and make
my abilities more powerful.
Who knew he would be
such a tough enemy!
Doesn't matter!
I'll win and bring you
back to your senses!
[LEOPOLD]
Focus.
[exhales]
[LEOPOLD]
Flame Magic: Spiral Flames!
Look at that. You did manage it.
But unfortunately,
I have Air Magic.
Air Blockade!
[gasps]
Don't bother with
those puny flames.
I'll just blow them
out like a candle!
Now, Air Magic: Crushing
Air Blast technique! Ha!
[LEOPOLD groans]
--[CRIMSON LIONS gasp]
--Leo!
[RANDALL]
Come on, be a good boy.
It'll be easier for everyone
if you would just
drop dead already.
[LEOPOLD grunts]
I'm not gonna lose!
The fire of the Crimson Lion
Kings can never be put out!
Not by you or anyone!
[CRIMSON LIONS gasp]
I'm with Leo on this one!
We'll combine the strength
of all of all our
senior-ranked mages!
Let's remind our vice captain
who he really is!
[CRIMSON LIONS]
Right!
Huh.
I say we start off with
my Iron Creation Magic:
Iron Bullet!
And Flame Magic: Burst Javelin!
Try Stone Magic:
Solid Rock spell!
We'll show you the valor
of the Crimson Lion Kings!
[GROUP yells]
[RANDALL sighs]
You humans are a stubborn bunch.
No matter how many of you
come at me at once,
you're all done for.
[yelling]
[yells]
You can't run!
It's time to take care
of the other side!
Air Magic: Explosive
Air Wave Palm!
[screams]
Forti!
[CRIMSON LIONS
yelling, grunting]
He's so fast!
[ROKKEN] He moves his body
through the sky by kicking,
then he attacks with invisible
chunks of the atmosphere itself!
Talk about a solid strategy.
No one can touch him!
[RANDALL]
Air Magic: Crushing Air Blast!
[ROKKEN groans]
Even a team of
senior-ranked mages
isn't enough to defeat him now!
If only Sir Fuegoleon
could help--
Don't say that!
Our skills are being
put to the test.
This time, we're the ones
who need to protect him.
[rumbling]
[GARETH]
Stay strong, mages.
if we can survive this barrage,
then we have a
chance to counter!
[RANDALL]
No, you won't. Found you.
[RANDALL sighs]
Trained by the best, eh?
It sure didn't help you much.
That's it!
[LEOPOLD yells]
[gasps]
[RANDALL] Thought you'd take
me by surprise, did you?
It seemed like you were
beginning to cooperate,
but you were just
waiting for your shot.
Here, this'll show you.
Now, Air Magic:
Crushing Air Blast!
[LEOPOLD]
Don't trust your eyes. Feel it!
[CRIMSON LIONS gasp]
He dodged it!
Well!
[LEOPOLD] With so much mana
here, the most effective way
to win against Air Magic
is to read the mana itself.
I may have been standing by,
but it wasn't out of fear!
I'm starting to
observe more and more.
I've come to understand
the calm within the flame!
Don't get cocky
over a little fluke.
Air Magic: Explosive
Air Wave Palm!
[yells]
Your attack hit mine head-on,
which cut their damages in half.
And, you immediately
cast that flame chaser
as I was dodging the impact.
[RANDALL]
Perhaps it wasn't a fluke, then.
Great skill and fast growth.
Just what I expect from
someone with royal blood.
[GARETH]
You can say that again.
[gasps]
Leo, there's no doubt
you're going to become
the leader of this
squad someday.
So let us buy you a little time.
Please get out of
this place and live;
take the wounded with you!
[LEOPOLD]
Guys, no! We're teammates.
I can stay and
fight by your side!
[GARETH]
Run! Hurry!
[ROKKEN]
Our squad's counting on you!
We are the honorable
and courageous
Crimson Lion Kings!
So for the sake of our comrades
and the nation we love,
we will eliminate this
threat without fear!
[CRIMSON LIONS shout]
Gareth! [pants]
I can't just abandon you.
We'll all survive
this battle together!
[LEOPOLD]
It's so close.
I can almost reach
out and touch it!
[RANDALL]
Hm...
[yells]
[LEOPOLD grunts]
[LEOPOLD]
But my body won't...
Leo!
[chuckles]
[CRIMSON LIONS groan]
[RANDALL] Your breakthrough came
a moment too late, I'm afraid.
As you can see by your
sudden inability to stand,
using an unfamiliar
fighting style like that
is a drain on the old stamina.
And you're supposed to
be their leader one day?
Well, I'll just ensure
that day never comes.
[LEOPOLD]
Dammit, no! Come on, body, move!
Don't do it!
[RANDALL] Soon. All humans
will die brutal deaths,
especially royals like you!
[LEOPOLD]
I won't give up. How could I?
I made a promise!
There's no way I'm gonna die!
Not now. Not here!
Come on. Please stand up!
[gasps]
[LEOPOLD] Whoa. What kinda
weird mana is this?
Where'd that come from?
[LEOPOLD]
More enemies? No.
It feels warm.
Like a flame that's
enveloping everything.
[gasps]
You've fought well,
Leo. I'm proud.
I can't believe you're here!
[ALL gasping]
But you have much to learn.
Stay back. I'll handle this.
Who are...?
[LEOPOLD]
That mana. It feels so familiar!
Salamander? How did you...?
[FUEGOLEON] As head of
the Crimson Lion Kings,
and as your older brother,
I will be bested no more!
Where am I?
[FUEGOLEON]
I feel it.
The blazing mana of
Leo and the others.
I have to come to their aid.
It's my responsibility,
both as a Magic Knight
and as the captain
of our brave squad.
[FUEGOLEON grunts]
Can you not endure?
Is this the extent of
your so-called power,
Fuegoleon Vermillion?
[gasps] Could this be the
Fire Spirit, Salamander?
[FUEGOLEON]
From now on,
I won't allow anyone
to stand in my way!
Though I may have lost my arm,
though flames may
scorch my body,
as long as there are
people waiting for me...
[FUEGOLEON] ...the captain
of the Crimson Lion Kings,
Fuegoleon Vermillion,
will press on!
[FUEGOLEON]
What's this?
[FUEGOLEON] It fills me
with both life and mana!
[FUEGOLEON]
Perhaps there's something left
that I'm meant to do. Is that
what you're telling me?
Fire Spirit. Mark my words.
I swear to use your power well.
I apologize for the delay.
It's all right!
I knew my brother wouldn't
let a scratch like that
keep him away forever!
[FUEGOLEON] All of you
have fought valiantly!
Even while I was
deep in slumber,
the brilliant blazing of your
mana was able to reach me!
[CRIMSON LIONS
laughing, cheering]
Thank goodness you're alive!
[LEOPOLD] Right. That's the
Fire Spirit, Salamander!
Asta said it used
to be partnered
with a top member of the
Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Then one day,
it just disappeared
in the middle of a battle!
[LEOPOLD] My brother
is honest and determined.
He has a trusted reputation
as a Grand Magic Knight
and the eldest son of the
royal House Vermillion!
When you put all
those things together,
why wouldn't Salamander
have wanted him?
[gasps] A human for a partner?
But how is that possible?
And a royal at that!
They're the most
corrupt of them all!
Randall!
I've just awakened,
so my flames may be unruly.
Stand firm so you
won't be consumed!
Is that so?
Even if you were
chosen by a Spirit,
you're still
pathetic human trash!
No matter what you do,
you'll never outmatch an elf!
You've got this!
Casting Flame Spirit Magic:
Salamander's Breath!
[RANDALL grunts]
[RANDALL]
These flames are too powerful.
I can't blow them out!
I'm about to choke
from the heat.
The air. He's taking
everything from me!
Agh. Damn you, royal!
Now, Flame Binding
Magic: Leo Palma!
I had to stamp out this evil,
even if the vice captain's
body was damaged.
You're back!
Thank you!
We're saved!
[CRIMSON LION 98M]
Sir Fuegoleon!
[CRIMSON LION 98N]
You really are the greatest
Magic Knight there is!
Hurry! Help the injured!
[GARETH]
Right!
[LEOPOLD] That was awesome!
My brother's still got it!
I'm gonna be even better
one of these days, though!
[FUEGOLEON]
As your captain, I solemnly vow
that you will be returned
to your former self.
[LEOPOLD] Oh, yeah, while
you were out of commission,
our sister became the captain.
She what? Is this true?
Um. Yes, sir.
[CRIMSON LIONS]
That's what happened,
Former Captain Fuegoleon!
[FUEGOLEON grunts]
[FUEGOLEON]
Our sister, eh?
She should have been our
captain in the first place.
But she couldn't
even be bothered
to join the Magic Knights.
Seems I've forced her
to act out of character.
[FUEGOLEON] Salamander has made
me aware of the sinister,
non-human magic
power that's been
permeating the royal capital.
While I've been asleep,
the situation's
intensified a great deal.
[FUEGOLEON]
When the Eye of the Midnight Sun
ransacked the city that day,
I knew that I was the person
they were targeting.
That's why I decided to play
right into their hands.
[FUEGOLEON]
Strange. What is this place?
It's you!
[FUEGOLEON]
This mana. William Vangeance?
I don't understand.
It appears you've arrived.
I had hoped you would
surmise our plan
and not come here.
I prayed for that.
Please explain yourself!
Tell me the truth! What plan?
You will see,
quite soon, in fact.
What is happening to you?
[PATRY, WILLIAM]
No one knows my secret.
Not even the Wizard King,
who gave me my mask.
[PATRY]
But you will understand things
when you see the other me.
Enough of this nonsense,
who are you?
And what have you
done to William?
Interesting. The captain
of the Crimson Lion Kings.
You're normally so collected,
but now even you seem shaken.
All I need is an instant.
[FUEGOLEON]
I have so many questions.
Why didn't he kill me
when he had the chance?
Who was that person, and
what has become of William?
However, I won't breathe
a word of this matter
until I can ascertain the truth.
Crimson Lion Kings!
Clover Kingdom is
in grave danger!
We must end this bloodshed!
With the fires of strength
and pride that burn deep
within our hearts, we will
strive to vanquish the enemy!
[CRIMSON LIONS]
Yeah!
[FUEGOLEON] The real fight
is just beginning.
[BAVAL] Hm? These outfits
are awfully similar
to the garment worn
by that human royal.
That's strange, isn't it?
I'm sure the person
who gathered us here
made that decision. Talk about
a sick sense of humor.
I'm not sure I follow you.
They expect us to wipe out
the human race, obviously.
Right, that's simple enough.
After all, the humans killed us,
and they've been living
the good life ever since,
without a care in the world!
We've got more than enough
reason to be upset,
if you ask me.
Oh, I see you made it.
[LANGRIS] Well, well, well!
The gang's all here.
I was trapped in a pretty
strange place when I awakened,
but I had fun getting out.
Humans infuriate me.
Always so smug
in their stupidity.
I'm assuming your
cousin was the one
who brought us together,
right, Latry?
Correct, this is
all Patry's doing.
Birds of a twisted feather
flock together, I suppose.
I know I'm itching
to get my hands
around the throats of those
despicable royal scum!
The Midnight Sun has set.
It's time to show
humankind the wrath
of a brand-new Golden Dawn!
[LANGRIS]
Brother. Are you there?
[FINRAL] Langris? You're back
to normal! I'm so glad!
[FINRAL]
Huh? Wait up! Hey, come back!
Please don't leave! Langris!
[FINRAL grunts]
[FINRAL]
Ow!
What the heck was that?
And where am I?
Is my name even Finral anymore?
How long were you plannin'
to snooze, numbskull?
[FINRAL]
Captain Yami?!
[YAMI]
As you can see,
things aren't goin'
too well out there.
You felt it, right?
That evil, inhuman power
that your brother
was givin' off?
The stuff is everywhere now.
Okay, then. Let's go.
[FINRAL] Langris. I'm gonna
save you this time!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[FUEGOLEON]
"Waking Up."
[CRIMSON LION 98AA]
Sir Fuegoleon!
[CRIMSON LION 98A]
Thank goodness you're awake now!
I believe there's
something I'm meant to do!
[CRIMSON LIONS]
Right!
[CRIMSON LION 98A]
Wait, what?
[NARRATOR] Fuegoleon Vermillion:
a man who refuses to suffer
a single misplaced hair!
[CRIMSON LION 98AA] Um,
not that it matters right now,
but your hair looks great!
In that case,
there's something else
I'm meant to do!
[CRIMSON LIONS]
Right!
[CRIMSON LION 98A]
Come on, seriously?
[NARRATOR] Fuegoleon Vermillion:
a man who lovingly brushes
every tooth not once,
but three times!
[CRIMSON LION 98AA]
Okay, I'm sure your mouth
is clean enough, sir!
Well then, there's yet another
thing I'm meant to do!
Five more minutes, please.
[CRIMSON LIONS]
All right, this is ridiculous!
[NARRATOR] Fuegoleon Vermillion:
a man who diligently
achieves his beauty rest and--
Enough of this foolishness--
this is no laughing matter.
[FUEGOLEON]
I am the steadfast captain
of the Crimson Lion Kings.
Fuegoleon Vermillion!
Black Clover , Page 99:
"The Desperate Path
Toward Survival."
I'm sorry. Did you just
call me "Former Captain"?