[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy
who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world,
and to become the
next Wizard King!
[NARRATOR] In preparation
for the coming war
with the Spade Kingdom, Asta and
his comrades train diligently
with the Heart Kingdom's
Spirit Guardians.
Now halfway into
their training period,
the Magic Knights have learned
the Heart Kingdom's Mana Method
and are growing steadily.
Since Asta has no magic,
he sparred with Gaja,
seeking insights that might
lead to a new technique.
Meanwhile, in the
Clover Kingdom,
Yami finally learned the
trick to using Mana Zone.
[NARRATOR]
And now...
[ASTA]
Gaja! Guess who's back for more?
Very impressive.
It seems you've grown quite
a bit these past few days.
Yeah!
Yesterday, I had a scrap
with the Wind Spirit Guardian.
He helped me train my ki,
so I'm way better at
reading sneaky attacks now.
And today, I fought the
Earth Spirit Guardian,
and she has super sharp
senses and she helped me
hone my fighting
instincts like "wa-bam!"
Wait, I thought you
were supposed to be
training with Luck?
He's taking some time
to see what he can learn
from the other Spirit
Guardians, so it's just me.
I came at the right time then.
Spar with me! I wanna
try out what I've learned.
I'm perfectly willing
to fight more.
But before we start,
let's talk a bit.
Even by arcane stage standards,
a mage who has no magic
is quite the anomaly.
What's even stranger about
you is the astounding rate
at which you've grown.
So that I might aid
you on your quest
for even greater strength, I'd
like to ask you some questions.
Please tell me about your
life up until this point.
And share whatever you know
about the devil
in your grimoire.
Okay then. This
might take a while.
[ASTA]
Father Orfai says he took in me
and my childhood friend
Yuno on the same day.
We were just babies when
were dropped on his doorstep
in Hage village, on the
outskirts of the Clover Kingdom.
Time passed, and
eventually, we grew up.
[ASTA]
Sister Lily!
Will you please marry me?
[ASTA] In those days, I lived
with my beloved Sister Lily,
Yuno,
and all the other orphaned kids.
Back then, my biggest problem
was that I couldn't
use any magic at all.
While Yuno's got so much of the
stuff, he does laundry with it.
[ASTA]
That's right!
I'm gonna get the most
awesome grimoire ever!
I'll join up with
the Magic Knights,
and once I make
a name for myself,
I'll follow in your footsteps
and become the Wizard King!
[ASTA] Each March, kids turning
15 gather from all over
the kingdom to be given
grimoires, and Yuno and I
were finally old enough
to receive our own.
[ASTA]
But...
Hey, uh...
Is my grimoire running
late or something?
[TOWER MASTER]
Er... Try again next year?
What?!
[laughs] Oh, wow,
you're kidding!
[TEEN BOY 1J]
That's actually kinda awesome.
[ASTA] Yuno ended up getting
a four-leaf grimoire,
just like the
First Wizard King had.
[ASTA]
I was so sure, all this time.
I just needed a grimoire,
and then I'd finally
be able to use magic.
And now, to not even
get a grimoire.
[ASTA]
No! I won't give up that easily!
[laughs] You're not winning
this round, fate.
Don't underestimate me!
It doesn't matter if it takes
a year, or two, or ten,
or 100! I don't care!
I'll work till
I get that grimoire!
[ASTA] But then this thieving
jerk showed up outta nowhere
and attacked Yuno
with his Chain Magic.
He stole Yuno's grimoire
and was planning to sell it.
[REVCHI]
Oh-ho.
I bet that pendant would
fetch a good price.
Don't mind if I do.
[ASTA]
Hold it!
[ASTA] I fought hard to
get Yuno's grimoire back,
but despite all my training,
I was no match for
the thief's magic.
He taunted me
for my helplessness,
saying that his chains could
measure anyone's magic power
and that I didn't
have a single drop.
[REVCHI] This world has
no use for someone like you,
a poor, magic-less fool.
You might as well give
it all up right now.
You were born a loser,
you worthless runt.
[ASTA]
Yeah. He's right.
No matter how hard I try,
I guess there are some things
that just aren't possible.
So... I might as well give u--
[YUNO] Hey! Who are
you calling a loser?
Asta, it's true that you
aren't going to become
the Wizard King. Not ever.
[REVCHI]
You hear that?
Even your little friend
knows that it's impossible.
That's because I am going
to be the Wizard King.
[REVCHI]
What?
You're wrong about Asta,
Revchi. Very wrong.
Asta's no loser. He's my rival!
[ASTA gasps]
Huh? This is who you
would claim as your rival?
The only person in the
world without magic?
You. Get off of me.
[REVCHI gasps]
[ASTA] Sorry you had to see me
at such a weak moment, Yuno.
Just give me a second.
[ASTA] That's all.
Then I'll destroy this guy.
[ASTA] And then,
right when I needed it,
the five-leaf grimoire,
said to have a devil inside it,
appeared in front of me.
Back then, I didn't
know anything about
the devil's powers
or the Anti-magic
that I was about to use.
I was offered a sword,
and I took it.
[ASTA]
So, yeah.
That's more or less
the whole story
of how I came to be the
wielder of this grimoire.
After that, me and Yuno left.
We took the Magic Knights
Entrance exam at the capital.
Yuno ended up joining the most
powerful and popular squad,
the Golden Dawn.
I was almost sent home
since I had no
magic to speak of.
But then Captain Yami
let me join the Black Bulls.
If I'm remembering correctly,
the captain of the Black Bulls
fights with a sword,
just like you.
Yeah! He takes a crazy
long time to poop,
but he still manages to be there
for us when we need him!
He's really strong,
and it's thanks to him
that I can use my ki.
The point is that he's someone I
have a whole lot of respect for!
Once the rest of the
Black Bulls accepted me
as a part of the squad,
I got my cape and embarked
on my first official mission.
That took me and my
squadmates to the dungeon
where I found my second weapon:
the Demon-Dweller Sword.
We also faced off with
one of the Diamond Kingdom's
Eight Shining Generals, Mars.
This guy was an
insanely strong mage
who had two different
magical attributes.
It was during that battle
that I realized:
[ASTA] I may not have any magic
power, but what I do have
are my friends!
[ASTA] I borrowed mana
from Noelle and released it
using the Demon-Dweller Sword.
And that was enough to break
through Mars's diamond armor.
Afterwards, when we reported
back on the mission,
we met the Wizard King.
"Get results.
A noble heart alone
can't protect anyone.
And the trust of the people
is earned, not granted."
With the Wizard King's
words in my heart,
I protected whoever I could
and I beat lots of bad guys.
But then, I met
a bad guy like no other.
[PATRY] I haven't introduced
myself yet, have I?
I am the leader of the
Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Call me Licht.
[ASTA] His light magic
was insanely fast.
It was able to hit me
before I could react
or even see it coming.
But thankfully, Captain Yami
showed up to save me.
He faced Licht head on,
batting his light magic away
like it was nothing.
I always knew Yami was
strong, but watching him
fight Licht proved it
in a whole new way!
[YAMI]
Hey, kid! Were you watching?
Uh, yes, Captain!
[YAMI]
That's good.
Because now it's your turn.
Yes, sir!
Wait, what did you say?
There's no way I can do that!
Yeah? Last I checked,
I was still your captain.
Which means, if I tell you
to do something, you do it.
Assuming you wanna be a
real man someday, Shrimpsta.
[ASTA] Captain Yami told me that
he wasn't just reacting
to Licht's attacks,
he was predicting them
by sensing Licht's "ki."
"A person's glance, their
breathing, their scent,
the way their muscles move,
the hint of their presence.
Taken together, all of that
living energy people give off.
That's called ki."
All I've been doing
is reading his ki
and using it to
predict his moves.
You've never done
anything like that before?
[gasps] Actually, yeah.
[ASTA] The captain's
lesson was so intense
that I could've died
in the middle of it.
But in the end,
I learned how to sense ki.
How interesting.
This "ki" sensing technique
seems to be well-suited
to a warrior who lacks
magic such as yourself.
Your Captain Yami
must have anticipated
that such a tool
would prove useful
as you improve your Anti-magic.
Come to think of it, yeah,
you're probably right.
Oh! Holy crap!
Captain Yami's so friggin' cool!
Though it's possible I'm
simply overthinking this.
By the way, there's another
question I'd like to ask you.
[gasps]
It's a simple one.
What do you have to do to enter
that special fighting state
where the power of your devil
manifests in your body?
Heh. Funny story.
The first time
I took on that form
was in the Forest of Witches,
after visiting the
queen who rules there.
I was fighting
this smirky creep
from the Diamond Kingdom
who had attacked the forest.
[ASTA]
My magic is never giving up!
Damn you! It can't be!
My magic should have
made me invincible!
[ASTA]
To be honest,
I didn't understand what
was happening any better
than the guy I was fighting did.
[LADROS]
No! No, no, no, no, no, no!
It's not fair!
I stepped on so many people
to get to where I am now!
I can't lose to you!
[ASTA] You always kicked
your friends down,
but my friends
helped me be better.
Stronger!
[ASTA]
Black Meteorite!
[LADROS screams]
[ASTA] I didn't figure out
how to take that form at will
till I was at Yultim Volcano,
a strong magic region
we went to for a training camp.
Since I couldn't use
mana skin, a technique
where you protect your body
by wrapping it in mana.
I was stopped in my tracks
by the super intense heat.
But then I realized something!
I could use the ki technique
I had learned from Captain Yami
to amplify the Anti-magic
inside my body
and create an Anti-magic
version of Mana Skin
that worked just as well!
And with that same method,
I can enter that
heightened state of being
anytime I want to!
I'm a lucky guy!
Captain Yami's done
so much for me!
I don't know what I
would've done if he had
never taught me
how to use my ki!
For real!
Check out this sword.
The Demon-Destroyer Sword.
It's a pretty wild one,
but thanks to my ki,
I can handle it.
I hear that sword goes beyond
nullifying magic itself.
It can also reverse
the effects of a spell.
Such a power has
great potential.
Yup!
I got the Demon-Destroyer
Sword around the time
we launched our attack on the
Eye of the Midnight Sun's base.
This was just before
our final battle with them.
[ASTA] Things were going well,
but then that "Disloyal" guy
fully reincarnated
and attacked us,
along with some of our
newly possessed friends.
Not long after that,
we ended up fighting the leader
of the elves in the
center of their base.
[ASTA]
His ki.
[YUNO]
That sword's got massive power!
[ASTA]
Uh-oh.
I can't stay in this
form much longer.
Come on, just a little more!
Asta. Careful, all right?
Yeah. I know that.
[YUNO]
Asta!
[ASTA] It turned out that
the leader of the elves
was the original
owner of my swords,
so he was able to use
their full power.
On top of that,
he was insanely strong.
But...
[ASTA]
I'm not done yet!
You're not killin' Yuno!
Or Asta, either!
[BOTH]
He's my rival!
[ASTA]
Even with Yuno, I couldn't win.
But when I least expected it,
the Demon-Destroyer Sword
I had picked up became
a part of my grimoire.
Thanks to that,
I was able to nullify the
Poison magic that was used
on the people of Hage Village
and return everyone who
had been reincarnated
into elves back to normal.
[ASTA] Afterwards,
in the Shadow Palace,
the memories that the
Demon-Destroyer had absorbed
flooded into me.
That's when I found out about
the massacre of the elves.
And not long after, I learned
that all the chaos, violence,
and hatred I had just witnessed
had a single source.
It all began with a devil.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Word Soul Magic:
"Voizuiinemidoren."
[ASTA] His goal was to leave
the world that devils come from
and appear in ours
in his full form,
with nothing to hold him back.
I couldn't let that
bastard have his way.
I had to stop him!
[ASTA] If Yuno could evolve,
then so could I!
[ASTA] Anti-Magic Demon
Slayer Sword: Black Divider!
[BOTH yell]
[YAMI] Dark Cloaked,
Dimension Slash: Equinox!
[ASTA] Nero used her
Sealing Magic to lock away
the damage I had taken.
Asta.
Remember.
You're going to be
the Wizard King!
Yeah!
[ASTA]
Right here, right now.
I'm going to push
past my limits!
[ASTA] I'm pretty sure
you know the rest.
I was put on trial for
cooperating with a devil,
but they set me free in the end.
I came here to the Heart Kingdom
to investigate a devil's curse,
hoping it would help me prove
my innocence back home.
Then I found out
that the devil's curse
in the Heart Kingdom is on
Queen Loropechika herself.
I will get stronger,
'cause that's my
only path forward.
I'll protect all
the people I can.
Back home.
And here in the
Heart Kingdom, too.
I'm glad that you allowed
me to hear your tale.
It was truly enlightening.
I finally understand how
you became so powerful,
despite the fact that you're
utterly spurned by mana.
[GAJA]
Now, let us begin.
The sun will be setting shortly,
but we can spar nonetheless.
I'll train you
as long as you'd like.
In the dark, if need be.
Ooh, right!
[NOELLE yells]
[yells]
Excellent! Noelle, that
was a sight to behold!
You put on quite the show.
I think anyone could see
that you've improved
since you first arrived here.
Well, since I'm royalty myself,
I'm a fairly quick study.
[NOELLE]
I can't believe it!
She actually praised me!
In truth, you're the
one who's amazing,
Water Spirit Undine.
You keep finding new ways
to draw out more and more
of my water magic.
[giggles] Thank you
for the compliment,
but you aren't the only
one who's growing fast.
Take a look at this.
[LOROPECHIKA]
It's not just you and Nero.
Your comrades from the
Clover Kingdom are learning
Heart Kingdom techniques faster
than we ever could've imagined.
They're all getting stronger
just as fast as you are.
We may be fast, but we
still aren't as strong
as we need to be to defeat
the devil in the Spade Kingdom.
Right?
Yes. You're exactly right.
That said, I have complete
faith in each of you.
The Magic Knights
who are training
so diligently here, and your
comrades who stayed behind
to help prepare the
Clover Kingdom for war.
If we all work together,
then in time,
a ray of hope will break through
the Spade Kingdom Devil's
cloud of despair.
In fact, I'm certain
that we'll win.
[NOELLE] And when we do,
I'll avenge my mother.
[yells]
You shouldn't expect the
same trick to work twice.
[ASTA screams]
That move is strong,
but as it is now,
you can only land a hit
with it reliably
if you catch your
opponent by surprise.
Seems we'll finish before dark.
[GAJA]
Lightning Magic: Tenjiolia.
Not yet!
[NARRATOR]
The leaves of a clover are said
to each contain one thing.
In the first three dwell
integrity, hope, and love.
The fourth leaf is given
over to good luck.
[gasps]
[NARRATOR] And in the fifth,
there lives a devil.
[panting]
[ASTA]
Wait, my sword?
What the--?
Your capacity for growth
continues to surprise me.
In order to reveal the extent
of your hidden powers.
I'll attack you with
everything I have.
That is, if you think
you can withstand more.
Yeah, gimme
everything you've got!
[yells]
Things are starting
to get interesting now.
[laughs]
[ASTA] Our training's finished,
and it's finally time
to fight the Spade Kingdom.
Next time on
Black Clover , Page 158:
"The Beginning of
Hope and Despair."
I'll protect everyone
in the Clover Kingdom,
and everyone in the
Heart Kingdom, too!