[NARRATOR] Within the clover's
fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
[NARRATOR] Asta, born
unable to harness mana,
was granted the
power of Anti-magic
from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability
to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members
of Spade Kingdom's
Dark Triad also possess
powers from the devils
of the underworld and used them
to launch an invasion on
the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from
his belief in himself
and from the support
of his friends,
Asta continues to fight
for the safety of this world.
I don't care how fast
or determined you are,
it won't help you now.
[SVENKIN]
Skin Magic: Skin Fort!
[LUCK]
True Lightning Magic: Ceranos!
[NARRATOR] Svenkin,
a Dark Disciple who attacked
the Heart Kingdom
under Vanica's command,
was soundly defeated by Luck.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, the Black
Bulls' hideout was ambushed
by Dante, one of the Dark Triad.
[ASTA]
Don't do it!
--[VANESSA] Oh, no!
--[GREY] He hurt Gauche!
[NARRATOR]
With an unknown spell,
Grey rescued Gauche
from the brink of death.
Grey...
[VANESSA]
She sealed the wound!
I didn't know her Transformation
Magic could do that!
[VANESSA]
What is this spell?
[ASTA roars]
[NARRATOR] Asta was enraged
by his friends' suffering,
and his devil's power
went berserk,
but it wasn't enough
to stop Dante.
[DANTE chuckles]
Magnificent!
Yet another
arcane-stage fighter.
[NARRATOR] Seeing Vanessa
and Grey's potential,
Dante tried to take them.
Then, Yami returned
to the hideout.
[YAMI]
Hey!
That's my squad, so keep
your mitts off of 'em.
[NARRATOR] But the captain had
been Dante's target all along.
He believed Yami was
the key to connecting
this world with the underworld.
[YAMI]
If they're "arcane-stage,"
that's the first
I've heard about it.
And they're not
here to serve me.
I just brought 'em on
because I liked 'em.
[YAMI]
Mana Zone: Condense.
Dark Cloaked, Iai Slash.
They're not going anywhere.
Not with you, y'damn freak.
[DANTE groans]
[DEVIL]
Kill.
I'll kill them. Kill them all!
They must pay!
Kill. Kill!
Hold on. Killing?
[DEVIL]
Kill them all!
[ASTA grunts]
[ASTA]
What the heck just happened?
My body won't move at all.
Wait, what about Gauche?
[ASTA sighs]
I can still sense his ki.
Good, he's alive!
[ASTA]
That jerk from Spade.
[YAMI] Using my Iai blade,
if I cast Mana Zone
with condensed mana...
[YAMI]
...then it'll never miss.
[DANTE]
Oh... [chuckles]
[DANTE laughs]
I'm surprised.
I never thought anyone would
make me use this magic.
[DANTE laughs]
[YAMI]
What in the world is he doing?
[VANESSA]
This is completely different
from the techniques
he was using before!
What's going on?
All this envy,
and rage, and hatred.
I can't get enough of it!
Color me impressed,
Yami Sukehiro!
[DANTE] I was bored with
absolutely everything.
[DANTE] There was
nothing in this world...
[CROWD cheering]
[DANTE] ...that could slake
this extreme malice.
Yami, my friend.
Believe me, this is only the
beginning of what's in store.
You're going to open up a
brand-new world for me soon.
Stop it, man,
you're creepin' me out.
And that goatee looks awful.
You said somethin' about
me bein' the key
to the underworld, but I got no
idea what you're talkin' about.
Pretty sure I'm not
that special, pal.
Don't flatter yourself.
The key to the underworld
isn't you, per se.
It's a magical channel
known as the Tree of Qliphoth.
To bring that channel into
being, we need Dark Magic
and World Tree Magic,
both at the arcane stage.
Which means...
...that the crucial players here
are you and William Vangeance.
[YAMI] So, this guy knows
about William's magic.
All right, let's say
we do connect this world
to the underworld,
then what happens?
[DANTE] Then, this realm will
become infested with devils.
[YAMI gasps]
[DANTE]
And once they've taken over...
[DANTE cackles]
[DANTE]
...every possible kind of malice
will descend upon this land!
[DANTE cackles]
And that's sure to be
awfully entertaining.
Right, Yami Sukehiro?
[YAMI]
That's it.
No more chit-chat.
I'm taking you down
here and now!
These jerks are burning
the forest, which means
they're destroying the food,
and there's no way
I'm gonna let that happen!
[gasps]
[HALBET giggles]
O lovely flames, engulf me
and my gorgeous
hair in your warmth!
[VILLAGER 164A]
No. The Polnfrume Forest.
[VILLAGER 164B]
We're done for!
They took down
a Spirit Guardian!
If Sir Potrof
hadn't shielded us,
we would all be dead!
[HALBET]
Consider yourselves lucky.
It's true that you're
about to die, but at least
the immaculate beauty of
Dark Disciple Halbet Chevour
is the last thing you'll see.
[CHARMY]
What do you think you're doing?
Oh?
It seems an unsightly
fatty has arrived.
[VILLAGER 164C]
Sir Potrof! Charmy's here!
[POTROF]
Charmy.
Hey, it's Charmy!
Well, how about that?
Did you sneak away
from your training again?
Do you wanna take a snack break?
I can tell how incredibly
talented you are!
Let's do our best!
You won't get away with this.
[GIANT SHEEP bleets]
That's her magical sheep!
Save us, Charmy!
Heh. Looks like your
magic is as soft as you.
Our spells are passing
right through each other.
Perhaps this is what they mean
when they say "affinity."
[GIANT SHEEP bleets]
But there's one major
difference here.
[HALBET]
My magic is able to protect me
from incoming attacks.
[HALBET] But yours
doesn't shield you at all,
so you're wide open!
[HALBET]
Thanks to the devil's power,
my hair isn't just
devastatingly beautiful.
It's also impossibly strong!
[BOTH]
Charmy!
[HALBET] That roly-poly little
body of yours has no chance
of wiggling away from me.
Why bother with food?
Eating is a foolish
waste of time.
I've found all you really need
for maximum beauty and strength
is the proper nutrition!
Anyway, your fatness
is an eyesore.
So I will embrace you
with my beauty as you die!
[CHARMY]
Hey.
Didn't I tell you
when I got here?
[WOLF growls]
I won't let you
get away with this!
[CHARMY]
Hey.
Didn't I tell you
when I got here?
[WOLF growls]
I won't let you
get away with this!
[WOLF growls]
What is that?
She doesn't even
have devil powers.
How is she doing this?
[CHARMY]
Food Magic: Glutton's Banquet!
[WOLF growls]
[gasps]
Seems like we've got a slippery
opponent on our hands.
Well, then.
[HALBET gasps]
[CHARMY]
I'll just cook her!
What?
[coughs] What's happening?
[CHARMY]
The Mana Method is my kitchen.
And when I use it
to cook something...
[screams]
[CHARMY]
...any dish becomes delicious!
And my wolf is sure
to scarf it down!
[HALBET screaming]
Charmy is terrifying.
I can't believe she was capable
of this much destruction!
[WOLF growls]
[HALBET] How dare you do such
a thing to someone so gorgeous?
This looks pretty tasty!
Here we go. Down the hatch!
[HALBET screams]
[CHARMY] This is what you get
for disrespecting food!
The only way to get
true beauty and strength
is from a balanced diet!
Thank you for saving us!
You ate that witch for dinner!
[TOWNSPERSON 164A]
They took down Sir Floga,
the Fire Spirit Guardian!
[TOWNSPERSON 164B] Even he
couldn't beat these guys.
I don't think I've ever seen
a technique like that before.
How would you even dodge it?
[TOWNSPERSON 164A] That young
man from the Clover Kingdom
doesn't stand a chance.
[LEOPOLD panting]
[LEOPOLD grunts]
[LEOPOLD]
Where are you?
[SIVOIR]
Well, he's resilient.
That strike didn't
even pierce his body.
But how long can he last?
His mana is dwindling
away by the second.
Wherever you run,
pathetic little neophyte,
you'll never escape
being riddled with holes
by Dark Disciple Sivoir Snyle!
[SIVOIR]
I'm using an Eye Magic spell
called Catoblepas's Evil Eye.
My eyes are everywhere.
Not only can they track you,
but they gauge your
mana and stamina.
And, by watching your
eyeline and muscle movement,
I can predict what
you'll do next!
Once I've locked onto my target,
I'll fire using the shells
that I make from condensed mana.
[SIVOIR cackles]
[SIVOIR]
And these things never miss!
[LEOPOLD grunts]
Damn it.
[LEOPOLD]
Floga's down.
I think you'll get
better results
if you try to focus
on your strengths.
My strengths? Like what?
You're the kind of
person who has
the strength to endure anything.
I mean, you're you, right?
[LEOPOLD] I just have
to sharpen my senses!
There you are!
[LEOPOLD] Flame Magic:
Profound Spiral Flames!
[panting]
Did you really think
that I wouldn't
be able to dodge that, you fool?
It doesn't matter
what clever tricks
the Heart Kingdom
taught you, it's no use!
[LEOPOLD grunts]
[LEOPOLD]
It took him a little longer
to throw something
at me this time.
That's because he had to take
a second to evade my attack.
Feel free to keep moving
in closer all you want.
I'll just keep
creating distance.
[LEOPOLD grunting]
[LEOPOLD]
That's what I thought.
We're both moving, but we're
not any farther apart.
He's getting as far away
from me as possible,
but staying in range to fight.
No one's ever been able
to injure me in a battle.
In fact, I've never
even felt any pain.
So, a mere simpleton
like you would be foolish
to believe he could land
a single hit against me.
[LEOPOLD grunts]
Don't give up.
I have to endure
until I bring him down!
You don't know when
to quit, do you?
Just roll over and die.
[gunshots]
[LEOPOLD grunts]
[LEOPOLD]
It's true.
I may not have as much talent
as my older brother and sister.
But, with them to look up to,
I've held strong and let
my inner flame keep blazing!
You realize that
endurance isn't enough
to win, don't you?
Time to finish this.
[SIVOIR]
Hold on.
Where is he?
[SIVOIR]
What?
Where did that enormous
array come from?
When did he have a chance to--?
I endured you
so that I could take
my time creating it.
And I did the whole
thing while you were
so focused on keeping
your eyes on me.
[SIVOIR] No! I have
to get out of this array!
[yelps]
[LEOPOLD]
True Flame Magic:
Crimson Eruption!
[TOWNSPEOPLE gasp]
[TOWNSPERSON 164C]
Whoa.
That's the biggest array
I've ever seen in my life!
[SIVOIR screams]
It's gonna burn me to a crisp!
I never learned how
to deal with pain!
I've gone my entire life
without enduring so
much as a scratch!
How dare you do this to me?!
[LEOPOLD]
Thanks for making so much noise!
Now I know exactly
where you are!
[SIVOIR gasps]
You don't get to whine
about the pain you're in
after all the suffering
you've caused!
No! Stop!
If you're not tough enough
to handle getting burned,
then don't play with an inferno!
[TOWNSPEOPLE murmuring]
[GAJA] You're finished
here, Dark Disciple.
Amazing!
Thank you, Sir Gaja!
[SARADO] I've gotta
hand it to you, Gaja.
You really are an
incredible fighter,
even among the Guardians!
[GAJA] I didn't think
I would make it in time.
Now I need to get
everyone to safety
and return to Queen Loropechika!
[LOROPECHIKA] They defeated
all the Dark Disciples!
Excellent fighting, everyone!
Yeah, whatever. I guess
they did all right.
That was amazing. I'm so
happy they're all okay!
[LOROPECHIKA] I'm grateful
they could defend the places
where my water couldn't reach.
[LOROPECHIKA] No matter
how strong their foes are,
the Clover Kingdom Magic Knights
evolve their skills to match,
even mid-combat!
[ALL gasp]
[ROBERO cackles]
[ROBERO]
Oh, my!
I sense the mana of some
delicious ladies in here!
We knew you'd
show up eventually.
That's right, we're prepared!
[ROBERO yelps]
[MIMOSA] Plant Magic:
Magic Cannon Flower!
[MIMOSA] Serves you right
for being creepy!
That was a wonderful
technique, Mimosa!
It wouldn't have been possible
without all that
mana you sent me!
[gasps]
[VANICA]
Yoo-hoo!
[NOELLE]
This mana--it's so sinister!
I haven't seen you in so long.
So I came to play!
Happy to see me,
little Loropechika?
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[LEOPOLD]
The Strength to Endure.
I bet you're gettin' close
to the end of your
rope, huh, Charmy?
The heck are
you talking about?
This is easy-breezy!
[ASTA] You don't need to
push yourself either, Leo.
Don't be ridiculous!
Floga showed me how
to maximize my endurance,
and I'm gonna use those lessons
to defeat you. Wait and see!
[ALL groaning]
[ASTA]
So hot!
[LEOPOLD]
Need water!
[ALL gasp]
Go ahead and hop on out, Charmy.
N-Nobody's gonna
judge you, I promise!
No way, you're the one
who needs to get out!
You look like a
big angry popsicle!
[ASTA] L-Leo, didn't y-you say
you're not good with the c-cold?
I've got the strength to endure!
They're so lively!
[LOROPECHIKA]
Vanica, I won't let you
have your way any longer!
Because now, I have friends
I can depend on to help!
Black Clover , Page 165:
"Water Crusade."
Today is the day
we end this fight!