[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] Asta lost the use
of his arms after Vetto
cast an ancient hex on him.
His only hope of lifting
the curse lies with
the Queen of the Forest
of Witches. But...
The Queen is more deadly
than you can imagine.
So much so that
the Diamond Kingdom
won't even try to
stand against her.
And there's no hope of
reasoning with her, either.
[NOELLE]
We're going.
Whatever it takes for us
to heal Asta's arms.
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, Vanessa, who hails
from said Forest, had also
returned there in hopes
of bargaining for
Asta's healing.
[DOMINANTE]
Over there!
[FINRAL, ASTA, FANZELL yelling]
[NARRATOR] But when Asta
and his friends finally
reached the Queen's palace...
Take your foot off of her!
She's one of us!
So leave her alone!
Pitiful fools.
What could such imperfect
creatures possibly
hope to do for her?
[gasps]
I didn't expect it
to happen so soon.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun.
The Midnight Sun?
Why would they come here?
You're not just making up
stories to trick us
into not attacking you, right?
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Imperfect.
What?
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
If I were so inclined,
I could obliterate
every last one of you
with naught but
a snap of my fingers.
Why would I bother
deceiving you?
[BOTH gasp]
[ASTA]
It's her! From Nean!
The Third Eye is bad news.
That big hairy guy
that messed up my arms
was one of them, too!
Then it's safe to say she's
just as strong as he was.
She might even be stronger.
[FINRAL]
This is not good!
I'm always getting
caught up in these things!
Let them come.
My superior power
will vanquish those
imperfect fools with
perfect grace.
Go, tell my children!
A witch who absconded with
one of the magic stones
is somewhere within
those woods as we speak.
And those vicious humans
who took Vetto's life
are in there, as well.
That's true!
They must have been
alerted to the presence
of the magic stone.
They will pay!
I'll destroy everything
and secure the magic stone.
[CIDANE laughs]
Excellent.
I'm sure Master Licht will
be quite pleased with that.
It appears that they're
in the center of the forest
with the Queen of Witches.
Go on, Mistress.
Burn it all down so there's
nowhere left to hide!
[FANA] Flame Spirit Magic:
Salamander's Breath.
[WITCHES screaming]
[WITCH 57B]
Fly away!
We're under attack!
[ASTA]
The Forest!
Whoa.
They've got some really
powerful Flame Magic!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Salamander, the fire spirit.
Despite not having reached
its perfect form,
it's already quite strong.
Stronger than my
scrying predicted.
Is my ability faltering?
Slight imperfections beget
larger imperfections. No!
[ASTA]
There's more of 'em?
[DOMINANTE]
No, those are--!
Right, we're close to the
border of the Diamond Kingdom.
Yeah.
I see. So... It's true.
I'd thought this, too,
was not yet to be.
The Forest is being breached
by one more entity.
The Diamond Kingdom Army.
I don't believe it.
They're on their way, too?
Oh, rats!
And just when I had settled
into that aromatherapy soak.
What's the big emergency
summons for anyway?
It's the Third Eye.
They're preparing
to launch an attack
on the Forest of Witches.
During the confusion,
we're to enter the Forest,
and capture the Queen
without being detected.
Why bother with all
the sneaking around
when we know this is an
easy win for us either way?
Because orders are orders.
Well, we know that guy's tough.
He's the one we fought
back in the dungeon!
He's still alive!
That's so awesome!
That makes you happy?
[FINRAL] This is so unfair!
Why's it have to be this way?
I knew coming here
was gonna be risky,
but we got forced into
a major battle again!
Is this just normal for us now?!
[FANZELL]
That boy. I think it's Mars.
And the one next to
him must be Ladros!
[DOMINANTE]
Zell.
Okay. Let's protect the Forest!
I can take down the
Eye of the Midnight Sun
and the Diamond Army!
That might be tough
without arms.
[yelps] Right, I forgot!
Wow, Asta. That's the
whole reason we're here.
Did you not get it
the first time?
No, I remember now.
There's just so much going on,
it slipped my mind.
[ALL but ASTA]
Fair enough.
[ASTA]
Aw, man!
[VANESSA]
Captain?
Asta. What are you doing here?
[ASTA]
Vanessa! You're awake!
You had us all worried!
Thank goodness!
Don't do that!
A guy can only take so
much stress all at once!
[VANESSA]
Noelle. Finral.
You're here, too?
Oh, and more familiar faces.
One of whom is shirtless.
Uh, yeah.
It's his favorite thing to do.
Will you please stop
telling people that.
It's been so long, Vanessa.
We came to the Forest
of Witches to find a way
to get the curse lifted
from Asta's arms, too.
It's kind of funny that we all
wound up in the same place.
[VANESSA gasps]
That's right!
[VANESSA]
Don't you worry, Asta!
I'll make a deal with
the Queen, and your arms
will be back to
normal in no time!
Not gonna happen!
[VANESSA]
Huh?
You'd have to trade your
freedom for it, right?
Sorry, but that's
a big fat "no" from me!
What?
Do you even hear how
selfish you sound?
This is our only
option, you idiot!
[ASTA] I don't think so--you're
the one who's bein' selfish!
Tryin' to sneak back
to your mom's place
without tellin' us. That's
the dumbest idea ever!
And what would you have done
in that situation, rugrat?
Um. Now, now, you two.
Let's not fight.
[VANESSA, ASTA]
Shut up!
[FINRAL] You can't say that!
I'm your superior!
[ASTA chuckles]
Well, I don't need your help!
I've still got one last
resort to fall back on!
[panting]
Whoa, Asta, be careful!
I'm not a doctor,
but it kinda seems
like he's lost it.
You're right,
this can't end well.
Hey, what are you doing?
This is what I'm doing!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
That sword.
[ASTA growls]
[BOTH gasp]
[screams] Ow, it hurts so bad!
[NOELLE]
Asta!
What'd you do that for?
That curse is already lodged
deep inside of your body!
It doesn't matter how
strong you are, Asta.
Sometimes there's just
no way to escape your fate!
[panting]
Oh, so what you're sayin' is
that I'm stuck like this,
unless I let my good
friend sacrifice herself?
What kinda guy would
I have to be to go along
with somethin' like that?
If fate wants to take my arms,
then I'm gonna kick
fate in the butt!
[gasps]
[YAMI]
Huh?
You say we ended up here
because it was our "fate?"
Yeah, yeah, old Mr. Fate.
Man, I hate that guy.
Why would anybody obey him?
I live how I want, even if
it means kickin' fate's ass.
[VANESSA]
Of course.
That's what Captain Yami said.
[ASTA]
One more try!
Stop it! Don't be so stubborn!
Listen, Asta!
Friends don't exist
to be sacrificed!
Friends help you overcome a fate
you can't defeat on your own!
That's why I'm here.
I never intended to just
throw my life away!
You wanna hear my plan?
I was going to trick
the Queen, get your
anti-magic power
back, and use it
to get the hell out of here!
I mean, what?
Oh, really? Why didn't
you say so earlier?
[FINRAL] Well, she definitely
shouldn't have said so now!
[NOELLE]
Hey. Queen of Witches.
If you can heal Asta,
stop standing around
and do it already.
Did you forget?
Your Forest is in danger.
[NOELLE]
Asta's itching to get out there
and save your people.
He may be stupid,
but he's strong!
If you fix him,
he'll be a huge help.
Besides...
Wherever he goes,
we all follow him!
[NOELLE]
You're outnumbered.
You'll need every bit of
extra muscle you can get.
You're the Queen.
So make the smart choice.
Let us help you win this!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES] I do agree
the strength of my daughters
would prove imperfect
against foes like these.
Very well.
I will not only repair
the small one's arms--
they'll be more
robust than before.
Wow, really? Awesome!
You mean I'm gonna be as big
and buff as Captain Yami?
She said they would be "robust."
That doesn't necessarily
suggest you'll get bigger.
--So...
--[ASTA] Aw!
Come on, please?
There really isn't much
point in asking me.
I'm impressed, Noelle.
You've sure got a lot of guts!
I know!
I don't think I've ever
seen anybody stand up
to the Queen like you just did!
Well, I am royalty.
[NOELLE] Oh! My legs
are shaking like crazy!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES chuckles]
Rejoice while you can.
But come what may, both my
foolish daughter Vanessa
and the power of that
brat's anti-magic sword
will ultimately belong to me.
Now, Blood Recovery Magic:
Curse-Breaking
Blood-Filled Cocoon.
[ASTA gasps]
My arms, they feel so
light! This is awesome!
[gasps] That spell was really
advanced, and quick, too!
I can see why she's the Queen.
Oh, yeah! I am back in the game!
See, look what I can do!
[ALL]
Oh, Asta!
[ASTA]
Now I don't have to rub my back
against walls when it itches!
Oh! And I can pick
my nose again!
But what I'm most excited
about is getting back
to strength training!
[BOTH]
Oh, Asta...
You never change.
This is sweet!
I can't tell if they're
more robust or whatever,
but they feel like they're
burstin' with power now!
Get ready! It's time to go!
[NOELLE, FINRAL]
Yeah!
[ASTA]
Get ready! It's time to go!
[NOELLE, FINRAL]
Yeah!
[NOELLE, FINRAL, VANESSA]
But...
[NOELLE]
First, we punish you!
Yeah, don't you ever
worry us like that again!
Reckless little idiot!
[ASTA screams]
[NOELLE] You think just
because your arms are fixed,
everything's supposed
to be hunky-dory?
Here! Take your dumb robe, too!
[ASTA] Okay, okay,
thanks for your help!
I'm sorry and I'll
never do it again!
Hey, wait. I didn't
feel anything.
[FINRAL]
So tough!
[VANESSA]
Is that Reinforcement Magic?
[ASTA]
Nope, just all-natural muscle!
[laughs]
Glad you're better, Asta.
[ASTA] Yeah, thank you guys
for helping me, too!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
I have fulfilled my promise.
But our pact is imperfect
until you use that strength.
Oh, yeah, you just wait and see!
Thanks for fixin' me up, ma'am!
Huh.
[FANZELL]
If it's all right with you,
let us take care of
the Diamond troops.
Mars and Ladros...
Well, let's just say that
I have a bit of a history
with those two.
Sure thing, old man,
they're all yours.
Be careful.
[FANZELL]
Right.
And, uh, get dressed, would ya?
Yeah.
[NOELLE]
Same to you!
[laughs] Yes,
that's right, burn!
You can't surrender
after just one blast.
That wouldn't be any
fun for me at all!
[TREE GOLEM 58A growling]
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGE 58A]
Look over there!
So, I'm guessing
these are the enemies
you were telling us
about earlier.
Who do they think they are?
Are you ready, Akimo?
[AKIMO]
Yeah! Let's protect the Forest!
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES gasp]
I've never seen a
creature like that!
[roars]
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES scream]
[TREE GOLEM 58A growling]
Ha, ha! It's no threat
to us at all!
[WITCHES scream]
[TREE GOLEM 58A groans]
[WITCH 57B]
Her Majesty's golem!
What do these people want?
[laughs] Our Lady of the
Third Eye is marvelous.
Mind-boggling power and
unparalleled beauty to match!
Oh, how happy I'd be to have
Mistress Fana on my arm one day.
But for now,
I suppose I'll just have
to settle for the company
of these impudent
little witches!
Seize them!
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES]
Sir!
Any who appear valuable
should be captured alive!
The ones with exceptional
magic abilities
will make lovely
slaves, I'd wager!
[WITCHES yelp, scream]
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGE 58A laughs]
Stop! Let go!
[yells]
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGE 58A groans]
You okay?
[gasps] Ew!
A man rescued me? Disgusting!
[WITCH 58B]
Hmph!
[ASTA]
Hey, what's your problem?
Sorry, but we witches
believe that women
are the mightier sex.
That's why she gave
you an attitude.
Try not to take it
personally, kiddo.
First, I'll put out this fire!
Good idea, thanks Noelle!
And I'll try to get all
the witches to safety!
[VANESSA]
Please do, Finral!
They're really doing
some damage here.
But no matter what,
this is still my homeland!
And I'm going to fight for it!
Are you ready, Asta?
Born ready!
[LADROS]
Well, there they are!
This should be fun.
We've completed all
of our preparations
for the attack.
Ooh! Sounds like
somebody's rarin' to go!
Even so. Ah-ah-ah! Not so fast!
What'd be the point in tangling
with a bunch of small fries?
We'll let both sides fight
it out for a while,
and then we'll feast
on the survivors.
Right!
Is that them?
So many.
Even with the witches' help,
they've still got us
outmatched in magic power.
But it all depends
on how we fight.
Don't you agree, Master?
[FANZELL]
True.
The three of us should split up.
What? But we can't!
I promised you I
would keep you safe!
I know, sweetheart.
And I'm grateful, but now's
not the time for chivalry.
I'm sure you know that,
given how brilliant
you are when it comes
to military strategy.
It's our only chance of winning.
If you say so.
[CIDANE cackles]
What a wonderful selection
of beautiful slave girls!
No!
Let us go!
That scumbag!
He's trying to kidnap
those cute girls!
[VANESSA]
That's a lot of defense mages.
I'm guessing he's the leader.
Hey, Vanessa!
Can you use your
threads to fling me
over to where that ugly guy is?
What?
If I did, you'd be too far
out for me to pull back!
You wanna fight him in midair
with no strings attached?
Yeah, I'll be okay!
If that's what you want,
then I trust you!
[yells]
Hey! What's he doing?
He's launching right toward us!
Take this!
[ASTA]
No, take this!
That's him!
It's the same anti-magic
boy who defeated Vetto!
Strike him down!
[ASTA grunting]
He's using them to climb up!
Wow, who does that?
Well... It is Asta, after all.
I've had enough of you guys
makin' a mess of everything!
[gasps] You stay
away from me, boy!
[VANESSA]
Asta's stronger now.
He's unstoppable!
Just cut it out!
[CIDANE]
Damn you!
This is your chance!
You can't tell us
what to do, you man!
And don't expect us
to thank you, either!
Hurry, let's go!
Huh?
At last. It's you.
You're the boy who killed Vetto!
[ASTA gasps]
Uh-oh. I'm dead.
Wait, no. This'll be easy!
[ASTA yells]
[gasps]
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES yell]
[screams]
Whew! Just in time!
Finral! Nice!
You've been getting
in our way at every turn.
I'll make sure this
is the last time.
Keep on showin' up,
and I'll just keep on
fightin' you off!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[LADROS]
"Not So Fast!"
Ooh!
There's nothing I like
more than a hot cup
of Magic Power Noodles
while everyone else
battles it out!
But, wait.
Ah-ah-ah! Not so fast,
you can't eat 'em yet!
The package says you're
supposed to wait three minutes
after you add the magic!
But I wanna eat them now.
Nope, not so fast!
I like my noodles more firm.
Sorry, but ya can't!
Can.
It's too soon!
That's my choice--
Too early!
Hey!
[BOTH yelling]
[LADROS]
Ready! Time to eat!
Ah, perfect.
Early!
I'm so glad Asta's
arms are better!
And isn't the Queen
of Witches great?
I mean sure, she's
evil or whatever,
but if you look at her,
she's pretty cute!
Black Clover , Page 59:
"Flames of Hatred."
My magic is appreciating
a wide range of lovely ladies!