[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy who
was born without it.
His name is Asta.
[NARRATOR]
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world,
and to become the
next Wizard King!
[NARRATOR] Asta and the others
traveled to the Heart Kingdom
to learn more about the devil's
curse, but Asta was abducted,
leaving Noelle,
Mimosa, and Finral
to do battle with the
Spirit Guardian Gaja.
Meanwhile,
Asta was forced into
a confrontation as well,
against a powerful Water Spirit
by the name of Undine.
[UNDINE]
You may address me as Undine.
I'm one of the
Four Great Spirits,
and I'm contracted to the
Queen of the Heart Kingdom.
[NARRATOR]
Undine and Gaja:
both presented
serious challenges
for Asta and his companions.
But...
[SECRÉ]
Sealing Magic: Inverse Release!
[NOELLE]
Here's the deal.
We can't just back down
after watching you show off!
Mind if I join you?
[gasps]
[ASTA]
That's weird.
I could've sworn I sensed
somebody's ki here.
[gasps]
[ASTA]
Uh. Hey.
[LOROPECHIKA]
Oh, my gosh, I am so sorry!
This thick beaver pelt just felt
so nice and soft on my skin!
[ASTA groans]
[ASTA]
What was that for?!
[LOROPECHIKA]
Where'd my glasses go?
Loropechika.
What in the world
are you up to now?
I told you to hurry up and
change out of your pajamas,
we have guests!
Right, I apologize.
[ASTA] So that girl's the
Queen of the Heart Kingdom?
[GAJA] I only survived
thanks to my defensive spell.
It appears she was holding
back. What a great talent.
As for the others...
[NOELLE]
He's so fast!
Please forgive my rudeness.
I forced you into
a battle with me
so that I could accurately
judge your magic stages.
Uh...
[SECRÉ]
Magic stages?
Is that the scale
I heard about before,
where, the smaller the number
is, the more capable you are?
[LOROPECHIKA] Yes. Here,
strength is judged
by magic power,
not the number of foes.
For example, if there was
one mage ranked very high
in the scale,
he might be victorious
against dozens of lesser
opponents at the same time.
So, in a war between
magical nations, each side
is generally judged by the magic
stages of their military forces.
More specifically,
a kingdom's power
is typically determined by
the number of mages it has
who are ranked near stage zero.
Of course, if it's a devil
you're dealing with,
any fighter who's
lower than stage one
won't be able
to hold their own.
[ASTA]
A devil. That's why we're here!
The thing is, we came because we
picked up a huge curse signal,
and a devil's gotta
be the cause of it!
[gasps]
[UNDINE]
How did they find out something
only Spirit Guardians
should know?
[ASTA] Can you guys tell us
anything about devil curses?
[SECRÉ]
Always so direct.
[UNDINE]
Unfortunately for you,
no one will ever
talk about them.
Actually, I happen to suffer
from a devil curse myself.
If nothing's done about it,
I'll be dead
within a year or so.
--[ASTA] Huh?
--[SECRÉ gasps]
Honestly!
Huh?
Why? Why would you
tell them that? Fool!
[LOROPECHIKA]
Uh...
[UNDINE]
Huh?
[LOROPECHIKA]
Uh!
Oh, sweet Loropechika,
that adorable ignorance of yours
will be the end of me
one day, I just know it!
It's true.
The reason we brought
the two of you to this place
against your will and tried
to discern your magic stages,
is because we desire
to defeat Megicula.
the devil who cast this curse.
[gasps]
[UNDINE] Clearly, you stand
to benefit from this as well.
So, residents of
the Clover Kingdom,
please join us--
[gasps]
[ASTA]
Yeah? What's wrong?
[LOROPECHIKA]
Excuse me!
I forgot to water
the poplatatta trees!
[ASTA]
Really? I'm pretty sure we were
in the middle of a life-and-
death conversation here,
but hey, do what
you gotta do, I guess!
If this is the way
their queen behaves,
then I'm very
concerned about them.
[ASTA]
Whoa, this is so crazy!
Okay, here you go. Drink up!
Oh, my.
The zozo squirrels
are energetic as ever.
Uh-oh, slow down there, Michely,
it's dangerous if
you run too quickly.
It looks like old man
Kakalasa's cough
is starting to clear up now.
And look, the totohl fruits are
growing so splendidly as well!
It's good to see
everything going smoothly.
She's watering the
whole place at once!
[SECRÉ] She sees the entire
kingdom at a glance,
and singlehandedly
controls the water.
She has an all-encompassing
warmth about her,
so no living thing in her
domain goes uncared for.
This magic is fitting for the
Queen of the Heart Kingdom.
[UNDINE]
Now, now, Loropechika.
How about we change you
into more appropriate attire?
You see, our current ruler
has inherited the ability
of most of the queens
who've gone before her.
She's our beautiful
kingdom's guardian deity,
the all-knowing priestess.
Therefore, we simply
cannot lose someone
as precious as her
to a devil's curse.
There is no one else like her!
[gasps]
[UNDINE]
That's better.
You're quite pretty when you
put in the effort, you know.
[LOROPECHIKA]
Ugh, it's hard to walk in this.
[gasps]
[LOROPECHIKA yells]
[ASTA]
Come on!
[UNDINE]
What am I going to do with you?
[ASTA]
Hey, I get it!
The clumsiness must be part
of the devil's curse, too, huh?
[LOROPECHIKA] Oh, no,
I'm just naturally a klutz.
[ASTA]
Wow, that's bad!
[UNDINE]
Megicula, that loathsome devil
who cursed my dear Loropechika,
is currently in
the Diamond Kingdom.
[MAGNA] We came to scout the
Diamond Kingdom to be safe.
[VANESSA]
What happened?
He wiped out all of those
Diamond soldiers on his own.
[MAGNA] And some of them were
as tough as our captains.
Who is this guy?
[laughing]
Don't you go getting
any bright ideas, Luck.
As much as I hate to admit it,
I've never felt like
this in my whole life.
Believe it or not,
I don't wanna fight this guy.
[footsteps]
Oh, guys!
--[ASTA] Hey!
--[FINRAL] Asta!
I'm so relieved
that you're safe!
You're the worst.
Stop getting kidnapped!
It's starting to get really old!
Her Majesty the Queen is here.
[GROUP]
Huh?
[MIMOSA]
She's so majestic, and the magic
that she possesses
is immeasurable!
[NOELLE] So that's the Queen
of the Heart Kingdom.
Wow, talk about
a treat for the eyes!
How lucky am I
to be in the presence
of such an exceptional goddess?
Wait, stop it, Finral, you're
supposed to be better than that!
You're a one-woman man
from now on, remember?
Get it together, would ya?
What's goin' on?
Is Finral okay?
Nope.
Residents of the Clover Kingdom.
I humbly ask that you
lend your strength to us.
[yells]
[MIMOSA, NOELLE]
Really?!
[UNDINE]
Come now, Loropechika,
do try to behave
more like a queen!
Oh, a nosebleed.
Aw, you're still adorable!
What happened?
[LOROPECHIKA]
Aw. I got blood on my dress.
[UNDINE] Of course.
All right, give me a moment.
This is precisely
why I was so against
her conducting this
meeting in person.
[ASTA]
I guess now that that's over,
what did you need our help with?
I was under the impression
that the Heart Kingdom
had plenty of mages
at stage one or higher,
not to mention the Spirit
Guardians, so what can we do?
As I explained,
when battling a devil,
every mage involved
needs to be ranked
at least stage one
in order to keep up.
But even a zero
still wouldn't have
what it takes to
achieve victory.
[gasps]
[LOROPECHIKA] You see, Spirit
Guardians are able to wield
powerful magic by borrowing
energy from natural mana,
but they cannot defeat a devil.
Unlike us, your kingdom created
magic types that are not
derived from nature,
such as Chain, Steel,
and the eccentric Spatial Magic.
In exchange, they lose
the divine protection
of natural mana.
And some of the
irregulars who were born
in that environment have
the necessary traits
to best a devil.
[GROUP gasps]
[LOROPECHIKA] One example
of this is Julius Novachrono,
who possesses Time Magic.
There is also the Black Bulls'
Captain Yami Sukehiro
and his Dark Magic.
Unfortunately, it appears
the majority of Julius's power
has been used up at this point.
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
She knows about that?
I wonder how much
information she has.
And you. Asta and Nero.
For combat, Nero's
about a stage six,
but she's got
ancient Sealing Magic
and has used forbidden magic.
Asta has no mana,
but because of that,
he was granted the
use of Anti-magic.
People like you two
who possess unique,
inexplicable powers are
referred to as "arcane stages."
So we're...
[LOROPECHIKA] I would like you
to lend us your arcane powers
to help us defeat that devil.
And, as a reward,
I will happily share
any information that
I have with you.
But we don't have the authority
to make a major
decision like that!
[ASTA] Good thing we've got
this magic item, then, huh?
I'm takin' a dump here!
Oh, you have somethin'
important to ask me?
Well, I happen to be doing
somethin' important myself.
In fact, this could be one
for the history books.
Call back later!
--[click]
--He just hung up on me!
Pooping is crucial.
[ASTA]
You're on his side?!
You mustn't say such
vulgar things, Loropechika!
[giggles]
Well, I had my suspicions
that something like
this would happen,
so I borrowed a magic item
that allows us to connect
with the Transmission
Magic that Marx uses.
[NOELLE]
Good thinking!
[ASTA]
Nice one, Mimosa!
All right, let's try it out.
[MARX]
Mimosa. Did something happen?
Wait, is that who I think it is?
Oh, wow! You must be the
Queen of Heart Kingdom!
So what kind of
magic do you use?
[MARX] Please don't pop into the
frame like that, Your Majesty!
Have you forgotten about your
condition? People will see!
[JULIUS] Well, you just
called me "Your Majesty,"
so now they know it's me.
--[MARX] Ah!
--[JULIUS laughs]
[ASTA] Ah, it's no big deal,
the queen already knew.
[MARX]
What?!
[ASTA]
So, anyway.
She says they need our
help to beat a devil
because we're arcane stage,
or something like that.
That's fine by me.
You and your friends could gain
something amazing from all this.
Honestly, I think I'd like to be
over there helping you, myself.
That's out of the question!
I suppose that settles it then.
How wonderful!
Then again, if you
tried to fight a devil
in your current state,
you would all be slaughtered
in the blink of an eye.
[ASTA]
That's kinda blunt.
I mean, is the Spade Devil
really supposed to be
that impossible to take down?
Yes. Even more deadly
than the devil you
fought with previously.
[ASTA]
Worse than him?
We only won that time
because we had help
from super-powerful people
like the First Wizard King
and the leader of the elves.
And even then,
it was a close call!
[LOROPECHIKA]
Megicula is responsible
for the scar on Gaja's face.
[NOELLE] What? But we
barely stood a chance
against that guy before!
[JULIUS]
Ah, yes, I remember dueling
with that Spirit Guardian
fellow in the past.
He's extremely skilled.
You guys fought?
[NOELLE] So, even
someone the Wizard King
speaks that highly of isn't
able to defeat this devil?
[ASTA] The way we are
now, we can't win.
We have to get stronger!
[LOROPECHIKA]
Megicula is currently haunting
the Spade Kingdom, and using
its citizens to gather up
enormous amounts of power.
Soon, that devil could
invade and conquer
not only the Heart Kingdom,
but Clover and Diamond as well.
[gasps]
[LOROPECHIKA]
If nothing changes,
then I will eventually
be killed by this curse.
That's why I'd like to
invade the Spade Kingdom
before my power
becomes too weak.
We can take half a year.
Let's make our forces
as strong as we can.
We should enlist any mages
who stand a chance
in battle against a devil.
Train for six months,
then, we will fight
together to stop Megicula.
If you help us...
[ALL]
...we can do it!
[MARX] Sir, are you certain
you approve of this?
Remember, the Magic Knights
are still exhausted
from fighting the elves.
It's true that we have half
a year, but this is a devil.
Just think of the casualties,
for Clover and for Heart.
I take it you heard the report
from the scouts
we sent out, Marx?
Considering the state
Diamond is in,
our only hope is to
have our Magic Knights
improve their skills.
I'm sure the Queen
of the Heart Kingdom
knows that, as well.
I guess you're right.
[JULIUS] Assemble all of the
Magic Knight Squad Captains.
Sir!
[CHARMY munching]
How long is Captain Yami
gonna make us wait?
We've got a major
announcement to make, here!
Keep your voice down,
you little shrimp.
We all know that the captain
can't do his business
if he doesn't have
peace and quiet.
[ASTA]
Pooping again?
Woo nelly.
Wait a minute, don't tell
me you've been in there
since we called you?
The war's not over yet.
Trust me, I'd love to kick back
and celebrate today's victory,
but the next battle's already
startin' to rear its ugly head.
Metaphors or not,
it's still gross.
Well, anyway, let's
hear what went down
during your visit
to the Heart Kingdom.
[FINRAL]
Oh, yes, sir!
It was so eventful,
I'm not sure where to begin.
Get this!
We found out who was cursed
by a devil over there,
and it's the queen,
of all people.
Pretty crazy, right?
[NOELLE] And if the curse
isn't broken soon,
then she's only
got a year to live.
[FINRAL] Since she was chosen by
one of the Four Great Spirits,
she's the most powerful
mage they've got.
If they lose someone like that,
they're in big trouble.
[sighs] Obviously, we should
keep all that on the down-low.
I hope you at least got a little
bit of useful information
on the devil, too.
We have a name. Megicula.
And a location!
In the Spade Kingdom!
In Spade?
If that's really true,
then what we saw
makes a lot of sense.
Huh? Did you guys
find somethin' weird?
Apparently, when they
went to check out
the Diamond Kingdom, they ran
into one of Spade's mages
close to the border.
Whoa, really?
Except, he wasn't
just a normal mage.
[MAGNA] There were hundreds of
Diamond soldiers on the ground.
He beat them all by himself
like it was nothing.
[VANESSA] And that cold,
dark magic he had.
I wouldn't be surprised
if he got it from a devil.
I don't know if it's
possible, but I wonder
if we might've seen Megicula
without even realizing it!
Oh, no.
If that's him, then
the Diamond Kingdom is...
[YAMI]
Pretty much done for.
All because of that one guy.
[ASTA]
But, Mars...
Even from that distance,
one thing was obvious.
That man could've
easily killed us.
If we had picked
a fight with him,
we'd have suffered the same fate
as those Diamond soldiers.
Yeah, you're not
tough enough yet.
If we can't defeat that devil,
then both the Heart Kingdom
and the Clover Kingdom
are gonna be history.
So the only solution
is to try to get stronger.
The queen told us to spend
six months training.
And after that,
the Heart Kingdom
will launch their attack
on the Spade Kingdom.
As Magic Knights, it's our
job to spend every minute
of the next six months getting
as powerful as we can.
And then we'll be able to
help them defeat Megicula
and keep everybody safe!
One thing.
[ASTA]
What is it, Zora?
Just so we're clear,
are you sure training
is all we have to do?
'Cause beating a devil is
hard, even for the best of us.
[SECRÉ] Unless we're
stage one mages or higher,
we won't even be
able to keep up.
To put that into terms that
we're more familiar with,
that would be like a
First-Class Senior Magic Knight.
No, even that wouldn't be
good enough in this situation.
[MAGNA]
Wait a minute.
Are you telling us we have to
get up to a vice captain's level
in just six months?
[VANESSA]
Heh. Easier said than done.
Unfortunately,
as far as we know,
the only people in our
kingdom who stand a chance
of defeating the devil are
mages whose power lands them
in the arcane stage,
including Asta,
Nero, Captain Yami,
and the Wizard King.
Well, whether I have
what it takes or not,
I refuse to give up. We can
all get there eventually!
Right?
[NOELLE]
I have to.
Megicula is the one
who killed my mother.
Hear that? Put your
big-boy pants on!
The royal just said that
she's not gonna give up.
And since we outrank her,
we're not allowed to
chicken out, you got it?
Yeah. That wasn't like me, huh?
After all, our friend's
life is on the line,
so I can't afford
to give into fear.
Wait. What friend is this now?
[murmuring] I'll do
everything in my power
to make myself a stage one mage.
That way I can look out
for my bestest buddy, Asta.
Crap, I forgot!
If I don't do something about
this Megicula thing soon,
I'm gonna be sentenced to death!
How could you forget?
I guess there's no choice, then.
[ZORA] No self-respecting
Magic Knight would let a devil
run wild and do whatever
it wants, right?
All right! I'm in!
I have no idea what
I can do to help out,
but I'll try my hardest!
[FINRAL] I'll use these
six months to make myself
an even more powerful mage and
get rid of that terrible curse!
Maybe then I'll be worthy
of Lady Finnes's heart.
[NOELLE] After we stop Megicula
and the curse has been broken,
I wanna talk to Nozel
again about our mother.
[ASTA] All that matters right
now is beating that devil!
And then, maybe I can understand
a little more about
my own devil, too.
[SECRÉ] For the sake of their
futures and this world,
I can't let another
devil take control.
[clapping]
Okay, for the next six months,
I'm just gonna let
the Black Bulls loose,
which means you can
do what you want.
So you get to go wherever,
team up with whoever.
Your only mission is to
build up your strength.
Remember, this is a devil
and the Spade Kingdom
we're dealin' with.
Train like your life
depends on it.
'Cause I'm gonna kill
you if you don't.
Now I usually tell you to do
this in the heat of a battle,
so six months should
be plenty of time.
Push past your limits,
Black Bulls!
[BLACK BULLS]
Right!
[JULIUS]
This isn't just about us.
It's a life-or-death situation
for the Heart and
Diamond Kingdoms, too.
Black Clover , Page 130:
"The New Magic Knights
Captain Conference."
Let's prepare ourselves
to face that devil