[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] The castle was
infiltrated by Langris,
as well as others
from the Golden Dawn
who had been possessed by elves.
[NARRATOR]
Yami and Finral were soon forced
into a harrowing battle.
[MAGIC KNIGHT 107A] It doesn't
matter how many of you
there are--you'll
never overpower us!
[cackles] You're exactly
the ones I want to slice up.
So thanks for coming out!
[NARRATOR] With Jack's aid,
they gained the upper hand.
[GOLEM ARMOR groans]
[NARRATOR] After regrouping
with Nozel and the others,
the team entered the castle.
But Kivn had already
invaded the Silvas' home,
where she attacked
Solid and Nebra.
[SOLID]
No!
Nozel, it's you!
And Noelle!
Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Roar!
[KIVN]
Compass Magic: Another Atlas!
[NARRATOR] Nozel and
Noelle joined the fray,
but Kivn's Compass
Magic took a toll.
Stop her, Nozel! Please!
Stay there, Solid.
You'd only hold us
back as you are now.
I will handle this.
[SOLID]
Mother! Mother!
[giggles]
You could at least try to
fight back, little slowpoke.
[yelps]
That's odd! I thought
I trained you better
than to start eating
before I do!
If it makes you angry,
then do something about it.
[NEBRA]
With a face like that,
it must be hard
to look in the mirror.
You're lucky I'm always
so kind to you.
That sad grimoire of yours
is practically paper-thin.
Are you sure you're
really royalty?
Not being able to
control your own magic.
That's the most pitiful
thing I've ever heard.
And this wretch
is my little sister?
Embarrassing!
[NOZEL] You will never
be a member of my squad.
There is no room in the Silver
Eagles for a disgrace like you.
[SOLID]
So sad.
Pitiful!
And would you believe the
girl's been going outside
alone every night
so that she can practice
her abilities on a dead tree?
The best part is,
she always misses!
Every once in a while,
a spell will backfire on her
and she ends up soaked!
It's hilarious!
[NEBRA laughs]
Really?
I couldn't even
do that as a joke!
She's talented!
Talented at being
a failure, that is.
I hate that she
and I are related.
Noelle.
I have decided which Magic
Knight squad you'll be joining.
[NOELLE]
Huh?
[BOTH gasp]
[NOZEL] You'll be a Black Bull.
It's already been settled.
[NOELLE]
What?
Ah, the Black Bulls,
the worst of them all!
How very fitting.
They only do small missions
in the sticks, don't they?
Like hunting boars?
Just your speed, Noelle!
[NEBRA, SOLID laugh]
[NOELLE] It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
I went through all that
training. I'll succeed.
I can do it!
I won't let you hurt
my family anymore!
Let's show her
our power, Noelle.
The House Silva stands strong!
Right!
Ha!
[gasps]
Unfortunately for you,
this is a sealed space.
Which means that,
no matter what you do,
your attacks won't reach me.
Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Lair!
[KIVN] You're just
wasting magic and energy.
What a shame.
And I tried so hard to
give you a peaceful death.
[NOELLE] She's too good.
What am I going to do?
Even with Mana Skin,
Sea Dragon's Lair
won't have any effect in here!
[NOZEL]
Despite using all my strength,
this is the best I can do.
[yells]
[NOZEL] All I can manage now are
simple movements at close range.
There's only one strategy.
You're quite determined,
but I wonder
how much longer you
can keep this up.
[NOELLE]
He's struggling. Come on, think!
If Asta or the other
Black Bulls were here,
I bet they could come up
with some crazy idea!
[screams]
Damn it! If we don't
figure out something
to counteract her magic,
we'll have no way out!
[NOELLE]
No way out?
[NOELLE] I may not be able
to use creation magic
in such a
controlled environment.
But what if... I lose control!
[NOELLE]
Nozel! Lend me a hand!
This is...
[KIVN]
I don't understand!
You fool!
You just flooded a completely
enclosed space with water!
[KIVN] Another Atlas confines
everything within its fortress.
If I don't want to be
drowned in my own spell,
I have no choice
but to call it off!
[gasps]
[KIVN]
You wretched human.
[yelps]
[KIVN]
No. I don't believe it.
She annihilated me
in a mere instant!
Amazing.
It makes sense from Nozel,
but not from her.
Um. Guess we pulled
it off, huh, Nozel?
Hey. I really appreciate
you going along with my idea,
even though it was a bit of
a shot in the dark and all.
[NOZEL]
It was certainly unorthodox.
Fighting that way
is unbefitting of royalty.
[NOELLE gasps]
But it still resulted
in a victory for us.
You've learned many
impressive things
since you joined that squad.
I had feared, because
you look so much
like our late mother, that I
might lose her a second time.
[NOELLE gasps]
[NOZEL] I didn't expect
you would ever become
a strong person, so I decided
that I had to protect
you at any cost.
I tried to keep you
from the battlefield.
[NOZEL] But you proved
me wrong, Noelle.
You're more capable now
than I ever could have
predicted you'd be.
[clears throat]
What I mean is...
I... I apologize, Noelle.
Nozel apologized?
That's impossible!
Um. Thank you, Nozel.
[NOZEL]
We aren't out of danger yet.
We'd better see
to Nebra's wounds.
[NOZEL grunts]
[gasps]
[NOZEL]
What?
[gasps] Nozel.
[NOELLE] How did this happen?
Please, wake up!
I almost feel bad for you.
You're trapped now,
here, in this place.
There's no stopping it anymore.
It's far too vast and powerful!
You're lying!
There has to be some way
to escape from this madness!
All you can do now
is accept your fate.
This is the price you'll pay
for your sins, royals.
[NOELLE]
I won't give up!
There's a solution to this.
I know there is!
Think hard, Noelle!
You can defeat her!
You finally proved yourself
to your brother, right?
So you can do anything!
If you don't, Nozel and
Nebra won't make it!
I would prefer to watch as you
gradually give into death,
but I think I'll have mercy
on you sinful human fools
and get this over with
quickly instead!
[NOELLE]
They've been cruel to me.
But still.
I won't let her take
away my family!
[NOELLE]
Long-range spells are out.
Magic manipulation, too.
I need something simple
that packs a punch.
Something that doesn't
need to travel far!
[gasps]
[NOELLE] This is a spell I can
only use because of where I am,
and who I am, in
this exact moment!
[NARRATOR] In order to
manifest a magic ability,
the most crucial component
is the user's natural talent.
However, unwavering effort and
training may also play a part.
In rare cases,
a deeply heartfelt wish
can grant power during
a time of crisis.
Many royal mages are able
to acquire spells intuitively
by employing
their innate prowess
and natural resourcefulness.
Because of their advantage,
those individuals
rarely undergo training,
do research,
or have their lives endangered
on the battlefield.
Although Noelle
possessed considerable
magic power and talent, she also
worked hard to improve herself
and risked her life
in combat many times
alongside the Black Bulls.
Her longsuffering, combined
with her resolute desire
to protect her siblings, gave
her all the power she needed
to overcome her
current challenge!
[NOELLE]
Water Creation Magic:
Valkyrie Armor!
[gasps] Noelle!
[KIVN]
What kind of magic is that?
She's giving off an
enormous amount of power!
That won't be enough, royal!
[yells]
[KIVN]
How does she move so swiftly?
Is she riding the mana from
my attacks and the disturbance
they're creating
in this sealed space
like waves on the sea?
That armor must be a spell
that lets her
control nearby mana!
[KIVN]
Fine.
But can you avoid all of these?
[KIVN]
I still have the advantage here.
If I can find the slightest
hole in your defense,
this world I've created
will rip your armor clean off!
[gasps]
[NOELLE] Just moments ago,
I was struggling.
[NOELLE] But now, it feels like
I've burst out of my cage!
[NOELLE] I had no idea magic
could make me feel so free!
[NOELLE] I wonder if this is
the same feeling my mother had.
[gasps]
[NOZEL]
Mother.
The Dancing Princess
of the Battlefield.
How?
How did you cut through
everything I threw at you?
It's over!
[KIVN]
Willful Compass!
These mana currents you
seem to dance through
so elegantly... I'm
about to redirect them,
and send you straight to hell!
You're mine now, royal brat!
[gasps] Did she overrule
my mana compulsion?
[NOELLE]
I'm not concerned with elegance.
This armor, anything that comes
into contact with this mana,
is under my control!
I'm fighting with
everything I've got,
so I can move forward!
I'll crush you and this
world you've made!
[KIVN groans]
[NOELLE pants]
Did I win?
Come on, let's get Nozel
and Nebra to safety!
[NOELLE]
Oh, no.
I don't have enough magic
left to fight these guys!
How dare you hurt Kivn?
It appears we
might've underestimated
your strength, humans.
But that will not happen again.
Begone!
Solid, behind you!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 108A groans]
See, now that's how you
do a surprise attack.
[gasps]
[ZORA chuckles]
Not bad, huh?
Even better when you double it.
What kind of magic was that?
I've never seen
anything like it.
Damned humans. Stay on guard!
That last battle was
flashy, to say the least,
so I kinda assumed it
was gonna draw a crowd.
Zora!
[ZORA] Hey, kid! Don't you
work for these people?
Make yourself useful!
Huh? What's the matter with you,
dragging me into
something this dangerous?
I'm the guy who saved
your ass, remember?
So you had better listen to me.
I can't.
[ZORA]
You can, and you will.
Now hop to it, kid, or you
won't have masters anymore.
[gasps] Hey!
It's Lord Nozel and Lady Nebra!
They need my help!
Bubble Recovery Magic:
Bubble Refresher!
Lord Solid, please bring
Lord Nozel over here!
Lord Solid?
What's wrong,
are you takin' a nap?
Some royal Magic Knight
you are, buddy.
How could you let this
chick beat all three of you?
Maybe if you snobs didn't
run your mouths off
all the time,
you would fight better!
I mean, this moron
here is a captain!
And he couldn't even look
out for his own family!
[ACIER]
Nozel.
[ACIER] You're finally getting
your grimoire next year.
I'm looking forward
to finding out
what sorts of amazing
things you're going to do.
I'll learn spells
of unparalleled power,
so that I can become a
strong Magic Knight Captain
just like you are, Mother.
[laughs] That's great.
Solid and Nebra both have Water
Magic like your father does,
and I have a feeling
it might be the same
for the little one, too.
The only one of my
children who inherited
my Steel attribute
was you, dear.
So be sure that to use it to
protect your siblings, okay?
[NOZEL]
That's right. I should...
Royals like you are supposed
to be more powerful
than us commoners, right?
Come on, show a little spirit!
I think we've heard
quite enough out--!
[NOZEL]
Stop.
But, Nozel. I don't...
[NOZEL]
Everything he's saying is true.
If I let this be the end of me,
I'd be a disgrace to the
royal House of Silva
and the Silver Eagles!
[NOZEL] I'll reinforce
my body with magic.
[NOELLE] He's can fortify
himself with Mercury Magic?
What an advanced technique!
Are you ready, Noelle?
Yeah!
[ZORA chuckles]
You snooty rich kids
have so much magic power,
it makes me sick.
Tone it down some for
the rest of us, would ya?
Ash Magic: Revelation
of the Cowardly.
[ZORA]
Now!
Take my magic
with you, Noelle!
[yells]
I've got you!
Not quite.
She's too fast!
We'll catch her.
[ALL grunt]
It's Trap Magic!
And there's more
where that came from.
[ZORA]
The Revelation of the Cowardly
shows where I've placed
each of my trap spells.
The second they screw up,
these royals'll be all over 'em.
[yells]
In that condition, you won't
be able to avoid this!
Nozel!
He's not fazed at all by
the strength of our spell.
What kind of magic was that?
Tch. Bunch of amateurs.
Guess you don't know about
complicated techniques
like my counter-traps.
Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Roar!
It looks like your control is
starting to falter, little girl!
Mercury Magic: Rain of Silver!
That's nothing to me!
[BOTH gasp]
[ZORA] These spells have
been evolving for years.
It's complex human magic.
But you elves wouldn't know
about that either, would ya?
[FINRAL] Langris! No matter
what you think of me,
you and I will
always be brothers,
and nothing's gonna change that!
Black Clover , Page 109:
"Spatial Mage Brothers."
I can do it if I try my best!