[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy
who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
[NARRATOR]
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world,
and to become the
next Wizard King!
[NARRATOR] In order to defeat
Megicula, the devil lurking
in the Spade Kingdom, the Magic
Knights have been training hard.
[NARRATOR]
In the briny depths of the sea,
another dangerous
threat has emerged.
[GIO sighs]
[GIO]
Kiato! Kahono!
You two make a run for it.
[KAHONO]
We can't!
[GIO]
You must.
Seek the aid of
the Magic Knights.
[KIATO]
Come on. We've gotten this far!
[GIO groans]
--[KAHONO] Father!
--[KIATO] Dad!
[KIATO]
He's right. Let's go!
[KAHONO]
Okay.
[NARRATOR] The beach town
of Raquey is hot year-round
due to the strong mana
that surrounds it.
This makes it a popular resort.
But it is also an
excellent training ground
for magic users.
Water mages most of all.
[NOELLE] If I can just
maintain this force.
[NOELLE pants]
[NOELLE]
I can create two twisters now,
but I need to keep them
both supplied with mana.
[song plays]
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
Is that crying? A song?
I'm not sure why, but it
feels sort of nostalgic.
[NOELLE gasps] Wait, why did
I just see my mother?
[ASTA]
Black Bulls, fight!
Ya feel that burn?
[MAGNA]
Oh, yeah!
[ASTA]
Wait, push through it!
[MAGNA]
Right behind ya!
[FINRAL pants]
Are you out of steam already?
[FINRAL] Well, it's not
like I run very often.
I mean, c'mon. What gives?
Why can't we just
train with magic?
Because, when we were
fighting against the elves,
Yami and Asta proved that this
kinda training matters, too.
The stronger your body gets,
the stronger your
magic's gonna be.
Right. Come on!
Let's get to it, Finral!
Bulk up till you're
as big as Captain Yami,
and you'll be unstoppable!
[FINRAL] Aren't you setting
the bar kinda high?
We should all get super
buff and then all of you
should try to fight me
at the same time!
Round two, guys!
I wanna hear that fighting
spirit even louder this ti--!
[ASTA screams]
[ALL groaning]
[ZORA]
Damn it. I missed one.
What the hell did you trap
us for, ya sneaky bastard?
Last time I checked,
the best way
to train up your magic
was to use it.
So, that's just
what I've been doing.
I'd say sorry, but I
didn't join this squad
to make friends with you idiots.
What was that?
[MAGNA]
Damn it, Luck!
Are you trying to bury us?
You bet I am! Here!
[FINRAL]
Aw, man!
[GROUP chattering]
Good grief.
[NOELLE] How can just four
people make this much noise?
[GREY]
Th-- This is terrible.
I can't hide my face
while I'm doing this pose,
it's so embarrassing!
[VANESSA] I've been eating a
whole lot of Charmy's cooking
lately and its starting to show.
Gotta lose weight.
Gotta lose weight!
The simplest way to
bulk up is to stress
your muscles in a
controlled manner.
When weight training,
you should probably break up
your workout into three "sets."
You should also track
your protein intake--
This info on the connection
between the deltoids
and trapezius proves that
by gaining more anatomical
knowledge, I can make my new
Marie doll far more accurate!
Question for you, Gordon.
I thought you said you
had trouble spending time
in the sun without
getting burnt.
Were you able to get over that?
Yes, I can stay out as
long as I'd like to now.
It's all thanks to
this special sunblock.
Would you care to try
it out for yourself?
[GAUCHE] I'd love to.
Thanks for offering!
[GORDON]
You need to be meticulous
when dealing with
UV rays. Here you go.
[GAUCHE grunts]
That's cold!
Just what do you think
you're doing back there?
[GORDON]
Huh? Uh. What?
[HENRY]
Hello. Here... you... go.
Who the hell says ya can't
have beer for breakfast?
[SECRÉ]
Captain. For you.
Thanks. Aren't you gonna train
like the rest of the squad?
Glad we talked.
Hey, guys! Food's ready,
come and get it!
[sighs]
[BLACK BULLS]
Thanks for the meal!
[BLACK BULLS chattering]
[song plays]
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
It's that song again.
[MAGNA, ASTA]
Huh?
[ASTA]
Noelle?
[NOELLE] This is about where
I was the first time I heard it.
Hey!
Asta.
Did somethin' happen, or what?
Not exactly, but do you
hear anything strange?
Like what?
[BOTH gasp]
[KAHONO, KIATO panting]
Hey, look.
Wait, Kahono?
And Kiato?
[NOELLE]
What are you doing here?
I could ask the same,
but since you're exactly
who we're looking for,
I'll chalk it up to providence.
[KIATO] The sea goddess
is as beautiful as ever.
[ASTA] So what gives?
Is there trouble at home?
[KIATO] Oh, right.
We came to ask for help.
It's bad.
We ask that you meet us
back at the temple.
[ASTA]
You were attacked by a monster?
[GIFSO]
A strong one.
Likely a Guardian of the Sea.
[KAHONO] They've been around
since time immemorial.
They're said to be
servants of the Sea God.
[NOELLE]
So this creature is sacred?
If you serve the same god,
then why would it attack you?
Something's begun to
disturb the flow of mana
in this part of the sea.
As a result, much
of the local fauna
has become quite aggressive.
I decided to investigate with
magic, and then I saw it.
The mana disturbance made
it hard to make out details.
But I know what I saw.
South of this Temple, in a place
called the Void of No Return,
there lurks a Guardian
of the Sea that has been
wholly consumed by its own rage.
I'm sure that the
disturbance I've felt
in the mana here was caused
by this Guardian's fury.
The temple mages might
have calmed the Guardian
by performing their
song and dance,
but they never got
a chance to try.
Our best warriors were
wounded trying to defend us.
[NOELLE]
Kahono.
[GIFSO] We've brought
you here to request
that you grant Kiato and
Kahono your protection.
Please use your considerable
strength to escort them
to the Void of No Return safely.
Sounds like a whole
lotta not my problem.
We're all really busy
training right now.
You spent all day drinking
in a beach chair!
Please, sir!
I ask because I know how
powerful the Black Bulls are!
You proved this in the
battle royale we fought,
and through your ability
to reach the Underwater Temple
safely despite
being land-dwellers
Though that was through
the sea goddess's protection.
[YAMI] This may sound harsh,
but have ya got any proof that
your song and dance can actually
calm this Guardian down?
Not exactly.
Protecting the kingdom
isn't a hobby for us,
it's a job.
We need to put our efforts
where we know they'll count.
I'm not about to loan
you my squad members
when your resolve is this weak.
[NOELLE]
So basically,
we just need to convince
you that this could work.
Huh?
What do you mean?
[NOELLE] This mana
disturbance is affecting
a massive part of the sea.
It's possible that there's
a devil behind this, too.
As magic knights,
we are sworn to protect.
I'll get your mages
to the Guardian safely,
there's no doubt in my mind.
[KAHONO]
Noelle.
[KIATO]
The Sea Goddess provides!
I'm sure now.
We'll quell the Guardian's
rage, you have my word!
We've sung and danced
for the almighty sea god!
We're prepared for this task!
One way or another,
we will make the Guardian
hear our prayers!
That's the kinda resolve
I can get behind.
Now. Convince me it'll work.
I have a plan, and I
think you'll like it.
[KAHONO]
It's over there. See it?
The Void of No Return.
Its name is based on
the legend that
those who wander into its
depths are never seen again.
We were told stories as kids,
but I never thought
they were real.
Even now, it's a bit of a
struggle to believe my eyes.
[FINRAL]
How deep do you think this goes?
[YAMI]
So, what's your plan?
I'll make a smaller and
more powerful version
of the Sea Dragon's Cradle.
There's a trade-off.
It'll be durable, but it won't
carry more than four people.
[YAMI] Well, with you, Kahono
and Kiato, we've already got
our first three passengers,
but we could still fit one mo--
Me! Me! Me! Me! Please?
Oh, man, I wanna go so bad!
Why sing to the Guardian
when we could kill it?
I wonder how strong it is.
I can't wait to find out!
Just send me and
I'll get it done quickly.
Marie awaits me.
Her deltoids need carving.
Please tell me there's
something I'm missing here!
Maybe this Guardian wants
to rejoin the cycle of life!
Talk about well-aged
meat, am I right?
Yeah, I'm not
sending any of you.
[LUCK, CHARMY]
What?
[GAUCHE grunts]
[YAMI]
And you're not goin', either.
[ASTA groans]
Are you serious, sir? Why?
Is it because I can't swim?
Forgot about that.
You really can't go.
[groans] This isn't fair!
[NOELLE]
He's such an idiot.
Finral.
You go.
Huh?
Get 'em out if things go bad.
Even if you have to die
to do it. Understood?
Yes, sir!
[YAMI]
Oh, and Noelle.
[NOELLE gasps]
[YAMI] You're the one
who decided to do this,
so make sure you see it through.
Sir!
[NOELLE]
Such violent mana.
If I let my guard down for
even a second, we're finished.
[grunts]
Look there!
[FISHMAN 136A growls]
[NOELLE]
What the heck are those?
[KIATO]
I don't know.
We've never seen anything
like them before.
[growls]
Kahono!
Leave it to me, brother!
Now! Song Magic: Mother Lullaby!
[singing]
It's strange, but my guess
is that the local fish
were turned into monsters
by the powerful mana that's
concentrated around
the Guardian.
Is that even possible?
[FISHMEN growl]
[NOELLE]
We're surrounded!
There's no end to these things.
[FINRAL] We'll just have
to push through them!
[ALL gasp]
[KAHONO]
Noelle!
[KIATO] Just sit tight
and leave this to us.
[KAHONO]
Song Magic: Destructive Beat!
[FISHMEN groaning]
[NOELLE] Wait, don't be stupid!
Hold on a second!
[KIATO gasps]
[KAHONO]
Together!
[KAHONO singing]
[KIATO]
Right!
[KAHONO, KIATO]
Combo Spell: Sea God's Descent!
[KAHONO, KIATO yell]
[growls]
[KIATO]
There's too many of them!
[FINRAL]
What do we do?
[NOELLE]
What's wrong with me?
I'm supposed to
protect those two,
not stand by and watch while
they do all the fighting.
[gasps]
Get out of here, Noelle!
Finral, are you
hearing yourself?
I can't leave while
you're down here.
If I did, then you'd be
thrown into the ocean!
It'll be fine.
Once I grab those two, I'll
meet you back at the temple.
But how are you
gonna pull that off?
Look, the captain said
to bring everyone back.
He said to do it
even if it kills me.
And I might be a screw-up,
but I'm not so bad
that I'd abandon a girl
in a place like this.
Now, get out of here!
But you can't--
[growling]
[FINRAL groans]
[NOELLE groans]
[KAHONO]
Noelle!
[KIATO]
Kahono!
[NOELLE]
Everyone.
[grunts]
[NOELLE]
I can't just give up.
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
That's right.
I can't let this
be the end for me.
If I die here, then I'll never
be able to take vengeance
on the devil that
killed my mother!
[LOROPECHIKA] You see, Spirit
Guardians are able to wield
powerful magic by borrowing
energy from natural mana,
but they cannot defeat a devil.
"Natural mana."
This water's teeming with it.
I just need to get
it on my side.
Please, lend me your strength!
[KIATO]
No way.
Oh, hey.
[yelps]
[FINRAL] I don't get it.
She'd need crazy magic control
just to make more
than one of these.
So how are they all so strong?
Well done! You're even more
amazing than I thought you were!
I'm sorry that it took me
so long to think of this.
Now that we're safe,
let's find that Guardian.
[MONSTER growling]
Hey. What's that sound?
[KIATO]
Damn, it's the kraken!
[FINRAL yelps]
Like the Guardian of
the Sea, the Kraken
is a fierce defender
of the Sea God's domain.
[FINRAL] So I'm guessing
it wants us outta here?
[ASTA yelps]
[CHARMY]
Get in my mouth!
Nicely done, Finral!
[FINRAL]
Here it comes!
This ink. It's
obstructing our vision
and disrupting the flow
of mana. At this rate...
[NOELLE] Water Creation
Magic: Valkyrie Armor!
[yells]
[gasps]
Noelle!
[NOELLE] Sorry, but I need
you to take a little nap.
This is our chance!
[KIATO, KAHONO, FINRAL]
Right!
Looks like an ancient ruin.
Who would've thought?
I wonder who built all this.
[FINRAL]
Same.
Do you think people
actually lived here?
[ALL gasp]
It's the Guardian. It has to be.
[SEA GUARDIAN growls]
[NOELLE]
Such powerful mana.
It's like there's an aura
of pure rage around it.
Is it threatening us?
I don't speak whale.
[inhales]
[singing]
[gasps]
[FINRAL] I see. The Guardian
hasn't turned bad.
It's just protective
of its baby.
As for the creatures we fought.
I suppose they must've
been trying to help.
Oh. I get it.
[SEA GUARDIAN PUP whimpers]
So that's the sound
I've been hearing.
The lullaby you sing
for your baby.
[NOELLE gasps]
Wait! That was my mother!
Do you know her?
[SEA GUARDIAN calls]
[gasps]
Sea Goddess. Thanks. I--
Hey. Don't tell me
you're injured.
Huh? Um. No. I'm fine.
Just nostalgic.
[NOELLE]
Strangely enough,
it seems like Mom might've
come here before me.
Though I'm sure I was clumsier,
and I must've taken far longer.
I followed in her footsteps.
See, Mom? I'm growing.
Thank you so much
for helping us!
Are you really sure that this
is all the thanks you need?
I think Grandpa was hoping
we'd get to throw
a feast for you guys.
This is gonna be delicious.
Wait. We could've had a feast?
You two take care, all right?
And tell your grandpa, "hi."
Come see us once
things calm down.
I've got a very special welcome
in mind for the Sea Goddess.
The four of us should
do another double date!
I'm sure it'll be a blast!
Huh?!
Sure! I'll be looking
forward to it!
[NOELLE]
Hey, hold on a second!
[FINRAL]
Kahono's so forward!
A girl after my own--
No! Stupid brain!
You have Lady Finnes, remember?
Good work down there.
Uh... Yami.
[YAMI] You know, it was in that
temple that you first started
to turn from a
good-for-nothing coward
to a man that fights
with his squad.
Yeah, I still
remember that fight.
But tell me this.
Do you still remember
what I said to you?
Before you got strong?
I figure that you've probably
got your own way of
fighting, don'tcha?
Yeah. I've found
my way of fighting.
And now, I'm making strides
towards my next goal.
At least, I'm trying.
Good for you.
There's just one
more thing, though.
Sir?
[YAMI]
You used your spatial magic
to sic a giant squid leg
on us, didn't ya?
[FINRAL] It was a
spur-of-the-moment thing!
I'm sorry!
[YAMI] Yeah, not in
the mood for excuses.
Oh... Hey...
Welcome... back... guys.
What's up, Henry?
It's good to see ya!
Well, anyway. I want some chow.
[ASTA]
Yeah, I'm starving!
[VANESSA] What are you
making us, Charmy?
We'll start with a
nice seafood barbecue.
I wanna show off the natural
yumminess of the fish.
[GORDON]
A protein-rich meal!
[GAUCHE]
Wish I could send Marie some.
[SECRE]
I want to eat squid.
[FINRAL] Yeah, I'd be happy
if I never saw a squid again.
[NOELLE] I'll keep
getting stronger, Mom.
Watch me. I'm just
getting started.
[KAHONO]
Noelle! Asta!
You chase your goals
and keep getting stronger.
I'll chase mine until
I become an idol!
Next time on
Black Clover , Page 137:
"Charmy's Century of Hunger,
Gordon's Millennium
of Loneliness."
Cheer for me, 'kay?