[NARRATOR] Threatened
by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed
lost until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR]
Vetto of the Third Eye
cast an ancient Hex upon Asta.
His Black Bull compatriots
have dedicated themselves
to finding a way
to heal Asta's arms.
For their part, Noelle
and Finral call upon
a certain man, hoping
he might have a lead.
We'd like to talk!
Sure.
I was just getting out
of the bath, so--
[NOELLE screams]
[NARRATOR] The man they'd come
to see was Fanzell Kruger.
But how could he help?
Who was this mysterious man,
and what possible connection
could he have to Asta?
Our story begins
five months earlier.
[NARRATOR] Asta and Yuno
had received their grimoires,
but they had not yet set out
for the Magic Knights
Entrance Exam in
the royal capital.
Asta was camping in the woods
near Hage Village, diligently
training with the sword
he had recently been given.
[pants]
[yells]
Whoa...
I have no idea what
I'm doing... at all.
I mean, I've never
trained with a sword
before in my life.
I don't even know how
I'm supposed to hold it.
Does hacking at trees
really count as training?
[FANZELL screams]
If I were you, kid,
I would get outta
the way, and quickly!
Don't run right at me!
Hurry and jump to the side!
[panting]
Take that!
[BOAR 55A groans]
[FANZELL]
Very impressive.
You took out that big guy
in one blow. My mistake.
I was doin' some
fishing in the river,
and I guess I must've wandered
into the boar's territory.
Uh, yeah.
Anyway, name's Fanzell.
I'm something of
a nomad these days.
Nice to meet you.
[FANZELL]
Call me "Zell."
Okay, I'm Asta
from Hage Village.
[FANZELL]
It's a pleasure, Asta.
Now tell me, are those yours?
Yeah. Why do you wanna know?
[stomach growls]
So good! I thought
I was going to starve!
I haven't eaten
so much as a bite
in two whole days.
Never did catch any fish.
Awfully dense, aren't they?
It's amazing how they
just suck all the moisture
right out of your mouth.
Yeah, they do.
So, are you gonna tell me
why you're naked?
I didn't wanna get wet
while I was fishing.
What are these things?
You just ate them
without knowing?!
They're pop-potatoes,
a Hage Village specialty.
Cool.
Hey, are you okay?
--Here ya go!
--[FANZELL] Yes, please.
Thank you.
Ah!
What is this stuff?
It's got such a bitter taste.
It's my special moguro-leaf
juice for increasing
your magic power.
Well, I'm certainly
feeling better.
If you don't mind
coming to my house,
maybe I can find a way to
thank you for your help.
[ASTA]
Your house?
[FANZELL]
Well, to be honest,
I'm just kind of
squatting there.
[ASTA] I never knew there
were places this nice
way out in the woods!
Every now and then
you'll see one around.
Guess I should go ahead
and get some clothes on.
[FANZELL] Huh! A sword
that can nullify magic?
That's new to me.
It's new to me, too,
but this baby is what's
gonna get me through the
Magic Knights Entrance Exam.
That's why I've been holed up
here in the mountains training.
Yeah, that so?
What brings an old guy
like you up here, anyway?
"Old guy," huh?
I'm actually only 28,
thank you very much.
Twenty-eight?
No way! Wow!
You look so much older.
Right. Let's just
leave that there.
[FANZELL]
I'm waiting for someone.
[ASTA]
Kind of a weird meeting spot.
It's complicated.
[ASTA]
Okay.
So, tell me, Asta.
You're sleeping outside, right?
Why not stay with me while
you're training instead?
Really? That'd be
awesome, thanks.
Hold on, are you just
after my pop-potatoes?
Always treasure your
encounters and connections
with the people you meet.
True, they may not
have a concrete form,
but those experiences will
pile up in your heart
and keep you company.
Are you kidding me?
This guy's obviously
a total creep.
Are you actually going
to stay with him?
Okay! I think I'll
take you up on that.
Thanks a lot, Mister Zell.
[FANZELL] Great! Then let's
talk about chores.
How are you at choppin' wood?
[ASTA]
What?!
[ASTA grunting, yelling]
[yelling]
Man, this doesn't seem
to be working at all.
[FANZELL] Well, maybe it's
because all your weight
is in your knees.
Huh?
[FANZELL] The problem you've
been having is that you
can't manage a second blow once
you swing your sword, right?
It throws off your balance.
Uh, yeah.
I know something that
might help with that:
keep your toes pointed in the
same direction as your sword,
then you take a
half-step forward
with your right foot
to shift your weight.
Go on, try.
[yells]
[gasps, laughs]
Woo-hoo! I did it!
--I can't believe I actually...
--[FANZELL] Uh, yeah.
You did it. Picked it
up pretty fast, too.
That was impressive.
[ASTA]
That was amazing!
How'd you know that trick?
You fight with swords, too?
Well, no, not swords,
exactly. Hold on a sec.
[laughs]
Wind Creation Magic:
Emperor of Slashing Winds.
Whoa! So cool!
You see, it's not a true sword,
but rather my magic
taking on the shape of one.
It's the Emperor
of Slashing Winds.
I call it "Slashy" for short.
You're awesome at
naming stuff, too!
Well, anyway, working
with this thing is
how I picked up a
little swordsmanship.
Hey, then you can teach me?!
I'm sure anything
you know will help.
I dunno.
Just a few lessons, that's all.
Please! I'll work hard!
Sure, no problem.
Huh?
Sounds good.
It does, really?
[FANZELL]
Mm-hm!
Awesome, thank you so much!
All right! Yes!
I've got a teacher! Oh, yeah!
Awesome. Awesome. So cool!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
[FANZELL] However, there's
one thing I want you
to promise me in return.
Asta, why are you working
so hard to get stronger?
To become the Wizard King.
Ah. I see. Well, that's good.
Yes, it's very good.
Wait, you're not gonna laugh?
No. Why would I do that?
Because it's impossible
or whatever.
But how can you know
whether or not something
is impossible until
you've give it a try?
Listen closely.
I want you to make
me a promise, Asta.
That you'll only ever
use what I teach you
to make that dream come true.
Sure. What's that mean, though?
Just don't use what
you learn here for evil.
Use it to achieve your
goals, not as a tool
for harming the innocent
or bullying people.
I don't need anybody to tell
me not to do that stuff.
[FANZELL]
So, you promise?
[ASTA]
Yeah. I promise.
Okay. Then let's get to work.
Right! I'm ready
whenever you are!
[ASTA grunting, yelling]
No! You're too slow.
Don't pause between hits.
What we're after
is rapid-fire attack.
Right! [yells]
[FANZELL]
You really are fantastic, Asta.
Your defense and offense
are both solid,
and your footwork
is improving, too.
What I don't understand is,
if you're this strong,
then why didn't
you just take care
of that giant boar yourself?
Without either a sword
or my grimoire on me,
there wasn't a lot I could do.
And besides, my skills
with the sword
aren't anything
particularly advanced.
You just seem to be especially
good at putting them to use.
[ASTA]
I dunno.
I think it's because
you're especially good
at teaching them.
Heh! I did do some
teacher-y stuff
once upon a time, so maybe.
Oh, really?
The students that I
taught didn't think
very much of me, though. Ha, ha.
You know, I've had
more than 100 pupils,
but the way you're
progressing, you might rank
among the top three at least.
The top three?
Top two, maybe.
The highest ranked is kinda
out there, not even using
the sword as a sword, so I don't
know if that really counts.
Well, anyway.
Even if you are accepted
into a Magic Knight squad,
I think you'll turn out to be
a respectably skilled swordsman.
You really think so?
Then let's go.
We've got some more
training to do!
Whoa, not so fast!
We aren't even done eating yet.
[NARRATOR] Several more days
passed, until a visitor arrived.
I've returned, Master.
Sorry it took so long.
Who's that?
You're back! So, what did
you find out, Mariella?
[ASTA]
"Mariella"?
[FANZELL] One of my pupils.
She's helping me.
I've asked her to
track down my fiancée.
That girl's your student?
If you need to find your
fiancée, wouldn't it be better
just to go out and
look for her yourself?
The full explanation
is a bit complicated,
but I can't draw attention
to myself right now.
I'm Asta from Hage Village.
The old man here's teaching
me how to use the sword.
Nice to meetcha.
Please, this is no
ordinary "old man."
While it might be
true that he's old,
he is an amazing old man. So...
--[MARIELLA] Look...
--[FANZELL] But I'm... not old.
...he is not the kind of old man
that you can casually
refer to as "old man."
There are rules to follow
for this sort of thing.
--Like I told you...
--[FANZELL] I'm 28.
...and I don't see
what's so wrong
about calling an
old man "old man."
It's a simple matter
of perception.
If you truly realized
how amazing he was,
you would be addressing
him with the proper
amount of respect and deference.
But when you say "old man,"
it doesn't sound
the least bit
respectful or deferential.
How am I supposed to make
the words "old man"
sound respectful?
Maybe we could just
let it go now, huh?
Listening to you two bicker
isn't exactly doing wonders
for my self-esteem.
So, what about Dominante?
Where is she?
Forgive me, Master.
I don't know how
to say this, but...
I believe it's possible that
Domina has passed away.
[gasps]
Oh, no.
[NARRATOR] And so, Fanzell
shared his story with Asta.
Fanzell and his fiancée
Dominante had been members
of the Diamond Kingdom's army.
No longer able to
stomach the army's
extreme methods, the couple
plotted to desert but wound up
separated as they sought to
escape the kingdom's assassin.
Desperate to find his fiancée,
Fanzell asked his former
pupil and fellow deserter,
Mariella, to search for
her while he laid low.
Fanzell knew that
when he made a move,
the killer would, too.
Not wanting to endanger
Domina if she were
in hiding nearby, he was
forced to go to ground
in an abandoned house.
[ASTA]
Wow.
[MARIELLA]
Here's Domina's wand.
It was found where the assassin
was thought to
have attacked her.
That, and a great deal of blood.
[FANZELL]
I see.
If you'll excuse me, I need
a moment to myself now.
[knocking]
Master. Pardon me.
[MARIELLA]
I'm sorry, but...
There's something I need
to talk to you about.
Back when you helped me and
the other students escape.
Do you remember?
[FANZELL] Yeah. How's
everyone doing these days?
Oh, wow. That actually
got a smile out of you.
You know, it's funny
that you ask,
because everyone else
but me is dead.
Huh?
They were murdered by the
Diamond Kingdom's assassain.
Every last one of them.
What the hell are you doing?
This is my job now.
I do the kingdom's
dirty work, provide it with
useful intel, and dispose of
its defectors when necessary.
If I hadn't agreed to
cooperate with them,
then I would be as dead
as the others are now.
Don't worry, though--
we aren't going
to kill you here.
I was given
specific instructions
to bring you back alive.
And in case you're thinking
of trying to escape,
you should know this
building is surrounded.
[MARIELLA] That Mage Knight
has entered the final stages.
We'll need your advice
on finishing touches
to ensure proper functionality.
That is where you were
previously stationed, I believe.
[FANZELL]
It's Mars.
Sorry?
The boy has a name,
and it's Mars.
Stop talking about him like
he's some kind of weapon.
All right. Doesn't matter
to me one way or an--
[ASTA yells]
Are you okay?!
And you! What's your problem?
Aren't you grateful for what
the old man's done for you?
Yes, I am.
I recognize that the combat
techniques he taught me
when I was his student are
what's helped to keep me alive,
and for that, he still
has my respect.
If he didn't, why would
I ever be concerned
with the way in which
you address him?
But then why would you
do something like this?
[MARIELLA]
If I fixated on those details,
I could never get my job done.
So would you kindly
not interfere?
I doubt you want to die for
an old man you don't know.
I'd say that I know him
pretty well by now!
No, Asta. Please just
listen to Mariella.
You have to get outta here.
You promised me!
You said you'd only ever
use what I taught you
about the sword to
achieve your dream.
You shouldn't use your
skills here in defense
of some random old man,
so get going!
I mean it, run!
Like I said,
you're not just some
random old man to me!
Hey, don't worry about it.
I may be old, but I
can still handle
these goons without your help.
You're already wounded!
I'll make my own promise:
I swear not to die
at the hands of
these Diamond mages.
I'm gonna hold you to it.
No dying until I see you again,
you understand me?
Right!
[FANZELL]
I'm sorry, Asta.
This is for the best.
Domina...
[ASTA yelling]
[ASTA panting]
[FANZELL] Asta. Please.
I don't care what happens.
There's no hope left in me.
No reason to go on.
I'm so very tired of all this.
Just get out of here.
Leave me be.
No way!
A reason to live,
to keep going, to hope.
Life doesn't just hand
you those. It takes work.
You have to fight
to find them yourself.
[gasps]
If you're done moping,
I could use a little help here.
[grunts]
[ASTA grunts]
[ALL yell]
[FANZELL]
Wind Creation Magic:
Emperor of Slashing Winds.
Winter Wind.
[ASTA]
Yeah!
[DIAMOND MAGIC KNIGHTS groan]
That spell allows me to send out
a lot of Slashies at once.
I call it The Flying One.
Wow, what an awesome name!
You saw me at a
very ugly moment.
I'm feeling better
now, don't worry.
[ASTA]
Good!
[FANZELL]
Behind you!
[yelps]
He negated my spell?
What's wrong, old man?
Have you decided
to give up after all?
We each get to choose
for ourselves
when the time has
come to admit defeat.
And thanks to you
I realize that for me,
that day isn't today.
There's no way I'm
about to let this
bunch of idiots end me now.
We're withdrawing.
Huh?
[MARIELLA]
I'll bring up the rear.
Round up any casualties.
I want an orderly retreat.
[ASTA]
You guys are just leaving?
When you're staging an attack,
make sure to go in
with at least three times
the number of troops
as your target.
If your number is halved,
changed tactics.
If halved again, retreat.
Or, so a certain instructor
of mine told me once.
Don't think for a second
that this is over, though.
I'll spend my whole life
on your trail if I have to.
That's fine by me.
As of today, I've decided
I'm done running.
From you, from myself,
from anybody.
And I'm done being a coward.
Domina is out there
somewhere, alive.
I know she is.
I'll find her no matter what.
So you just try to keep up.
You hear that, Mariella?
I hope you're ready to deal
with his old-man smell
for the rest of your life!
Will you stop talking,
please? Words can wound.
I guess we'll both
do our best, huh?
[MARIELLA]
And...
I think you might be
learning the proper way
to say "old man."
Keep practicing.
[ASTA]
Are you really leaving already?
Yeah. I'll keep
looking for Domina,
no matter how long it takes.
When I finally have her,
I'll try to find a way to atone
for all the harm
I've done in my life.
I haven't figured
out exactly how
I'll manage that yet,
but considering my past,
it'll probably take many years.
Which means, I won't
be dying anytime soon.
You're the one I have to thank
for giving me that resolve.
I'm just glad I could help.
I should get going,
or it's gonna get
too hard to say goodbye.
--See ya.
--[ASTA] Right.
Hey, wait!
You're seriously gonna
leave, just like that?
Sure am.
See, I'm a guy who
likes to get things done.
I've been sittin'
around for too long,
and now I'm ready
to get to work.
Just like you should be
doing. Times a-wastin'!
What does that mean?
[FANZELL] You're a guy who
likes to get things done, too,
aren't you? So get going.
There's no reason to wait.
You have everything you
need to start making
your dream come true.
Come on, now's when
you decide to get
all teacher-y on me, old man?
See ya! Good luck!
[FANZELL]
Go become the Wizard King!
All right. Guess I'll
head back to the village.
--[BOAR 55B growls]
--[FANZELL yells]
Actually, I've got one
last lesson for you.
Take this monster down, will ya?
No way! You can do it yourself!
And why are you naked this time?
Don't tell me you
were fishing again!
[FANZELL]
I'll explain later, just help!
[ASTA]
Stay away from me!
[FANZELL]
Where are you, my Domina?
I know you're still
alive somewhere.
Uh, excuse me, miss, uh,
can I ask you something?
Wait, please don't run away!
Black Clover , Page 56:
"The Man Named
Fanzell, Continued."
Just ignore the fact
that I'm naked.