[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy
who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
[NARRATOR]
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world
and to become the
next Wizard King!
Your Majesty!
You know your wandering
privileges are suspended!
[JULIUS] I didn't think you'd
find me if I went this way.
Do you have any
idea how many years
I've been serving you?
Now, please go back to your
office and take care of
that mountain of paperwork.
But I already handled
everything for today.
What?
I understand your concern, Marx.
It's important to keep up
with reports and all.
But, to really get
to know my people,
I need to come out
and walk among them!
--[MARX] Please wait!
--[JULIUS gasps]
I wish I could let you go, sir.
But with that devil and
Spade threatening us,
the risk is just too great.
Yes, that's true.
I still only have a fraction
of my magic power,
so there isn't much
I can do at the moment.
Well then, I have a few
favors to ask of you, Marx.
You're about to be very busy!
[NOELLE]
Okay, Asta, get ready!
[ASTA]
Right!
[NOELLE]
Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Waterball!
[ASTA]
Go, go, go!
You need to fight harder!
You can't hold back just
because this is practice!
[NOELLE] All right, fine.
But you better not cry!
[NOELLE] Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Roar!
[ASTA growls, yells]
[NOELLE gasps]
Train for six months,
then we will fight together
to stop Megicula.
We're not there.
We haven't trained enough!
[ASTA grunts]
Aw, you blocked it.
You're no fun.
Huh? Uh, what?
It's Sally!
Good to see you, Asta!
How's it going?
Why are you here?
Don't tell me you escaped.
Nah, I wish!
Mr. Mushroom Head over there
brought me to visit!
I'd prefer it if you
didn't call me that.
[ASTA] Oh, yeah, that's the
Wizard King's assistant!
And, uh, some other guy!
Makusa, from the Magic
Item Research Lab.
[NOELLE]
Huh?
[ASTA]
You can make magic items?
[MAKUSA]
Yes!
His Majesty was impressed
by Sally's knowledge
of magical science, so he
asked her to invent an item
that would give us an edge in
the battle that's coming up!
I have my reservations, but...
Okay!
First off, I'm gonna need to
get some baseline data,
so I'll just experiment
on the two of you!
In your dreams!
Even if you have turned
over a new leaf,
only an idiot would
agree to that!
[ASTA]
Let's go!
Hey! Did you really
have to rip your shirt off?!
I gave you my word.
After the last fight,
I said do what you want to me.
[chuckles] I'm so glad
you remember that.
[ASTA]
Just try not to do anything
that hurts super bad, okay?
So you'll let her take
all your organs as long as
she numbs you first?
You might want to rethink that!
[MAKUSA] Organ removal?
She wouldn't, right?
[MARX] If things get too gory,
we may have to pull the plug
on the whole endeavor.
Now... Let's do it!
[chuckles]
Actually, here's a better idea.
I'm gonna save you
for last, Asta.
Huh?
[SALLY] Well, the thing I want
to make is supposed to increase
mana output, and you don't
have any to speak of.
Which means I should
probably start with you!
Look, I don't want anything
to do with this at all.
I'm royalty, and even if I
wasn't, I would still say no!
By the way, are your
squadmates here?
They're out. Assignments
and training and all that.
But most of them should
be back by now.
[GROUP]
Yikes!
Oh. I guess they're here--
Oops, I forgot I have a thing.
I should throw this out!
Hey, look at the time!
Lucky me! So many test subjects!
Hey, stop!
Come back!
You need our permission to
do that, and you don't have it!
Look, the Wizard King!
[GROUP]
Eh?
--[SALLY] Ha-ha!
--[yelling]
[MARX]
Sally! [growls]
Listen to me, you two!
Forget about us,
just stop her, right now!
We're on it!
[MAGNA panting]
'Kay, I think I'm
far enough away now.
I'm not letting that
psycho science chick
lay a finger on me-- Aww!
[yells]
Put me down, right now!
You are so dead!
Aw, but when I create
this new magic item,
it's gonna make you a lot
stronger, so don't you think
you should help me
out, Dumbglaspunk?
If you have to insult me, can
you not do it in shorthand?
So Glaspunk uses Flame Magic.
[MAGNA]
Stop making it shorter, dammit!
Which means the dark
magic equation should yield
a mana exponent of...
Ah! I know the perfect formula!
And now, using Sticky Salamander
as a temporary trial subject...
Observe!
[MAGNA]
Ah? Ah!
[gasps]
What the hell's happening?
There's so much
mana burning inside me,
I feel like I might melt!
I know! Pretty great, huh?
Uh-oh. This is way too much.
Make it stop or I'm gonna...
...blow... a fuse...
[SALLY]
Huh. I'm guessing that means
the dark magic equation
is still incomplete.
Maybe the liquid's
too concentrated.
Got some data, though!
Let's keep working!
No need to be scared!
I won't dissect you guys!
Transformation Magic--
[GAUCHE]
Hang on! Don't attack her!
Why? What is it?
Oh, wow! That's Marie!
I don't want anyone
to harm my precious angel!
You do know that's
not her, right, Gauche?
She's made of goo!
[GAUCHE] Goo or no goo,
that's still her face!
Are you ready?
You guys use combination
magic together,
so I wanted to test
you simultaneously!
You're pairing us up?!
That's so embarrassing!
Marie!
[VANESSA grunts]
[VANESSA] Come on, Vanessa, you
said you'd restrain yourself.
Ah, but this is a rare vintage
I may never see again!
That's obviously a trap.
Can we please get out of here?
[SALLY]
Now, the next experiment!
[CHARMY]
Ooh!
A tempting trail of cupcakes.
Wonder if it leads
to pastry paradise?
[CHARMY chomping]
Too easy!
Say no, Vanessa, you have to!
See? Told you it was a trap.
[NOELLE]
Finral and Vanessa!
[ASTA]
You guys okay?
Yeah. Why, did something happen?
[ROUGE meows]
It looks like
we got here too late.
We can't let Sally
hurt anybody else!
--[explosion]
--[BOTH gasp]
[CHARMY sighs]
Food... Food everywhere...!
Ugh, none of my tests
have been going the way
that I planned. I need
more data to work with.
--[ASTA] Hold it!
--[SALLY] Uh?
Charmy! Say something!
[CHARMY chuckles]
Asta, what gives?
You're supposed
to be the last one.
Did you get tired of waiting?
--[ASTA growls]
--Hey!
I won't go back on my word!
You can do what you want to me,
but leave my teammates alone!
You should go back on your word,
otherwise, this lunatic is
gonna chop you to bits!
We owe her. She's the reason
we made it to the capital.
Because of Sally's group, we
managed to save our friends!
That's why I have
to keep my promise to her!
[SALLY giggles]
Good boy!
It's important to be
a man of your word!
Just please give me
something to knock me out!
Oh, this won't hurt
a bit--you'll barely feel it!
Here goes!
[NOELLE]
Asta!
[SALLY giggles]
It's all mine now!
I can culture it later!
What? All you
wanted was my hair?
Weird.
Well, yeah.
Don't you remember
what you said?
That I could experiment
all I wanted,
as long as I didn't
harm anybody.
But in the end,
I guess I did cause them
a lot of distress, huh?
[ASTA chuckles]
[SALLY] Don't worry, they'll
all be back to normal soon.
Their mana just got
cranked up to the max,
and their bodies
kinda shut down.
Wow, Sally.
Crazy or not, you still kept up
your end of the deal!
Actually, you know something?
I don't think I can get by
with just your hair.
How 'bout some
nail clippings, too?
Sure, I don't mind!
[NOELLE] That's not how
you clip someone's nails!
While I'm at it, do you
mind if I draw your blood?
It's all in the name of science.
And I might as well take your
heart, lungs, and eyeballs, too!
Take the hair and get lost!
Test away!
If your research helps
people, I'm all for it!
[SALLY]
Ah...?
That was rough.
I'm so glad it's over now.
Time for a little payback!
You sick freak!
Calm down, guys.
Everyone's better now--
let's just move past it!
As for the data
that was gathered...
Wow!
I don't understand this at all,
but it's fascinating!
Makusa will investigate
these findings at the lab.
After that, the magic item
will be created.
Do your best, science guy!
And you work hard too, Sally!
[SALLY]
Okay!
[MAKUSA]
We've got this!
Well, at least
they got some solid data.
Let's hope that
it does some good.
[CHARMY, GREY]
Mm, mm!
You better not screw this up!
If you do, then you're dead.
[SALLY gasps]
What are you waiting for?
Use your Spatial Magic
and send them on their way.
Uh, right.
[FINRAL]
Why's she bossing me around?
[MARX]
Let's head back, Sally.
[SALLY]
Coming!
Research that helps people, huh?
Maybe he's onto something.
Good luck! See ya soon!
I hope you're right, Asta!
We're close to Arandom Village.
It's odd that you and I
were sent together,
since we're captains
of two different squads.
I don't care how strange it is.
My goal is to find anyone
who dares threaten our kingdom
and strike them down.
[MARX] What could've caused
the crisis in this village?
Your Majesty.
I've brought the two Magic
Knight Captains you called for.
Sorry to take you
away from your squads
when you're so busy.
No.
It's fine. What's wrong, sir?
Have either of you
heard tell of a place
called Arandom Village?
It's in the Forsaken Realm.
I happened upon it while
I was out wandering--
er, I mean investigating
different areas
of the Clover Kingdom.
According to several reports,
Arandom Village has begun
to suffer from a bandit
problem recently.
Then we should send a team
there to deal with them.
No, that won't be
enough to solve this.
I'm not sure why, but I have
a feeling that something
unfavorable is going on.
The only question is what.
[NOZEL]
Something unfavorable?
[FUEGOLEON]
Sounds ominous.
That's where you two come in.
You'll disguise yourselves
and mingle with the villagers.
Perhaps that way, you'll
learn something useful
about the bandits.
It's an undercover
investigation!
[MARX] Sounds like
he's thought this through.
Are these really our disguises?!
[MARX]
Listen, I hate to criticize,
but this only makes us
look more suspicious.
These outfits are our only hope.
We don't know how to conduct
ourselves like commoners,
so our best strategy is to hide
our appearance altogether.
Some nobles do forsake
their lives of luxury.
Perhaps people will assume
that's the case with us.
Right. That makes sense.
Anyway, where should we
begin gathering intel?
[NOZEL] The village square's
as good a place as any.
Perfectly sound.
And lest we forget,
the Wizard King said
we're supposed to act casual.
So let's do our
best to blend in.
[MARX] Blending in
isn't their strong suit.
Maybe if they could relax,
we'd be able to pull it off.
But I mustn't
overstep my station.
[MARX]
What happened here?
We knew there were areas
that hadn't been restored yet,
but this is true devastation.
It's unspeakable.
We'll have time to address
this matter eventually.
We need to focus
on the mission at hand.
I'll go this way.
I'll try here.
[sighs]
[FUEGOLEON]
Pardon me.
Huh? Hello there.
I don't believe
we've met before.
I'm Leon. I'm a traveling mage.
Yes, and the same goes for me.
My name's Mark.
Traveling mages, eh?
We heard about the bandits
that target this place,
and we'd like you to
tell us everything you know
so that we can
protect ourselves.
I don't know jack!
Why don't you go
bother somebody else?
[VILLAGERS murmuring]
[MARX]
They're wary of us because of
these so-called disguises.
[MARX] What should we do,
Fue-- er, I mean, Leon?
--[FUEGOLEON sighs]
--[JULIUS] Oh, yes!
If you three run into any
trouble while you're there,
there's a special word you
can say that'll probably
clear it up.
Chronovala.
Huh?!
You're kidding. No way!
[VENDOR 140A]
I can hardly believe it.
Are you friends of Chronovala?
[MARX gasps]
[VENDOR 140A] That old woman was
a huge help to our village!
One time, when business
was really slow,
she rustled up a ton
of customers for me!
[VENDOR 140A]
Man, I made a fortune that day!
But then suddenly,
she disappeared.
So, how's that sweet
little lady been doing?
[MARX]
Chronovala... Wait. Chrono.
[gasps]
[MARX]
Novachrono! I get it!
When His Majesty
wandered out here,
that was the alias he used!
[GUY 140B]
You guys know Chronovala?
[GUY 140C]
Everyone loves her!
[VENDOR 140A]
Here, take this!
Huh?!
All my fields were
destroyed a while back,
so I can't offer you much.
I couldn't possibly
take it for free.
Will this cover it?
Huh? What?! All this yul?
Forget the carrot,
this much would buy you
my whole inventory!
Go ahead and keep the rest.
Use it to help
restore the village.
You sure that's okay?
That's crazy!
I wonder who they are.
Apparently, they're friends
of Chronovala's.
[MAYER]
Hmm.
[MARX]
King Julius is amazing.
They respect him so deeply,
without even knowing it's him.
So much for not drawing
attention to ourselves
while we're in town.
Hopefully,
he's doing a better job.
Oh my goodness, do you know
Chronovala, too, sir?
That incredible woman
saved my sweet baby's life!
[NOZEL]
Really?
I went into labor
while I was out in
the fields one day, and she
called for a doctor to help me!
I even named him
Vala, after her!
Here, would you
like to hold him?
Oh no, that's-- All right...
[giggles]
[NOZEL sighs]
[NOZEL]
I don't think I've held a baby
since Noelle was this tiny.
[MARX]
Noze.
Noze?
[MARX] Everyone here seems to
know Kin--er, I mean Chronovala.
[NOZEL]
Yes, I've noticed.
My name is Mayer, and I'm
the mayor of this village.
There isn't much that we
can offer you, but we'd like
to invite you gentlemen
to stay for the night.
Oh, yeah, great idea!
Stay with us!
Our food's in short supply,
but we can cook for you, too!
What do you think?
We have no reason to decline.
We were told we
should mingle amongst
the villagers. And this
is the perfect chance.
Um, well, I guess
that's that, then.
In the end, we didn't
learn anything about
the bandit attacks.
And it's not just that.
We still don't know what
"unfavorable" activity
is going on here.
Shh.
What? What's happening?
[NOZEL]
I knew it.
[VENDOR 140A]
I think they're asleep.
[GUY 140A]
Let's go.
[BANDITS yell]
Just as I thought!
You must be the group of bandits
that we've heard about!
[VENDOR 140A]
So what if we are?
Give us your money, now!
[LADY 140B]
Unless you want to get hurt.
[VENDOR 140A]
Take them down!
[GUYS grunting]
[VENDOR 140A groans, grunts]
What? That can't be right!
You did this?
[groaning]
I wish I could say
that it came as a shock.
It's over now, everyone.
But, sir--!
We knew this would happen,
even though we only
did it so we could survive!
After the Eye of
the Midnight Sun attacked,
our village was
left in shambles.
We had hoped to receive
aid from the royal capital,
but no one ever came.
So we were plunged even
deeper into poverty than before.
That being said, despite our
intent to rebuild our village,
we were still committing
a terrible crime.
[sighing]
I led my people to
engage in this behavior.
Therefore, I ask that
you allow me to take
all the punishment myself!
--[gasping]
--What? You can't do that!
You were only trying to help us!
[MARX] I had no idea
things were so dire.
If we'd been quicker
to address the problem,
this wouldn't have happened.
[VENDOR 140A] We can't let the
mayor take the blame on his own!
[LADY 140B] If you're going
down, we're going down with you!
[MAYER]
No, you mustn't!
[VILLAGERS whimpering]
[gasps]
--[gasping]
--This can't possibly be real!
Lord Fuegoleon and Lord Nozel!
[VENDOR 140A] Two of
the Magic Knight Captains!
[LADY 140B]
Hmm?!
You're obviously in need
of our assistance,
so we can overlook
what you've done.
There you go again,
being too soft.
They're bandits.
They should be arrested
and tried for their crimes.
[FUEGOLEON] Well, I'd say
you're being too harsh.
[gasping]
I order you all
to participate in
the reconstruction of
every village in this area!
A crime is still a crime,
and you must atone
for what you've done.
--[gasping]
--So, we're... forgiven?
I swear, the capital
hasn't forsaken you.
But it seems that
we weren't entirely aware
of your situation.
We're going to make
even greater strides to restore
this kingdom, so please
have faith in us.
[sobbing]
[MAYER]
Thank you so much!
[NOZEL] That's everything
we have to report from
our time in Arandom.
Great job, Captains.
Seems like you
made the right choice.
We've sent some knights
to the other villages.
That way, we can determine
what sort of aid each one needs,
and how much.
[JULIUS] Hmm. As Wizard King,
my job, and yours as well,
is to ensure that all
of our people can
live safely and peacefully.
And now that you've spent
some time with them,
perhaps you've learned
to see their situation
in a new light?
[NOZEL]
Of course.
[FUEGOLEON]
That's why he sent us.
Captains, from now on,
I want you to work even harder,
to lead the Magic Knights
and protect this kingdom!
[BOTH]
Yes, Your Majesty!
[JULIUS]
Hmm. Don't let me down.
Now that that's taken care of,
I think I'll wander
around by myself.
Certainly not.
No? Well. Then I suppose
I'll check in with Yami.
I'll tell you, Marx,
all this sitting around
is driving me batty.
[MARX sighs]
[MARX] I know you feel
useless, but right now,
the Clover Kingdom needs
you more than you realize.
[NARRATOR] Since his squadmates
are mostly royals and nobles,
Yuno struggles to
find common ground.
Black Clover , Page 141:
"The Golden Family."
Just like Asta,
Yuno also possesses
the magic of never giving up.