[ASTA]
It's not over. I'm not done.
I will be the Wizard King.
[REVCHI]
The Wizard King? You're joking.
The thing is, these
chains can measure
the magic power of anyone
they come in contact with.
And you have none,
not a single drop.
[gasps]
You were probably born that way.
I guess this explains why
you didn't get a grimoire.
To possess not the slightest
bit of magic in a world
where magic is everything?
Why, that makes you a rare
and precious bird, indeed!
[REVCHI laughs]
[ASTA]
If that's true, then...
No matter how hard
I push myself,
I'll never be able to use magic.
You know, I really can't think
of anything more pitiful.
Forget about becoming
the Wizard King,
you'll be lucky
to just get a job.
I bet your friend,
the genius over there,
is having a good laugh at
your expense right about now.
[ASTA]
Yeah, maybe.
Yuno's so great, the
four-leaf clover chose him.
Then there's me.
This world has no use
for someone like you,
a poor, magic-less fool.
You might as well give
it all up right now.
You were born a loser,
you worthless runt.
[ASTA]
Yeah. He's right.
No matter how hard I try,
I guess there are some things
that just aren't possible.
So, I might as well give--
[YUNO] Hey! Who are you
calling a loser?
Asta.
It's true that you aren't going
to become the Wizard King.
Not ever.
[REVCHI]
You hear that?
Even your little friend
knows that it's impossible.
That's because I am going
to be the Wizard King.
[REVCHI]
What?
You're wrong about Asta, Revchi.
[YUNO]
Very wrong.
Asta's no loser. He's my rival!
[ASTA gasps]
Huh?
This is who you would
claim as your rival?
The only person in the
world without magic?
You. Get off of me.
[REVCHI gasps]
[ASTA] Sorry you had to see me
at such a weak moment, Yuno.
Just... give me a second.
That's all. Then I'll
destroy this guy.
[ASTA]
Is that... a grimoire?
[YUNO]
I knew it.
Like you wouldn't
be chosen, Asta?
There's no way.
[YUNO]
This is what you've always done.
You have a way of making
the impossible, possible.
[YUNO]
Now, and back then.
[ASTA]
I'm gonna be the Wizard King.
I'll keep you, and
everybody else safe.
No more worrying
about food or money.
You'll have everything
you ever wanted.
I'll prove it.
I'll show them all.
Show them? Prove what?
That even if you're poor,
a commoner and an orphan,
you can still become
the Wizard King.
[YUNO panting]
[YUNO]
W-Wait up!
[panting]
[yelps]
[ASTA]
Yuno!
Oh, jeez! Are you okay?
[ASTA]
Wanna hand?
Yeah, thank you.
[ASTA] Sheesh. You're such
a crybaby sometimes.
[YUNO]
I know.
C'mon, you're gonna be okay.
You know I've always
got your back, right?
Yeah!
[ASTA]
Okay! Let's get going, then.
They're all waiting
for us up top!
[laughs]
This bread is yummy.
Yummy, but a bit hard, maybe.
Amazing, Sister Lily!
You're the best cook and
awesomest baker ever!
Hey, when I grow up,
we should get married,
and you can cook for me.
Actually, Father's the
one who baked that.
So maybe you should marry him.
Nuh-uh! He's gross!
I wanna marry you, Sister,
not some old man!
Sister!
Marry, marry, marry me!
[LILY]
That's a good boy, Asta.
I'm telling you,
it'll never work.
She can't marry.
She's, um... Sister Lily
is a woman of the cloth.
I'm not giving up!
I'll keep asking her
till I'm old and gray.
She'll say yes eventually!
[YUNO]
Well, good luck.
[LILY] "And so, a deep, cold,
and seemingly endless darkness
covered the world.
It was on the brink of being
destroyed by a ruthless demon."
That demon's a jerk!
[LILY] "But then, one brave
mage stepped forward."
[ASTA]
Whoa!
[LILY] "Hoping to dispel
the darkness and bring dawn
to the world,
he battled the demon."
Huh?
[LILY] "Finally, he defeated
the foul creature,
and when he was finished,
the world was a brighter place
than it had ever been before."
"The long night ended at last,
because the mage had brought
dawn to the world."
[ASTA]
Hooray!
[LILY] "The triumphant mage
was hailed as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend."
[BOTH]
Wow! The Wizard King?
[LILY]
"Peace and prosperity reigned."
[BOTH gasp]
[ASTA]
Hey, Sister.
There's still one now, right?
A Wizard King, I mean.
Yes.
[LILY] That role is one of
the most vital in the kingdom.
The duty has been passed
down throughout the ages,
from one Wizard King
to the next.
[LILY] With the power of
his magic to protect us,
we live in relative safety.
It's because of the Wizard King
that the Clover Kingdom
is so peaceful.
[ASTA]
Oh, wow!
[YUNO] So, he's a really
important person?
[LILY] Yes. Second only
to our nation's king.
[YUNO]
Huh...
[ASTA]
All right! It's settled.
[LILY] What do you mean?
What's settled?
[ASTA]
I'm...
...gonna be the Wizard King.
Uh...
[ASTA]
Sister?
[LILY] Sorry. I'm
surprised, that's all.
So, where did this come from?
[ASTA] Well, he beat
the demon, didn't he?
So, he's way strong,
and he's super cool, too!
I wanna be just like
him when I grow up.
And, that's not all.
[gasps]
He's important.
The Wizard King has power,
and that means
I can make all of
your lives better.
[ASTA]
Think about it.
Wearing nice clothes, filling up
on as much food as you want.
I'll rebuild the church. Yeah,
I'll fix this crumbling dump!
[LILY]
Now, don't call it that.
[ASTA] Just wait, Sister!
You'll be living the high life!
Well, that sounds
wonderful. Right, Yuno?
[YUNO]
The Wizard King.
[ASTA] I'm gonna be
important when I grow up!
I'll be the Wizard King.
So, you should marry me!
Those two subjects
are entirely unrelated.
[sputtering]
[ASTA]
I won't give up! I'm not done!
[LILY]
Yes, you are.
[ASTA]
Not done! Not done! Not done!
[LILY]
Very done.
[giggles]
[exhales]
[ASTA yells]
I don't understand
what's wrong with me!
No matter how hard I try,
I still can't use any magic.
[ASTA]
Hey, let me help Sister!
I can hang the laundry
up to dry for you.
Thank you. That would
be very helpful.
Okay! So you'll marr--
I won't.
Marr--
No way.
Mar...
Still no.
[ASTA] I'm begging you!
Please marry me!
[NASH crying]
It's not going to help
if you start crying, too.
But, poor Nash. He...
He just seems so upset.
[NASH crying]
Wait! Let me take care of it!
Okay...
[ASTA] I mean, I'm gonna
be the Wizard King, right?
Calming down a baby or two's
gotta be a piece of cake
compared to that!
Now, hand 'im over!
Hush, now, you're okay.
There's nothing for you
to cry about, I swear.
Everything is totally awesome!
[LILY]
There, there, little one.
Whoa!
Way to go, Wizard King.
That was impressive.
Aw, you shut up.
[HIGH PRIEST]
Down we go.
Sorry, I need to borrow
one of the youngsters
to run an errand for me.
Me, me, me, me!
I'll do it, Father!
I need this letter delivered
to the village chief.
It shouldn't take too long.
Me! Me, me, me. Me.
[HIGH PRIEST]
It's a very important letter.
Could you deliver
it for me, Yuno?
What? Me? Why?
Like I said, it's a
very important letter.
I'm worried about
trusting it to Asta.
Please just do it.
I have to meet with the chief
of the neighboring village.
We won't make it
through the winter
unless we can get
some food from them.
Our stores are low.
The pop-potatoes
are especially low.
I'll go. You can just stay here.
Father's giving me
this responsibility.
So, I'm going to take it.
Are you sure? You'll be okay?
Of course. I'll be fine.
I won't be long.
[REKKA] Well, come on.
Don't just stand there.
There's firewood to chop.
And, if you can't do magic,
we might as well
put you to use for manual labor.
Yeah, and what have
you done today?
Have you even dug up
the pop-potatoes?
[REKKA]
I finished doing that hours ago.
[ASTA growls]
[LILY]
Look at that sky.
It'll be a cold one tonight.
[BARKEEP 2A]
I've had enough!
You're not welcome here anymore!
[DRUNK MAN 2A]
Whaddya think yer doin'?
[BARKEEP 2A]
If you're gonna keep drinkin',
then you'd best be ready to pay.
I'm not in the habit of
givin' out freebies, pal.
I don't know why
anyone would wanna
drink in this dump anyway!
[muffled laughing]
[DRUNK MAN 2A]
Damn it.
Whoa. Stood up too fast.
[YUNO yelps]
Ow.
[YUNO]
I should be more careful.
The snow's really piling up.
[VILLAGE CHIEF 2A]
Great, thank you very much.
You can tell the priest
that you successfully
delivered his message.
[YUNO] Yes, sir. I should
be heading back now.
It's getting late.
Be careful out there
in the dark, son.
I will be. Thank you, sir.
[panting]
[YUNO]
I'm, uh... I'm sorry.
[LILY] It's late.
I wonder where Yuno is.
I'm starving to death, here.
Father hasn't returned from
the other village, either.
[ASTA] Why cant we just
eat without them?
You should be
worrying about Yuno,
not your stupid stomach.
[ASTA]
Yeah, yeah.
--[thud]
--[YUNO grunts]
[DRUNK MAN 2A laughs]
Give that back to me. It's mine!
[DRUNK MAN 2A]
Not anymore.
I'll get a nice chunk
of change for this.
Give me back my--
[DRUNK MAN 2A]
Shut up!
Respect your betters, you brat.
Filth like you doesn't deserve
something as fine as this.
Just give... it back.
[YUNO]
It's mine. Give it back.
[laughs] You've gotta
be kidding!
Am I supposed to be intimidated
by the puny urchin
and his puny spell?
You fight me with
that, and you die.
[ASTA]
Yuno!
[ASTA growls]
[ASTA groans]
Another brat?!
That belongs to Yuno!
Give it back!
[yells]
--[ASTA growling]
--[YUNO gasping]
[grunts] Give it
back right now!
[YUNO whimpers]
Get your filthy little
hands off of me.
Damn you! Stupid twerp!
[grunts, groans]
[pants]
I'm not done with you yet, jerk!
[DRUNK MAN 2A]
Hey!
[yelps]
I'm still not d--
[DRUNK MAN 2A]
Persistent little bugger!
[ASTA]
Still not done!
[DRUNK MAN 2A]
Stop, damn it!
[ASTA growls]
I'm not done yet!
[ASTA growling]
[DRUNK MAN 2A]
What the hell?
Damn brat wouldn't give up.
I've got better things to do.
Asta! I'm so sorry!
[YUNO whimpering]
It's my fault. I should've...
C'mon, don't sweat it.
It's like I said.
I've always got your back.
You know that.
[YUNO]
Asta...
This is what you've always done.
You have a way of making
the impossible, possible.
[REVCHI]
But you don't have any magic!
How could you get a grimoire?
And that sword?
What kind of freak
of nature are you?
[yells]
You took my spell
and turned it into
your magic power?
Even without
traditional magic power,
I will be the Wizard King!
[screams]
My magic is never giving up!
[ASTA yells]
[REVCHI grunts]
[ASTA pants]
I always figured,
if I can't use magic,
at least I can use my body.
I trained to build up
strength, and it looks like
it's finally paid off.
[YUNO]
Asta.
Asta! Hang in there.
I'm sorry. It's all
my fault. I'm so sorry.
[ASTA] This? Please.
Don't worry about it.
This is nothin'. After all,
I'm gonna be the
Wizard King, right?
I'm gonna be the Wizard King.
I'll keep you and
everybody else safe.
No more worrying
about food or money.
You'll have everything
you ever wanted.
[ASTA] I'll prove it.
I'll show them all.
"Show them"? Prove what?
That even if you're poor,
a commoner and an orphan,
you can still become
the Wizard King.
You really think so?
[ASTA]
Yeah!
Commoners? Orphans?
Anybody can do it.
As long as they're
willing to work hard.
[YUNO]
Anybody?
Even me, and even you.
[gasps]
I... I'm never
going to cry again.
I've decided.
Whatddya mean?
I'll do it, too.
I'm going to become
the Wizard King.
I'll work hard and get
strong so I can protect you
and everybody else.
I'll do whatever it takes,
and I'll never give up!
Check it out, Yuno,
I got a snazzy new grimoire.
Okay, it's a little beat-up,
but I'll treasure it all
my life, anyway. I will!
[laughs]
[YUNO]
Well. You saved me yet again.
[ASTA]
Huh?
[YUNO]
I will repay my debt one day.
Asta. We made a promise.
Do you remember it?
[ASTA] So, you wanna be
the Wizard King, too?
That means...
Yuno.
[YUNO]
Asta.
[ASTA, YUNO]
You are my rival!
I actually can't believe
you remember it.
The way you've
been acting lately,
I was pretty sure
you'd forgotten.
Like I'd be friendly with
someone I consider my rival.
You showed me it was possible.
Gave me hope.
That even though
we're poor orphans,
commoners,
we can still make
something of ourselves
in this world.
And to prove that...
[ASTA] To make Sister Lily
and everybody else happy...
[ASTA, YUNO] ...we'll fight to
see who will be the Wizard King.
Whatever it takes.
[ASTA]
So what if I can't use magic?
I'm still gonna join
a Magic Knight squad
and become the Wizard King.
Black Clover , Page Three:
"To the Royal Capital!"
My magic is never giving up!