[NARRATOR] Within the clover's
fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
[NARRATOR] Asta, born
unable to harness mana,
was granted the
power of Anti-magic
from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability
to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members
of Spade Kingdom's
Dark Triad also possess
powers from the devils
of the underworld and used them
to launch an invasion on
the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from
his belief in himself
and from the support
of his friends,
Asta continues to fight
for the safety of this world.
Ooh, I just had a great idea!
Hey, Megicula, let's not
kill her after all.
[MEGICULA]
Oh? And why is that?
She's the wisdom
of the Heart Kingdom.
I thought it best
to eliminate her.
[VANICA] Eh, who cares
about that stuff?
We should take her back
to Spade with us.
[gasps]
By the way, Noelle.
I just remembered, I did fight
some lady with armor like yours.
What was her name?
Oh, yes: Acier!
She was so much fun!
[VANICA]
And, as I recall,
her powers got super
strong when she saw
that I took some poor
little kid hostage.
[VANICA] So, if I kidnap
Loropechika here,
then I can only assume you
would get a lot stronger, too!
I can't pretend that
I understand this feeling,
but you're desperate to protect
her because she's your friend.
Right?
None of our people
are going to mind,
so I say we go for it.
[MEGICULA] You know, Vanica,
you're so full of surprises.
It's great.
[VANICA]
Well, now that's decided,
I guess we're done here.
Loropechika! And Noelle!
What is it, my lady?
We're leaving for the
Spade Kingdom already?
Do you think we could
wait a minute or two?
I've almost got
this little beauty
--right where I want her and--
--[VANICA] Don't talk to me.
You're disgusting.
As a matter of fact,
I have no use for you anymore.
[ROBERO]
Huh?
[ROBERO groaning]
[VANICA] Curse-Warding
Magic: Exploding Life.
[MIMOSA gasps]
[MIMOSA]
His mana's expanding!
Wait. Lady Vanica.
What are... you...?
This is what's
called a curse bomb!
That devil's power I
gave you Dark Disciples?
Well, it's just about to go...
Boom, bang, crash, pow!
[yelps]
No! What's happening to me?
You wouldn't! Would you?
Please don't,
Lady Vanica! I beg you!
[gasping, screaming]
[VANICA] This whole area's
gonna blow sky-high!
But I'm sure you can survive
that, right, tough girl?
And when you do,
I'll be waiting
for you in Spade!
Get strong for me!
Fare thee well,
my little Noelle!
Vanica!
[ROBERO screams]
[gasps]
[laughing]
[ASTA grunts]
[laughs]
[ASTA yells]
[ASTA]
Whoa!
[YAMI] The kid's Anti-magic
is the key to winning this.
Somehow, we gotta land a hit
on that guy with Asta's sword.
[ASTA]
Crap! I'm holding him back,
I know I am!
Captain Yami is the only
reason I'm not dead yet!
Even with six
months of training,
I'm still no match for this guy!
Don't give up now!
Keep the attacks coming!
I'm ecstatic.
You have no idea what an
immense pleasure this is for me!
[ASTA] I may not understand
these powers I have inside,
but our only hope is for me
to use them at full blast!
Hey, you've been watching,
right, devil?
Good to see ya.
[screams]
What the heck are you?
[laughs] I can't believe
you'd say that to me.
I've been your closest
companion for a while now.
Right, I remember.
[ASTA]
We've met like this before,
but you seem
different this time.
[DEVIL]
I'll kill them. Kill them all!
They must pay!
Kill. Kill!
Earlier, I could feel
your rage welling up.
I don't know your reasons,
but you wanna beat
this guy, too, don't you?
I should've had a real
heart-to-heart with you
a long time ago, so I could
understand you better.
No time like the present.
Come on, lend me
your powers! Hurry!
[laughs] Okay, sure.
I guess I can let you
take my true strength
for a little spin!
Sadly, it won't work with
things the way they are.
I'll need you to give me
something equal in return.
In return?
You're gonna let me take
a part of your body!
[laughs] Remember, you're
making a deal with a devil.
You sure you don't mind?
No matter what it takes.
Even if it means
becoming a devil.
I have to push past my limits!
I'm gonna need
backup over here.
Asta!
[ASTA] When Captain Yami
said those words,
it meant everything
in the world to me!
If I can't get through this,
then I'll never become
the Wizard King!
You know, kid, I like you.
Come join our crew.
And then, once we're done,
you go and become
the Wizard King.
I will, Captain Yami.
But before I do that,
I want to prove
I've become the person
you always hoped I would be!
All right, it's a deal.
Knock yourself out.
[DANTE] Gravity Magic:
Gravity Singularity!
[ASTA]
As of right now...
[laughing]
[FINRAL, VANESSA, GREY gasp]
This is it! All I've got!
[ASTA growls]
[DEVIL]
Hey, kid.
You should know, that right arm
isn't the same as it was
back when I was just giving you
a little power at a time.
Now it's become power!
You've got 50 seconds
till your body gives out!
[ASTA growls]
That's plenty!
[DANTE laughs]
Such marvelous work!
[DANTE yells]
[YAMI] I can tell from
the way he's fighting;
he's on guard when Asta attacks.
That must be Anti-magic
coming from his right arm.
If he can get at least
one decent hit in there,
we can win this!
Show him what
you're made of, Asta!
[YAMI]
He's crushing it!
Better step up my game!
Let's show him together!
[ASTA, YAMI yell]
[ASTA yells]
[ASTA yelps]
[DANTE laughs]
[YAMI yells]
What's that supposed to do?
[ASTA yells]
[DANTE grunts]
[DANTE laughs]
[yells]
Excellent fighting
technique, you two!
[DANTE]
But don't stop.
Give me more!
[BOTH gasp]
[VANESSA]
Asta.
[FINRAL]
Yami!
I know you're not done yet.
Keep the entertainment coming!
[FINRAL]
Look at them.
They're moving insanely fast.
[FINRAL]
But they're totally in sync.
--[ASTA yells]
--[YAMI grunts]
[laughs]
[FINRAL]
Despite everything,
they actually look like
they're having fun.
[DANTE]
Fight me.
Fight with all you've got.
It won't matter because, in the
end, I will crush everything.
You've already lost!
[laughs]
Dweller!
Destroyer!
Ah! You're mine!
[DANTE cackles]
[DANTE]
I am immortal!
This is the end!
The end for you.
[gasps]
[ASTA panting]
Looks like we haven't
lost after all.
[grunts]
Well done, Asta,
you crazy son of a bitch.
Thanks.
That was incredible!
You totally took him down!
I mean, wow.
That battle--it was amazing!
Yeah, guess so.
Damn straight it was.
Did... you... beat him?
[GAUCHE sighs]
What happened?
[GREY]
Gauche.
You didn't die! Thank goodness.
You're really okay!
Are you okay?
[GREY]
Huh?
[GREY yelps]
Um. I'm so sorry!
What are you
apologizing for?
Yeah, something is up
with those two, for sure.
Going somewhere?
What's up?
[sighs] He may be out of
commission now, even dying,
but we should tie
him up to be safe.
[FINRAL]
Oh, good point!
I'm glad we're finally finished
with this psycho stalker.
I've better ways
to spend my time.
Though, we did capture the
enemy's top devil-possessed.
So I guess it's happily ev--
[YAMI gasps]
[FINRAL]
Man, I am officially beat.
--I can't wait to...
--[thudding]
[FINRAL]
No. Yami!
[YAMI] I screwed up.
He's got me pinned.
[FINRAL]
Who is that?
And there.
It's the captain
of the Golden Dawn!
[DANTE] The key to the
underworld isn't you, per se.
It's a magical channel known
as the Tree of Qliphoth.
To bring that channel into
being, we need Dark Magic
and World Tree Magic,
both at the arcane stage.
So this was the source
of the magic fluctuation
I was sensing.
There's no salvation for them.
We hold existence itself
in the palms of our hands.
You gave a speech
like that, then lost.
What a pathetic leader
you turned out to be.
A spatial magic user.
[YUNO]
You bastard!
[ZENON] I'm still feeling the
effects of my previous fight.
Fortunately, he shouldn't
be a problem anymore.
I'd've liked to take this
one, too, but time's up.
Over my dead body!
Don't let him get away!
[VANESSA]
The world will end!
[HENRY]
Captain!
[HENRY grunts]
[ASTA]
Please. Devil!
I'll let you claim
another part of my body
if that's what it'll take!
Please, I need to borrow
your powers again!
--[DEVIL] No.
--[gasps]
[DEVIL] Your body can't
even move anymore.
It doesn't matter how desperate
you are to keep fighting.
You wouldn't be able
to handle another deal.
So that's it, then? No deal?
[DEVIL] That's right.
Because you're weak.
Finral, a portal! Go, Rouge!
[ROUGE meows]
[VANESSA]
Just touch the captain once.
That's all it'll take!
[ROUGE meows]
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
[ASTA gasps]
Captain Yami, no!
[ZENON] Heh. We've gotten what
we need from the Clover Kingdom.
[FINRAL]
No. They have Yami.
What are we supposed to do now?
Black Clover , Page 168:
"Stirrings of the Strongest."