[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy
who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world,
and to become the
next Wizard King!
It's finally time
for us to go and train
in the Heart Kingdom!
[FINRAL] I swore I'd become
worthy of Lady Finnes's love
and earn my place as the
head of the House of Vaude.
If I fail, it'll all be a lie!
The Spirit Guardians
won't break,
even if I give it my all, right?
This'll be so much fun!
Yup! I'm gonna get
seriously strong out there!
[LUCK]
Get as tough as you want.
I'll still be way
ahead of you, Magna!
[MAGNA]
You wanna bet?
[NOELLE] I have to take out
Megicula and avenge my mother.
But first, I need to
build up my skills!
[ASTA]
Awesome, everybody's here!
[MIMOSA]
Hi, Asta!
Well, it's about time
that you showed up, rival!
[CHARLOTTE]
Training in another land.
I wish Yami were here.
[MIMOSA]
By the way, Asta.
Yuno wanted me to
give you a message.
What is it?
All he said was,
"I'll get stronger
with my squad." Weird.
Not sure why he didn't
wanna come with us;
he obviously would've
learned a lot.
Nah, Yuno's gonna get better
no matter where he trains.
I won't let him outdo me though!
I see that you've all arrived.
We all appreciate
the invitation, sir.
Come with me.
The queen is waiting.
[LOROPECHIKA]
I see a few new faces
that I haven't had the
pleasure of meeting.
Welcome to the Heart Kingdom.
Under normal circumstances,
I would've ordered a magnificent
feast to celebrate your visit,
but unfortunately, it wasn't
possible at this time.
It pains me that we
cannot offer you more,
but please accept our greetings.
Is something wrong?
I'm sorry.
I know it's rude to interrupt,
but that person
resting in your lap...
Why, it's Charmy, obviously.
[NOELLE]
No, trust me, we know who it is,
but what the heck
is she doing here?
[CHARMY] Wherever snacks be,
you'll find me!
[MAGNA]
Sounds about right.
Must the Black Bulls always
be so unprofessional?
Maybe it's not such
a big deal, though.
Queen Loropechika seems
to be fine with it.
Well, if it's okay
with the queen,
then it's okay with me.
She seems to be pretty relaxed
for a monarch, doesn't she?
I don't know if "relaxed"
is really the word I would use.
Brave Magic Knights
of the Clover Kingdom,
we're honored.
[CHARLOTTE] It's a privilege
to be in your care.
[LEOPOLD]
Yeah, thanks for havin' us!
Now then, about your training.
Gaja, would you please explain?
The first thing you all
need to know, is that Spade
has already captured most of the
Diamond Kingdom's bases,
and that their invasion is
at a standstill for right now.
In other words, it won't
be long before they decide
to turn their focus on us
or the Clover Kingdom.
To prepare for that, we will
be subjecting each of you
to rigorous training in order
to accelerate your development.
Sounds good to me!
That's not a problem.
As you've explained,
it is imperative that
we improve quickly.
[GAJA] Then allow me to
introduce the Spirit Guardians
who'll be teaching you.
[GAJA]
Guardian of Earth, Sarado.
It's nice to meet you!
[GAJA]
Guardian of Plants, Potrof.
Let's learn together!
[GAJA]
Guardian of Fire, Floga.
Work up a sweat!
[GAJA]
Guardian of Wind, Smurik.
They seem like a pretty
serious crowd, huh?
Oh, man, I can't decide
which one of 'em
I wanna spar with most!
Captain Charlotte
and Lady Mimosa.
I would like you both to begin
your training with Sarado.
Understood, sir.
We are ready.
Great, I'm looking
forward to it!
[GAJA] Finral, you'll be
learning from Smurik first.
Yes, sir!
[GAJA] Captain Rill, I'd like
you to start with Potrof.
All right, let's get to it!
I'll see you in
the forest then!
We'll be sticking to attributes
for the rest of you.
The fire mages
will work with Floga.
Don't go easy on me,
you got that?
It seems you're both
taking this seriously!
I can't wait to meet
the two of you!
And you'll begin
training with me, Luck.
As long as you
put up a good fight,
I don't care who I train with.
Hang on!
Don't you think you might be
forgetting about somebody here?
[GAJA] I'm sorry, but you
don't possess any mana.
Spirit Guardians are gifted,
but we can't create
power out of nothing.
[ASTA]
Huh?
Well, then what was
the point of me coming?
[GAJA] You're one of
the arcane-stage mages,
which means you'll give us
an advantage against the devil.
I would like you to
face me in a battle,
so that I can get a
sense of your strength.
After that, we will decide
how best to proceed.
All right, looking
forward to it.
[GAJA] As for the other
arcane-stage fighter...
I will see to Nero's
training myself.
She'll be training
directly with the queen?
I'm very excited
to work with you, Nero.
Undine and I will
also be overseeing
Noelle's training regimen.
Do your best!
Right. I'm ready.
[GAJA] That should cover
all of our assignments.
[MAGNA]
Wait a second!
[ASTA]
What's the matter, Magna?
Luck here.
We're always competing
with each other.
Any way I can train under you,
too, so we can keep that going?
Fine by me.
Awesome!
Well, I don't really mind,
but are you sure
that you can hack it?
Of course I can!
[GAJA] I should mention: none
of you are permanently bound
by the assignments
I've chosen for you.
Once your mana grows
a bit, you'll move on
to a different Spirit
Guardian next to see
what new insights
they have to offer.
That way, you can
learn even more.
Magic Knights, your
training will begin now.
Please don't let us down!
[MAGIC KNIGHTS]
Right!
[ASTA] Magna uses Flame Magic
and Luck uses lightning spells.
And both of those
are natural things,
which is how you guys
like to fight
here in the
Heart Kingdom, right?
Which means these two should
be perfect, shouldn't they?
On a basic level, I suppose.
First, I'll show you how
you can use natural mana
to create mana words.
--Oh, wow!
--[MAGNA] What the hell is that?
[GAJA] It's a necessary
skill for combat here.
When you build spells
out of mana words,
it allows you to add
some simple commands
into your magic techniques.
For example...
Uh?
[GAJA]
Dodge this attack.
'Kay.
[ASTA gasps]
[ASTA groans]
Mana words will give the spell
a more complex directive,
such as "become larger"
or "pursue him."
That's nuts!
Cool.
Yeah, I wanna learn that!
[SARADO]
Plants grow from the earth.
To strengthen plant-based magic,
you begin with the soil.
When you put it that way,
I think I get
what you're saying.
You're saying the first step
is understanding the earth.
It's probably easier to explain
if I give you a demonstration.
[MIMOSA, CHARLOTTE gasp]
So this is what mages are
capable of in the Heart Kingdom.
Our magic attributes
may be different,
but we all need to be in tune
with nature to use our spells.
As soon as you have
a good grasp on that,
your abilities will begin
to grow quite rapidly!
That was an impressive display.
Your magic type is similar to
that of one of my subordinates,
but it's much faster and
far more powerful than hers is.
[SARADO] It seems you Clover
Kingdom mages rely solely
on your own mana, without
making use of the natural mana
that always surrounds you.
[MIMOSA]
That sounds complicated,
but we'll do our best.
[CHARLOTTE]
How does it work?
Easy!
First, you gather it
all up from a big area,
with a "ker-swoosh!"
Then "kablammo,"
you're good to go!
I'm sorry, but I
think we'll need you
to be more specific.
[SARADO] You sense the mana,
like "ding-ding-ding!"
Then once you've got it,
you just have to go "whoosh!"
You know?
Then we'll get into the
technical stuff later.
--I didn't get a word of that.
--[MIMOSA] Sorry, I didn't get
a word of that.
[leaf whistling]
[FINRAL]
He's a little... different.
[SMURIK]
The gusts from the mountains,
the breeze off the ocean, it
all passes through this valley.
[FINRAL]
Oh, okay.
That must be why
it's so windy here.
I have heard about the young man
who was chosen
by the Wind Spirit.
I was very eager to meet him.
[FINRAL]
Right, you mean Asta's rival.
But then, you were
sent here instead.
There must be
a reason. I wonder.
I mean, I'm sure
Gaja just figured
we'd be a good match, is all.
Huh?
Well? It's your move.
[gasps]
Is this training?
That's a dumb question,
I know, but I really can't tell.
[SMURIK] Whether this is
for training or a real battle,
the wind that blows between
us remains the same.
Don't you agree?
[FINRAL] I can't seem
to figure this guy out.
What is he acting
so intense for?
[SMURIK]
Spatial Magic is mainly meant
for supporting your friends.
That is what you believe, yes?
[FINRAL]
Yeah, and?
Well, then, if an
enemy targets you,
do you expect your friends
to come to your rescue?
Don't be a liability.
Uh--
[SMURIK] Your purpose
is greater than that.
Wh-What the--?
What will you do now?
Let me try again!
Very well.
Wherever the wind may blow.
Ah! The weather's clear.
Perfect day for training.
I look forward to working
with you, Floga, sir!
First things first.
Let me see your magic ability.
Eighty percent should do it.
[LEOPOLD]
Flame Magic: Spiral Flames!
All right, if this is what
you can do at 80 percent,
then I'd say you've got
incredible potential!
That's nice, but if you ask me,
this isn't nearly good enough.
I need to learn everything I can
and get a whole lot stronger.
No way I'm gonna let this
opportunity go to waste.
Understood.
[LEOPOLD] Also, I hope this
doesn't come off as rude,
but can you show me
your powers, too?
Sorry, what?
That way I can judge for myself
whether I can learn
much from you.
[FLOGA]
Ah, that makes sense.
Okay, then.
[LEOPOLD grunts]
So, that answer your question?
Yes, I should have never
doubted your strength.
I apologize.
[FLOGA]
Don't worry. I don't mind.
[LEOPOLD]
The flame was so intense.
I want to do that myself!
Your potential is far
greater than mine.
Once you learn how
to harness natural mana,
you shouldn't have any
problem pulling off techniques
that are even more impressive
than I just showed you.
You will get there,
but gaining full control over
natural mana is no easy feat.
[LEOPOLD] Thank you so much
for taking me under your wing!
Push! Push! You can do it!
Oh, man, c'mon!
[GAJA] As I thought,
your magic is still too weak.
Too weak?
You're about at the fifth
stage, but in order to use
these techniques in battle,
you'll need to reach
at least third stage or higher.
[LUCK laughing]
This is so much fun!
[GAJA] That one seems
to have a knack for it.
[LUCK laughs] Guess I'll get
stronger without you, then!
Wait, Magna.
Just leave him alone, Asta.
If he can't get any better
than he is right now,
then he'll never be worth
anything more than that.
--[GAJA] Sorry to make you wait.
--Wha--?
As I mentioned earlier,
I'd like us to fight
so I can get a better
sense of your ability.
Attack me with all your might.
[ASTA] I get to fight someone
who's almost on par
with the Wizard King!
Then may the best man win!
[POTROF]
This is a good spot.
So, what are you
gonna teach me first?
How to bask in natural mana!
All the plants and animals, the
ground, water, wind, sunlight.
This place is filled
to the brim with life!
Which means it's
also rich with mana.
Now that you say something,
I think I'm already
getting a feel for it!
Good! Never let go
of that feeling!
You need mana words in order
to master our techniques.
Listen close.
Once you become one
with natural mana,
you'll be able to use
those words for spells!
That's amazing!
You know, just watching
the creative way that
you use your magic
is giving me a serious
burst of inspiration!
[POTROF]
Then you should try it!
Use mana words however
your heart desires.
It might not be perfect
at first, but that's fine.
[RILL]
Okay!
Not bad. There were
no mana words, but--
[RILL] Ooh! The need to create
is welling up inside me!
Wait, I've got an idea.
I can see that you're
an excellent painter,
so let's try writing them
this time instead.
Look, think, read, and write!
[RILL]
Like this?
Whoa, look at that!
Oh, my!
And after only
seeing them one time!
Well, don't stop now.
No, not the painting part!
[RILL]
Thanks for your help, Potrof.
I think this masterpiece will
be even better because of you!
[POTROF]
Not the point.
[CHARMY grunts]
Hey.
You're one of the
Black Bulls, right?
Actually, I know her as
Queen Loropechika's pet--
er, excuse me. I mean
her guest, of course.
Weren't you eating
back at the palace?
Well, yeah, but I
kinda-sorta ate everything
they had there, so I
figured I might as well
go searching for new
and undiscovered treats!
You're saying that you devoured
all of the palace's supply?
[CHARMY]
Uh-huh!
All right, then. Since you
traveled all this way
to the Heart Kingdom,
how would you like to learn
some of our special
combat techniques?
That doesn't really
line up with my goal
of eating all the
delicious noms I can find.
Aw, don't be that way!
Look, these are
called mana words.
They often come in handy.
[POTROF]
Wow! We've got another prodigy!
But your execution could
still use some work.
The secret to that is,
you have to be in touch
with the natural mana.
[CHARMY] There must
be more succulent fruit
somewhere in these woods!
I bet if we venture a bit
deeper into the forest,
I'll find some
scenery that really
gets my creative juices flowing!
[POTROF] I'm begging you,
just listen to me
for a few minutes, please!
[NOELLE] Queen Loropechika,
we're ready to learn
from you and Undine.
[LOROPECHIKA]
Of course.
But first, there's something I'd
like to bring to your attention.
I need you to rescue me.
If nothing changes, I'll be
killed by this curse, and soon.
You'll be okay.
We'll stop the devil
before that happens.
That's why we
came here to train.
[LOROPECHIKA] We are the ones
who will defeat Megicula.
[gasps] Sorry, could you
explain what you mean by that?
[LOROPECHIKA]
Obviously, striking down
the Spade Kingdom's invasion
will require the help
of the other
Magic Knights, but...
Megicula's inside someone.
An extremely powerful mage.
Her name is Vanica.
The only way we'll
even stand a chance
against a foe like her is if
Undine and I work together
with the two of you.
And you already have an idea
of what this Vanica person
can do, is that it?
She sounds pretty tough.
Well, since I'm the
Water Spirit, it's my job
to fight alongside the queen
and to protect her from danger.
But the two of us were no match
for Vanica's
astounding power.
Because of my weakness,
Her Majesty must live in fear
of her impending death.
No. Please don't ever blame
yourself for my curse, Undine.
A person who has been
possessed by a devil
cannot be defeated
by normal means.
I get it. So, by teaming
up with me and Nero,
you get some kind of
special advantage
that should be enough
to stop her, right?
[LOROPECHIKA] We can't be
sure of that just yet.
But I've come to the conclusion
that the four of us
working together
creates the best
possible scenario for victory.
Noelle. I hope the two of you
will agree to cooperate with us
and save Loropechika's life.
[LOROPECHIKA]
With Nero's arcane-stage spells
and your combative spirit
and fighting style--
if we four train hard,
then we'll become
a formidable team.
And then hopefully, we can
overpower Vanica and Megicula!
All of that makes sense to me.
Nero. Can we count you in, too?
We're grateful!
[NOELLE]
No need for that.
Trust me, I've my own reasons
for wanting to be the
one to kill Megicula!
Good, then we agree.
Let's begin our training.
Go ahead, and don't hold back!
[FINRAL grunts]
That's the right idea.
But if you can't figure out
your opponent's attacks,
it won't help you.
[FINRAL]
Come on, Finral!
You can't support
anybody like this!
[yells]
[screams]
Great work, ladies!
Just keep on using
those mana words!
I know you'll get the
hang of it eventually!
[yells]
[ASTA]
Gotcha this time!
[screams]
The power to invalidate magic
is second to nothing.
But you're too narrowminded
to use it to its full potential.
I'm not done!
[GAJA] A fighting style that
relies solely on your grit
and determination is not
enough to sustain you forever.
[panting]
[GAJA] To truly unleash your
abilities, it's only logical
that you use them to back up
your allies, as well.
Let me try one more time!
I suppose you
won't be satisfied
with that advice alone.
[ASTA yells]
[FINRAL] Day one, and they're
already running me ragged.
And it's not just me;
it's all of us!
[YAMI]
So? Are you seein' any progress?
[FINRAL] It looks like
everybody's gotten the hang
of the Heart Kingdom's
special techniques.
If it's like this every day,
I'd be surprised if we weren't
crazy-tough at the end.
Great. Well, keep it up, then.
[FINRAL]
Right!
Looks like they're
all workin' hard
to push past their limits.
So I guess I'd better
up my game, as well.
[YAMI] Since everybody's out
there working their butts off,
the hideout's actually
quiet for once.
Black Clover , Page 156:
"Awakening Powers."
I'm pushing as hard as I can!
And I don't mean
in the john, ya idiot.