[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed
lost until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
These children have been
completely drained of magic.
It's been taken.
And I don't know if they
can ever regain it.
What kind of monster are you?
Meanwhile, I'll see
what I can do
about this little
runt over here.
Huh?
[yells]
[BARO groans]
[ASTA]
You won't get away with this.
I will make you pay!
[SEKKE]
Ha... ha! Huh.
The Black Bulls' headquarters
are closer to Nean
than any of the other
Magic Knight squads'.
So why are they taking so long
to respond to the alert?
[SEKKE]
Ha-huh?
Then again, who knows what
a bunch of misfit crazies
like them might be up to
in the middle of the night?
[BLACK BULLS cackling]
[SEKKE]
Ha... ha.
Is anyone here? We have
a request for backup.
[SEKKE]
Ha... huh?
Right, well, I guess
I'll just head back, then.
I'm not running
scared or anything.
More like the
Black Bulls ran off
because they were afraid of me.
Ha, ha.
I know. I'll head for
the Blue Rose Knights!
That gorgeous garden of girls.
Farewell, creepy old mansion.
Sekke's got a date with
some lovely la... dies.
[mumbling] Beautiful
moon out tonight.
[screams]
[mumbling] Hi, I'm Gordon.
But you can call me "Donny."
[SEKKE screams]
No!
Please, stop! I swear
I'm not trespassing!
[mumbling] Hey, I think
I recognize you.
You're Sekke Bronzazza of
the Green Praying Mantises.
Would you like to
be friends with me?
[SEKKE]
I'm going to die.
That is the face of a man
who wants to kill me.
[SEKKE screams]
[mumbling] Shall I put the
kettle on for some tea?
Back! Get back!
No! Don't kill me!
Ha--hawgh! Ha-huh?
[GREY exhales]
Ha, ha! Another psycho!
I gotta get out of here!
[YAMI]
Shut up!
Jeez. Just when a guy's
gettin' some quality shut-eye,
it's all "ha, ha" this
and "ha, ha" that.
Do you have any idea
what time it is?
[SEKKE]
The Black Bulls captain.
Huh?
Ha, ha...
[SEKKE]
My apologies for the late hour.
I have a backup request
for the Bla--
Who the hell're you?
Hey, you're not here to collect
on my bar tab, are ya?
Bar tab? No, I'm no--
I was sent with an alert from
the Magic Knight Headquar--
I've never been to
any Magic Knight bar.
[SEKKE]
No, it's Nean Village!
I already paid my tab in Nean.
Ha-huh?
Can we forget about
paying up for a second?
[YAMI]
You think I'm gonna pay twice?
[SEKKE]
Wha...?
[mumbling] So, do you
take any sugar?
[GREY exhales]
[SEKKE whimpers] What is
the deal with this squad?
Why didn't I go to
the Blue Rose Knights
when I had the chance? Ha, ha!
[panting]
Hey, quit zoning out like
a moron and take him down!
[yelps] Go!
These things again?
Mirror Magic: now...
Reflect Refrain!
[SNOWMEN groaning]
[screams]
[GAUCHE]
Are you done now?
[NEIGE whimpering]
Then die. Feeble little wretch.
No! Get away!
[NEIGE] Snow Binding Magic:
Snowlime Lock!
I've got you now!
He's trapped!
No! His mirror's been silenced.
Don't worry, Gauche!
I'll save you.
[GAUCHE]
Save me?
If you're trying to show off
for Marie, it won't work!
[screams]
Now isn't the time
for your stubbornness!
Shut up! I have
everything under control.
Or rather, we do.
Neige, behind you!
[NEIGE groans]
[NEIGE]
H-How are there two?
[GAUCHES]
Mirror Magic: Real Double.
[GAUCHE] My Real Double
spell summons a clone
from the mirror world
into this one.
I cast it quickly right before
you used your Snow Magic
to capture me.
[ASTA]
So cool.
Your magic is officially
awesome, Gauche!
[SISTER THERESA]
The smaller of the two
has tremendous magic power.
Enough to make snow fall
over an entire village.
Baro...
[SISTER THERESA] But Gauche's
power is just as great,
and he's always exceled when it
comes to fighting with magic.
He truly is strong.
If only he weren't such
an ill-mannered thug.
[BARO] Don't just lay there
like a useless lump, Neige.
Get up and fight!
[BARO]
Dammit. I can't move.
There's got to be something.
[BARO]
That's it. I could try--
How could you do
something so screwed up?
You stole their magic!
Can you imagine if
somebody had taken yours?
[BARO chuckles]
[BARO cackles]
Except they didn't,
now did they?
If a bunch of snot-nosed
brats lose their magic,
that's their problem, not mine.
[ASTA growls]
Why, you...
Wait, no!
The pain you're in is nothing
compared to what you deserve.
You will find a way to fix this!
[SISTER THERESA]
That's enough.
Don't waste your energy on him.
He's not worth the effort.
[SISTER THERESA]
What's important right now
is taking care of the children.
Hey! Tell us how to
make their magic return!
Yes, I'll tell you
whatever you wanna know,
if you'll just let me go.
It's time to quit stalling!
You're scum, all right,
through and through.
Asta, use your sword
to break the spell
that's on the children first.
And you. Don't try
anything funny.
Yeah, well, I'm kinda
tied up at the moment, so.
[BARO]
Mud Magic: Mud Men.
[ASTA grunting]
--[CHILDREN groaning]
--[GIRL 32A] Where am I?
[GIRL 32B]
Mommy! Daddy!
[BOY 32A]
My legs hurt!
[BOY 32B]
Sister!
[SISTER THERESA] There, there.
It will be all right, children.
[LUCA]
Asta!
Everything's gonna
be fine, don't worry.
[GAUCHE] Hurry up and heal
Marie's injuries, you old cow.
I was going to anyway,
you uncivilized oaf.
[SISTER THERESA]
Flame Recovery Magic:
Sacred Healing Light.
[GAUCHE] Hey, you brats
in the middle there.
Marie should have the best spot,
so move over and make room.
It's okay, I don't
care where I sit.
[gasps] That's my Marie.
With the kindness of an angel.
And an angel deserves the best!
The spell will work the same
no matter where she is.
[ASTA] I've got some dried
pop-potatoes here, Marie.
They'll perk you right up.
[GAUCHE] Keep that garbage
away from my sister!
[ASTA] Hey! It's my
hometown's specialty.
[cackling]
[SISTER THERESA] Asta, weren't
you raised at the church
in Hage Village?
Yeah, how did you know?
[SISTER THERESA]
Well, as it happens,
Sister Lily once came
to my church to train.
She told me all about a young
orphan who was in her care.
Seriously?! You actually
know Sister Lily?
One of the sweetest
young ladies I've ever met.
I know, right?
[gasps] Wait! What exactly
did she tell you?
Was it good?
She told me that you
were little and noisy.
[yelps]
Of course, that wasn't
the only thing she said.
[LILY sighs] Once this is done,
I'll move on to the windows.
Easy now, you'll
wear yourself out
if you work this
hard from day one.
Sister, this is
nothing, I promise.
I know someone who works so hard
he puts my efforts to shame.
Oh?
There's a boy back
in Hage who can't
use magic at all but still
spends every day training
in hopes of becoming
the Wizard King.
You must be joking.
He can't even get into
a Magic Knight squad
if he doesn't have magic.
Probably not.
But if you told him
to give up, he'd say,
"Not yet! I'm not done!"
So, maybe he will.
Now I'm saying it, too.
Get some rest?
Not yet! I'm not done!
[SISTER THERESA]
She also told me that you're
a hard worker,
who doesn't give up
no matter what
obstacles he faces.
A boy with a strong heart who
makes her proud every day.
And now I can see that
all of your hard work
has paid off.
[gasps, laughs]
Yeah, and I'm not done!
I'm gonna be the
Wizard King someday, too!
Now about that.
I'm not giving up!
[ASTA] Sister Lily, I'm not
giving up on you, either.
So please, please, please,
please, please marry me!
[NEIGE screams]
You're the one who hit her.
Marie told me.
That crime can only be
paid for with your life.
That's enough, Gauche.
I'm fine! All healed
up and everything!
Please don't hurt him anymore.
Can't you just forgive him?
[GAUCHE]
Not a chance.
[GAUCHE] If someone poses
a threat to my beloved Marie,
I will show no mercy!
We need to focus on
getting that magic back,
not petty vengeance.
Tell me. Why did the
two of you do this?
These children are the
hope of our kingdom.
The three-leaf sprouts upon
which our future depends.
I didn't want this.
I just wanted to make
some new friends.
It hurts. Please, Baro,
tell me what I should do.
[BARO]
Well for a start,
you could quit whining
like a little brat.
Damn, damn, damn! It's not fair!
Why did this have
to happen to me?
[BARO]
It's all her fault.
I thought we were
gonna make a fortune,
but it was a trick
the whole time.
[BARO]
Come on! Show your stupid face!
[SALLY]
Wow!
--That sounds like...
--[BARO] Finally!
Pretty slow for someone
who can use Spatial Magic!
We hit a snag.
Think I could get
a little help here?
[SALLY] Ugh, I am so
sick of your whining.
But it looks like you brought me
a present, so I'll let it slide.
Asta!
The Eye of the Midnight Sun.
[SALLY laughing] I didn't expect
to see you again so soon!
[ASTA]
It's the crazy lady!
[YAMI] What? Somethin's
goin' down in Nean?
And you didn't think you should
mention it sooner, you idiot?
[SEKKE]
But I did try to tell you.
No excuses!
[SEKKE sobs]
[YAMI]
So, they need backup, do they?
Huh?
[mumbling]
[YAMI]
No one's ever really sure
what these two
weirdos are thinking.
Guess I should go.
Except I don't wanna.
[SEKKE] How did these three even
make it into the Magic Knights?
[NUN 31A]
Everyone, please remain calm.
Head to the church for now.
[KAI]
Where are they?
[PIM]
I miss them.
It'll be okay! They'll be
home soon, I'm certain.
They may not look it,
but Asta and Gauche
are both really strong,
and we'll be getting backup
from headquarters, too.
Yeah?
[PIM]
Really?
[REBECCA] You kids wanna
help with dinner?
[PIM]
Sure!
[NOELLE] We are getting
backup, aren't we?
[SALLY]
What's this?
I came when the Transmission
tool alerted me,
but you haven't
gathered much magic.
[BARO] Yeah, well,
it's all their fault!
[SALLY giggles] Eh. It doesn't
really matter anymore.
[SISTER THERESA] Stay here,
children. No one move.
[gasps] Is it them, Asta?
The terrorist group who
attacked the capital?
Yeah, it's the same people.
You're the one.
My Marie was in danger
because of you?
You're dead.
Gel Magic: Go,
Sticky Salamander!
I'm trying to have a
touching reunion here,
and you're messing it up.
Maybe I should keep all of you.
Dissection party!
What sort of sinister
magic is that?
Be careful. It's real strong.
I heard she blocked the captain
of the Silver Eagles' attack.
[SALLY]
Here we go!
[ASTA]
Look out!
[yells]
[giggles]
[ASTA]
No!
Silly Asta, your Anti-Magic
attacks can't do much
if they don't connect.
[GAUCHE]
What about this?
Mirror Magic: Reflect Refrain.
[GAUCHE]
She's warping the beams!
Hey, it's nice magic and all,
but if it just refracts
inside Mister Salaman here,
it's not exactly effective.
Maybe you'd have better luck
if you tried something stronger!
[gasps]
[ASTA]
Gauche!
[SALLY]
This one's for you, Asta!
[yells]
[ASTA yelps]
[SALLY giggles]
There you are, my pretty one.
[ASTA]
C-Can't move.
[SALLY] You look like
such an ordinary human.
But you're not. You're special.
[ASTA screams]
[ASTA]
That hurts! And it's freaky!
Oh! Your blood's
ordinary enough.
Now. Next up.
I need a fingernail sample.
[screams] Stop!
[SISTER THERESA] Flame Magic:
Brilliant Flame Cross!
Aw! Mister Salaman melted away.
[SISTER THERESA yells]
You might as well back off!
You're not taking him.
You really shouldn't
get in my way.
[ASTA]
That was awesome!
Hey, thanks! Wow!
You're really powerful, huh?
Don't underestimate Theresa
the Crimson She-Leopard!
Once a Magic Knight,
always a Magic Knight.
Whoa!
[ASTA]
Didn't see that one coming!
You were a Magic Knight?
"Crimson She-Leopard."
So you know Captain Fuegoleon?
Little Fuego? Of course.
[ASTA]
"Little Fuego"?!
Back when I was
stationed at court,
I was in charge
of his education.
Your mana is all over the place.
Oh, right.
Your foes won't
hesitate in battle.
You must learn to focus
and remain calm at all times.
Ma'am!
[SISTER THERESA]
He was a real mess back then,
but he turned out all right.
[ASTA]
I cannot picture that.
I don't know if you heard
about what happened
to Captain Fuegoleon, Sister.
They, well...
[SISTER THERESA] Yes, I know.
And we will capture them.
[GAUCHE] Think you can
help me out, you old bat?
[SISTER THERESA]
What are you doing over there,
you boorish brute?
Shut up, old crone.
So, it's three
against one, then.
I'm not liking these odds.
[BARO]
Hey, over here.
[SALLY]
Hm?
If I was free, I could use
my Mud Magic to help you.
Cut me loose,
it'll be a win-win.
You can do something, right?
Well, yeah, there is
a way to get you out,
but are you really
sure you want me to?
[BARO]
Of course I'm sure!
Whatever it takes. Come on!
Okay, why not? You're sure?
[BARO]
Yes!
Really sure?
[BARO]
I said yes! Just do it!
Hey, what're you two
muttering about over there?
Hurry up, wouldja?
Get me out of these and
pay me like we agreed,
and I'll help you take
down all three of them.
[BARO]
Yeah, right.
As soon as I'm free and I've
got my money, I'm outta here.
[SALLY]
All right, then. In that case...
Here.
[ALL gasp]
What the--?
[SALLY giggles]
[BARO grunts]
[screams]
What's happening?
[ASTA]
What'd she do?
[gasps] He's becoming
some sort of monster.
His magic's swelling up
and spilling out!
[BARO growls]
[BARO roars]
[SALLY]
Whoopsie! That didn't work.
I mean, you can move,
and you've got scads
of magic power now.
Which would be cool
except for the whole
not being human thing.
[CHILDREN screaming]
[SISTER THERESA] Gauche, Asta,
keep the children safe!
[ASTA]
On it!
[MARIE gasps]
We're leaving, Marie.
Hold on! We can't go!
All of the other kids
are still down there.
Forget about them!
The only thing that matters
is getting you away
from that monster.
What?!
That fool!
[ASTA yelps]
[laughs] I'm not going to
let you go this time, Asta.
You're all mine!
[MARIE]
Big brother.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[GORDON mumbling]
Clover Clips.
"Go, Go, Gordon!"
All right I've delivered
the backup request
for headquarters, so now
I can get outta here, ha, ha!
This hideout. It's like a maze.
Where--? Ha-huh?
Who the heck are you?
Why are you following me?
Ha, ha!
[BEAST 7A growls]
[SEKKE]
What room is this?
[mumbling] The captain's
beast room. Cozy, isn't it?
[SEKKE]
Ha, ha!
[mumbling] This is the bathroom.
[SEKKE]
Ha, ha!
Ha...
I should be safe here.
[mumbling] The water feels nice.
Ha, ha, ha!
Please! I'm way
too young to die!
How the heck do
I get out of here?
[mumbling] Don't cry.
That's what I've been
trying to show you.
[GAUCHE]
Mirror, mirror, on the wall,
who's the--never mind.
Marie's the cutest.
I don't need a mirror
to tell me that.
Black Clover , Page 33:
"To Help Somebody, Someday."
My magic is protecting Marie!