[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR]
The Eye of the Midnight Sun
set themselves up as the
enemy of the Clover Kingdom
and worked behind the
scenes with the intent
of establishing their
own sovereign state.
They believed that
gathering the items
known as magic stones would
allow them to be reborn
in their "true forms,"
granting them great power.
However, they must still
collect three more
before this rebirth can occur.
One of these stones was
in the Underwater Temple,
part of a strong magic region
where the mana is said
to be especially powerful.
Thank you, Yami,
I'm counting on you.
Oh, and Asta?
[KLAUS] We've neatly squared
away another mission.
I have no doubt that
Captain Vangeance will praise
our accomplishments when
we report back to him.
I'm sure!
But, Yuno.
Yes?
Your Wind Spirit--Sylph, right?
That is powerful magic indeed.
However, I don't want you
fighting on your own
again like you did today.
We are a team, understand?
[MIMOSA] Something tells me
it's going in one ear
and out the other.
And that means do as I say.
Stop immediately charging in
and taking down the enemy
without consulting me first.
We do things my way,
with my strategies!
Are you listening?
Yes, sir.
Well, good.
[WOMAN screams]
[KLAUS]
A scream?
I think it came from down there.
It sounds like
someone's in trouble.
Let's go!
[VANESSA]
Oh, just give it up already!
[NOELLE]
No, don't!
[MIMOSA]
That voice...
A robbery?
[yelps]
[NOELLE shrieks]
[MIMOSA]
Noelle!
[YUNO]
What's going on?
You're the ones who
came barging in here!
[YUNO]
Swimsuits?
[VANESSA] That's right.
Swimsuits, Golden Boy.
'Scuse me?
We're taking a trip.
Heading to the beach.
Noelle here doesn't
have a swimsuit,
so I offered to help
her pick one out.
Personally, I thought
it would be easier
if she just borrowed
one of mine.
But she declined.
It was nothing but strings!
You expect me to wear that?!
Oh, my. That
sounds interesting.
So, then, all the screaming
we heard earlier...
[NOELLE] That was when
Vanessa started ripping
my clothes off
without permission!
I was helping.
It's not like you can try a
swimsuit on over your clothing.
That's the kinda thing
you have to be naked for.
Back me up!
[laughs]
Can we leave now?
[VANESSA] Here. What do
you think of this one?
Adding some little seashells
doesn't make it any better!
[KLAUS]
Hm. Only a false alarm, then.
Trying on swimsuits
for a beach trip.
Is that what constitutes hard
work for the Black Bulls?
Excuse me! This is
for a mission.
A mission?
That's right, and it's
one big secret job.
So, you wanna come with, kiddo?
Heh. Adorable.
There are other things
we need to be doing.
I'll have to pass.
That's a shame.
I'd love a trip to the beach.
Our next mission
starts tomorrow, though,
so we're all booked up.
[CHARMY]
Ah! It's him!
My prince of provisions is here!
Oh! My darling has never seen
me in a swimsuit before.
I wonder what he'll say!
It's too much! I can't
handle the sexiness.
You're...
...delicious!
You think so?
[stomach growls]
Eat me right up, I'm ready!
[CHARMY groans]
Hey, wait! Where did
my sweet prince go?
[VANESSA]
You mean the Golden Boy?
He and his friends all left.
Ah! Aw.
[VANESSA] It looks like Charmy's
got her suit picked out.
Now you just need
to decide on one.
Here, how about this?
What? Not a chance!
That doesn't cover anything!
Maybe you should consider
that one over there.
Which one?
[BIKINI RETAILER 40A]
It is a bit pricey, of course.
I'm not worried about the cost,
and it has a certain charm,
but I don't know.
There' still a lot
of skin showing,
and does it really
have to be that shiny?
Wear this to the beach,
and you're sure to
have all eyes on you.
All... eyes...?
[NOELLE]
What about Asta?
Will his eyes be on me, too?
This might actually get
a compliment out of him.
[gasps]
[NOELLE] Not that I care
about getting a compliment
from him of all people.
So, um.
Is this the one you want, then?
[NOELLE]
I'll take it! Let's go!
And keep the change.
[BIKINI RETAILER 40A]
What?
[MAGNA] All right, gang!
We ready to roll out?
[VANESSA yawns]
I'm so sorry, my dearest Marie.
I wish that I could
take you along
to get a glimpse of the beach.
I wonder which one's stronger--
a whale or a shark.
[GORDON mumbling]
A shark's skin may look smooth,
but it actually has
a rough texture.
[snoring]
What the hell do you two
think you're doing?
Don't just plop your butts
on my Crazy Cyclone
without askin'!
Well, I can't really fly,
so I kinda had to hitch a ride.
Same here. Or did you forget?
What an idiot.
Oh, yeah, Miss Priss?
If you're gonna be like that,
then get a ride
from somebody else.
A royal is deigning
to ride with you.
You should be more
grateful, commoner.
[MAGNA]
You're the one who can't fly!
Hey, Captain Yami isn't
still sleeping, is he?
No, he said he was
going ahead of us
to check on something.
Wow. So miracles
really do happen.
The captain is actually working?
[MAGNA]
Yep, that's our Yami for ya!
All right, Black Bulls,
the beach is waitin' for us!
Crazy Cyclone, movin' out!
Yeah!
[ASTA, NOELLE]
Woo-hoo!
[NARRATOR] Asta and the other
Black Bulls were headed
for the seaside
village of Raquey.
The strong mana in the area
kept it warm year round,
making it a popular vacation
destination for royalty,
nobility, and Magic
Knight squads alike.
Wouldn't it have
been easier to use
your Spatial Magic
to get there, Finral?
This is my first
visit to Raquey.
You should know by now
I can only use my magic
to go to places
I've been before.
[sighs] What good are you?
Flying there like this is
a complete waste of time.
[FINRAL]
I'm your superior, dammit!
There's a shock.
I figured you would have
made it your life's mission
to visit any place
where you were guaranteed
to find a bunch of
babes in bikinis.
Hah. I've always found half
the pleasure of something
lies in the anticipation of it.
I've long anticipated this.
Yes, Raquey, here I come!
It won't be long now,
lovely ladies!
Wait, where's that
person who's always
blowing smoke and making
that growling noise?
[MAGNA, VANESSA, FINRAL]
Eh?
[GORDON]
I'm right here!
[BLACK BULLS]
Huh?
[GREY exhales]
That was actually Grey
transformed this whole time?
And if that's Grey,
what happened to
the real Gordon?
[GORDON mumbling]
Hey, everyone?
Are you still asleep?
But, uh, shouldn't
we be heading out?
Wait. Did they...
Did they all leave without me?
[MAGNA] Okay, we should be
seein' it any second now.
[ASTA]
Seeing what?
The ocean, Lil' Rasta.
I can't wait.
I've never laid eyes on it.
Me, neither! We've been
flying for a while now.
Do you think it'll
be much longer?
[MAGNA] I mean. I figured
we woulda seen it.
What are you talking about?
You're both staring right
at it. See all that blue?
[ASTA]
No way!
This is it?
[ASTA]
I never knew it was that big!
It's more incredible
than I ever imagined!
[ASTA, MAGNA]
It's the ocean!
Wow, we're really here!
The ocean! And it's
freakin' enormous!
[ASTA]
This is awesome! So awesome!
I wish Yuno and the kids
back home could see this.
Um, hello?
And I've definitely gotta bring
Sister Lily here someday.
What am I, chopped liver?
Isn't the sunset
beautiful, Asta?
Indeed. It certainly
is, but, Sister.
It's still not as
beautiful as you.
I am the Wizard King now.
So please, Sister Lily.
Kneel.
[ASTA]
Ka-chick.
Say that you'll marry me!
[LILY]
Of course!
I can just see it now!
Oh, yeah, it's gonna be perfect!
What's that goofy
look on his face for?
[NOELLE]
Wait. He's not thinking about
that stupid kiss
she gave him, is he?
Well, if he is, he should
knock it off already.
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
Not that I care.
I don't wanna kiss
him or anything.
[NOELLE] Maybe it's time
to give that insect
a proper eyeful of
this new swimsuit.
He better not get the
wrong idea, though.
I-I don't want him to want me.
I just want him to see that
I'm more appealing than Rebecca.
Yeah, that's all.
[NOELLE]
Nope, too embarrassed!
Mm, but I want him to see me!
Ah, but I'm too
embarrassed. Just do it!
I got a new swimsuit.
Hey, Asta, what do you think?
[MAGNA]
Check it out!
The resta you guys
got nothin' on this!
[ASTA] Whoa! Is that
your swimsuit, Magna?
Bold choice!
Sexy, huh?
Instead of goin' traditional,
I figured I'd wear a
loincloth like Yami does.
How lame.
And now it's time
to swim in a sea
as big as our captain's heart.
You ready, Asta?
Ready! Let's do it, Magna!
[VANESSA] Hey, have you
two seen my new suit?
Well, what d'ya think?
Looks pretty good, right?
Actually, that's more or less
what you always look like.
What would a virgin
street punk like you
understand about it, anyway?
I'm not a virgin street punk!
[LUCK]
How 'bout a race?
[MAGNA screams]
[ASTA]
All right! Magna's on fire!
Will you stop running
around like idiot children?
It's done. Do you like your
big brother's sculpture?
Yes! It's amazing.
Will you turn me around?
Show me the ocean!
Absolutely, angel.
Well, there it is.
What do you think?
Oh, wow! It's so beautiful!
Next time I'll bring you, too,
and we'll splash around
in the water together.
--[laughs]
--[MARIE gasps]
[ASTA]
Whoo! That's really cold!
Hey, Asta's there!
When you bring me to the beach,
can he come along with us?
[GAUCHE growls]
So, um. I got a
new swimsuit, Asta.
Feel free to turn around
and check it out if you want.
Anybody who would
tempt Marie must die!
--[NOELLE] Hey, Asta?
--Mirror Magic: Reflect Ray!
[ASTA screams]
Tch.
[yelps] It's so salty!
Right, I can't swim.
This isn't good!
[NOELLE] Come on! Will you
look at me already?
[BEACH BABE 40A]
Catch!
[BEACH BABE 40B laughing]
[BEACH BABE 40C laughing]
Oh, yeah!
So many bathing-suit
beauties to choose from!
So many! It's time
to get flirting!
All right, Grey,
transform into me.
Let's go!
Now there's twice
the Finral to go around.
[FINRAL]
Okay, here's the plan!
We're sexy twins who use witty
banter to lure the ladies in.
Think you can handle it?
Of course, I'm you!
Visualize the watermelon!
You can do this! No one
knows food better than you.
Ah! Wonderful!
There's something about
the beach that just
makes a drink taste better.
Move right, Charmy.
Just a little bit more
and you should have it!
Oh, hey.
Aren't you supposed
to be helping Finral
with his flirting?
I was for a little while.
But that got old,
so I decided to ditch him.
A couple steps to
the left, Charmy!
[VANESSA]
No, you need to go right!
[GREY]
Left! Left!
[CHARMY]
I've got it. Almost there.
Just another ten steps!
[panting] Thought I was a goner!
Hey, uh, you know, this is new.
Gotcha!
[ASTA screams]
You can't just go
around hitting people
with sticks, Charmy!
If that had been anyone
else, they'd be dead now!
Oh, look. Watermelon juice.
[ASTA]
My head's not a watermelon!
Hello! Don't forget my swimsuit!
Hey, look!
Transforming into you
reminded me how gross
bein' all buff like this is.
You really gotta
find some serious
uses for that
Transformation Magic, Grey!
Gah! You're wasting it!
[NOELLE]
About my swimsuit.
[ASTA]
Oh, hey!
Do you like it?
[ASTA yells]
I knew it!
This sand is awesome
for leg training!
Feel the burn! Yeah!
You will look at me
in my swimsuit!
And you're going
to do it right now!
[ASTA panting]
Jeez, you still haven't learned
how to control your magic yet?
--I mean, not that I'm...
--[LUCK] Aw, no fun.
It went out.
I don't have my
wand right now,
so local defensive spells
are the only ones I can cast.
You're bragging about that?
Oh! Ah, ha...
[screams]
[groans]
[laughs]
[SEKKE] Ha, ha! So this is
the famous Raquey beach.
I can hear the ocean
calling my name.
Is now really the
time to be relaxing?
Yeah, don't you have
work to do or somethin'?
[SEKKE] Well, I've just
accomplished so much lately.
The Wizard King personally
awarded me 100 stars. Ha, ha!
Even Captain Jack himself
praised my efforts.
Thanks to me, dozens
of innocent children
were rescued from an
evil traitor's clutches.
What's the harm in
taking a little break
to stop and smell the roses?
[FINRAL]
Well, hello there, ladies.
Looking lovely today.
And where did you come from?
[BEACH BABES]
Home.
Home, huh?
Well, now that you're here,
wanna hang out?
[BOTH]
Yeah, no thanks.
Uh-- No, wait!
Hold on a second!
Some creep's prowling the beach
for unsuspecting girls.
Why don't you guys pick up
some ladies of your own?
What? With you?
Ha, ha. I could
never do something
as vulgar as that! No, I'll
simply meet back up with you
once you've had some success.
[APHRO, PHATI]
Which basically means
he's gonna wander over,
crash our party,
and act like he's the
one doing us a favor.
Remember, the only reason
you're here is because
you happen to have a friend
among the Magic Knights.
I've given you a killer
opportunity. Now, off you go.
So, we're doing this?
Do we have a choice?
What's that?
I see the perfect targets
for you right over there.
Ha, ha! Now, don't
worry about me, boys.
Go get 'em!
[PHATI, APHRO]
You "go get 'em."
--[PHATI] Jerk.
--[APHRO sighs]
Huh! Hah!
Hey there, cuties.
Great day for a swim, isn't it?
Do you have a few minutes
to chat with us
about how awesome
magical girls are?
Leave us alone, insects.
Wait!
[SEKKE] That's the girl
from the Black Bulls.
No way. So he must be...
Huh?
[gasps]
[ALL shouting, yelling]
[SEKKE]
Hah!
Ha, ha, ha!
[BLACK BULLS yelling]
[SEKKE]
Ha, ha!
[BOTH]
Oh, boy.
Any idea what I hit?
Nope!
It felt like I hit
something, too.
Munch, much, much...
Hey, gang!
We came here to look for
the magic stone, didn't we?
So, what're you
messin' around for?
Like you're not.
Oh, hi, Captain Yami.
[YAMI groans]
Okay, you incompetent
knuckleheads, listen up.
While you were all
busy goofin' off,
I was out scorin' us some intel.
Apparently, the Underwater
Temple is beneath
the surface of the
ocean around here.
Unfortunately, the
mana-driven currents
are too strong,
so even a skilled mage
can't normally get near it.
The only time the mana
is weak enough to even
possibly access it
is during a full moon.
[BLACK BULLS]
What?
Captain Yami's actually
doing his job?
And he's super
serious about it?!
Someday, I'm really
gonna kill ya.
If ya didn't guess already,
the Underwater Temple
is on the ocean floor.
You need magic to
get there. So, Noelle.
[gasps]
[YAMI] That's where your
Water Magic comes in.
Huh?
We're gonna hitch a ride on it.
[NOELLE]
But, sir...
I'd need exceptional
control over my magic
to manage something like that.
No, I can't do it!
Find someone else!
If you were all relying
on me, and I messed up...
[YAMI]
We die.
You blow this,
and that's it for us.
We get swallowed by
the current and drown.
This is a top-secret
mission the Wizard King
entrusted to the
Black Bulls alone.
There is no "someone else."
There's just you, Noelle.
The full moon's a week away.
You've got till then to
learn to control your magic.
Push past your limits.
[NOELLE] Sea Dragon's Lair.
Currently my only spell.
Developing it should
be the quickest way
to get where I need to be.
[NOELLE]
Still.
[panting]
[NOELLE]
Vanessa taught me some tricks
to control my magic,
but no matter
how many times I try,
it never seems to go very well.
I just don't have
the knack for it,
and maybe I never will.
[NOELLE]
But that's no excuse.
It's no reason to run away.
I'll just keep trying
until I can do it!
[NOELLE]
I've got it!
[ASTA yelling]
[NOELLE] So, you're
out here training, too?
You're training?
Please, I'm royalty.
We're just naturally perfect.
[ASTA] Hey, why don't
we train together?
[NOELLE]
Hm?
I can stop your spells
if they go crazy.
No one'll get hurt.
Yeah, right.
As if I would make a
mistake like that again.
[NOELLE]
Just the two of us. Training.
Well, fine.
If you insist,
I suppose training
with you wouldn't
be the absolute worst.
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
Hey, Asta?
[ASTA]
I hear something.
[NOELLE]
Huh?
[singing]
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[NOELLE]
"Look at Me!"
Hey, Dorksta, look at me.
Notice anything? Huh?
How do you like me
in a swimsuit?
[ASTA]
Huh?
Well?
[ASTA]
Uh...
Wow. It's so sparkly!
Isn't it heavy? Bet you could
keep birds away with that.
[ASTA] Like this scarecrow
we had back in the village.
[NOELLE]
Hey!
What are you
looking at, you creep?!
[CRAB 40A]
Crabbity!
[screams] But you
told me to look!
Well, stop it, Stupidsta.
[CRAB 40A]
Crabbity...
[SEKKE]
Ha, ha!
Did you enjoy
another installment
of Sekke's stunning exploits?
I'm never more ha, ha than
when I ha, ha at the shore!
Black Clover , Page 41:
"The Water Girl Grows Up"!
One, two, three: Ha, ha!