[NARRATOR] Within the clover's
fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
[NARRATOR] Asta, born
unable to harness mana,
was granted the
power of Anti-magic
from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability
to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members
of Spade Kingdom's
Dark Triad also possess powers
from the devils of the
underworld and used them
to launch an invasion on
the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from
his belief in himself
and from the support
of his friends,
Asta continues to fight for
the safety of this world.
[NARRATOR] Upon returning
to his home village of Hage,
Yuno was introduced
to a mysterious man
from the Spade Kingdom
named Ralph.
[RALPH]
Lord Yuno.
Our nation's future
is in your hands.
You belong to the royal
House of Grinberryall.
Its scion, the prince
and rightful heir
to the Spade Kingdom's throne!
[NARRATOR] Ralph revealed
the truth about Yuno's birth.
[NARRATOR]
Just then,
Yuno received word that the
Golden Dawn headquarters
was under attack.
[YUNO] Even so, I'm also Yuno
of the Clover Kingdom.
[NARRATOR] The perpetrators were
two Spade Kingdom mages
named Gaderois and Foyal.
[GADEROIS] Only a select few
were good enough to get powers
from the Dark Triad, and we
were at the top of the list!
We're the Dark Disciples!
All of us are stage-zero mages!
[NARRATOR] They were led
by Zenon of the Dark Triad,
who was possessed by a devil.
[NARRATOR] And their goal
was soon clear.
[WILLIAM] World Tree Magic:
Magic Warding Ash!
So that's World
Tree Magic, is it?
Our side could
certainly use that.
I'll be taking you with me.
[ZENON]
Bone Magic: Eternal Fangs.
[NARRATOR]
By the time Yuno arrived
at the Golden Dawn
headquarters...
[YUNO]
I'm here!
[NARRATOR] A grim tragedy
had already unfolded.
[YUNO] What the hell do
you think you're doing...
...to my comrades?
[ALECDORA] When you came
to the Golden Dawn,
some of our squad looked down
on you for being a commoner.
They resented you and were
jealous of your powers.
And I was no exception.
How can you stand up
for people like us,
given the way we've behaved?
[YUNO] We're comrades.
I don't need another reason.
Just that I care.
Apologies.
[HAMON]
When we're finished,
let's all go out
to eat together!
[KLAUS]
Hey, come back!
[SHIREN]
Yuno.
[HAMON]
You're invited.
In fact, we specifically
invited you.
Oh, I didn't...
[LETOILE] Hamon knows
some great restaurants
around the royal capital.
[DAVID] Yeah, we thought it
might be fun to hit the town
with the whole squad and party!
[DAVID]
Hey!
Don't you go getting a big
head just because you moved
all the way up to Vice Captain
in only 18 months!
Yeah, you better watch it.
I'll try.
[DAVID]
Oh, you got an attitude?
That's it, you're about to get
the noogie to end all noogies!
[GOLDEN DAWN 154AA]
Yuno. You've been smiling
a lot more, recently, huh?
[GOLDEN DAWN 154AA] It's a
good look for you, though!
Excuse me!
I'm the only one who's allowed
to pay that much attention
to Yuno's gorgeous face,
and don't you forget it!
[GOLDEN DAWN 154AA]
Ow, stop! Don't do that!
[GOLDEN DAWN 154BB]
No fighting, guys!
[GADEROIS cackles]
We musta killed about half.
And the rest ain't far behind!
Well, at least they died
fighting a strong
opponent, right?
I think they should
feel honored!
[YUNO]
Wind Spirit Magic: Spirit Storm!
[GADEROIS]
Ah! So, you've been chosen
by the Wind Spirit, eh?
How about that?
But since my Stone Magic
techniques are enhanced
by devil power, they're
tougher than iron or steel!
So your spells
won't scratch me!
[YUNO] Mana Zone:
Spirit's Hushed Dance.
[GADEROIS] He's attacking me and
protecting his wounded friends
at the same time!
That arcane-stage captain
should be fighting
Lord Zenon right now.
Well, well!
Didn't think anyone below the
captain would be zero-stage!
It looks like
things are finally
getting interesting here!
My name's Gaderois, kid!
Now what's yours?
You don't need to know
my name. You're my enemy!
[GADEROIS grunts]
[GADEROIS laughs]
Don't be like that!
I want us to get acquainted
before I kill ya!
[yells]
Tell me. Why are
you doing this?
Beats me. Just followin' orders!
Only thing I know
is the Dark Triad
is lookin' to snap up
an arcane-stage fighter.
And as long as I get
to have some fun,
that's good enough for me!
[YUNO]
Arcane-stage?
Ah, now, let me tell ya,
these guys are a riot!
They killed that softie
of a king we had
and then gave even
more power to those of us
who were looking
for some action!
The former king was a fool!
Might is always right!
'Cause when you're strong,
you get to make your own rules!
You're insane.
How does somebody enjoy
making people suffer?
Are you even capable
of human emotions?
Of course.
Nothing's more human than
the incredible rush you feel
when you kill somebody.
[GADEROIS]
I'm hooked on it, I tell ya!
And you're a tough guy
like me, so you understand!
[YUNO]
Let's get one thing straight.
I am nothing like you!
[YUNO]
Wind Spirit Creation Magic...
...Spirit of Zephyr!
[yells]
[grunts]
[laughs]
Hey, that's not a bad trick!
But you're no match
for me, little man.
Might as well quit!
I think I understand.
The reason this world is so
screwed up is people like you.
Like me?
[YUNO] That's the way it's
been since the dawn of time.
What are you rambling about?
[GADEROIS] My Stone Magic.
He's canceling it out instantly!
[GADEROIS groans]
[YUNO] Whether I'm
a Clover Kingdom mage,
or a Spade Kingdom
prince, either way.
I have to cut you down!
[FOYAL cackling]
[KLAUS]
This spell has enormous range.
I have no way of knowing
where the enemy is!
[FOYAL]
I have to admit,
I'm impressed that your
magic is so solid.
[KLAUS] Steel Magic:
Blazing Spiral Lance!
Heh. It's too bad though.
No matter how
sturdy it may be,
it isn't capable of doing
any damage against me.
I'm getting tired
of playing with you,
so it's time to die.
Ready?
[ALL gasp]
[GOLDEN DAWN MAGES groan]
I'm a zero-stage mage.
A genius who was specifically
selected by the Dark Triad!
Even if there was a whole
army of you amateurs,
you'd never be able to stop me!
[LETOILE] How are they so much
more powerful than us?
He's not even the leader,
and his magic's on par
with a captain's!
There's something suspicious
about their abilities!
[LETOILE] My squadmates
are low on mana!
If I don't do something,
we'll all be wiped out.
But I can't even
track where he is!
Useless North isn't responding
to his Mist Magic,
and Another Atlas is
already at maximum size!
[WILLIAM] Some of the elves'
magic still dwells within us.
I'm sure those
who were possessed
would like to renounce it,
after the suffering
it caused our people.
But I disagree with that.
We should take their strength
and use it as a force for good
to protect our great kingdom!
[LETOILE] I'm not as strong as
an elf, but after six months,
I've made that power my own.
[FOYAL cackling]
[LETOILE] Even so, I'm no
match for someone like him!
[cackling]
[FOYAL] Your magic and your body
are completely worn down.
You should surrender!
You seem smart,
so surely you must have
enough intelligence
to understand
that you can't possibly
survive this battle.
[KLAUS]
You've weakened me physically,
but you'll never break my will!
[FOYAL] Then will yourself
to die, you piece of trash.
Klaus, I'm here to help you!
Yuno!
[FOYAL]
He just blew my mist away.
He might be a worthy foe.
Almost.
[FOYAL] Mist Creation Magic:
Sealing Spectral Hands.
[YUNO] I'm still wounded
from that last fight.
You look tired.
Are you sure you can do it?
Come at me,
every last one of you.
You're all as good as dead.
[LETOILE] Thanks to Yuno,
I can see where you are now!
'll move myself
and Another Atlas,
breaking your illusionary armor!
[FOYAL]
You subhuman scum!
He's severely injured.
How is he able
to keep on moving?
[KLAUS] Every time I face
someone who's naturally skilled
like he is, I have
the same thought.
I worry that I may never
surpass their abilities,
no matter how much
intense training I undergo.
But I've learned how
to handle that insecurity.
[gasping]
[KLAUS] I've just got to keep
breaking through those walls!
"How do I keep on moving"?
[FOYAL groans]
I've trained for
this exact moment.
It's over.
Yuno! Er, Vice Captain Yuno.
Thank you.
It was nothing, sir.
[KLAUS]
You don't need to be so formal.
You outrank me now.
You're the second-in-command.
[YUNO] Hearing you call me
"Vice Captain" feels weird.
Just use my name, it's easier.
Honestly. I couldn't care less.
[BELL]
Well, I do care, thank you!
Yuno's a vice captain,
which means that
he's almost at the top!
And do you know
who was there for him
every step of the way?
That's right,
it was yours truly,
his ultra-cute
right-hand lady,
AKA, the greatest partner
in the whole wide world!
Right, my darling?
There's a big difference between
Captain and Vice Captain.
[BELL]
Aw, you're always so modest.
--Owie!
--[YUNO] Huh?
[rumbling]
What is that mana?
Huh?!
[gasps]
He took down Captain Vangeance.
It can't be.
Who the hell is that?
Oh, dear.
It looks like we left
a few of you alive.
[VILLAGERS screaming]
[YUNO]
You must be...
[ZENON] I see Gaderois and
Foyal have been defeated.
Those two were only
at 40 percent power.
I suppose I shouldn't have
bothered bringing them
if they couldn't
surpass halfway.
[BELL]
Yuno! Hurry and use Spirit Dive!
This guy... He's serious!
[YUNO]
There's no time to dodge it!
[KLAUS, LETOILE, YUNO yelling]
[LETOILE]
He's too strong!
What should we do?
Really?
You okay, Klaus?
[YUNO gasps]
You bastard!
[YUNO]
Spirit of Zephyr won't work?
Wait, it's worse than that.
He's regenerating himself
extremely quickly!
[ZENON]
A stage-zero?
Well then, let me show you...
[YUNO gasps]
[ZENON]
...a bit of my devil's power.
[YUNO gasps]
[ZENON]
Fifty-five percent.
Do you see what your problem is?
It isn't that you're weak.
I'm just that much better.
All of this is for the glory
of the Spade Kingdom.
[thud]
[panting]
[BELL sobbing]
[gasps]
Wait. This is...!
[RALPH]
Prince Yuno!
Please, Yuno! Don't leave me!
I can't live without you!
[RALPH]
The prince. He's dead?
No.
[RALPH]
It's not true. It can't be!
You can't die. Not like this!
[BELL]
Huh?
A tree? How?
It's so huge.
I know this spell!
[BELL]
That's the captain's magic!
[YUNO grunts]
[gasps]
Yu-Yuno.
[cries]
Thank goodness!
I'm fine.
[BELL]
You scared me!
Klaus?
Somehow we're still alive.
This is Lord Vangeance's
World Tree Magic.
And he was wounded so severely.
He must've used all the
strength he had to save us!
Has anyone seen the captain?
No way. There's no
way he's been taken.
Survive, Lord Vangeance.
[YUNO]
Where are the others?
[YUNO gasps]
[GOLDEN DAWN 161B]
Shiren.
[GOLDEN DAWN 161C]
He's dead.
Oh, no. Please, no.
[KLAUS]
Hamon.
He saved so many
of us from dying.
But even his magic couldn't
bring back the people
who were already dead.
[YUNO]
Half our squad... was killed.
Damn it.
[YUNO]
I should've been stronger!
[screams]
[ZENON]
This is only the prologue.
Once our objective
comes to fruition,
all of you will be plunged
into profound misery.
Black Clover , Page 162:
"The Great War Breaks Out."