[RALPH panting]
[RALPH] I need to get through
this strong magic region
before I run out of mana.
[WOLF 158A barks, growls]
[RALPH grunts]
No.
Whatever happens,
I can't die here!
[RALPH] I have to live
long enough to tell him.
[groans]
[VILLAGERS groaning]
The giant traveling
fortress of Candelo,
created solely for
the purpose of crossing
the strong magic region.
It sure is coming in handy, huh?
But these people
are way too weak.
They run out of
magic power so quickly.
They're trash!
[COMMANDER 158A] We just
need half of them to live
if we wanna get through.
Life energy contains mana.
So we'll collect every drop,
even from the smallest child.
I realize this
summons was abrupt,
so thank you for coming.
Don't worry about
that, Loropechika.
Anyway. Spade's forces are
drawing closer, aren't they?
Indeed.
It won't be long before
they make it to the border.
They've done great damage
in the last six months.
Diamond's essentially
been taken over.
Both our own nation
and the Clover Kingdom
currently stand in harm's way.
So, in spite of
all that preparation
we've been doing, they're
still one step ahead of us?
Well, I'm ready
for a fight whenever.
Good, then I'd like
to send a team
to the strong magic region.
That's where their
forces are now.
We can ambush them.
I think timing is gonna
play a big role here.
It might be easier to win if we
can draw them in closer to us.
[MIMOSA] They're crossing
a strong magic region,
so I'm sure they'll be worn
down when they get here.
That'll be the time to strike!
Actually, I doubt they'll be
weakened by the trip at all.
Apparently, they're
going to arrive
in some sort of
traveling fortress.
You're kidding me!
[LOROPECHIKA] The worst part
is the way they're abusing
the weaker people
of their kingdom.
They've been using them
as a source of energy.
[footsteps]
Asta, hold on!
We're still coming up
with a strategy here!
What should we do now?
Do you think we should track him
down and bring him back?
[sighs] It's fine.
Asta can break through
their front lines.
I have confidence in him.
He won't be easy
for them to defeat.
The only people who would
normally be expected
to obtain meaningful results
from this training
are the ones who are loved
by mana, and experienced,
higher-stage mages.
Asta has no magic at all,
and yet he's improved
by a surprising amount during
the time he's spent with us.
It's great that he's
at the arcane stage,
but I was even more
impressed by his hard work
and refusal to give up.
[MAN 158B grunts]
Guess that one's done.
So, which one of you
chumps wants to go next?
Make sure you carry
the fallen to the back.
Sir. I beg you.
My sister's so small.
Her mana is still weak.
Please, sir, let her live!
[laughs] You have some nerve,
talking out of turn like that.
[WOMAN 158A gasps]
When you're just a
piece of low-stage trash!
Pathetic weaklings like you
can't even muster
any attack spells.
The only thing you're good for
is using your puny magic power
to move this fortress
around for us!
So if you scum know
what's best for you,
then you'll do as
we say. [laughs]
If you ask me,
you're getting off easy.
I mean, you're not gonna die,
not till your mana
runs out, anyway.
[laughs] Let's see...
I think you'll be the lucky
young lady who gets to go next!
--[gasps] No!
--[CHILD 158A] Big sis!
[SOLDIER 158A] You're
actually about to be useful
for once in your pitiful little
life, you should be happy!
[laughs]
--[gasps]
--[ASTA yelling]
[ASTA] Man, these strong magic
regions are somethin' else.
The weather sucks!
[ASTA laughs] I guess I don't
have full control over this yet.
Slayer!
You're through!
Given the robe,
I take it that you're a
Magic Knight from Clover.
What are you doing here?
Look at this loser!
He doesn't have any mana!
Heh! Pathetic!
And he's here alone?
How stupid can one guy be?
I don't know what
you're trying to do,
but you're wasting your time!
I'll stop you
in your tracks, kid!
Now die!
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[ASTA] The only person
wasting time here is you.
Even if I'm outnumbered,
I'm gonna take every
last one of you down.
So you might as well
come at me all at once!
You little brat!
Who the hell are you?
[SOLDIERS groan]
Okay. I'm Asta from
the Clover Kingdom.
I'm a member
of the Magic Knights!
Black Bulls!
I came here to help
you guys get away!
So don't worry.
You're all safe now!
No, we're doomed.
They were only
letting us stay alive
so that we could
fuel this thing!
There's no hope for us.
[ASTA]
She's completely terrified.
[WOMAN 158A] We can never
leave this fortress.
Even if we're set free,
there's no way
we could escape the strong
magic region with our lives.
Why is this happening?
None of us ever wanted our
kingdom to be part of this war.
[ASTA]
These poor people.
Now where's the jerk
who's makin' 'em suffer?
[WOMAN 158A] The captain who's
in charge of this fortress
has a bizarre power.
It's something strange, as if
it's from a different world.
Right! I'm gonna go beat up
every bad guy on this thing
so you won't have
to be afraid!
[WOMAN 158A]
What? But that's impossible!
Who knows how many soldiers
they might have on board!
--It's okay!
--[alarm blares]
[gasps]
[SOLDIERS grunt]
There's the intruder!
--[SOLDIER 158F yells]
--[SOLDIER 158E] We'll stop you!
Dweller, now!
[ASTA]
Black Slash!
[SOLDIERS groan]
[VILLAGERS gasp]
Up there.
[SOLDIERS yell]
[SOLDIER 158G]
What the--?
[gasps]
--[SOLDIER 158H] That's it!
--[SOLDIER 158I] You're mine!
[yells]
[SOLDIERS scream]
[SOLDIER 158L]
Take this!
[SOLDIERS scream]
[SOLDIERS yell]
Who the hell is this guy?
[ASTA]
Let's see. Must be there.
You just had to show up here
and make a mess of things,
didn't you?
From the looks of you,
I assume you also have
the power of a devil.
Your people are terrified!
How could you torture
them like this?
[COMMANDER 158A]
Torture them? Not at all.
They're sacrificing
themselves in service.
They're nothing but trash,
so this is the best fate
they could have asked for.
Your people are not trash!
[ASTA]
Whoa. My body!
[ASTA sputtering]
[COMMANDER 158A] I don't know
how manaless filth like you
managed to get your pitiful
hands on a devil's power.
But you will not be able
to evade my technique.
You're no match for
a higher-level mage
such as myself.
Poison Creation Magic:
Basilisk's Breath.
You're worthless.
You won't even make suitable
food for this creature.
Destroyer!
What?
No. How?
He erased the poison?
[COMMANDER 158A] How could
a worm like him be so strong?
[ASTA]
You may have a devil's power,
but it looks like you've
only got a tiny piece of it.
Sacrificing your people
to help your kingdom?
That's bull!
If you wanna fight so badly,
I'll give you all
the fight you want!
He's making a mess as usual.
That idiot.
How the heck did he do that?
All right, I took
care of the big guy,
and I wiped out his
little buddies, too!
You're all safe now!
--I don't believe it!
--[MAN 158F] Seriously?
[magic whirring]
[ASTA]
Hey, look who's here!
Man, Noelle's water
armor is so cool!
And now she can use that
bubble thing at the same time?
She's gotten way stronger!
[NOELLE] Look, just for the
record, using a transport spell
while moving through
a strong magic region
is really difficult.
[MIMOSA giggles]
We realize that, Noelle.
Thanks for getting
everyone here safely.
You did a wonderful job.
Truly, it was quite impressive.
[NOELLE]
Hey, don't patronize me!
I'm royalty, you know!
[MIMOSA]
Uh, yeah, so am I.
[NOELLE]
What's the big idea, stupid?
Who said you could go
barreling out of that meeting
and leave us in
the dust like that?
I mean, that's pretty
typical for him.
[NOELLE] You could've at least
taken me along with you.
[FINRAL] Wow, the excitement
of being with Noelle and Mimosa
almost killed me.
Wait, no it didn't!
I wasn't excited at all!
Lady Finnes is the only woman
who does that for me now.
[gasps]
Oh, my, are you all right, miss?
You look like you're distressed!
I only hope you'll
allow me to comfort you--
Stop it! No comforting
other ladies!
Hey, Big Sis? That
man's kinda scary.
You've improved
a lot, too, Finral!
I'm so proud of you!
Thanks a lot.
I'm doing my best.
[NOELLE] No way, why would
you be proud of this loser?
Huh?
I still can't believe
there's a woman out there
who actually agreed
to marry you, Finral.
Are you sure that you
didn't just imagine her?
I told you, she's
real! Quit asking!
Where'd that come from?
What's happening now?
I can't replenish your mana,
but I can heal you, at least!
Plant Recovery Magic:
Princess-Healing
Flower Paradise!
Awesome!
You've gotten way better at
using your magic, too, Mimosa!
Seriously cool!
That means a lot,
Asta. Thank you!
That's amazing.
But still...
The place that all of you
came from; it was taken over?
That's right. Our
village was attacked.
One night, the army
suddenly showed up,
with no warning at all.
Anyone who defied them
was killed on the spot.
If we tried to go back,
they'd probably execute
us for escaping.
There's no need to worry.
No need?
We'll fix this.
Our friends are
on their way there.
Running off without
a plan? That moron!
We should follow Asta's lead!
Yeah, no way am I gonna
let him get all the action!
[LOROPECHIKA]
Hm...
[NOELLE]
She's not very regal.
Then again, she is in PJs.
[gasps] No. I'd rather
you not follow him.
I have a different
job for you two!
[BOTH gasp]
[LOROPECHIKA]
This is our chance.
I want you to help me take over
the Spade Kingdom's
outlying base!
[BOTH gasp]
Now, Finral, Noelle,
and Mimosa,
please go and provide
backup for Asta.
Um, sorry, it's just...
I'm not sure it's a
good idea to split us up.
It'll be all right.
You've all trained hard.
You can do this.
Man, this is such
a waste of time.
Why did we have to get stuck
watching over this
stupid village?
Hey, keep your voice
down, would ya?
If the captain hears you,
we'll all be screwed!
[SOLDIERS yelp]
An intruder!
[SOLDIER 158P yells]
Die!
[LUCK grunts]
[laughs]
Seriously? Is that
the best you got?
[LEOPOLD] I was told they
were all stage two or weaker.
So no matter how many
there are, we're sure to win!
Flame Magic:
Profound Spiral Flames!
[SOLDIERS scream]
No way! Is it over already?
I guess so!
Sorry, there's no one
left for you to beat up!
[LUCK]
Boo.
Okay, we're all done over here.
[ASTA]
That fast?
What's the matter, Asta?
Did ya think you were
gonna hog all the glory?
Keep dreaming!
Holy crap, Leo! Looks like
you got a lot taller!
[LEOPOLD] Well, duh, look who
my brother and sister are!
Awesome is just
in my genes! [laughs]
So lucky!
I'm gonna head out now.
I marked this place,
so I'll be back soon.
Heh! Thanks for the help,
Finral. See ya then!
[LOROPECHIKA]
Seems everything went well.
We just received word
that they were successful
in taking control of the base.
And they did even better
than I could've expected.
That was impressive!
[GAJA]
True, but still.
Yes, I know.
The real battle
has yet to begin.
[MAN 158C]
Is the fighting over?
Can we leave now?
--Are the soldiers all gone?
--[MAN 158D] We're saved.
What about our village?
What will you do to it?
Huh? What do you mean "do"?
I mean, the ones who
just seized control,
they're all with
you, aren't they?
And you came here from
the Clover Kingdom.
We have to obey the strong
if we want to survive.
That's the way
things work, isn't it?
Oh, we won't do anything.
That's your village.
Do what you want with it!
[gasps]
Our friend Finral,
he's gonna make sure
everyone gets back
safely. So hang tight!
Wow, really?
--[WOMAN 158B] We're free!
--And they won't take our mana?
Thank goodness!
We're so grateful, sir!
Yeah, thanks for being so nice!
No problem! We just
wanna stop the devil
that's hiding in
the Spade Kingdom!
The devil?
Uh, well, you see,
as it stands right now...
Our nation is governed
by the Dark Triad.
And they've bestowed power
upon another group below them
called the Dark Disciples.
Believe me, sir,
they're extremely strong.
Rumor has it, the Dark Triad
are every bit as fearsome
as devils themselves.
Oh, man. That sounds bad.
[DANTE] It appears as though
you've gotten quite comfortable
with wielding the devil's power,
Zenon.
Yes. Mostly.
We've received reports that
our outlying base has fallen.
The same happened to Candelo,
the mobile fortress
we sent toward
the Heart Kingdom.
Let's not worry about that.
Our soldiers need something
to keep them occupied, anyway.
Dante. What's the deal?
Why does Zenon get all the fun?
You let him go to Diamond
all by himself, too!
Because I was better suited
for that assignment.
So? What's your point?
You only used about 40 percent
of your power that time!
I'm capable of the exact same
thing, thank you very much.
Come on, guys.
When are you gonna let me
do something interesting?
[DANTE chuckles] You have
improved quite a bit, Vanica.
That's right!
So let me prove it!
Yes. You are ready,
and it's time to make our move.
[laughs] Yay, finally!
I get to eat my treat.
I've been saving that thing
for so long, but no more.
So, why did we wait
for half a year?
We needed to be fully prepared
for the events to come.
After all, what would be the fun
in letting the game end swiftly?
We're going to wipe out
this entire world.
All sense of order, mankind's
successes, nature's beauty.
Everything will be meaningless.
The keys we need to open the
door are well within our reach.
You mean the
arcane-stage mages.
There is no possible
salvation for them now.
At this point,
we hold existence itself
in the palms of our hands.
Asta's off in another
land doing his best.
What'd he say?
"I think the big battle's
going to start soon"?
[gasps] Oh, my,
it's getting cloudy!
[grunts]
[gasps] Sir! What happened?
Please. Lord Yuno.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[MIMOSA]
Comparing Heights.
Check it, Asta! I've really
grown a lot lately!
Yeah, that's great and all,
but I feel like
I might've grown
a little bit, too,
if you look at me super close!
We're pretty much
the same height now,
so there's no reason to
brag about stuff like that!
Come on, that's ridiculous.
Let's compare, shall we?
See, I'm taller!
Asta needs me to help him!
I know just what to do!
[ASTA yelps]
Ha! There we go, we're
basically the same size now!
How did you do that?
I'm glad I could
make him happy.
While I'm at it,
why stop at a tie, right?
Eat that, Leo!
Now I'm way taller
than you'll ever be!
At first I thought you had
been eating your veggies,
but turns out you're
just standing on them.
[laughs] Oopsy daisy.
[ASTA] Leo! Who said
you could grow without me?
[LEOPOLD]
It has been six months!
[NOELLE]
I've also grown a lot--
Hey! My eyes are up here, buddy!
[ASTA]
Huh?
[LEOPOLD]
Black Clover , Page 159:
"Quiet Lakes and
Forest Shadows."