[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] The Royal Knights
is an elite team
of warriors chosen from
only the most capable
Magic Knights in all
of the Clover Kingdom.
And the selection exam
was finally underway.
Asta, Mimosa Vermillion,
and the mysterious
mage who called
himself Xerx Lugner
were among the first to
battle in the tournament.
[MIMOSA, ASTA gasp]
[ASTA]
What the--?
[NARRATOR] For some reason,
Xerx made no attempt to fight.
So Asta and Mimosa
were forced to charge
into enemy territory
on their own.
Do it now!
[NARRATOR] Just as victory was
starting to look impossible.
Xerx's Trap spell was
activated, bringing about
a surprising comeback
for Asta's team!
[NARRATOR] As for the contenders
in the second battle...
My, what an eyesore.
I'll thank you not to
interfere with the splendor
of the magnificent
Kirsch Vermillion!
[KIRSCH]
Ah, woe is me.
Why must this wretched
world be overrun
with such aesthetically
unpleasing creatures?
And why was I cursed
to be born so beautiful
amongst this pile
of ugliness? Tragic.
[ASTA]
I don't get this guy!
Just shut up!
It's bad enough to think you're
better than everyone else,
but you could at least
keep it to yourself!
Ah! Please don't fret,
my homely friend.
--Wha...?
--[KIRSCH] I understand
that you envy my dashing
good looks as anyone would,
but it isn't your fault
that you're ugly.
You can't just go callin'
people ugly, ya pretty-boy!
And I'm not ugly! Are you crazy?
No one in the world is
as beautiful as Char is!
You're just a nasty,
narcissistic, disgusting man!
Oh, my.
Such lowly words must never
pass the lips of a maiden,
regardless of how utterly
baseless they are.
What a shame, you almost have
the potential to be pretty.
If you modeled yourself
after my example,
you could improve your
appearance quite a bit.
[ASTA] He does know they're
supposed to be teammates, right?
Mimosa! It's good to see you!
Have you come to gaze
upon my glorious face?
Be careful not to get sick
from an overdose of beauty!
Thanks for your concern,
but you're making me feel sick
for a different reason.
How can you say such words?
Can you not comprehend
my splendor?
Are you ill?
Allow me to heal you!
You're the one who's
ill, big brother.
If I'm being honest,
I hope you lose this battle.
Come, now. You
shouldn't make jokes.
You've never been
very good at it.
Really?
Yes, jokes are to be told
with elegance and grace!
In other words, they should be
beautiful, like yours truly!
[ASTA] Mimosa's older
brother sure is unique.
Not sure if that's
a good thing or not.
It seems like she's
havin' a hard time
dealing with him, though.
[KIRSCH]
Hm?
Oh, hey, it's nice to meet ya!
Mimosa's been a big help--
And you must be that
commoner boy, Asta.
That's me.
Don't you dare speak
to me so casually,
you speck of dirt.
[ASTA]
Whoa! His eyes just went dead!
[KIRSCH]
I can't bear the sight of you.
Your aura is far from beautiful.
Your presence, unsightly.
[ASTA groans]
[KIRSCH]
Clothes, dirty.
[ASTA groans]
[KIRSCH]
And those muscles are grotesque.
[ASTA groans]
The human form is
designed to be beautiful
exactly as it is, you idiot.
There's no need to train it.
Such a thing is for the weak.
Uh...
Well yeah, I was pretty
wimpy a long time ago.
It's hard not to be when you
don't have any magic power.
That's why I worked so hard!
My muscles may be ugly,
but they're my weapons!
[chuckles] We're born with
a predetermined capacity
for magic power,
and that's that.
No matter what ugliness
we stoop to in our struggle
to change it,
we can never do so.
Predetermined? I don't...
[KIRSCH] Your brains are
as repulsive as your face.
How did a disgraceful
commoner such as you
even come to be a Magic Knight?
Good luck, Kirsch!
I do want you to win
this battle, after all!
Mimosa! What a sweet sentiment!
Does this mean you've recognized
my gorgeousness at last?
No, I'm just looking
forward to the chance
for me and Asta to obliterate
you beyond recognition.
Do your best!
Oh. Obliterate. Ah.
It's such a beautiful
choice of words!
[YUNO]
That guy is flashy.
Even from here,
he's blinding me.
Yeah, he's a little much.
His name's Kirsch Vermillion.
Mimosa's older brother.
Every bit as creepy
as he is annoying.
That's no way to introduce him!
That man's the Vice Captain
of the Coral Peacocks!
Show some respect!
Despite the way he looks,
I hear he essentially runs
the squad by himself these days.
Since their Captain,
Dorothy Unsworth,
is perpetually napping.
You said "despite the
way he looks." That means
you think he's a fashion
disaster, too, right, Specs?
Yeah, Specs agrees with us.
Glad you're with us, Specs.
That's not what I think!
Well, a little.
How much longer must I wait?
Bring on the next match!
I'm so restless,
I can't bear it!
Then let's begin.
[EMCEE MAGE]
For the next fight:
Team C: Kirsch, Sol, and Magna,
versus...
...Team D: Cesc,
Adrian, and Willy!
Round one, match two. Go!
[MAGIC KNIGHTS cheer]
Prepare to be overwhelmed
by my magnificent visage!
[BOTH]
Shut your trap!
We should get back
to the waiting area
so we can cheer
for Magna's team!
[MIMOSA] Oh, gosh. Asta's
so close to me right now.
[ZORA]
Someone's cocky.
You do realize that the
next team they're gonna
be up against if they
win is us, right?
--[ASTA] Xerx.
--[ZORA] Uh?
That stuff you were
sayin' after the match.
About how you're
not here to win,
but you have a purpose in mind.
I said I was lying.
Come on, no more secrets.
You may get on my nerves,
but we're still fighting
on the same team,
and you're strong!
If all three of us
work together,
I know we have what it takes
to win this tournament!
[MIMOSA]
Asta.
[laughs] Fine, I'll let
you be the decoy again.
No, that's not what I meant
when I said "working together"!
[ZORA]
They're starting.
Have some of this, buddy!
Flame Creation Magic:
Grand Slam!
You guys want some more?
Good. 'Cause here it comes!
I'm gonna march
straight over there,
smash the crystal
into smithereens,
and take home the win.
How's that for a strategy?
That's it, now you're talking!
That's some impressive
magic ability!
A Junior-Ranked
Fifth-Class Knight.
A peasant like him has no
business being that brazen.
He's certainly off the list.
Okay, Copper Magic!
Pursuing Jackals!
[JACKALS growling]
[MAGNA]
Bad dog! Get back!
Hah! Let's see
how you like this!
Hey!
Come over here and fight
me yourself, ya coward!
Come on!
My magic'll burn you to a crisp,
and your little dogs, too!
--[KIRSCH] Phew.
--What the--?
Mowing everything
down indiscriminately...
You've no style to speak of.
Where the hell did
you come from?
[KIRSCH chuckles]
You're trying too hard at this.
There's no reason to
act haphazardly when
you have proficiency in both
short- and long-range spells.
The mana weeps for you.
What'd you say?
Get a stronger read on
your opponent's magic,
almost surrendering to it.
Then you can launch the right
attack for the distance.
If you can master that,
your flame will burn
much more beautifully!
Uh...
[MAGNA] Different spells
for different ranges, huh?
Okay. So I just gotta
stop tryin' too hard
and surrender to their mana.
[JACKALS growl]
[JACKALS howl]
[MAGNA]
First, the close up ones.
[JACKAL F howls]
[MAGNA] And now for the
ringleader in the back!
[gasps, yelps]
[MAGNA]
Gotcha!
How's that?
Wait, where'd that
little showoff go now?
[SOL] Earth Creation Magic:
Raging Mother Goddess!
Outta my way!
I'm doing my part to make
the Blue Rose Knights
get a higher rank
so Char'll be happy!
[WILLY]
Mud Binding Magic: Flashbog!
Sorry, miss, but I'm afraid
it won't be that easy.
My bottomless mud
will swallow up
you and your golem!
How'd he get there? Aw, crap.
Such a simple method of attack
is an affront to my eyes!
What?
[KIRSCH] Your Creation
spell generates golems
that can follow orders, yes?
Our strategy does not
involve distracting our foe
with this garish
thing's wasteful size.
[SOL]
You watch your mouth!
Why not break it up into
five smaller golems
to cause them confusion?
An ambush from underground
is also an attractive option.
Your creative mana should
be capable of that.
Uh, sure. 'Kay!
Earth Creation Magic:
Multi-Mother Goddess!
[SOL]
Less power, more speed!
Your mud will never
catch up with them now!
This isn't fair.
I'm outnumbered!
And since I've been
guarding the crystal,
it remains untouched
and flawlessly beautiful!
Blossom to your heart's content!
[KIRSCH laughs]
[ADRIAN] Actually, you left
your crystal wide-open.
Water Creation Magic:
Climbing Coelacanth!
[ADRIAN]
It's mine!
[BOTH gasp]
So sorry.
[CLONES laughing]
It's too late for you.
My dazzling spell has
you in its clutches!
Cherry Blossom Magic:
Raging Magic
Cherry Blossom Storm of Petals.
Plus my beautiful illusion.
[MAGIC KNIGHTS gasping]
[KLAUS] He's covered
the field with a storm
of cherry blossom petals?
Damn it! I can't keep
track of them in this!
[MAGNA]
All right. This I can work with!
[MAGNA, SOL] He just gave us
a clear path to their crystal!
Go on!
Let's Tread the flowered
path to victory!
Burst into bloom!
[KIRSCH] Bloom, bloom,
bloom, bloom, bloom!
[MAGNA, SOL]
Ready! Full bloom!
[EMCEE MAGE]
Team C wins!
[MAGIC KNIGHTS]
Whoa!
What a gorgeous display!
[KIRSCH] In this world,
there are but two great crimes.
Failing to radiate
beauty in every way...
[MAGNA, SOL]
...and failing to notice beauty!
[MAGNA] All right, we got
through it somehow!
[SOL] He's a pain, but I'm
still glad he's here!
So fast!
There's a lot more to that guy
than I thought there was!
Still creepy, though.
How the heck are we
supposed to beat him
when we get to the second round?
You know, perhaps
the greatest crime
is my unbridled handsomeness.
Tell me the truth.
What did you think
of our battle?
Egregiously beautiful, yes?
[MAGIC KNIGHTS]
That's right. Of course.
[SEKKE]
Ha, ha...
[MAGNA]
Why did I go along with that?
[SOL]
I'm so ashamed.
That flower spell.
The initial phase of it
allowed him to create copies
of himself to confuse the enemy.
Then, a storm of petals
scattered across the field,
obscuring their vision
and scrambling their
magic detection.
Once that was done,
it gave his team
a path to the crystal.
A feat like that could
only be possible
with the enormous magic power
possessed by royalty!
Oh, dear. I'm so
beautiful it scares me.
Now I understand
why Kirsch Vermillion
is the most likely candidate
to succeed Dorothy Unsworth
as Captain of the
Coral Peacocks!
He's still weird, though.
Well!
[ASTA]
Did you see that?!
Your brother was
incredible out there!
You two are obviously siblings!
I wish you wouldn't say that.
Silence, filth. Your
shrieking pollutes the air.
Now it's your turn to face me.
Too bad you're a cracked vessel
that can't hold a drop of power.
My lovely spells will
smash you to pieces.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I'm not worried, 'cause
I've used a lotta bowls
with cracks in 'em, and they
can still hold stuff,
even if it spills a little!
That's not...
Aw, you've used a lot
of cracked bowls.
Must be because
you were so poor.
How unsightly.
No, wait, that's not the point!
Sister Lily bought that
bowl for us to eat out of!
Even though it's
got cracks in it,
it's the symbol of the love
that she and I share,
and it means the
whole world to me!
And I'm gonna use it forever!
You just try and stop me!
Calm down, it was
just a metaphor.
Your brains really are useless.
Nuh-uh!
Now it's time to begin
the third match
of the first round!
[EMCEE MAGE] Team E:
Finral, Leopold, and Hamon,
versus Team F:
Borja, Kyle, and Gaston!
I can't wait to heat
up my Flame Magic
so that our team can smoke
out the competition!
And attacking them
with my Glass Magic
is sure to add a touch of
grace and sophistication!
Watching the way Kirsch
conducted himself
in that last battle gave me
a real spark of inspiration!
Why don't we try to fight
beautifully as well?
I don't give a crap
about bein' beautiful!
Forget your "spark
of inspiration."
I'm bringin' a
full-blown inferno.
Besides, that guy
kinda creeps me out.
[FINRAL] No. You should leave
our attack strategy to me.
My magic will help
us move swiftly.
We should make use of it.
I haven't fought
alongside the Black Bulls
all this time for nothing.
[FINRAL] There's no way
I'm gonna lose now!
--[HAMON] Hm...
--[LEOPOLD] Hot damn!
You're rarin' to go,
huh? I like that!
I'm sure you'll bring
out the best in us!
[GASTON] Leopold and Hamon
are skilled fighters.
[GASTON]
Go after the Black Bull!
[LEOPOLD]
Like I'm gonna let that happen!
[LEOPOLD yells]
[LEOPOLD] He's right, that
Spatial Magic's pretty handy!
[GASTON grunts]
Borja!
Feather Magic: Feather Tornado!
--It's over for you!
--[FINRAL] Ready for this,
--[LEOPOLD] Yup!
--Leopold?
[BORJA]
You're mine!
[yells]
[LEOPOLD yells]
[BORJA] They've been trying to
cause friendly fire all along!
And on top of that,
I have a serious
weakness to Flame Magic!
That portal user has a good eye
for what works on
this battlefield.
[HAMON] He assesses the area
and drops us in the spot
where our spells are
most advantageous!
[KYLE gasps]
Glass Creation Magic:
Épée de Verre!
[yelps]
[HAMON] To think the Black
Bulls had an ace like him
up their sleeve!
Why did they keep him
under wraps for so long?
[LEOPOLD]
Now's my chance to attack
with all the power I've got!
Flame Magic: Spiral Flames!
[EMCEE MAGE]
Crystal destroyed! Team E wins!
Got it! Whew!
[FINRAL] I'm glad we won,
but that was nerve-wracking!
[HAMON]
Finally! Now a delicious meal!
There's nothing like it!
And It'll bring us
closer together!
A meal, huh? Okay!
I say we make it a competition
to see who can eat more!
Count me in, pal!
I don't think my stomach
can take that right now.
Woo! Wow, Finral!
You were awesome out there!
That was great.
That Spatial Magic guy's
a force to be reckoned with.
[MAGIC KNIGHT 75A]
And he's just a Junior Knight?
[MAGIC KNIGHT 75B]
Yeah, all the Black Bulls
taking this exam are Juniors!
[GARETH]
I guess I underestimated them,
because they're
strong for the level
of experience they have.
Their squad must've really
stepped up this year!
[LANGRIS] Not bad for
the one who brought shame
upon the house of Vaude.
But I'm about to show
everyone how different we are.
It's time to continue
on to the fourth battle
of the first round! Team G:
Langris, Fragil, and Sekke,
versus Team H:
Gareth, Simon, and Medio!
--Ha, ha.
--[SEKKE] No, no, no,
this is all wrong!
Everyone here's so much
stronger than me.
I should've known I was still
too green to take this exam!
But Captain Jack said he
wants to give the small fry
a chance, so it's kind of his
fault for pressuring me!
This is a huge problem!
How did I get picked for this?
I mean, I volunteered,
but still!
I can't be held responsible
if I fail, right?
[FRAGIL]
Are you okay there?
Ha, ha?
All the Knights
from the Black Bulls
are Junior level, but they've
been really successful.
I'm sure you're just
as good as they are.
Ha, ha!
You've seen right
through me. What to do?
[gasps]
[SEKKE] I hate to show off,
but you leave me no choice.
Ha! I think I'll start by
making a grand and glorious
entrance on my
Sekke Shooting Star!
That sounds like
an excellent plan.
Our team's crystal's
now completely covered
with a barrier spell.
Good luck trying
to destroy it now.
--Hm?
--[engine revving]
[MEDIO chuckles]
I'd prefer to charge
toward them at full speed.
Ha, ha! Not a problem!
[GARETH]
They're headed this way.
What kind of absurd
vehicle is that?
Imbeciles.
We've set trap spells
all over the ground.
You'll never make it past!
[LANGRIS]
He, he.
[gasps]
[MAGIC KNIGHTS murmuring]
Well now.
He sliced through space.
How is that possible?
[gasps]
[EMCEE MAGE]
Crystal destroyed! Team G wins!
[SEKKE laughs] I hope you all
witnessed my awesome triumph!
I'm Sekke, master of the wind!
[SEKKE yelps]
[SEKKE]
Ha, ha.
A beautiful victory for the
illustrious House of Vaude.
Wow, Finral's older
brother really knows
how to win a battle.
[ASTA] I hope my sword can cut
through that kind of magic.
[SEKKE]
Ha, ha.
It's too bad that you'll
never be anything
more than a means of transport.
But my magic is useful.
So do try to stay
out of my portals
during the next battle.
It would be a shame if
you were to permanently
disappear somewhere.
Forget about what it would
do to Mother and Father--
I think a certain
someone would be
quite devastated as well.
Yeah, good point.
So if I wanna prevent that,
then I'll just have
to win, won't I?
That's my dear brother.
Still insolent as ever.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[FINRAL]
"I Can See It!"
It's amazing how you
can look at the whole
battlefield at once
so you always know
the best places to
put your portals!
Well, I'm lucky to
get personal training
from Captain Yami every day!
Really, what kinda training
do you do with him?
For example, after we eat...
If he's patting
his belly like that,
it can mean only one thing!
You must need to
use the bathroom!
[FINRAL] I'd know that
angry knock anywhere!
That's the signal you're
out of toilet paper!
Then there's... newspaper time!
Your bath time coffee milk!
I'll give you the usual.
A rugged look that
says "I didn't shave,
but I didn't not shave!"
And that's pretty much it.
Wow! Cool!
Kinda sounds like the
Captain's using him.
Uh-huh.
[KIRSCH]
Greetings, peasants!
I've come to
beautifully grace you
with my beautiful beauty
on this beautiful day.
Please try to contain your joy.
Beautiful Black Clover ,
even more beautiful
Page 76: "Mage X."
My great beauty
is beyond limits.