[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] In an effort to
undo the curse that Vetto placed
on Asta's arms, our friends
headed to the Forest of Witches
to speak to the Queen.
Once there, they found
Vanessa in dire trouble.
She's got Vanessa!
Vanessa!
[ASTA]
What do you think you're doing?
I don't care if you are
the queen or whatever,
get your foot off of
our friend, right now!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
You dare barge into my home
and address me that way?
[ASTA growls]
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
What a foolish girl I've raised.
She told me she would become
my slave and live out
the rest of her days here.
All for restoring those
silly arms of yours.
[ASTA growls]
She really did that?
[NARRATOR] But, just when
they were about to battle
the Queen and save their friend.
[gasps]
I didn't expect it
to happen so soon.
[NARRATOR] New enemies
descended upon the Forest.
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
The Eye of the Midnight Sun.
[FANA]
Flame Spirit Magic.
Salamander's Breath.
[NARRATOR] Recognizing
the severity of the threat,
the Queen of Witches restored
Asta's arms in exchange
for help against
their common foe.
Oh, yeah!
I am back in the game!
Get ready! It's time to go!
[GROUP]
Yeah!
[NARRATOR] Her superior
healing magic made Asta
even stronger than before.
And so, he began his battle
against the vengeful Fana.
I'll make sure
this is the last time.
Keep on showin' up,
and I'll just keep
on fightin' you off!
I'll keep fighting
you off forever.
[FINRAL]
Hmm.
[ASTA]
So bring it on.
Again and again and again
and again, do you hear me?
Whatever you throw at me,
I'm always gonna throw it
right back at you,
a hundred times over!
Let's go!
--I guess he must've built up
--I dare you to come at me,
--a lot of energy while his arms
--you big jerkface!
were out of commission.
You're vile.
But this time,
without a doubt...
...you'll die!
Here she comes!
Now, Flame Spirit Magic.
Salamander's... Talon!
[FINRAL]
Wha-- Seriously?!
It's so powerful!
[VANESSA]
The fire spirit, Salamander,
is believed to possess
the greatest offensive
strength among
all Four Great Nature Spirits!
[VANESSA] We might as well be
facing an entire nation's army!
[yells]
[gasps]
Amazing!
Spirits are mana made flesh.
And Asta's anti-magic sword
tears mana to pieces!
Oh, man, that was scary!
But it's really awesome, too!
I want a Salamander!
How can I get me one?
[VANESSA]
With Asta...
You're pretty good,
but that Vetto guy was
a whole lot quicker on
his feet than you are.
Me and my team, we've got this!
[VANESSA]
...we might just win!
[VANESSA] Hmph. Honestly,
watching you makes me feel
downright silly
for being scared.
Ugh, why are these flames
impossible to put out?
They just keep coming back!
[grunts]
I guess I'm just wasting
my magic power at this point.
I'm worried.
I hope they'll be okay.
How could you be so despicable?
I hate you.
Now! Counterattack!
Yeah! Sure.
You know what?
I think we should
have a little talk.
Huh?!
[FINRAL]
You've gotta be kidding me!
[VANESSA] She's not
someone to chit-chat with!
You say that you hate us.
What the heck did we do
to make you that upset?
What's your beef with
the Clover Kingdom?
Can't you explain?
I mean, how are we supposed
to understand one another
if all we ever do is fight?
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
Heh. Ready to talk?
Be quiet.
[yells]
What'd I tell you?!
Help me out here, Finral!
You got it!
[FANA gasps]
[ASTA grunts]
--How?
--Your old buddy Vetto?
That guy had it out for us, too.
We, the Eye of
the Midnight Sun,
had golden dreams
and bonds of blood!
[VETTO DEMON ELF]
Yes! Despair!
[ASTA]
And he was full of despair, too!
I want to know why!
Help me to understand you!
[FANA]
Licht, is that a human?
Yes. He's a good friend of mine.
[FANA] There's something
very mysterious about him.
I truly believe
there will soon come
a day when all of us can
exist together in harmony.
Let's foster understanding.
Your elvish mana really
is a remarkable thing!
If we combine that with
our own magic-item technology,
this land will be safer
and more prosperous!
Let's all work together,
hand in hand!
[laughter, cheering]
[ELF 46A] Congratulations
to the happy couple!
I can sense that the mana
has blessed our lives, as well.
We're so happy to bring our
new child into this world,
and I know your kind
is pleased to welcome it.
This little one here
is our future.
The bridge between
elves and humankind!
[ELVES screaming]
It's the humans!
They're attacking us!
[groans]
Oh, no. Please don't die!
[gasps]
Goodbye, dear.
[ELF 59G sobs]
Why, damn it?
He did this.
He's the only one
who knows this place!
I knew it!
That human betrayed all of us--
[LICHT whimpers]
[LICHT]
No...
No!
[FANA]
You...
How could anyone
trust your kind?
[NOELLE gasps]
[bellows]
[ASTA yelps]
What's that magic?
There's so much hatred in me.
Do you really think you'll be
able to withstand it all?
[ASTA]
She's got a third eye, too.
Whoa. That thing's huge now!
[yells]
I've got you, Asta!
[ASTA grunts]
Here's a portal!
So not only
has it gotten bigger,
now it's using a new power, too?
It'd be nice to catch
a break for once!
[ASTA yelps]
The flames of my hatred
will burn you into oblivion!
Well, this is a pain!
In that case...
...I'll just have to bust
out my special move!
Oh, wow.
That's no ordinary mage.
I just thought of a great idea!
[ASTA growls]
[GROUP yells]
[grunting]
[growls]
Come on!
[ASTA] The force of
the heat threw me back!
I'll need some help
to get close to her.
Vanessa, you doin' okay?
Finral, how about you?
Still hangin' in there?
I think so.
She's tricky!
It looks like she used her
insane amount of magic power
to generate a mana forcefield.
I'm having a really hard
time creating my portals!
And the second
I cast my Thread Magic,
it burns right up!
This girl is untouchable!
So this is a spirit, huh?
It's like fighting
a god incarnate!
[FANA]
You're done.
Here she comes!
[NOELLE] Water Creation
Magic: Sea Dragon's Cradle!
What're you three doing?
Good thing I'm here!
[GROUP]
Perfect timing!
What gives?
I've been putting out fires,
but they keep coming back!
Time to address the source!
[roars]
[NOELLE] Yikes, I wasn't
expecting something so scary!
Like I said,
I'll just go ahead
and knock this out real quick!
She's just who we needed.
Got that right!
Water beats fire!
[gasps]
The water's turning to steam!
Now, Flame Spirit
Magic: Salamander's Talon!
All right, everyone,
hang on tight!
--[FINRAL wails]
--[ASTA] Hurry!
That monster won't
be easy to defeat.
[NOELLE] Still, it's all up
to me and my Water Magic.
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
I can do it. I know I can!
I can! I can! I can!
[SOLID]
Don't be stupid.
You were born defective,
and nothing's changed.
You'll lose now just like
you've always lost before.
That attack of yours
at the Underwater Temple?
A fluke that only worked
because you let your emotions
get the best of you.
[NOELLE whimpers]
[BOTH] Face it: you're
nothing but a failure.
[laughter]
[sighs]
They're right. I'm useless.
[ASTA]
You are strong!
[gasps]
Noelle! Listen to me, okay?
You can do this!
We can't fight those flames.
It's up to you!
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
What are you saying?
Does he have to be so loud?
I can feel a headache coming on.
[FINRAL] Um, Asta, think
you could keep it down?
[ASTA] You're a big,
bad Magic Knight now!
Hey, Finral, why're you
plugging your ears?
Is the wind bothering them?
I think it feels...
Noelle. You ready?
[NOELLE]
Yes!
Get it together.
How many times has Asta given
you the courage to fight?
[ASTA]
You've got what it takes!
Like I need you
to tell me, Dorksta!
You just sit back and watch!
You've done your part.
Now it's my turn to
give you courage!
[VANESSA]
Here goes!
Get ready!
[NOELLE] I only have enough
power in reserve for one cast
of Sea Dragon's Roar.
[NOELLE] Everything is
riding--on this single shot!
Nothing but a failure?
That's not me anymore!
Water Creation Magic:.
Sea Dragon's Roar!
[gasps]
[FANA gasps]
You shattered it!
Begone.
Look out!
I'm not finished yet!
[gasps]
[BOTH]
No way!
[ASTA]
Amazing! [laughs]
We're alive!
You must die. All of you.
Well, Asta. See?
I bet you didn't know
I was that powerful.
Yay! I did it!
You crushed that thing!
Showed it what a real
Black Bull can do!
Way to go!
[FINRAL] The Salamander's
down for the count
thanks to Noelle's attack.
It's now or never!
[BOTH]
All right!
--Asta! Let's go!
--Ready? Let's go!
Okay! Finally time
for my special move!
[FANA]
You will die.
Mineral Creation Magic: Harpe.
[ASTA]
Huh?!
Wait, how is she using
something besides Flame magic?
That's so not fair!
[ASTA]
This spell...
[FANA]
Now, Flame Recovery Magic:
activate Phoenix Robe.
And she can wield
Recovery spells?
Seriously? Not cool!
[ASTA gasps]
I've seen that one before, too!
I knew it.
Hey! Flame lady!
[FANA gasps]
Do you happen to have a
brother who's incredibly pale,
has really spikey hair,
and looks like he's
never smiled before?
[FANA whimpers]
'Cause if so,
he's approaching from
the far end of the forest!
Aw, man, I thought
we were done
with the shouting, Asta.
I don't know that person.
And if I were to
claim any siblings,
it would be Licht and
the other villagers.
[FANA] You must be taught
a lesson, filthy humans!
I will kill every
last one of you!
Argh. I'm not gettin'
through to her at all!
Man! Guess we'll
just have to stop her
with my special move before
she can finish healing herself.
Yeah, and speaking of which.
What exactly is this new special
move you're so excited about?
I was wondering that, too.
[chuckles] I've been waiting
for you guys to ask me that.
See it goes like this:.
I hold both swords out
in front of me,
fly through the
air at super speed,
and plunge 'em right
into the enemy's magic!
I call it.
[BOTH]
Is that even possible?
Wait. You mean it isn't?
[VANESSA]
Hmm.
[BOTH] Maybe it wouldn't
be if we weren't here!
[VANESSA] You're always coming
up with the craziest ideas.
Let us give you a hand
with that new move!
[ASTA yelps]
[VANESSA] It's like
I told you before, Asta:
Friends help you overcome a fate
you can't defeat on your own!
We're here for you.
Your special move is
gonna be incredible!
Here we go!
[ASTA growls]
It's too late!
You're not killing
anybody, you hear me?
[gasps]
[gasping]
[ASTA]
Bull Thrust!
[GROUP]
We won!
All right!
My special move totally
kicked her butt!
[FANA]
It can't... be.
I failed...
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[ASTA]
"Again and Again."
[ASTA] Bring it on,
again and again and again
and again and again!
I'll just keep fighting
you off, every single time.
Again and again and again!
Try me!
[ASTA]
Om-nom-nom-nom!
Yeah bring it on,
fishcake after fishcake
after fishcake!
I'll just keep eating you up,
every single time try me!
Yeah! Bring it on, soybean
after fermented soybean!
I'll just keep slicing you up
again and again,
fermented soybeans!
[wails]
My swords are covered in it now!
Wouldn't wanna get
stabbed by those things.
[VANESSA]
You did it, kiddo!
You defeated Salamander!
Black Clover, page 60:
"Defectors' Atonement."
No, Asta.
It has nothing to do
with toning your muscles.
The word is "atonement,"
as in paying for your sins.