[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy who
was born without it.
His name is Asta.
[NARRATOR]
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world,
and to become the
next Wizard King!
[NARRATOR] The Black Bulls
traveled to Raquey for training,
hoping to fortify
their magic skills.
There, Asta and Noelle reunited
with Kahono and Kiato,
and were called upon
to solve a problem that was
brewing under the waves.
A Guardian of the Sea
had gone on a rampage,
posing a deadly threat to the
people of the Underwater Temple.
Noelle and a few of the
others took to the water
to quell the chaos.
[NOELLE]
I'll keep getting stronger, Mom.
Watch me. I'm just
getting started.
[NARRATOR]
But...
Noelle wasn't the only
member of the Black Bulls
who had vowed to
become stronger.
[giggles]
[SHEEP COOKS bleat]
What is this?
Apparently these foods
are supposed to
explosively enhance mana.
Sounds interesting.
I didn't know you could
make food like that!
All right, down the hatch.
Not sure what you
expect to happen,
since you don't have any magic.
I dunno, maybe it'll make
my anti-magic better somehow.
It's worth a try, right?
[BLACK BULLS]
Time to dig in!
[MAGNA] Whoa, feels like
it's already working!
[NOELLE] Yeah, my mana's
flowing like a waterfall!
[MAGNA]
What the hell's going on?
--[MAGNA screams]
--[LUCK laughs]
[MAGNA] This is some
powerful stuff, man!
[ASTA screams]
[laughs] It's so much fun!
Easy there, you guys!
I wonder what was in that food.
[gasps] Oh, no,
it's all three of 'em!
[ASTA yelps]
Hey!
Charmy, do somethin'!
Somebody's gonna get hurt!
[ASTA yells]
[CHARMY]
That food wasn't good enough.
I know! I'll go see him!
[gasps] You want me
to train you?
[SHEEP COOKS bleating]
[JAMO] Her eyes are
glistening with focus!
That bit of drool on her
chin is glistening, too.
And her forehead
glistens even brighter!
This girl is special.
She always has been!
[JAMO]
You got it, shortcake!
Starting today, you're going
to be my cooking student!
[CHARMY]
Thank you!
[JAMO]
So, what's the end goal, here?
[CHARMY] Well, you see, sir,
my magic allows me to cook meals
that recover a person's mana,
but that isn't enough!
I need to whip up something
that'll kick my friends'
magic into overdrive!
Ah, I see.
That's not going
to be an easy task.
Hope you're ready to
work hard, shortcake.
You know it!
[CHARMY yells]
[CHARMY]
...986...
...987...
[JAMO] These sheep cooks
are your magic,
but you can't simply work
on making them stronger.
That isn't going to give you
the result you're after.
The only way to make that happen
is to put aside your magic
and concentrate on training
beyond your physical limits,
so you and the sheep cooks
will have what it takes
to create the food that
can enhance mana!
One... thousand!
[JAMO]
Your stamina's much better!
According to this book,
the next thing you need to do
is gather some
unknown ingredients.
Three items so rare,
even I've never seen them!
That's pretty vague,
but leave it to me, sir!
[JAMO] First, we need the bulb
of a mentanpin mandoradora!
--[MANDORADORA screams]
--[CHARMY] Got it!
[JAMO] Next, hunt down the
noonesheardofthis coelacanth!
[JAMO] And lastly, the butt hide
of a surprisesquatch!
[CHARMY]
Gimme your butt fluff!
[JAMO] Shortcake did what?
Are you kidding me?
It's her!
Why did you push that hard?
[CHARMY]
Master... I did what you said!
And now...
I, Charmy Pappitson,
will create the most powerful
mana-enhancing dishes that
have ever existed in this world!
Tonight, I'll cook up
a feast for all my friends!
So whatever this is,
it'll enhance everyone's mana?
Um, why do I have
to be a part of this?
Because we need an escape
plan if things go south.
[FINRAL]
Wait, what's gonna go south?
[ASTA] Charmy must've worked
really hard to make this food.
Eat it!
You know what? I'm stuffed.
Yeah, I'm not hungry.
We should go. Thanks, Charmy!
Guys, please! We have to eat it!
[BLACK BULLS]
Hm?
[ASTA] We gotta show Charmy
that she didn't do all of this
for no reason!
[JAMO]
I beg you to stay!
[BLACK BULLS]
Hm?
This meal was made by the sh--
no, Charmy--after
she risked her life
to obtain the ingredients
to enhance her friends' magic!
[NOELLE]
Wait, who the heck is this guy?
[CHARMY]
Master. Asta.
Eh. I'll bite.
[BLACK BULLS gasp]
You see that? Demon food!
[MAGNA] I don't think
you cooked this enough!
Don't worry!
[FINRAL] Spatial Magic:
Fallen Angel Gate!
[BLACK BULLS, JAMO yelp]
[YAMI]
What are you bozos doing?
[ASTA]
Captain Yami?
You better not be runnin'
off with my wheels.
What if I need to go
to the bathroom?
[FINRAL] Sorry, sir, but you'd
just have to hold it in!
[YAMI]
That looks bad.
[DEMON FOOD roars]
I knew it. It's demon food!
No, not demon food!
You just made
that up, didn't you?
Why don't you cut the crap
and be straight with us!
Is that someone we know, or...?
[JAMO]
I've never seen it firsthand,
but legend has it,
a massive amount of mana
combined with the love
of a devoted friend
can cause food to come to life!
[NOELLE]
It absolutely can't!
[JAMO]
No?
Then how else would you
explain what's happening?
Charmy's desire to improve
her squadmates' magic power
was as pure and
genuine as it gets!
That's how the food she made
ended up so jam-packed
with mana, there was nothing
else that could've caused it!
[DEMON FOOD roars]
My food's an evil monster? No...
Hey, are you okay?
Aw, man, it's got me!
[gasps] Magna?
I dunno why, but my body
feels really weak now.
[ASTA]
Luck!
It's draining away our mana!
How is this even possible?
That's what makes demon
food such a deadly threat.
It absorbs mana from
everyone in the vicinity
until it becomes unstoppable!
No, really, who are you?
I worked so hard on those noms.
[YAMI] Hey, kid!
Quit daydreamin', already.
That thing is usin' mana and
you've got an anti-magic sword.
Do you need me to
spell it out for you?
It's just that...
Fine. Guess I'll
take care of it.
I'd like to think I could
count on my squad
to clean up their own messes,
but here we are--
[ASTA]
No, don't!
[YAMI]
You wanna explain yourself?
Captain, we can't
just destroy the food
Charmy worked so
hard to make us!
Hey, wait, that's
right, it's food!
Yeah, I thought
we covered that.
[CHARMY]
Please, Asta...
Stop it! You have to!
Okay!
[roars]
[YAMI]
Is he gonna--?
[ASTA yells]
This meal was a
labor of love,
and I'm not gonna
let it go to waste!
[ASTA grunts]
That'll come out of
both ends later!
[YAMI]
Feels like my mana's recharging.
Oh, yeah, it's flowin' out
of the part he's gnawin' on!
[CHARMY] Not so fast, Asta!
I'm not letting you eat it all!
Bet you want a piece of the
action, too, don't you, buddy?
Obviously!
All right, I want
the rest of you
to help them polish it off;
it shouldn't take too long
if all of you contribute.
But I'm just the transport!
[NOELLE]
And this is beneath me!
[MAGNA, LUCK yell]
Dude. Who are you?
And there ya go.
Good job, fatsos.
[NOELLE]
They did it to themselves.
Hey, I meant to tell you.
I feel like that
food was different
than what you usually cook,
and I don't just mean the part
where it tried to kill us.
Huh?
It's kinda hard for me to
put into words, but I dunno,
it seemed like the
only reason you made it
was to build up our mana.
When I eat your food,
I can usually taste how much
you care about making
people happy and stuff.
It just felt like that
was missing this time.
[CHARMY whimpers]
Uh! Whoa, that came out
really rude. I'm sorry!
Master?
[JAMO]
Hm... That's a good point.
In our quest to cook
the perfect meal,
we forgot the most important
thing about being a chef.
Charmy... No, I mean, shortcake!
One more try!
[CHARMY]
I'm ready, sir!
Let's do it again!
Here goes!
[ASTA]
Hah!
Gimme another!
[GORDON] Lately, I spend most
days surrounded by friends.
I'm extremely happy,
possibly happier
than I've ever been in my life.
Our battle with the devil
is fast approaching,
and we have to win.
If we fail, then our
happy days will be over.
[ASTA] Well, I thought that
last one was pretty good!
[GORDON]
Asta.
Do you think that I could
train with you for a little bit?
Yeah, of course you can!
Hey, Noelle, is it cool
if Gordon tags in for ya?
[NOELLE]
Uh, sure.
Gimme everything you got!
[GORDON]
Okay.
My best?
I didn't plan to do that,
but I'm sure Asta can handle it.
All right, here I go.
[GORDON] Poison Curse Magic:
Dwelling of the Poison Cloud.
[ASTA growls]
[gasps]
[ASTA]
Oh, sorry, Gordon! Are you okay?
As I expected.
I'm no match for you.
[GORDON]
I was fighting with all I had.
[GORDON] Maybe I've been
getting weaker of late.
[GORDON] When I first met
the team, I was truly alone.
[GORDON]
But that was largely because
I was as sharp as a knife,
and I refused to let anyone
get close to me.
And now... I've lost my edge.
[GORDON]
I love it here with my friends,
but I can't remain complacent.
If we're going to
defeat the devil,
I must regain the strength
I had in the past.
[GORDON] And that means I've got
no choice but to be alone again.
[GORDON] Lady Mereoleona sure is
powerful, and she got that way
by walking through a strong
magic region on her own
when she was young.
So I'll cross the Forest
of Poisonous Magical Beasts,
near the Forest of Witches.
I thought it over, and
the strong magic region's
a little too scary for me,
so I'll stick with this.
[GORDON sighs]
Things are going well so far.
I knew living my life alone
was the best idea.
Okay, time for a break.
I'm a little hungry.
Huh?
[MONKEYS chatter]
That's my food for
the whole week! Wait!
[GORDON]
I still can't find my bag.
Maybe I'll go home now.
I've probably been
alone long enough.
[GORDON] Uh-oh. I don't
know how to get back.
[GORDON] Eating by yourself
isn't as good.
[GORDON] Our meals together
were always loud and rowdy,
but I had fun.
I really wish
my friends were here
to help me get through this.
[GORDON]
Don't worry, Gordon!
I'll find you something
to snack on right away!
We're the G-G Guys, remember?
Pull yourself together, buddy!
You look so tired,
it's scary! Eek!
Be tough like me, dude.
I know you can do it!
Forget Magna,
I'm gonna kill you!
[GORDON] Great, I'm already
starting to go crazy!
[rustling]
[gasps]
[GORDON]
Now's my chance.
Let's see how much
stronger I've gotten
since I left the Black Bulls!
[GORDON] Poison Curse Magic:
Dwelling of the Poison Cloud.
[gasps]
I'll try again!
[GORDON]
No good!
[GORDON] My Poison Curse
Magic didn't work.
Guess I'm weaker than I thought!
[GORDON] This is the first water
I've found in three whole days.
I can live here by
myself for a while.
I'll hunt for food alone.
Sleep alone.
And wash my face alone,
just like this.
Back at the hideout,
Asta and I would always
wash each other's backs.
Some nights I'd
drink with Vanessa
while we talked
about our dreams.
Gauche let me help take
care of his Marie doll
every once in a while.
[GORDON] And Luck and I would
fight almost to the death.
[GORDON]
I must improve myself.
But, the thought of being
alone has become so painful,
even though that
was normal for me
before I joined the Black Bulls.
I wonder what my friends
are up to tonight.
[GORDON]
This is nuts!
We need to get a
move on, right now!
Come on, there's
no time to lose!
Yes, sir!
[GORDON]
They'll come looking for me.
I just have to trust them.
[gasps] You guys!
You found me already?
[WOLF 137A growls]
[GORDON] That must be the
smaller one's mother!
[roars]
[YAMI]
This is nuts!
We gotta get a
move on, right now!
Come on, there's
no time to lose!
[BLACK BULLS]
Yes, sir!
[panting]
[GORDON] Poison Curse Magic:
Aufwachen Dachs!
[GORDON]
It's no use.
My magic isn't affecting
these things at all!
[gasps]
[roars]
[GORDON]
This is it.
I'm going to die alone,
without friends at my side!
[GORDON]
No, wait.
[GORDON] The Black Bulls
didn't abandon me after all!
I understand now.
I don't need solitude
to make me stronger.
No, I'm strong because of
the bond I share with them!
Loneliness is the
deadliest poison of all,
and the only antidote
that cures it
is the love of
my dear friends!
[GORDON]
I'm so sorry.
I allowed fear to take over,
and I wrongfully attacked
you and your little one.
As a Magic Knight
who's been tasked with
protecting this land,
that's a mistake
that can never be forgiven.
You're my allies and fellow
residents of the Clover Kingdom.
What's more, you're
my friends, too.
[GORDON]
Thanks for leading the way.
I see, the two of you
have an immunity
to the type of magic that I use.
So that's why my spells
didn't do anything.
[GORDON]
I'm home!
Oh.
[GORDON]
What great friends.
They must've gone out
to look for me.
There's no telling what kind of
trouble they might be in.
[GORDON] Now it's my turn
to go rescue them.
I swear, I'll never leave my
dear friends behind again!
I want all of you to
push past your limits
by stuffing your faces tonight!
I sure pushed past mine!
[MAGNA] Hey, boss, is it me,
or is everybody staring at us?
Who cares? Apparently,
they're trying to sell off
their excess ingredients
right now, which means...
We can eat as much
grub as we want
and get 90 percent
off our bill!
[CHARMY]
I refuse to give up!
No matter how much
is on my plate,
I'm gonna eat every
last bite of it!
'Cause my tummy
deserves nothing less!
Black Clover , Page 138:
"In Zara's Footsteps."
Wait, who's Zara?
Oh! Must be Zora's dad!