[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] Continuing their
assault upon humanity,
the ten elves known as
the Apostles of Sephira
brought forth the Shadow
Palace, the border between
this world and the next that
lay inside Clover Castle.
[BAVAL] When we place the final
magic stone into its pedestal
inside the palace, the
elves' great reincarnation
will be complete!
Of course, a price must be paid
for our use of these bodies.
Sadly, their human souls will
be sent to the underworld!
[YAMI]
'Kay, so there's a magical space
growin' over there.
[cackles] Sounds like our
cue to head that way.
Huh?
[KLAUS] You won't stop
the Apostles of Sephira!
It's one thing after another.
Can't these jerks
just give us a break?
[NARRATOR] Fortunately,
reinforcements arrived!
Hey! Is that...?
[BLACK BULLS]
Here we are!
--[ASTA] You guys okay?
--[BLACK BULLS yell]
A huge bull? No way!
[laughs] Ya buncha dumbasses!
Better work on that entrance!
[KLAUS]
Curse you, humans!
Bring in whatever
reinforcements you like,
you're still no match
for the elves!
[NARRATOR]
Thanks to Asta and the others,
it appeared as though the
tables had turned, however...
[BLACK BULLS gasp]
Don't tell me this ki
is what I think it is.
[ASTA]
I know her!
That's the captain of
the Coral Peacocks!
Did she get possessed, too?
[DOROTHY]
Dream Magic: Glamour World.
[NARRATOR]
Dorothy Unsworth,
captain of the Coral Peacocks,
had also reincarnated as an elf.
She used her magic
to teleport Vanessa
and the others into
the dream world.
[CHARMY]
Wee! Wee!
Cool! Where are we now?
I can't see very well
without my glasses,
but it sure seems fun!
This place is freaky.
Anyone know where
the heck we are?
The captain of the
Coral Peacocks' magic.
I don't know what
else it could be.
[VANESSA]
Rouge wasn't able to evade it
because she couldn't identify
it as an attack spell.
This is the best!
It's one of the most powerful
spells a mage can produce!
Man! I'm freaking out!
[MAGNA] Will you please
just reign it in?
[gasps] Wow. This place
goes on forever.
There's no end to it.
Huh? Don't be a moron.
How's that even possible?
It's a lot more likely
than the possibility
of you becoming smart!
What the hell did
you say to me?!
You're in the Glamour World now.
In this place, the
impossible becomes real.
[ALL gasp]
[DOROTHY yawns]
Welcome to the world
where I control everything.
[ALL yelp]
The bed just...
[yawns] Everything here
is how I wish it to be.
I don't know what that thing
is, but it's really big!
And it just keeps
getting bigger.
[CHARMY]
I wonder if it's tasty.
[DOROTHY]
I hate to disappoint.
But you have no
chance of winning.
[ALL gasp]
And now, sleep.
Goodnight forever.
[ROUGE meows]
[ALL gasp]
How dare it try
to eat us instead?
[MAGNA]
I thought we died.
Get a load of this,
you stupid pig!
[DOROTHY]
The result was altered?
So... that magic really
does influence fate.
That little red cat
is so stinkin' cute!
[ROUGE meows]
You're not one of the
Black Bulls, you know.
If you stray too far,
her magic won't affect you.
Be careful.
I get it! Just you guys.
There'd have to be limits
on a spell this great!
Dream Magic and Thread Magic.
These two witches
are super cool!
Wanna research!
I feel like she's bad news.
Think so?
Here, eat! When you use magic,
you have to eat up so
you can recover your mana!
That magic is great!
You wouldn't happen to
be a witch, would you?
No, ma'am. I just really
like to cook and eat.
[DOROTHY]
An inexhaustible magic supply
and absolute evasion.
This won't be easy.
If this ridiculous place
is also a world of magic,
then all we have to do
to get out is defeat her.
Looks like it.
[LUCK, MAGNA yell]
[yawns] No.
[SALLY gasps] Can she use any
magical attribute in this place?
Oh, wow, I wonder
what her limits are!
Wow, this is fun!
Weirdo! This isn't fun at all!
I mean, what are we
even supposed to do?
She's invincible.
Your magic's not that
interesting. Hate to tell ya.
The hell did you just say?!
Well, then, do you
wanna fight me?
[VANESSA] This is not the
time to be playing around!
[CHARMY]
Yeah, she's right!
[VANESSA] I'm the
cornerstone of our defense,
and Charmy's vital
to mana recovery.
We can't both stay stuck here.
We have to hurry back
to the others.
But how?
[ROUGE meows]
[VANESSA] All I can do is help
us evade with Rouge's magic.
Time to recover your mana!
[MAGNA]
Come on! Eat, Vanessa! Hurry!
[CHARMY] Go! Go! Come on,
Vanessa! Eat it all!
[VANESSA] I am gonna slap all
of you if I get fat from this!
[DOROTHY] There has
to be some kind of limit
to her healing abilities.
An ever-flowing pool of water.
[DOROTHY] Which has blade-fish
continually spawning from it.
A never-ending onslaught.
[BLACK BULLS scream]
Step off my noms!
[VANESSA]
Crap! That's not good!
Oh, water. Say, there,
lightning boy.
Think you could attack
that overgrown puddle?
Yeah. I'm not sure
if I can destroy
something that big, though.
That's fine, just
give it your all!
Now, Lightning Magic:
Thunderbolt Destruction!
Well. That sure didn't work.
Okay, then, fire protozoan,
it's your turn!
Who you callin' a
fire protozoan, jerk?
Oh, come on. Put your
ego aside and shoot it
with everything you've got.
Who the hell do you think I am?!
[SALLY] If I guessed
correctly and that pool
really is made of water...
[SALLY]
...it's gonna explode!
[ALL gasp]
[BLACK BULLS coughing]
Yay! Intensity!
That's what I'm talkin' about!
Whoa. What just happened?
Ah. I broke the water
down electrically,
and then set fire
to what was left.
[LUCK]
Huh?
Well, if you unleash
Lightning Magic
and Flame Magic on water,
you can create
an explosion big enough to
destroy an entire mountain.
What the--?
How could you make us do
something so reckless?
[laughs] Who cares? You
could evade with the cat!
[LUCK] Ooh, I'll try that
with Noelle's magic next!
Anyway, the experiment
made a few other things
clear to me, too.
First of all, what she's
generating are actual
objects that she's visualized.
Which means real-world
principles work on them, too!
Yummy! It's a
real-life, tasty fish!
Secondly, because of
that, she's unable
to manipulate the
spells we cast,
nor can she control the
resulting phenomena.
That makes sense.
Otherwise, that explosion
and Rouge's ability
to manipulate fate
wouldn't have worked.
And, then... thirdly...
It's still going to be really
difficult to beat her.
Jeez! You think she'd
ease up a little!
We had better hurry up and
find a way outta this place!
Sorry. You don't have
that kind of time.
[CHARMY groans]
Charmy?
I'm so sleepy.
Hey! What are you talking about?
This is no time for...
[yawns]
[SALLY]
Uh-oh.
Oh, no, this is...
How unfortunate.
You can't evade the drowsiness.
That's how it is.
Everything that exists
in Glamour World
will eventually get
drowsy. Worse yet,
those who fall asleep
will never awaken again.
Who are you talking to? Ow.
I managed to stay awake during
all of Yami's all-nighters!
This is nothing!
[yawns]
This isn't good.
I don't know what we can
do to evade this attack!
[DOROTHY] You will sink
into the sleep of death.
For in this enchanted space,
you cannot resist.
[yawns]
[SALLY] Aw, everything
was already blurry--
now it's getting even blurrier.
Not having my
glasses really sucks.
Oh, yeah!
[SALLY]
Hey!
Check it out!
Do you have any idea
what these are?
If not, I'll tell ya.
Glasses! Like 'em?
What are you babbling
on about glasses for?
Now's not the time
to worry abou--
Yay! Look!
--[MAGNA] What?
--[VANESSA] Huh?
She just made those.
Where did those come from?
Everything in this world
does as she sees fit.
That's why the objects
that she visualized
in her head materialized.
Now, if you ask me...
What this world needs most
is an exit, exit, exit!
Make one, please?
[laughs] It's hard to
not think of something
once your mind has
already visualized it.
Hooray for the
power of suggestion!
Aw, hell yeah!
She's only invincible in
this dumb Glamour World!
If we can escape it,
we'll figure this out.
[YAMI]
Tch. What the heck's goin' on?
It's all the same,
no matter how far we go.
We can't even find any
walls, let alone Licht.
Then there's the faint
ki that I'm feeling.
Dammit, you think that--
[JACK cackles] Looks to me
like someone's magic
is causing us to lose our way.
Huh. So, I guess
you noticed it, too?
Beanpole weirdo.
Right back at you. Ya meathead.
They've got some
nerve hiding from us.
I'm impatient. I want
to dice them up already!
Let me have 'em.
No, they're mine to slash up!
I found them first,
it's only fair that I do it.
What are you talking about?
I found them first!
I did!
It was me!
Ugh, you are such
a pain in the ass!
[cackles] The early bird
slashes the worm!
[BOTH]
They're right there!
What are you slashing,
you jerk?
The enemy's totally right there!
No way!
Don't be dumb, they're
right over there!
I mean. Do you not even
know how to hit an enemy?
Well, you didn't
hit anything, either!
Ugh, whatever! I am
officially done with you!
[JACK]
That's my line, stupid beefcake!
Go over there!
[YAMI]
No, you go!
[JACK]
No, you!
[BAVAL] Yikes! That was
too close for comfort.
Though, I suppose,
in my warped space,
they were both correct,
technically speaking.
Thank goodness I rolled a six.
That should keep them
busy for a little while.
With Dice Magic,
the higher the number,
the more effective it will be
in the situation at hand.
I won't let anyone
get in the way
of the Apostles of Sephira.
I would appreciate
it if these two
could keep quiet
just a bit longer.
[ASTA grunts]
[whimpers] There's no way
I can keep this up anymore!
Their overall power is
much higher than ours.
I'm... about to...
reach my limit...
This is pointless.
Just give up already.
[ASTA grunts] I don't think
so! We're not done yet!
Right!
[ASTA]
What should I do? Think!
If only I could get into
my dark form. But...
I don't think he's gonna
give me a chance for that.
[NOELLE]
Asta and the others...
[MIMOSA] I hate that
all we can do is watch.
[MARIE]
Big Brother.
I know.
We must keep Licht and everyone
waiting a bit longer.
Eclat. You know what to do.
[MARIE]
Mm.
Here we go.
[ASTA grunts]
Huh?
[BOTH gasp]
[GORDON]
Asta!
[ASTA]
This spell...
It's the same one Gauche
used to avoid attacks!
[ASTA yelping]
[GAUCHE]
Yes, come right this way, kid.
Licht's Demon-Destroyer Sword.
It severs cause-and-effect
relationships nearby.
He can nullify
Eclat's eye magic,
so I'll get rid of him first.
Look here.
No, thank you!
Can you evade attacks
with your eyes closed?
[ASTA]
I can, with ki!
In that case... How about this?
[ASTA]
There's so many. Not good!
[ALL]
Asta, no!
This time, it's our turn.
We're going to save him!
Go!
I'm going to rip right through
that pitiful attempt.
What?
[ALL gasp]
Here we go. Now I can fight!
You're mine!
[ASTA yells]
You just...
[GAUCHE, MARIE]
...looked.
[ASTA] The magic item
in his left eye. Crap!
[GAUCHE]
I've had enough of you, brat.
[ASTA yelps]
[GAUCHE] I will destroy
every piece of you,
so you can't fight us again.
[ASTA grunting]
[ASTA] I'll never undo
the binding spell in time.
There's no way!
Asta's in trouble!
[GREY]
Oh, no, and my magic can't reach
nearly that high up!
[NOELLE]
Asta!
Goodbye now.
[HENRY]
We're here, Asta!
Poison Magic: Violet Schirm!
[GREY]
Transformation Magic:
Magic Conversion,
Poison to Mirror!
I owe ya one, guys, thanks!
That actually wasn't too bad.
[HENRY grunts]
[GORDON, GREY yelp]
[pants]
[HENRY]
Just as we thought.
Gauche is way stronger than
usual like this. Still.
Come on, now. Move!
[HENRY] Together, the
three of us can do this.
I'm still able to fight!
[panting]
[GORDON]
Henry!
That was close!
You okay in there?
I'm... all right!
[HENRY]
Come on, magic.
Please hold out just a little
longer. That's all I ask!
[NARRATOR] Many mages
use magic to reinforce
their natural defenses,
and Henry is no exception.
But, in Henry's case,
his very life depends on it.
His blood vessels, muscles,
and organs are incredibly frail.
He will die unless
he continually
reinforces them with magic.
However, he'd been
granted a constitution
that absorbed magical power.
One which enabled him
to gain it from others.
Despite being born into
a renowned noble line,
his body was deemed too frail.
His family, and the
rest of the world,
could not accept him
for what he was.
This can't be!
If we continue to
harbor that thing,
it will only bring disgrace
to the great name of Legolant.
[HENRY'S MOTHER] How can you
speak of our child that way?
[HENRY'S FATHER]
We have no other choice!
This is for our family.
[NARRATOR]
Placing too much value on status
can warp one's morals.
Henry's parents gave
him very little.
A house in the forest
that stored up magic
but remained unseen by others.
A sad and lonely existence.
[HENRY]
This is just as it should be.
All I ever do is cause
trouble for people.
You must be that mysterious
ghost I've been hearin' about.
Actually, sir... I'm not...
a ghost... at all.
Cool, well. My name is Yami.
I'm a brand-new
Magic Knight Captain,
and I'm lookin' for a hideout.
This place seems
to be a good fit.
[HENRY]
Before he came to me that day,
I was basically dead.
[YAMI] You should live.
It's more convenient.
But... I...
I mean, think about it.
If there's a buncha rowdy
Magic Knights causin'
a ruckus all the time; it might
even make you feel better.
[HENRY] That's how my
house became the hideout
for the Black Bulls. And up
until that moment, I was...
[pants]
[HENRY] I'm alive today,
and it's all because of them.
That's why I feel this way.
I don't care what happens to me!
[ASTA yelling]
[GAUCHE] He managed to
escape Eclat's binding.
[ASTA] I'm gonna stop
you two, no matter what.
I will turn you back into
the normal Gauche and Marie!
[HENRY] Yes. I will
save him at all costs.
I don't care what happens to me.
I'll save my friend! I swear!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[GAUCHE]
"You Saw."
[ASTA] I'm gonna stop
you two, no matter what.
I will turn you back into
the normal Gauche and Marie!
No, my name is Droit.
My name is Eclat.
And we are never going
to turn back now.
[GAUCHE] But... I would
like to learn more about
this human named Gauche.
This doll that looks
just like Eclat.
I had it when I reincarnated.
It's just too cute. And these.
The pictures of her
in different outfits.
He is truly a man of culture!
[GAUCHE]
This guy knows what's cute!
[MARIE]
Big Brother?
Oh, sorry, nothin' weird
going on over here. Nope!
[ASTA] Ah! You have a Marie
doll and her pictures!
Did you... see?
I did.
Why can't I move?
[HENRY]
Black Clover... Page 112:
"Humans Who Can Be Trusted."
I'll save... my friends...
no matter what... it takes.