[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[ASTA] Now we have to
defeat their leader?
What's with the sword?
[NARRATOR] Licht had awakened
from his centuries-long slumber,
overwhelming Asta and Yuno
with his devastating
strength and magic power.
[ASTA grunts]
[YUNO yells]
You're not killin' Yuno!
Or Asta, either!
[BOTH]
He's my rival!
[NARRATOR]
Even their perfectly coordinated
simultaneous attack had
no effect on their foe.
Well, 'bout that time.
Let's go pay the rest
of our friends a visit,
and then, we'll wipe
out all humankind!
[NARRATOR]
After escaping from the hideout
by the skin of their teeth,
Asta and Yuno joined forces
their friends and hurried
toward the capital, determined
to save the Clover Kingdom
and return the possessed
Magic Knights to normal.
However...
Poison Plant Magic:
Now, Zhovniir's Garden
of Lingering Burns.
But, that's...
[BOTH]
...the Village!
[NARRATOR] The pair soon
realized that their hometown
was under attack
by elven forces.
Stop!
Oh, no! Stay back!
[yells]
[LILY]
Asta. Yuno.
You're really brave, Nash!
Good job!
[BOTH]
Stay back. It's our turn now!
[DIGIT] So, you blocked
my attack. Nicely done.
You must be Magic Knights,
just like the previous
owner of this body was.
Let's see. What
will you do next?
Poison Plant Magic:
Zofnir's Breath.
And Zofnir's Fingers,
for good measure.
[DIGIT] I wonder,
will you succumb to poison
the way they did,
or will you be impaled?
Your choice.
[BOTH]
Not happening!
[yells]
Look at them now!
They're strong!
[HIGH PRIEST]
It's a miracle.
Those two were left at the
church on the same day.
They grew up in this village.
And then, the two of
them set off courageously
into the world,
with their aspirations
to become the Wizard King.
They've grown into
such capable young men,
and now they're here
to save Hage Village!
[CHILDREN crying]
Asta told me once.
If you don't give up,
you can achieve your dreams.
You can make everybody happy!
Yes.
They may have been
gone for a while,
but we've still kept
them in our hearts.
And we know they've
been working hard
toward their goal of
becoming Wizard King.
Thank you.
I knew we were right
about you, Yuno!
The pride and joy of Hage,
making it into
the Magic Knights!
Not that I'm surprised.
Yuno can do anything!
Yeah, anything!
Everyone in the village
will be so excited
when they hear.
And what does Asta's letter say?
Can you even make out
that terrible chicken
scratch of his?
[NASH] Yeah, he writes
like a five-year-old.
So does he say when
he's coming home?
When he does get here,
we'll have to cheer him up.
Even Asta will have a hard time
bouncing back from this.
Maybe a pop-potato party
will lift his spirits.
Actually, he says
that he got in.
[BOTH]
Huh?!
--[HORO] What?
--[ARLU] Huh?
They both passed.
[ALL but LILY]
What?!
[BOTH]
Seriously?
[LILY]
Mm-hm!
Oh, wow. You're not
kidding, are you?
Really! He did it. So, um.
I guess, then, Asta won't
be coming home, will he?
Right. We'll go let everyone
know about our Magic Knights.
This will be the best news
Hage Village has ever gotten.
Amazing!
He's gonna be a Magic Knight,
just like he said.
He did it!
[LILY] As time went on,
the occasional letters
from Asta and Yuno
became a special treat
that we all looked forward to.
[ASTA]
How's it goin', Sister Lily?
Is there anything
new goin' on with Nash
and the rest of the gang lately?
My first assignment as a member
of the Black Bulls
was to go boar-hunting.
But we ended up running
into this mysterious
bad guy who was super tough!"
[gasps]
You stand no chance of
prevailing against me.
Why not accept that and give up?
If I gave up now, then
who would protect them?
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[ASTA]
I realized something.
[HEATH]
Hm?
Sooner or later, I'm going
to be the Wizard King.
But it's not just
about keeping a promise.
It's about keeping people safe!
You ready, Asta?
Here we go.
All the magic power
I've got left!
Now, my Soul Ball.
[MAGNA] Flame Magic:
Prison Death Scattershot!
[MAGNA yells]
[HEATH] This is the final
spell of your pathetic life?
What a complete waste.
[HEATH]
Your time is up.
[ASTA]
You wish!
[HEATH]
That wasn't the real attack.
He's reflecting the spell.
[ASTA]
Not done yet!
As long as I can still
move, I'm not done!
No. You can't...!
Like hell!
[ASTA yells]
[ASTA] We managed to
win the battle somehow,
but we couldn't prevent
him from destroying himself
in the end, and we weren't able
to keep all the
villagers safe, either.
I can tell it's gonna be
a long road to becoming
the Wizard King,
but no matter how hard
things may get,
I'll never give up!
[NASH] Never giving up
is the one thing he's better
at than anybody else.
[ARLU]
Go get 'em, Asta!
[HORO]
Yeah, go!
"And one more thing.
Please, Sister Lily,
can we get married someday?
Asta."
He hasn't changed...
[NASH] I do wish he'd
give up on that, though.
[REKKA] Sister Lily, can
you read Yuno's letter now?
[ARLU, HORO]
Read it, read it!
Yuno!
I can read that one myself,
if you don't mind!
[HIGH PRIEST] Let's see here.
"Greetings, everyone.
I visited Magic Knights'
Headquarters the other day,
where I got to meet
the Wizard King.
Sincerely, Yuno."
[HORO, ARLU gasp]
So cool!
What's the letter
say after that?
[HIGH PRIEST] Er, it looks
like that's all of it.
[NASH] Yuno's letters are always
so short and to the point.
I've noticed that.
There's a lot more
detail in Asta's writing.
He says. "Me and Yuno
went to Headquarters
to give a report
about our mission."
[KLAUS]
No, is that really...?
I never dreamed you would
greet us personally, sir.
He's flashy. Who do
you think this guy is?
You idiot!
This is none other than
the current Wizard King:
Sir Julius Novachrono.
[yelps]
[YUNO gasps]
[YUNO]
It's actually him.
[ASTA]
The Wizard King!
[JULIUS]
Anyway, well done.
You did a marvelous
job out there.
Much appreciated.
[ASTA]
Uh, er, uh-- uh--
Jus-- Can I-- Can I-- Can I
maybe ask you something, sir?
Sure, what is it?
I was just wondering...
[BOTH] How can I become
the Wizard King?
[laughs] I see, so the
two of you are looking
to become the
Wizard King, are you?
Not surprising, given that
you are Magic Knights.
You two must realize
how rude it is
to ask a question
like that so directly.
Now, listen.
The Wizard King must
be noble of heart
and have the implicit
trust of all of his pe--
No, Klaus.
It's about results.
A noble heart alone
cannot protect anyone,
and the trust of the people
is earned, not granted.
You want to know
what you need to do
to gain the title
of Wizard King?
Get results. Prove that
you're the strongest.
Do what it takes.
Devote yourself
to getting results.
That's all there is.
Anyone who is not capable
of that cannot hope
to stand at the summit.
[BOTH]
Exactly what I wanted to hear.
[ASTA] "Devote yourself
to getting results."
The way he said it was simple,
but his words really
stuck with me.
I'm gonna get results
on top of results,
as much as I can!
[LILY]
Those two are working hard
in a completely different world.
A place those of us
in the Forsaken Realm
can't even imagine.
Hearing about
their accomplishments
always filled us with
so much courage and hope.
[LILY]
But then...
[ASTA]
Dear Hage Village,
I'm about to go explore
the Underwater Temple
at the bottom of the sea!
[LILY] We didn't know why,
but that was the last bit
of correspondence
we received from Asta
for quite some time.
[LILY] We told ourselves
"no news is good news,"
since that's what
the old adage says.
But after Asta's letters
stopped coming in,
we found ourselves
worrying about his safety
more and more.
[LILY] When a message
did eventually arrive,
we were shocked at what we saw.
It was pages and
pages long, almost like
he'd written down everything
that had ever happened
in his life.
[ASTA]
To everyone in the village.
I'm sorry I haven't written
to you in a long time.
Don't get me wrong,
I really wanted to!
I just couldn't.
[LILY] Asta told us the story
of a fierce battle against
the Eye of the Midnight Sun
in the Underwater Temple,
and explained that
both of his arms
had been rendered useless
by Curse Magic.
When he received an
examination, the doctor said
he would never write
a letter again,
much less hold a sword.
His fellow Black Bulls
learned about his predicament
and set off on a relentless
search for a cure.
Then, he wrote that he had gone
to the Forest of Witches,
where the Queen
cast a spell that
rid him of his curse.
[ASTA]
My magic is never giving up!
[LADROS] So you had this
big dramatic transformation.
Did you expect me to be
impressed by that or something?
[LADROS]
You're mine!
[yells]
[LADROS groans]
[LADROS yells]
[LADROS]
What... are... you?
How the hell is this happening?
I want you out of my sight!
[ASTA growls]
[ASTA growling]
It's not fair!
I stepped on so many people
to get to where I am now!
I can't lose to you!
[ASTA] You always kicked
your friends down,
but my friends helped
me be better. Stronger!
[ASTA]
Black Meteorite!
[LADROS screams]
[growls]
[LILY] Not long after that,
both Asta and Yuno wrote to us
about their excellent showing
at the Star Festival,
and how they'd won the approval
of those in the royal capital.
Hearing of their success made
our hearts glow with pride!
My, that certainly was an
exciting entrance, wasn't it?
Let's all applaud for
the rookie who's done
the most for the Black
Bulls this year. Asta!
Aw, shucks, thank you, guys!
[JULIUS] Yuno and Asta
are the top earners
among all of the novice Knights,
which means they're
two new stars to watch!
They've produced
outstanding results,
considering the fact
they've only been
Knights for half a year.
Interestingly,
these 16-year-olds
are childhood friends
from the same hometown.
For being so young,
those two are doing
marvelous things!
Yeah, they're probably nobility!
[SEKKE] Actually, they're
naught but commoners!
[CITIZENS gasp]
It's true ha, ha!
The scrawny guy
from the Black Bulls
doesn't even have any magic,
isn't that so sad?
[CITIZEN 70Y]
Commoners?
[CITIZEN 70Z]
Really?
[CITIZEN 70AA]
He can't use magic?
[CITIZEN 70II]
Makes you wonder if they really
earned those stars.
That's so rude!
What is the matter
with these people?
[YUNO]
Bell.
What is it, Yuno?
Let's show them.
Ah, ha! It'd be my pleasure.
[CITIZENS gasping, chattering]
Ooh!
Yuno, wait. What are
you about to do?
Asta, remember how
we used to train
back when we were little kids?
Yeah, but...
[ASTA grunts]
[CITIZENS yell]
Why do you always
have to pull crazy stuff
like this on me outta nowhere?
You're stronger now!
What, are you tryin' to kill me
during my 15 seconds
of fame, ya big jerk?
[YUNO] If that'd killed you,
we'd know what your limit was.
Good thing you survived.
[ASTA]
Why, you little!
[CITIZEN 70AA] Whoa, that
magic power was devastating.
[CITIZEN 70AB]
And he blocked it!
[SEKKE]
They're shah- ha ckingly strong!
I invite anyone who still
doubts their worthiness
to please step forward,
now that you've witnessed
their abilities.
Yes, it's true these
two are commoners,
but they've worked harder
than any of their peers
to make it where they are today.
Proud citizens of
the Clover Kingdom,
let us commend these
brave knights!
Regardless of rank or status,
our nation's path
to victory is to
join together as one!
[CITIZEN 70AC]
Wizard King.
[CITIZEN 70AD]
Commoners aren't so bad.
[CITIZEN 70AE]
Hear, hear!
This is no time to dwell
on our differences!
[CITIZEN 70AF]
We can all fight together!
Yuno.
Yeah.
Look at us.
We've really come this far.
[ASTA]
It's me again, guys!
Someday...
[YUNO]
[ASTA, YUNO]
I'll become the Wizard King!
Every time I cut it
down, it grows back!
If we keep going like this,
we'll never get anywhere!
[REKKA]
Father! Hang in there!
[CHILDREN sobbing]
Please don't die, okay?
[ASTA] Poison? The demon-slayer
sword can fix that!
Just like it did before, right?
[ASTA] Hey, Yuno! Can I
leave it to you for now?
[YUNO]
Yeah, I'm fine.
I can win this with
my eyes closed!
He's all yours then. I gotta
do somethin' real quick!
Hold on!
[REKKA]
Asta! Please help!
He protected us, and he
ended up getting hurt!
Here goes!
[LILY, NASH gasp]
Why didn't it work?
[ASTA] He's not under any
spell! This is bad news!
The magic's run its course,
and the poison's spread
through his body!
[HIGH PRIEST groans]
[ARLU]
I'm so scared!
[HIGH PRIEST]
I-I think this is the end.
You can't give up so soon!
Just stay with me!
It's all right.
[HIGH PRIEST] In the end, I got
to see you and Yuno again,
all grown up and strong.
That's enough for me.
I'll think of it as God's reward
for the deeds I've done.
Don't talk like that!
[HIGH PRIEST sputters]
Our little Asta. I'm so proud.
Take care of them for me.
[REKKA, ARLU, HORO]
Father!
[ASTA]
No.
Not yet.
You're not done yet!
You hear me?
Don't die. You can't die!
You were supposed
to stick around
for a while to watch over us.
To see me through!
To see all of us through!
[ASTA]
That sword. It's his!
I saw it back at the
Midnight Sun's hideout!
It must've slipped into
my grimoire somehow!
[ASTA]
Maybe if I use it, I can...!
[ASTA screams]
[HIGH PRIEST] It seems like
only yesterday I was changing
their diapers,
and now look at them!
You two boys will always
be my precious sons!
Black Clover , Page 103:
"Release from Misfortune."
I should be clear.
You're like sons to me.