[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[roars]
Man! It's huge!
We can't even hope to
defeat something that big.
[CHILDREN screaming]
[SISTER THERESA]
For now,
we need to get the
children out of here.
Go!
Get on his back, and he'll
take you to safety!
[BOY 33B]
Okay!
Amazing!
[GIRL 33A]
Wow!
[BOY 33B]
It's so warm!
[SISTER THERESA] It could
take half an hour or more
for us to get them all out.
We'll have to hold
our ground until then.
[ASTA] I'm not letting
you get any closer!
Die! Die!
All of you.
[growls]
You aren't yourself anymore.
What did she do to you?
[roars]
You know me. I'm your brother.
[roaring]
[gasps]
[NEIGE]
Why? Why would you save me?
You can't die.
Take responsibility
for what you did.
That's the punishment
you deserve!
[gasps]
Plus, your own brother
just tried to kill you,
and that's not cool. He's even
sicker than I thought he was!
My sword seems to
work fine on you,
so I'll just cut
ya down to size--
[gasps]
Your Anti-Magic is the cutest,
but even it won't
take him down that easy.
You saw that dark magic tool.
It drains the lifeforce
from the subject
and makes 'em swell and
swell with magic power!
She's a special kinda crazy!
[ASTA grunts]
[yells]
It just grows right back!
[SALLY giggles] I've got a
little present for you, Asta.
Here!
[gasps]
[ASTA]
Sister?
Aw! You interrupted us again!
That's starting to get annoying.
I don't have time
for crusty old ladies
and their feeble magic power.
You'd better watch
your tone with me,
little whippersnapper.
It's true that
our bodies produce
less magic power as we age.
But no matter how old you are,
you can always increase
your ability to work
with natural mana.
When it comes to
technique, I'm a master.
Your youth has nothing
on my experience.
Try me! You'll see
what I can do!
Jeez, you're loud.
You should try not
to get so worked up.
You'll keel over and die
if you're not more careful.
I'm not going to lose
to a mouthy brat.
[roars]
[SISTER THERESA] I'm doing
my best, but I can't fight
as well as I'd like to while
covering the children's escape.
This is going to
go downhill, fast.
Damn Gauche, running away
like the selfish idiot
he's always been.
[MARIE]
We have to help them, brother!
No! I'm taking you
back to the village.
[MARIE]
Please! It's not too late.
Turn around!
My magic is useless
against that woman,
and now with that mud monster
she's got backing her up,
it would be an
even riskier fight.
I'm not going to put you
in that kind of danger!
What about the others?
[GAUCHE]
As long as you're safe,
I don't give a damn about them.
[GAUCHE] That's right.
No one else matters.
[GUEST OF HONOR 33A]
The renowned House Adlai.
They're the envy of
all other noble families.
[HANGER-ON 33A]
Little Gauche is so intelligent.
Just like his father.
[HANGER-ON 33B] And Marie
takes after her mother.
Look how beautiful she is!
[GUEST OF HONOR 33A] Do you have
a moment to talk business?
I believe you said something
about wanting to invest?
[GAUCHE]
What?
Mother and Father can't
be dead--that's impossible!
[GUEST OF HONOR 33A]
It's true, I'm afraid.
They were attacked by bandits
on their way home
from my office.
You won't have to worry
about any of the pesky
financial details,
though, since they left
everything they had to me.
And he does mean everything.
You're lying!
[gasps] It was you who--
That's enough!
[HANGER-ON 33A]
That look! Such insolence.
[HANGER-ON 33B]
Who could love a brat like that?
Get out of my house.
Brother.
You'll be okay, Marie. I'm here.
I promise I'll protect you.
No matter what it takes!
That's what I said!
[MERCHANT 33A]
Ah!
You again? Get back here!
[GAUCHE]
I'll steal anything for Marie!
Is it good?
[MARIE]
Mm-hm! [giggles]
[GAUCHE] That's all I need.
To see Marie smile.
[whimpers]
[GAUCHE]
Give me all your money.
Careful, I'm a noble, you know!
As a noble, isn't it your duty
to help people in need, like me?
[NOBLE 33A whimpers]
[GAUCHE]
Only Marie matters.
[SECURITY CHIEF 33A]
Stop right there!
We're arresting you for crimes
against the kingdom.
[GAUCHE growls]
Go right ahead.
I'd like to see you try!
Please! You insolent street rat.
[GAUCHE]
Marie.
I've never cared
about anyone else,
and I won't start now.
[yells]
[GAUCHE groans]
You're the meanest,
most uncool big brother ever.
I hate you!
[gasps]
I know it hasn't been easy,
and there've been
people who've done
really awful things to us,
but Sister Theresa
and the church kids
are different.
The only reason I don't get
lonely when you're gone
is because I've got them.
They're my friends!
Isn't that why you joined
the Magic Knights--
so you wouldn't be alone?
People's lives are
all connected, you know?
Everybody has to have friends.
They're what make us who
we are. Don't you see?
[SISTER THERESA, ASTA yelling]
[MARIE]
Besides,
Magic Knights are supposed
to keep people safe, right?
I was so proud when I found that
you were going to
become a Magic Knight,
and I want to keep
being proud of you.
Please, brother.
[GAUCHE]
Marie.
[MARCO]
Hey! Over here!
[MARIE gasps]
It's Marco!
I was worried about you!
I'm glad you're okay.
I was real scared,
but then Sister
and Asta showed up.
I knew they would
come to rescue us!
Hey, kid! Where'd you get
that robe you're wearing?
It's Asta's.
He let me borrow it!
I was afraid of being alone
while he and Sister
came here to save
the other kids.
But he told me it's full
of Magic Knight courage.
I'm sure I'll be safe enough
if I wait out here with Marco.
You go back and help the others.
Don't worry I won't let
anything bad happen to Marie!
[GAUCHE] You better not,
you sad excuse for a bodyguard.
Or something equally bad will
happen to you, I promise.
[MARCO]
Um...
[MARIE]
Big brother!
[BOY 33C]
Oh!
Marco!
Marie!
[MARIE]
You're here!
I'm glad you're okay!
Sister got us out using
her awesome flame magic.
She and Asta are still
back there fighting,
but the monster's really strong!
It's fine, you'll see!
My big brother's gonna
go and help them.
He and Asta are in the
same Magic Knight squad,
so they have to stick together.
[CHILDREN]
Wow.
[GIRL 33B]
The same as Asta?
[GIRL 33C]
Then he must be super strong!
[MARIE]
Yeah!
Marie, you better keep
yourself well hidden.
Right!
[MARIE]
Big brother.
[CHILDREN]
Good luck!
[GAUCHE]
Asta this, Asta that...
What's so great
about him, anyway?
The captain, the other
squad members,
they're all crazy
about this kid.
But he was basically
useless back there.
He and the old hag
have probably given up
and made a run for it by now.
When you get down to it,
people will always put
themselves ahead of others.
That's just the way
the world works.
[gasps]
[yelling]
[panting, coughing]
No. Not yet. I'm not done!
[GAUCHE gasps]
You don't know
when to quit, huh?
Just forget about
protecting them
and let me capture you already.
We'll have so much fun!
[ASTA]
Forget about protecting them?
No way. Never. Not a chance!
You would have to kill me first!
[GAUCHE]
Is he insane? Or just an idiot?
[ASTA]
Forget about protecting them?
No way. Never. Not a chance!
You would have to kill me first!
[roars]
Which isn't gonna happen,
because there's
no way I'm gonna die
before I become the Wizard King!
Quick, Asta! On your right!
[ASTA]
Crap!
[yelps]
You know, for someone who was
going on and on about
not dying today,
it sure did look like
you were about to.
Gauche, you came back!
Why'd you run away in
the first place, you jerk?
--[GAUCHE] Shut it!
--[ASTA screams]
I wasn't running away.
I just needed to get
Marie to safety.
So, the idiot decided to
come back and help after all.
[GAUCHE]
I'll take you on myself!
No, you can't!
Been there, tried that.
It didn't work!
I'll fight the best that I can.
So Marie will love me.
And then she'll be proud
of her big brother again!
[BOTH]
Go, Real Double!
[GAUCHES]
Double Refrain!
Oh, man, that's so cool!
[gasps]
[GAUCHE]
Any time we cut part of it off,
more magic pours in
and repairs the damage.
Pretty frustrating, huh?
[GAUCHE] I haven't even
scratched that woman.
This is my worst pairing
since the captain.
Should I play my trump card?
No. No matter how strong
my Mirror Magic becomes,
it won't work.
Gauche, are you okay?
[BARO growls]
[GAUCHE] Damn. This isn't
how I wanted to die.
[ASTA yells]
Why'd you go after it
alone like that?
We're supposed to be
in this together!
We're squadmates and
friends, aren't we?
And that means, when we fight,
I protect you and
you protect me.
Then nobody can take
either of us down!
That's what I call
a foolproof strategy!
[ASTA laughs]
[GAUCHE] That's what I call
a sloppy strategy.
He really is an idiot.
Although...
I knew someone else
who fought sloppy.
[GAUCHE panting]
So, you still wanna fight?
'Cause I can tell ya right now,
you're done running.
But my sister. She's waiting.
[YAMI]
Oh, really?
Well, if she's that
important to you,
come and join my squad.
Pay's pretty decent.
You want me to join
a Magic Knight squad?
But I'm an escaped criminal!
--[YAMI] And?
--[gasps]
[GAUCHE]
A-And, I don't trust people.
And I'm a thief, and the only
thing I care about is my sister.
[YAMI]
Fine.
[gasps]
[YAMI]
I won't stop you.
Protect whatever you
think needs protecting.
Keep doing that, and it'll
help someone someday.
[GAUCHE]
Captain.
Did you know this would
happen eventually?
[ASTA yells]
Hey, Sister, how's the
escape plan going?
Not many left now.
[roars]
[GAUCHE]
I have no choice.
[gasps]
I don't get why, but Marie would
be heartbroken if you died.
So I'll protect you.
Is this boy really Gauche?
Don't act like you're
doin' me a favor, here.
We're friends. Helping
each other is what we do.
Hey, watch the attitude.
As your senior squad member,
I will be treated with respect.
Hold on. What's happening?
Not sure.
[yelps]
It's... like that
time in the dungeon.
[roars]
[yells]
Yeah!
[gasps]
[roars, groans]
[groaning]
Huh?! That doesn't
hurt it, either?
[laughs] Cool! What was that?
Some kind of flying
Anti-Magic slash thing?
How did you do it?
Tell me, tell me!
[GAUCHE] If we're going
to defeat this thing,
we need to hit it hard
all at once,
faster than it can regenerate.
Our best bet would probably
be Asta's slash attack, but even
that doesn't hit fast enough.
[GAUCHE gasps]
[GAUCHE] What if... I use my
magic on someone else?
[NARRATOR]
Gauche, who had spent his life
distrusting others and always
preferred to work alone,
had never before
imagined using his magic
to support somebody else.
But from his desperation
to win back Marie's love,
his grudging acceptance
of Asta came forth.
A fundamentally similar,
yet entirely different spell,
inscribed on a new page
in his grimoire,
and not a moment too soon.
[GAUCHE]
Good!
But I don't have enough
magic power to cast this.
Hey, old hag!
Buy me some time
to renew my mana.
--Please!
--[gasps] You cad.
Ordering an old lady
around like that.
I won't be able to hold out for
very long, so make it snappy!
You've used up
all the good stuff,
and what's left just
isn't gonna cut it.
It's your turn to play, Asta.
Do your slash thing again!
[ASTA] Yeah, trust me.
I would if I could.
Aw! Party pooper.
Man.
[GAUCHE]
I've kept it hidden,
but using it now may be
our only way out of this.
[GAUCHE]
Asta!
What's up?
[GAUCHE]
Look at me!
My left eye has been replaced
with a Mirror Magic tool.
I'll use the power stored
inside to cast my new spell.
Mirror Magic: Mirage Brigade!
[ASTAS yelling]
Go!
[ASTAS]
Mirror Slash!
Not yet! Not yet! Not yet!
[gasps]
[ASTA]
I'm not done!
[BARO groans]
[SALLY yelps]
[laughs]
[BOTH]
We did it!
[SISTER THERESA] Incredible.
They combined their magics?
Whatever they did, it looks
like they were finally
able to drain the power
out of that creature.
Goodbye, brother.
[sobbing]
[BARO]
Jeez, you're such a crybaby.
How much longer are you gonna
keep up the waterworks?
Here, I guess you can have this.
[NEIGE gasps]
Thanks, brother Baro!
I swear.
I'll hate her forever for
turning you into that monster.
And me?
How can I forgive myself
for blindly following you
and doing whatever
you ordered me to do,
no matter how awful it was?
What you said before was right.
I have to take responsibility
for the things I've done.
I'll do it.
I will atone for my sins,
and for my brother's, too.
Good, and once you get
that outta the way,
you and I should be friends.
With all the cool
magic you can do,
I bet you're gonna be
a pretty popular guy.
Huh?
That would be...
[gasps]
It's that bright light again!
[GAUCHE]
So much... magic power...
I've never felt anything
this huge bef--
[GAUCHE]
I didn't see anything.
What happened?
[SISTER THERESA]
Another one?
Haven't they done
enough damage already?
Asta!
[gasps]
No! Old hag!
[ASTA]
Sister!
[LICHT]
You have injured my compatriot.
It's only fair that
I return the favor.
It's him! The guy we saw
at the group's hideout!
I haven't introduced
myself yet, have I?
I am the leader of the
Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Call me Licht.
[ASTA]
No. No way.
[ASTA] Just like Yuno's.
A four-leaf clover grimoire!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[GAUCHE]
"Marie's in Danger."
And-a one, two, three.
How to say "no" to an angel!
As much as I like
to spoil Marie,
I must sometimes harden my heart
and decline her requests,
no matter how angelically
she makes them.
Like so:
Hey, big brother,
please go back to
help Sister and Asta!
[GAUCHE]
No. You'd be in danger if I did.
Hey, big brother!
I want some rice gratin
with hot, melty cheese.
[GAUCHE] No! Your tongue
would be in danger.
It would get burned.
Hey, big brother,
can we stay out here
in the sun all day?
[GAUCHE]
No! Your skin will be in danger
if you stay out in
full sun too long!
UV rays are a mighty foe!
Hey, big brother, show me
a super cool spell!
No! Wait, yes!
[GAUCHE]
Marie, look at me.
Mirage Brigade!
[MARIES]
Big brother, you're awesome!
[GAUCHE]
Uh-oh. Now I'm in danger!
[MARIES]
Hey, big brother?
Big brother? Big brother?
Big brother?
[ASTA] This guy was in the Eye
of the Midnight Sun's hideout!
You attacked the Clover Kingdom,
and Captain Fuegoleon!
You won't get away with it!
Black Clover , Page 34:
"Light Magic vs. Dark Magic."
Whoa! Captain Yami!