[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] Every year,
the Wizard King awards
stars to Magic Knight squads
for their performance,
with each team vying
to earn the most.
The squads' achievements,
along with the total number
of stars they've collected
during that year,
are announced to the public
at an annual event known
as the Star Festival.
However, during what
should've been
a peaceful, celebratory evening,
Captain Yami and
Captain Jack were locked
in a dramatic confrontation.
the pretense of which
was entirely trivial.
Now let's see here.
[NARRATOR]
After their battle reached
an unexpected conclusion,
the two captains
and their squad members
made their way back
to the Star Festival grounds.
Huh?
[ADMIRER 68A]
She's so beautiful!
[ADMIRER 68B]
Look at her!
[ADMIRER 68C]
She must come from money.
[ADMIRER 68A] Hey, why don't
you go talk to her?
[ADMIRER 68B]
Oh, no way, I can't!
[ASTA]
They're right, she is pretty.
I betcha Finral would go crazy!
[gasps]
[BALMAIN]
Oh, my, my.
Quite fetching indeed! Yes.
I choose this one to accompany
me for the evening!
[CITIZEN 69A] That's Baron
Balmain of House Bamilton!
Come along now,
you pretty thing,
and we shall enjoy
all the luxuriations
the Festival has to offer.
[BALMAIN] Hm... Playing
hard to get, are we?
That's precious, but I
won't stand for it!
You must not have any idea
who I am, do you, dear?
Hey!
[BALMAIN, MEN groan]
[CHARLOTTE]
That's enough.
Oh, hey, why don't
you put this on?
It's a festival, so we might
as well dress up! Uh-oh.
[CHARLOTTE]
Who exactly do you think I am?
[ALL gasping]
I know that magic!
She's the Blue Rose
Knights' captain!
Uh, Char, whatcha doin' there?
Call me "Captain," Sol.
Okay, Char!
[BALMAIN groaning]
"Come along," you said.
Were you intending to use me
as some sort of arm decoration?
And it came as a command,
not a request.
[BALMAIN groaning]
[CHARLOTTE]
House Bamilton, ha!
I hail from the House Roselei!
Did you approach so boldly
just because I am a woman?
You are not superior to me.
Not in the slightest.
--[BALMAIN groaning]
--[CROWD gasping]
That jerk.
I still can't figure out
where he ended up.
Yeah, and whose fault
is that, Noelle?
I can't believe how many
people there are here!
You can hold my hand
so you don't get lost.
--[NOELLE] What?
--[CROWD murmuring]
[gasps]
[CHARLOTTE]
Well then?
Why aren't you using your
magic to dispel my briars?
Oh yeah!
That's our amazing
leader Char for ya!
Call me "Captain," Sol.
You got it, Char!
Wait, no, somebody stop her!
She's gonna kill him!
What happened? Did you see him?
Nah, just some drunk
guy dancing naked.
It's not fit for royal eyes.
[NOELLE]
Hey, wait a minute!
Uh, hi there.
I know you. The runt!
From the other ceremony!
[ASTA]
Who you callin' a runt?!
[SOL]
Sorry, but that's what you are.
Fine, then you're
some kinda giant!
Huh? The little bug
is talking like he
wants to get squished.
Please don't hurt me!
[ASTA yells]
Whatever, back to Char!
Call me "Captain"!
[SOL]
Got it, Char!
Anyway, I found you
a super fabulous dress!
I don't see what's wrong
with the one I'm wearing.
[SOL]
It'll look great on you!
--Come on! In here!
--[CHARLOTTE] Wait. Sol!
I really don't need it.
Aw, don't be such a stiff!
Wow!
Your skin is so pale
and beautiful, Char!
It's as smooth as marble, too!
[CHARLOTTE]
Would you stop that?
Ah, hoo-hoo!
Alcohol always tastes better
when you drink it at a festival!
Yeah! There's something
special 'bout the food, too.
You can't get that
flavor anywhere else!
Yikes, there're way
too many people here!
Hey, that's pretty good!
How I miss Marie.
Why is this apple extra yummy?
'Cause we're at a festival?
Oh! Or maybe it's
'cause I'm with you!
Festivals always get
me way fired up!
I'm feelin' real manly now!
I know, right?
Wanna spar with me a little bit?
Thanks, but no thanks!
[GORDON mumbling]
Enjoying a deviation
from our normal routine
is a great opportunity
to strengthen our already
rock-solid friendship.
It's a page of priceless
memories in the book of my life.
[FINRAL grumbles]
I keep striking out!
Man, I must be off my game! Huh?
Ah! I smell exquisite
beauty nearby!
Gotta go!
How rude.
There's plenty of beauty
right over here!
He's sure got some nerve!
Anyway, I wonder what
could be taking
Captain Yami so long.
[FINRAL]
Woo-hoo!
[SOL]
You look so pretty!
I mean, you're always
gorgeous in your helmet, too,
but this is something else!
She's divine! Oh, fate!
Thank you for blessing me!
I'm in the presence of
an angel, no, a goddess!
Whoa she's really beautiful!
Compose yourselves at once!
This is not a show!
[CROWD]
Huh?
Only the Blue Rose
Knights are allowed
to get all goo-goo-eyed
over Char's beauty,
you understand me?
[CROWD]
What?
[CHARLOTTE]
That's hardly the issue.
I just can't risk letting
the other captains
see me looking like this!
Especially him.
[YAMI]
What's all the racket over here?
You must be partyin' hard, eh?
Uh--
Good to see you're
still with us, kid!
[laughs]
Hey, don't laugh about that.
I coulda been
seriously hurt, ya know!
What? Don't be such a baby.
It's not like it killed ya.
[gasps]
[CHARLOTTE]
Oh, no, Yami's here!
Why is it him, of all people?
Ah! You're like,
stupid hot, Char!
[CHARLOTTE]
No.
I can't lose my composure
in front of Sol.
Calm down, Charlotte.
Don't panic.
Besides, in this outfit,
he may not even recognize me.
Huh? Princess Prickly?
[yelps]
[laughs] What's with that getup?
You look like a damn doll!
[CHARLOTTE]
Deep breaths.
You mustn't let him get to you!
Forget my clothing.
Take a look at yours.
[CHARLOTTE] Mostly the bottom
half. Are those undergarments?
Well! If it isn't the
shabbiest, stinkiest man
of the whole disgusting bunch!
The captain of the Black Bulls!
Jeez, what's she so
worked up about?
Think your squad might
need a talkin' to.
--Rosie?
--[SOL] Shut up!
And keep your hairy
naked man-legs
away from our captain!
Sol. That's quite enough.
[laughs] Good,
I finally found you!
What are you up to, Captain?
Let's go get a drink, shall we?
[meows]
Oh. Vanessa.
[VANESSA]
Who is this woman?
And why do I suddenly feel like
I have to defeat her
at all costs?
[hisses]
You don't like the
Blue Rose captain?
[gasps]
[CHARLOTTE]
Who is she?
Yami seems to be rather
chummy with her.
Is she a member
of the Black Bulls?
I'm so jealous!
A lousy Black Bull
like you has no right
to glare at our
illustrious leader!
What? I wasn't glaring and
I'm certainly not lousy!
[SOL] You and your pals wouldn't
stand a chance against her!
Never in a million,
billion years!
[laughs]
Hey, nice insult. Real original.
[VANESSA] I can't take
this kind of harassment
from a Blue Rose! That's it.
I need to find a way to
defend the captain's honor!
Enough chit-chat!
Time for us to duel!
[CROWD cheers]
That's absurd.
The ceremony is
about to begin, Sol.
Stay focused.
Say what?!
Char's gonna destroy
you for sure!
We accept your challenge!
Good luck, you two!
So, what'll it be then?
I should say,
I'm stronger now than
I've ever been before,
so I won't go down easily.
[meows]
You fool.
If you knew me,
you would realize
how preposterous you sound.
I am the captain of
the Blue Rose Knights.
Uh, Captain?
This is about to get really bad!
Shouldn't we stop 'em?
No.
[FINRAL] Now, now, ladies,
if I could just interject here.
We're at a festival,
so let's settle this amicably--
Of course a man would say that!
The only thing you could win
is a flirting contest!
[FINRAL]
Ouch.
In that case, let me
offer you a suggestion!
The perfect battle
for two beauties
on such a festive evening:
a dress up showdown!
[CROWD cheers]
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
What's wrong?
Are you scared
you're gonna lose?
Of course she's not!
You could put Char in a burlap
sack and she'd still rock it!
[gasps]
[CROWD cheering]
It sounds like they're
all having a good time.
Well, good for them.
They don't appear to be causing
any trouble, so it's fine.
Let's make our way
to the ceremony.
We mustn't be late.
I agree.
It's a big night,
so I'm a little nervous!
There's no need for
us to be nervous.
We're sure to take the top spot.
Right.
But the Black Bulls
have been doing
such a great job lately,
I'm kind of worried
they'll surprise us.
Indeed, they may
have improved a bit.
No, they definitely have.
Asta in particular has done
incredible things this year.
It can't be, that's impossible!
They are the Black
Bulls, after all!
They've always been
clowns and ruffians!
The Golden Dawn need not
concern ourselves with them!
Right, Yuno?
You're asking if I
think we'll be outdone
by the Black Bulls,
the lowest of the low?
Not a chance.
[CROWD cheering]
First up:
It's the lovely captain
of the Blue Rose Knights,
Charlotte Roselei! And
she'll be dressed up as...
[FINRAL]
Ooh, a sexy witch!
I'm spellbound! Yahoo!
I knew if we copied
that loser's outfit,
it would be obvious
how much more elegant
and classy Char is!
The choice is crystal clear!
Char's the winner, hands down!
Ha, naturally.
I could never lose
to a weakling like her.
And call me "Captain."
[CHARLOTTE]
Agh, I hate this!
Why do I have to wear
these humiliating clothes?
Please, Yami, avert your eyes!
Although, since he's here,
he might as well look.
If I resemble that woman
who's so friendly with him,
perhaps he'll be
inclined to become
that friendly with me as well.
But it's embarrassing!
Don't look! Please,
I can't bear it!
That Blue Rose lady
looks pretty good
as a witch, doesn't she?
Yeah, not half bad.
Be still, my heart!
Next up, let's hear it for
the Black Bulls member,
Vanessa Enoteca!
And her costume is...
Oh, my, I wasn't
expecting a nun!
Talk about a blessing!
[VANESSA] She doesn't know
the first thing about men.
They love to have their
expectations turned upside-down!
This modest look
is a complete 180
for a gal who tends
to let it all hang out!
I pray that you all will lead
safe and fulfilling lives.
Whoa, check her out!
I've never seen Vanessa
look this good!
She cleans up nice.
[FINRAL] Okay, fellas,
now send your magic power
to the lovely lady
of your choosing!
Obviously, the winner needs
to be Charlotte the witch!
No way, the nun's hotter!
[FESTIVALGOER 69C] This is
the toughest choice ever!
And, polls are closed!
Let's see. Which one
of them got more love?
It's too close to call it!
Looks like we have a tie!
[CROWD cheers]
Aw, c'mon!
Hmph. It doesn't make
a difference to me.
[CHARLOTTE]
All that, just to tie?
I've shamed House
Roselei! Still.
I wonder what Yami thought
about the whole thing.
Perhaps he sees me
differently now.
If that's true, I would
consider this ordeal
to have been worthwhile.
Yeah right--as if
Char would ever tie!
Let's settle this for real!
U-Uh...
I'm ready when you are!
Okay, then our next battle
will be a swimsuit competition!
Feel free to change
on stage if you don't mind--
Tying me up, huh? I mean, sorry!
Anyone who agrees with him
will meet the same fate.
[CROWD gasps]
[FESTIVAL VENDOR 69A]
Step right up, folks,
and quench your thirst with
a Clover Premium Select!
It's a rich and mellow brew
with a hint of fruity flavor,
made right here
in Clover Kingdom
with only the
finest ingredients!
[VANESSA gasps]
Uh, Captain Yami?
You like a girl who knows
how to drink, right?
[gasps]
Huh? Where'd that come from?
Yeah. So we can drink together.
It's good bonding. But why?
[CHARLOTTE]
Oh. I see!
[VANESSA]
This one's in the bag.
I challenge you to
a drinking contest!
Spare me.
Your silly games are
getting old. I'm done.
It's almost time
for the star ceremony.
Don't worry, Char,
I've got you all set up
and taken care of over here.
Now give that catty witch
a taste of her own medicine
and drink her under the table!
These are the rules!
Whoever can consume
the most beer
in the next hour
will be victorious!
We'll be drinking
Clover Premium Select.
It's a local treasure!
However, there's no chugging!
It's just not a good look.
And it's polite to the brewer
to drink slowly and taste it!
[CHARLOTTE]
How is this happening?
And now, let the drinking begin!
[CROWD cheers]
That's it, Char,
show her who's boss!
I don't really know
what's goin' on,
but I'm rootin'
for ya, Vanessa!
[CHARLOTTE]
She definitely knows
how to hold her alcohol.
This won't be an
easy fight for me.
--Ah. You've got your work
--[CHARLOTTE] What?!
cut out for ya now,
Little Miss Man-Hater.
[CHARLOTTE]
Oh my, it seems she's already
three sheets to the wind!
The nerve, challenging
me in that state!
I can keep knockin' these
things back for days!
[CHARLOTTE]
That's it!
[groans]
Whoa! Strong stuff!
No, she's just a lightweight!
Aw, but she's so adorable
when she's all tipsy!
[VANESSA chuckling]
What the hell are
these broads doing?
[CHARLOTTE] I'm fighting an
impossible battle just for Yami.
There must be something
wrong with me!
[WOMAN] A curse. A curse
on House Roselei!
On your daughter's
18th birthday,
a terrible magic
will be awakened,
and you'll be
helpless to stop it!
It will swallow up
every one of you,
and entrap you within
a cage of time!
Oh.
Charlotte, what a
dreadful thing this is!
[CHARLOTTE'S MOTHER]
If only we knew a way
to lift this unspeakable curse!
Please don't cry,
Mother, Father.
I'll just... get strong,
really strong!
And then someday,
I can break it myself!
[CITIZEN 69B]
She's had another fine showing.
[CITIZEN 69C]
Yeah, she may be a newcomer,
but she's obviously
really powerful!
[CITIZEN 69D] Not to mention
drop-dead gorgeous.
[CITIZEN 69E]
Miss Charlotte.
I'd be honored to
make you my bride.
[CITIZEN 69F]
No, marry me instead, please!
[CITIZENS yelping]
Anyone who can't defeat me
cannot hope to handle my curse.
[CITIZENS grunt, yelp]
[CHARLOTTE] Every man is the
same, all bark and no bite.
The only person who
can rescue me is me.
[CITIZEN 69G]
What the hell?
[CITIZEN 69H]
It's the curse on House Roselei!
[CITIZEN 69J groans]
There's no hope.
It's too strong!
[BOTH yelp, scream]
[CHARLOTTE] I can't stop it!
At this rate, the village...
[CHARLOTTE] Damn it!
So pitiful, so shameful!
[CHARLOTTE]
Forgive me. Father. Mother.
[thudding]
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
You really made a
mess of things, huh?
Made me spill the pasta I was
eatin' all over the place.
[CHARLOTTE]
Yami Sukehiro!
How could I let him see
me in this sorry state?
I am defeated.
[YAMI] I'm not a fan of
chicks who prance into battle
actin' all smug when they
have no reason to be.
I prefer women who are strong.
[gasps]
[YAMI]
But you can lean on someone else
every once in a while.
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
You know how you can find lots
of other strong
people to lean on?
By joinin' the Magic Knights.
[CHARLOTTE]
Having my heart stolen by a man.
That was the secret
to ending my curse.
[YAMI]
Hey, it went away. Lucky break.
[CHARLOTTE]
And of all the men in the world,
it had to be this
stubborn brute.
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
You don't drink, right?
Didn't I tell you
a long time ago
it's not good to force yourself?
[CHARLOTTE] Sharing mugs
is practically kissing!
[FINRAL]
The contest is a draw!
Aw! Good job, Char!
Even if it was just a tie!
Yeah, and you did
great, too, Vanessa!
Well, that sure turned out to be
a whole lotta
nothin', didn't it?
[FESTIVALGOER 69D]
The Star Ceremony's
getting ready to start!
[FESTIVALGOER 69E] All the
captains are going to be there!
[FESTIVALGOER 69AA]
Even the new captains
of the Crimson Lion Kings
and the Purple Orcas!
I wonder what they're like!
Uh... All of 'em? Uh-oh.
Dammit, we're late.
Eh, they'll wait for me.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[SOL]
"The Seven Faces of Charlotte"!
That witch's costume
is just not enough!
I wanna see Char in all
kinds of cute outfits now!
First up: Sister Charlotte!
[SOL]
Wow, that just saved my soul!
[FINRAL]
Number two: Bride Charlotte!
Oh, yeah, till death do us part!
[FINRAL] Number three
is Samurai Charlotte!
Cut me to bits!
[FINRAL]
Number four:
Meet Professor Charlotte.
Instruct me in the ways of love!
Number five is
Policewoman Charlotte!
[SOL]
Go on, cuff me!
[FINRAL]
Costume six: Ninja Charlotte!
Ooh, sneak up on me anytime!
[CHARLOTTE] I don't have
time for this. Poof!
[YUNO]
I thought there were seven.
[GORDON mumbling]
It's finally time to reveal
the Magic Knight standings!
Black Bulls may have
a decent chance this year.
I know because I've been
watching my friends
without blinking, from
a very close distance.
Black Clover , Page 70:
"Two New Stars."
We'll be friends forever.