[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward
and took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] Yami and Asta were
locked in a desperate battle
against Licht, their
defeat all but certain.
Take your last breath,
Yami Sukehiro.
Engaging Light Magic:
Ray of Divine Punishment.
And we're dead.
[NARRATOR] But then,
some unexpected help arrived.
He came back?
Go Mirror Magic:
Full Reflection!
[NARRATOR] Gauche's spell
reflected Licht's attack
back at its caster,
saving the Magic Knights.
Your magic might be
fast and powerful.
But Mirror will
always reflect Light.
[NARRATOR] It was a
close call, but the leader
of the Eye of the Midnight Sun
was finally defeated.
[panting]
Wow. Nice save.
Good one, Gauche.
[ASTA gasps]
Whoa! No way!
Hey, you guys,
what just happened?
How are we all still alive?
My Mirror Magic
reflected his attack.
I didn't see it
hit the smug bastard,
but there's no way
he could've dodged it.
[laughing]
Glad ya dragged your
scrawny butt back
and that you brought
a fancy new spell with ya.
--[laughing]
--Captain.
You made me who I am today.
Thank you. I owe you everything.
[YAMI laughs]
Ooh. Is that so?
Then I get all the credit for
beatin' the light mage, right?
[ASTA] What kinda
sense does that make?
Gauche did everything
while you just stood there!
--Shut it.
--[ASTA yelping]
[YAMI] So you think
since you beat Skinnybones
you can just say whatever
you want now, huh?
Hey, the important thing is
that everybody did his best.
There's no need for violence.
[YAMI, GAUCHE]
Oh, yeah? What'd you do?
[FINRAL] Excuse me?
It was my Spatial Magic
that made it all possible!
No one cares. Now,
send me back to Marie.
[FINRAL] All right, I've
had it. I am your superior!
Well, my angel,
your big brother did it.
And soon, you'll be in my arms,
hugging me tight, Sweet Marie!
Well? Let's go.
I am your superior.
Well, anyway. I told you I only
had one more spell in me.
Nobody's leaving this cave
until my magic recovers.
--[BOTH] Tch.
--[FINRAL] Don't you "tch" me?
Marie should never
be kept waiting.
Here I thought he couldn't
get any more useless.
Now you're just being mean.
[ASTA groaning]
[YAMI] So much for
that super powerful
spell of yours, Lineface.
Guess your magic has
more than one natural enemy.
Nice try, though.
[LICHT grunts]
I'm sorry. I should
never have hurt you.
Me? What're you talking about?
[YAMI] Oh, didn't know
you guys were friends
or I wouldn'ta beat him up.
Of course I'm not friends
with this monster.
One day, you'll understand.
Huh?
[YAMI] I don't think
I'll ever understand you
and your little
minions, but we'll be
haulin' you back
to Headquarters anyway.
You can tell us all about
the Eye of the Midnight Sun
when we get there.
At last, the King of
Overly Serious People
has been avenged.
May he rest in peace now.
But he's not dead yet, sir!
Do we have to worry about
every little detail? Jeez!
[ASTA]
"Little detail"?
Okay, now, let's see here.
I've got a Binding
spell somewhere.
Just gotta find it.
Right, here it is.
Go, Dark Restraints.
[NOELLE] We should have gotten
some reinforcements by now!
Where is everybody?
Hm-ha! Well, Miss Black Bull,
I'm happy to report that
I informed your captain
about the situation ages ago.
You went to the hideout?
It was positively awful.
He wouldn't listen
to a word I said.
Okay, so what did
Captain Yami do?
[SEKKE] Probably headed out
soon after that. Ha, ha!
What? But where did he go?
He hasn't shown up here!
[SEKKE]
Ha, huh?
Luca. Marco.
--[CHILDREN chatter]
--[NOELLE] Huh?
[NOELLE, REBECCA gasp]
Phew, ha. Good thing
it's about shift change.
I've earned myself some rest.
[yawns]
The captain usually
wakes up around now,
and he'll be expecting a report.
"Why didn't you tell me sooner?
How about I tear you
in two? He-he!"
I'd much rather skip that part.
Captain Jack's a scary man.
[LITTLE GIRL 35A]
Mommy!
[FATHER 36A]
Oh, thank goodness!
I was so scared!
You're okay now, sweetie.
[LITTLE GIRL 35A]
Mm-hm! Don't worry!
--[sobbing]
--There, there.
Everything will be
all right now.
[NOELLE]
The village children!
They're back!
And no one looks hurt!
Some Magic Knights
came and saved us!
You're the one who told them
we needed help. Thank you!
Oh. Sure. It's the
Magic Knights' duty
to protect the
people, after all.
[NOELLE] And all I did
was call headquarters.
They went straight there
instead of stopping by
the village first. Why did
they leave me behind?
Sister Theresa helped, too.
You shoulda seen the
awesome spells she did!
And there was this mean guy
who got turned into mud.
It was really scary!
Where are Luca and Marco?
Did they not make it
back with you?
What about Asta and Gauche?
I don't see any other
Magic Knights for that matter!
[NOELLE gasps]
[ALL murmuring]
--[NOELLE] Asta!
--[REBECCA] Luca! Marco!
[BOTH]
Big sis!
[REBECCA]
Oh!
Thank goodness! You're back!
[MARCO]
I was so scared!
[REBECCA] What happened
to Sister Theresa?
Is she going to be okay?
Don't you worry about me, now.
I'll be on my feet in no time.
I've got at least another
100 years in me.
Thank you! I don't know
how we'll ever repay you
for bringing them back to us!
You're welcome, but I
certainly didn't do it alone.
Those boys were--
[coughs]
[NUN 31A]
Please, Sister, no more talking.
[NOELLE]
That robe.
Oh, it's Asta's,
but he let me borrow it.
He said, as long as I wore it,
I wouldn't be scared,
and he was totally right.
I had so much courage.
I didn't even cry!
Good job! I'm proud of you.
And Asta? He came back
with you, didn't he?
He stayed behind at the cave.
[NOELLE]
What?
He's still there.
The battle isn't over yet.
[coughs] Yes, another
one showed up.
[NUN 31A]
Sister!
Another one?
A mage named Licht.
The Eye of the
Midnight Sun's leader.
[gasps] And that's who
Asta's still fighting?
[NEIGE] He's there with a man
named Captain Yami, and--
[MARIE]
My brother went to help, too.
A man who uses
Spatial Magic took him.
I know they're gonna be fine.
There's nothing my
big brother can't do!
Yes, I'm sure you're right.
They'll be just fine.
All four of them are strong.
They'll come back after
they've defeated him.
[MARIE]
Mm!
[NOELLE]
Finral and Gauche, too.
If they were here in town,
they could've taken me to Asta.
I mean, not that
it's all about him.
I'm not worried about
Asta or anything.
Magic Knights should
stick together.
It's the principle of the thing.
[ALL]
Uh...
Let it go.
Okay, and... who are you?
[gasps]
[NEIGE] Well, um, i-it's
kind of a long story.
[yawns]
Can we get outta here already?
No. You'll have to wait
a little longer.
Like I said, it's
gonna take a while
for my magic power
to regenerate.
--[YAMI, GAUCHE] Tch.
--[FINRAL] Again with the "tch"!
[YAMI]
Tch, you like that. Tch. Tch.
--Don't let it get to you.
--[FINRAL] But it does!
Well, then, get me
back to Marie.
[FINRAL] Unlike someone,
I didn't get any extra magic.
Though, if we wait longer,
our reunion will be
that much more joyous.
Yes. Ha, ha.
That's certainly been
true in the past.
What's been true in the past?
I'm not talking to
you about anything
that pertains to Marie!
[ASTA]
What? Why not?
Anyone who approaches
Marie is my enemy!
[ASTA]
Seriously?!
[stomach rumbles]
[YAMI]
Ugh. I'm friggin starving here.
Can't you at least use a
portal to get us breakfast?
[FINRAL]
I'm not a delivery service.
Tch. Huh?
[GAUCHE]
Hm?
Is something wrong?
That's a lot of mana.
[LICHT]
Hm.
Who are they?
More enemies.
Spatial Magic!
But he's still
out cold. So, how?
[yawns]
Oh, man. Looks like something
didn't go as planned.
There was a hell of a battle,
and Licht and Valty
clearly weren't the
winners. [grunts]
Cleaning up this mess will
be a real pain, but still--
[yawns]
You gotta help out
your friends, right?
[RHYA]
Huh. That's a unique design.
Well, not that it matters.
[YAMI]
This guy moves fast, too.
[YAMI] Dark Magic:
Dark Cloaked Lightless Slash!
Ow! Jeez. Now, that's
literally a pain.
Well, whatever, I can
heal it up easily enough.
Light Magic:
Healing Light Particles.
The same spell.
This guy can heal, too.
Thank you for coming.
I'm sorry. My power alone
was not enough to defeat them.
You're hurt. Is it bad?
I'm fine. Better now
that you're here.
Yes, it will be all right.
Now, Flame Recovery Magic:
Phoenix Robe.
[ASTA, GAUCHE,
YAMI, FINRAL gasp]
I know you'll succeed
where I failed.
Thank you, my friends.
Hold on! I thought
this guy was their leader.
Ha.
[yawns] See, Licht?
Trying to do everything on
your own is way too much work.
You insects! Do you know
what we do to people
who harm our friends?
I'll show you.
When I'm finished,
your limbs will be torn
from your body like wings
plucked off of a butterfly.
I detest anybody who
hurts Licht. I hate them.
Right. So, who are
these people, exactly?
I'll introduce you.
These three are the strongest
members of the Midnight Sun.
They're the strongest?
[LICHT] Indeed. Their
power surpasses my own,
especially when
it comes to battle.
They are the Third Eye.
And they're more
powerful than you?
So... Third Eye, huh?
That's impossible.
Stronger than a Light mage?
He's got to be bluffing
about that, right?
[yawns] We wouldn't bother.
Bluffing's such a pain, y'know?
Your kingdom takes
the clover as its symbol,
as befits its name.
Let's consider it, shall we?
Each of the clover's leaves
supposedly represents one ideal.
None of which your
kingdom truly embraces.
They are integrity,
hope, and love.
Such pretty words.
These three bear titles
with opposite meanings.
Antithetical to integrity,
we have Rhya the Disloyal.
As the antithesis to hope,
we have Vetto the Despair.
And, as the inverse of love,
we have Fana the Hateful.
If someone dares to harm Licht,
I will gladly kill them.
Kill.
Disloyalty, despair, and hatred.
[GAUCHE grunts]
Congratulations, those are
some real spiffy names
you got there, but
they don't tell me
if you're worth a damn
when it comes to a fight.
I guess we'll just have
to show you, then.
Man, how lame. [yawns]
[YAMI grunts]
No way.
[ASTA]
It's just like Captain Yami's!
Copy Magic: Dark Cloaked
Lightless Slash.
Your name's Rhya
the Disloyal, huh?
Swiping spells? Not cool.
I'll sue you for
copyright infringement.
Watch out!
Where are you looking?
Beast Magic: Bear Claw.
[GAUCHE] Damn it,
I'm still short on magic.
[VETTO]
You maggots!
[yelps]
He dodged it?
[YAMI]
Did he pick up on my ki?
[VETTO]
Ha!
[VETTO yells]
Beast Magic: Bear Claw!
[VETTO chuckles]
I can't wait to see the look
of despair on your faces
when you lose all hope.
Nothing seasons a meal
better than abject misery.
Hey, you! That katana
was special order
and very expensive!
You owe me big!
Really, sir?
[YAMI grunts]
Haven't even finished
payin' the thing
off yet, damnit.
Hm?
Loathsome. Abhorrent.
You must die.
[YAMI]
Hm? A salamander?
That's Spirit Magic.
[ASTA]
Spirit Magic?
Does he mean... like Yuno?
Hey, Fana the Hateful, isn't it?
Your personality
could use some work.
[YAMI] Not fully
developed yet, but still.
The spirit of fire,
one of the four elements.
[yawns] Let's end this. 'Kay?
[VETTO growls]
Got any final words?
You hurt our friend.
We will repay that
pain a hundredfold.
[YAMI] You three stay
right here. Ya got me?
Wait. Captain Yami!
[YAMI grunts]
Right. Here we go!
[VETTO yells]
Go on. Incinerate him.
You're keeping up well.
But how much longer
can you hold out?
[YAMI grunts]
Just give up!
He got hit!
[FINRAL] Keeping us safe is
limiting the captain's movement.
And I still haven't
recovered enough mana
to cast my Spatial magic.
[GAUCHE] These guys are
on a whole other level.
Sir! Let me help!
No! I told you to stay put!
You're not worried
about me, are ya, kid?
'Cause I'll tell you right now,
it's about a billion years
too early for that.
You just make sure
you're watching.
Things are gonna get serious.
It's time to push
past my limits.
I didn't expect you
to be defeated easily,
but it will happen.
Every member of the
Third Eye is stronger
than even a
Magic Knight captain.
Now, let's get this over with.
Ha!
Kill them. Spirit Magic:
Salamander's Breath.
[RHYA grunts]
[VETTO grunts]
[GAUCHE, FINRAL, ASTA]
Captain!
--How?
--What the--?
[LICHT]
Hm?
[BOTH gasp]
You're having way too much
fun on your own here, Yami.
You should let the
rest of us in on it.
So, every one of you
is stronger than
a Magic Knight captain, huh?
We'll see.
Aw, man.
Just when I was about to have
some kind of awakening, too.
What're you doin' here, my
high-and-mighty fellow captains?
I would expect somebody
who was in your position
to speak with greater care.
You'd better watch
your back, foreigner,
because I will see you
executed one of these days.
I swear it.
Jeez, look at your hair.
How'm I supposed to
take you seriously?
Pitiful. You couldn't handle
a few measly mages without us?
[YAMI]
C'mon, cut me some slack, huh?
Amazing!
Three of 'em? Whoa!
Who are they?
You're kidding! They're
Magic Knight captains!
--Meh.
--Aren't you even
a little interested?
They aren't Marie, so...
You've really got to work
on this little sister thing.
[FINRAL] Captain of the
Green Praying Mantises:
Jack the Ripper,
wielder of Severing Magic.
A super-sadist who
particularly enjoys
"tearing things in two."
Apparently, he and Captain Yami
flattened a mountain
during one of
their little spats.
Yeah?
[FINRAL]
The imposing, royal captain
of the Silver Eagles:
Nozel Silva.
He's got a very
commanding presence.
--And looks, too, damn him.
--[GAUCHE] Meh.
[FINRAL gasps] It's the captain
of the Blue Rose Knights!
Ms. Charlotte Roselei,
the cool beauty! Aah.
Jeez. What are you
so worked up about?
Look at her! She's
absolutely gorgeous!
Three captains?
This is getting tedious.
[yawns]
Ha! Come on. Big deal.
Captains or not,
they're no match for us.
If someone harms Licht,
I will kill them.
Kill them. Kill them.
I'm ready to tear
someone to pieces.
Let's get this party
started, shall we?
You're from the
Midnight Sun, are you?
There are a great
many questions
that we would like answers to.
[VETTO growls]
[JACK laughing]
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[RHYA]
"Sleepy."
[yawns]
Sleepy. In spring
it's nice and warm.
Good sleeping weather.
[yawns]
In summer, nothing beats
a long nap on the beach.
In autumn, the leaves fall.
They make a nice bed.
[yawns]
Winter's best, though.
[VETTO] He'd sleep the whole
year away if he could.
I have a hard time
falling asleep,
and I hate anyone
who does it easily.
You guys mind?
I'm hibernating here.
[RHYA yawns]
So sleepy.
I am a little more
awake now that
three Magic Knight
captains have shown up,
but not much.
Black Clover , Page 37:
"The One with No Magic."
That is a thorny young woman.