[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy
who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
[NARRATOR]
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world,
and to become the
next Wizard King!
It's imperative we restore
the public's faith
in the Magic Knights
so that everyone feels
safe and secure again,
while also improving the
morale among the squads.
If we can do that, then we'll
be much better prepared
to face Spade and
triumph over the devil.
Sorry. What exactly are
you suggesting, sir?
[chuckles] I'm going to have
the captains battle each other.
[KING CLOVER]
Ahem. Folks!
The Magic Knight Squad Captains
are going head-to-head
in a team battle.
And it begins now!
[laughing]
[MAGIC KNIGHT 151A]
Start the fight!
Not to worry,
citizens of Clover!
Your beloved king
is going to explain
everything you need to know!
The fight will last
for half an hour!
During that time, whichever
team manages to destroy
the other team's crystal
while protecting their own
will be recognized
as the winners!
[KING CLOVER] Also, the match
will be broadcast kingdom-wide
so that everyone may witness it!
[KING CLOVER]
This is your chance to marvel
at the amazing skills
of these great mages,
whom I personally spilled blood,
sweat, and tears to train!
So, you're welcome!
By the way, due to
unforeseen circumstances,
Captain Rill Boismortier
of the Aqua Deer
will not be participating today!
[sighs]
[WALTER]
Oh, Master Rill!
Those melancholy sighs are a
sign that you've fallen in love!
Your first step into adulthood!
[RILL] Miss. I wish I could
figure out who you are,
and where I'm
supposed to find you.
[JULIUS]
Thanks for your help, Marx!
With your Communication Magic,
everyone in the kingdom can
enjoy this historic event!
I'm happy to hear that, sir.
[OWEN clears throat]
[OWEN] How much longer do
I have to wear this disguise?
Aw! Poor Julius! Take it easy!
[KING CLOVER] With the
Wizard King out of commission,
I've got a golden chance to
gain favor with the populace!
[KING CLOVER]
How are you feeling, old friend?
[MARX] Now that I think about
it, we really should come up
with a different solution
to that, for Owen's sake.
World Tree Magic:
Magic Tree Descends!
I won't let you interfere!
You're leading with that?
[JACK]
Severing Magic: Death Scythe!
[YAMI]
Not too shabby, string bean.
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked--
[YAMI grunts]
[gasps]
I'll slice you up!
Of course.
I knew this would
be complicated.
As did I.
Well, then, let's
keep to the plan.
Understood.
[CHARLOTTE] We only recently
discussed a joint training
session with the Black Bulls,
and now I have to fight Yami?
No! Don't think about that!
Remain calm! Calm!
Let's do our best!
I'm psyched! You?
I am. Let's fight!
I don't remember the last time
I had this many
targets to cut up!
You're all mine!
[sighs] This guy's like
a kid in a candy shop.
[NOZEL]
Not so fast!
[sighs] Of course the
riffraff barrels right in.
That's all right.
We'll focus on
defending our crystal.
[JACK cackles]
Come out, come out
wherever you are!
[YAMI] Do you even know where
you're going, smart guy?
[JACK] I don't recall
asking your opinion, pal!
[YAMI] Just sayin'. Walkin'
around in the open like this
is a pretty good way
to get ambushed.
Keh!
Like I care about
playing it safe!
If you don't wanna get cut up,
you just gotta cut them first!
Mercury Magic: Rain of Silver.
You should know
your meager spells
are nowhere near sufficient to
stop an opponent such as myself!
And you should be well aware...
[NOZEL]
...that whenever I run away,
it's always a tactical retreat!
[FUEGOLEON]
Very well.
Then whatever plan you may have,
it'll burn to ash
along with you!
Sir Nozel. Please
allow me to assist you.
[KAISER]
When I fought Sir Fuegoleon,
I was no match for his power,
despite having my Vortex Magic
amplified by elven mana.
This is a chance for me
to redeem myself!
I have a plan.
Just follow my lead.
[SEKKE] I'm getting used to
being the king's right-hand man.
The citizens must be clamoring
to learn more about me.
I bet they're like,
"who's that ha -ttie standing
next to His Majesty?"
Ha, ha! It's me.
[KING CLOVER]
Sekke? I hope you know that
if any of the captains
hurl their attacks
in my direction,
you'll be expected
to protect me with
your very life.
Uh?
[SEKKE] Nope, you're
on your own, buddy!
Oh, yeah, real clever
of you, pickin' away
at your opponents
little by little,
always maintaining
a safe distance.
Now, come closer!
[JACK grunting]
Dark Magic: Black Hole!
Interesting.
--[YAMI] Dark Magic:
--[JACK] Severing Magic:
--Dark Cloaked, Lightless Slash!
--Death Scythe, Lunatic Slash!
[NOZEL] Mercury Creation Magic:
Silver Star of Execution!
[YAMI]
Oh, I'm sorry.
We totally just leveled
that forest, didn't we?
Now you've got
nowhere left to hide.
[VANGEANCE]
Quite all right.
That stunt put a sizable dent
in your magic reserves.
[JACK yells]
Yoo-hoo!
[JACK]
Yami!
[KIRSCH]
How beautiful!
It would appear our brilliant
Captain Dorothy has lured
Yami of the Black Bulls into
her lovely world of dreams!
But, unfortunately,
Communication Magic
isn't capable of crossing
over into that realm.
Which means the rest of us
won't be able to bask
in the splendor of
their magnificent battle
until she brings him back.
There's something so
beautiful about a fight
that can't be observed.
[DOROTHY]
I used my Dream Magic
to transport you
to Glamour World!
Might as well relax until
time runs out, Yami dear!
Too bad!
My squad tells me if
you fall asleep in here,
then you won't be able
to go outside ever again.
Oh, and whatever random crap
you imagine becomes real, right?
Exactly!
[YAMI]
Well then...
Onsen! Sushi boat!
And good saké!
[YAMI]
Ugh.
[DOROTHY giggles]
It has to be something
that I'm familiar with,
or it won't work!
Aw, man, I was really
looking forward to that.
Oh, well.
Exit door.
[DOROTHY giggles]
[DOROTHY] That little elf
who was possessing my body
before had a hard time
with specificity.
But I'm not gonna make
the same mistake.
I guess I'll have to
take a direct approach.
It's more my style anyway.
[DOROTHY giggles]
Sounds like a plan!
Okay. How do you like this?
[YAMI]
Now, Dark Cloaked...
[BOTH]
...Lightless Slash!
Howdy, partner,
it's nice to meet ya!
My name's Yami, and I'm
the rootin'-tootin' captain
of the famous Black Bulls squad!
Is she making fun of me,
or does she really
think I talk like that?
The foreigner's
mana disappeared.
[NOZEL] He must've been
captured by the Dream Magic.
He won't be escaping
for a while.
We need to protect ourselves
from any further setbacks.
Let's take care of him, now!
[KAISER]
Leave it to me!
[FUEGOLEON] Normally,
I would have the upper hand
against Mercury Magic, but since
he's constantly using a massive
amount of mana, he can
repair the cage instantly.
And I can't touch them
if they're outside
the vortex. Quite clever!
[LEOPOLD]
He's trapped!
Wide-range Mercury
Magic and a vortex!
With sophisticated
technique's like that,
they're formidable opponents
even for Captain Fuegoleon!
Amazing. So this is
how captains fight!
Just wait.
My brother's still
getting warmed up!
[gasps]
What do you think
he's about to do
with all those flames?
[gasps]
[NOZEL] The fire won't reach us,
but the heat will.
What's he plotting?
How hot is the
blast going to be?
[FUEGOLEON yells]
What? Which way did he go?
[NOZEL]
He used Salamander as a decoy
so we wouldn't detect his mana.
[JACK yells]
Nice try--
[YAMI]
I'm toast.
See? You shoulda known
a copycat could never
outdo the original.
Hate to tell ya,
but you're still within
reach of her spell.
[DOROTHY]
Cool thing about copies is
I can just keep creating more!
Hah! Send all the
knockoffs you want to.
Crap, this sucks.
[YAMIS] Now, Dark Cloaked,
Lightless Slash!
How did you?
The signal is a bit faint,
but I'm picking up
on Jack's mana!
[NOZEL]
Things look grim.
However, if we can hit
him with one attack,
we may still have a
chance of winning this!
I'm surprised you
haven't given up yet.
[NOZEL] Mercury Magic:
Silver Shining Regal Spear!
[yells]
[panting]
No! I can't hold out
for much longer!
[NOZEL] You seemed so
confident before, Jack.
Don't tell me this
is the best you can do!
[JACK panting]
[DOROTHY]
Nice work, Yami dear!
You're tougher than I thought!
Although, I'm sure you're
close to your limit.
[YAMI laughs]
Think so, eh?
Guess you've got a lot
to learn about me, then.
Little Miss Witch.
I'll show you the spell
I used a while back.
A time when I really
pushed past my limits!
Can you move?
Keh! Who do you think
you're talking to, royal boy?
Let's end this fight. Now!
I don't take orders
from snobs like you!
Hold nothing back!
[yells]
I don't think so.
As a royal who
guards this kingdom,
and as Captain of
the Silver Eagles,
I refuse to be defeated
in such a pathetic manner!
I'm sure you're watching,
Crimson Lion Kings!
Remember, there is nothing
our passionate flames
cannot incinerate!
[CAPTAINS yelling]
Ah!
Since I'm a Squad Captain,
I have to be extra strong!
I wanna become so good
at Dream Magic
that I can even trap
devils in here!
[YAMI] You guys are all
copies of the version of me
that the little witch girl saw.
The thing is, I've gotten
better since then!
Mana Zone: Dark Cloaked,
Dimension Slash, Equinox!
[JULIUS]
Oh, my!
Talk about a fantastic battle!
I can't believe I got to witness
such an astounding
exchange of magic power!
Especially the grand finale!
[JULIUS] Who could have expected
that Yami's Dimension Slash
would cut both teams' crystals
in two at the same time?
You made us go to all that
trouble, and it's a tie?
Well, if somebody hadn't spent
the whole battle in la-la land!
I think we can all agree
those two are hopeless.
After such an
exhausting competition,
it's impressive they still
have enough energy to argue.
What a bummer!
I was hoping I would get
to be on the broadcast,
but Yami dear had to go
and spend the whole fight
stuck in the Glamour World!
[CHARLOTTE] "Yami dear"?
What happened between those two?
I'm still in shock!
You Magic Knight Captains always
find a new way to surprise me!
[MARX] Something
tells me he just wanted
to watch the greats in action.
[JULIUS]
You were amazing, too, Marx!
Thanks to you, the entire Clover
Kingdom was lucky enough
to be part of this
unforgettable event!
Not only that, but I bet
it made them feel much safer
knowing that a group of
capable mages like you
are protecting them.
And, after seeing all
of you captains--
rather, Grand Magic Knights--
in action, your subordinates
will have an even higher opinion
of you from this day forward.
Every moment brings us closer
to facing Spade and the devil.
I hope today's contest
inspired you and your squads
to reach even greater
heights until then!
[CAPTAINS]
Sir!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[CHARLOTTE]
"Yami and Yami."
Pardon me, Yami,
but it seemed like
Dorothy's dream world was giving
you quite a bit of trouble.
What exactly was
going on in there?
Oh, it was a huge pain.
This other version
of me showed up,
and he was pretty
freakin' strong. It sucked!
[CHARLOTTE]
Another version of Yami?
[YAMI]
You've got the Sexy Yami.
Or me, the Wild Yami.
[BOTH]
Which one do you prefer?
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
Huh?
[JULIUS] The days pass,
and time continues to flow.
Even I cannot turn
back the clock.
Tomorrow will always come.
Black Clover , Page 152:
"To Tomorrow!"
I'm glad to know our kingdom's
future is in good hands.