[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR]
Round one, match six
of the Royal Knights
Selection Exam.
[KLAUS]
Steel Creation Magic:
Full Metal Fortress!
[LUCK]
Lightning Magic:
Thunderbolt Destruction!
[PULI]
Gotcha!
Wing Magic!
Angel Flapping
oughta do the trick!
[KLAUS]
Go for it!
[LUCK]
Oh boy, this is a lot of fun!
More.
[ROB grunts]
Let's fight some more!
[NARRATOR]
Thanks to their fine teamwork
and Luck's unexpected
increase in strength,
Team K won their match!
Then, in the eighth and
final match of round one...
[ASTA] It's gonna be Yuno and
Noelle on a team together!
Can we please not do this?
[NARRATOR]
The Silva house is divided.
Noelle vs Solid.
Meanwhile, the bad blood between
Alecdora and Yuno,
born of a festering jealousy
over Vangeance's respect
for the commoner,
erupts into a full-blown
grudge match between the two.
I will be the one to
bring Sir Vangeance's
dream into reality!
Wind Magic: Towering Tornado!
Why would I care about
someone else's dream?
I only fight for my own dream.
Sea Dragon's Roar!
[EMCEE MAGE]
Crystal destroyed! Team P wins!
I'm not weak. Not anymore!
This can't be. There's no way.
Yuno managed to
defeat my best spell.
He made it look like nothing.
He didn't even use
his spirit magic.
All that power, and he
was still holding back.
I will make Sir Vangeance's
dream come true.
Here's the thing
about you nobles.
When you stumble, you break.
[ASTA] Yeah! That was
an awesome fight, Yuno!
[YUNO]
Same to you, Short Stack.
[ASTA]
Now you're calling me that?
That was super-cool, Yuno!
I could watch you fight
like that all day long.
Here! I brought your
usual post-battle dessert.
[YUNO] It would help me
keep up my stamina.
Thank you for this.
It's just what I needed.
[echo] Thank you for this.
It's delicious.
[CHARMY gasps]
[ASTA]
Hey, Charmy! You feelin' okay?
[BELL] Oh, come on, five-head,
get over yourself!
That meant nothing!
Shut up, or I will stuff
your nose with sparkles
till you suffocate, you hear me?
--Take that! And that! Hya!
--[ASTA] I guess you're good.
[EN clears throat]
Hey there. So listen.
Just wanted to say
you were great.
Honestly, I had no idea
you were that powerful.
I feel like your personality
changes quite a bit
when you're not doing
the mushroom thing.
But still...
[EN]
I've been listening to Solid
since before the battle began.
The way that monster
treats his baby sister
is unacceptable!
Noelle, an older brother's
most important job
is to look after his siblings
who are younger and weaker.
But, judging by the
many hurtful things
I've heard him say, it
doesn't sound like he's even
trying to uphold
that responsibility,
so thrash him once and for all!
Um. Thank you...
...for what you said back there.
[gasps]
You did great work.
Ya know, that's
a bit patronizing.
I am still royalty.
[laughs] Let's do our
best next time, too.
[NOELLE] That Mana Skin training
I did really helped me
to regulate my magic.
I just have to keep this up,
and I'll be chosen
as a Royal Knight!
[JULIUS]
Whew!
Those matches were
really something else!
I can't wait for the next one!
Yes, I require more amusement.
[KING CLOVER] It's a shame
that the two commoners
who embarrassed me are
still in the running.
Why won't they just lose?
All right then.
Let's move on to
the second round.
Oh, but before we start...
Go ahead. You know what to do.
[TERRAIN MAGES]
Sir!
[FINRAL] Whoa! The field! It's
shifting right in front of us!
So cool!
For us to get a good
sense of your abilities,
we need to see you fight
in various circumstances.
Hey, I'm back.
Hello there.
Take a good look!
This is the stage on which
round two will be fought!
They can change the
stage all they like,
but my beauty shall
remain constant.
[BOTH]
Yeah, yeah.
Oh. As for this
bit of human waste:
I'll wipe you away like the
unsightly stain you are.
You'll find out I'm
stickier than you think!
Talk trash all you want,
but Asta's strong,
and he has me with him!
So you're the one who's about
to get wiped away, brother!
Hey, Asta!
You better not pull
any punches with me!
Not a chance, Magna.
I'm kickin' your butt!
I hope he doesn't break
your ugly purple glasses.
Shut'chur freakishly
big face, lady.
[ZORA]
Oh, my.
It looks like we're
up against royalty.
I guess we'll just have to keep
relying on that teamwork, huh?
[ZORA cackles]
You're laughing now,
but you looked worried
when the field shifted.
So be honest.
You rigged the field
with traps again
this round, didn't you?
[ZORA]
That's weird. How'd he know?
I guess he must've picked up
on some ki or something.
[ZORA]
All right, yeah. I did.
I came out here
yesterday and scattered
a bunch of traps
around the stage.
My intel told me this was
where the test would be,
so I took advantage
of that knowledge.
[BOTH gasp]
[MIMOSA]
His Intel?
But the location of
the Royal Knights Exam
should be highly
classified information.
What could his source be?
[ASTA]
You placed the traps yesterday?
That's playin' dirty,
ya stupid jerk!
It's part of the
game, you idiot.
What, haven't you heard
of information warfare?
Did you see something
in the rules saying
not to set traps
the day before? Huh?
No one's yelled at me
about it except you.
Hey. Dude. Stop! Stop!
[MIMOSA]
He won that argument fast.
Aw, Asta's so cute
when he's mad.
Okay! Then at least let us
know where the traps are
so we can coordinate with you!
We'll work together!
Not happenin'.
You'd probably give it away
to the enemy by accident.
[MIMOSA]
I mean, he's not wrong.
Look, I've got my
way of fighting,
and I'm stickin' to it.
Man! Fine!
But if you're doing
this your way,
then you'd better believe
that I'm gonna do the same!
It looks like they're having
a bit of an argument.
I hope it isn't
anything serious.
[mumbling] They say
that constant bickering
is the truest sign
of friendship.
I hope we'll have an
argument ourselves someday.
Do you expect me to believe
you'll come up with
your own plan?
With that puny little
brain of yours? No way.
Hey, I've got more brains
than I know what to do with!
That's right,
you tell him, Asta.
The only thing small
about you is your stature!
Yeah, so--! Hold on, what?
Your attention!
Team B: Xerx, Mimosa, and Asta,
vs Team C: Kirsch,
Sol, and Magna!
Round two, match one. Begin!
Mimosa.
You've stood by these
peasants for too long,
allowing their crude
mana to taint your own.
What a sad sight.
But fear not, sweet sister,
I'll release you from the
grasp of these filthy beasts
before any of you can fight.
[KIRSCH]
Cherry Blossom Magic:
Raging Magic Cherry
Blossom Storm of Petals!
Plus my beautiful illusion.
Well now, that's quite a view.
So pretty!
This calls for
a celebratory snack.
And that's for you.
[KIRSCH] Now, in the embrace
of my most beautiful spell,
you're free to relinquish
your soiled past self!
[MIMOSA] I know I talked
big a minute ago,
but, as hard as
I've been training,
and as much as I've improved,
I don't think I have a single
spell that can counter this.
[ZORA]
We shouldn't be hasty to act.
Our best bet is to sit tight and
wait for them to set off a trap.
[ASTA]
What an amazing spell.
I can't see a thing right now.
This might be our only way out.
What is he doing?
[ASTA]
All right. Here we go!
[JULIUS] Hm. Feels like
something big's about to happen.
[ASTA]
That's the way. Just like that.
Flow right on through me.
That darkness...
[ASTA]
Come on. Gimme more!
[MIMOSA]
What is that aura?
It doesn't feel
like magic at all.
It's so strong. So fierce.
It almost... feels sinister.
Get ready!
[ASTA]
Black Hurricane!
[gasps] The cherry blossoms.
Wait. Forget those,
he'll destroy my traps!
Wow. Asta's good.
That attack. It's from before.
[mumbling] Indeed, I knew
he'd been practicing it
ever since his trip
to the volcano,
but I didn't realize
he'd increased its power
to such a degree.
I truly am proud to call
Asta my friend and comrade.
[FINRAL] He's wiping out the
cherry blossoms bit by bit!
Impossible.
How'd that lowborn runt summon
such a dreadful power?
--[SOL] Look at that.
--[MAGNA] Not bad.
He's pretty strong.
I know that wasn't easy.
[MIMOSA] Wow. That
was amazing! Nice work!
Do you have any idea
what you've just done?
[ASTA]
You seem kinda pissed.
I guess you really do care
about these fights.
Now! Let's join forces and
win this thing together!
You rotten imbecile.
[KIRSCH gasping]
What is this ugliness?
What in the world happened?
How did that commoner
dispel all that magic?
Asta will only get
stronger from here on.
[YUNO]
And same goes for me.
Very impressive.
It would seem Asta's mastered
yet another curious power.
Open wide, 'kay?
[ZORA] Do you ever think
before you act, runt?
All the time I spent setting
traps is wasted effort now.
[ASTA giggles]
It sure was!
They're all gone. Rough, I know.
[ASTA]
But it happened.
Time for you to give
us a back-up plan!
One where all three
of us can win this!
Huh?
[ASTA]
You're a crafty guy.
I'm sure you can
think of somethin'.
Come up with a new
underhanded plan
and we'll beat those
guys fair and square!
[laughs]
You do realize that you're
contradicting yourself, right?
[MIMOSA]
Thank goodness.
Looks like the old Asta's back.
We don't need a plan.
That attack of yours should
be more than enough
to take out their team.
So go get 'em.
[laughs] Totally would,
but unfortunately for you,
that move takes a lot out of me,
so I'm gonna have
to wait a while
before I can whip it out again.
Why are you acting so
damn happy about it?
Seriously, are you
sick in the head, kid?
Don't you get it yet?
I want us all to fight
as a friggin' team!
So I don't care if you laid out
all those traps yesterday!
It's time you started
treating me and Mimosa
like real partners.
[MIMOSA gasps]
[ASTA] We're fighting to get
picked as Royal Knights.
If we win, it'll be
on us to take down
the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
No one can fight them alone.
Not me. Not you. Not anyone!
There's only one
way to beat a team
as strong as that,
n' guess what?
It's by makin' a team
that's stronger!
[ZARA]
Look, son.
Yes, my fellow Magic Knights
are amazing people,
but the thing that
makes us amazing
is that we never have
to stand alone.
We all trust that if we face
death, we'll face it together.
[ASTA] Look, the team that
we're up against right now
has the vice captain of
the Coral Peacocks in it.
He's a real piece of work,
but he's also strong!
We need to hit that
jerk hard and fast
with everything we've got!
What the--?
Hey, if you don't like my ideas
then just say so next time!
I wanna join that royal guard
like I want a pet tapeworm.
[gasps]
But my goals aren't about
to achieve themselves.
So I guess that leaves
me with no choice
but to put you to use,
ya little punk.
[laughs] I don't really
care what your motive is.
All that matters to me
is that we fight together.
[ZORA]
Huh.
As I'm sure you've noticed,
my magic attribute is Ash.
And my specialty is Trap magic.
[ZORA] But it's not exactly easy
to create large-scale traps
like the ones from
our last match.
Bigger traps require a lot
more time and magic power
to get going, but they're
also far more effective.
I told you I didn't get
any sleep last night.
[MIMOSA, ASTA]
Wait, that was actually true?
You and your weird
sword blew away
a whole night of work
just like that.
Yeah, sorry about that,
but we didn't really have
a whole lotta options.
[ZORA]
Lemme think.
There are some traps that
I can pull off right now.
Three, actually
'Kay, what are they?
[ZORA]
First one's a snare trap.
Touch the magic circle,
and it roots you in place.
Ensnares you.
[ASTA]
Cool, cool. Go on.
[ZORA]
Next up is the pitfall trap.
It's pretty
straightforward, too.
Ya dig a hole, and wait for
your target to fall inside.
[ASTA]
Very nice!
[ZORA] Trap type number
three is the landmine.
It triggers a simple
attack spell on contact.
[ASTA]
Yeah, I remember that one.
All of those traps'll disappear
once they've been set off.
So unless I invest a lot of
time and magic power in them,
we can't expect much payoff.
Now. What'll it be, kid?
[KIRSCH]
Dear me. I can't believe it.
To think that my
perfectly beautiful spell
was corrupted and destroyed
by that peasant's
insidious weapon.
Heh, you know, I can't
say I'm surprised.
See, I knew that Asta had been
practicing that move plenty.
The kid put in the work,
and now he's got
an ace up his sleeve.
Maybe this'll teach you not
to underestimate commoners.
Oh, side note, I'm one myself.
Don't say it!
You mean to tell me
you're a commoner, too?
Yeah.
And if it mattered,
you would've noticed.
Oh, no!
I could never fight
beside a commoner!
I would just end up
being defiled!
Hey! Wait up ya damn narcissist!
We already fought together once!
What's it gonna hurt
to do it one more time?
There's no need.
I have power enough
to eliminate these
fools by myself.
You two stay there and
protect the crystal!
Ya know what, fine.
Do whatever ya want.
But if ya think I won't do
the same, guess again.
Good grief.
The male animal
certainly is stupid.
There's no doubt about that.
[KIRSCH]
Commoners are brutish.
They are unclean.
And they are fundamentally
lacking in magic power.
How shameful.
He shouldn't even be allowed
to share a stage with royalty,
let alone to stand at
our beautiful sides!
[KIRSCH]
There's Mimosa.
Probably heading
for our crystal.
And I'm sensing that
Xerx fellow's magic power
from right there.
As for the human waste--
I'm getting nothing from him.
What in the world
is he? And where?
[KIRSCH gasps]
Hey, ya want some crystal?
Come and get it!
There you are,
you filthy urchin.
Cherry Blossom Magic:
Dance of the Beautiful
Cherry Blossom Blades!
[ASTA yells]
[gasps]
[ASTA] These petals slip through
the smallest openings.
[ASTA yells]
You're really strong!
[KIRSCH]
Such ugly cowardice.
You shan't escape me!
[ASTA]
Come kick my butt!
Should be easy for a royal!
[KIRSCH] It may be faint,
but I still sense magic.
This is an obvious
attempt to entrap me.
I can see through
this plan with ease,
you craven wretch!
Cherry Blossom Magic:
My Beautiful Clones!
[ASTA]
Oh, no! The traps!
[KIRSCH] Did you really
think you could stop me
with such a shoddy plan?
First you chose to
enter a cramped space
which constrains your blade,
and then you gave up
your only escape route.
I didn't think of that!
If only I was as
smart as royalty!
Begone! Commoner!
[KIRSCH yelps]
[KIRSCH]
No. How could this be?
My clones disposed of every
trap spell in the area.
I was sure of it.
--[ZORA laughs]
--[gasps]
True.
You've got a real
good nose for magic,
and you rely on it
way too much, dumbass.
See, we knew you'd be on
the lookout for trap spells.
So we dug this pit with
plain old elbow grease.
Who's dirty now, royal?
[KIRSCH]
They made this not with magic,
but with effort and muscle?
I should've expected this.
You pathetic primitives.
Still, I'll fly right out--
[KIRSCH yelps]
I really hate to do this
to Mimosa's big brother,
but I'm gonna have to
knock you out for a bit!
Stay away from me,
you filthy beast!
[KIRSCH]
Anti-magic?
Heh!
I told ya that you and me
could make a good team.
Well, for the record,
I was only using you.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[KIRSCH] And now,
"The Life of a Narcissist."
Oh, Master Kirsch, won't
you please stop crying?
[MIMOSA]
Ever since he was born,
the boy had eyes for
no one except himself.
No, no, no, my dears.
Not one of you can
match me in beauty.
[MIMOSA] Never happy with the
looks of his potential brides,
he remained forever alone.
In time, his warped
personality drove
everyone who could've
loved him away.
His twilight years were
remarkably lonely.
[KIRSCH] Ah. There's
a sight for sore eyes.
Oh! So pretty.
You truly are beautiful.
If I could just touch--
[MIMOSA] And so, my stupid
brother met his miserable end.
At least I was in
beautiful company!
If you don't stop fawning
over your own face,
I might just drown
you myself! Ha!
[ZORA]
Friends? Don't be ridiculous.
I'm just using these people
to reach my own goals.
That's all.
Black Clover , Page 79:
"Mister Delinquent
vs. Muscle Brains."
My magic is trapping
the unaware.