[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[ASTA]
Well, come on!
What, are ya done already?
[ASTA yells]
[YUNO]
Asta!
[MARS]
Tell me, boy. What are you?
I am...
I'm somebody who was born
without a single drop
of magic power.
And I'm still gonna
be the Wizard King.
I'll fight and bleed
all I have to.
But I will prove
that I can do it!
[FANA]
Mars?
When you grow up,
what do you want to be?
[MARS]
I...
I live only to destroy!
That's why you live, to destroy?
Well, the Wizard King lives
to protect his kingdom
and his people!
[FANA] We'll keep everyone
in the country safe.
That's why we were born, right?
I will never lose.
Not to somebody like you!
You're in my way.
Begone, pebble!
Sure, I might be
a pebble, but if so,
I'm going to be the pebble
that shatters the diamond!
[panting]
[yells]
There, that should hold him.
[ASTA] You sure that Binding
spell's gonna be enough?
Are you questioning
the strength of my magic?
It's a sturdy spell that won't
be broken by an injured mage.
Plus, I have his grimoire.
Okay, okay, defensive much?
Here. Have some. It's good.
I don't want your
half-chewed leftovers.
Yuno?
I think I'll pass.
I'm so relieved that none of us
were seriously injured.
Are you sure you should be
up and about already?
Oh, yes, it's fine.
I'm mostly healed by now.
I have you to thank for
protecting me so valiantly.
No. I didn't do
anything special.
I just couldn't leave a dimwit
like you to fend for herself.
Well, you have my gratitude.
Fine, whatever.
Asta, do you think you could do
something about
yourself already?
Jeez, what am I doin'
wrong this time?
Just look at the
way you're dressed!
So why are you blushing
when I'm the one half-naked?
Don't be ridiculous.
I am not blushing.
My robe, though.
Aw, just look at it.
The poor thing got
seriously torn up.
Magna's totally gonna
kill me for this.
[LUCK] Vanessa'll fix it
up when we get back.
You think she can?
It's in really bad shape.
[LUCK]
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
[KLAUS]
Shameful.
I still cannot believe
we needed the assistance
of the Black Bulls.
[KLAUS]
As I was certain we would,
we arrived here first,
and thus, are the winners
of the competition.
However, this once,
I will allow you
to accompany us into
the treasure hall.
Come on, Four-Eyes,
could you be any more
high and mighty?!
Thank you so very much,
you enormous jerk!
You're welcome,
and shut your mouth
before it gets you in trouble.
Oh, have I upset you,
Sir Spectacles?
I'm terribly sorry.
I would chastise you for that,
but I simply don't have
the time for petty,
adolescent squabbles
with a Black Bull runt.
[ASTA]
Oh, please, Sir Spectacles,
I beg your forgiveness!
[YUNO] We're not just
involved, we're committed.
[KLAUS]
Now that is taking it too far.
[ASTA] Oh, I'll show ya
too far, Four-Eyes.
[KLAUS] Enough! We're off
to the treasure hall!
Let's go!
Whatever's hidden in there,
we're gonna claim it
in the name of the Clover
Kingdom's Magic Knights!
Will you stop yelling?
[NOELLE]
You're one to talk, loudmouth.
[ASTA, KLAUS]
So... How do we get in?
There's probably a
cipher here somewhere
that will allow us
to open the door.
Go on and find it, Four-Eyes.
[KLAUS] Be quiet!
And it's not Four-Eyes.
It's Klaus!
[LUCK]
Hm.
Looks like it's made of magic,
so you should be able
to slice right through.
Have at.
All right!
Please!
As if you'd be able to
counter such powerful magic.
[yells]
There, see!
[gasps] Whoa!
[ASTA]
This is awesome!
[ASTA laughs]
It's like a mountain
of treasure!
[laughing]
Hey, careful! We don't
know what's in there.
--[screams]
--[LUCK] Hey, Asta. What's up?
How'd he get in there?
[MIMOSA giggles]
It's so beautiful!
Look at this bubble thing.
What's it even supposed to do?
[KLAUS growls]
Enough! Cease your fiddling!
There could be priceless
magical artifacts in here!
Pokin' around some's
not gonna hurt,
Captain Short Fuse.
Use my proper name!
Okay, Mister Specs.
Don't think I won't hurt you!
Ooh! I'm scared now.
You wretch!
See? I was right.
You got a short fuse.
[KLAUS] Only because you
insist on baiting me,
you insufferable twerp.
[gasps]
[YUNO]
What's this? That writing...
I've never seen it before.
[YUNO gasps]
[MIMOSA, KLAUS gasp]
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
[YUNO]
It's gone.
What's going on, Yuno?
What was that light?
[YUNO]
I don't know.
You shouldn't have touched that.
Now, put it back
where it belongs.
[ASTA yelping]
C'mon, quit it, Nero!
You're peckin' me
to death, here!
Okay, what about it?
[yelps]
[KLAUS] His grimoire,
and what a singular one it is.
All patched together.
Interesting.
He got the four-leaf clover,
and he got something
that's so dirty
it's barely recognizable.
I guess you never can tell.
Anything good?
[KLAUS gasps]
[KLAUS grunts]
[LUCK]
This magic...
Quick, get back!
[MIMOSA, NOELLE gasp]
[BOTH yelping]
[gasps]
[KLAUS]
No, impossible!
My Binding spell
should have held him.
He was unconscious, injured.
How did he recover
in such a short time?
[KLAUS gasps]
Wait, is that...?
Flame Recovery Magic? But how?
Each mage can have only
one magic attribute.
The four elements:
fire, wind, water, earth.
A mage is imbued with
mana from one of these.
The attributes interact
in specific ways.
Fire is strong against
wind but weak to water.
It is a known law that
a mage can only use
one kind of magic stemming
from one of these attributes
or its derivatives.
[KLAUS]
Yet, in defiance of that law,
he can wield two types of magic.
And, while he clearly
commands attack magic,
he can cast recovery
spells, too?
Inconceivable!
Those jewels! Is this what came
of the Diamond
Kingdom's experiments?
[FANA] Mars, I know you'll
be a wonderful warrior.
[MARS gasps]
[FANA]
I'm sorry, Mars.
But this is the only way.
You have to die.
If I put out those flames,
it should weaken him.
Noelle's hit!
[grunts]
Noelle!
Noelle! Damn you!
How dare you hurt my friend?!
I've figured out what
your ability is now.
Seems that sword of yours
destroys any and all magic.
But what if the magic is
faster than your blade?
[grunts]
[ASTA]
Too quick!
[ASTA yelps]
[grunts]
How dare you hurt my friend?!
Are you ready?
Only those who are
strong will survive.
The weak deserve death.
[MIMOSA]
Noelle!
Only those who are
strong will survive.
[MIMOSA]
Noelle!
We're not done! Don't give up!
[LUCK, YUNO grunting]
There's no time for
Dream-Healing Flower Cradle.
[MIMOSA]
Plant Recovery Magic:
Princess-Healing Flower Robe.
Stay strong for me.
[MIMOSA] This is the best
Recovery spell I can muster now.
It has to work!
Please, you can't die!
Keep fighting!
[yelps]
[MIMOSA]
Ow, ow, ow. That hurt.
[NOELLE]
What are you doing, Mimosa?
Really, I swear.
Are you such a dimwit
you can't even walk?
Come on.
Thank you, Noelle.
I am a bit clumsy sometimes.
[MAN 18A gasps]
That's marvelous, Mimosa!
[NOBLE 18A]
Incredible, to be capable of
such powerful Recovery
magic at her age.
Given her strength as
a royal, she may very well
grow skilled enough to be
able to heal any wound.
[NOBLE 7A] Now that would
be something to see.
Have you heard, though?
[NOBLE 7A]
It appears the second daughter
of the Silva house,
a girl around Mimosa's age,
lacks sufficient control
over her magic power.
Apparently, she has
to practice daily.
[NOBLE 18A]
For somebody like that
to be born into
the royal family?
I suppose we of House Vermillion
are the true royalty
of the Clover Kingdom.
[NOBLE 18A laughs]
[splash]
[MIMOSA gasps]
[pants]
[NOELLE yells]
[MIMOSA]
If it were me,
I probably would have given up.
[MIMOSA]
Members of our class look down
on those who put forth effort.
Hard work is for the weak
and powerless, not for royalty.
To us, everything
should come easily.
[MIMOSA]
But you...
You've always worked hard,
and I have always
admired you for it.
[gasps]
Only those who are
strong will survive.
The weak deserve death.
Only those who are
strong will survive.
The weak deserve death.
[gasps]
[YUNO, KLAUS, LUCK]
If I could only use my grimoire!
[ASTA]
My sword.
Noelle! Mimosa!
He was right about
that magic being fast.
My sword's too big and
heavy to keep up with it.
He changed his fighting
style to counter mine.
I need to do the
same thing. But how?
Nero?
[ASTA gasps]
You have to die.
Only those who are
strong will survive.
The weak deserve death.
[gasps]
Mimosa!
[ASTA yells]
[gasps]
[YUNO, LUCK gasp]
Where did that sword come from?
[ASTA]
Leave them alone!
Your new opponent...
...is right here!
[yells]
One for me!
Begone, boy!
[ASTA] I can bust through
his attack spells,
but he's still got
that Recovery magic.
I can't finish
him off. What now?
[NOELLE] Why are you just
sitting there, insect?
Don't strain yourself!
You're awake!
[NOELLE] Listen to me.
I am royalty, Asta.
And you are the first
commoner I've accepted.
Now get moving.
And don't you dare give up
until you beat him.
Understand?
Yeah. I'll bring this guy down,
and I'll get one or two hits
in for you while I'm at it.
Give up. You can't win.
I live to destroy the weak!
Well, you're not
gonna destroy me!
I may not have any magic power,
but what I do have...
...are my friends!
You think that's
enough to defeat me?
[MARS groans]
[KLAUS]
Wait, how is that possible?
I didn't think he had any magic.
[LUCK]
A water-based slashing attack?
Did he... borrow Noelle's magic?
[KLAUS]
What in the world is that sword?
[gasps]
[ASTA pants]
I don't really know
how, but I did it.
I'm dead.
What's happening?
[NOELLE]
Asta!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[MARS]
"Long Suffering."
One of my more useful spells:
Flame Recovery Magic:
Phoenix Robe.
I have to say,
that looks quite warm.
It is.
And also rather heavy.
Very heavy.
What's more, if my face
itches, I can't scratch it.
[KLAUS]
Hm.
[MARS] Only those who
are strong will survive.
The weak deserve to die.
Pebbles that will be
ground into gravel
and scattered by the wind.
Black Clover , page 19:
"Destruction and Salvation."
My magic will destroy all.