[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
My, how imperfect.
Since he's able to
wield that sword,
I had assumed he must be
a member of that bloodline.
Why don't we show them
what you really are?
[heartbeats]
[ASTA]
Huh? What is this place?
Don't tell me I'm... dead?
[ASTA]
No, it can't be.
I still haven't gotten
to marry Sister Lily.
[ASTA]
And...
Come on. No.
[DEVIL]
Hey, you. Good to see ya.
[screams] What the heck are you?
[laughs] I can't believe
you'd say that me.
I've been your closest
companion for a while now.
Uh-- I'm pretty sure I'd
remember a guy like you!
Ah, well, doesn't
make any difference.
I got a chance to manifest
in the physical world,
so I'm taking it.
Your body belongs to me!
[ASTA] Tell me what's
goin' on, right now!
You should be glad--it's a
pretty sweet deal for you.
I mean, really!
You wanna win this?
Then all you have to do
is leave it to me.
You shut up!
I'll beat this guy with
nothin' but my own power!
[DEVIL] Quit naggin'
and let me take control
of your mind already!
Just relax and let go
of your consciousness.
A half-pint like you doesn't
stand a chance in this fight.
[ASTA]
That's not up to you, now is it?
Ya know what?
It's kinda perfect
that you're loomin'
over my head like that.
[DEVIL]
Huh?
'Cause if you're up there,
then I can use you
to climb straight to the sky!
[DEVIL laughs]
Some places can't be climbed to.
You should just give up.
[REVCHI] This world has no
use for someone like you,
a poor, magic-less fool.
You might as well give
it all up right now.
You were born a loser,
you worthless runt!
[ASTA grunting]
[ASTA]
Give up?
[ASTA] There was a time
in my life when I might
have given up, but that's
all behind me now!
[ASTA, DEVIL yell]
[ASTA]
My magic is never giving up!
[LADROS]
What? How's he back on his feet?
[NARRATOR]
The leaves of a clover are said
to each contain one thing.
In the first three dwell
integrity, hope, and love.
The fourth leaf is given
over to good luck.
And in the fifth,
there lives the devil.
[NOELLE]
This feeling... It's not magic.
What's with him?
Something isn't right here.
[LADROS laughs] So you had this
big dramatic transformation.
Did you expect me to be
impressed by that or something?
[LADROS yells]
[LADROS]
You're mine!
[LADROS grunts]
[LADROS yells]
[LADROS] I can see that
you're a little quicker
on your feet now!
But how long will this new
trick of yours hold out?
[LADROS yells]
[ASTA growls]
[yelps]
[LADROS] D'you think I was
gonna fall for that twice?
[LADROS]
Damn. He's not messing around!
How did he get so strong?
[yells]
This next attack
can't possibly miss.
[thud]
[ASTA growling]
[LADROS screams]
[ASTA]
What's happening?
My body's chilled to the bone,
like I'm floating
in a freezing lake.
My mind feels clearer than ever.
And my physical
strength is overflowing!
[LADROS groans]
I thought for certain
he'd lose consciousness,
but he's still
maintaining control.
Not only does the
demon-slayer sword
conduct anti-magic energy
in massive amounts,
it absorbs the magic
of all who touch it.
Therefore, no one should
be able to wield this blade,
but you are without magic,
and so its power
courses through you.
You've been dictating
its ebb and flow
from the beginning without
even realizing it.
When I used my
blood to heal you,
it increased the rate
of that power's movement.
In doing so, I intentionally
removed any limitations
on the sword's capabilities.
Now, your magic power
will burst forth
in a massive wave, and you
will become the vessel
for this torrent of anti-magic.
[LADROS whimpers]
[LADROS yells]
[LADROS groans]
[LADROS yelps]
[ASTA yells]
[grunts]
[laughs]
[LADROS yells]
[panting]
What... are... you?
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
I'd suspected you were
of a certain bloodline,
but I was wrong.
[LADROS]
What is this awful feeling?
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Due to your body's mutation,
the mana did not
dwell within you.
Simply put, you're defective.
But because of that, you're
able to hold the sword.
How the hell is this happening?
You aren't anything special.
Not in the slightest.
And that is precisely what
makes you extraordinary.
[LADROS]
I want you out of my sight!
[BLOOD DRAGON growls]
[growls]
Now that you're in this form,
all magic is powerless
against you. Finish him.
Damn you! It can't be!
My magic should have
made me invincible!
Get back! Just stay
away from me!
It's no use.
Your abundant anti-magic
will chase down
and quell his power.
[NOELLE] A black shooting star,
climbing to the sky.
[ASTA growling]
[LADROS] No! No, no, no,
no, no, no! It's not fair!
I stepped on so many people
to get where I am now!
I can't lose to you!
[ASTA] You always kicked
your friends down,
but my friends helped me
be better. Stronger!
Black Meteorite!
[LADROS screams]
[panting]
[LADROS grunts]
[LADROS]
I'm completely out of magic now.
Why me? And why'd
it happen here?
[LADROS] I think... I may
have finally reached my limit.
Goodbye... Ladros.
[NOELLE]
Asta. He's so strong.
And the way he was fighting--
he was like a different person.
[NOELLE]
He looks so terrifying now.
Like a...
Just kill me.
Go ahead, I'm ready.
You must be crazy!
Huh?
It's better if I keep you
alive so you can help
all the people that you hurt!
And then I'm gonna make you
apologize to all of 'em!
Now patch yourself
up and get going!
You may be all bloody
and gross-lookin',
but that doesn't mean that
I have to go easy on ya!
[laughs]
[coughs]
[ASTA]
What the heck is your problem?
[LADROS gasping, groaning]
[LADROS]
Damn. I can't catch a break.
You're a tough guy.
Ooh!
This is outta character.
Maybe... now that the magic
stone's been destroyed,
my head's starting to
feel a little bit lighter.
Aw, man.
[ASTA] You sure you're
okay? 'Cause you fell...
[LADROS] Someone like you
is headed straight to the top,
that's for sure.
Makes me wonder.
If we'd met sooner,
maybe you and I
could've made each
other better, too.
[FANZELL]
Thank you, Asta.
[ASTA]
Dude, are you sleeping?
Keep your eyes open
so I know you're alive!
[NOELLE] I'm overthinking it.
He's still Asta.
I'm normal now. That was weird.
[ASTA] What was all that
black stuff earlier?
It felt like I was fighting
something inside of a dream.
[ASTA] But I had some
kinda mysterious power,
so that was pretty awesome!
I mean, I owned it!
Is this what everyone
else feels like
when they use their
magic abilities?
[ASTA groans] Oh god, my whole
body started hurtin'
all of a sudden, and it
feels like my insides
are bleedin' like crazy, too!
I'm gonna die!
Hey, can somebody
please help me?
--[NOELLE] Help you?
--[FANZELL] Look at us.
Wait, the rest of you
are in bad shape, too?
Hey, you two! You've
got Recovery Magic!
Come on, don't tell me
you already bit the dust!
[MARS grunts]
[FANA grunts]
[ASTA]
Oh, good, you're alive!
Don't just lay there!
[FANA] Oh, dear, I hope
I'm not too heavy.
No.
In fact, the pressure
feels kind of comforting.
[ASTA]
He's way different now!
[FANA]
Mars, stop it.
[ASTA]
Hello?
Well, it's gonna take a whole
buncha trips back and forth,
but I guess the only
thing for me to do
is to carry everybody
back to safety!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
That's not necessary.
[ASTA yelps]
It's you!
The Queen's here!
I took care of the
Eye of the Midnight Sun
and all those
Diamond Army soldiers!
So that outta make us even
for you fixin' my arms, right?
And you did it without me having
to involve myself in the least.
Imperfect though you may be,
I must say, you've
done quite well.
Aw. It's no big deal!
Hey, while I've got you here--
and I kinda hate
to ask this, but...
Do you think you could heal
everyone real quick, too?
[ASTA]
Huh?
Ah. That's also unnecessary.
[NOELLE]
Huh? What is she--?
[VANESSA]
Noelle!
[screams]
[coughs]
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Blood Creation Magic:
Fresh Blood Execution Ground.
[DOMINANTE gasps]
They're going to be
okay. I just know it.
You're right.
[FANZELL]
Her power is horrifying.
[ASTA]
You show up outta nowhere,
and then you do thi--
[ASTA groaning, screaming]
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Yes, my magic allows me
to manipulate blood as I please.
Ever since I cast that
healing spell on you,
I've maintained total control
over your blood, as well.
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
I am the Queen here.
Why should I fulfil the
requests of a pathetic worm
such as yourself?
The only one who
must obey is you.
Blood Magic: Puppet's Blood.
[BOTH]
Let him go!
That aside, your death would
prove inconvenient for me.
You alone will receive healing.
Blood Recovery Magic:
Curse-Breaking
Blood-Filled Cocoon.
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Stay by me, and you may wreak
all the havoc you like.
[NOELLE]
Casting such advanced spells,
one right after the other.
This isn't like
the Spirit's power.
Just being close to it
is giving me chills!
She's worse than I thought!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
As for that sword...
If I cannot wield it myself,
I simply need to be the
master of the one who can.
And you've just demonstrated
how you use it.
So, for as long as you live,
you're going to
carry this weapon
as though it were mine.
[gasps]
No! What's happening?
[VANESSA] All this time,
she was only after
the anti-magic sword?
And now for your first order.
I want you to kill every
one of these weaklings
with your own hands.
Do a perfect job,
and leave no one alive.
Asta... No.
[yells]
[FANZELL] So, the Queen
just wanted control
of Asta's anti-magic all along.
Damn, with powers like that,
no wonder she isn't aging!
Black Clover , Page 64:
"The Red Thread of Fate."
Vanessa! What kind
of spell is that?