[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed
lost until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] With Asta's help,
Fuegoleon subdued
the insane mage who had
let loose an undead army
upon the capital in
his search for revenge.
I get that you wanted
people to take you seriously.
But I don't understand why
you had to do it like this.
[gasps]
Magic?
[VALTOS] Allow me to thank you
for your service, Magic Knights.
What the--?
[NARRATOR] Caught off guard
by a Spatial Magic spell,
the elite members of the
Magic Knights were pulled
from the attack's
aftermath and transported
far from the capital.
I knew there was a strong
Spatial Magic user
working with them,
but even so...
To do this?
Transporting us all would
require great skill.
Spatial Magic again, eh?
Very well.
Maybe now we'll get
to the bottom of this.
[NARRATOR]
Fuegoleon Vermillion,
captain of the
Crimson Lion Kings,
was himself warped away
to a mysterious realm.
It's you!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, having
avoided the spatial ambush
that ensnared his colleagues.
Yuno battled a powerful
witch who used
her Ash Curse magic
to leave him in a state
of total sensory deprivation.
But then...
I'm not done!
There's just one
very important thing
to know about me.
[gasps]
The truth is,
I would rather give
my life than lose!
Wind Spirit Magic:
Sylph's Breath!
[CATHERINE screams]
[CHARMY]
Wow!
Munch, munch, munch!
Munch, mm!
Munch! Mm, munch!
Mm!
Munch, munch, munch, munch!
So good!
Wonderful! Yes!
This little shortcake
knows how to eat!
It's a chef's dream come true!
Keep going!
Savor every last bite.
Yes, eat it all!
That's the plan!
[STAFF 23B] The entire
capital's under siege,
and this is what
they care about?
You just say when
you're ready for more,
and I'll make you
seconds, even thirds!
All right!
[HEAD CHEF 23A, STAFF gasp]
What now?
[CATHERINE coughs]
[HEAD CHEF 23A]
A witch? We're under attack!
What the hell do ya
think we've been
trying to tell you?
Please, Chef, it's time to bail!
[HEAD CHEF 23A]
Run for it, shortcake!
[gasps]
[CATHERINE]
My mana. It's draining!
I need to steal some more!
What are you doing,
shortcake? Just run!
[CATHERINE] That little girl's
saturated with mana.
She's greasy with the stuff!
[CATHERINE] I need every last
drop of it. Give it to me!
I want it!
Give you what?
Wait, you don't mean...
Not my lunch. Not my lunch!
Ah! No way, lady!
[CATHERINE growls]
Now give it to me!
I don't wanna!
[CITIZENS murmuring]
[YUNO]
I can still sense her mana.
That witch has to
be alive somewhere.
[YUNO gasps]
[YUNO]
I won't last much longer.
[YUNO] What? That's a
massive surge of magic!
[CATHERINE]
Relinquish it to me!
[whimpering]
[CHARMY]
I told you no.
[gasps]
And when I say "no," I mean no.
This is ridiculous!
[CHARMY]
You won't think so for long.
Cotton Creation Magic:
Strike of the Sleeping Sheep!
[gasps]
[SHEEP bleets]
[ALL gasp]
That was awesome!
Oh-- Well? Ya see that?
My cooking gave the
little shortcake's
magic power the boost it
needed to defeat the witch!
Seriously? Chef, sir?
I'll work with you
for as long as I live!
You saved us with your feast!
It was nothin'!
I don't care who you are.
Nobody ever lays
a hand on my food.
Your patronage is
not wanted here!
[STAFF]
Ha, ha!
Please tell me I'm beautiful.
[gasps] My dear Eliza.
Yes?
I'll always love you,
young or old.
And I love you!
Eliza!
My dearest!
[CHARMY]
Whew!
[screams]
[CHARMY]
My lunch! Come back!
[CHARMY screams]
[YUNO]
A child?
[YUNO] That outrageously
powerful burst of magic.
Was that her?
[YUNO] She's wearing
a Black Bulls robe.
It must've been.
You saved my food.
Oh, uh. Here.
I don't get it, but sure.
Thank you so--
[yelps]
[CHARMY] My princely
savior of sustenance!
Um.
I owe you a tremendous
debt, noble sir!
Uh...
[CHARMY]
So. Could, um...
Could you tell me what...
A short rib?
Oh, yeah, they're great!
You can try one if you want to!
Wait, no, no, no, no!
That's not it.
I meant, could you tell
me what your name is?
I mean, don't get me wrong,
you can have one, but I
know what a short rib is.
[YUNO]
Here comes the crash.
That magic took a
serious toll on my body--
it used up a ton of mana.
[YUNO]
I need practice.
Gotta learn to be
more efficient.
[gasps]
[CHARMY]
Look out!
[gasps, squeals]
Saved ya!
[breathing heavily]
[CHARMY] Guess I'll just
eat this and be on my way.
[BELL]
Hm?
What is that infernal
racket out there?
Will you order them
to quiet down?
Don't they know it's my naptime?
I'll look into it, sire.
[yawns]
[MARX]
Is it him?
It's about time
he made his return.
[laughs]
[HEAD CHEF 23A] You've forever
won a place in our hearts,
little shortcake!
[STAFF]
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
Just stop on by
whenever you're hungry,
day or night!
We'll feed you until
you're ready to pop!
Yay!
Ah!
[LEOPOLD]
You evil bastard!
Tell me where you
sent my brother!
[RADES cackles]
[laughing]
He's just toying with you!
He wasn't the one who cast
the Spatial Magic spell.
But the pinpoint accuracy of it.
No one could pull that off
unless they were close
to their target.
They're hiding nearby.
[NOELLE]
Asta?
[yells]
[gasps]
[NOELLE] He was hiding
beneath the pile of corpses?
[VALTOS]
Nice observation skills.
I had a feeling you'd suss out
my magical transformations,
but I couldn't even
get past you with this shabby,
putrescent disguise.
You really are quite the animal.
Regardless, it's
already over now.
Over?
What is?
[NOELLE screams]
[screams]
No! Fuegoleon!
[grunts]
[ASTA]
But how?
How can someone be that strong?
That's just insane!
They-- His arm.
This can't be.
No.
You can't die, Fuegoleon!
No, not my brother.
He would never lose.
He'd never lose.
Never!
[gasps] It's Captain
Fuegoleon's grimoire!
Wait, if his grimoire's
still intact,
then he's not dead yet!
We have to stop the bleeding!
Impossible. There's no way.
[NOELLE] If only Mimosa were
here, she could fix this.
Leopold.
Your brother's grimoire
is starting to disintegrate!
Snap out of it!
I need your help!
My brother.
[NOELLE]
Leopold!
Are you just going
to let your brother die?
Well, Magic Knight,
not so sure of yourself
anymore now, are you?
Pull it together!
[groans]
[gasps]
[NOELLE] He still has
a reserve of magic power.
[RADES]
Ha!
[RADES cackles]
Perhaps you could have
become a great man
if you had gone down
a different path.
This is where the lack of
a just heart has led you.
[RADES]
I lack a just heart, do I?
Well, I have to tell ya,
the way I live my life,
my heart's done
just right by me.
Looks like you'll have
to save your preaching
for the afterlife, Captain.
[VALTOS] You've fulfilled
your purpose here.
Take your leave, Rades.
Before the other Knights arrive.
[ASTA]
No way. Not yet!
[RADES]
Huh?
It's little Asta, right?
Don't worry, I promise
to kill you soon enough,
and make a plaything
of your corpse!
Something we can both
look forward to, you brat!
[ASTA growls]
[yells]
Asta!
[ASTA]
I'm not close enough!
I'll never make it!
Just let him go!
[NOELLE] He's losing too
much blood--he has to stop!
[ASTA]
I can do this!
Remember what Captain
Fuegoleon told you.
Stay calm and think.
There must be some
way I can stop him.
I just have to figure
out what it is.
Spatial magic is still magic.
And I've still got my sword!
I'm gonna hack that
spell to pieces!
The hell?
[VALTOS gasps]
[ASTA yells]
[screams] That hurt!
You're gonna pay for that,
you little wretch!
Unfortunate.
[RADES gasps]
You're whining
about a little cut?
After the pain you've caused?
You want pain?
I'll give ya pain!
[grunts]
[ASTA]
You tortured innocent people
and laughed the whole time.
[groans]
[RADES]
Stop it!
Those poor innocents
you're so worried about?
That only proves
how weak they are!
It's just the natural order!
The weaker mage will
always succumb to the one
with greater power!
And you.
You were born to die,
you magic-deficient swine!
[ASTA]
The natural order, huh?
Then what d'ya call this?
Ah!
[ASTA]
That's right.
Maybe I don't have any magic,
but I'm still the
strongest one here!
And I'll prove it to everyone
when I become the Wizard King!
Hey, Valtos! I could use
a little help here!
[VALTOS] Hmph. I've already
done everything I can.
Anti-Magic, it's trickier
than I expected.
Seems like the smartest
plan of action
is to take care of him first.
[NOELLE]
He's gathering magic power.
But for what?
[NOELLE gasps]
[NOELLE] Is he going to attack
through a spatial portal?
Asta! Behind you!
[gasps]
[VALTOS]
Too late!
[LEOPOLD panting]
Being upset won't help us.
Always remember to stay
calm. Right, Brother?
Let's go, Asta.
Please be careful!
[RADES growls]
[panting]
So, what should I do?
I can't afford to
lose Rades just yet.
Get away from me!
Stay back! Get away, dammit!
[GEORK]
How pitiful.
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
[GEORK] I come here after
receiving word from the master,
only to arrive and find
you fighting this?
Pitiful indeed.
[NOELLE]
This magic...
I've never felt anything
so piercingly cold.
[LEOPOLD]
So now there's five of them?
[ASTA]
This curse I've got on me.
None of these scrapes and
scratches will stop bleeding!
I'm gonna be in serious trouble
if I lose any more blood.
Ugh.
I don't remember putting out
the call for any extra help.
[SALLY]
Really?
You might want to
try thanking us.
What?!
You know what would've
happened to you
if we hadn't shown up
to bail you out?
You would have been captured,
cut open, gutted,
and skinned alive.
And if you are
gonna get dissected,
I wanna be the one to do it!
[RADES]
Will you shut up?
Well now, it looks
like the tables
have finally turned,
you little brats.
[ASTA]
Heh.
[RADES]
Huh?
[laughs]
[ASTA grunts]
Huh?
Asta!
What was that?
Small surgery.
Now I'm ready to fight again!
Watch. I'll prove it to you.
[RADES]
Seriously?
Did he just strike himself
with his own blades
to dispel the curse?
Unbelievable! Who would do that?
[SALLY giggles]
This kid's funny!
Can I pretty please
dissect him later?
Be quiet and focus.
Phooey. You're no fun.
[ASTA]
Here's the thing.
I've been fighting an uphill
battle since I was born.
No matter how many
guys you've got,
and no matter what you do to me,
I'll cut right through
every last one of you!
You hear me? Let's see
what you've got!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[VALTOS]
"They'll Never Find Me."
He's just toying with you!
He wasn't the one who cast
the Spatial Magic spell.
But the pinpoint accuracy of it.
No one could pull that off
unless they were close
to their target.
They're hiding nearby.
[VALTOS chuckles]
They're never gonna find me.
He's not in here!
Not here!
You're dead.
Not here, either!
[VALTOS]
Any second now.
I'll make my grand entrance
and blow their simple minds.
Well, we know he's not here,
so let's check over that way.
Good thinkin'!
I'll bet you a month's wages
that I'll find him
before you two.
[VALTOS] Wait, what?
Should I just lie here?
[HEAD CHEF 23A]
Hey, Magic Knights.
Fill up on my cooking!
And then do your fighting!
I'll fight on my own
battlefield, the kitchen!
Black Clover , Page 26:
"Wounded Beasts."
My magic is cooking
incredible food!