[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy
who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
[NARRATOR]
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world
and to become the
next Wizard King!
[NARRATOR] Asta and the others
are training to defeat Megicula,
a devil who waits
in the Spade Kingdom.
[ASTA yells]
[NOELLE]
Sea Dragon's Roar!
[LEOPOLD]
Spiral Flames!
[NARRATOR] Queen Loropechika
of the Heart Kingdom,
who suffers from
Megicula's curse,
gave them six months to prepare.
In that brief span of time,
these young knights
must surpass their limits
and become unstoppable!
[ASTA]
Gah! I'm so exhausted!
--[stomach growls]
--And so hungry.
[FINRAL]
Good job in your training, Asta.
[gasps] Hey, Finral!
Is there a problem or something?
Sadly, yes.
It turns out I'm cursed, too!
[yelps]
Being salacious doesn't mean
you're cursed, Finral.
It just means
you're insufferable.
Hello there, Noelle,
you're looking
positively radiant today!
Wait-- No, bad Finral!
You have to stop!
Bad, bad, bad, bad...
Insect.
That's rough.
No, hold on!
Let me explain, okay?
It was something
Langris told me.
It's plain to see
that you're cursed!
[FINRAL]
What?
[LANGRIS] You hit on every girl
you meet like a wannabe playboy!
[FINRAL]
Playboy?
[LANGRIS] And the time you
spent shirking your duties
made you a bigger
failure than ever!
[FINRAL]
Failure?
[LANGRIS] That freewheeling life
has left you with bad habits
--that won't just break!
--[FINRAL] Bad Habits?
[LANGRIS] There's no way that
a self-centered degenerate
like you could make
Lady Finnes happy!
[FINRAL]
That stung.
And I have my heart set
on a very special woman,
so I have to be freed
from this curse!
If I don't change my ways,
I'll never be good enough
for Lady Finnes!
[NOELLE] That must be the person
Captain Yami mentioned before.
Wow, I had no idea Finral could
be serious about someone.
[FINRAL]
So, Asta.
I'm gonna need
a training partner!
Help me get past
this terrible curse
and make my heart stronger!
Sounds like you mean it.
Sure! I'll do whatever
I can to help you out!
Let's go kick that curse's butt
so you can make that lady
super happy one day!
Thank you, friend!
[NOELLE] If they're training
to make his heart stronger...
[BLACK BULLS]
Bottom's up!
[NOELLE]
What are they doing at a mixer?
[ASTA] I didn't know goin' to
mixers made your heart stronger,
but hey, this is fun!
[LUCK] Hope I get to
fight somebody this time!
[REBECCA] Why would Asta invite
me to a mixer all of a sudden?
I wonder what he's thinking.
I'm certainly not
gonna complain, though!
[KAREN] Since when is
Rebecca so buddy-buddy
with all these Magic Knights?
Whatever, I just
wanna get married.
I don't even care
who I end up with.
[ELIZA] Mm... I'm not
interested in real guys.
I just didn't wanna
turn down the invite.
Let's get this over with
so I can go home
and finish reading my book.
[FINRAL]
This is the perfect battlefield
to start my training!
It'll be rude not to sweet-talk
these ladies and make
them feel special,
so it's even more
of a challenge!
That curse'll be
gone in no time!
[NOELLE]
Training, really?
To think, I almost changed
my mind about that sleazeball.
I'm just here
because I'm worried.
Wait a sec, what exactly
am I worried about?
You've got a little
bit right here.
Huh? What right where?
[NOELLE shrieks]
[NOELLE] Of course!
I forgot all about that girl!
Easy! I know this is
your first day and all,
but could you maybe try
not to destroy my bar, miss?
Mind your own
business, beer boy.
[TAVERN OWNER 135A] I'd say this
is my business, wouldn't you?
Fine, but I'm watching you!
If you break anything else,
you're fired, do you
understand me?
[gasps]
Nero, why'd you get
a job at this place?
[SECRÉ]
Just because.
This isn't something
you should do for fun.
It's a very serious profession!
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
Oh, no, she's adorable!
If Asta sees her like that,
what's to stop him from
falling in, in you know?
What's wrong?
Uh. I'm gonna go
check on Asta's table,
you can take care of
whoever else you want,
just leave that one to me.
[NOELLE] Wait, why am I trying
to keep her away from Asta?
It's not like I care
if he has feelings for her
or anyone for that matter!
[CUSTOMER 28A]
'Scuse me, sweetheart!
I'll take another beer!
Go and get it yourself, insect.
[CUSTOMER 28A]
Wait, not you again!
--Huh?
--[SECRÉ] Enjoy, sir.
[CUSTOMER 28A]
Wow, she's an angel!
[ASTA] Hey, Finral, why are
you staring off into space?
It's your turn to introduce
yourself to the group!
Eh. I'd prefer to eat
quietly without socializing.
Huh?
You see, all I wanted was
a little time to relax alone,
but you had to drag me
to this place instead.
[stammering]
[KAREN]
Ugh. Every mixer I go to,
there's always this one jerk
who thinks it's cool to act like
he doesn't wanna be there.
[REBECCA]
He changed his hair,
but this is definitely the
same jerk from last time.
Well, we're here now,
so let's enjoy our
dinner together okay?
Finral, I'd love to hear
about your adventures
as a Magic Knight--
[FINRAL] Nah. That's not really
my thing, I'm gonna pass.
[REBECCA, KAREN]
What isn't your thing?
[FINRAL] Gah, I'm dying!
She's actually interested
in having a conversation with me
and I'm supposed
to push her away?!
Try to stay strong, Finral!
It's all part of your
training, remember?
Oh, no!
My muscle memory is making me
reach for a bouquet of flowers!
Take it easy there, right hand!
Man, asking me not
to flirt with girls
is like asking a fish
to climb a tree!
[KAREN]
I do not understand this guy.
[ASTA]
Oh, I get it!
Finral's doing everything he can
to fight against his curse!
Oh, he's so tough!
[LUCK] I wonder when
the battle's gonna start.
[NOELLE] Maybe there's
nothing to worry about.
[SEKKE] I finally made it
to the bar! Ha, ha!
Sorry it took me so long.
I've been really busy
protecting the kingdom
from certain destruction,
you know how it is!
Naturally, I can't share
any of the details,
but the point is that something
truly a- ha -wful happened
and I'm the hero
who saved the day!
Some Magic Knights
lost their ma- ha -rbles,
but I was there
to set them straight!
It's only a matter of time
before they promote me
to captain, ha, ha!
It's true. My life
is suddenly awesome.
And the King! He loves me!
What can ya do?
Whoopsie!
Did I divulge too much
to- ha -p secret info?
Well, at least I
haven't been reading
dirty magazines
like my pal here.
Though, I'd better
not reveal that either.
Dude! You already told
them, as plain as day!
The ladies like it when a guy
has a touch of
mystery about him.
[NOELLE] Apparently,
this is a popular spot
for weirdos to have mixers.
What's that loud
guy's name again?
I don't mean to brag,
but according to the guys
who went to visit
the Heart Kingdom,
there's some kind of amazing
secret behind my Bronze Magic.
Protecting the world
is a tough job,
but it's something only
yours truly can do!
Not to worry, there's no
need to thank me!
Unless you want to. Ha, ha!
[NOELLE] Oh, right.
This is the "ha-ha guy."
[SEKKE]
Da- ha -rling!
Bring us another round
of drinks, please,
and make it snappy!
[GROUP yelps]
As soon as I read that
weird article about you,
I knew there had to be
some kind of mistake.
Asta, a criminal? Come on, now.
Thanks, but it's
not totally wrong.
They are planning to execute me
for treason pretty soon.
You're being
sentenced to death?!
Yeah, but it's not
that big a deal.
It's just a little treason,
and I didn't even do it.
Hey, so, you came here to
become stronger, too, right?
Y'wanna fight me?
[KAREN]
What's he talking about?
Is he using "fight"
as a code word?
I'm flattered,
but don't you think
it's a little too early
for us to get physical?
[LUCK]
Huh?
[FINRAL]
How am I the only one
who's not having
flirtatious banter?
Wait a second.
Maybe I'm looking
at this all wrong!
If I made it this long
without hitting on anyone,
that means my training
must be a huge success!
[FINRAL]
Then again...
I do feel bad that these girls
wasted their evening.
I'd better apologize
and explain later.
[ELIZA]
It's you.
My dream guy does exist,
and he's right in front of me!
[screams]
Take all these beers
to table three.
Thanks! Whoa, you sure
you got all that?
[TAVERN OWNER 135A] She's the
best waitress I've ever had!
She more than makes up
for that other one.
[sneezes]
Enjoy.
[SECRÉ] Isn't that man
from the Golden Dawn?
[WOMAN]
Thanks a lot, miss.
[SECRÉ]
What is he doing here?
Hey, easy there!
[MAGIC KNIGHTS gasp]
[SECRÉ] They're with
the Blue Rose Knights.
[SECRÉ]
Pardon--
That's the Blue Rose captain,
and our captain's here, too.
This must be about the devils.
[CHARLOTTE] It was kind
of my subordinates
to throw this dinner
party for me, but...
[YAMI] Knowin' the Blue Rose
Knights are picking up the bill
makes the food taste that much
better, doesn't it, fellas?
[MAGNA]
Yeah, that's for sure!
I just wish I knew
where Asta ran off to.
I was gonna invite the
little guy to eat with us.
[CHARLOTTE] They really are
just here for the free food.
[GORDON] I thought it was
just dinner among friends,
but judging by
Captain Charlotte's attire
and the seating arrangements,
this is a mixer, isn't it?
I'm looking forward to
getting acquainted with you!
Yes, I hope we can
become great friends!
[SOL muffled] On one hand,
I want Char to be happy,
but I can't stand the idea of
a man stealing her away from me!
Ugh, I don't know what to do!
I just wanna eat my feelings!
You're gonna get a stomachache
if you don't slow it down.
[SOL] Mind your own
business, DumGlasPunk!
Did you actually try to
abbreviate "Dumb Glasses Punk"
to insult me faster?
Good grief, woman,
you are in a hurry!
You have no clue what
I'm going through!
Uh. I'm sorry?
That's it!
I challenge you
to an eating contest!
[MAGNA]
Hah! Piece of cake! Let's go!
[CHARLOTTE] I'm not sure
about this dress.
Isn't it too revealing?
No, I need to trust
Puli's advice.
[NARRATOR]
Puli Angel!
This Fourth-Class Junior
Magic Knight has another side
to her personality that
not everyone has seen.
Many of her fellow
Magic Knights have come to her
for guidance in
the ways of romance.
Puli often acts as a Cupid--
or an angel of love,
as her name suggests--
doing her best to bring lovers
together wherever she goes!
[PULI]
You're more beautiful
than ever today,
Captain Charlotte.
He doesn't stand a chance
against your charms.
Work it, girl!
[CHARLOTTE] My knights
are pulling out all the stops
to support me. I should do
everything I can to succeed.
[YAMI]
Hey, Prickly Princess.
[gasps]
You must be freezing cold
in that skimpy dress.
[yelps]
I don't need
judgement from a man
who can't be bothered
to wear real clothes.
I'll have you know this
is my nicest undershirt!
[CHARLOTTE] This is the
man Yami's always been.
I was such a fool to
expect any different!
[PULI] I heard he was
on the stupid side,
but this is worse than
I could've imagined!
I have no choice but to
call an emergency meeting!
[CHARLOTTE] I'm sorry
your captain is a coward.
Don't talk like that--
the fight isn't over yet!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 135A]
You can do it!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 126A]
Hang in there!
[CHARLOTTE]
Where did you two come from?
[PULI] The Captain of the
Black Bulls seems to prefer
the prim and proper type.
We'll fix you up in no time!
[CHARLOTTE]
What? I'm fine the way I am!
Not true!
The outfit is only
one part of it,
you need to work
on your appeal, too!
Uh-- Wait. Appeal?
Number one!
Get him some food to show him
how considerate you are!
When a plate comes to the table,
grab it and serve it
to him immediately!
That way it'll be obvious
that you're thinking of him!
Because there's nothing
sexier than a partner
who anticipates
your needs, right?
I... suppose so.
Next step!
Try to be a good listener!
Everyone wants to be able
to talk about themselves
as much as possible.
Let him ramble
to his heart's content,
and he'll love you for sure!
Your responses can
be anything, really.
"Wow!" "That's crazy!" "I had
no idea!" "You're amazing!"
Is that what people want?
I didn't realize.
And now, here comes
the final secret!
And this one is
absolutely pivotal!
What? Tell me everything!
Something called
the casual touch!
[CHARLOTTE]
Casual touch?
I'm sorry, there's simply no way
I could do something
so daring as to make...
[PULI] Hate to break it to you,
but being considerate
and listening only account
for about ten percent
of attracting a man.
The other 90 is
all about the touching!
Well, that doesn't seem fair!
[CHARLOTTE]
It's no use.
I don't have what it takes!
We believe in you, ma'am!
You can't just let
your rival defeat you!
[gasps]
But, I...
[PULI] We'll be behind you
every step of the way, Captain!
Thank you. All of you.
I understand what
needs to be done.
At some point,
I'm going to touch Yami!
Finral, I love how
cool and aloof you are.
You're just like the
Magic Knight Fiorel
from the novel I'm reading!
Fiorel is the ultimate hero
because he can harness
the powers of Light, Dark,
Flame, Wind, Water...
[FINRAL] All of those?
That's just bad writing!
So, Luck, it sounds like you're
a really talented fighter.
You want me to show you?
[KAREN]
Oh, wow!
I didn't expect him
to be that forward!
From what I've heard
about the Heart Kingdom,
it must be a beautiful place.
I'd love to see it someday.
I'd be happy to take
you there for a visit
once this whole thing is over!
We can take your siblings, too!
She's got nerve!
If I let my guard down around
her, she'll scoop him right up!
[TAVERN OWNER 135A]
Why did I hire this girl again?
Huh?
[REBECCA]
Noelle?
Um, listen.
So far, I don't really
have any friends
outside of the Black Bulls.
So I would love to get
acquainted with you.
Oh, and I should
probably mention,
my hobby is making dolls,
so I hope it wouldn't bother you
if I crafted one in
your likeness, Miss Puli.
Aw! I'd be honored if you did.
I'll even give you
my measurements
so it'll be an
accurate depiction!
[GORDON]
Uh, great!
[MAGNA] There's no way I'll lose
after the expert coaching
I've had from Charmy!
[CHARLOTTE]
I can't exactly reach out
and touch Yami out of nowhere.
I'd better start
with serving him food.
[gasps]
[YAMI]
Here. Have some.
[CHARLOTTE]
Oh, thank you.
He beat me to the punch!
What am I supposed to do now?
[YAMI] You sure were taking
a dump for a long time.
Oh, sorry, I mean,
"powdering your nose."
How crude!
I needed to have a conversation
with my subordinates,
not that it's any
of your business!
Uh-huh. Guess that's
why I keep seeing
your Blue Rose girls
sneaking back and forth.
You noticed, then?
Well, I suppose they
were hard to miss.
[YAMI] They're probably
worried about you.
We all know you can't
hold your liquor.
[CHARLOTTE]
That's not--!
I mean, I certainly
can't dispute that fact.
Whether we're on
a mission or not,
the Blue Rose Knights always
have my best interests at heart.
They were the ones who arranged
this dinner party
tonight, just for me!
I tend to get so focused
on fighting and being strong
that I forget about
everything else.
So I end up relying on them.
[CHARLOTTE]
Oh, no!
I'm running my mouth when
I should be listening to him!
[YAMI]
That's all right.
You gotta learn how to
lean on other people more.
Heh. I depend on my squad.
For dumps. Oh, I'm sorry,
for powdering my nose,
I have one of 'em make a portal
for me so it's easier--
[CHARLOTTE] Shouldn't you
do that for yourself?
[YAMI] You know,
that meat's pretty good.
You oughta try it
with some pepper.
[CHARLOTTE]
All right.
[PULI]
Ah?
[CHARLOTTE]
I feel Yami's hand on mine.
Is this a casual touch?
[screams]
[PULI]
Captain?
[SOL]
Char!
For crying out loud,
you don't have to act like
you just got infected with
the damn plague or somethin'.
I keep my hands clean!
I'm pretty sure that's
not the problem.
[ELIZA] I want you to understand
how great Fiorel is!
I think we should have
a reading party tonight,
just you and me
all alone in my room!
Nah, I'm good.
I appreciate the offer, but that
sort of thing isn't my scene.
[FINRAL]
It's not fair!
The one time a pretty girl
actually looks my way
at a mixer, and here I am
trying to be decent!
Don't you dare
touch her, Finral!
I know you!
As soon as you make
physical contact,
you're gonna go right back
into ladies-man mode!
[ASTA] Stay strong, Finral!
Please, we're almost home free!
Hey, looks like he's already
in a battle of his own,
that kinda makes me jealous!
You and I ought to fight, too!
Right here, right now!
You seriously want us to do it
in front of all these people?
What kinda floozy
do you think I am, mister?
[FINRAL]
Come on, you can do it!
Pull yourself away,
one muscle at a time!
Just say no!
[FINNES] Poor Finral.
He looks like he's in pain.
[CHARLOTTE screaming]
[FINRAL]
Captain Charlotte?
[screaming]
I'll save you!
Good evening, Captain.
You look absolutely
ravishing tonight.
[FINNES gasps]
I know I just swooped in
and saved you like some
prince charming,
but I didn't have a single
ulterior motive for my actions!
My heart already belongs
to someone else,
and it always will!
[FINNES]
Finral!
[LANGRIS]
You're kidding.
Wow, I didn't know we were
having that kinda party.
[gasps] Get your
hands off me, now!
I was fooling myself.
My ideal man only exists
in storybooks, not real life.
Your aggressive behavior tonight
made me realize something.
If I'm too focused
on getting married,
I'll probably end up with a
brute like you and hate my life.
Goodbye!
[laughs]
I brought us here in
disguises so we could keep
an eye on my brother, since
he'd mentioned something about
training to get over his curse.
But, I guess he was just
being his normal stupid self
and there was nothing to see.
I'm sorry.
[FINNES] No. Actually,
I'm really thankful
I was able to be here
for this, Langris.
It's true, Finral does have
a strong interest in women,
but he's also very
kind, and I think
that's one of the
ways he expresses it.
[LANGRIS] You can call him kind.
I call him a girl-crazy loser.
[FINNES chuckles]
Anyway, we should head home.
I didn't know you
guys had jobs here!
Yeah, what are the odds, right?
Small world.
Yep, it's a total coincidence.
You should try being a bit
more forward with Asta.
We both know he
isn't too bright.
What? I don't know what
you're talking about.
I don't have anything to say
to his dumb face, no way!
[REBECCA giggles]
I'm sorry, Asta.
I dragged you out here
to help me train,
and then I kept
screwing things up.
Just forget it.
I'll never be good enough.
Come on, you can't throw
in the towel yet, Finral!
This is only the
beginning, okay?
Thanks, Asta.
Well, I can't say
I've ever seen you
in a situation like that before.
So, is that the
kinda guy you like?
The dashing young hero?
Don't be ridiculous,
that fool could never
obtain my love.
My heart is spoken for.
By someone important to me.
Oh, you don't have
to tell me that.
[gasps]
Your heart belongs
to your squad,
you've said it a million times.
[YAMI]
Hm? Are you okay there?
[PULI] Looks like you
still need some help
from your angel of love!
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
[CHARLOTTE]
He's so close!
Well, let's do our best
to get along for
six months, all right?
Yes.
[REBECCA] With all the brave
things Asta's been doing lately,
it's no wonder I've got
more rivals than before,
but I refuse to give up yet!
Black Clover , Page 136:
"A Black Deep-Sea Story."
Kahono? Don't tell me
she likes him, too!