[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] The long-awaited
Star Festival had just begun.
This event features
the annual rankings
of each Magic Knight
Squad, followed by
an announcement from
the Wizard King
regarding which squad
earned the most stars.
Kahono! And Kiato!
[NARRATOR]
Asta had invited his friends
from the Underwater Temple
to join in on the fun.
[NARRATOR] The magic from
the Queen of Witches
restored both Kiato's leg
and Kahono's voice.
[NARRATOR] Then, during
all the excitement...
[KAHONO]
Hey, Asta!
I've been meaning to ask you...
What do you think about Noelle?
Uh... What do I think?
You're pretty great.
I like you a lot, Noelle.
[shrieks] Where did
that come from?
I swear, you get
dumber every day!
[ASTA yelps]
What did I do?
[ASTA screams]
[NARRATOR] To Asta's surprise,
he discovered Yami
and Jack the Ripper, Captain
of the Green Praying Mantises,
involved in what looked
like the beginnings
of a bitter showdown.
Ah! I'll take
another one, please!
[KAHONO singing]
Gather round, everyone!
It's a spectacular
song-and-dance
from under the sea!
What a beautiful melody!
He's such a talented dancer!
I'm happy to see the
two of them doing
the things that they love again.
It's touching. Not bad, Dorks--
[ATTENDEE 68B]
Hm?
Just who do you think you are?
Don't crowd royalty!
Oh! I'm sorry!
[NOELLE]
I guess I did blow him off.
I wonder where he ended up?
Ugh, he's such an idiot!
All right, Asta,
where did you go?
Would you like a plate?
No, maybe later.
Care to try your luck, miss?
Maybe later.
A snack for a lovely lady?
Later.
[NOELLE]
Actually...
Yeah, now's good.
I have to admit,
commoners really
know their food.
This is tasty!
Now I just need to figure
out where Asta landed.
[NOELLE] What's with that
big concentration of mana?
Hey, everyone, who's hungry?
[gasps]
Yeah, step right up!
Try some of Captain Yami's
famous grilled squid
'cause Yami makes it yummy!
[SEKKE]
Don't listen to him! Ha, ha!
Captain Jack's meat dishes
are second to none!
One bite and they'll
send your taste buds
on a one-way trip
to culinary paradise!
That's right, you've never
had anything like it!
It's food for the
body and the soul!
Come and get it.
Hah!
What's goin' on out there, kid?
If you don't work on that
sales pitch and bring in
some more customers,
you're gonna be
the one gettin' grilled!
Right! I'm on it.
Hey there, mister, what do ya
say to some delicious squid?
The price is fair,
and the flavor
is totally ink-credible,
I squid you not!
Come on...
Hey, rookies!
If you three don't
draw in some business,
I'm going to carve you up next.
Ro- ha ger! All right,
now who's hungry?
Come have a taste!
Help me or we'll
all be lunchmeat!
--[APHRO] Please buy our food!
--[PHATI] We're gonna die!
Who wants some grilled squid?
[SEKKE]
Delicious meat!
[BOTH]
We're begging you!
A customer!
Okay, he flat-out ignored me.
This is only happening
because Captain Jack
decided to get competitive with
the Captain of the Black Bulls.
We can't give this stuff away.
It's so tragic. Ha, ha.
[BOTH laughing]
Did you say something?
--[SEKKE] Mm, so delicious!
--[APHRO] Get it while it's hot!
Look, it's not like
they're poisoned!
[NOELLE] Forget the stagnant
mana, what are you doing?
You gotta help me
out here, Noelle!
What? Oh, hey. The ha, ha guy.
Greetings, fair maiden!
I'd prefer it if you didn't
call me "ha, ha guy."
My name is Sekke Bronzazza!
[NOELLE]
Yeah, whatever, I don't care.
Anyway, what are you doing with
this Sekke person,
or whoever he is?
[ASTA]
Captain Yami...
[SEKKE, APHRO, PHATI]
...and Captain Jack are...
[JACK cackles]
I always knew that we'd end up
settling the score eventually.
[growls]
Your concession stand or mine.
Let's see who can sell
the most food! Get ready!
No one's gonna buy
from a freak like you!
Hurl your insults now,
because when you lose,
I'll flay you alive!
You're the loser
here, string bean.
And that means you're
about to be wipin' my ass
for the rest of eternity!
That'd be terrifying if
I had a chance of losing.
Let's put an end to this.
[BOTH]
Now!
[ASTA, SEKKE, APHRO, PHATI]
So, yeah.
Really?
That's why we're tryin' to get
all the customers we can!
But neither of us have
sold anything! Ha...
Come on up and get your
grilled violetsnake, folks,
piping hot off the fire.
Sounds good. I'll take--
[YAMI] Don't get distracted
by other stalls.
Yeah, but they
have violetsnake!
My rainbow squid is better.
I risked my life in a storm
off the coast of Raquey
to catch those things with my
years of fishin' experience!
They're the best squid
money can buy!
So don't you dare compare 'em
to those damn purple worms.
Jeez, I'm sorry!
If I lose to Jack, it's
gonna be all your fault,
do you hear me?
[yelps] Come get your
grilled squid here!
Caught off the coast of Raquey
by the Captain himself,
and they're just as good
as the pop-potatoes
from Hage Village! Ow!
You tryin' to ruin my business?
[yelps]
[YAMI] No wonder I haven't
had a single sale today!
[crack]
[ASTA]
Squid. Buy some squid.
[NOELLE]
Oh, no, Asta!
This kid's friggin' useless.
[JACK] Mine were just
as unhelpful. [cackles]
You know, this
method of competition
is a bit too slow,
if you ask me.
That's funny. I was just
thinkin' the exact same thing.
So now what?
I say we do somethin' that's
a little more our style.
[BOTH]
Time to fight to the death!
"The death"?
Look here!
[JACK cackles]
Huh?
[BOTH]
Let's play "Made-Ya-Look!"
This way!
[NOELLE]
Idiots.
Let's change it up!
Your funeral, pal!
[BOTH]
Next game!
[YAMI]
This is goin' nowhere.
[cackles] Come on.
Fight me! For real!
[YAMI] Yeah, you don't
want me to do that.
Am I supposed to be intimidated?
[YAMI] Look, we're
killin' the party here.
Let's take this showdown
somewhere else.
[PHATI, APHRO]
This is a good time to leave.
[NOELLE]
Asta! What's wrong with you?
--[YAMI] Hey.
--Get ahold of yourself,
Dorksta, this is embarrassing!
[YAMI]
Noelle!
What is it?
Go and hunt down Finral for me.
Hey, this is...
I don't think we'll be botherin'
anybody all the way out here.
This squid's got me
feelin' energized,
so you'd better get
ready for a beatin'.
I'm glad you're
enjoying that squid,
because you're about to be
chopped up and fileted as well!
How did I get dragged
into this again?
[NOELLE]
This one's pretty good, too.
Our Captain Jack once
cut a whole mountain
clean in half like
it was nothing!
Sorry, but the Captain of
the Black Bulls doesn't
stand a chance
against defeating him!
[laughs]
Uh, What's the ha, ha guy
all worked up for?
Women tend to be more
flirtatious at festivals.
I'm missing out on a golden
opportunity right now.
Oh, well.
[JULIUS] An all-out duel
between Yami and Jack.
How exciting.
I can't wait to see what
kind of powerful spells
they might show us!
Last chance to walk
away, Jackie-boy.
[cackles] Thanks for the
concern, Yami Suckyhiro,
but under the circumstances,
I think you should be
more worried about yourself.
These blades of mine are just
aching to rip you to shreds!
So let's go!
Last time we fought,
it wasn't a whole lot
of fun for me, since you were
on your last leg, and all.
Wait, who'd ya say
was on their last leg?
You, obviously.
Those punks from Eye
of the Midnight Sun
beat you senseless!
Don't be ridiculous,
that was an act.
I was just gettin' ready
to turn the tables on 'em
the second you showed
up on the scene!
[cackles] Sure ya were.
I can see that you're
feeling pretty confident,
so cutting you to
smithereens is going to be
a real treat for me!
Somebody's gettin' cut,
that's for damn sure!
[FINRAL] Well, these two
are as scary as ever.
[ASTA]
Whoa!
This is awesome--their
ki is through the roof!
[NOELLE] Why can't there be any
normal Magic Knight Captains?
A breathtaking battle is
about to begin! Ha, ha!
[NOELLE]
Again, what's with this guy?
[ALL gasp]
Ha, huh?
Ooh!
Dark Magic:
Dark-Cloaked Black Blade!
[cackles] That's not bad.
Severing Magic: Death Scythe!
Did you see that?
Oh, come on, that was nothing.
We all know Captain Yami has
way more powerful abilities.
That's our Captain Jack! Ha, ha!
[YAMI coughs]
Damn, that was dangerous!
He's okay!
That's right, his
Lightless Slash allows him
to draw in his opponent's
magic attacks.
So, that's why Captain Jack
couldn't hurt him!
We never doubted you
for a second, Captain!
Now we're talking!
Both Yami and Jack have such
incredible magical prowess!
Why dontcha let me
show you somethin'?
I just happen to have
an ace in the hole.
Oh, well then, let's see it!
[YAMI] During that
Underwater Temple mission,
I awakened a brand new spell.
Now I even scare myself.
[cackles] That
sounds interesting.
Show me what you've got then!
Did he say "new spell"?
No, he wouldn't.
What's all this?
[gasps] He's gonna
use that on him?
This is bad news, Finral.
Don't you think you'd better
put a stop to it soon?
What? Me?
That spell's too
serious for just this!
You're right, Jack is a
Magic Knight Captain.
We can't let Yami hit him
with something that deadly!
[FINRAL]
Yeah, good point.
[NOELLE]
If one of them goes down,
someone'll be held responsible!
Besides, the Clover Kingdom's
defenses will suffer
without them, and
then what'll happen?
Something bad?
What if the
Diamond Kingdom army
or the Eye of the Midnight Sun
decides to attack us?
[gasps]
If you don't stop this now,
then it's on your head!
You'd blame me for that?
A- ha ll your fa- ha lt!
Do something!
Ugh, this guy's the worst.
You will fix this.
It is a royal command!
Oh, You love using
that, don't you?
[FINRAL] She's right, though.
I have to intervene.
We can't afford to
lose one of them.
When he first cast
Dimension Slash.
I thought the cave
would fall in.
If it does...
[FINRAL]
...we're all screwed.
I'm the highest-ranking Knight
here, so it's up to me!
Hey, I think you'd better stop
this right now, Captain Yami--
[YAMI]
No!
[ASTA]
Finral!
Mind your own business!
Talk about being useless.
Indeed, that was
utterly shameful!
You're not exactly
helping either.
Bring it on.
After you.
[YAMI]
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked.
[JACK]
Severing Magic:
--[JACK] Go, Death Scythe!
--[YAMI] Dimension Slash!
[ALL gasp]
Time-Binding Magic:
Chrono Stasis.
[JULIUS] I would have liked
to see that new spell.
But unfortunately, as Asta and
friends so wisely concluded,
we shouldn't allow
such harm to befall
our Magic Knight Captains,
nor should we risk
the cave collapsing in on itself
from the impact,
for that matter.
We'll just save Dimension
Slash for another time.
[MARX]
Your Majesty!
Where did you go now?
Oh, hello, Marx.
I've been out observing
something interesting.
We're much too busy for
fun and games, sir.
We have to prepare
for the announcement
of the Magic Knights'
rankings during
the Star Festival this evening!
Oh, is that today?
Would you please try
to be reasonable?
Our nation's King is waiting!
You must return at once!
It isn't healthy for you
to be so uptight, you know.
Do try to relax more, Marx.
It's because of you!
Well, it would appear that
I am needed elsewhere.
I'm sure we'll meet again soon.
Ah!
Before I take my leave,
let's be sure to prevent
these two from fighting anymore.
Now let's see here. There,
that should do the trick.
[YAMI]
Dimension Slash--
[JACK]
Go, Death Scythe!
What just happened?
[YAMI]
Uh...
Put some pants on, ya sicko!
[cackles] Back at you!
Keh.
[YAMI, JACK laugh]
[YAMI]
Man. I feel pretty stupid now.
Stop making me laugh, Yami.
I think I've lost
my urge for slashing.
So, is it over?
Whew, that's a relief.
Now I won't have to worry about
getting blamed for
anything! And, you two!
What would you have done
if somebody had died?
[BOTH]
You idiot!
We all know this guy wouldn't
go down that easily!
Ah.
[FINRAL]
You're missing the point!
The closer people are,
the more they fight.
Just make sure to do
it responsibly! Ha, ha!
Look, your little
schtick is getting old.
[JACK cackles]
Hey, this is decent.
Your food isn't
half bad, either.
Well, I'm glad you think so.
Gimme a minute and I'll whip
up some dessert for you.
Why are you standing there?
Go get the thing!
Yes, Captain.
[JACK]
Watch and learn.
[SEKKE]
It's so co- ho ld!
Wow. That's impressive.
[JACK]
Give it a try.
[YAMI]
Thank you.
[NOELLE] They fight because
they're so close, huh?
Maybe Sekke was right.
Uh. Hey, Asta.
Look, if you argue with
me once in a while,
I guess I don't mind too much.
Uh, okay. Huh.
Yeah, I think I'm
gonna go and see
what everyone else is up to.
Eh, we might as well call
it a draw for the day.
That puts me at 53 wins,
no losses, and 34 draws.
I don't think so.
Because by my count,
we're at 98 wins, no losses,
and one draw for me.
Oh, I'm sorry, I meant
to say I've got no losses
and a 156 wins.
Then I've got 567 wins!
No way!
I can prove it!
If you wanna settle the score
once and for all,
we can do it right now!
I thought you'd never ask.
Bring it, shrimp!
Come and get me, musclehead!
Again? Hurry, Asta,
you have to stop them!
Why me?
Because you're the
only one here!
You're here, aren't ya?
I can't, I'm royalty!
Wait a minute, let's
all ca- ha lm down and--
Shut up!
[NOELLE] See, now there's
really no one else!
If you say so.
Here's the thing, Captain
Yami and Captain Jack.
We came to the festival
to have a good time,
not beat each other up,
so could you maybe
just try to get along,
for today? Pretty please?
[YAMI]
Look, kid.
Don't butt in!
[ASTA screams]
Asta, come back!
[KAHONO]
Thank you so much!
You've been such
a wonderful audience!
Just wait and see!
One day, we'll become
famous pop stars!
The singing, dancing,
magic-using idols.
Kahono!
And Kiato!
[KAHONO, KIATO]
We look forward to your support!
And making a lot
of money! A whole lot!
[ASTA screaming]
Hey, Kiato! Hey, Kahono!
Asta?
[VANESSA sighs]
There you are, Finral.
I was starting to wonder
what you were up to.
Collecting rejections, I assume?
I mean, that is a
thing that happened.
But there's a lot more
to the story, too.
Oh, is that so?
[FINRAL]
Yeah, I'm exhausted.
Aw, loosen up,
the Star Festival
is just getting started!
[FINRAL]
Oh, thanks.
[VANESSA] Go on.
Drink up, sweetie. Cheers!
Eh, might as well.
[mumbling] I know what happened.
Captain Yami must've
summoned you
and ordered you to use
your Spatial Magic.
That must've been rough on you,
so here's to a job well done.
[screaming]
Are you okay, son?
[ASTA] Sheesh, Captain
Yami, did ya have to
throw me that far?
He survived that?
Wow, talk about resilient.
Where the heck am I now?
I gotta hurry and get
back to the others.
Huh?
[ADMIRER 68A]
She's so beautiful!
[ADMIRER 68B]
Look at her!
[ADMIRER 68C]
She must come from money.
[ADMIRER 68A] Hey, why don't
you go talk to her?
[ADMIRER 68B]
No way, I can't!
[ASTA]
They're right, she is pretty.
I betcha Finral would go crazy!
[ASTA]
Wait a second.
I think I've seen her before.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[YAMI]
"Grilled Squid."
[YAMI] Today I'm gonna
show you how to prepare
this tasty grilled squid.
[BOTH]
Yay!
It's so easy, anyone can do it.
But you're not going to cheat
and use magic like that one
chef did before, are you?
What? Just watch.
First, pull out the guts
and cut slits into it.
[ASTA]
Real directions!
[YAMI]
Yeah!
Then you season it with salt,
sugar, mirin, and ginger.
Okay.
[YAMI]
Then grill it.
[BOTH]
Normal cooking!
[YAMI]
And, done.
[BOTH]
Yummy!
There ya have it.
Grilled delicious squid
that anyone can make.
No joke this time.
[FINRAL]
Festivals are great!
Girls are way more in the
mood to be flirted with here!
I swear, this is
gonna be my shot!
Black Clover , Page 69:
"The Briar Maiden's Melancholy."
Whoa, Captain Charlotte's
got makeup on!
She's even hotter than normal!