[NARRATOR] Within the clover's
fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
[NARRATOR] Asta, born
unable to harness mana,
was granted the
power of Anti-magic
from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability
to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members
of Spade Kingdom's
Dark Triad also possess
powers from the devils
of the underworld and used them
to launch an invasion on
their neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from
his belief in himself
and from the support
of his friends,
Asta continues to fight for
the safety of this world.
[NARRATOR] Asta and the others
took over the town of Tolon,
one of Spade's bases, and
returned to the Heart Kingdom.
However, they weren't
able to rest for long.
Charmy's power and
appetite had increased
during her training,
and, along with a group
of various wild animals,
she came close to devouring
all of the food in the forest.
[RILL] Picture Magic:
Invasion of Heat-Infused Ice!
[RILL, ASTA yell]
[NARRATOR]
Peace was briefly restored.
Meanwhile, Yuno returned to his
home village of Hage after
receiving a strange message,
and heard some unexpected news
from the man he met there.
[RALPH] You belong to the
House of Grinberryall.
Its scion, the prince
of the Spade Kingdom!
[DAVID]
Where's the vice captain?
[GOLDEN DAWN 154A]
Apparently, he got a message
from his hometown, so he
had to finish up a mission
and hurry back there.
[GOLDEN DAWN 154AA]
He's always so efficient.
He is from Hage, isn't he?
That village out in the boonies?
Uh-huh!
With the amount of magic
he has, it's hard to believe
that he comes from
the Forsaken Realm.
Who cares where he's from?
What matters is that Yuno's an
extremely talented Magic Knight!
Uh-oh. So that's how it is, huh?
Sorry?
[DAVID]
You'd better get in line.
Wha...?
[DAVID] Yuno has insane fan
clubs all over the kingdom,
just so you know.
Hey, shut up,
it isn't like that!
He is amazing, though.
If he made VC in just a year
and a half, then I'm sure
he'll end up becoming
the Wizard King one day.
Yuno is what?
He's the prince of
the Spade Kingdom?
I mean, I knew he was special,
but the boy was actually
royalty all along?
This is incredible!
It's a little surprising,
but I did always
have a sneaking
suspicion, deep down!
Yuno: Prince Charming!
[squeals]
You're so loud.
[laughs]
So that's where that elegant,
sophisticated air comes from!
What is this creature?
I am the Wind Spirit Sylph,
one of the Four Great Spirits!
Oh, and I'm closer to Yuno
than anyone else is!
So you control
the Wind Spirit?
You're amazing, Prince Yuno!
Wait a minute. Then,
what does this make Asta?
Who's Asta?
[HIGH PRIEST] The other
child who was left here
at the same time.
They were side-by-side!
Oh. I'm sorry.
I'm not familiar.
All I know is that
you are Prince Yuno
of the Spade Kingdom!
Hold on. This is going too fast.
You're saying I'm
some kind of prince?
Yes!
If I was someone that important,
then why was I abandoned at a
church in the Clover Kingdom?
Well, you see...
[YUNO]
Let me change the question.
Who are you,
and why are you here?
Right, I should've said.
My name is Ralph.
And my purpose here
is to tell you the truth
about who you are.
I traveled through the
strong magic region,
carrying the thoughts and
mana of my brethren with me,
just as my father did.
Here.
[RALPH]
Flame Magic: Trace Mirage.
Once you see this,
you'll understand.
Where am I?
[RALPH] They say, on that day,
a beam of light cut through
the clouds that hovered
above the Spade Kingdom.
It seemed like a sign
that a brighter future
was just over the horizon.
[RALPH'S FATHER]
My King.
Worrying won't do any good, sir.
--You're right.
--[BABY cries]
The child has arrived!
[MIDWIFE 160A]
He's a healthy baby boy!
I'm so grateful you've
come into my life.
My beautiful son.
[LOYCE]
Ciel. My love.
I know you're exhausted.
[CIEL]
Darling.
I obtained this
magic stone long ago
when I was traveling through
the strong magic region.
[LOYCE]
It'll protect Yuno.
Is that his name, then?
[LOYCE] "Yuno if it's a boy."
I believe that's what you said.
Yes!
[MAN 160A]
He's here! The prince is born!
Our kingdom now has an heir!
The prince of the Spade
Kingdom is born at last!
[RALPH] The festivities carried
on well into the night.
Your birth was truly a ray
of hope that warmed
the bitter, cold winter that had
isolated our land for so long.
Everyone always smiled
whenever they were
in your presence.
[crying]
Easy there!
How do I calm him down?
[laughs] The First
Division Captain
of the Mage Defense Force
can't handle a kid, huh?
Did you forget
what you learned
from raising your
own son, or what?
Well, for the most part,
my wife handled
this sort of thing.
[YUNO crying]
Hey! I got him to stop crying!
King Loyce and Queen Ciel.
Wow, talk about a great legacy!
Yeah. This kid's gonna be
a way stronger mage
than you are in no time.
[FRIEND 160A]
Hey, you watch your mouth!
[WOMAN 160D] Prince Yuno
really is a sweet child!
Things are peaceful for now,
and it's our job to
ensure that continues.
My son, one day you'll join
the Mage Defense Force,
and protect Prince Yuno
with your very life.
Yes, Father!
[YUNO whimpering]
[LOYCE]
He's stopped crying.
Yes.
Do you think he's
going to be all right?
[CIEL]
Huh?
Well, he's very sensitive.
Someday, he'll need to be
strong enough to take my place
as the ruler of this kingdom.
[laughs]
What's wrong?
He's just an infant, darling.
Isn't it a little early
to concern ourselves
with things like that?
You think so?
[CIEL]
It's much too soon.
Right, crybaby?
[RALPH]
Those were such happy times.
None of us could've predicted
they were about to
come to a sudden end.
[ROYAL 160A] The Zogratis
siblings have returned!
[LOYCE] Your subjugation
mission was a success.
Now, please take
some time to recover.
We need you at your best
to maintain peace
in the Spade Kingdom.
For peace. Yes, of course.
As you wish, sire.
Those three siblings.
Keep a close eye on them.
But why do you say that, Father?
I have a bad feeling.
[RALPH]
Oh.
Loyce, Darling.
Did those three kill
that group of rebels?
[LOYCE]
Yes.
Were they acting
on orders from you?
[LOYCE]
Don't be absurd!
[cries]
[CIEL]
There, there, it's all right!
For some reason,
I just don't trust them.
[RALPH]
I wonder why Father said that.
All I know is nothing will
shake my loyalty to this land!
[RALPH grunts]
[RALPH'S BUDDY 160A] Hey, Ralph,
you ready to take a break?
Yeah. Might as well.
Thanks, buddy.
[RALPH] Those three turned out
to be the Dark Triad.
If I had listened
to my father's words,
we may have been able to
avoid that terrible tragedy.
[VOICE 160A]
Treason!
[VOICE 160B] The Zogratis
siblings are attacking
the castle!
This is great! [giggles]
You traitors!
Stop right there!
Oh, boy, I'm so excited! Yay!
I get to stack up
even more dead bodies!
I don't believe it.
[MAGE 160A] They're wiping out
the entire Mage Defense Force!
We can't stop them!
They're too strong!
It was true all along;
those three have been
bestowed with the power
of the underworld!
[DANTE chuckles]
Dante. How could you?
[RALPH] Father! Where are
the king and queen?
Are they...?
The kingdom's future
was left with me.
They're all just so weak!
It's kinda boring, honestly.
Then I'll buy us
some time. Hurry!
Don't you think so?
I suppose.
Thank you.
I swore I'd protect him
with my life.
Make sure you survive!
I will, Father!
[RALPH yells]
[RALPH] That night was the
last time I ever saw him.
[MAGE 160A]
Is the prince all right?
Yes.
He's not safe here.
If they found him, they most
likely wouldn't kill him, but...
[RALPH'S FATHER]
They'll kidnap him, for sure.
Exactly, they have
no right to the throne,
so they'll try
to take him alive.
[RALPH'S FATHER] What makes
you think it's the throne
those villains are after?
What else could it be?
Couldn't say.
But I sense that their
intentions are deeply sinister.
We can't let them
have Prince Yuno.
The Zogratis siblings know
all of this kingdom's secrets,
just as we do.
We must leave, now.
Do as we discussed!
[PURSUER 160A] They've gone
in three separate directions!
[whimpers]
Don't cry.
Everything's all right.
After all, I swore on my life
that I'd always keep you safe.
And I'm sure
that stone will help
protect you, as well.
[YUNO crying]
The strong magic region!
There's no way he'll make it!
What should we do, sir?
[ZENON]
Doesn't matter.
But if the prince lives,
we'll have a problem, won't we?
If that concerns you,
then kill him.
[BOTH]
Er, right!
[RALPH'S FATHER panting]
[RALPH'S FATHER] I will
protect you, whatever it takes!
[RALPH'S FATHER]
Prince Yuno!
That's... a church.
He'll be safe there.
[RALPH'S FATHER] This will be my
final spell for you, my prince.
Now, live, and be strong!
[RALPH'S FATHER]
That was fast.
[RALPH'S FATHER] I led them
far away from the church.
They shouldn't be able
to find him now.
Stay safe, Prince Yuno.
I refuse to be killed by you!
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH scream]
[RALPH'S FATHER] Ralph.
The future is in your hands.
[YUNO gasps]
[LILY]
Yuno.
Considering the massive
amount of mana you have,
I assume you're able to see
that everything I showed you
actually happened.
There were no lies
in any part of it.
Yeah, well, that's exactly
what a liar would say!
Don't believe this creep, Yuno!
My family served the
House of Grinberryall
for generations.
It's not just me.
You have countless subjects
praying for your
safety, your Highness.
And they're in grave danger!
[chiming]
What's wrong?
[DAVID]
There's trouble, sir!
[GOLDEN DAWN 154A] The
headquarters is under attack!
Please help us!
Oh, no!
We're allowed to have
as much fun as we want.
Right, Lord Zenon?
As long as you leave the
arcane-stage Magic Knight alive.
Yuno?
[RALPH]
Please wait, sir!
If they were able to enter
the Clover Kingdom that easily,
they must be the Dark Triad,
or someone just as strong!
You can't be rash!
Sorry, but I am the vice
captain of the Golden Dawn!
[YUNO grunts]
[RALPH]
Prince Yuno! I'll go, too!
I will--
[LILY]
No, you need to stay in bed.
Yuno.
Let me guess, you look scary
'cause you're thinking
about all the different
ways you're gonna
punish the bad guys.
I'm right, aren't I?
I'm so smart!
[RALPH] You belong to the
House of Grinberryall.
[RALPH] Its scion, the prince
of the Spade Kingdom!
[YUNO] Even so, I'm also Yuno
of the Clover Kingdom.
I need to get there faster!
From the looks of them,
they're Spade Kingdom mages!
I don't know how they got here,
but they must be tough
if they made it into
our headquarters!
Teach them a lesson!
Go! Blast 'em with
your attack spells!
What?
What the--?
They're not hurt?
[DAVID]
But where'd the other one go?
[GADEROIS] Come on!
Is that the best you can do?
But I heard you guys
were supposed to be
the toughest squad
in the Clover Kingdom!
Well. Guess I can't blame you.
Only a select few were
good enough to get powers
from the Dark Triad, and we
were at the top of the list!
We're the Dark Disciples!
All of us are stage-zero mages!
Stage zero? No way!
He's gone!
Hey! Stone Magic, just like me!
[GADEROIS yells]
Too bad you're such a weakling!
Shiren--!
[GOLDEN DAWN MAGES groan]
[GOLDEN DAWN 160B screams]
When you've got a devil's power,
it takes your magic
to a new level!
Our army captains can
do about five percent.
But I'm strong enough
to unleash closer to 40!
[GADEROIS] And since
Lord Zenon's possessed...
[GADEROIS]
...he's got upwards of 80!
So here you are.
You're Captain Vangeance
of the Golden Dawn.
We hear you're one
of the few Magic Knights
whose power has reached
the arcane stage.
[WILLIAM]
This mana...
[ALECDORA]
Stop!
Get away from Lord
Vangeance, right now!
Stand down, Alecdora!
They're too powerful!
Last time, I allowed myself
to become possessed,
but this is my chance to stand
up and fight for my captain!
They will kill you!
As a Magic Knight
of the Golden Dawn...
[ALECDORA]
...I will strike you down!
[ALECDORA grunts]
[ALECDORA]
What did he do?
[WILLIAM] World Tree Magic:
Magic Warding Ash!
Lord Vangeance. Thank you.
Devil-possessed or not,
you'll pay dearly for causing
harm to my subordinates!
So that's World
Tree Magic, is it?
Our side could
certainly use that.
I'll be taking you with me.
[ZENON]
Bone Magic: Eternal Fangs.
I'm here!
Someone else joining the fun?
Sorry, buddy, you're
late to the party.
[YUNO] What the hell do
you think you're doing...
...to my comrades?
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[DAVID]
"Yuno's Fan Clubs"!
Who cares where he's from?
What matters is that Yuno's an
extremely talented Magic Knight!
Uh-oh. So that's how it is, huh?
Sorry?
[DAVID]
You'd better get in line.
Wha...?
[DAVID] Yuno has insane fan
clubs all over the kingdom,
just so you know.
Duh, of course I know about
the fan clubs; who do you
think is the president
of the Golden Dawn chapter?
[DAVID]
There's a Golden Dawn chapter?
You said yourself,
they're all over the kingdom,
and this is the squad Yuno's in,
so why wouldn't we have one?
Right.
[GOLDEN DAWN 154AA]
I have buttons, folders,
acrylic statues
every single piece
of Yuno merchandise that exists!
And of course,
I follow his social media!
Wait, really? You mean
Yuno's on the internet?
[YUNO chuckles]
[YUNO]
You monster.
I won't let you do this
to my squadmates!
Black Clover ,
Page 161: "Zenon's Power."
Whether you have the
strength of a devil or not,
mark my words,
I will defeat you!