[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives a magicless
boy named Asta.
This brave young hero devotes
blood, sweat, and tears
to becoming the
next Wizard King.
Though Asta's situation
is practically unheard of,
there are others
residing in this kingdom
who possess at least
a tiny amount of mana,
yet can barely
use spells at all.
They make up a
very small minority,
living their lives
in the shadows.
[NARRATOR]
But, like everyone else,
they do their best to survive.
[MARIE]
Where am I?
What am I doing here?
[MARIE]
Wait, I remember!
[SECREÉ]
You're finally awake.
[MARIE]
It's you.
You're friends with
Asta and my brother!
Yes.
[SECREÉ] Our magic's been sealed,
so we can't escape.
And I borrowed a tracking
device from Asta,
but they took that, too.
Who kidnapped us?
Do you know these people?
[SECREÉ]
Mm-mm.
[SECREÉ] The only thing this
girl and I have in common
is that we were accused
of working with the devil.
They're probably planning
to use us for leverage somehow.
This is all for the
sake of justice.
Yes, indeed, Master Kabwe.
It's our responsibility
to rid this kingdom
of the devil's evil servants,
and to rebuild
what they destroyed.
It shall be done, at all costs.
[CROWD chattering]
There're so many people.
Our kingdom deserves justice,
and the Devil Banishers are
going to make sure we get it!
Kill those traitors, now!
[CROWD]
Yeah!
--[GUY] Just get on with it!
--We want to see blood!
I can't wait for the show!
It serves them right!
This is insane.
[GAUCHE] They'll all die
for disrespecting my angel!
[ZORA]
They sure are amped up
about watching a
couple of girls die.
[GREY]
This is so terrifying!
[GORDON]
Yeah.
Hang in there, you two,
the Black Bulls are
coming to the rescue!
Listen up, everyone,
we got a message
from Julius on the way.
[gasps]
[JULIUS] It looks like all
squads are in position.
The execution's
scheduled for noon,
so we've only got a little
while left to wait.
We don't know their
numbers, but I'm sure
they'll be using a combination
of spells and various drugs.
Though this mission
may prove difficult,
I'll trust you'll do everything
you can to recover the captives.
The Silver Eagles and
the Crimson Lion Kings
will assist with the rescue
and make sure that none of
the civilians in the crowd
are harmed in the process.
The Blue Rose Knights
and Green Praying Mantises
will patrol the
square at all times.
And, given their closeness
to the situation,
the Black Bulls will be
the main squad in charge
of saving the hostages.
Sounds good.
One thing though.
There's a certain
someone over here
who's got nothin' to do
with the mission whatsoever.
I'm guessing he tagged
along out of guilt,
seeing as how his
subordinates are probably
behind this whole mess.
But I think it's
gonna be bad news
if he decides to act on his own.
[JULIUS]
This rescue is top-priority.
Can we trust you'll go along
with our operation, Damnatio?
Yes, that is my intention, sir.
But I need to confirm
something first.
If Asta uses the devil's power
in front of this large crowd,
then it will only create
more anger and confusion.
So I'm asking--
Of course he's not gonna do it.
Did you think we'd
be that stupid?
All right, squad, everyone
but Gauche and the kid,
keep an eye on the square
like we discussed.
These girls are two of our own,
so don't screw up!
[BLACK BULLS]
Right!
Good luck. Be safe.
[MARX] The other squads are
watching over the Noble Realm,
as you requested.
[JULIUS]
Right.
We have to keep in mind that
the execution could be a ruse
to distract us while they
cause trouble elsewhere.
[MARX] We'd better make sure
we put a stop to their plans.
If they carry this out,
it'll throw the kingdom
into an even greater panic.
Yes. It's up to
the Magic Knights.
[MIMOSA] We haven't seen
anything unusual yet.
I hope the rescue
mission goes smoothly.
[KLAUS] With Captain Vangeance
away protecting the border,
we can't contribute much
to the main part of the plan,
but let's be on alert!
[MIMOSA, YUNO]
Right.
Ugh! Why do we have to patrol?
You're the best fighter--
you should be right in
the middle of the action!
The plan's been made,
that's that.
Hey, wait for me, Yuno!
[WOMAN 145AA]
It's almost time!
The purveyors of justice
will soon arrive!
[MAN 145AE]
Forget the Magic Knights
and the Magic Parliament!
Only the Devil Banishers
can set this kingdom right!
[WOMAN 145A]
I agree!
[GUY 145B]
Someone must uphold the law!
[FINRAL] I bet those guys
are in the crowd somewhere!
[NOELLE]
How are we going to find them?
[ZORA]
Man, these people have lost it!
Makes me wonder if they've
all been drugged, too.
[growls] I can't stand this!
Look, Captain, you gotta
let me go down there!
Ooh, can I come with you?
Pipe down!
If you go waltzing in there,
you'll blow the lid
off this whole plan!
Okay, but we can't
just do nothing.
[YAMI] You're the ace
in the hole, kid.
We need to wait for our moment.
Right.
We still haven't seen
any sign of them yet.
Odd.
It's noon now. Where are they?
[bell rings]
[SOL]
I gotta say.
I'm not really seeing
anyone who looks suspicious.
[CHARLOTTE]
Stay on guard.
[SOL]
Will do, Char.
Keh! They're not
even here on time!
[DEMON MASK 142A]
Hey, witch.
[DEMON MASK 144B] If you want
your friends to survive,
then you'll do as we say.
You make one wrong move,
and we'll kill the hostages
before they even get
out in front of the crowd.
[DEMON MASK 142A] Start walking
slowly toward the exit.
[VANESSA] I knew I wouldn't
sense their mana,
but I didn't expect them
to approach me like this!
It's all right.
I'm sure the others can
pull it off without me.
[VANESSA]
Understood.
And there they are.
[KABWE]
Greetings, enemies of the devil!
The time has come to strike
in the name of righteousness!
[KABWE]
We are the Devil Banishers!
Those who wish for
the devil's demise!
[CROWD cheers]
--[GAUCHE] Marie!
--[ASTA] Nero!
Settle down!
Now I can understand
how they were able
to conceal their
mana so completely.
Except that it looks like only
those three are wearing them.
[KABWE] The evidence of this
woman's guilt is obvious!
Notice the pair of
horns on her head!
Proof that she worked with the
devil and used forbidden magic!
[GUY 145C]
How disgusting!
[GUY 145D]
That girl's evil incarnate!
[KABWE] The child next
to her, whose brother
is a former criminal,
is also the devil's servant!
We have undeniable proof
that their actions have
destroyed countless lives!
[GUY 145E] How could anyone
condemn that sweet little face?
[GUY 145F]
Kill them both, now!
[LADY 145A] They should've been
put to death a long time ago!
Lord Damnatio, if that
barrier spell explodes,
it's going to harm a
large number of civilians!
[DAMNATIO] Kabwe. I understand
that you seek justice,
but how can you
expect the innocent
to pay the price for it?
That magic.
Since it's a barrier,
I'm guessing one of
Scale-Boy's lackeys
is responsible.
[KABWE]
But we mustn't forget.
There's one boy who was
possessed by the devil himself,
and we hate him most of all!
That traitor's name...
...is Asta!
[ALL gasp]
[KABWE]
Every drop of blood spilled
by the Eye of the Midnight
Sun is on his hands.
We know that you're
here with us, Asta.
And we want nothing more
than to see you dead!
[MAGNA] It's just like
Captain Yami said.
[NOELLE] Even if Asta
took the blame for that,
they still wouldn't stop this!
[KABWE] However, if you
come forward immediately
and plead guilty, we will allow
your two companions
to walk free.
Nero! Marie!
[KABWE]
Why haven't you responded?
It must mean that you
value your own life
over those of your cohorts.
[LADY 145B]
Of course he does!
[GUY 145I]
That's what a devil would do!
[NOELLE] Asta would never
abandon his friends!
[KABWE]
Very well. We have our answer.
[ASTA]
I'm over here!
[BOTH gasp]
[KABWE]
Good. Now approach the stage.
[YAMI] I don't see Vanessa,
but there's no time
to track her down now.
[DEMON MASK 145D]
You little freak!
That's him, everyone!
He's the villain who
destroyed our kingdom!
[WOMAN 145A]
You murdered my entire family!
[GUY 145J]
Kill him!
[GUY 145K]
Serves him right!
Look, I swear. We don't
work with the devil!
[DEMON MASK 145D]
Shut your mouth, demon!
[BOTH gasp]
[KABWE]
Stop right there.
[KABWE] We'll be confiscating
your grimoire, as well.
What, did that ruin your plans?
We know that you intended to
use Anti-magic to cancel out
the barrier we've set up
around the square.
[GUY 145L]
Come on!
[GUY 145M]
Execute him, already!
If I take the blame,
then you'll let them go?
[KABWE] Well, yes,
that is what I just said.
Then step away from them!
And put down your swords!
[KABWE]
Certainly.
[KABWE] Now, then.
Hand over your grimoire.
[ASTA]
Okay.
[KABWE]
No!
[ONOBY]
What? Two Astas?
All we needed was for you
to look away from the hostages
for a couple of seconds!
[YAMI]
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked,
Lightless Slash!
[CROWD yells]
[yelps]
Yikes, that was
so embarrassing!
[ASTA yells]
[ASTA] Your sleeping potions
won't work this time!
[SIONA]
Paper Magic: Dagger-Folding
Early Summer Rain!
[yells]
Hurry! Now's your chance!
[FINRAL]
Uh--
[SIONA]
Nice try!
[yelps]
[LUCK laughs]
You ready?
Let's go!
Keh, keh. Now it's
getting interesting!
[GUY 145N]
Run!
[DAZU] The others are
buying some time.
[KABWE] Transparency Magic:
Share the Same Fate!
[ASTA]
Nero! Marie!
Come back!
Move it! Get away!
Hey, kid, where are you?
A drug?
Water Magic: Sea Dragon's Lair!
[whimpering]
Something's wrong.
I can't control it!
Do something, it's gonna
close in and squish me!
[gasps]
What happened? And why
don't you have Marie?
Asta went after her.
I'm sorry, I was gonna go, too,
but the smoke's affecting
my eyesight, and I can't
really use my magic.
The traps that I set up
around the square
aren't responding.
Not sure what,
but there's something
in that smoke that
messes with mana.
If that's how they
wanna play, fine!
That's what I'm talkin'
about, Captain Yami!
Way to teach 'em a lesson!
Now help all the
civilians evacuate.
Fall to your knees.
[DEMON MASKS groaning]
Begone!
[YAMI]
They vanished.
[gasps]
Care to say where we're going?
[DEMON MASK 142A]
Nowhere, really.
[DEMON MASK 144B] We happen to
know that your magic grants you
the ability to change
the course of fate,
so all we were trying to do was
to get you away from the square.
I see. Except, even
without altering fate,
I already know that my friends
have set the two hostages free.
Which means I don't have
to cooperate with you.
[DEMON MASK 142A] We know we
can't beat a Magic Knight.
We also know you read the
memories of those you capture.
[DEMON MASK 144B] In other
words, our job is done.
We went into this operation
completely prepared
to sacrifice ourselves.
[VANESSA] They just took their
own lives like it was nothing!
I don't know what their plan is,
but how could it have been
that important to them?
[ASTA]
I feel their ki.
They must be close!
[KABWE]
It's all over.
Chasing us down without thinking
is exactly what we
wanted you to do.
Ha! Fool.
Time to surrender the grimoire!
[BOW] And don't resist, or we'll
exterminate your friends!
Asta.
Don't worry!
We'll get out of this!
[ONOBY cackles]
I'd like to see you try that
without using the devil's power.
Shall we take them away
before the others
arrive, Master Kabwe?
No, I'd rather take
care of them right here.
[gasps]
[DAZU]
That's not what we planned!
The Magic Knights are powerful.
I underestimated their strength.
We were lucky to get this far.
If we want to succeed, then our
safest bet is to kill them now
while we have the chance.
[DAZU]
But, sir!
[DEMON MASK 142B]
You coward!
Why are you so scared?
Don't disrespect him!
[yells]
[DEMON MASK 142B groans]
[DEMON MASK 142B]
You little--!
Nero!
You won't be able
to avoid these!
If you do, they'll
just hit the girl!
Paper Magic:
Dagger-Folding
Early Summer Rain!
What's happening?
This must be them.
The Devil Banishers.
Yuno? Where'd you come from?
[BELL giggles] Oh, we were
just in the neighborhood,
so we figured we would drop by.
It's no biggie!
We were only supposed
to be patrolling,
but I believe Captain Vangeance
would probably want
us to intervene.
Asta! I hope you're not injured!
[ASTA]
I'm fine, just help Nero!
You'll pay for this!
If they hadn't showed up,
we would've had Asta for sure!
We need to retreat
before they catch us!
[ASTA]
Give Nero back!
That's not going to happen.
Now stand down,
or we'll slit her throat!
Really, they're running away?
Unbelievable.
They say that a devil dwells
in the five-leaf grimoire,
so we'll be taking
it off your hands.
No, wait!
Asta.
--They're gone.
--[KLAUS, MIMOSA] Asta!
Make sure Marie's okay, Mimosa.
Sure!
[KLAUS]
So, they took your grimoire.
They really thought
of everything.
[YUNO]
Not everything.
Asta's magic doesn't
come from his grimoire.
What do you mean?
[KLAUS]
I don't follow.
That's right.
I'll get Nero back,
and my grimoire.
Because my magic
is never giving up!
[GAUCHE]
Marie!
Please don't die!
I need my angel with me forever!
Don't leave me behind.
I can't bear it!
She's just sleeping.
Owen says she needs rest,
but she'll wake up later on.
[GAUCHE]
So, she's gonna be okay?
Yes.
[GAUCHE]
Good.
I guess this means
that I owe you again.
[DAMNATIO] Today we discovered
that my subordinates
were indeed responsible
for the kidnappings.
Please allow me to apologize
for my oversight.
You said they had a
strong sense of justice,
but taking a whole
crowd prisoner
doesn't exactly scream
"do-gooders" to me.
I wonder if the Devil Banishers
are being manipulated
by a completely
different entity.
You're right, they did
take Asta's grimoire.
Someone other than Kabwe
could've wanted it
for their own purposes.
[YAMI]
Hey, wait.
You're throwing ideas out there,
and you weren't even
at the first meeting.
After you cried like a baby
and made a big thing out of
proving your loyalty, too!
To clarify:
I was the one who asked him to
go keep an eye on the borders.
If the Spade Kingdom were
to make a move right now,
there'd be chaos.
Everyone, there's something
that I need to show you.
[MARX]
We investigated the memories
of the Devil Banishers
we took into custody.
Apparently, their organization
is largely made up
of paid hires.
[knocking]
[MAGE 143A] I apologize
for the interruption!
What's wrong?
[MAGE 143A] We've just received
a message from Kabwe!
Kabwe?
We're listening. Where are you?
[KABWE groaning]
It's a lie.
These people aren't trying to
bring about the devil's demise.
Not at all.
The truth is that...
...they're after
the devil's power!
What do you mean?
[KABWE] This organization
actually worships the devil.
They're called Devil Believers!
[GAUCHE] Ah, thank goodness
my angel's back safe!
But this isn't over yet.
Black Clover , Page 146:
"Those Who Worship the Devil."
I won't stop till I've beaten
the crap out of those freaks!