[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[ASTA] Here we go!
Into to the Shadow Palace!
[NARRATOR] In order to
save the souls of those
who had reincarnated as elves,
Asta and the others
stormed the Shadow Palace.
[ASTA]
These paintings.
[RILL]
Hey there!
[ASTA]
It's Rill!
Here's an idea.
How 'bout I wake
you up right now?
[NARRATOR]
Inside the Shadow Palace,
Asta and Mimosa
encountered Rill,
while Noelle met Fana.
You again?
I don't understand this--
why are you here?
I may be Fana, but I'm
a much different Fana
than the one you remember.
[MEREOLEONA] I'm about to
teach you the importance
of respecting your elders,
you mangy brat.
[NARRATOR]
Mereoleona faced off with Vetto,
and Fuegoleon with Kaiser.
Both found themselves
in a heated battle.
[KAISER]
Begone!
You're mine, human!
[BOTH]
Not me.
[FUEGOLEON]
I must prevail!
[MEREOLEONA]
I have to be strong!
[FUEGOLEON,MEREOLEONA yell]
[NOELLE grunts]
[FANA]
Ha!
[FANA yells]
[FANA]
How did I lose her?
[NOELLE grunts]
[NOELLE] I may not be
using my Valkyrie Armor
to its fullest potential yet,
but I can still maneuver
better than she can.
She must be Fana the Hateful
in her final form,
the one who also possessed Fana
of the Diamond Kingdom.
In that case...
Up until this moment,
I've been afraid of using
its full power,
focusing on control instead,
and holding back in my strikes.
But, now it's time
to go all out!
[NOELLE] Water Creation
Magic: Sea Dragon's...
...Roar!
[NOELLE panting]
[gasps, screams] Oh, no!
I am so sorry!
[gasps]
[FANA] Flame Recovery Magic:
Phoenix Robe.
Oh, wow, that attack
was pretty intense!
And it appears I've
lost my clothes again.
[gasps]
[FANA]
Pretty neat, huh?
The forbidden magic
we used allows us to draw
on the power of the other world
to cast supernatural spells.
[NOELLE]
This isn't good!
Apologies. I was getting
kinda sick of dying.
[NOELLE] How am I supposed
to win against that?
[PAINTED BEASTS roaring]
[ASTA grunts]
[yells]
[MIMOSA] Plant Magic:
Magic Cannon Flower!
[PAINTED BEASTS growling]
[ASTA]
It never ends! Aw, man.
No time to switch
into my dark form!
And even if I could pull it off,
if I can't land a hit
on Rill, what's the point?
What's this?
Oh, you're still alive?
[PAINTED BEAST D growling]
[MIMOSA]
This isn't going well.
[gasps]
Thanks, Asta! I'm so
sorry! I'll heal you--
Thanks, but it doesn't
look like we're gonna
get a break anytime soon.
I know! Mimosa,
hop up onto my back,
then use some vines
to tie us together!
[MIMOSA]
Huh?
Combining's the only
chance we've got, here!
What? Combining?
[ASTA]
Hurry!
[MIMOSA]
Uh, right!
Plant Recovery Magic:
Princess-Healing Flower Robe!
Okay, then! Come at us!
[MAGIC KNIGHTS yelling]
[ELF 114 grunts]
[ROUGE meows]
[LUCK]
Whoopsie!
That's no good.
[VANESSA] This group of elves
is especially strong.
We've gotten close,
but we haven't managed
to strike a decisive
blow just yet!
Sorry, you missed me!
[LUCK]
This magic.
Expand your Mana Zones,
form magic paths!
Everyone, join the Magic
Knights already fighting.
Focus your energy
on supporting them
with long-range offensive
spells. Right, let's go!
Whoa!
He's so...
He's beautiful.
His looks are no match
for mine, but still.
He's just stunning.
There's no way.
[ZORA] How could he gather
all the Magic Knights
scattered throughout
the kingdom so quickly?
It's not possible.
[CHARMY]
Yuno! I'm so glad you're here!
I made this.
Please, help yourself!
This doesn't seem
like the time.
[BELL]
Yeah, now shoo!
What are you doing here, anyway?
[CHARMY chuckles]
The castle was in trouble,
so I came to offer
my culinary services.
[YUNO gasps]
[YUNO] This food.
It can restore my magic?
Thank you. That's amazing.
[YUNO echoing]
[CHARMY]
He said it was amazing!
My prince liked his provisions!
I could die happy!
[YUNO]
What's going on?
[CHARMY] Well, you see, Asta
and the captains are fighting
the ultimate battle against
all the enemy's strongest
team members inside
that pitch-black castle,
but, unfortunately the
entrance is already closed.
[YUNO]
So, Asta's fighting in there?
That light. What do
you think it is?
[BELL]
Hey, let go!
Get away from Yuno this instant!
[CHARMY] But he hasn't even
had his dessert yet!
[BELL] Oh, shut your mouth!
I'll be his dessert!
[CHARMY] I vow to follow you
to the ends of the world
and cook you delicious food!
[YUNO]
Sit tight, Asta.
Wait, am I seeing things?
Asta's hot rival friend
just got inside.
Yeah, so did Charmy. No fair.
[CHARMY screaming]
Yuno? Where could
he have run off to?
And what was that weird
place we just went through?
Also, where am I now?
[CHARMY]
Oh, I'm in hell.
[PAINTED BEASTS roaring]
Oh, no! What the actual
heck is this place?
[ASTA]
Charmy?!
[CHARMY]
Asta!
How did you get in?
[CHARMY]
Uh! I have no idea!
I was just hanging onto Yuno,
trying to feed him
and now I'm here!
[CHARMY yelps]
Uh! Yuno's inside, too?
Where could you
have gone to, Yuno?
What is all of this?
[ASTA]
These monsters are spells.
Rill drew all of them.
We have to do
something to stop him!
[MIMOSA]
Is that...?
[ASTA]
Charmy? Oh, no.
[RILL] That's not it.
It just isn't right.
This isn't what I want!
I drew some monsters
because I thought
they'd be a fitting
end to humanity.
But, in fact,
I actually wanna draw
something prettier.
That's the truth.
I don't wanna create art
like this; it's so ugly.
This is all the humans'
fault! They did this!
Look at you, you're all upset.
Maybe you're in a bad mood
'cause you're hungry. Ah?
A little food might
calm you right down.
Here.
[ASTA gasps]
[MIMOSA]
When did she...?
[RILL]
Shut up!
[gasps]
Get away from me, you cretin.
I would never eat anything
that was made by human hands.
Rude.
[RILL]
Huh?
Who do you think you are?
[CHARMY] Cotton Creation Magic:
Strike of the Sleeping Sheep!
If I want to create,
I must first destroy!
[RILL]
I'll tear them down!
The humans and everything
they've built!
[ASTA]
She's...
Charmy! No!
Are you okay?
[ASTA]
Wait, what's going on?
[MIMOSA]
What is this mana?
[ASTA]
Is-Is it her?
[WOLF]
Hey. Can I come out now?
[MIMOSA] What is this magic?
It's not normal.
It doesn't feel...
entirely human.
[WOLF growls]
[ASTA]
No way! Why did she get bigger?
[RILL] This seems familiar.
I've felt this magic before.
It means you were born
to a human and a dwarf.
Then, you have characteristics
of both. You're a hybrid!
So, she's a human...
...and a dwarf?
Wait. You... You're
saying I'm part Dwarf?
[ASTA]
She didn't know, either?
[BOTH] Hold on just a second.
What even is a dwarf?
What are they?
Dwarves are-- Well.
I, uh, only know from the
folktales our elderly butler
used to tell us, mind you.
They lived separate
from the elves,
but like them, they're
a race from long ago
who possessed special powers.
Whoa, hold on--
Weren't you a sheep
just a minute ago?
Shut up.
When did you learn to speak?
At the moment, that's the
least of our concerns.
Well. I admit you have a point.
We can talk later.
I'm starving, so let's eat.
[WOLF growls]
[RILL] You are so annoying.
And, half-dwarf or no,
if you think that you
can stand in my way,
I'll disappear you!
Yeah. Make more monsters, elf.
[WOLF]
My appetite's insatiable!
[CHARMY]
Food Magic: Glutton's Banquet!
Whoa. That thing
is eating magic!
Aren't her spells
usually a lot fluffier?
This isn't good.
[RILL]
I've heard of this before.
That hybrids can end up
with two distinct magical
attributes. Now what?
When that wolf eats my
magic, it becomes hers!
And it's eating so fast!
Way faster than I can draw!
I refuse to let your appetite
wipe out my imagination!
You hear me?
[CHARMY]
I'll make you regret it.
Nobody wastes the food I make!
Eat this! That's
for the protein!
And this! That one's
for the fat!
[RILL] I know they're just
punches enhanced by magic,
but they're so powerful!
And now... This is for
the wasted carbs!
Oh, you cannot be serious.
Do you actually imagine
this could be enough
to get rid of my
hatred for humans?
Oh, yeah?
I'm not even close
to being done!
This is for the vitamins!
This is for the fiber!
This is for the collagen!
This is for the sodium!
What is happening?
Uh. She's totally lost it!
Hey, Asta! You go on ahead!
I gotta pound a
lesson about wasting
perfectly good food
into this jerk's brain!
[ASTA]
We'd better hurry.
Okay! We're countin'
on you, Charmy!
[CHARMY]
Just leave it to me!
[ASTA]
Mimosa! Which way?
There were a number
of paths before,
but a few of them
have gotten blocked
because of all the crazy
fighting. If we could go up...
We should try
getting out that way!
[ASTA]
Right!
[FANA laughs]
I'm sorry.
You can't win, no matter
how much you attack.
[NOELLE gasps]
Get ready, because
I'm gonna reduce you
to ashes real soon!
[NOELLE] I never thought I'd
say this, but I miss Asta!
Asta! Huh?
[cackles] Well, well, well.
This chick seems like
she wants to get sliced!
Ugh, did it really
have to be you?
'Scuse me?
Are you telling me we got
a problem here, little girl?
Huh?
[ASTA]
Who's that?
[MIMOSA]
It's David!
He's a fellow member
of the Golden Dawn.
He was possessed by an elf,
like most of the squad was.
Guess somebody already
knocked him out.
All right. Lucky break.
[MIMOSA] There are faint
traces of magic here.
I can sense them now.
But, it's weird.
It doesn't seem to belong
to humans or elves.
What's going on?
I'll use Magic Flower
Guidepost again.
[MIMOSA]
What's this?
Underneath the strongest
point, there's a space
with something in it
that looks like a pedestal.
There seem to be
three elves there!
And I think that magic
might be... It's Yuno!
Let's go, then!
Wait for me, Yuno!
[RHYA]
Well, this is quite a surprise.
We sent Ado's group to
pick you up, but, instead,
you took them out and
got here on your own.
I mean, don't get me wrong,
I'm glad you were able to
get here safely and all that.
So, congrats.
Hand over that magic stone.
Immediately, please.
I've been waiting
for this moment.
[RHYA] As usual, Ronne,
you're so quiet that
I can't even understand
what you're saying!
[PATRY] Finally, everything
we've lost will be restored.
Including our future.
[PATRY]
And Licht's smile.
[PATRY] Light Creation Magic:
Light Swords of Conviction.
[RHYA] Copy Light Magic:
[YUNO] Mana Zone:
Spirit's Hushed Dance.
What's this?
[PATRY] How did he manage
to evade all those attacks?
[YUNO]
Mana Zone: Spirit Storm Double!
[RHYA]
In the time it took to get here,
he managed to
level up his power,
both as a human and
as an elf. This kid.
In terms of sheer talent,
he might surpass even Licht.
[YUNO gasps]
[YUNO] I don't understand
why my Mana Zone
couldn't detect him.
It wasn't super speed.
He just suddenly
appeared! Again!
No. He made me move.
He can forcibly change
someone's position,
even if he's only
touched them once!
[YUNO] I don't know if
it's a magic stone or not,
but that belongs to me.
Give it back!
[RHYA]
Nice job, Ronne!
I see you're still
as quick as always.
No one could ever
beat you at tag.
And, now, we can finally
make things right.
Indeed.
[RHYA]
I can tell when someone's lying.
And I wonder why you told
a lie just now. Ronne?
What's going on?
[RHYA]
Who the hell are you?
Huh?
[growling]
[RHYA]
Don't tell me.
This reincarnation...
It can't be.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[RHYA] "I Can Tell
When Someone's Lying."
You really can tell
when someone's lying,
can't you, Rhya?
Oh, yeah. Sure can spot a liar.
[PATRY] So, if a liar told you
flat-out that they were a liar,
you'd be able to figure out
if that's true or not.
Have I got it right?
[RHYA] Yeah. 'Cause I can
tell when someone's lying.
I mean, if a liar is telling
you that they're lying,
they might honestly just be
telling you that they're lying,
but it can be hard
to tell with a liar.
But, like, they could be
lying about being a liar,
which would mean
they're being honest,
and honest people don't
typically lie about anything.
So that would make them
a liar, wouldn't it?
But liars wouldn't just come out
and say that they're liars.
They usually try to hide that,
so that they can use it
to their advantage.
So, um. I don't know.
I've officially confused myself.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know!
This is a famous
paradox, you see.
You all should think
about it, too.
[RHYA]
That guy isn't Ronne.
This magic.
Who could this man be?
Next time on Black Clover ,
Page 115: "Mastermind."
Wait. What have we even been
trying to do this whole time?