[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives a magicless
boy named Asta.
This brave young hero devotes
blood, sweat, and tears
to becoming the
next Wizard King.
Though Asta's situation
is practically unheard of,
there are others
residing in this kingdom
who possess at least
a tiny amount of mana
yet can barely
use spells at all.
They make up a very
small minority,
living their lives
in the shadows.
[NARRATOR]
But, like everyone else,
they do their best to survive.
[NARRATOR] The group of
kidnappers led by Dazu Tayak
and Bow Nocde, who had
originally identified themselves
as the Devil Banishers,
were later revealed
to be called the
Devil Believers:
those who worship the devil.
After their true intentions
were made known,
the Devil Believers murdered
Kabwe and the other
Magic Parliament members
whom they had manipulated.
Then left with Nero
and Asta's grimoire.
So what, you think they might
wanna offer it Nero as a gift?
Huh. That reminds me,
they still have the
kid's grimoire, too.
[JULIUS]
Once they pay tribute,
they'll defect to
the Spade Kingdom.
Or rather, the devil inside it.
Right. Good luck.
[NARRATOR]
Asta and the other Black Bulls
set out after the
Devil Believers.
[MAGNA] It's gonna be pretty
difficult to catch up to them
if they managed to make it past
Breed Mountain in this weather.
[gasps] Look down there.
I think I see them!
[NARRATOR] They finally
managed to catch up.
However...
How are there so many?
This is insane.
[BOW]
How lovely.
The sunset.
[DAZU]
Oh, yes, of course.
I honestly hadn't noticed it.
[BOW] It only takes a few brief
moments for the sun to go down,
but it always shines
so brilliantly
until the very last second.
It's such a peaceful thing
to watch, don't you think?
Yes.
Sorry, is your name Bow Nocde?
You live in the forest on
the outskirts of town, right?
[BOW]
You've heard of me?
[DAZU] Yes, my mother-in-law's
mentioned you before.
Let me guess.
She told you to avoid
that strange woman who makes
those questionable medicines.
Oh, no! Nothing like that!
Is that what those are for?
[BOW]
Yes.
[DAZU]
Wow. You're incredible.
How so?
[DAZU] Well, most people
in this kingdom
use magic for everything.
But you actually
make things yourself.
Where did you learn how
to create medicines like that?
[BOW]
Nowhere, really.
What?
I learned all that I could
about different herbs,
then I kept trying
until something worked.
[DAZU]
All alone?
[BOW] I barely have
any magic ability.
So, I figured out the one thing
I could do and stuck with it.
I should be going.
[DAZU]
Uh, wait!
My name is Dazu! Dazu Tayak.
I hope this isn't
too presumptuous,
but could I visit you sometime?
Of course. It'd be nice
to see you again.
I'll even make a batch
of medicine for you,
if you'd like to learn.
[DAZU]
This is great.
The bombs you make
are so effective.
[BOW] Looks like we're clear
to keep moving forward.
We should hurry,
before it gets too dark.
We need to pass
through Breed Mountain
and cross the border
as quickly as we can.
[DEMON MASK 142A]
Once we do, we'll be out
of the Clover
Kingdom's jurisdiction.
That way, even if the
Magic Knights find us,
they can't do anything.
[DEMON MASK 144AA]
We'll be in Spade before long.
[SECREÉ]
No, you won't.
Even if you get out
of the Clover Kingdom
without being caught,
you'll still have to go through
a strong magic
region on the way.
[NARRATOR] The Spade Kingdom
is a mysterious land
covered in snow and secrets.
Between there and
the Clover Kingdom
lies a neutral zone
belonging to no nation.
Most of this area is classified
as a strong magic region.
The term "strong magic
region" refers to a place
that possesses a powerful
force field of mana,
which causes various
magical phenomena
that keep outsiders at bay.
This and other harsh conditions
make these places
quite treacherous.
[SECREÉ] Getting through a strong
magic region's a difficult task
even for a Magic Knight,
so how do you expect to do it
with almost no magic
ability to speak of?
[DAZU]
Well...
[BOW]
You bring up a good point.
Do you plan to die?
[DAZU] Die? I suppose
that's a possibility.
But, it's enough to know
that we have a chance.
[DAZU]
Let's go.
[BOW]
Right.
Hey, Captain Yami,
this is Magna.
Let me know if you can hear me!
We tracked down
the Devil Believers,
but they got us pretty
outnumbered here!
So we're waitin'
for your orders, boss!
Are you there? Come in!
The mana in this area
seems a little messy.
And we're close to the border
where that strong
magic region is,
so that might be why
the signal's bad.
All right, you two.
I'm gonna look for a spot
with better reception
so I can talk to Captain Yami.
Stay here so I know
where to find you.
I'll come back soon
with reinforcements,
and then we'll be ready to roll!
Let's kick it into
high gear, Crazy Cyclone!
Hey! Magna! Wait up!
If we have to stay out here in
this rain for too much longer,
then we're going
to catch cold for sure!
Though, they say idiots can't
catch cold, so Asta's safe.
[ASTA yells]
What's the matter with you?
The second he tells us
to stay put,
you go barreling
up the mountain?
[ASTA]
I'm worried about Nero!
Believe me, I wanna
rescue Nero, too,
but we need some kind of plan!
Could we make them
scatter somehow?
[ASTA]
No, that won't work!
Then what are you thinking?
I'll talk to them some more.
Maybe we'll understand
each other better!
If it were that simple,
then we wouldn't be
in this mess right now!
Nero...
Good grief. You are so stubborn!
Come on.
I'll help you get up there.
You'd better say thank you.
Thank you so much, Noelle!
Sure, it's fine, but,
uh, you owe me one.
[MAN 147B grunts]
[MAN 147A]
Whoa, you okay?
[MAN 147B]
Yeah. I'll be all right.
[MAN 147A]
Here, take my hand.
[MAN 147B]
Thanks.
I can't stop shaking.
It's even colder now that
the sun's going down, isn't it?
Yes, but we have to press on.
[WOMAN 147B] Thinking back on
everything I've been through,
this is nothing at all!
[DAZU] After everything I've
been through, this is nothing.
[BOW]
You're exactly right.
Beautiful.
[DAZU]
Just like back then.
A full moon.
[BOW]
Perhaps the mana will be weaker
in the strong magic region.
[DAZU] The odds may be against
us, but there's still a chance.
Thanks to chance,
I was able to meet you,
and to make it this far.
You've helped me get
through so many trials
and hardships, Bow.
I'm eternally grateful.
[BOW]
So am I.
We've come such a long way,
but we still have a very
difficult road ahead of us.
[DAZU] Then let's
keep working together.
[BOW]
You and me.
[FOLLOWER 147A]
What's that?
[FOLLOWER 147B]
Could it be...?
--[FOLLOWER 147AA] Look!
--[DAZU, BOW gasp]
[DAZU]
Asta!
[DEVIL BELIEVERS gasp]
We finally tracked you down!
[ASTA]
Nero, where are you?
Hey, wait.
Something isn't right.
I'm sure you're
too dumb to notice it,
but I'm not detecting much mana
from these people at all.
Huh?
[NOELLE] Just like the boy
we saw back in the village.
He only had that faint,
fleeting mana.
[NOELLE] Is it really that
common for people in our Kingdom
to have such weak magic power?
If this is just some of them,
how many more are there?
[ASTA]
Found her.
Nero! We're here to save you!
Hey, be more careful!
It's fine. The wind's
real strong, so if they
try to hit us with a
sleep potion or something,
it'll blow away!
It's still pretty risky, though.
[NOELLE]
We're Magic Knights.
We're supposed to protect
these people, not fight them!
But Asta's my squadmate.
I have to protect him, too.
[ASTA]
Now what?
Master Asta, you're really here!
That's him, the one who's been
blessed with the devil's power!
[NOELLE] They're praising Asta
because they worship the devil!
[ASTA] You're Dazu Tayak,
the leader, right?
[DAZU]
Asta.
[ASTA]
And you're Bow Nocde.
You can't have Nero!
She's really important to us,
and we have to bring her home.
Asta.
I know what you're doing:
you think that if you give Nero
and my grimoire to
the Spade Kingdom,
they'll say you can join
forces with them.
Good plan.
Too bad you don't have me.
[DAZU] If you know all that,
then one thing should be clear.
[BOW] There's no way we
can give your friend back.
[ASTA]
After you cross these mountains,
you'll be on neutral ground.
The strong magic region up
ahead won't be as bad tonight
since there's a full
moon, so I'm guessing
you're gonna try
to push through.
But with so many people,
there's no way
you'll all make it.
[DAZU]
We're well aware.
Even so, I--we must press on.
[DAZU] I barely have any mana,
so I can only use small spells.
As you know, magic is everything
in the Clover Kingdom,
so I was regarded as worthless.
I might as well
have never been born.
Even my own parents
looked down on me.
I was bullied.
My teachers mocked me
and I couldn't make friends.
Everyone gave me dirty looks.
I'm sure you understand, Asta.
Yeah.
[DAZU] That's why I worked
so much harder than my peers,
but no matter what I did,
my lack of magic ability
always made me the target
of disgust and ridicule.
[ASTA]
But, you weren't alone!
Your husband
accepted you, right?
[DAZU]
Accepted me?
When that old lady Maggie
from Tiulyu talked about you,
she said your mother-in-law
was happy that her son
had married such
a wonderful girl!
I know things were hard,
but at least you had a family
who loved you the way you were!
So even if you didn't
have much power,
you were still happy
about that, weren't you?
[DAZU] I wasn't happy at all!
I knew how they really felt.
Maybe, if they had lived...
No, people are all the same.
[DAZU] Every day I spent
with them was a nightmare.
They always smiled at me,
told me my cooking
was delicious, and
complimented my hard work.
That's good!
[DAZU] I'm sure our neighbors
saw my husband and his mother
as kind, charitable people.
But behind closed doors,
they still mocked me.
They looked down on me,
just like everyone else!
Those two didn't
accept me at all.
They were only using me!
They enjoyed treating
me like trash!
It was the one thing that
made them feel better
about their own pathetic lives!
I'm happy they're dead!
They deserved what
happened to them!
[BOW]
Dazu.
[DAZU]
I'm sorry, I just...
[BOW] The details of
the situation may vary
from person to person,
but everyone in our group
has had a similar experience.
You all feel like that?
[BOW]
Yes.
I'm able to create medicines
and potions that are
far more effective than
the magic of an average
recovery mage, so my
skills are quite valuable.
Despite that, I was still
shunned for my lack of mana.
Occasionally, people would
rely on my expertise,
but once my usefulness
had run its course,
they wanted nothing
more to do with me.
[DEMON MASK 142A] That's what
happened to me, too!
I spent countless nights
pouring over my books
while my peers were
out having fun!
[DEMON MASK 144AA]
I always had to work so hard!
[FOLLOWER 147A]
So did I!
[FOLLOWER 147B]
Me, too!
[FOLLOWER 147C]
We all did!
[FOLLOWER 147D]
Everyone made fun of us
because we couldn't use magic!
[FOLLOWER 147BB] Sometimes it
felt like we didn't even exist!
[FOLLOWER 147E]
But that's over now!
[FOLLOWER 147F]
We're leaving this awful place!
[BOW]
Look at these poor souls.
We met them on our way
to the Spade Kingdom
and realized they had suffered
the same terrible things.
But they lived in the shadows,
so we never would have
known about them.
I had no idea this many
residents of the Clover Kingdom
were dealing with
such discontent.
[DAZU] To think that all these
people understood our pain
and wanted to help us.
And you!
How dare you tell us
to go back now?
You would have us return
to that miserable existence?
[BOW]
We've had enough!
[DEMON MASK 144AA] You of all
people should understand!
Trust me. I get it.
Asta.
I know how much it sucks!
That's exactly why
I have to stop you!
What is it about
the Spade Kingdom
that makes you so desperate
to fight alongside them?
[DAZU] We want to gain
the devil's power.
You're kidding!
[SECREÉ gasps]
[DAZU] Kabwe from the
Magic Parliament told us
there was a devil
in the Spade Kingdom.
We thought, if we went there,
the strength of that great
being might be shared with us.
[DAZU] I crave power.
All of our people do.
[BOW] After aligning with the
Spade Kingdom and receiving
the devil's
overwhelming might...
[DAZU]
...we'll return to Clover...
[DAZU, BOW]
...and seek revenge.
Come on. Don't do this!
[DAZU] "The three leaves of
a clover are said to contain
integrity, hope, and love.
The fourth leaf is
given over to good luck,
and in the fifth leaf
dwells a devil."
Isn't that how the saying goes?
That's right.
[DAZU] Even though you had no
mana and couldn't use magic,
you still gained
the devil's blessing
because you had this grimoire.
[BOW]
You joined the Magic Knights
and accomplished great things.
You have no idea
how much we admire you.
Don't admire me! Not for that!
[DAZU]
We want to become like you.
[BOW]
That's why we're going to Spade.
[DEMON MASK 142A]
Once we have the devil's power,
we can be reborn!
[DEMON MASK 144AA] And then our
suffering will be avenged!
[DAZU]
That is our only objective.
[ASTA]
But I'm different!
[DAZU]
Different?
[ASTA]
That's right!
I trained my butt off to make up
for not having any magic,
and people still
treated me like crap!
I've spent my whole life
being made fun of, too!
But I never hated
anybody for it!
It's true, I was able to
use the devil's Anti-magic
because I had that grimoire,
but I never once
thought about using
it to get revenge
on the Clover Kingdom,
or to punish
any of the people
who treated me badly!
I only used it to help!
Whether they're rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
I just want everybody
to be happy!
[DAZU] I can only imagine
how happy we could've been
if we looked at the
world the way you do.
[BOW]
Indeed.
[DAZU] However, the flames of
our hatred cannot be quenched.
Which is why we won't
be releasing your friend!
[BOW] We'll continue our
journey toward Spade.
Sure, whatever.
But Nero's stayin' right here.
[DAZU]
Did you not hear me?
[ASTA]
Then let me go instead!
Oh, no.
[ASTA] Wouldn't it be
better to have me, too,
not just my grimoire?
You went after both of us
the first time you showed up,
so obviously I was
part of your plan.
[DAZU] Fine, but we'll
have to restrain you.
Of course.
[DAZU]
And her, too.
What?
[ASTA] Now let Nero go,
like you promised.
[DAZU]
We'll be glad to do that.
[BOW] After we safely deliver
you to the Spade Kingdom.
You just made a mistake.
Nah, don't worry.
I have faith in them.
[DAZU] We'll do whatever it
takes to win the devil's favor.
And the more gifts we can offer,
the better our chances.
[BOW] Asta and his grimoire, the
girl who used forbidden magic,
and a royal, as well!
[DAZU] I think they'll
be pleased with this.
That's if we get through
the strong magic region.
[DAZU] Yes, of course.
Now, let's proceed.
[NOELLE]
We're at the border.
[DAZU, BOW panting]
[DAZU]
Almost there.
[BOW]
Get ready.
[NOELLE]
I can feel it.
Full moon or not, the mana's
so strong, it's overwhelming.
How do you plan to do this?
[DAZU] As you know,
our magic capability
is basically nonexistent.
[BOW]
But not entirely.
We do possess
a small amount of mana.
[DAZU] Using my Catalyst Magic,
I can gather the scraps of mana
we each possess and combine
them into something great.
Just as even the
tiniest drops of water
can become an
unstoppable current.
[BOW]
Dazu's Catalyst Magic will draw
all of our strength together.
And then we can use that power
to survive the
strong magic region!
That's crazy!
[DAZU]
Maybe. But it's our best shot.
There's too much
distance to cover,
and no way to be sure that
your mana will hold out
until we get there.
This won't work.
[DAZU]
I understand it's a gamble,
but at least one of us might
make it, and perhaps that person
will obtain the devil's power.
There's no turning back;
we must see this plan
through to the end.
[BOW] Or we won't get revenge
on the Clover Kingdom.
You can't.
--[DAZU] Let's proceed.
--[BOW] Yes.
[engine revving]
[DAZU]
What's that?
[gasps]
[MAGNA]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The cavalry's here!
[ASTA]
Magna! Captain Yami!
[DAZU gasps]
[NOELLE]
We are the Magic Knights.
Our job is to guard
the Clover Kingdom
and keep its inhabitants
out of harm's way!
Black Clover , Page 148:
"Becoming the Light That
Shines Through the Darkness."
Those who are lost in the dark
are the ones who need us most!