[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy
who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
[NARRATOR]
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world,
and to become the
next Wizard King!
[NARRATOR] In order to
learn the Mana Method
and acquire the power
they'll soon need,
Asta and the others train
as hard as they can
in the Heart Kingdom.
[ASTA yells]
[ASTA]
Gotcha this time!
[screams]
The power to invalidate magic
is second to nothing.
But you're too narrowminded
to use it to its full potential.
I'm not done!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Yami seeks
to improve in his own way.
Looks like they're
all workin' hard
to push past their limits.
So I guess I better
up my game, as well.
[ASTA yells]
[GAJA]
Lightning Magic: Tenjiolia.
[yells]
[screaming]
[ASTA] I've been sparring
with this guy for days now,
and I still can't
get a single hit in!
It's fortunate that
I opted to hold back.
You'd be in far worse
shape if I hadn't.
You've trained to
your physical limit,
obtained the rare power
known as Anti-magic,
and forged friendships
with capable allies.
That's gotten you this far.
However, it won't be enough
to overcome the enemy
that we're about to face.
If you can't find
a way to defeat me
in one-on-one combat, you will
fall to the Spade Kingdom Devil.
One more round! Let's go!
[GAJA] Perhaps it's that
unwavering willpower
that's allowed him to become
this strong so quickly.
It isn't just him though.
All of the Clover Kingdom
mages are growing quickly.
Some have already developed
new techniques here.
[LEOPOLD]
Faster. I need to be faster.
And stronger, too!
[LEOPOLD yells]
Hey, Leopold.
[LEOPOLD]
I should be able to do more.
I know I should!
Those were some really
excellent moves.
Good work.
Nice use of the
Mana Method, too.
You're a lot faster with it now.
That said...
Hm. How to put this?
Every now and again,
you seem to waver a bit
when you're
sparring with me.
It feels like something's
causing you to hesitate.
Do you have any idea
what that might be?
I think I know.
I have an older brother
and sister who I look up to.
Their power is incredible,
and it's been permanently
seared into my eyes.
I can't help but compare
my own achievements
to theirs, and when
I do, I feel pathetic.
[MEREOLEONA]
Stand up.
A lion should never
look so pitiful.
[LEOPOLD]
The stronger I get,
the more out of reach
they seem to become.
It feels like, no matter hard
I try, or how far I get,
they'll always be better.
[LAVA MONSTERS growling]
Flame Magic: Calidos Brachium!
[LAVA MONSTERS groaning]
[YAMI]
Whew! S'hot down here.
Hey, Sisgoleon, good to see ya.
The name is Mereoleona,
as you know.
Did you come for a dip
in the hot springs, too?
Do your part and clear out
some of the locals beforehand.
Sheesh. So you killed
those magical beasts
just to make sure they
wouldn't interrupt your bath?
You are every bit as violent
as I remember you bein'.
Not like it was a big chore.
I wouldn't even
call that a warmup.
Of course not.
Tell ya what, though.
If you need a warmup,
you could fight me.
I see.
Did you come all this
way looking for me?
Yeah. I did.
See, when I was fightin'
that word devil,
I was able to use
a technique of yours.
Think you call it "Mana Zone."
But I don't have a good handle
on how it works just yet,
and somethin' tells me I could
get more use out of it if I did,
so I wanna experiment a bit.
Uh-huh. Couldn't you
do that alone?
Well, it's just that
you're so experienced.
I was hopin' you'd be willin'
to show me the ropes.
[MEREOLEONA]
Fine.
I was thinking that I should
get some more training in.
But be warned. Against me,
you might just burn before you
even get to try my technique.
Oh, boy. I'm not
sure if she sees
the difference between
teaching me and killing me.
Hey, on second thought,
I think I'll just go.
That's prob'ly not
gonna fly, is it?
You're the one who
chose to bring
fresh meat into a lion's den.
Well, I guess it's best
for you come at me
with some murderous intent.
How else am I supposed
to push past my limits?
[MEREOLEONA] Very well.
I'll burn you to a crisp!
[YAMI grunts]
[yells]
[yelling]
[ASTA yelling]
[ASTA]
Black Meteorite!
[GAJA]
Is he tracking my mana?
One way to find out.
Whoa!
[ASTA screams]
I know how you
predict my moves.
Or I know enough to come up
with countermeasures, at least.
Exactly how long do you intend
to struggle against me?
Shall we fight until
you wear yourself out?
[ASTA]
Crap. What do I do?
I can't get anywhere
near this guy,
so how am I supposed
to land a hit?
Let's talk about
your Anti-magic.
It's essentially
the opposite of magic,
but opposites tend to
share certain fundamentals.
Both are forms of
intangible power.
This could mean that they
can be wielded in similar ways.
The first step
of the Mana Method
is to feel the mana
flowing around you.
So perhaps you should
try something similar.
[ASTA]
Right.
I need to feel
the flow of Anti-magic!
[laughs]
She's faster than I can track.
This all you got?
Think you can dodge
your way to victory?
[YAMI]
How the hell is she this fast?
[MEREOLEONA grunts]
[YAMI]
No worries.
If it's thanks to her Mana Zone,
then I should be
able to match her.
[MEREOLEONA]
Too slow!
You wanna see what
Mana Zone can do?
I'll show you!
[MEREOLEONA yells]
[YAMI]
Whelp. This isn't good.
This place is way too hot.
What was I thinkin',
fightin' a Mana Zone expert
in a place like this?
Hey, I thought cats liked
to play with their food.
Slow down, ya furball.
[MEREOLEONA] Hmph! I see no
point in toying with weak prey.
Why don't you try
struggling more?
[yells]
[YAMI] If this was a contest of
speed alone, I'd probably lose.
[YAMI gasps, grunts]
[MEREOLEONA growls]
[YAMI] Dark Magic:
Dark Cloaked, Black Blade!
[ASTA]
Black Divider!
[yells]
[ASTA]
He disappeared!
[GAJA] You enlarged your
blade to extend your reach.
Not a bad idea.
But you're still far too slow.
[ASTA] Even if I can sense him
with my ki, I can't keep up.
I'm using the Mana Method
to enhance my speed,
which makes avoiding
you a simple task.
[ASTA screams]
The Heart Kingdom
teems with natural mana,
and the mages here
make regular use of it.
For those of us who
master the Mana Method,
this power source
may as well be unlimited.
Which means that,
as long as I can keep
avoiding your attacks,
I can fight indefinitely without
needing to tap into my own mana.
[ASTA]
I get it.
So if I keep burning
through my Anti-magic,
I'm sure to lose.
[YAMI grunts]
[MEREOLEONA]
You call that an attack?
Come on!
[laughs] This is pathetic!
Why wait for the
devil to end you?
I can do your last rites
here and now, if you'd like.
Thing is, I already
owe you so much
for helpin' out
with my training.
So thanks for the offer,
but I'll pass.
Looks like step one is gonna
be figuring out that trick
where she walks on thin air.
Once I've learned that,
I can enter the ring.
[ASTA]
Come on!
You need to come up with an
attack that he can't dodge.
Something with the
range to reach him
and the speed to catch him.
I've already seen the powers
of the Demon-Slayer Sword
and the Demon-Destroyer Sword.
I assume that this sword
is unique as well?
[ASTA]
Right. The Demon-Dweller Sword.
It probably has powers
that I haven't drawn out yet.
That reminds me.
Right after I found this sword,
I channeled Noelle's
mana with it.
I'm not sure,
but there's a chance
I can do the same thing
with my own Anti-magic.
Interesting. I take it
you've had an epiphany?
Please let me have another try!
If that's what you want.
I won't hold back
as much this time.
If you manage to land
a single hit on me,
then I'll declare
you victorious.
To be honest, I wish
you'd just go all out!
If you won't move,
I'll bring the fight to you.
[YAMI]
'Kay, now kick the air!
[screams]
Just as lions toss their young
off cliffs to test them,
I have absolutely no problem
hurling you into the lava.
[YAMI] Are you really
chasin' me right now?
[YAMI] Sucks to admit,
but Sisgoleon's right.
If I let myself lose here...
[YAMI] What chance would
I have against that devil?
Ah. Nice.
Looks like I can finally
fight you on equal ground.
"Equal ground"?
We're floating above lava, fool.
[YAMI]
You get the point!
I'm saying it's
an even fight now!
Hah! When it comes to Mana Zone,
you're just a baby
learning to walk.
[YAMI] I need to
figure out how to deal
with those fists of hers.
All right, Asta.
It's just like when
you borrowed Noelle's mana.
I just need to infuse
the Demon-Dweller Sword
with my Anti-magic!
[GAJA]
In accordance with your request
that I stop holding back,
I will now show
you my true power.
[YAMI] I just need to
keep increasing my speed
with Mana Zone, and stop
her from throwin' out
any new spells.
[yelps]
You're not bad.
You've developed a rudimentary
grasp of how to use Mana Zone.
[YAMI grunts]
[MEREOLEONA] Which means
I can stop holding back now.
Do you seriously think you
were holding back before?
No way.
This gift is to thank you
for the good time.
Do your best not
to let it kill you.
[MEREOLEONA yells]
[YAMI]
Not sure I can stop all that.
Then again,
I have to.
No point in asking if I can.
I have to, so I will!
[BOTH]
Right here, right now.
I'll push past my limits!
[YAMI] Mana Zone!
Dark Magic: Black Hole!
Okay now.
[MEREOLEONA]
Is he nullifying my mana?
[YAMI] Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked
Lightless Slash!
[MEREOLEONA grunts]
[yells] There!
Quite impressive.
[panting]
Way to go, me!
I actually got a hit in!
[MEREOLEONA laughs]
This is getting interesting.
Once I've burnt you to cinders,
my bath'll be that
much more enjoyable.
[YAMI] Nah. Got the gist
of it, so I'm leavin'.
Don't be coy,
or are you just afraid?
Terrified. Catch ya later.
Well, that's disappointing.
It's time we
shared our progress.
Please report.
Rill and Charmy
are doing great.
They both took to the Mana
Method faster than expected.
They're brilliant,
if a little unusual.
The most I can do for them
now is prepare their meals
and bring out their potential
with the occasional
word of advice.
Charlotte and Mimosa
have come a super long way.
They seemed confused at first,
but then something went
"cuh-lick" in their
heads, ya know?
Our students have grown, too.
I suspect they've grown
faster than any of yours.
Although... when someone's
being instructed
by the Queen of
the Heart Kingdom
and the Great Water
Spirit herself,
I suppose that's only
to be expected.
[laughs] I can tell
you're proud of 'em.
Tell me, Smurik.
How has Finral
been coming along?
For the time being, we must
let the wind guide us,
and trust it to nurture the
storm that grows within him.
You have an awfully hard time
getting to the point, don't you?
Did someone say something?
I couldn't quite make it out
over the whispers of the wind.
Don't fight, you two.
Floga. How goes it?
Not bad.
Leo's a talented mage,
but he's plagued by self-doubt.
I think you'll
get better results
if you try to focus
on your strengths.
My strengths? Like what?
[FLOGA] You didn't get
this far on talent.
You did it with patience
and determination.
Your power grows as
your technique improves.
With every day of practice.
You're the kind of person
who has the strength
to endure anything.
I mean, you're you, right?
The strength to
endure anything...
I wanna draw out potential
he hasn't realized yet.
At least, that's my idea.
We'll see how it goes.
Yes. Well, I'm sure
you'll get through to him.
And what about Asta?
Asta's Anti-magic
is uniquely potent.
We'll need it to
defeat this devil.
As for Asta's progress...
He's becoming stronger
in his own way.
Unfortunately, time is
running short now.
Please put everything
you have into this training.
[GROUP]
Yes, ma'am.
Let us join together to beat
the Spade Kingdom and the
devil lurking within it.
[RALPH]
There are so many.
Looks like they're almost ready
to start the invasion.
If we're gonna make our move,
we need to be fast.
Look there!
How fortunate!
Through your labors, you
people will get to contribute
to the Spade
Kingdom's prosperity!
Where are they making us go now?
We have to stay quiet.
[MAN 156A groans]
Come on, buddy!
You're almost there!
Don't, Ralph, there are
too many of them.
I know, but still.
We've reached the
strong magic region.
It's unlikely that all of us
will make it across,
but remember, only one of us
needs to reach
the Clover Kingdom.
As long as one of us
makes it, there's hope.
Hang onto that hope,
no matter what happens!
Let's go!
[RESISTANCE MEN gasp]
Look at that;
we've found ourselves
a pack of stray rebels.
[SOLDIER 156C]
Your friend ratted you out,
but that isn't too surprising,
not with a beloved child's
life on the line.
[RALPH]
Run for it!
[SOLDIER 156C yells] If I bring
your heads back to my superior,
I'll get a promotion
and a raise for sure!
[RESISTANCE MEN groaning]
Don't turn your back to me!
Ralph!
[panting]
[RESISTANCE 156B]
Ralph!
[RALPH]
What are you--
We're entrusting
you with our mana.
Use it well.
You're on your own now.
You have to pull
through, for him!
Our hopes go with you.
Finish the work
your father started!
You won't escape us!
Go! Now!
[RALPH panting]
[RALPH]
I'll reach the Clover Kingdom.
No matter what it takes.
The strong magic region
is just past this cliff.
Can I really cross it?
Stop that!
Don't let their
sacrifice go to waste.
Follow in your
father's footsteps.
You can't give up!
[SOLDIER 156D]
There he is!
[SOLDIER 156C]
Get him!
[RALPH]
I can't let them take me.
I'm the last hope.
[RALPH]
For Yuno!
[SOLDIER 156E]
Did we hit him?
[SOLDIER 156C]
I couldn't tell.
But even if he's alive,
that's a strong magic region.
The environment'll
kill him before long.
And I don't know about you two,
but I'd rather not chase him.
[SOLDIER 156E]
Yeah, he'll die soon.
[SOLDIER 156D] Serves him
right. Damn Resistance.
Let's go.
I don't like being this close
to the strong magic region.
Who knows what'll happen
if we stay too long?
[SOLDIER 156C]
Heh. Nothin' good.
[DANTE]
You say this is a son
of one of the Mage Defense
Force's former commanders?
[SOLDIER 156F]
Yes.
We interrogated one of the rebel
conspirators we captured
and learned that
his name is Ralph.
And, sir.
His name actually appears in a--
[DANTE]
It matters not.
Let this fly buzz
around as he will.
We'll swat him down
if he decides to stand
in the way of our grand design.
[ANTI-MAGIC DEVIL cackles]
Who am I, you ask?
I guess I wouldn't mind
sharing a little.
[NARRATOR]
Next time on Black Clover ,
Page 157: "Five-Leaf Clover."
Within the clover's fifth leaf,
there lives a devil.