[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy who
was born without it.
His name is Asta.
[NARRATOR]
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world
and to become the
next Wizard King!
[ASTA] It's in the heart
of the--the kingdom!
The one with all the hearts!
Stop actin' all squirrelly
and try to make some sense.
Think about what you say.
We got Gordon's dad
to help us look around
for big curses and he
found a stupidly huge one
right in the middle of
the Heart Kingdom, okay?
Huh?
[ASTA] I'm pretty sure
it's a devil curse;
I mean, it's gotta be right?
So that's where I wanna go next.
Where's your pal, Gordon?
What does he think about this?
He wanted to learn some
Curse Magic from his dad.
So he decided to stay
home a little longer.
All right. Fine.
Now wanna tell me
why the two of them
look like they've just had
their brains scrambled?
I think it's because
of the food we were given,
but I'm fine. Actually,
I thought it was great.
Fair enough.
Think I'm up to speed.
Cool! So can I go
to the Heart Kingdom?
Sure. Just sit tight for now.
I'll look into it.
It's not happenin'.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Apparently the Heart
Kingdom can't be entered.
[BOTH]
Huh?!
[ASTA]
Are you serious, sir?
[NOELLE] I was planning
to go to there, too!
That's where we'll find the next
clue we need, I'm sure of it!
Well, the border's airtight.
The entire length
of it has been rigged
with a bunch of trap spells.
Trip one, and we'll
be wanted criminals.
Might spark an
international incident.
No way!
Wait. Why don't we
just destroy the traps
with my Anti-magic
and sneak in that way?
Because that's dumb.
They'll sense the
traps disappearing.
[ASTA]
Oh.
Well, that's troublesome.
Not even Rouge's power could get
you through there undetected.
[YAMI]
Whatever we try, they'll notice.
[meows]
Huh...
Wait. There has to be some way,
because I heard Mimosa say
that she had been there before.
Whoa, really?
[NOELLE] It's true. She said
there was some sort of
student exchange program
between our nobility and theirs.
All right, Finral.
Take these twerps to
the Golden Dawn's base.
'Kay!
Uh. Finral? I'm kinda confused.
Why aren't'cha complaining about
gettin' used as an errand boy?
Because I'm excited.
There's someone I
wanted to see there.
Believe it or not,
it was your brother Finral who
managed to stop you, in the end.
Ugh. Arrogant jerk.
[knocking]
Langris, hey! I heard
you finally woke up!
I'm really glad!
So you came.
Hello, Finral!
Lady Finnes. I'm
glad you're well.
Must be satisfying.
Huh?
I tried to murder
my own brother,
but found myself defeated.
Then, as my parents
desperately apologized for me,
I tried to murder my king.
I guess I'm the one who's a
disgrace to the family name now.
Wait, what are you saying?!
That was only because you
were possessed by an elf!
Everyone will understa--
And, worst of all,
it was you who saved me.
[FINRAL]
Uh...
[LANGRIS] I heard all about
your squadmate's trial.
Both you and that commoner.
You're insufferable.
You don't have any talent.
And yet, you've still managed
to outdo me somehow.
This isn't over yet. Understand?
[FINNES gasps]
Yeah. That's the spirit!
This just confirms that I'm
right to declare war on you.
Starting now, I'll work hard,
prove myself to Father,
and become the kind of man
who deserves to lead our house.
Also, I'll be the man
who makes Lady Finnes happy.
[FINRAL] I'm sorry to drag
you into this, Lady Finnes.
But, I promise,
once I've become worthy,
I'm gonna come back for you.
I guess I'm willing to wait,
but don't take too long. 'Kay?
[BOTH giggle]
[LANGRIS]
Let's take a walk, Brother.
[FINRAL] Huh? Should you
be moving right now?
I have to ask you to
wait here, Lady Finnes.
Don't worry.
I'm not planning to fill
him with holes again.
[FINRAL]
Whoa, Langris. Too soon.
What's up? Is
something the matter?
Unless you
transform drastically,
you'll have no chance of
making Lady Finnes happy.
Huh?
[LANGRIS]
Here's why.
[LETOILE]
Hello, Vice Captain Langris.
You're feeling well enough
to get out of bed now, sir?
Oh, yeah!
What cloud did you
angels fall from?
Some babes are just
too hot for heaven.
Just as I expected.
It's plain to see
that you're cursed!
[FINRAL]
What?!
[LANGRIS]
You hit on every girl you meet
--like a wannabe playboy!
--[FINRAL] Playboy?!
[LANGRIS] And the time you
spent shirking your duties
made you a bigger
failure than ever!
[FINRAL]
Failure?!
[LANGRIS] That freewheeling
life has left you
with bad habits that
won't just break!
[FINRAL]
Bad Habits?!
[LANGRIS] There's no way
a self-centered degenerate
like you could make
Lady Finnes happy!
[FINRAL]
Yeah. You're totally right.
Sorry if we're interrupting
whatever this is.
[MAGIC KNIGHT 128A]
I hear the vice captain's
been acting strangely
ever since he woke.
[LANGRIS]
Make sure you do your level best
to rid yourself of that curse.
If you can't pull it off,
I might end up marrying
Lady Finnes myself.
[FINRAL]
Wait, so was breaking my curse
part of this investigation, too?
[doorbell rings]
Heh.
I won't let you get your
happy ending that easily,
Brother.
I understand now.
You need to get inside.
[MIMOSA]
Anything to help Asta.
It's true that I've been
to the Heart Kingdom.
I was around 13 at the time.
My brother and I were both
sent over as exchange students.
Though I would've preferred
different company.
We were only allowed
access to a limited area,
but I still learned a lot.
Their magic's amazing.
The techniques they use are like
nothing you would
find here in Clover.
The Heart Kingdom
is a verdant land
through which water
is always flowing.
And its rich
environment generates
a tremendous amount of mana.
If you're right in
saying that what lies
at the center of it is
a devil-induced curse,
then we have cause to be scared.
Although it's honestly
hard to believe.
[NOELLE]
A devil's curse.
This could give me a clue
about the devil that
mother encountered.
[MIMOSA]
We weren't allowed to meet her,
but I was told that
the queen who rules
over the Heart Kingdom
is every bit as powerful
as one of our
Magic Knight Squads.
They say that she's
an all-knowing mage
who sees everything that
happens in her kingdom.
No way! Whoa!
[ASTA]
A queen, huh?
If she's like the Witch Queen,
then we might be in trouble.
Well, we're not goin'
over there to pick a fight,
so it's fine. I'll just
keep my guard up.
I believe they're
accepting applications
to visit as we speak.
I'll see if I can get
us all permission to go.
[ASTA]
Thanks a bunch, Mimosa!
It's huge!
I've never seen such an
enormous ship in my life!
It's actually on the smaller
side, but it does look nice.
Calm down, Asta,
this isn't a vacation.
You never told us that you
owned your own ship, Captain.
Did ya pick it up
recently, or what?
[YAMI]
Well, I met with Julius' helper
and made a few threats.
Or, uh, compelling points,
and he lent it to us.
Huh?
[YAMI] If you damage it,
I'll kill you hard.
Right!
[KLAUS]
Asta. Be careful.
Protect Mimosa.
You have nothing
to worry about, Klaus.
We're making this trip
to investigate something,
not to fight.
But still, if something should
happen while you're out there,
we won't be able
to come to your aid.
I'd feel much better about this
if I could go along, too.
Well, there're only four spots.
First up's Asta.
The royal from the Golden Dawn
who arranged all of this.
Noelle, who looks none too
willing to give up her spot.
And then, Finral.
[FINRAL]
Yeah, Captain.
Why'd ya want me to
be the fourth anyway?
'Cause havin' wheels
tends to come in handy.
Agreed?
[BLACK BULLS]
Mm-hm.
Yeah, there's no arguin'
with that logic.
You said it.
He is quite convenient.
I get it. Spatial Magic
is nice to have,
but he's really
just a pack mule.
[FINRAL] Ya know what?
You don't need to understand!
Asta!
Go kick some ass in the
Heart Kingdom for me!
You better not.
Right!
[LUCK] Take care of things
there, and come home soon, okay?
The two of us still need
to have a duel, Asta.
Right!
If you get homesick
and can't sleep,
just take a swig of this stuff
and you'll pass right out.
[ASTA]
Mm-hm!
You're underage, Asta.
Okay, you've all
said your goodbyes.
Now stop wastin' time; you've
got a job of your own to do.
[MAGNA]
Yeah, yeah, we remember.
Let's do this!
[YAMI]
Later.
You scram, too.
Try to stay on your
toes out there.
[ALL]
Right!
[ASTA] ...2,031, 2,032,
2,033, 2,034, 2,035...
[FINRAL]
Stay calm. Just stay calm.
Stay calm.
Out of all the people I
could be traveling with,
why did it have to be two
supremely adorable royal babes
and a cool beauty
who turns into a bird?
I don't think I'm gonna
be able to sleep at night.
Oh, come on. Tough it out!
Pull yourself together, man!
From now on, you have eyes
for no one but Lady Finnes!
[MIMOSA]
Hey.
Um. I packed us all
some lunch. See?
[ASTA]
Ooh! Thanks, Mimosa!
[MIMOSA] I-It's not much,
but I hope you enjoy it, Asta.
You made all this
yourself? Looks tasty!
So good! Yum.
Thanks for saying so, Asta.
Jeez, slow down.
Save some for us, okay?
[NOELLE grumbles]
Why does this bother me?
Mouth's dry!
Here, have some water.
[ASTA]
That's too much!
[NOELLE]
There. Now thank me.
I'm not grateful. You scared me!
That water almost pushed
me into the ocean!
[MIMOSA] I don't get
why this bothers me.
[FINRAL] What the heck
am I watching right now?
[ASTA] More important
than me drowning?!
[ASTA] Check it out,
we finally made it, you guys!
Who would've thought we could
just enter the kingdom legally?
Once again, Asta:
we aren't here on vacation.
I'm sorry that I wasn't
able to get permission
for anyone else to come.
Nah, don't worry about it!
I'm nothin' but grateful
to you for getting us in,
and if we need help, we can
use Finral's spatial magic!
You're gonna get
us all arrested.
Whoa. Why did it get
so foggy all of a sudden?
It's one of the Heart
Kingdom's defense measures.
No vessel can pass
through this fog
unless it's permitted
to by the Queen.
[groans]
[FINRAL] I couldn't
sleep a wink last night
knowing I was surrounded
by beautiful girls. Damn it!
Now I'm wondering what the Queen
of Heart Kingdom looks like.
Is she hot, too? She must be!
[ASTA]
The Heart Kingdom's just ahead.
I can't wait to see it!
[GROUP gasps]
So this is the place.
The Heart Kingdom.
It all blends together.
City, forest, and water.
So cool.
Their ship is arriving
right on schedule.
The Clover Kingdom's devil
has significant power.
[UNDINE]
Power that we must obtain.
Huh. I guess you
could say it's pretty.
Where do ya think we're
supposed to tie up the boat?
[gasps]
[GAJA]
Please continue sailing forward.
[MIMOSA]
Wait, you're--
Allow me to welcome you
to the Heart Kingdom.
I'm the Spirit Guardian Gaja,
and I will act as your guide
while you're here.
Is he important?
He sure seems to be.
[GAJA] It's been quite
a while, Lady Mimosa.
You and I met the
last time you visited.
It's lovely to see you, Gaja.
I consider it an honor
that you remember me.
How could I forget?
You were well-liked by everyone
who made your
acquaintance, my lady.
Spirit Guardian Gaja,
meet my friends
Asta, Noelle, and Finral.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Would you care to try
some crimson orange juice?
You can use mana to
sweeten it. For you.
[MIMOSA]
Thank you very much.
What is this stuff?
It's fantastic.
Mine tastes super
bitter, Noelle!
Would you run some of your
mana through it for me?
Well, if you're
gonna beg, then fine.
You told us to keep
sailing forward,
but this looks like a dead end.
[GAJA]
Fear not.
[GAJA] The queen will
guide your ship onward.
[GROUP gasps]
[ASTA] Whoa-ho-ho-ho, so it's
the Queen who's moving us?
All of this is being
controlled by one mage?
Both the mist barrier
and the water stairs:
they're products of
the Queen's Mana Zone,
which spans across
the entire kingdom.
That's awesome!
And so's this weird
red juice of yours!
[NOELLE] He can't be serious.
It covers the whole kingdom?
Is that really possible?
Whoa!
Even the butterflies
are extra pretty here!
[MIMOSA]
This truly is a lovely kingdom.
It's hard to believe that
there's a devil here.
[GAJA] Our kingdom was
founded 1,200 years ago.
Since then, our Queens have
also acted as priestesses,
forming pacts with the spirit
Undine to gain its strength.
This is a country
of water and life.
We steward the land and
it rewards us with mana.
Enough to keep out
any unwanted guests.
Incredible.
To think that one queen
is able to protect
the whole country
through peaceful means.
Yes. That's been
the case so far.
But the future's uncertain.
Even to our queen.
[NOELLE]
Asta!
How could you?
Just what do you think
you're doing, Gaja?
We need his help
to protect the peace
we've cultivated here.
We have to go after him!
[grunts] Leave it to me!
[NOELLE]
Don't slow down, Mimosa.
Put your faith in
our transporter!
[MIMOSA]
Right!
[FINRAL] Spatial Magic:
Fallen Angel's Wingbeat!
Ah. It's only about
a third stage, but still.
You have some rather
intriguing magic.
[FINRAL gasps]
Look out!
Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Lair!
[yelps] How's he floating
without using any spells?
[NOELLE] I don't know what
you're trying to pull.
[NOELLE] But you have
just abducted the friend
of a Clover Kingdom royal, and
that action has consequences!
Yeah, Noelle, that's my girl!
A cute face and a cold stare!
What am I saying? Lady Finnes
is the only girl for me!
[GAJA] Her magic is both
rare and powerful.
Definitely first stage.
That's some remarkable
Water Magic you have.
If you aren't holding back,
then I won't either.
[NOELLE]
What kind of spell is this?
[ASTA screams]
[LOROPECHIKA] I'm sorry for
treating you so roughly.
But I must protect my country,
and it has need of your devil.
[ASTA] Where the heck did
that weird bubble take me?
Was that the Heart
Kingdom's Queen talking?
'Cause if so...
Stop!
[NOELLE]
His attribute is lightning?
Then what's the deal with
those runes he makes?
[MIMOSA] It looks like
he's using a type of magic
unique to the Heart Kingdom.
Lightning Magic: Tenjiolia.
[NOELLE]
It's fast.
But my Valkyrie armor is faster!
[GAJA]
She truly is a first stage.
But...
My spell has orders.
It will give pursuit until
it strikes its target.
Please, Gaja.
Bring our friend back right now.
Refuse, and we'll have
no recourse but to fight.
[GAJA]
An attack spell.
It seems Lady Mimosa has
become a third stage herself.
As for the spatial mage, it
looks like he can make a portal
between any two points
he has sight of.
Allow me to show
you a brief glimpse
of the difference
in our strength.
He cast it into the sky?
[NOELLE gasps]
So much power.
[GAJA] Nature itself
supplies me with mana.
No human can match its might.
[ASTA yells]
[UNDINE chuckles]
[ASTA]
I can't keep this up forever.
Just how much mana
does this lady have?
Besides, why are we
even fighting, anyway?
[UNDINE]
So that's your devil's power.
Magic negation.
[ASTA]
What the--?
Abominable as that is,
it also sounds quite useful.
[ASTA grunts]
Pleased to meet you,
Devil-possessed
child from Clover.
You may address me as Undine.
I'm one of the
Four Great Spirits,
and I'm contracted to the
Queen of the Heart Kingdom.
You are quite impressive.
But that doesn't mean
you're any match for me.
[UNDINE]
Intriguing.
You don't have any magic
of your own, do you?
Why, that puts you even
beneath the ninth stage.
The ninth stage? The heck
are you talking about?
Oh, that's right.
There isn't a system
to quantify magic strength
in your kingdom, is there?
The weakest mages
are of the ninth stage,
the eighth are above them,
and the seventh above them.
Our system shows which
mages have the most talent.
[ASTA]
I can't move or breathe!
Care to guess which
stage is the highest?
It's stage zero.
True Lighting Magic:
Irial Astrauza!
[GAJA]
If they were still within sight,
I'd be able to sense their mana.
They must've fled
with Spatial Magic.
A wise choice.
But no matter where
they try to hide...
[GAJA] He created a portal
to a place he couldn't see?
[MIMOSA] Plant Creation Magic:
Magic Flower Guidepost!
Spatial Magic.
Fallen Angel Gate!
Here's the deal.
We can't just back down after
watching you show off!
[NOELLE] Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Roar!
[groans]
Your system's trash.
You can't measure ability
just by looking at talent.
[SECRÉ]
Sealing Magic: Inverse Release!
[gasps]
[UNDINE]
This magic...
[ASTA] I'll keep my
Anti-magic all around me
so she can't pull me in again.
I can feel a person's ki
just ahead of me.
And if there's a human up there,
then there must be air!
[gasps]
Mind if I join you?
[NARRATOR] Asta and the
others are attacked
as they arrive in
the Heart Kingdom.
Could it be that this land has
been taken over by a devil?
Black Clover , Page 129:
"The Devil Megicula."
In which Queen
Loropechika appears.