[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] With their
reincarnation finally complete,
Licht and his comrades set out
for the royal capital
to begin their invasion.
[NARRATOR]
Nozel, Noelle, Mimosa, Zora,
Kirsch, and En,
with the still unconscious
captain in tow,
hurried to stop the onslaught.
Someone's attacking that area.
But, that's...
[BOTH]
...the village!
Stop!
Oh, no! Stay back!
[yelling]
[NARRATOR] Asta and Yuno
took a detour and soon
discovered that Hage Village,
their childhood home,
was being threatened
by a violent elf
possessing a Magic
Knight's body.
[LILY]
Asta. Yuno.
You're really brave, Nash!
Good job!
[BOTH]
Stay back! It's our turn now!
Crescent Moon Sickle,
Four Blades!
[DIGIT whimpering]
His mana says it all.
The elf spirit inside him
is crying out in pain.
[ASTA] Is it possible?
Are the elves asking for help?
Hey, Yuno!
[YUNO]
Let's go, Asta!
He's turning into something
that's not an elf at all!
We should set him free!
[ASTA growls]
[screaming]
[YUNO] Did he undo
the Reincarnation Magic?
[ASTA] Now that I have
this sword, I can save them!
Huh? What's up with that
giant rock in the sky?
I don't believe this.
Where did that thing come from?
Oh, boy, I think it's
finally time for me
to have some fun for real!
What the hell?
The city's in danger!
That's our cue, Vanessa!
--Okay!
--[MAGNA] Uh! Uh,
uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh!
Hey! Take your own
broom, would ya?
There's no time to get
flustered. We gotta go!
I wasn't flustered,
I'm just sayin'!
Whatever. Just hang
on tight, okay?
Here we go, Crazy Cyclone,
pedal to the metal!
[YUNO gasps]
[YUNO]
I sense elven magic up ahead.
It's coming from the
north and the south.
[DIGIT] Since there are
two places in danger,
perhaps we should split up?
[ASTA]
Ready?
[YUNO]
Of course.
[BOTH]
See you at the capital!
[CITIZENS screaming]
[LUCK cackling]
[MAGNA]
This ain't right.
I was expectin' to run
into a bad guy here.
[MAGNA]
Instead we find you.
Why?
He, he!
What gives?
Stop that!
Heh!
[BOTH gasp]
What, are you, like, stupid?
Talk to us, Luck!
Luck who? Oh, right, I remember.
I think there was somebody
he wanted to see.
Was it you two?
Either way, he can't.
Because thanks to the
Reincarnation spell,
this body now belongs
to me, Rufel!
Who's Rufel?
What are you goin' on about?
That spell is forbidden magic!
Huh?
I'm not sure of the
details, but some other
entity has taken
over Luck's body!
[MAGNA]
Who could've done that, though?
Wh-- The Eye of
the Midnight Sun?
[VANESSA]
Probably.
Luck and the rest
of the Royal Knights
did infiltrate their
base, after all.
[MAGNA] Wait a minute.
So that big, glowing ball
we saw hoverin'
in the sky was...
[VANESSA]
The hideout.
Crap. I guess the
plan to eliminate
those monsters musta
fallen through somehow.
[clapping]
Hey, you got it! I'm surprised.
It turns out you're not
as dumb as you look!
And by the way, we killed
those Royal Knights,
every last one!
[BOTH gasp]
Here's a tip.
If you decide to get in my way,
the same thing'll
happen to you, too!
[LUCK]
Weird.
For some reason, my kick went
in a different direction.
[ROUGE meows]
[LUCK] Oh. This must be a spell
to protect your friends!
It's so interesting!
You're tryin' my
patience here, pal!
I'll make you feel the burn!
Eat this. Explosive Scatter...
[MAGNA yelps]
[meows]
[VANESSA]
The red thread of fate!
Rouge is always on the
side of the Black Bulls.
So she'll protect Luck,
even though his body
is possessed right now.
[MAGNA] Does your little
pet have an off switch,
'cause it ain't helpin' me!
[VANESSA] Seriously?
If it weren't for Rouge,
Luck's last attack
would have killed you!
Besides, if what he said
before was the truth,
then Luck's lying
dormant in that body!
[MAGNA] Yeah, I know,
that's why I'm tryin'
to give the guy a wakeup call!
And I've got just the thing.
I'll use Flame Magic:
Explosive Scattershot, go!
[LUCK] That's such a simple
spell. It'll never make contact.
[LUCK] They're gone!
I still sense their mana.
I call this one
Explosive Annihilation
Scattershot!
[laughs]
He's fast!
[LUCK] There's not a spell
in the world that can hit me.
Which means two pitiful humans
like you don't stand a chance!
Shut up!
Come on. You're too slow
to dodge my attacks.
Just give up!
[MAGNA]
Thanks, Vanessa!
Honestly, you boys are so quick
to lose your tempers
during a battle!
Why don't you let me intervene?
Then again, if you do
manage to defeat Luck...
Who knows? He might
wake up out of shock!
If you say so--!
Explosive Scatter...
Time to show how
much you've improved
after training with me!
Give it a rest, wouldja?
What does it look
like I'm doin'?
I told you, it won't hit me.
Luck and I may have
fought together
1,000,000 times,
but he's never seen
what I'm about to do next!
Time Bomb Explosive Scattershot!
Whether it makes contact
or not, it still explodes!
Good luck dodgin' em all!
You must be kidding.
That spell is nothing!
Too easy! You could at least
make it a challenge for me!
Whoops!
I thought you said these
things would explode
even if they missed! You
wouldn't lie to me, would ya?
Or did you run out of magic?
[VANESSA] If he's dodging
by sensing the mana,
Magna can just throw in
some regular Scattershots!
[MAGNA] From this
distance, I can't miss!
[LUCK]
Ha, ha!
[gasps]
[LUCK] Too bad.
I picked up on your mana.
[MAGNA]
Nice trick, but I already knew
you had that up your sleeve.
And I know how fast you are!
[LUCK] Did he just make
sure it would explode
at that exact moment?
[MAGNA]
You're definitely not Luck.
Because he woulda figured out...
...I'm stupid enough
to blow myself up, too!
You're a wily fella,
I'll give ya that much,
but only Luck himself
coulda seen that comin'!
And I know how to take a hit,
which is more than
I can say for you!
Flame Magic: Gargantuan
Exploding Fireball!
[MAGNA] One more thing.
Flame Bondage Formation!
[panting]
Listen man, I happen to know
Luck pretty damn well.
You're nothin' but an imposter.
And that means, you don't know
the first thing about
him or about me!
So come at me all you want,
but you'll never win.
Now give our squadmate
back to us, right now!
--[LUCK laughing]
--What?
[MAGNA]
You!
Whoa. What the--?
[LUCK]
I'm sorry.
Who can never win?
Think again, human!
[LUCK]
Now, would you care to explain
how you two weaklings
plan to defeat me?
I'd just love to hear.
Keep on talkin'.
I'll throw as many
of these fireballs
as I have to until
Luck wakes up!
Ah! He vanished!
[LUCK]
Forget it.
You won't put another
scratch on me.
[MAGNA]
He's so fast, I can't see him!
You slow humans could never
catch me at this speed!
I thought the guy
was a monster before,
but this is somethin' else!
Looking for me?
Well, here I am!
Looking for me? Oh, no--
The cat.
[meows]
[LUCK]
Controlling the future.
No, controlling fate
is more like it.
Oh, well. Even a cat
only has so many lives.
And I'm sure that
spell really drains
your magic reserves, right?
The elves are the ones
who were originally blessed
by mana, so between you and me.
Which one of us do you
think will last longer?
[grunts]
[laughs]
[VANESSA panting]
Don't tell me you're
tired already!
I haven't even
broken a sweat yet!
[LUCK giggles] I warned you
about getting in my way.
Let me go.
[meows]
Now every human in
this kingdom will die.
That's the fate you deserve,
and we elves will be happy
to make it a reality!
Shut up, you freak.
Not one more word.
It doesn't matter to me
whether you're an elf or not.
Because I'm through
talkin' to you.
Luck is the one I wanna talk to.
So you hurry up and get
outta that body, right now.
You hear me?
Luck is mischievous.
Always being reckless
and causing trouble,
but he's still like my little
brother! Let go of him!
All you humans are
selfish traitors.
Why should I believe
that you care about him?
[laughs] Don't make me
laugh, there's nothing
that can undo the
reincarnation spell,
especially not
whatever flimsy bond
you claim to have
with this Luck person.
That disgusting human soul
has already been destroyed!
[LUCK cackles]
Is that right? Well,
if that's how it is...
[MAGNA]
Then what are you cryin' for?
You're actin' like
someone you're not,
but I can tell that
you're in there, Luck!
Somewhere!
And I want you
to know that while
you were goofin' off,
I was workin' hard
and trainin' myself
to be stronger!
If that pisses you off,
then snap out of it
and fight me already,
you little moron!
[LUCK]
That's enough.
[VANESSA]
Luck! If you think you can
get rid of us that easily,
you've got another thing coming!
My red thread of fate has you,
and I am never
letting go of you!
Take control of your
body and stop this!
No. Shut up!
[VANESSA]
I won't!
It's not gonna work!
[MAGNA]
Come on!
Shut your mouth!
Please don't!
It's over, human!
Luck!
[ASTA]
You think I'd let you hurt them?
Not a chance!
[VANESSA]
Rouge used up all her power
to trigger a destiny that
would bring Asta here!
[meows]
And who are you?
[ASTA]
I think you know.
But I'll say it
as much as it takes.
We're Luck's friends and
fellow Magic Knights!
[panting]
Asta.
Thank goodness.
[LUCK]
Friends, huh?
This whole routine
is starting to get old.
Hey, wait a second, you don't
have any magic, do you?
I didn't think it was possible
for anyone to be that
despised by mana.
Yeah, well, there's one group
who accepts me
just the way I am!
And they're called
the Black Bulls!
Luck is part of that group,
so you can't have him!
Heh. You can ramble about
friendship all day long.
But you still won't be
able to keep up with me!
[LUCK] You're going to die
by your comrade's hands!
[gasps]
[LUCK] A human shouldn't
be able to match my speed!
[yells]
[ASTA growls]
How's that possible?
Your ki is so full of rage
that I can read it
loud and clear!
And this blade'll follow
you anywhere you go,
it can't resist powerful
magic like yours!
[LUCK]
Now I'm annoyed!
I'm actually impressed! But...
[LUCK] It's no use.
You're no match for my anger!
[grunts] Oh, crap!
[LUCK yells]
[cackling]
[ASTA] He shouldn't
be able to detect me,
but his combat sense
is off the charts!
Hey, Magna and Vanessa,
could you guys give me
some backup over here?
[MAGNA]
You bet!
[LUCK chuckles]
[LUCK] What makes you
think your attacks
will affect me now?
Not only that.
This time, I've got a handle
on how fast you are!
Asta, no!
[ASTA]
I can't hold out for long.
Better make this count!
I've already beat you.
You can stop now.
[yells]
[LUCK]
He's got no magic,
so their plan is to
hide him from me?
Fine, then. I'll spread out
my mana in all directions
until I detect the moment
his weapon interrupts it.
[LUCK] Found him, and he's
headed straight for me.
He can't escape now.
[LUCK]
My rage overpowers everything!
[LUCK giggles]
[LUCK]
There you are!
[VANESSA]
Do it!
[MAGNA]
Here goes!
Huh?
[LUCK]
They messed up my timing!
Now!
He's wide open!
[ASTA] You're strong,
but our bond is stronger!
You lose!
[LUCK groans]
[BOTH]
Nice goin', Asta!
Let's get you outta there!
[ASTA]
He's got so much power left!
You humans are doomed.
Just wait and see!
You really don't know
when to throw in the towel,
do ya, punk?
We're not going to
give up on our friend!
We told you!
[LUCK]
Stop it.
Get your hands off me!
[VANESSA] Luck, you're my
precious little brother!
Hurry up and come back
so you can tease
Magna and eat people's
pudding without permission!
Black Clover ,
Page 105: "Smiles, Tears."
I'm not letting anything
tear the Black Bulls apart!