[NARRATOR] Within the clover's
fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
Asta, born unable
to harness mana,
was granted the power
of Anti-magic
from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability
to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members
of Spade Kingdom's
Dark Triad also possess
powers from the devils
of the underworld
and used them
to launch an invasion
on the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from
his belief in himself
and from the support
of his friends,
Asta continues to fight
for the safety of this world.
[ALL]
We're going to take you down!
[LOROPECHIKA]
The fate of existence itself
is in our hands.
[NOELLE]
Valkyrie Armor: Mermaid Form!
[NARRATOR] Noelle and
Loropechika faced off
against Vanica using the
strategy they had prepared.
However...
[laughs]
[VANICA] Are you ready
for the big one?
Here we go!
You get my best! Lucky you!
Here's 70-percent power!
Do it, Noelle!
[NOELLE]
We were waiting for this!
Nero!
I'm about to seal away
that devil's power
you seem so proud of!
[SECRÉ] Mana Method.
Sealing Magic: Eternal Prison!
I won't let Queen Loropechika,
or this world,
be harmed by scum like you!
It worked!
[SECRÉ]
I did it.
I sealed away her magic
and the devil's power!
Now, the Heart Kingdom
should be safe
from Megicula's wrath,
once and for all!
And the queen's curse
should be gone.
[gasps]
What?
[MEGICULA laughs]
[MEGICULA]
You're obviously weaker than us,
and yet you produced
some surprising magic.
[MEGICULA] You put up
an interesting fight.
I'll give you that much.
[gasps]
[UNDINE]
This ominous mana.
Oh, no! Loropechika!
What in the world is happening?
[laughs] You shouldn't
have looked away!
[yelps]
[ROBERO laughs]
Oh, no!
[ROBERO]
Take this, girlie!
[MIMOSA yelps]
[MIMOSA]
I know what'll stop you!
[ROBERO grunts]
[ROBERO laughs]
[MEGICULA]
You must've thought so carefully
about how to defeat us.
You came terribly close
to containing my power.
[MEGICULA]
Truly splendid, all of you.
Let's play some more.
I haven't had enough yet.
How did we fail?
What went wrong?
Nero's magic should've been
enough to seal you away!
[MEGICULA] Curse-Warding
Magic: Decaying World.
It weakens any spell arrays
that are used against me.
And, it was already active
at 70-percent capacity.
Apparently, it can even
weaken the Sealing Magic
of an arcane-stage opponent.
I'm happy I tried that out.
[VANICA]
Slow down, Megicula!
You're totally
getting in the way!
I'm trying to have fun, y'know!
[UNDINE weakly]
Loro... pechika.
[MEGICULA]
This is the first time
I've ever cursed a Water Spirit.
I see. So, that's what happens.
I'm learning so much
from this experiment.
No. Undine.
[UNDINE]
Where are you?
There!
[giggles]
[giggles] You are
just the cutest!
[LOROPECHIKA]
It's time to study.
Let's take today off.
What? Can we?
Sure we can!
A little break
never hurt anybody!
All we have to do is come back
extra strong tomorrow!
[LOROPECHIKA]
She was always by my side.
[UNDINE] You're doing
so well, Loropechika.
Really? I'm not so sure.
Am I good enough?
Of course you are!
Believe in your abilities!
[LOROPECHIKA]
She always consoled me
when things were tough.
[LOROPECHIKA]
It's beautiful.
[UNDINE] Yes. This is
our precious kingdom.
[LOROPECHIKA]
Tell me, Undine.
Do you think I can
protect this place?
I know you can, Loropechika.
[LOROPECHIKA]
She was always close to me.
Closer than anyone.
[LOROPECHIKA]
Undine.
[screams]
[MEGICULA]
Oops, pardon me.
Your curse must have activated
because I moved closer to you.
You're in too much pain to move,
and now your Water Spirit
can't help you. It's all over.
You better not throw in
the towel, Loropechika!
It was just getting good!
Come on, you've got a little
fight left in you, right?
Hang on, Undine.
Don't die!
[VANICA]
I guess that's it for her.
Well, then, you might
as well die, too.
Loropechika.
Hey, you two.
What?
[NOELLE]
It's not over yet.
Because you both still
have to contend with me!
Please. No one cares
about you anymore.
Without Loropechika's magic,
you're not even a threat now!
See? Way too slow.
[NOELLE grunts]
Let me help you!
[ROBERO laughs]
What a naughty girl,
trying to interfere like that.
[ROBERO] Trust me, honey,
you're about to get a serious
tongue-lashing for
what you've done!
[VANICA sighs]
You can't even compete.
So boring.
[NOELLE]
Not yet.
Say what you want.
I'm not done!
[VANICA]
This girl.
[NOELLE]
You've hurt so many people!
And we'll never forgive you!
Ever!
Aw, cute! You really
gave it your all
for that last little push,
but it doesn't affect me at all!
[NOELLE] I'll protect her,
no matter what!
Point-Blank Sea Dragon's Roar!
[VANICA]
Red Beast!
[gasps]
[VANICA]
Y'see? What did I tell you?
Those measly attacks
won't do any--
What?
[VANICA]
Wait a sec.
[NOELLE panting]
[VANICA giggles] Hey, brat.
What did you say your name was?
[NOELLE]
Noelle Silva.
I am a royal of the Clover
Kingdom and a Magic Knight,
a Black Bull!
[laughs]
[clanging]
[YAMI grunts]
[coughs]
[laughs]
So, you managed to
injure me again.
That certainly was
an impressive feat.
However, this magic I'm
using: it's a bit unsightly.
I'm going to show you something
since it's just you
and me, Yami Sukehiro.
You're about to witness
the awesome power
bestowed upon the
devil-possessed!
[YAMI]
Sounds good.
I've got somethin'
to show you, too.
I call this the power
of an ordinary human!
[FINRAL]
We were keeping watch until
the right moment
to attack Spade.
How did things
turn out like this?
Should I focus on
supporting Yami?
Or should I try and round up
some other Squad Captains?
[FINRAL gasps]
[FINRAL]
No, I can't.
If I make a move,
he'll kill me on the spot!
[DANTE] My Devil Power just
increased to 80 percent.
Eighty-percent? Was that
supposed to impress me?
[YAMI] Dammit, where's all
that mana coming from?
[YAMI] By the way, your
eyeliner's running, creep!
When possessed by a devil,
one's power is shared with
a resident of the underworld.
By its very nature, that
exchange must take place
between two realms.
And until the door is opened,
we cannot reach 100 percent.
[DANTE] Though, I'm not
sure whether that applies
to the little imp over there.
Now for Gravity Magic.
Gravity Singularity technique.
You'd be no use as a dead man,
but I can rip off
a leg, at least.
[ALL gasp]
[YAMI]
Seriously?
That would've taken a lot
more than my leg!
[DANTE laughs]
[YAMI]
Dark Cloaked...
...Dimension Slash!
[YAMI] Wasn't expecting
him to warp that!
This gravity's way stronger
than what he was using
at the beginning!
If I use Black Moon, they might
cancel each other out.
But, as long as he's
generating gravity,
I can't afford to
waste that move.
I'll just keep my
Mana Zone condensed
and my senses sharp
until I can get behind him!
[YAMI]
No, wait!
There's no point
in cutting him down
if he's just gonna regenerate!
I need something
powerful and precise!
[YAMI]
I'll focus on one spot.
You were surprisingly
entertaining to fight,
Yami Sukehiro.
I mean, you're just
a human, but... still.
Huh?
--[FINRAL] Yami!
--[VANESSA] Captain, no!
[DANTE]
Now, then.
Who's up next?
[ASTA growls]
[gasps]
[GROUP gasps]
[YAMI]
Right here and now.
I'll push past my limits!
If I let my squad down...
Well, then I'd be a
piss-poor captain, wouldn't I?
[YAMI] I'll take that condensed
Mana Zone and condense it more!
Focusing it on one spot!
[laughs] I admit, that's
quite a clever strategy,
but you'll need a lot more
than that, my friend!
[YAMI]
Dark Magic...
...Death Thrust!
[grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
Well, I said "thrust,"
but it was more like a cannon.
[ASTA]
Whoa.
Captain Yami really
is incredible!
Sorry, pal.
I couldn't help it, you had
"target" written all over you.
[DANTE]
Impossible!
There's no human capable
of beating me at my best!
No.
Obviously, I'm wrong.
There is someone, and he just
blew a hole right through me!
[DANTE] That was irritating,
to say the least.
But, thank you, Yami Sukehiro.
[gasps]
Is he... regenerating?
How did that not kill him?
[DANTE]
My innate ability is Body Magic,
and the devil's power makes me
even better at restoring myself
after a hard hit like that.
It's impossible for me to die,
grow old, or deteriorate!
But, let me be clear.
I detest how ugly
it is when I morph.
The sight of it reminds me
that I'm being pushed.
So, I prefer never to use
this magic if I can help it.
This is gettin' way out of hand.
I mean c'mon, are you
even human at this point?
Hideous though it may be,
it's quite gratifying!
[DANTE growls]
[YAMI]
Death Thrust!
You've amazed me once again.
You should be proud.
Your instincts and combat
finesse are superior to my own.
It's making me jealous!
But you see, I can't die!
Otherwise, you might've
stood a chance.
You may be skilled, but that
means nothing in this fight!
The world is just
so terribly unfair!
Try as you might, there are
still things you can't control!
It's the same for me!
[DANTE] Every once in a while,
be it because of raw talent
or careful training, some foe
manages to miraculously
point their blade at my throat.
In the end, I have no choice
but to decimate them completely!
That, my friend,
is the height of ecstasy!
[DANTE growls]
[grunts]
Be careful!
Be careful, Captain!
[YAMI] I can't get close
enough to land a hit!
[laughing]
[YAMI]
But if I move too far away,
he starts chucking rocks at me!
Damn you!
[DANTE laughs]
[ASTA]
Captain Yami is still fighting.
He pushed past his limits,
and here I am.
Stand up! Come on,
stupid body, move!
Please. Please!
[cackling]
[YAMI panting]
[ASTA]
Captain Yami.
[grunts]
[ASTA growls]
[ASTA]
No!
[sighs] I'll admit it.
I can't win this
fight on my own.
This guy's creepy and insane!
Plus he can't die and he
never runs out of mana!
[YAMI] Hey! I'm gonna
need backup over here.
Asta!
You got a death wish, boy?
Hey, kid! Were you watching?
Look alive, kid.
Why're you just standin' there
like some kinda chicken?
I wouldn't give you more
than you could handle.
Do something.
Fight him your way, kid.
[laughs] You fell down!
[YAMI] You're not worried
about me, are you, kid?
'Cause I'll tell you right now,
it's about a billion years
too early for that.
Ready!
You're both going to
challenge me at once--
how absolutely delightful!
Entertain me!
I'm starting to get bored.
[panting]
[YAMI]
You'd better keep up, Asta.
[ASTA]
We've got this, Captain Yami!
[ASTA, YAMI yell]
[laughing]
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[ROBERO]
I Wanna Lick.
Come on. I wanna lick!
And you're looking
awfully lickable!
Um. That doesn't work for me.
Here! Maybe you'd like this!
[laughs] This is so
yummy and sweet.
A perfect candidate
for a lick, if you ask me!
Then I bet this'll
be even better!
[laughs] This is sweet too, but
the rich flavor and cold texture
put it very high on
the lickability scale!
Now that you've
got what you want,
we can put an end to all this
pointless fighting, right?
Actually, there's still one
more thing that's missing.
[NOELLE]
Leave this part to me, Mimosa.
[ROBERO groans]
Is this what you had in mind,
you stupid sicko?
[ROBERO]
It's perfect! Unless, of course,
you're willing to step
on me even harder!
I figured that was it.
Thank you, Noelle.
Looks like you're a lot
braver than I am.
[YAMI] Ready, Asta?
It's time for the counterattack!
[ASTA]
I'm on it, Captain Yami!
I'm gonna push past my limits
and destroy this freak
once and for all!
Black Clover , Page 167:
"Black Oath."