[mumbling] Black Clover time.
Let's do it!
[NARRATOR]
The semifinal match of
the Royal Knights
Selection Exam has begun.
Asta and the B Team
are pitted against
Langris and the G Team.
It's fight after
ferocious fight,
struggle after savage struggle,
and clash after cutthroat clash!
[ZORA]
You jerks.
My father knew what
a knight should be.
And you are no Magic Knight!
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile...
[CHARMY whimpers]
[SHEEP whimper]
[NARRATOR] Charmy had left the
battlefield for a nearby forest,
where she was foraging
for ingredients to use
in tasty dishes for Yuno
and the Wizard King.
But she inadvertently nibbled
a hallucinogenic mushroom
and fell into the
strangest dream.
[CHARMY whimpering]
[SHEEP whimpering]
[yells]
[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[CHARMY roars]
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone meatshank
appeared and put
an end to the fight.
Oh! So yummy! Feed Charmy more!
[CHARMY munching]
This is what happy tastes like!
Now that my tummy's
nice and full,
I feel kinda sleepy.
[NARRATOR]
After its triumph, it was hailed
as the Miracle Shank,
and its story became legend.
[mumbling] That sounds familiar.
I feel like I've heard
it somewhere before.
[whimpering]
[CHARMY]
"The Seven Faces of Charmy"!
For the world, no,
for the universe full
of diehard Charmy Pappitson
fans out there.
We're going to answer
your prayers and show you
all the adorable Charmy moments
you've been dying to see!
I'm ready!
[CHARMY]
Number one: Charmy the Wanderer!
Number two: Festival Charmy!
Look at all the
yummy festival food!
[CHARMY] Number three:
Happy Birthday Charmy!
Number four:
Charmy the Thunder God!
Rawr!
[CHARMY]
Number five: Charmy the Alien!
Take me to your leader!
[CHARMY] Finally,
number six: Merlion Charmy!
So cool!
I thought there were seven.
[ASTA, YUNO]
"The Mystery of the Grimoires."
Um. What happened?
I think we've shrunk.
Anyway, like I was saying.
My grimoire and yours
are totally different.
[YUNO]
Okay.
A grimoire's measurements,
it's size, thickness, etcetera,
are determined by
its owner's talent.
All right then, let's
compare grimoires.
Come on, hand it over.
No way.
[ASTA] Why not? You're afraid
you'll lose, aren't you?
[YUNO]
Not a chance.
[ASTA]
Hey!
Don't get so cocky just 'cause
the girls kinda like you.
--[YUNO] Let it go.
--[ASTA] Ugh!
[YUNO]
Asta Versus the Anti-Birds.
[grunting] Hey, get off of
me you psycho birds!
Shoo! Shoo!
Wait, stop! What do
you think you're doing?
No! Hey! Let go!
[YUNO]
Bye, Asta!
[ASTA] Don't just
stand there, you jerk!
Help me!
[NARRATOR]
"The Spitting-est Image!" Go!
And the winner is...
[NARRATOR]
This anti-bird!
[NOELLE, ASTA, MAGNA]
What?!
[SALLY]
"Salamander on Rice: So Nice!"
Gel Magic: Go Sticky Salamander!
'Mander!
Aw, it's so adorable!
I suppose, but Nero here
is obviously much cuter.
[NERO chirps]
You should try it
over rice some time.
Totally delicious!
[STICKY SALAMANDER gasps]
This girl is crazy!
Yum, I want a bowl!
That one is, too!
[NOELLE]
Show Some Respect!
I am so regal,
it's beyond belief.
Wouldn't you agree?
An illegal mountain thief?
Who are you calling
a bandit, commoner?
I'm royalty! Did you mishear?
Oh! So you're a buccaneer.
Who are you calling
a pirate, peasant?
I'm of the royal family.
Wait, hold on. We're family?
[gasps] Just shut up.
[NOELLE]
"Look at Me!"
Hey, Dorksta, look at me.
Notice anything? Huh?
How do you like me
in a swimsuit?
[ASTA]
Huh?
Well?
[ASTA]
Uh...
[ASTA] Wow. It's so
sparkly! Isn't it heavy?
Bet you could keep
birds away with that.
Hm... Like this scarecrow
we had back in the village.
[NOELLE]
Hey!
What are you looking
at, you creep?!
[screams] But you
told me to look!
Well, stop it. Stupidsta.
[CRAB 40A]
Crabbity...
[GAUCHE]
"Changing Voices."
[coughs]
No! Marie's sick?
Did she catch a cold?
It's from being
in that dank cave!
Are you okay, my angel?
[YAMI'S voice] I'm fine.
My throat's a little sore,
that's all. Hold on.
My voice sounds funny.
What? No!
Why does my precious,
perfect angel
sound just like Captain Yami?
Never mind, Big Brother.
Just forget about me.
Asta's the one who
needs your help now!
[YAMI'S voice]
Take my magic power with you.
You might need it.
Not you, too, old hag!
[YAMI'S voice] I've used up
so much mana, I might only
have one spell left in me.
And Finral now?
[coughs]
[MARIE'S voice] My throat
is starting to hurt, too.
[ALL, in YAMI'S voice]
Aw, what a cute voice!
[GAUCHE]
"Marie's in Danger"
And-a one, two, three.
How to say "no" to an angel!
As much as I like to spoil
Marie, I must sometimes
harden my heart and
decline her requests,
no matter how angelically
she makes them.
Like so:
Hey, Big Brother,
please go back
to help Sister and Asta!
[GAUCHE]
No. You'd be in danger if I did.
Hey, Big Brother!
I want some rice gratin
with hot, melty cheese.
[GAUCHE] No! Your tongue
would be in danger.
It would get burned.
Hey, Big Brother,
can we stay out here
in the sun all day?
No! Your skin will be in danger
if you stay out in
full sun too long!
UV rays are a mighty foe!
Hey, Big Brother, show me
a super cool spell!
No! Wait, yes!
[GAUCHE]
Marie, look at me.
Mirage Brigade!
[MARIES]
Big Brother, you're awesome!
[GAUCHE]
Uh-oh. Now I'm in danger!
[MARIES]
Hey, Big Brother?
[GAUCHE]
"Double Gauche."
Big Brother!
Will you swing me
around like Asta?
[ASTA, MARIE laughing]
Swing you around like him?
Are you okay?
I can't bring myself
to disappoint her.
I'll just have my
clone handle it.
Mirror Magic: My Real Double!
Now, swing her around.
I could never put
Marie in any danger.
You're so right!
Let's try this instead!
[GAUCHES]
Here we go! Around and around!
Aw.
[FINRAL]
"What is Mana?"
All right, Asta, let's hear it.
Can you tell me
something about mana?
Yes! One thing I know is
this is how you write it.
See, there it is: mana.
Write it like this,
and it's "man alive."
That's right. And mana
is supernatural energy.
It's a vital force in this world
that all mages call upon.
Yeah, and everyone has it,
whether they're a
noble or a commoner.
Everyone but me!
[FINRAL] As I was saying, mages
call upon mana to cast spells.
If you don't have enough
mana, you're out of luck.
You can't use magic
until it's restored.
You getting all this?
Yeah, I got it.
[FINRAL]
Hm? Oh! What a lovely flower!
I think this would make
an excellent present
for some lucky lady.
I'll save you!
[FINRAL]
My! How feisty.
We can pick up the lesson later.
[MAGNA, LUCK]
"Crackling Magna Typhoon!"
Hey, everyone! How's it going?
Where's your excitement, people?
Kick it up a notch
or two already!
Today we're going
to teach you a fun
and easy way to pull off
a Crackling Magna Typhoon
in the comfort of your own home.
First, get a length of
lightning rope ready, like so.
Are you kidding?
Then, you wrap it around
your very own Magna.
Quit zapping me!
Right. Now you try
whipping up a rope, Magna.
I can't do that!
You're doing great.
We're almost done!
Once the rope's nice and tight,
give him a push
to get him spinning.
Here we go!
There ya have it, folks!
A Crackling Magna Typhoon,
so easy anyone can do it!
No, you idiot!
You're the only one
who can do it!
I hate you!
Bye for now!
[MAGNA]
"The Real Story:
24 Hours with a
Magic Knight Squad!"
This is lukewarm.
Yes, Yami, sir!
[YAMI]
Too hot!
[MAGNA]
Yes, Yami, sir!
[YAMI]
Can't see anything.
Yes, Yami, sir!
Now get out.
Yes, Yami, sir.
[SEKKE]
"Sekke's Ha-hah! Lesson!"
Ha, ha!
[SEKKE]
No, like this. Ha, ha !
[ASTA]
Ha, ha!
[SEKKE]
I'm sorry, Asta, but you have
not yet attained Ha-ha-hood.
Ha, ha!
What is "Ha-ha-hood"?
[SEKKE]
"Sekke's Ha-hah Lesson! Part 2."
[ASTA]
Wait, we're doing this again?
Of course, what did you expect?
There's a great deal
more work to be done
if you wish to
attain Ha-ha-hood.
[ASTA] Your Shooting Star
is totally awesome.
[SEKKE]
I'm glad someone appreciates it.
[ASTA]
Well, yeah.
Especially that thing
on the front. So cool!
[SEKKE]
Excellent!
You're getting closer
to Ha-ha-hood.
I see now!
That's what ha, ha is!
Yes! Now you, too, are ha, ha!
[laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
Are all men such idiots?
[GORDON mumlbes]
"My Magic."
[mumbling] There's something
I'd really like to show you.
It's my curse magic.
Within the next ten minutes,
you will blink your
eyes. Let's Go-rdon!
[SHEEP whimpering]
[whimpering] Let's Go-rdon.
[mumbling] No matter where you
go, I'll always be there.
[CHARMY]
"Magical Sleuth Charmy"!
Hello, everyone.
The great Magical
Sleuth Charmy here.
You're joining me just
in time to help me solve
a mystery and uncover what
dastardly villain ate my cake.
On my honor as
a master detective,
I will determine whodunit!
[YAMI]
That's easy: you did it.
[CHARMY]
The scene of the crime: my room!
This is a brazen thief!
Look, it's you, okay?
[CHARMY] But the scoundrel
made a big mistake:
They left this handprint behind!
That looks a lot
like your handprint.
The thieving cake eater.
Yeah, that's you.
[gasps]
It was me!
[GROUP]
Well, yeah.
[HEAD CHEF 23A]
"3-Second Courtly Cooking."
Hello, everyone,
Clover Kingdom's
royal chef here, bringing you
easy three-second recipes
even a beginner can make.
Today we're whipping up
a three-second curry.
To keep it simple,
we'll start with a roux
purchased from the market.
Then carrots, onions,
and potatoes.
You can add mushrooms
or tomatoes if you like.
Flavoring your curry
with a touch
of chocolate or coffee
can give it more depth.
Now, simply take your
ingredients, and...
[yells] Use magic to
dice them up and stew them.
The more passion
you put into it,
the better your curry will be.
Three seconds and done!
Wasn't that easy?
All right, come to Mama!
So good!
This has been Three-Second
Courtly Cooking,
with easy recipes that
anyone can make.
[BOTH]
See you later!
Impossible!
[YUNO]
"Birthday."
I finally figured out how
to command the wind spirit.
I've decided to name you Bell
and make today your birthday.
I got you a cake and everything.
Yay!
[YUNO]
There's just one candle.
I hope that's okay.
Hooray. Happy birthday, Bell.
Pretty!
Go on, make a wish,
then blow it out.
[BELL]
Well, um...
Ah!
[inhales]
[BELL]
Huh? Where did the cake go?
I found it.
[KLAUS]
"It's Not Like I'm Worried."
[KLAUS] He's brushing each tooth
carefully and thoroughly,
ensuring maximum cleanliness.
[KLAUS gasps]
Don't scrub so roughly!
[KLAUS whimpers]
[KLAUS]
His eyes! No!
Safe.
It's a chilly night.
Is he going to catch cold?
Um, Klaus, at this
point I'm not sure
if it's sweet or just creepy.
Just creepy.
[YUNO]
"Family."
So. Yuno.
Is it true that, when
you make new friends,
you treasure them like you
would your own family?
What a lovely idea!
That sounds so wonderful.
Yeah.
Family.
So, does it look a little
something like this?
Hey, Big Brother Klaus!
[giggles] Aw, that tickles!
Little Brother Yuno.
I got something special for you.
[YUNO gasps]
My own glasses!
Wow, you're the best.
Thank you, Brother!
Yeah, no way.
[MARS]
"Long Suffering."
One of my more useful spells.
Flame Recovery Magic:
Phoenix Robe.
I have to say,
that looks quite warm.
It is.
And also rather heavy.
Very heavy.
What's more, if my face
itches, I can't scratch it.
[ASTA, NOELLE, CHARMY]
"How Come?"
[ASTA grumbles]
What's bothering you?
So, if that Salamander thing
was surrounded by flames,
how come Fana didn't
get burned to a crisp?
Uh, because it's magic?
Okay, and when we
use Sea Dragon's Lair
to go underwater, how come
our clothes never get wet?
[NOELLE]
Again, it's magic.
And if kelp grows underwater,
then how come it doesn't
turn the ocean into broth?
Leave all of the
culinary questions
to the brilliant
Professor Charmy!
You see, the explanation
is quite elementary.
Kelp possesses a component
within its cells
known as glutamic acid.
That's the stuff that
produces a broth!
Because of a
characteristic we call
selective permeability,
kelp is able to take in only
the materials necessary
to survive and excrete
everything that's extraneous.
And since the broth-producing
glutamic acid helps to keep
the kelp alive, it remains
inside the cells until
the organism eventually
dries up and dies.
When that happens,
the cells burst open,
releasing the glutamic acid
and creating the broth!
Just say "it's magic"
and leave it at that.
[YAMI] "Captain Yami's"--
Ugh, seriously?
Why did I get stuck
doin' this crap?
Okay, so obviously the
Wizard King is at the top,
then after that you've got
your Grand Magic Knight.
Man, this is boring.
Shouldn't someone
lower-ranked be doin' this?
I'm gonna kill you!
[ASTA, NOELLE]
What?
[YAMI]
"Grilled Squid."
[YAMI] Today I'm gonna
show you how to prepare
this tasty grilled squid.
[ASTA, NOELLE]
Yay!
[YAMI]
It's so easy, anyone can do it.
But you're not going
to cheat and use magic
like that one chef
did before, are you?
What? Just watch.
First, pull out the guts
and cut slits into it.
[ASTA]
Real directions!
[YAMI]
Yeah.
[YAMI] Then you season it with
salt, sugar, mirin, and ginger.
Okay.
[YAMI]
Then grill it.
[BOTH]
Normal cooking!
[YAMI]
And, done.
[BOTH]
Yummy!
There ya have it.
Grilled delicious squid
that anyone can make.
No joke this time.
[CHARMY] "The Seven Faces
of Charmy, Part II"!
Since we're well aware
that there's been
a worldwide outcry
from the Charmy Army
for more content featuring
your favorite character,
today we're bringing you
an all-new installment
of this beloved bonus segment!
Number one:
Christmas Tree Charmy!
Number two: Charmy the Ninja!
...for I am but a shadow
cloaked in the darkness!
[CHARMY] Number three:
Lion Dance Charmy!
Number four: Charmy
the Foot Soldier!
Number five: Samba Charmy!
And last but not least,
number six: Buddha Charmy!
Nope. You still didn't
make it to seven.
[CHARMY] "The Seven Faces
of Charmy Special"!
Special number one:
[CHARMY]
Stag Beetle Charmy!
Special number two:
Ooh-la-la!
[CHARMY]
Sexy Charmy!
Special number three:
Luchador Charmy!
Hi-yah!
[CHARMY] Special number
four: Mistress Charmy!
[CHARMY]
Special number five:
I'm a star!
[CHARMY]
Ballerina Charmy!
And finally, special number six:
Santa Charmy!
Yeah, that was still
only six of them.
[CHARMY chuckles]
[CHARMY gasps]
[CHARMY]
My prince of provisions?
Hm?
Guess it was just a dream.
Oh, well, better
gather more goodies
and get back to the battlefield.
[CHARMY sings]
[NARRATOR] And so Charmy's
nightmare came to an end.
Or, whatever it was.
Anyway, it's over.
But wait! Asta's battle
isn't! Far from it!
In fact, it's growing
more heated by the moment!
[ZORA]
Look at him, smirking with
all the confidence in the world.
Dammit.
You jerks.
My father knew what
a knight should be.
And you are no Magic Knight!
[NARRATOR]
The fight pitting Asta, Mimosa,
and the mysterious Xerx
against Langris,
Fragil, and Sekke has
reached a fever pitch.
Who will win the
semi-final match?
Black Clover , Page 83:
"Burn It Into You."
The battle continues next time!