[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR] After his triumph,
he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] After hearing Yami's
tale about how never
giving up can open new doors,
Asta was filled with fresh
resolve to face his rival.
[ASTA]
All right!
Time to work hard, catch up to
Yuno, and leave him behind!
[NARRATOR]
Just then...
[banging]
[MAGNA] Damn! That's the
biggest owl I've ever heard!
Quit bangin' the door down.
If you're lookin' for Captain
Yami's Black Bulls,
then you came to the right--
Whoa, what just happened?
[ASTA] Hey, I recognize her!
That's Fuegoleon's sister!
Dude. What is this about?
Is the Captain of the Crimson
Lion Kings really here?
[LUCK]
Mm-hm.
Yeah, Captain,
why're you showin' up
on our doorstep out of nowhere?
[MEREOLEONA]
It's Mereoleona!
[ASTA screams, groans]
[YAMI] Hey, why's it so damn
noisy in here all of a sudden?
Sheesh, can't a guy
even take a du-- Oh.
Dangerous animal on the loose!
Everybody, hurry up and get
outta the building now!
Trust me, if you get caught,
just play dead!
Don't make eye contact
or it'll eat--
Ow!
[MEREOLEONA]
Shut up and take this, moron.
[YAMI]
What is it?
Lemme guess, it's some
kinda poison drink
that'll tear holes in my throat
and make me spit
fireballs, right?
[MEREOLEONA]
It's for visiting my brother!
Do you have a death wish?
I don't need a thank-you
present for that.
Besides, if this is what
a beast like you drinks,
I guarantee it's not fit
for human consumption.
Don't want it.
[MEREOLEONA]
Then I'll kill you!
So you came here to thank
me and you've already
moved on to killing me?
I'll thank you then kill you.
[YAMI]
Man, you do not joke around!
That's because I hate jokes.
Captain! You sure
you don't want this?
Fine. I'll take it! [hiccups]
[meows]
Oh, I understand now,
you're only here to talk
to Captain Yami,
that's all! What a relief!
And here I thought I was
about to get dragged off
to somewhere crazy agai--!
Uh.
Ha!
[MEREOLEONA]
You three. Come with me.
--[LUCK laughing]
--[ASTA screaming]
I don't like this!
Where are we goin'?
It's somewhere bad,
I just know it!
Wait! Why am I getting
dragged off, too?
Maybe there's gonna be a fight!
[NOELLE groaning]
[whispering] I just made
everyone some tea,
but I guess you're
heading out now.
Hey, Captain!
This madwoman is
trying to kidnap
three of your squad members.
Don't you think you
should do something?
As long as she leaves,
she can do whatever she wants.
[ASTA] What do you mean she
can do whatever she wants?
If you don't help us,
we're gonna be barbecued!
Come on, Captain, you
can't let her do that!
[laughs] If it's only
you three she wants,
then you guys musta done
somethin' really rotten!
You deserve this,
especially you, Luck!
These are the squad
members who passed
the Royal Knights
Selection Exam.
[MAGNA screams]
Huh?
We made it?
So we're in the Royal Knights?
That means even though
I lost the tournament,
Yuno didn't get ahead of me!
We're still neck-and-neck
in the race
to be the next Wizard King!
This is great!
[NOELLE] Yay! I'm so
happy I made the cut!
Now Asta and I can finally--!
Uh, I mean, not that I care
about anything like that!
I'm glad Asta passed the exam,
but only because I'm proud
of him as a squadmate!
That's all he is to me, really!
Nothing more and nothing less!
End of story!
Hey, Noelle! We're gonna
be awesome Royal Knights!
Yeah. Sure.
Just don't rush in
on your own again
and ruin things for
the rest of us.
I won't! But I've been
training super hard,
so it'll still turn
out okay if I do!
Idiot! What part of "don't do
it" did you not understand?
Sorry!
Actually, wait.
There was supposed to
be one more Black Bull
who made the Royal Knights.
[VANESSA, MAGNA]
Really? There's one more?
Um. I'm sure it was probably me.
Over here! Pick me! Me! Me!
I don't see him.
I'm right behind you!
It's Magna Swing of
the Black Bulls here!
It isn't you!
[MAGNA gasps]
Oh, well. He received
his summons.
[MAGNA]
I didn't pass after all.
Man, that's rough.
[LUCK]
Ha! Aw, too bad for you, Magna!
Working with the Royal Knights
is gonna make me even stronger,
so you probably won't be
a match for me anymore.
Hold on, Luck, be
careful what you say--
Rub it in my face all
you want to, jerk!
If I fall down seven times,
I'll get up eight times!
I just hope that you
won't be too intimidated
by how buff and awesome I am
when you come back
to the hideout!
All right! Time to start
on my training!
Let's do this, Vanessa!
Me? But I was just about
to pop open this booze.
I want to get stronger,
and pronto!
No, I have to get stronger!
Well, if you insist.
I guess I can make time
for you, Mr. Delinquent.
[meows]
I'm not a delinquent!
Better say your prayers, Luck!
And uh, come back
here in one piece.
[laughing] Sure!
The same goes for you guys!
Gotcha!
Obviously.
[whispering] Your friends'll
be cheering you on.
[YAMI]
Heh.
Look at 'em. Smiles all around.
Give 'em hell.
[MEREOLEONA] From the
Silver Eagles, Nils Ragus!
[NILS]
Here!
The Vice-Captain of
the Coral Peacocks.
Where is Kirsch Vermillion?
Uh, I never tire of hearing
the beautiful melody
that is my name.
From the Blue Rose Knights,
we have Puli Angel!
In the flesh!
What do you say, folks?
Did you miss me?
'Cause I'm back!
[MEREOLEONA] En Ringard of
the Green Praying Mantises!
Yes! I'm fired up!
Let's put the "mush"
in "mushroom"!
Yay.
[MEREOLEONA]
Representing the Aqua Deer,
Captain Rill Boismortier!
As well as Fragil Tormenta!
--Here.
--Yep. That's me!
I'm the failure who lost even
though he's a captain.
Please, sir!
Now's the time to dig
deep and stay strong.
And from the Golden
Dawn, Hamon Caseus,
Klaus Lunettes, Mimosa
Vermillion, and Yuno!
Sound off!
[KLAUS, MIMOSA, YUNO, HAMON]
Here!
Ha, ha! I see our squad
is the most represented
among this group.
Well, we are the
best of the best.
Can't say I'm surprised.
It's only natural they'd
want you on the team!
I mean, you were
basically the MVP
of the whole tournament!
Hey, are you listening?!
Now then, the Black Bulls.
Luck Voltia, Noelle
Silva, and Asta!
Are you present?
[LUCK, NOELLE, ASTA]
Here!
How's that, Yuno?
No way am I gonna let
you leave me in the dust!
Even if I stumble,
I'll keep on goin'!
And then stumble again.
He is pretty good at that.
[ASTA] Really, you
think so? Thanks a lot.
Wait, what did you say?
You know it's the truth.
Okay, but I'm good at
not givin' up, too!
[NOELLE] I can vouch
for the stumbling part.
Oh, Asta. I'm so happy
you and I get a chance
to work together again!
Yeah! Should be fun!
[NOELLE grumbles]
Let me introduce
myself as well.
As you may know, I am
Mereoleona Vermillion.
The Captain of
the Royal Knights!
No way!
I didn't know she would be
in charge of this thing!
Come on. Are you guys
not surprised?
No. I had assumed
it would be her.
She was the one
who came to get us
and now she's doing
the roll call.
What's wrong?
Nothin'! Everything's
peachy, Captain, I swear!
Our Captain really is
something special.
She was the one who rallied
the Crimson Lion Kings
after what happened
to Captain Fuegoleon.
Right.
[KLAUS] I personally wish
that title had gone
to our Captain Vangeance,
but he's busy commanding
security forces in the capital.
So she'll have to do.
If anyone has a complaint,
then please don't hold back.
I certainly won't hold back
when I crush you for it!
[YUNO]
Really?
[MEREOLEONA] Now then,
let's get back to business.
After enduring a cutthroat
competition,
you 16 have been selected
to be a part of this team.
Assuming there are
no objections,
I hereby announce
myself as your leader,
from this moment until
the Eye of the Midnight
Sun is annihilated!
[ROYAL MAGIC KNIGHTS]
Yes, ma'am!
[MEREOLEONA] Hm? One, two,
three. Someone's missing.
Does he think
promptness is a joke?
[ZORA]
I'm a bit late. Sorry, guys.
[MEREOLEONA grunts]
Well, well. A class clown.
Heh. Come on,
let's be reasonable.
If I'm entrusting my life
to you, I'd be stupid
not to find out
what you're made of.
Anyway, the pleasure's all mine.
Hey, it's you again!
[gasps]
[ASTA] Wait. Why are you
wearin' a Black Bulls robe?
[laughing]
You! Explain to me why you're
wearin' that robe, right now!
Idiot. I'm one of
the Black Bulls,
why wouldn't I be
wearin' the uniform?
[ASTA, NOELLE]
Huh?
Wow!
You're a Black Bull?
Like, our Black Bulls?
That's it! I want to know
everything in detail!
[laughs] All of a sudden,
you got me feelin' nostalgic
for the old days.
I used to go around
beatin' the daylights outta
Magic Knights one by one,
and I had some pretty
good reasons for doin' it.
You hurt Magic Knights, really?
That is not okay--
Chill out.
I just told you I had a good
reason for it, didn't I?
Here's what happened.
Not too long ago,
I ran into this outrageous
monster of a guy and ended up
takin' a serious beating.
[panting]
What's your problem?
What's this?
I like ya, so I want to
give you one of these.
If you don't like it,
you can toss it.
[ZORA] Stop playin' games
with me, Magic Knight!
Like I'd be caught dead in this!
Besides, I don't think
you're supposed to go
handing these things
out like candy!
Oh, I wasn't expecting
you to know that.
[gasping]
Well, if you ever do
feel like putting it on,
then be my guest.
And that's how it went down.
Captain Yami scouted me
for the Black Bulls
and made me an official
member of the squad.
But that's not fair, Xerx!
You're obviously playin' dirty!
I had to work so hard to get in!
Yeah, by the way,
my name's not Xerx.
I'm Zora Ideale,
and I outrank you.
--[NOELLE gasps]
--[LUCK laughs]
[ASTA]
Huh? What's this Zora stuff?
Don't tell me that's your name!
Heh. If I'm not mistaken, that's
exactly what I just said, runt.
Why would you lie about that?
[ZORA]
You know what they say.
To fool your enemies, you have
to start with your friends.
[ASTA]
What? But who's your enemy?
And are you really
higher ranked than me?
[ZORA] That's right.
So start grovelin'.
[ASTA] Forget it!
You start apologizing!
Not cool, Xerx,
I mean Zoola, whatever!
[NOELLE]
Zora.
My head hurts!
This is confusing!
Damn, you're a noisy
little guy, aren't ya?
[ZORA]
This is it.
From now on, I'm
gonna set my sights
on bein' a super mage.
A real Magic Knight!
Here. As a souvenir
of our reunion,
have a rainbow stinkbug.
[ZORA laughs]
The stench! It comes
at you in waves!
Huh? Hey, it's not so bad
once you're used to it.
I highly doubt that!
[ASTA]
No, you're right!
It's burnin' off
all my nose hairs!
You're tough. We should
spar sometime!
I'm hearing an awful
lot of jibber-jabber
from over here!
[NOELLE, ASTA]
Sorry, ma'am!
Hey, wait. It's just us!
[MEREOLEONA]
Everyone else left ages ago
to change into their
Royal Knights robes!
You mean we get special
uniforms and everything?
This day keeps gettin'
cooler by the minute!
They were designed
for our fight against
the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Which means they'll be
exceptionally resistant
to magic attacks.
Now quit wasting my time
and go put yours on!
[BELL]
Hey! Check this out!
Handsome, huh?
This thing is practically
made for him.
I've fallen in love
all over again!
[ASTA gasps]
I never imagined you
and I would be wearing
the same robe, Asta.
It's not like you'll ever hold a
candle to my magic abilities.
I'm going to become
the next Wizard King.
No way. I will!
Keep dreaming.
All right! Is everyone
wearing their robes now?
Ah, it's so beautiful.
To think a mere manmade garment
would suit a god so perfectly!
To think your narcissism
would give me
such a perfect urge to puke!
They certainly make it official.
And I must say, they're
awfully flattering
on those of us who sport
a more robust figure.
That's right!
I'm ready for anything!
I suppose they're
not too terrible.
Hey, uh...
How come mine is so short?
Yours is the only one like that!
Asta, don't joke around.
But I'm not joking! This is just
how it was when I put it on!
[laughing] I guess when
you're half a man,
you only get half a robe.
We ran out of fabric.
You see, apart from you lot,
we ended up calling upon
some extra people to help out.
--[ASTA] Extra people?
--[NOELLE] Some extra people?
These Magic Knights may not
have participated in
the selection exam,
but their special skills
will be indispensable.
Meet Cob Portaport
and Shiren Tium.
Shiren's Stone Creation
Magic can summon
a mockup of the enemy's hideout,
and give us an idea
of the magic power possessed
by the mages hiding inside.
And Cob can wield the
ever-useful Spatial Magic.
We've enlisted his support
since Finral Roulacase
is still in recovery.
Last but not least,
Nozel Silva!
He'll be joining us as well.
[NOELLE]
My brother's here?
The Silver Eagles captain
will be fighting with us?
I'm glad we have him!
Definitely!
Having the opportunity to
fight with somebody like him--
it's really an honor!
I was certain you would
refuse my offer.
What caused you to
change your mind?
Please spare me
the idle chit-chat.
I'm only acting on orders
from His Majesty.
With these three,
the Royal Knights are complete.
I'm expecting great things!
Hey! That's not very
nice of you, Nozel.
What makes you think you
can just waltz in here
and become one of
the Royal Knights?
I mean, you didn't even compete
in the selection exam!
A better question is why
you chose to take the test
in the first place,
despite being a Captain.
Huh?! I thought that
was the only way in!
Salutations!
The Eye of the Midnight
Sun is strong!
So we're lucky to have
the help of our fearless
Magic Knight Captains,
especially those who
possess royal blood!
You are called the
Royal Knights, after all.
Get it?
Hey, it's the King!
Let's give a warm
welcome to His Majesty,
King Augustus Kira Clover
the Thirteenth.
[KING CLOVER] Oh, dear!
She's terribly intimidating!
I'm not used to being
addressed by my full name!
Listen well, Knights!
You mustn't sully
the proud name of--
As I'm sure you're aware,
victory is all we need!
The Eye of the Midnight Sun
is a contemptible
terrorist organization!
If we don't pull it up
by the roots ourselves,
our nation will
never know peace!
We may have successfully
banded together
to drive them out during the
attack on the royal capital,
but the cost was
unspeakably great.
My fool of a brother, Fuegoleon,
fell for their scheme and
remains bedridden to this day!
Based on what
we've learned from
the operatives we've
captured thus far,
their leader is a
mage called Licht,
who carries a
four-leaf grimoire!
Their three mightiest fighters
once made up a group
called the Third Eye.
The Eye of the Midnight
Sun intends to gather
magic stones because they
believe that doing so
will allow them to be reborn
into their "true forms,"
and come to possess
incredible power.
They have all but three stones.
Fortunately, we've
been able to recover
two of them before
they were located.
What's more, we defeated
the Third Eye's Vetto,
a wielder of Beast Magic.
And, for now,
we've deterred Fana
and her Fire Spirit, Salamander.
The final member
of the Third Eye
is the Copy Magic
user known as Rhya.
He and their leader Licht
are, without a doubt,
the greatest and most
powerful enemies
we'll face during our campaign.
Their stronghold is the last
line of defense they have.
If we attack it,
the enemy is likely
to put up all-out resistance.
We may see some casualties,
but victory will still
be ours in the end!
Every life in the
kingdom is at stake!
If anyone here is
uncomfortable with that,
then I'll kill you now and
save the enemy the trouble!
Are you ready?
[ROYAL MAGIC KNIGHTS]
Ma'am!
And now, His Majesty
King Augustus
Kira Clover the Thirteenth!
Oh! There's no need
to raise your voice!
I'm done, feel free to
continue with your address.
Er. Thank you.
[KING CLOVER]
"Continue," she tells me!
After she so rudely interrupted
me with such a lengthy spiel!
Why, there's nothing
left for me to say!
Ahem! Well, do your
best, Royal Knights!
Dismissed!
[NOELLE, ASTA]
Uhh...
Was that it?
[YUNO]
Hm.
Wait, Your Majesty!
Where do we find
the Eye of the Midnight
Sun's hideout, anyway?
[KING CLOVER]
Oh, my!
For a vexatious commoner,
he brings up a good question.
You see, it--
Rest assured, we will
be making our way
to their base immediately!
Listen up! It lies in the
floating dungeon found within
the strong magic region
called Gravito Stones!
[RHYA yawns]
Wow, it sure is late.
Hey, Rhya!
As I expected,
you're wearing the same
cowardly expression as usual.
[RHYA]
Aw, come on, don't be like that.
We should go get
some drinks together.
No. Forget it.
[LUCK]
Heh. You're a lightweight.
[RHYA]
Oh, hey, there you are.
Hello, Rhya.
What took ya so long?
Let me guess, waking up
is a pain, too, now?
You're the worst.
[RHYA]
Get off my case. Hey, Patry.
I can see you're still
clinging onto Licht
like nobody's business.
He's gonna belong to a
human after tomorrow's
big ceremony, so you better
start letting go of him.
Leave me alone, Rhya.
That's my choice to
make, not yours.
[RHYA]
Excuse me?
It's all right, even
after we get married,
Licht will still
belong to everybody.
[RHYA] Man, human princesses
are so generous.
I'd be careful what I say if
I were you, though, Tetia.
Before long, there
won't be any room
in his busy schedule
to spend time with you.
You don't have to be
so blunt about things.
Patry knows what to expect.
So what's it like?
Knowing that you'll be a father
in a few months' time?
I can sense that the mana
has blessed our lives, as well.
When our child arrives,
we know that your kind
will welcome it.
We're quite thrilled.
[TETIA laughs]
This little one here is
the key to our future.
The bridge to unite
elves and humankind!
[RHYA] Congratulations,
Licht and Tetia!
[VETTO, FANA, PATRY, RILL]
Congratulations!
[LICHT, TETIA laugh]
[RHYA gasping]
That was odd. What a dream.
Kinda faint, though.
It's almost time to wake up.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[MEREOLEONA, ASTA]
"Robes Aplenty. Part 1"!
Wow, we get special police
uniforms and everything?
This day keeps gettin'
cooler by the minute!
They were designed
for investigating
criminal activity.
Now go and put yours on!
This doesn't feel right!
Why is mine different
than all the other ones?
[MEREOLEONA, ASTA]
Part 2!
Wow, so we get special
school uniforms now?
That's way cooler than
what you gave me before!
They're made for wearing
to academic institutions.
Now go and put yours on!
Hold on a second, how
young do you think I am?
[MEREOLEONA, ASTA]
Part 3!
Wow, so we get special
doctor uniforms to wear?
I'm pretty sure it doesn't
get much cooler than that!
These outfits are designed
for practicing medicine.
Now go and put yours on!
Ugh, really?
Why can't I have a cool one?
[YUNO]
This might hurt.
[ASTA] Finally, it's time for
us to fight the Midnight Sun!
No matter what, the Royal
Knights are gonna protect
the Kingdom and everyone in it!
Black Clover, Page 88:
"Storming the Eye of the
Midnight Sun's Hideout!!!"
Our new Captain
is pretty strong.
And scary, too!