[LIEBE] Devils are born
in the underworld.
From the first breath
you take, you have a spot
in the pecking order, and
it's impossible to change it.
Since I was born with
no magic, obviously,
I was at the bottom.
I spent every day
covered in my own blood.
You're so pitiful,
it's not even fun
to beat you up!
If only that didn't exist.
[LIEBE]
Every devil wishes they could
cross over into the human world.
But the underworld gate stops
them from getting through.
So to pass the time,
the strong oppress the weak,
and the weak oppress anyone
weaker than they are.
That's how shitty
things are there.
Go on and cry. Scream
for mercy like always!
[LIEBE]
I didn't care about anything,
not even whether
I lived or died.
You brat. What's so funny?
[DEVILS laugh]
[LIEBE] I figured I would
crash into the gate
and my body would shatter.
[LIEBE] But since
I didn't have any magic,
I slipped right through.
And before I knew it,
I ended up in the human world.
Maybe it was because
I was helpless.
Or because I was exhausted
from all the beatings,
but I didn't care one way
or the other about humans.
Still...
Over there! It's got horns!
Could it be...?
A devil! He'll curse us!
[MAN 170B] Someone call
the Magic Knights!
[LIEBE]
It didn't take long
for humans with powerful magic
to find and attack me.
My body started shutting down.
I was ready to accept my death.
[LIEBE]
Finally, this pointless life'll
be over forever.
[footsteps]
[grunts]
[LICITA gasps]
You're awake? Thank goodness!
My name is Licita.
It's nice to meet you!
I figured you'd be
safer at my house.
It's okay, you can relax.
No one knows you're here, so
they won't come looking for you.
I just used my magic ability.
If something doesn't have mana,
I can use my ability to put it
into and take it out of things.
I found you while I was out
gathering some firewood,
so I just popped
you in this bottle.
[LICITA] You can imagine
how shocked I was!
I mean, just the other day, I
found this five-leaf grimoire,
but stumbling across a devil
was an even bigger
surprise than that!
You're weird.
Shouldn't you be
more afraid of me?
[laughs] Why would I be
afraid of a little boy
who's all beat up?
After all, it's not like
you have any magic.
Yeah, but all humans
hate devils, don't they?
Tsk, tsk, tsk. Sure,
people might hate you,
but you're not the only one.
[LICITA] You see?
My body saps magic and life
away from anything that
gets too close to me.
I can't help it.
That's why I live alone.
I keep my distance
from the village,
so I don't bother anyone.
But luckily! You
don't have any mana,
and it doesn't look like
I'm draining your life, either.
I guess it's because
you're a devil?
It's gotta be destiny!
I know! Maybe I
should adopt you!
Adopt me?
[LIEBE] A human raising
a devil as her own?
I couldn't wrap my head
around it at all.
But...
Come on, we gotta hurry up!
[LICITA]
All right! Hello, dinner!
[LIEBE gasps]
[LIEBE]
That human...
[LICITA giggles]
It's so pretty!
Uh-huh.
[LIEBE] I couldn't believe
she would open her heart
to someone like me.
A devil, born with no magic
in a dark, hopeless pit,
who cursed my own existence.
That woman changed my
whole world for the better.
Just because you're a devil,
that doesn't automatically
mean that you're some kind of
evil being at heart!
Trust me!
I know for sure
you're not a bad guy!
Thanks to you,
I don't have to live
my whole life all alone!
You saved me, Liebe!
I saved you?
[gasps]
Liebe! What's wrong?
Are you okay? Liebe!
[LIEBE, LUCIFERO]
My name...
[LUCIFERO]
...is Lucifero!
[gasps]
I never thought I would
find a devil out here
in the human world who
hadn't made a contract
with anyone yet so,
I'm glad I took the time
to look around!
[LIEBE] That's one of
the highest-ranked devils!
He's taking control of my body!
Must be my lucky day!
If I play my cards right, I'm
sure there's a way I can use
this weakling to manifest
my own body in this world--
That's enough!
Get out of Liebe's
body, right now!
What a foolish woman!
I may not have full
use of my powers,
but you're still
no match for me--
[LUCIFERO]
She's draining my mana!
I suppose you have a death wish!
You're going to pay!
Don't hurt her!
You won't win.
[LICITA]
I won't let go! Not this time!
[LIEBE gasps]
[cackles]
I won't let you.
[LICITA]
You're not taking my son!
[LUCIFERO]
Impossible!
To think a mere human
could get in my way!
No matter.
I can meddle with
a lower devil anywhere.
I shall return in time.
[gasps] Licita, are you...?
I'm sorry. I guess
I'm kinda stupid.
This was the only way I could
think of to protect you
from that horrible monster.
I'll use my magic to seal you
into this five-leaf grimoire,
where you'll be safe.
By the time someone
releases you from it,
I'm sure you'll have gotten
a lot bigger and stronger.
Please, Liebe, live, okay?
I love you, my sweet little boy.
But, Mama...
Look, loser.
Just hand over
the body, already!
[ASTA]
His ki.
It's full of anger and
hatred, and... sadness!
[ASTA] I'm sure you have
your reasons, just like I do.
I'll try to accept that
and figure out
what you're so mad about.
Then I'll win!
[LIEBE] You gotta be
kidding me, you idiot!
You really think you can
beat me with one arm?
[ASTA grunts]
Yeah, you heard me!
I still got plenty of muscle!
[NACHT] The devil fights with
Anti-magic, which is primarily
used to nullify an
opponent's magic power.
Since Asta doesn't have any,
it's not much of
a threat to him.
But...
I'm not gonna lose to
a pathetic human like you!
[ASTA]
Captain Yami's katana!
Without my Anti-magic,
those swords are useless!
They're just hunks of steel!
I don't give a damn about
your physical strength!
You're screwed! No magic
means no spatial transfer!
So you can't break this blade!
[ASTA grunts]
[ASTA groans]
How could you stand a chance
against a high-ranked devil
if you can't even hold your
own in a fight with me?
Stop kidding yourself!
[LIEBE]
After that, I was sealed away
within the five-leaf grimoire,
with no means of escape.
[LIEBE]
They're gonna pay for this.
I'll kill them!
All of them! I swear!
[LIEBE] I spent all
my time cursing Lucifero
and the other devils.
And then...
I gained the power
of Anti-magic,
the power to nullify spells.
[LIEBE laughs]
This is it!
This is how I'll get my revenge!
[LIEBE yells]
[LIEBE]
One day, the five-leaf grimoire
chose a human to
become its master.
As luck would have it,
this kid was born
with no magic, too.
I realized that if I ever
wanted to go back out
into the human world,
the only way
was for me to use him as a host.
I'd take over his
entire body if I had to.
In case you haven't
figured it out,
every devil is an
evil piece of shit!
Which is exactly why
I'll personally make sure
every last one of
them is destroyed,
and I'll use your body to do it!
I'll let my hatred run wild
and kill them all!
You know somethin', pal?
I think I finally
understand you.
So that's how you feel.
Thanks for lettin' me know!
Huh? What are you saying?
[yells]
Look. Just give up!
You can't use magic
or Anti-magic now!
You're history!
But I still dodged your swords!
All I had to do was focus
on reading your ki, big guy!
[growls]
[ASTA] It's true,
I don't have any magic.
And without you, I don't
even have Anti-magic.
But I've got the will to win,
and my unbreakable bonds with
all the amazing people I've met!
Yuno and I were taken in
by the church in Hage Village
on the same day, and I didn't
have one bit of mana!
Yuno is cooler than me
and he's smarter than me!
But he's still my rival.
We decided we would compete to
see who'd become Wizard King!
Having him in my life
is what inspired me
to keep getting better!
Then, I met Captain Yami
at the entrance exam
and I joined the Black Bulls!
And without them, I wouldn't
be the person I am today!
And it's not just them!
I've met lots of people--
friends and enemies!
There were a lot
of tough battles.
A few of the opponents I fought
became my friends
after it was all over.
And some of them didn't.
But I won't forget
a single one of them!
Because each of those
people are a part of me,
and they always will be!
Get results. Prove that
you're the strongest.
[YUNO] It takes you so long
to do everything, Asta.
Hurry up.
I'm gonna need
backup over here.
Asta!
[yells]
[LIEBE]
No way!
[yells]
[LIEBE growls]
Even after the five-leaf
grimoire showed up
and I figured out that
I could use Anti-magic,
I trained!
[ASTA] I wanted to be
as strong as all those
amazing fighters I met.
Better than them, even!
The good guys and the bad guys!
I kept pushing past my limits!
[yells]
[ASTA grunts, yells]
Heh. Don't tell me that was
the best you can do, Asta.
I know you're capable
of more than that.
Let's go!
Right!
[ASTA growling]
[NACHT]
No matter how hard you train,
your body still has limits.
You don't stand a chance
the way you are now.
But all that work
may just pay off.
I'm a human with no magic,
but that's not all
that you're up against
when you face me!
I've fought with a whole
bunch of powerful warriors!
And each one of them
taught me something new!
[LIEBE]
A human won't stop me,
not after how much
I've cursed them!
I was all alone! All--
[panting]
I beat you. It's over!
[NACHT]
Well done.
The preparations for the
ritual are now complete.
The next step is establishing
a contract with your devil,
giving you total
control over him.
This part's easy.
Simply think "obey me,"
and from this moment on,
you'll have a devoted
familiar to aid you
and follow your every command.
That's the only way to
become the ultimate warrior.
Okay. Then...
Starting right now,
we should be friends!
What's the matter,
devils don't even know
what a friend is?
Okay, I'll try to explain.
It's like, uh...
Hold on a second.
Are you attempting to create an
equal contract with your devil?
Yep!
I mentioned this earlier,
but I never could have made it
this far without his help!
The thing is, I never
stopped to learn anything
about him, even though he's been
with me for such a long time!
If we're gonna keep
working together,
we need to become friends!
What are you talking about?
There's no guarantee
that this devil
will pay you any heed at all.
Do you expect that
contract to work?
There's nothing
binding about it!
[ASTA]
It's fine.
I could tell from the beginning
he wasn't fighting me for real.
He kept talking
about killing me,
but I knew he was holding back!
You can't kill anybody, can you?
What you can do is get angry
for someone else's sake!
That's why we'd get along!
You and I should work
together as equals!
[ASTA] This isn't
a devil-binding ritual.
It's a, uh...
A devil-befriending ritual!
[GIMODELO] Not the sharpest
knife in the drawer,
is he, Mr. Nacht?
It appears not.
If you ask me, it sounds like
we've got the same enemies!
So, what do you say to
forming a team with me?
Right now!
This is nuts.
I never knew anyone
could be as stupid as you are.
I'm still not sure
if destiny is real, but...
Oh, by the way.
You haven't told me
your name yet!
[LICITA]
Oh, by the way.
You haven't told me
your name yet!
What d'you mean?
[LICITA]
You don't have one?
That's okay, I'll pick
one out for you!
Hm...
Ah! Liebe!
Starting today,
your name's Liebe!
[LIEBE]
There's no doubt about it.
[chuckles]
[LIEBE]
He's Licita's kid.
You can call me Liebe.
Whoa, what's that?
[squeals] I finally
got my arm back!
Thank you so much, buddy!
[NACHT]
The contract is complete.
I must admit, you've done
something truly unprecedented.
I didn't expect such a
foolish move, even from you.
However...
You made the right choice.
[gasps]
Still, though.
Being right doesn't always
mean you'll be rewarded.
That's why you need strength,
to keep evil from prevailing.
You have two days.
Think you can become
the strongest?
Yeah!
Eh?
[NOELLE]
Loropechika.
I'll save you, no matter what.
Okay. Let's get ready!
[FINRAL]
We can win.
Even if they're crazy strong,
we'll push past our limits!
'Cause we're the Black Bulls!
Isn't that right, Yami?
[panting]
[YUNO] I'm training as hard
as I can to beat Zenon,
but I'm not getting
the results I need.
You can stop hiding.
Just come out here, already.
I figure it might be useful
to have a Spatial Magic
user to spar with.
After all, it's only fair of me
to help you with
your training, right?
Trust me, I'd much prefer
to handle it myself,
but this is something that
affects the whole Golden Dawn.
I know you've improved
your skills, too,
so I'll accept your offer.
I see you're still
an insolent brat,
but at least you're
more straightforward now.
[YUNO] I'm going to save
Captain Vangeance.
All right! Hang in
there, Captain Yami!
No matter how tough they are,
I'll take 'em down!
I'm gonna keep our kingdom
and the whole world safe!
[NARRATOR] In this place
where magic is everything,
there lives one boy
who was born without it.
However, despite the many
challenges he faces,
Asta works hard and
refuses to give up.
He and his childhood rival train
through blood, sweat, and tears,
in hopes of one day becoming
the next Wizard King.