[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy
who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
[NARRATOR]
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world,
and to become the
next Wizard King!
[MARX] Even the parts
of the Forsaken Realm
that were hardest hit by the
enemy have begun to recover.
Things are finally
looking brighter
for the kingdom as a whole.
[JULIUS] Yes. And to make
this an everlasting peace
rather than a fleeting one,
we all need to remain strong,
whatever comes our way.
Hope you're ready
to work, sir.
We've got the captains' meeting
as well as the
decoration ceremony.
Your schedule is packed today.
Our topic for today
is who will participate
in the Heart Kingdom's training.
[JULIUS] The battle against the
Spade Kingdom, which we promised
Queen Loropechika we'd help
with, is drawing nearer now.
Of course, I know that
you've all been making
great strides on your own,
but we just received word
that they've
completed preparations
for their training
regimen, as well.
We've reached the final step!
There are five Spirit Guardians
who'll be working with us.
Each of them can only take
a certain number of trainees.
As such, I'd like you all to
tell me which subordinates
you'll be nominating
from each of your squads.
Now, then. Which of the
Magic Knights are we sending?
Obviously, I pick Asta
and Nero, especially since
the Heart Kingdom already
told us they wanted 'em.
[JULIUS] Asta uses Anti-magic,
and Nero wields forbidden magic.
Not only that, but they're
both at the arcane stage.
We know from experience
that their unique abilities
will be a tremendous
asset in this fight.
And through further
training, I'm sure they'll
find ways to amplify
their strengths even more.
I'll send Finral and Luck, too.
Oh, and Noelle, definitely.
Aw, what's wrong?
Are you worried about her?
That's so sweet, you're such
a protective big brother!
I feel like she and Luck
would be a good complement
to the others on account
of their magic types.
Interestingly, one of
the Spirit Guardians
uses lightning spells,
and the queen
has the Water Spirit
known as Undine.
When you consider
all of those factors,
I believe your assessment
is right on the money.
Besides, Luck's itching
to go so badly,
he can't stand it.
And it seems like
Noelle is more motivated
now than she's ever been.
[DOROTHY]
That makes sense.
Megicula is the devil who
killed their mother, after all.
And, as for Finral...
Well, he's just handy.
We can't underestimate the
importance of support mages
like him, especially if he
improves his skill even more.
Perhaps he'll open up
some new strategies for us.
Oh, yeah, that's what
I was gonna say.
From the Black Bulls,
we have five mages.
Asta, Nero, Luck Voltia,
Noelle Silva,
and the spatial
mage called Finral.
That's more than I expected.
That's 'cause I've got
plenty of good people!
Should be a fairly
strong lineup.
As for the Golden
Dawn's nomination,
I submit Mimosa Vermillion.
We're fighting a devil,
so I'm certain
the conflict ahead
will be brutal.
We can't hope to succeed
without recovery mages.
Because she's a royal,
she was born with great talent.
If we can help her
to reach her full potential,
then that bodes well for us.
A wise choice.
But is she your only nomination?
I hear the Wind Spirit Guardian
is going to be
involved, after all.
Actually, Yuno has declined.
Knowing him, I assume
he had his reasons.
And who are the candidates
from all the other squads?
From the Crimson Lion Kings,
we have chosen
Leopold Vermillion.
Leo's ambition
is extremely high.
In fact, he asked our sister,
Mereoleona, to help him train
at the volcano in the
strong magic region.
Just thinkin' about
that makes me tired.
No one in my squad
can match Leo's passion
and work ethic,
but he's still hesitant.
I'm hoping that this opportunity
will ignite a flame
within his heart that burns
away that hesitation.
If he can overcome that,
then not only will he be
a powerful force in our battle
against Spade, but he can guard
this kingdom with all
the strength and pride
of a great lion!
Excellent.
I look forward to seeing how
much Leo progresses, then.
What about the other squads?
Is there anyone
you wish to nominate
from the Blue Rose Knights?
First, sire, I would
like you to clarify
something for me.
Is it possible for one of the
captains to nominate themselves?
Sure, that's all right.
Since you were possessed by
an elf in that last conflict,
I believe subjecting
you to this training
could provide some
interesting results.
[CHARLOTTE]
I still remember how it felt
to have that elf spirit's
power coursing through me.
Her red rose mana was
far superior to my own.
It doesn't matter how
I increase my strength,
I just know that I must!
I'll do whatever it takes
to experience that again!
Er, and by "experience,"
I meant the magic!
Nothing more!
Then, the only nominee
from the Blue Rose Knights
is Captain Charlotte herself,
is that correct?
[CHARLOTTE]
Yes.
Any other captains?
It troubles me to admit it,
but I believe that younger
candidates would be best.
I agree. And I'm quite capable
of conducting my
training on my own.
I'd be glad to go if it means
I get to slash the
Heart Kingdom open.
[cackles]
[YAMI]
Yeah, you're not goin'.
I imagine this regimen
will be grueling,
but they'll discover
and learn so much
that they would never have
been able to here in Clover.
They'll be in a brand-new world!
I expect them to take
full advantage of that.
Discovering a new world?
[WOLF]
My appetite's insatiable!
Keep being vigilant
and training with
your magic every day!
That would... take... protein.
[CHARMY] Eat this!
That's for the protein!
[JULIUS] Each one of you
has amazing potential.
I'd like to see it
grow even more!
[RILL]
Growing, yeah!
[CHARMY] And this!
That one's for the fat!
[RILL gasps]
[CHARMY yells] This is for the
vitamins! This is for the fiber!
This is for the collagen!
[RILL gasps]
Me, me, me, me, me!
Oh, my! Someone's
full of energy!
Yeah, where the heck
did that come from?
The only person
I want to nominate
from the Aqua Deer is me!
[RILL] If I get stronger,
then maybe that nice,
beautiful lady will notice me!
We've probably selected
enough candidates at this point,
but are there any others?
I don't have anyone
from the Silver Eagles,
but I assure you, we'll train
to the best of our ability
and be ready for the fight
against the Spade Kingdom.
As will we.
And we're going to
handle things our way!
[cackles]
Well, then, do we all agree
on the candidates
who were proposed?
[CAPTAINS]
I approve.
Lovely!
I'm expecting great
things from this group.
[CAPTAINS]
Sir!
Very well, then.
Today's captains' meeting
is officially adjourned.
Good. That's finally over.
See ya.
And just where do you
think you're going?
The decoration ceremony
is about to start.
Ugh, do I really
have to go to that?
But I got my wheels
parked out front.
And my squad never gets picked.
We were told that
all nine captains
are required to
be in attendance.
[YAMI]
What? Why?
[MARX]
Well, you see,
apparently the king himself
is going to
participate this time.
You're kidding me.
[SEKKE] The captains from
every squad, in one room!
It's an a- ha ll-star lineup!
[KING CLOVER] I see they
required all the captains
to attend since they knew
I'd be making an appearance.
Exactly as it should be!
Up till now, the king's only
seen me at a distance.
He's bound to figure it out!
[SEKKE]
Captain Jack!
[YAMI, JACK]
Hm?
[SEKKE]
Will you...
...let me...
...come back to the...
...squa- ha d?
[YAMI]
What's with him?
Guess he needs me
to slice him to pieces!
[yelps]
I believe everyone
is present now.
Then I say we start.
Attention, all.
This is a special decoration
ceremony for the Magic Knights
who bravely fought against
the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
The Wizard King is still
unable to use his voice,
so I'll be conducting
this myself.
Without further ado...
Sol Marron of the Blue
Rose Knights, with 21 stars.
As of today, you'll be a
fifth-class Senior Magic Knight.
With your calm, quick
thinking, you were able
to transport the injured
Wizard King to safety.
Please continue to exercise
that wise judgment
on the battlefield.
My, my!
That young lady moved up
three ranks at once!
She did save the
Wizard King's life,
so I'd say she's more than
deserving of such a promotion.
[SOL] To be honest,
I wasn't calm at all.
Not to mention, Char had to
be rescued by the captain
of the Black Bulls,
of all people!
Next time, I'll protect
her without the help
of some dumb, disgusting man!
Heads up, your subordinate's
starin' me down
somethin' serious.
Is that so?
[CHARLOTTE]
She's staring at Yami?
Oh, no! Please, Sol!
Don't tell me you
like him, as well?
Huh?
[SOL] Wow, she looks
so passionate!
Don't worry, Char.
I won't let you down!
Next, with 23 stars,
the Golden Dawn's
Mimosa Vermillion.
You're now a Second-Class
Intermediate Magic Knight.
During the battle at the
Shadow Palace, you showed
great humanity while
effectively fulfilling your duty
as a recovery mage.
And we know that you'll save
many more lives in the future.
If you ask me,
Mimosa's the reason
why so many more people
understand the importance
of recovery magic these days!
[MIMOSA]
This is a great honor.
I'll do my best
to live up to it
during our battle
with the Spade Kingdom.
And with a total of 18 stars,
Leopold Vermillion of
the Crimson Lion Kings.
You are now a Fourth-Class
Senior Magic Knight.
When the captains were absent,
you rallied your cohorts
and did everything in your power
to stop your vice captain,
who was possessed by an elf.
I hope the strength of your
character will continue
to lead us down
the path to victory.
It appears young
Leopold has advanced
by three ranks, as well.
I'm sorry, I can't accept!
[CAPTAINS gasp]
[LEOPOLD] That night, if my
brother hadn't shown up in time,
we'd have all been annihilated!
It's true I did
everything I could,
but it still wasn't good enough!
Everyone in my squad fought
really hard to protect me,
even at the risk
of their own lives!
Truth is, I'm only a weakling!
I don't deserve
this recognition!
[FUEGOLEON]
You're a fool!
Have you no idea why
they all put their lives
on the line for your sake?
They were moved by your courage.
Your very existence inspired
them to move forward!
They knew the future
of our squad
would be safe in your hands!
So accept the award!
It represents the tireless
hope and resolve
of the Crimson Lion Kings!
[LEOPOLD]
Hope and resolve?
Please forgive my hesitation!
I, Leopold Vermillion, will
protect my squad and the kingdom
from any foe, and become
a mighty warrior who can
lead the charge to victory!
[MARX] And now Yuno,
from the Golden Dawn.
[YUNO]
Sir.
[KING CLOVER]
Hmph.
[MARX] You've earned
77 stars, total.
[GROUP gasps]
Amazing!
During the Star Festival
for this year...
Did he just earn more
than my whole squad?
You're being promoted
as well, Yuno.
To first-class
Senior Magic Knight.
[GROUP gasps]
This brat?!
Wha- ha t?
[KING CLOVER] You would
award a title like that
to a mere commoner?
[MARX] You dealt a fatal
blow to the devil,
who was the source of
all that destruction.
We're very proud of
what you've achieved.
Thanks.
[MIMOSA] Now he's the same rank
as Vice Captain Langris.
I can't believe Yuno's
already made it
one step below
the Squad Captains!
I don't really know
what's going on,
but it sounds pretty good!
Great job, Yuno!
We should celebrate
with a date--!
[YUNO]
First-class Senior Magic Knight.
I'm that much closer.
These four mages have display--
Hold on just a minute!
[MAGIC KNIGHTS gasp]
Man, I get a headache
every time that guy
opens his mouth.
Let's show some respect.
Although, I don't disagree.
You do realize that's
just as bad, right?
You fools failed to
recognize the person
whose achievements in the
last battle were second to none!
[CAPTAINS]
Hm?
[KING CLOVER] The hero
who guarded our kingdom's
most precious treasure!
What about the great
Sekke Bronzazza?
Bah- ha ?
Not only did you slugs
have the audacity
to leave your king
unattended in a crisis,
but certain parties were nasty
enough to attack me, as well!
I kind of wish I would've
run him through.
Cool, shut up.
The glory belongs
to Sekke, not to them!
He's the real hero!
During that awful confrontation,
he bravely dodged
the enemy's spells
and rushed to my rescue
on that strange vehicle of his!
None of these other neophytes
even attempted
to help their king.
They should be punished,
not praised!
[SEKKE] Ah- ha nestly,
I just kinda showed up.
By my authority as
ruler of this kingdom...
...I award to Sekke the title
of first-class
Senior Magic Knight!
[GROUP gasps]
[SEKKE] Did he say "first-class
Senior Magic Knight"?
That's like the cream
of the crah- ha p!
[KING CLOVER] If that riffraff
is worthy of such prestige,
then there's no reason I can't
promote Sekke to the same level!
[panting]
Uh-oh.
[SEKKE]
Oh, my gah- ha d.
I've never felt this
hated in my life.
They're gonna have my head!
Right!
It's a privilege to accept
such an honor, Your Majesty!
I give you my word.
I will fight, and, um, win!
No matter what...
No matter what, I will always
take great pride in protecting
the Clover Kingdom
with my very life,
and that's a prah- ha mise!
[SEKKE]
So, please don't kill me, okay?
Well, then, will
that be all, sir?
Yes! I hope the rest of you
will follow his example
and always make me
your utmost priority. Forever!
[SEKKE] Whew, that was
a close cah- ha ll.
Ah-hem. Now, as I was saying.
Those five knights aside,
everyone else who fought against
the Eye of the Midnight Sun
will be promoted by one rank.
[CAPTAINS gasp]
[NOZEL]
I see.
That must be why they asked
all the captains to attend.
[DOROTHY] I knew that
old blowhard being here
wasn't a good enough reason
to require us to come.
[WILLIAM] The Wizard King cares
so deeply for our squads.
I'm grateful.
[FUEGOLEON]
All of the Magic Knights
who risked their lives
will be rewarded.
If not for the
Magic Parliament trial
causing all that chaos,
there might've been
many more promotions.
[MARX] And, although we cannot
award them at this time,
we've decided to give
credit where we can.
Black Bulls Captain
Yami Sukehiro.
Really? I got somethin'?
Please continue to
exercise great leadership
and help keep the
Clover Kingdom peaceful.
Eh, I was kinda hopin'
for money. But, thanks.
[MARX] This concludes the
special decoration ceremony.
In closing, I would like
to read you a message
from the Wizard King himself.
"Although we have
begun to recover
from the previous conflict, the
threat of the Spade Kingdom..."
[MARX, JULIUS]
...looms ever nearer.
[JULIUS]
I expect nothing but the best
from the knights
who were promoted today.
To those who did not
receive titles,
I trust that you will
continue to train hard,
work together as Magic Knights,
and protect our beloved
kingdom and all who reside here.
[ALL]
Yes, sir.
[FINRAL]
We're home!
[FINRAL sighs]
[FINRAL screams]
You're never gonna catch me!
Shut up!
Quit moving around,
ya little punk!
You think the enemy's
just gonna stand still
and wait for you to hit 'em?
Oh, hey, it's Finral
and Captain Yami!
Welcome back, you guys!
Can't you runts train outside?
It's too damn loud.
Hey, Luck!
Uh-huh?
Now I gotcha!
We're gonna send you
to the Heart Kingdom.
Really?
Does that mean it's official?
You and Nero, too, of course.
Plus Noelle and my wheels, here.
[ASTA]
You're coming, too, Finral?
It sure seems that way.
I can't wait till
I kick some enemy butt!
Yup. Go nuts, little fella.
[MAGNA] Please. You have
to let me go, too!
If he goes, I can't just
sit here on my ass!
I promise, I'll become
even stronger than he is!
It was already decided
in the captains' meeting.
Sorry, Magna.
[MAGNA]
Please, Boss!
I'm begging you here!
[MAGNA]
He's always a step ahead of me.
But...
[MAGNA]
If I'm going to be a real man,
then I refuse to be
left behind anymore!
I'll go, even if you
tell me to stay here!
[YAMI]
With mana like yours,
you're likely to
get yourself killed.
You good with that?
[MAGNA]
Yes, sir!
I can push past
the limits of my mana!
More than any
commoner has before!
All right.
I'll ask Julius if there's
room for another guy.
But just remember one thing.
It doesn't make a damn bit
of difference where you train.
It's how that's important.
You understand?
[MAGNA]
Got it!
This is great!
I'm so happy you're
coming with us!
It's no fun if I get
too far ahead of you.
[MAGNA]
Yeah, watch out!
I'll catch up
before you know it!
[laughs]
Sweet! We've got Finral.
Magna's going.
And Luck!
Now let's head over to Heart
and give it all we got!
[FINRAL, LUCK, MAGNA, ASTA]
Yeah!
[BELL] Look at you, climbing
to the top of the ladder
in one step! You really are
the coolest guy ever!
I know you'll become
the Wizard King soon,
maybe sooner than we thought!
Don't be dumb.
It's not like
it'll be that easy.
But yeah. Someday.
[YUNO]
It's only a matter of time.
[YUNO] I'll keep following
my own path, and one day,
I'll be the Wizard King.
Black Clover , Page 154:
"Vice-Captain Langris Vaude."
Don't hold back
when you challenge me.
You'll get hurt.