[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR]
The cornered Asta found himself
at a complete loss against
the overwhelming power
of the leader of the
Eye of the Midnight Sun.
However, he was saved
at the last moment
by Yami Sukehiro, the captain
of the Black Bulls.
Theirs was a breathless battle
of Light versus Dark Magic.
Asta pushed past his limits
to launch a counterattack.
But then...
[LICHT]
You hurt him. How dare you?
I will not allow humans
like you to continue
harming my compatriots.
You've done too
much damage already.
Light Creation Magic:
Light Whip of Judgment!
[LICHT laughs]
Your struggles are pointless!
It's crumbling!
[laughs] That nutball's not
holding anything back!
[screams]
Goodness.
And here I was attempting
to restrain myself.
Poor fools. You truly are weak.
Your kingdom as well.
It, too, will fall.
You destroyed them, Master.
Surely only a god could
wield such power.
If you wished it,
all of the Clover Kingdom's
Magic Knights would
cower before you!
[ASTA, YAMI yells]
They live?
[YAMI laughs]
Keep up that kinda focus,
and you'll even start
sensing ki out in nature.
We won't have to worry
about any falling rocks
hittin' you on the head, eh?
Awesome!
Heck, yeah! I love ki!
We'll teach this arrogant fool.
Here we go!
Time to kick it up a notch and
take out the white-haired guy
with the weird dots on his face.
[yelps]
Actually, right now I feel
like I could take him!
Aw, yeah!
With the power of ki on my side,
there's nothin' I can't do!
All right, Dottyface,
you ready to get beat?
[laughs]
Whoa, easy there, kid.
Huh?
[YAMI]
That guy is mine.
You wanna see what
I can really do, right?
Plus, he'd just kill you.
Aw, come on, that's not fair!
I got all pumped up
and ready to fight
the scary boss guy
and everything!
[YAMI]
Don't care.
You take Skinnybones Lineface
over there all right?
[YAMI]
Okay. This is gonna be fun.
Been a while since
I've had a real fight.
[YAMI yelling]
[YAMI grunts]
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked.
Lightless Slash!
[LICHT] I thought as much.
My magic is being drawn in.
[LICHT]
Such is the power of Dark Magic.
No matter.
Now that you've revealed
what you're capable of,
I should be able to evade
capture easily enough.
[YAMI]
Mm-hm, listen.
You were tellin' us some weird
little fairy tale earlier.
But that wasn't the
end of it, was it?
If you're carryin'
around a grimoire
with a clover on it,
you must be from around here.
Why attack your homeland?
[LICHT chuckles]
You're wide open.
[LICHT]
Was that his plan?
Leaving an opening
to make me careless?
Yami Sukehiro. You are
formidable indeed.
Okay, cut the crap
now and tell me
what you're really after.
There must be some
things that you see
more clearly than other people,
having come here
from another land.
The twisted ways
of this kingdom.
Some here are on the verge
of starving to death.
While others discard
food they cannot finish.
Citizens' ranks are
supposedly determined
by their power,
and yet some are met
with discrimination despite
the strength of their magic
because of their low birth.
Others are persecuted
for the simple crime
of having been born
in a different land.
These disparities that
taint the kingdom
are the reason we exist.
We were born in order
to see them rectified.
Yeah, you got me
a little confused now.
Seems like you people
are just basically doin'
the same thing, goin'
around hurtin' people
who don't deserve it.
And, well, that's kinda dumb.
No, it makes perfect sense.
We merely respond
to your sins in kind.
Yeah, I get it. You just
wanna do things your way,
and I sorta like that attitude.
But...
...you really annoy
the hell outta me!
[ASTA]
This fight is unreal.
So that's what it looks like
when the captain
doesn't hold back.
[ASTA] I train so hard,
but without magic,
can I ever surpass them?
Captain Yami. Yuno.
The Wizard King.
[VALTOS] He's strong
enough to hold his own
against Master Licht?
Incredible.
[VALTOS] Master, please!
Allow me to assist.
Look alive, kid.
[ASTA]
He almost squished me!
Why're you just standin' there
like some kinda chicken?
I put you in charge of
Skinnypants, didn't I?
I wouldn't give you more
than you could handle.
Do something. Fight
him your way, kid.
Right!
[ASTA]
Yes.
Whatever it takes, I will
become the Wizard King.
I can't waste time
being bummed out.
Eventually, I'm gonna
be the Wizard King.
But first,
I'm gonna be the
guy who beats you!
That's where you're wrong, boy.
Let's see how you
handle this spell.
Spatial Magic: Myriad Black.
You may have anticipated
a single attack,
but do you think you
can block all of these?
[ASTA yells]
[ASTA]
One of them got past my guard.
I can keep this up
as long as I want.
Until you're too weak
to stand, much less fight.
[ASTA yells]
[VALTOS]
You sin in defying Master Licht,
even magicless as you are.
And you shall atone
with your life.
[yelps]
[ASTA]
Not good.
There's no way I can keep this
up until he runs out of magic.
If I don't do something,
I'm as good as dead,
even if I counter his attacks.
Think. Stay calm. Do it my way.
You're tossing aside
your only weapons?
Have you lost your mind?
Very well, as you wish.
I'll bury you with
one final blow.
[ASTA yells]
[VALTOS gasps]
He dove into the portal?
[yells]
[groans]
[ASTA grunts]
[laughs] That's your way?
Punchin' the guy?
You're a funny one,
you know that, right?
Your guard's down.
[YAMI]
You sure about that?
[LICHT]
It absorbed my attack.
And... I can't move.
[YAMI]
From Dark Magic: Black Hole
to Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked.
Black Blade.
Captain Yami, sir!
[laughs]
You fell down!
That's quite a spell.
Its range appears to be
limited to about five meters,
but even so, a magic that can
not only absorb my spells
but also halt my movements.
Dark Magic. Incredible.
Such a powerful
attribute to have.
And the only one in
direct opposition to mine.
However, Dark Magic
is extremely slow.
Here, too, it stands opposed
to Light Magic's
extraordinary speed.
To make up for that,
you improvised by cloaking
your weapon in Darkness
and patching the gaps
with Reinforcement Magic.
Spot on, pal.
[ASTA]
That's all you're gonna say?!
[YAMI] What are you
waiting for, anyway?
You can use Recovery
Magic, can't you?
Get recovering, already.
Of course, when you do,
I'm just gonna
jam this baby into
your chest area.
So I guess maybe it's
not worth the trouble.
I will admit,
you are indeed strong.
Only the second I've faced
with the power to defeat me.
But I'm afraid I have no
more time to waste here
trifling with you.
Hold on, back up real quick.
What do you mean,
I'm the second one?
There was someone before you.
The man who wounded
my hand so badly
that it will never recover,
The Wizard King Julius
Novochrono--my greatest foe--
still remains.
[LICHT] This shall be my most
powerful spell so far.
Too swift for you to evade.
Too powerful and extensive
for your magic to
draw in as before.
There's no escaping fate.
This will be your undoing.
The moment that I cast
it will be your last
in this world, Captain
of the Black Bulls.
Whatever. Not a chance!
Don't underestimate
Captain Yami!
You think you're
somethin' special?
Nah. This could go pretty bad.
He's got some nasty magic.
[ASTA]
What?
[LICHT]
You, too, young man.
You must be punished for the
harm you've done to Valtos.
I'll be taking back
that grimoire.
[YAMI] Anyone with a four-leaf
clover is gonna have
some seriously strong magic.
And unless I surprise
him somehow,
he can dodge all my attacks.
So, what to do.
[YAMI]
That's future Yami's problem.
[BOY 33A]
Daddy!
[BOY 35A]
Mommy!
[BOY 33A]
I was so scared!
[MOTHER 35A]
I know, dear.
[FATHER 35A]
Are you hurt?
[sighs] Looks like we got
all of them out safe.
[GAUCHE]
Hey, old hag!
No dying on me!
Wake up, you decrepit crone!
You're an immortal
demon-witch, remember?
[MARIE, LUCA, MARCO]
Sister!
[MARCO]
No. What happened to her?
Please, Gauche.
I know you're worried about her,
but you're badly hurt, too.
Try to stay calm until your
own injuries have been--
Shut your mouth!
[FINRAL]
But I'm your superior!
Sir. It isn't as
bad as it looks.
He's almost completely healed.
Huh?
It's strange, but somehow
all the injuries
he sustained seem
to be located just shy
of where they'd be fatal.
Wow, it sounds like
he got really lucky.
[MAGE 35A]
Or maybe more than that.
You need to forget about me
and just heal the old hag!
[MAGE 35A]
Yes, sir!
Listen to me! You open your
eyes right now! Got that?
[SISTER THERESA]
Will you shut up?
[GAUCHE gasps]
I can hear fine, you fool.
No need to yell.
Old hag!
[ALL]
Sister!
[SISTER THERESA]
Take my magic power with you.
You might need it.
[GAUCHE gasps]
You're going to
help them, right?
Asta and the other one.
But I... I could never.
I'm so glad you
met that young man.
It changed you, somehow.
I'm counting on you, Gauche.
[GAUCHE]
Old hag...
[KIDS whimper]
You can't be gone.
You're too tough to die.
Bring her back right now!
But, sir--
Just do something!
Please, listen.
Do you wanna see Marie cry?
But she's alive.
Huh?
[MAGE 35A]
She isn't dead.
Stupid cow!
You can't go around
scaring people like that!
How many times
have you called me
an immortal demon-witch?
I'm not going to die.
Not easily, at least.
Stop worrying about me.
Just go help them.
Please, I want you
to take my magic, too!
And mine, mister!
Yeah, mine, too!
You gotta help Asta
beat those mean guys!
[NEIGE] Please, will you
use my magic, as well?
You, too?
Your sister was frightened
and hurt because of me,
and I can't tell you
how sorry I am.
If I came with you,
I would only get in the way,
but please go,
and tell Asta good luck.
[MARIE]
Big brother?
See? It's like I said.
People survive by
supporting each other.
Marie.
[YAMI]
I won't stop you.
Protect whatever you
think needs protecting.
Keep doing that, and it'll
help someone someday.
[GAUCHE] All right. I know
what I have to do now.
Finral!
Get ready. We're goin'
back to that cave.
You're not serious, right?
[FINRAL] Also, stop ordering
around your superior!
[FINRAL] I mean, even if you
do go, how are you planning
to handle the guy with the
crazy-powerful Light Magic?
He had you pinned before.
Maybe we should wait for
reinforcements from HQ.
I have an idea of
how we might beat him.
Huh?
I'm not saying it'll be easy,
but unless I'm wrong,
I think we have a shot.
I hope your big plan
isn't a sneak attack
with my Spatial Magic.
Extremely powerful
mages like him
are surrounded by
a mana forcefield.
I won't be able
to get you past it.
Besides, I've already
moved a lot of people
over great distances today.
I've expended so much mana,
I might only have
one spell left in me.
[GAUCHE]
That's all I need.
Finral. Please!
[LICHT] The wait is over.
Your end is upon you.
[YAMI]
Dark Magic: Black Cocoon.
What kind of spell is this?
Went into defense mode
to buy us some time.
'Course, we're probably
still gonna die.
Die?
And we're just supposed
to accept that?
No! Here I go!
I'm gonna knock that spell
of his right back at him!
[YAMI]
Try it and the only thing
that'll be left of you
is that sword.
[ASTA]
Come on, Captain!
There's gotta be
something we can do!
Well, guess we could
try not givin' up.
That's an awesome idea!
[YAMI]
We're in serious trouble.
He's got us cornered and there's
not a damn thing we can do.
[YAMI] Grit your teeth
and dig in your heels.
That's all we've got.
Take your last breath,
Yami Sukehiro.
Uh, Gauche. What happened here?
Are we in the wrong place?
No, look!
[FINRAL]
I see it! That's Yami's magic.
Oh, boy.
I think we stepped in the
middle of something big!
Engaging Light Magic:
Ray of Divine Punishment.
And we're dead.
He came back?
Go Mirror Magic:
Full Reflection!
Your magic might be
fast and powerful.
But Mirror will
always reflect Light.
Who do these people
think they are?
To have injured
Sally so badly...
Awful. Unforgivable.
[yawns] Well, it's gonna be
a pain, but it looks like
it's about time for
us to do our thing.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[GAUCHE]
"Changing Voices."
[coughing]
No! Marie's sick?
Did she catch a cold?
It's from being
in that dank cave!
Are you okay, my angel?
[YAMI'S voice] I'm fine.
My throat's a little sore,
that's all.
Hold on. My voice sounds funny.
What? No!
Why does my precious,
perfect angel
sound just like Captain Yami?
Never mind, Big Brother.
Just forget about me.
Asta's the one who
needs your help now!
[YAMI'S voice]
Take my magic power with you.
You might need it.
Not you, too, old hag!
[YAMI'S voice]
I've used up so much mana,
I might only have
one spell left in me.
And Finral now?
[coughing]
[MARIE'S voice] My throat
is starting to hurt, too.
[GROUP YAMI'S voice]
Aw, what a cute voice!
[GAUCHE]
I did it Marie!
Your big brother
beat the bad guy!
Now, to hurry back--
Hey! Where did you come from?
I thought we were done here!
Black Clover , Page 36:
"Three Eyes."
Marie. I'm not comin'
back just yet.