[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] Vetto's true might
had awoken within him,
and with it, staggeringly
massive power.
Asta called on all of
his remaining strength
to face the beast.
[ASTA]
The way I see it, not giving up
is the strongest
weapon I've got!
And there's no way I'm gonna
quit before my wish comes true--
do you understand me?
Not ever!
[NARRATOR] Asta's courage
spurred his teammates
into action.
I'm here now solely
because of your refusal
to give up the fight.
Our juniors are giving
it all they've got.
Time for us to show off
our most advanced stuff.
We're not about to
let you die, Asta.
We'll be fighting beside you!
[ALL]
Let's do this!
[VETTO yells]
[VETTO]
Nice try, brat!
But the Spatial spell's
power and your aura
give away your every move!
[VETTO]
What?
The thread's trajectory shifted.
[yelling]
[ASTA]
This is my weapon.
Now watch. I will defeat you!
[VANESSA, FINRAL gasp]
[ASTA]
It worked!
[VETTO]
Oh, you've done it now, human!
[VETTO grunts]
--Thanks!
--[FINRAL] Jeez.
That was close!
A second slower and
he would've ripped you
into pieces for sure.
That's how you do it, kiddo!
Now keep it up!
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I didn't do anything.
That was all you and Finral.
[NOELLE]
Amazing.
Who knew that those two had
that kind of talent in them?
[VETTO] As I suspected.
I can't heal this.
Did he cut off the very flow
of my self-healing magic?
[VETTO]
That's the only weapon here
that stands a chance
of defeating me.
His anti-magic sword.
Even with it, that runt
would be no match
for me on his own.
But with those two
giving him backup,
he has considerably
more mobility.
The Spatial Magic
is troublesome,
but the real nuisance here
is that woman's Thread Magic.
[VETTO] There are threads
strung all through this space.
They could come into play
at any time, from any corner.
The threads themselves
lack the strength to attack
or bind me on their own,
but they're too fine
for the eye to see or for
their magic power to be felt.
Which means I can't
predict the brat's moves!
[VETTO cackles]
How fascinating!
Taken separately, you humans
are so much trash,
but with three of you
working together,
it seems you can actually fight.
And I find that disgusting!
[VETTO] You may think there's
strength in numbers,
but that's just an illusion.
You have no hope!
He's coming!
Get ready!
[yells]
All right!
[ASTA yells]
--Go, Finral!
--Uh, yeah!
[ASTA yells]
[VETTO yells]
[ASTA yelps]
[ASTA]
I'm not done!
All right!
It's gonna take a lot
more than that!
We could cover him in scratches
and it wouldn't be enough
to take him down.
[FINRAL] Things are about to
get even more dangerous here.
[VANESSA] We have to get
the kid in as close
as we possibly can!
Get me right up
in his furry face!
I'll give it
everything I've got.
So I'm not imagining things.
What now?
It feels like an immense
and malevolent power.
[GREY whimping] Whatever it is,
it's even more unbelievably
massive than the unbelievably
massive magic I felt earlier!
It's unbelievably unbelievable!
Shut up! Quit babbling
like an idiot!
[GREY]
Please don't look at me!
Get over it already.
We need to do something.
Has your magic recovered at all?
[GREY] Um. No. Not even
a little, sorry.
Tch. I used up all of mine
against that Chain Magic loser.
I couldn't manage a single
Reflect Ray right now.
This is just great.
Hey, little piggy!
Don't tell me you went on alone!
Seriously, are you already
stuffing your face again?
[CHARMY]
Mm-hm!
Using that Strike of
the Sleeping Sheep spell
emptied my tummy along with
all of my magic reserves.
You wouldn't expect me to fight
on an empty stomach, would you?
Come on, we might as
well fill our bellies
while we wait for
our magic to recover.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Eating a little can't hurt.
We'll find the others
once we're rested.
Um. Okay!
[ASTA grunts]
[OCEAN DWELLERS cheering]
[OCEAN DWELLER 48C] The Magic
Knights are unstoppable!
[OCEAN DWELLER 48A] They're
up against a real monster!
[OCEAN DWELLER48B] Do you
think they actually beat him?
Yes, that's it!
That's the spirit!
Go get 'im! The best defense
is a good offense!
Keep going, and don't give
him a chance to fight back!
[GIFSO] When I think of what
that monster did to my son
and my grandkids...!
Avenge them!
Give him back every
ounce of pain...
[YAMI]
Well done.
Those two are normally useless,
but by joining forces,
they've pushed past
their limits.
Still...
[YAMI] Tch. Not again.
He took another blow?
Is this what I think?
[VANESSA] I can't lose focus
for a single second.
[FINRAL]
I'm not sure how much longer
I can stand this
kind of tension.
[yelling]
[ASTA]
So close!
[FINRAL]
Snap out of it, Finral!
Quit whining like you always do.
Asta's the one going
face-to-face with a monster.
The pressure you're under
is nothing compared to that!
Finral! How do your
magic reserves look?
With so many spells,
I'm draining them
pretty quickly.
I'm still managing, though!
[FINRAL] Guess it worked out
that I spent the whole time
here running away
instead of fighting.
[VANESSA]
So I was right.
We aren't the ones
who are slowing down.
[FINRAL]
Huh?
[VANESSA]
Not good.
He's starting to time his
moves to our attacks!
[VETTO]
There it is.
[ASTA grunts]
[grunts, pants]
Asta!
[ASTA]
Please! This? This is nothin'.
One blow just happened
to graze me, that's all.
Now come on, let's go!
[YAMI]
Hold up, kid!
Captain Yami?
[YAMI] Fightin' in close like
you are, you should know
better than anyone that blow
didn't "just happen" to land.
He wants to learn your timing,
your battle quirks,
your weaknesses.
To do that, he's been
holdin' back his attacks
and goin' on the
defensive instead.
[gasps] What, really? No!
If you fly in there hasty
and unprepared, well...
Next time, you're dead for sure.
[YAMI] If you fly in there
hasty and unprepared,
next time, you're dead for sure.
[NOELLE]
No! Is that true?
[VETTO chuckles]
That's a dark swordsman for you.
With battle instincts like that,
you're going to make
an excellent main dish.
But what do you
expect them to do
with this information?
Knowing my strategy won't
change their situation.
You pitiful humans.
Attack whenever you're ready,
but the next one
will be your last!
You don't know that,
you overgrown furball!
Or you, Captain!
We can't know what'll happen
until we actually try!
[YAMI]
The hell I don't know!
I'm like a gajillion times
stronger than you.
Is that right? Then how
about you quit watching
and get down here already!
[YAMI]
Oh, you went there, huh?
Hittin' me right where it hurts.
[growls] It's freakin' killing
me that I gotta just
watch all this play out.
Do you have any idea
how pissed off I am?
[gasps]
[YAMI]
Kid!
Calm down, okay?
I'm not tellin' you
not to attack.
Huh?
[YAMI] What I'm sayin' is ya
can't do it like ya did before.
You can beat him.
But you three have
to be smart about it.
--Finral!
--[gasps]
[YAMI]
Vanessa!
Kid!
Yes, sir!
[YAMI] You know what to do
at a time like this.
Let me hear you say it!
Right here, right now.
[ALL] We'll push further
past our limits!
[yells]
Okay, get ready!
We're gonna go even faster!
[ASTA]
Got it!
[FINRAL]
Asta!
[gasps]
[ASTA yells]
[NOELLE]
They both hit?
We're still in this!
Come on, you guys,
let's keep on pushing!
--Understood.
--Got it!
[VANESSA]
Kiddo.
When I see you fighting
so hard even though
you have no magic of
your own, I start to feel
a kind of courage
I never thought I had.
I'd forgotten.
Buried the knowledge
as deep as it would go.
Blotted out the memory
of my weakness
in the Forest of Witches.
[VANESSA]
Hey, did you know?
There's a big town
outside this forest,
and I've heard there are
tons of people living there
who aren't witches!
[BIRD]
Silly Vanessa.
You must have told us about
that place 1,000 times now.
Isn't that where all the
other witches have gone?
To have fun and find boyfriends
and stuff like that?
[DOLL] Why not escape this
cage and join them?
You want to, right?
[VANESSA]
What? No!
That's impossible. I mean...
[VANESSA] I could never
defy the Queen of Witches.
[BIRD] Hey, it's all right.
Don't look so sad.
[DOLL]
I know!
Want me to ask the Queen
of Witches for you?
That won't work.
You're nothing more than a
doll I made using my magic.
So if I can't do something,
you certainly can't, either.
[DOLL]
That's right.
And this whole conversation
is just you talking to yourself.
[BIRD] Someday, it would be
nice to have real friends
to talk to.
Yes, it would,
but it'll never happen.
I'm stuck here.
Inside this cage, forever.
I'll never be free.
[VANESSA] I assumed those were
the cards fate had dealt me.
It seemed hopeless,
so I gave up.
But...
[VANESSA] One day, I realized,
being stuck there
wasn't my fate after all.
I'd simply lacked
the courage to change.
[VANESSA] I left the Forest
of Witches and chose life
with the Black Bulls instead,
and it was the right choice.
We hold the threads of
fate in our own hands,
and it's our choice
what to do with them.
Asta! I'll pull you back in!
Just trust me and go!
Thanks, Vanessa,
I'm counting on you!
[VETTO growls]
You ridiculous little fool!
[ASTA yelps]
[FINRAL]
Take it easy, you two!
We don't wanna go faster
than we can handle.
This is the problem
with passionate people.
Much safer to be motivationally
challenged, like me.
[FINRAL'S FATHER]
Finral.
[gasps]
[FINRAL'S FATHER]
Why are you wielding your magic
so ineffectually?
For generations,
House Vaude has used
offensive Spatial Magic,
and it has served us
well as Magic Knights.
What use would that
spell be in battle?
But...
I don't wanna hurt
anybody or get hurt.
That sounds scary.
[FINRAL'S FATHER]
Gutless weakling.
[FINRAL'S STEPMOTHER]
My! Just look how much
of that column you shaved off!
You're amazing, Langris!
An absolute genius!
[FINRAL'S FATHER] Don't worry,
we'll have someone fix
whatever you've broken.
[FINRAL'S STEPMOTHER]
You just keep practicing.
We'll take care
of everything, dear.
[FINRAL'S FATHER]
Honestly, Finral.
Aren't you ashamed to be shown
up by your younger brother?
[FINRAL'S FATHER]
You're brothers.
How could there be such a
difference in your abilities?
[FINRAL'S STEPMOTHER]
Why, just look at Langris.
He's already been made
vice-captain of the Golden Dawn!
[FINRAL'S FATHER]
And what have you accomplished?
You're nothing but a pack
mule for the Black Bulls,
the worst Magic Knight
squad there is.
[FINRAL'S FATHER] Langris
will be taking over as head
of House Vaude.
[FINRAL gasps]
[FINRAL'S FATHER]
I trust you don't object.
[FINRAL laughs]
No, of course not.
I was just thinking it'd
be a huge responsibility.
Take good care of
the place, Langris.
I don't need you to tell me
how to handle my affairs.
You're a disgrace to our house!
[FINRAL] Uh... Yeah,
I guess you're right.
But hey, at least the girls
really like my pretty face.
[FINRAL] I ran away from my
father, my brother, my home.
From reality.
Hello there!
You ladies sure are looking
lovely! Wanna go grab a drink?
I know a nice café
not far from here.
[FINRAL]
I've got to say, darling.
If you're as sweet
as you are beautiful,
I don't think we'll be
ordering any dessert.
[FINRAL]
And then... I met you, Asta.
A boy utterly without magic.
Not too little--none at all!
Instead of running from the
fact that you couldn't cast
a single spell, you faced
it head-on and fought
without ever giving up.
True, I can't hope to best
my brother as I am now.
But...
[FINRAL]
Yami?
What?
It's just that... Why'd you
let me join your squad
knowing I'm not
much of a fighter?
Figured you'd come in
handy as a chauffeur.
[gasps] Yeah. I guess
that makes sense.
I mean, it's not like
my spells are good
for taking down
enemies or anything.
Maybe not, but you've
probably got your own way
of fightin', don'tcha?
[YAMI] There's a lot more
to battle than just
taking down enemies, y'know.
[FINRAL] Is it possible?
My own way of fighting?
I know I'll never be
the strongest mage.
But I'll do what I can
to make the Black Bulls
the strongest squad!
I stepped away
from my own fight.
And when I did, there were
words I couldn't say anymore.
But I can say them now!
[FINRAL] Asta! I swear
I won't mess this up!
Please, just trust me, okay?
Too late, Finral!
I already trust you completely!
[VETTO laughs] I'm impressed.
You aren't half bad.
But you'll be at
your limit soon.
If even one of you
slips up, you'll be dead,
and you'll take the
other two with you.
How long do you think you
can actually keep going?
Shut up! You really
don't get it.
We'll keep fighting like this
for as long as we have to!
[FINRAL] Asta said he
trusts me completely.
And I guess it has to be true.
Because how else could we
possibly be pulling off
this ridiculous
method of fighting?
[VANESSA]
Really.
How can you so easily put
your life in our hands?
A drunken lush and
a superficial slacker.
Still, whatever made
you believe in us.
[FINRAL, VANESSA]
We won't betray your trust!
[ASTA yells]
Well done.
Your ability to focus
is commendable.
Although... How is your
magic holding out?
You'll be scraping the
bottom of the barrel soon.
Absolute amount of power.
That is the definitive
difference between my kind
and yours, ya fragile
little insects.
[FINRAL]
He may be full of himself,
but unfortunately,
he's not wrong.
My portals are
starting to shrink.
[VANESSA]
My threads, they're screaming.
With my magic running out,
they could snap any minute.
[ASTA] I trust you two,
and we're gonna win!
[VETTO yells]
[yells]
[GAUCHE]
It's not just two!
Looks like we made it in time.
Yeah!
[GREY stammers]
[ASTA]
Gauche?! Charmy!
And, uh...
[GAUCHE]
That's Grey.
And this might sound like
a terrible joke, but,
that's actually what
she looks like.
[NOELLE, FINRAL, ASTA, VANESSA]
What?!
[GREY]
Please! Stop looking at me!
Save all that for later.
Right now, take this, with all
the magic power I can muster!
Mirror Magic: Reflect Refrain!
[VETTO]
What are you playing at?
Ya think with enough
blasts, one has to land?
I think you're right
where I want you to be.
Now, Fivehead!
Cotton Creation Magic:
[CHARMY]
Strike of the Sleeping Sheep!
Strike one!
Strike two!
You're out!
They want a smokescreen?
Good luck with that!
[yells]
Huh?
[ASTAS yelling]
[VETTO yells]
[gasps] But how?
Um. I used my Transformation
Magic to make some doubles.
I'm low on power, though,
so some of them
aren't quite right.
[GAUCHE]
Nicely done!
And you, keep going
with the giant sheep
till you run out of magic!
Aye-aye, sir!
[VETTO yelling]
I've had enough!
Time to plunge you
insects into despair!
Yeah, right!
Who has time to
waste on despair?
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
"Three-In-One."
Right. I'll just
pull on my thread,
and when I do, it will
change your direction.
And after she does that,
I'll use my Spatial Magic
to send you somewhere else!
But one slip-up and that's
it, you're done for!
Are you sure you've got this?
Yeah I'm good.
All I have to do is charge.
All right, Gordon.
Let's do this.
[VANESSA, FINRAL, ASTA]
Ready, set, green light!
We can win! I trust
you two completely!
--C'mon! Yeah!
--[VANESSA, FINRAL] Asta!
[BOTH]
We've got you!
[mumbling] Red light!
Wha--?
[ASTA] As much as I
like this game, Gordon,
I think it would work
a lot better if I could
actually hear you when
you said "red light."
[FINRAL]
I'm sorry, Asta!
[VANESSA]
Your foe was just too terrible!
[mumbling] That was so fun.
You can be "it" next time, Asta.
And I'll make it all
the way to you, too.
[GORDON mumbling]
Oh, no!
I can sense that my
friends are in trouble.
I wish I could go help them.
Please be all right, everyone.
I'm sending good
thoughts your way!
Black Clover , Page 49:
"Beyond Limits."
My magic is becoming
friends with anyone.