[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy
who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
[NARRATOR]
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world
and to become the
next Wizard King!
[NARRATOR] After the chaos
in the royal capital
had finally died down,
Asta and the Black Bulls
were headed back home.
[laughing] Look alive,
knuckleheads.
It's not that much farther now!
After all the crazy
stuff that's happened,
it feels like we haven't
been home in forever!
Yeah, I know!
Maybe I can have at least
one day to work out in peace
before we get
another job to do!
And that's peaceful to you?
Huh? Hey... look!
Almost... there!
[BLACK BULL BEASTS growling]
Aw, yeah! We're finally home!
Hey, Henry!
Hurry up and switch this puppy
back to the way it was before!
[HENRY]
Hm...
What's the holdup, Henry?
Is something wrong?
You gassy?
What does... the
hideout... look like?
I can't... remember!
[BLACK BULLS]
What?!
This guy's a freakin' riot.
[MAGNA]
What the hell?
Didn't you live here
longer than anybody?
I'll walk you through it.
First you come in and there's
the living room, right?
Then after that is...
You explain it to him, Asta!
What? Who, me?
No! I'm clueless here!
Next is my shrine to Marie.
Actually, I'm pretty sure
it was a giant pantry
with snacks from all
over the kingdom in it!
Nah, it was the sauna.
[ASTA]
Whoa, where did you guys live?
But, maybe we did
have a snack cabinet
and a sauna and a
weird sister shrine...
[NOELLE] To be fair, the rooms
were always shifting around,
so it's kind of difficult
to picture what went where.
[HENRY]
Well...
You guys... kept...
breaking everything!
Thanks for the years
of free home repairs,
but you didn't have to randomly
change the whole floor plan!
Without the help
of my Spatial Magic,
Captain Yami would've
never found his way
to the little boy's room!
Think of all the
awkward situations
that could've been avoided!
Sorry... everyone.
[ASTA]
Hey!
Why don't we tell Henry
everything we want in a hideout,
and then he can put
all of our ideas together
and make this
building the coolest,
comfiest place
in the whole kingdom?
Yeah, Asta, that's
a killer idea!
[BOTH]
Sounds like a plan to me!
[laughs] As long as
I can enjoy my drinks
in the new place, I'm in!
You're shooting for
the moon, aren't you?
[whispering] Home
is the place where
the greatest of
friendships are forged!
All right, you morons
knock yourselves out.
[BOTH]
We'll do that, sir!
[ASTA]
We're countin' on you, Henry!
Leave it... to me!
Everybody take one!
Write all the stuff you
want on these forms!
Oh! Can't forget you two!
[ZORA]
Ugh.
There's always a
"thing" with you.
[HENRY]
Wow...
[NOELLE]
He seems overwhelmed.
Do you think we maybe
asked too much of him?
My request was for the
hideout to be relocated
so it's right next to the
church where Marie lives.
[MARIE] This is great!
Now I can see you every day!
Oh, Marie!
I can't wait to
be your neighbor!
I am not too picky,
as long as I get to be
in the same room
as all my friends
every second of every day!
[GREY] I've reached the
pinnacle of embarrassment,
so I want a place where
I can hide away forever!
If I can be surrounded
by dark curtains,
I'll be more than happy, okay?
My dream is to live
where I'm allowed to eat
ten full meals a day!
Yeah, you already do that.
Hey, how about we throw
in an open bar, too?
[meows]
[NOELLE]
I'm surrounded by idiots.
Hey, guess what?
I requested a room that's right
next door to yours, Magna!
Which means that, if I
use my magic detection,
I'll always be able to
tell what you're doing
on the other side of the wall!
I can't wait to mess with you!
I'll knock your teeth out!
Go on and try!
[MAGNA] Oh! Say that again,
you little twerp!
[LUCK laughs]
[NOELLE]
Who'll be next to me?
I guess if Nero gets moved
into a different room,
then she can't
wake me up anymore.
I was only pecking you
so you would stop
snoring so loudly.
[NOELLE]
Hey, wait!
When Nero was in her bird form,
she used to sleep in
the same room as Asta!
I mean, to be fair,
he didn't know she was
a cute girl back then!
She just perched on
the windowsill, right?
Ugh! Why do I even
care in the first place?
Um...
[ASTA] Henry's really giving
this a lot of thought, huh?
[NOELLE]
Well, it's important!
[YAMI]
All right, get back to work.
What's all this stuff for?
You want us to go hunting
for bugs or somethin'?
Of course not, you idiot.
My adorable little pets used
to live here before our hideout
got wrecked by the
Eye of the Midnight Sun,
so now they're runnin' loose!
Go track 'em down before
they cause trouble!
[BLACK BULLS]
Sir!
I forgot about them!
It's no big deal, though.
They got pretty used to me
after I took care of 'em.
I'm sure this is gonna
be a piece of cake!
[YAMI]
Don't count on that, kid.
Huh?
These woods are their backyard.
They probably went feral again
after a couple of days.
The second you let your guard
down, they'll eat you alive.
Hang on, if they're that scary,
how come you're sending me out
there with only this tiny net?
Quit your panicking and
go get my pets back!
[ASTA]
Okay!
[YAMI]
There are three magical beasts.
If the rest of you
are bored, go help him!
[GROUP]
'Kay!
Yes, sir! Yami, sir!
It's gonna be so much fun to
spar with some magical beasts!
If you lay even one finger
on my precious babies,
I'll rip you limb from limb.
Would you two leave me alone?
I'm trying to have
a conversation
with a photograph
of my little sister.
Our friend's counting on us!
I hope this won't end
in total embarrassment.
Are you listening to me?
You guys ready to go?
I think the three
of us should team up
since we're the squad rookies!
[BOTH]
If you say so.
Wait, wasn't Zora here
just a second ago?
[ZORA] No thanks.
I got better things to do.
[YAMI]
Oh, well.
That mask-wearing punk
can bail if he wants.
I'll just punish him later.
I've got an important
duty to attend to.
I'm leaving this up to you guys.
Hey! Monsters!
Where are you?
Woof! Woof, woof, woof, woof!
Meow. Meow...
[NOELLE]
That's actually kind of cute.
Do you really think
that's going to work?
How stupid can you be?
Don't forget.
The captain said
they're probably feral,
so if we act like bait,
we'll just get mauled!
I know, but I was the one
who took care of them,
so maybe they'll
come to their senses
when they realize who I am!
Come to think of it, Nero,
you were kinda like my pet
back when you were
in your bird form,
so you understand what
I mean, don't ya?
You shouldn't patronize me.
In my bird form, I was watching
over your grimoire, not you.
If you ask me, you were the pet.
[NOELLE] They say the more
you argue, the closer you are.
I mean, not that it makes
any difference to me!
I only came along because
I had no choice in the matter!
What's that ki I'm sensing?
What? Um.
I don't know,
but there was no way
I was thinking about you two!
--[ASTA] Found ya!
--Asta!
[yells]
Hey, what's a flock of
anti-birds doing here?
They're about to
peck me to death!
They must be angry
because you're so noisy.
I'll see if I can locate
them from the sky.
[ASTA]
Save me!
[NOELLE]
Maybe I'm worried about nothing.
Kind of seems like
they hate each other.
[gasps]
Wait, we're alone now?
Man, this place
is friggin' creepy.
[LUCK laughs]
What's the matter? Ya scared?
What are you talking
about? I'm not scared!
Just shut your yap, and put
some pep in your step!
Hey, I told you to hurry--
Uh...
[MAGNA] That little snot
probably hid somewhere
so he could go "boo!"
and try to spook me.
Don't bother, small fry!
I'll make you regret this!
[MAGNA]
Ha!
Did you think an
amateur move like that
would actually work on me?
Boo!
[MAGNA screams]
[LUCK laughs] My "scare and
shock" plan was a huge success!
Oh! I'mma kill you!
I don't know,
are you sure you can?
Well, there's nobody out here
to make us stop fighting,
so feel free to come at me
with everything you've got!
Oh, I wouldn't say
that if I were you.
Things have changed,
and you and I
are on totally different
levels these days!
That's for damn sure.
You may not know this, but I
developed unbelievable strength
after our battle when
you were possessed!
Oh, really?
That makes two of us, then!
The mana's calling to me.
I haven't sparred
with you in ages,
so I'll probably have too much
fun and get carried away!
What are you waiting for?
Oh, gosh! What was
that loud sound?
Magna and Luck.
I think they're reigniting
their fiery friendship!
Who gives a crap?
And you two!
How long do you plan on
cowering behind me?
Please pretend I'm not here!
This whole situation
is so humiliating!
Why didn't you just stay home?
Well, I wanted to, but
there aren't any walls left
to conceal my shame!
[GAUCHE]
I'm not your damn wall!
[GORDON]
This forest is really scary,
and we're not sure when the
magical beasts might attack!
Don't worry, your face is
the most terrifying thing here!
Hey...
[GREY] I wish you'd stop
making eye contact with me!
[BLACK BULL BEASTS growling]
[GAUCHE]
Yep, there they are.
The faster I wrangle
these monsters,
the sooner I can visit
my sweet Marie!
You ready, guys?
Hey, what the hell
are you doing?!
I'm sorry, it's just that
they popped up out of nowhere,
and it caused my embarrassment
to evolve into pure terror!
--[GAUCHE] Let go of me!
--But I can't do that.
My heart's not ready
to let you go!
Ugh, I can't believe
I got teamed up
with the two biggest
scaredy-cats on the squad!
How am I supposed to
catch these things
with you two hanging onto me?
[yelping]
--[BEAR growling]
--[BLACK BULLS screaming]
Yum! This is so delicious!
Nothing's better than
scarfing down a meat bun
while you're hunting
magical beasts!
I prefer a strong drink.
[meows]
Hey, Finral, can you
make a portal
and go buy me another
bottle or two?
[FINRAL]
Um, don't you guys think
we should get back
to hunting soon?
Oh, quit being a goody-two-shoes
and drink up, you big nerd!
[CHARMY]
Here!
You know you wanna try
some of these nummy treats!
They're fresh out of the oven!
Listen, it's not that
I don't want to,
I just don't feel like
it's a good idea!
[FINRAL] If the captain found
out, he'd kill me for sure!
[FINRAL] Then again,
I'm sure the others already
caught them anyway,
so there's no reason
we can't relax for
a little bit--!
Hey, where'd Finral go?
To get me that drink!
By the way, do you have
any more snacks, Charmy?
[VANESSA]
Have I had too many?
Oh, my goodness, Charmy,
you're so tall all of a sudden,
and so hairy, too!
Not to mention those
nails of yours.
You're in desperate need
of a manicure, ya know!
Otherwise, that pretty boy
from the Golden Dawn
will never like you back!
That was a great fight!
You've really improved.
[MAGNA]
Back atcha. Just for now,
I guess I can let
ya off the hook.
That said, you're not
gonna leave me behind,
do ya understand me?
If you get ten times stronger,
then I will, too.
You might get a step ahead,
but you'll never outdo me.
I hope you're okay with that.
My bad!
Sorry, I couldn't really
hear your big speech
over all the growling.
Aw! Dammit, there's
always something!
Just gimme a second to
recover my mana and stamina,
and then I'll save
you, I promise.
Okay, that sounds fair!
Hey, don't eat me,
I'm the guy who used
to take care of you
before Asta came along.
Don't tell me you forgot
about me already!
Come on, I swear I
don't taste very good!
[MAGNA yells]
[ASTA] Jeez, where
could those things be?
Nero still hasn't
come back, either.
[NOELLE] Being alone with
him makes me jumpy.
[ASTA]
Those are Magna's glasses!
--Oh, no!
--[NOELLE] It can't be!
--They ate him?
[MAGNA groaning]
[BOTH gasp]
Luck.
Oh, man, are you guys okay?
Talk to us!
It's bad.
The other Black Bulls were also
defeated by the magical beasts.
[ASTA, NOELLE gasp]
Asta, forget about us. Just run.
Captain Yami. He's in trouble.
[knocking]
It's occupied.
[banging]
Hey! I'm in here, dammit!
Who is that?
Look, if you good-for-nothin'
slackers are back already,
then you better have
my pets with you.
I'm up against a
tough opponent here,
and if I don't concentrate, he's
gonna go back into hiding, so--!
[banging]
Gimme a minute! Sheesh!
I'm glad the three
of you are home,
but you're probably not waitin'
in line to use the john, huh?
[ASTA] Captain Yami's way
stronger than we are,
so he might be okay.
But Magna and Luck
almost got eaten alive!
If all three attack him at once,
I'm not sure if he'll make it!
Just hang in there, okay?
I'm on my way to rescue you!
[YAMI] Hey! Stop licking me
already, you big lugs!
Ugh, your drool
smells like garbage!
[ASTA groans]
What the heck, Captain Yami?
I rushed over here to save you
'cause I thought you were
being attacked by the magical
beasts, but you're fine!
Well, I guess they
technically did attack me.
They... wanted... some
attention... from you.
C'mon, that's it? Really?
These big fellas are
always crazy-affectionate.
In fact, they've been like that
ever since I first met 'em.
I remember I was on my
way back to the hideout.
[YAMI] When I found them,
the poor things' parents
had just been killed,
and they were all alone.
Guess some nobles were out
hunting magical
beasts for sport.
[YAMI]
Sorry, little ones.
Your folks aren't ever
gonna wake up again.
Look. I got separated
from my parents, too,
but all we can do is chin up
and keep on keepin' on.
Hey, don't get the wrong idea,
I never said I was
gonna take care of y--
Now, how'm I supposed
to say no to that?
Aw! Wow!
That was such a
heartwarming story, sir!
I bet those beasts
were so adorable
when they were teeny-
weeny little babies!
How... sweet.
Anyway, it didn't even take
six months for these guys
to grow up as big as
their parents had been.
Costs me a fortune
to keep 'em fed,
so I keep trying to abandon 'em.
[ASTA]
Okay, you just ruined it!
[HENRY]
That's... mean.
I sent you guys off
to capture 'em so they
didn't wander into a nearby
village and wreak havoc
or anything like that.
Although, if it seemed like they
wanted to return to the wild
and be free,
I was kinda thinkin'
of lettin' 'em loose in
the mountains somewhere
as soon as we could get
a hold of 'em again.
Whee!
Hey, Captain Yami's
still in one piece!
[ASTA]
Magna, you're back!
I thought you were
hurt real bad!
[MAGNA]
Nope!
But they did lick us all over,
so we smell kinda ripe now.
It seemed like they
were gonna gobble us up,
but they just wanted us to
pet them and play with them!
Apparently, it was enough
to make everyone
faint from exhaustion.
You're such a
troublesome group.
Well, we figured if they
were that excited to see us,
then Captain Yami would
have a really hard time
fighting them off, so we were
concerned for his safety!
[MAGNA]
But, the boss-man's A-okay!
[VANESSA]
I'm sure he's used to it.
He is their owner, after all.
[LUCK laughs]
Who's a good magical beastie?
I better make some dolls
of the three of you, as well.
Don't lick Marie,
or you're dead.
[NOELLE]
They're pretty cute,
but their drool
smells like death.
If you want us to
pet you some more,
go take a bath and
brush your teeth.
[ASTA]
I see.
They must love the rest
of the Black Bulls
just like they love the captain!
Hey there.
Since I'm your caretaker, do you
want me to pet you for a while?
[ASTA screams]
[YAMI]
Judging by that look,
they still think
of you as dinner.
Nah, that can't be it,
these guys totally adore me!
Here you go, I brought you
a little snacky-snack,
but you gotta sit first!
[ASTA screams]
This is hard to watch.
[yawns] Hey, did
I miss anything?
[ASTA]
Zora!
What have you been up
to this whole time?
[ZORA] I don't see how
that's your business, kid.
The hideout's still
not finished?
Sun's going down.
Actually... it is.
I just... need to...
put it... together.
[HENRY] Recombination Magic:
Black Bulls' Hideout,
Hard Rock Bison Style!
[BLACK BULLS gasp]
[HENRY] The outside...
was... Magna's... idea.
So tacky.
You know, for a royal,
you really don't know
sophistication and
class when you see 'em!
Sweet! I can't wait
to look inside!
[VANESSA]
Ah, it's just what I wanted!
This way I can drink
to my heart's content!
[meows]
[CHARMY]
I keep stuffing my face,
and the food never stops coming!
[ASTA yelps]
Why is there a giant
hole in the floor?
[GREY] I wanted a place where
I could hide in the dark
when I'm embarrassed,
which is constantly.
[GAUCHE] I couldn't be
Marie's neighbor,
but this is still nice.
Hey, Angel Marie,
tell Big Brother
tomorrow's forecast, huh?
[MARIE]
Mostly sunny, but partly cloudy.
Temperatures will be
mild during the day
and a little chillier
as night falls.
[GAUCHE] This talking
Marie doll is incredible!
Henry is a genius!
No cute maid, huh? Oh, well.
I can... clean...
your room... for you.
No thanks!
Just... an idea.
Uh, right. I appreciate
the thought.
What about the rooms?
Who's everyone paired up with?
I'm... glad... you asked.
This part... was...
Gordon's request.
[mumbling] We should all share
the same room as friends.
[NOELLE] What?! So I'm
not next door to Asta.
I'm sharing a room
with him? As friends?
That's a step above
"friends," isn't it?
This is crazy!
[ASTA] Kinda reminds me
of sharing a space
with Yuno and Nash
at the church.
Man, this is gonna be a blast!
I'm not okay with this.
Neither am I.
Right, this isn't up
to my royal standards.
[whimpering] So shameful!
Well, I can't say I'm crazy
about sharing a room with Luck,
but it'll be fun
to stay up late,
chattin' with Captain
Yami every night.
Yeah, I'm gonna veto
that right now.
[gasps]
Oh... right... I forgot.
The captain's... in a...
different... room.
[BLACK BULLS]
Seriously?!
The hell is this?
It... was a... request from...
the magic... beasts.
[YAMI] Well, when you put
it like that, I guess...
It's still a no!
[ASTA yelps]
[YAMI]
That's better.
We need a hideout, not a
freakin' amusement park.
That's why I made Henry change
it back into the dusty
old mansion it was
when we started.
The wine fountain was nice,
but it's a lot cozier this way.
[MAGNA] Yeah, it's got that
home-sweet-home feelin'.
[NOELLE] I'm definitely not
disappointed at all.
No way.
[ASTA] When I first
walked into this hideout
after becoming a Black Bull,
everyone accepted me
right off the bat,
even though I didn't
have any magic ability.
Ever since then, every day's
been an adventure.
We had plenty of close calls,
but it always turned out okay,
because they were
here to help me.
You guys.
There's something I need to say.
I'm really glad I joined the
Black Bulls and met all of you!
Aw, what's making you get so
sentimental all of a sudden?
[VANESSA]
I feel the same.
[FINRAL]
All of us have grown so much
because you never gave up, Asta.
[NOELLE]
You're reckless and stubborn,
but that's not a bad
thing... sometimes.
[FINRAL] We need to hurry
and clear Asta's name.
[MAGNA, VANESSA, CHARMY]
Yeah.
First things first.
We better figure out everything
we can about those devils.
[ASTA]
Right!
[ASTA] Now that we're
back at the hideout,
I'm gonna push
myself even harder!
Huh?
Where are you off to,
Captain Yami?
Black Clover , Page 126:
"The Blue Rose's Confession."
I wonder what Captain
Charlotte is gonna confess?