[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed
lost until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[LOTUS] Well, this isn't
a good turn of events.
If that's how it's going to be,
I suppose it's time
to get serious.
[LOTUS]
Smoke Creation Magic:
Prison of the Fallen King!
Poor, foolish little children.
[ASTA] The thing about
the Black Bulls is
we don't lose to anyone,
and that includes you!
Got it?
Time to go. This ends now.
What are you...?
[YUNO]
Wind Creation Magic:
Engaging Swift White Hawk,
paired with Wind Blade Shower.
[KLAUS]
He's performing a dual-casting?
Time to get out of
our way, Diamond mage.
The Golden Dawn will
reach the hall first.
[yelling]
Here!
[yelps]
[coughs]
Anyone else feeling kinda dizzy?
[NOELLE] This place is
filling up with smoke.
We'll wind up
suffocating at this rate.
Our only chance is to defeat
the spellcaster, and fast!
[LUCK]
I can sense his magic power,
so I have a good idea
of where he might be.
If we attack, he'll
most likely dodge it.
What do I know about his
fighting style so far?
[LUCK] When he's inside the
smoke, he can move really fast,
and he can pick up on
magic power quickly, too.
Our best shot is to find
a way to blindside him.
But how, when he can
sense our magic?
[ASTA yells]
I can sense your magic power,
so sneak attacks aren't
going to work on me.
Whoa, there! Wow, rapid-fire!
Getting desperate, are we?
I'm afraid you won't be
able to hit me like that.
It won't clear
the smoke, either.
I suppose it all comes
down to experience.
I've likely been in more battles
than all of you combined.
[yelps]
[groans]
[ASTA growls, yells]
[LOTUS groans]
[NOELLE]
That went really well.
You know, you were
right earlier.
Teamwork is vital.
[LOTUS] Oh, dear.
What have you done to me?
Feeble old man that I am.
[LOTUS]
Well, that's not good.
Arm appears to be broken.
Along with a handful
of ribs, I'd imagine.
[LOTUS] I'm in no shape
to fight like this. Hm.
The Clover Kingdom
sure does have
some rare gems. Take this
diamond in the rough.
A magicless lad wielding
an enormous blade.
Even with my
considerable experience,
I've never met anyone on the
battlefield who lacked magic.
[LOTUS] If I'm going
to be taken prisoner...
...I'd rather die.
[LOTUS]
Or just run away.
Hey, get back here!
Wait up, Asta!
You're not getting away.
Yes, my handy
Smoke Creation Magic.
Nothing like a ride in
the Hustling Lazy Car.
[LUCK]
Hah! I'm right on your tail.
[laughs]
[LUCK]
Whoa!
Aw.
We lost him, huh? Stupid smoke!
[panting] You guys...
are way too fast.
Man. That's too bad.
I was really looking forward
to finishing the fight
with that old guy.
But that's not
the mission, right?
Let's forget him and get
to the treasure hall.
Wait, you're turning
down a fight?
[ASTA]
Yeah, let's get movin'!
There's treasure to find!
[gasps]
[LUCK]
Oh, wow. So much magic power.
That guy was strong.
But there's someone here
who can give him
a run for his money.
[LOTUS]
Everyone doing all right?
At this rate,
we're going to have to
forego the treasure hall.
[grunts]
Well, I'm sure Mars
is capable of
handling it without me.
Let's not forget,
he is the Diamond Kingdom's
secret weapon.
[panting]
[KLAUS] Such frighteningly
sinister magic.
Yuno's using all his strength,
and yet, he's helpless.
[KLAUS]
Those embedded gemstones.
I've heard of them!
[KLAUS] There have been rumors
that the Diamond Kingdom
has been experimentally
cultivating mages
who have artificially
enhanced magic power.
[KLAUS] They select
children gifted in magic
from a young age, subject
them to fierce competition,
and embed magic-heightening
items into their bodies.
[KLAUS] In the end, they must
fight one another to the death.
The lone survivor of
that deadly free-for-all...
[KLAUS]
Is that... him?
[KLAUS] Whoever he is,
this situation is dire.
How can this be happening?
I am of the nobility.
A member of the
elite Golden Dawn!
[KLAUS] One ally has
already fallen to him.
And a commoner is protecting me.
[growls]
This is unacceptable.
I will not allow this
travesty to continue.
Now! Steel Creation Magic:
Spiral Lance!
Wait, Klaus, sir!
[KLAUS gasps]
A mineral clone?
[gasps]
Too close!
[sputters]
[MARS] Such pitiful magic.
It won't work on me.
[YUNO grunts]
It's no use.
[yells]
[MARS]
I'm telling you, it's no use.
[YUNO]
It's no use.
Let's just forget
about training. Okay?
I'm not done yet!
Not until I land a hit on you.
No way am I gonna quit now!
[yells]
[ASTA yelling]
[YUNO]
Asta...
[ASTA]
Not yet. I'm not done!
--C'mon, can't we just--
--[ASTA] No way!
I am never, ever,
going to give up!
[yells]
Stop your pointless posturing.
I won't.
[MARS]
Move.
I won't.
[MARS]
Give up.
[YUNO]
I will not.
[YUNO yells]
Yuno!
[ASTA yells]
[ASTA] Hey, you.
Freaky-lookin' pale dude.
Keep your hands off this guy.
Yuno's not yours to fight.
He's my rival.
[YUNO yells]
Yuno!
[ASTA yells]
[ASTA] Hey, you.
Freaky-lookin' pale dude.
Keep your hands off this guy.
Yuno's not yours to fight.
He's my rival.
You must be kidding.
Just when I thought I had
paid my debt to you.
I can't believe it.
I finally catch up to you,
and you're two seconds
away from being killed!
Were you just gonna let
that sucker beat you?
Mind your own business, Asta.
I was this close
to taking him down.
That's a lie, and you know it.
You're a wreck.
You were totally about to die!
No, I was about to launch
a very damaging counterattack.
[ASTA]
Lies! Lies! Lies!
I was waiting for
the right moment.
[ASTA] Ugh. This is
just like you, Yuno!
[YUNO]
Are you done interfering?
[ASTA]
Excuse me?
[YUNO]
You can go now.
Okay, I'll tell you what.
We'll fight to see
who brings him down.
Whatever it takes.
[KLAUS]
No. This is absurd.
Three members of the
Golden Dawn couldn't take him.
Yet, his incredible power
was bested by a commoner
from the Black Bulls?
[KLAUS]
No!
[LUCK]
Fragile, huh?
[KLAUS]
Is that...
...the mage infamous for
having savagely beaten
his exam opponent...
Luck the Cheery Berserker?
[giggles]
[KLAUS] He's the third mage
sent from the Black Bulls?
I'm being rescued by that ragtag
bunch of lunatic misfits?
Mimosa!
I'm ashamed to be
seen like this.
I suppose you were
right about me, Noelle.
A dim bulb, just like you said.
It's true.
You're rather lacking
in the sense department.
[NOELLE]
But that's all right.
Because I'm here now.
And I will protect you!
Thanks, Noelle.
[ASTA]
Are you the person who did this
to the Golden Dawn?
And what is it to you if I did?
It is the strong who remain,
while the weak fade away.
Simple as that.
He can create that many
clones at one time?
Ooh!
The battlefield is
a place of power.
On it, there is no
room for the weak.
That's why I was born.
To destroy those like you.
[ASTA]
Yeah? That so?
Well? Go on.
Destroy me!
[MARS]
I fully intend to.
[ASTA grunts]
[ASTA growls, yells]
[gasps]
[MIMOSA, LUCK, KLAUS, NOELLE]
Whoa!
[LUCK]
Aw, man.
I wanted to take him on.
Guess these guys'll have to do.
[LUCK laughing]
[YUNO grunts]
[KLAUS]
Impossible.
How could a commoner
with no mana do that?
[gasps]
Please, stop looking
so horrified
and accept it already.
He's powerful in his own way.
Asta has the ability
to nullify magic.
Nullify it?
Truly?
But a commoner like him
is beneath a power like that.
Perhaps he was just lucky to
be endowed with such a skill.
Was it luck or something else?
You can tell just
by watching him.
[ASTA]
Well, come on!
What, are ya done already?
[ASTA yells]
Asta!
[grunts]
[MARS]
Tell me, boy: what are you?
Sure, I'll tell you.
I'm somebody who was born
without a single drop
of magic power.
What? He has no magic at all?
Then it was just sheer
luck that he's so--
[KLAUS gasps]
[ASTA] And I'm still gonna
be the Wizard King.
I'll fight and bleed
all I have to.
But I will prove
that I can do it!
[KLAUS]
Just look at his body!
How much time has
he spent training?
The Wizard King...
Can he really mean it?
[FANA]
Mars? When you grow up,
what do you want to be?
[MARS]
I... I live only to destroy!
That's why you live--to destroy?
Well, the Wizard King
lives to protect
his kingdom and his people!
[FANA] We'll keep everyone
in the country safe.
That's why we were born, right?
I will never lose.
Not to somebody like you!
You're in my way.
Begone, pebble!
Sure, I might be
a pebble, but if so,
I'm going to be the pebble
that shatters the diamond!
[MARS groans]
[MARS grunts]
[panting]
[ASTA panting]
[yelling]
[ASTA]
You see?
You can do anything
if you don't give up!
[yells]
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[ASTA, NOELLE]
"The Treasure Hall."
We finally made it!
This place is amazing!
I wonder if any of this
will be suitable
for my refined tastes.
[ASTA] Okay, I'm gonna
see how much loot
this baby is hiding!
All right, but I wanna see
what's in there, too.
Open sesame!
[NOELLE]
Ugh. More like bleh-sure hall.
[ASTA]
Why does this always happen?
[LOTUS]
Whew, I'm all tuckered out.
Run ragged at work and at home.
A guy just can't catch a break.
Black Clover , Page 18:
"Memories of You."
My magic is letting
the younger generation
clean up the mess.