[NARRATOR] Within the clover's
fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
[NARRATOR] Asta, born
unable to harness mana,
was granted the power
of Anti-magic
from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability
to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members
of Spade Kingdom's
Dark Triad also possess
powers from the devils
of the underworld
and used them to launch
an invasion on the
neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from
his belief in himself
and from the support
of his friends,
Asta continues to fight for
the safety of this world.
[NARRATOR] Zenon--one of
the Spade Kingdom's Dark Triad--
attacked the Golden
Dawn headquarters
with two of his underlings
from the Dark Disciples.
[YUNO] What the hell
do you think you're doing...
...to my comrades?!
[NARRATOR] Enraged at the sight
of his friends being harmed,
Yuno defeated
the two lesser foes.
[ZENON]
Fifty-five percent.
Do you see what your problem is?
It isn't that you're weak.
I'm just that much better.
[NARRATOR] Just when Yuno's
death seemed all but certain,
he was revived by
the Budding of Yggdrasil,
the spell left behind
by Captain Vangeance.
[YUNO whimpers]
[yells]
Humanity is evil.
Rage.
Fear.
Hatred.
Revenge.
Destruction.
Evil is a human's nature.
And we have ceased to be
amused by this mundane world.
[DANTE]
Now then.
I suppose I should be on my way.
[DANTE]
What kind of human are you,
Arcane-stage mage,
Yami Sukehiro?
[VANICA]
This rules!
Huh. I wonder how
Loropechika and her pals
have been doing lately.
I hope they've got
lots of energy!
Then they'll be
extra fun to crush!
[giggles]
[slurps]
[CHARMY]
It's so yummy!
The Heart Kingdom's got all
kinds of delicious delicacies!
Oh, Charmy!
You're so adorable!
[MIMOSA]
My goodness.
Those two really do make
the perfect pair, don't they?
Cut it out, Loropechika.
She'll never stop eating if you
keep spoiling her like that.
Look, she's about to pop!
It's no problem.
Charmy'll be super precious
no matter how chubby she gets!
I couldn't agree more,
because a well-fed Charmy
is a happy Charmy, after all!
Did she seriously only come to
the Heart Kingdom to find out
what kind of snacks
they had to offer?
Seems that way.
We need to focus.
As it stands, we'll be fighting
the Spade Kingdom any day now.
Fine by me. I'm ready
to throw down whenever!
So am I! And we've taken over
all of the towns surrounding
the Spade Kingdom's border,
so that should give us
a decent advantage.
That's true, but we can't
afford to get comfortable,
which is why Rill and
Charlotte have made a trip
back to the Clover Kingdom
to participate in
a squad captains' meeting.
I know, but I've got all this
anticipation welling up inside,
so it's hard to contain it!
Then come spar with me!
Heh. Since I haven't gotten
a chance to fight against you
for real yet!
Yeah, that's a great idea!
Let's see if Asta
wants to join us, too,
and then we can make it
a three-way battle royale!
[NOELLE]
Asta's not here, though.
What?!
[NOELLE] Since we had
a break from our training,
he wanted to take
a few gifts back.
He and Finral
went there together.
[LEOPOLD groans]
The battle is sure to be brutal,
so it's smart to relax
while we still have the chance.
Perhaps everyone should
have something to eat.
[CHARMY]
Sorry, I've officially claimed
this pile of noms for myself.
On second thought, you'll have
to locate food elsewhere.
I didn't realize it,
but every single morsel of this
belongs to Charmy.
[NOELLE] That's why I said
not to spoil her!
[LOROPECHIKA giggles]
[LOROPECHIKA gasps]
Are you ready, Undine?
Of course.
[NOELLE]
What's wrong, Loropechika?
[LOROPECHIKA]
Spade is here.
It looks like...
...six of them, spread
throughout the kingdom!
[LEOPOLD]
That was quick!
What about the
Mana Zone barrier?
They tore right through it?
[LOROPECHIKA] Since Undine's
clones are spread out,
we were quickly able to notify
the Spirit Guardians
of their locations.
[UNDINE] And they've
taken defensive measures.
[LOROPECHIKA]
Even so,
all six of these enemies
are stage-zero mages
who possess a devil's power.
This could prove difficult even
for the Spirit Guardians.
I may ask for your help
if things get too dire!
Loropechika!
[LOROPECHIKA gasps]
This intense magic...
[LOROPECHIKA]
It's Vanica of the Dark Triad.
She's possessed by
the devil Megicula!
[NOELLE growls]
Megicula...
[VANICA]
Heh. Great!
From the looks of it,
I'd say we've killed
about 100 of them so far!
Lady Vanica, don't you
think we should head--
[groans]
[VANICA]
Not yet!
The more of Loropechika's
peasants we mow down,
the more fired up
she's bound to get.
That'll make this way more fun!
Yes, of course, milady. As you--
[groans]
[chuckles] Oh, yeah!
Step on me more!
[chuckles]
You pig.
[NARRATOR] The neutral zone
between the Clover
and Spade Kingdoms.
[NARRATOR] The Black Bulls'
hideout was placed here
to serve as a first
line of defense.
Hey, we're back from
the Heart Kingdom!
And we brought gifts!
You thought of us after
being away for so long?
Well, aren't you a sweetie?
Good thing, too.
'Cause we're completely
out of drinking snacks.
[GREY] Um, hey...
Nice to see you, Asta!
I sure wish I had a little
more Marie around here.
[ASTA] Yeah, I can't really
help you with that, Gauche.
Uh. The captain's meeting
should be over with soon.
Guess I better go pick up Yami.
You're busy, huh, Finral?
We really appreciate
everything you do, though.
[sighs] Yeah,
this job's exhausting.
I'll be gone for a while.
It's a long trip, so I'm
gonna make a bunch of stops.
Roger that!
[FINRAL]
See you later.
Hey, how's Gordon doing?
I bet he's been studying
his Curse Magic like crazy,
hasn't he?
[sighs] Don't ask me.
All I know about it is...
...I'm not going back there.
[GORDON]
This is hard.
[NATHAN]
You can do it, son.
[ROXANNE]
I believe in you.
Gordon. You really should eat.
That sandwich!
It's exactly the same as
the one you made for me
when we had our first date!
[NATHAN] Takes me back
to the good old days.
[JONNA] Yes, when you
were 18 and I was 17.
Our meeting was pure fate!
Papa, please tell me more about
how you and Mama first met.
[NATHAN]
With pleasure!
I'd rather just focus
on my studies.
[shrieks]
So, I guess Henry
is still resting up?
[VANESSA] Apparently,
his mana supply is low,
since so many of us have
been away from the hideout
because of training and such.
And with Charmy gone,
we don't have access
to that mana-recovery
food she makes.
Yeah, Charmy's hooked on
the snacks in the Heart Kingdom,
so she probably won't
be back for a while.
Nothing motivates her
more than food, after all.
Oh, by the way, where's Magna?
Right, I forgot to mention.
No sooner than he got back from
his trip to the Heart Kingdom,
he and Zora headed off
somewhere else together.
I guess they get along, since
they're both Grumpy-Guses.
[gasps] Hey... guys!
Is Henry awake?
I guess so.
Is something wrong?
[gasps] The hideout!
It's floating!
[DANTE]
So. Yami isn't home right now.
In that case,
perhaps you can entertain me
while I wait for him.
Shall we?
Spade's attacking us here?
He's the one who's
making us float?
By himself?
[DANTE chuckles]
--Go, Rouge!
--[meows]
[DANTE]
Oh?
Here... we... go...!
[HENRY] Recombination Magic:
The Raging Black Bull.
If he wants a battle,
then that's what I'll give him!
Large Reflect Refrain!
[HENRY]
Mana Rocket Punch!
[DANTE]
Insolence.
Gravity Magic:
Presence of the Demon King.
What the hell
kind of magic is that?
Half of the forest
is snapping like twigs!
And if it weren't for Rouge,
then that would be us right now.
[DANTE]
Despite being hit by my spell,
you're still in one piece.
[chuckles]
I'm guessing
one of you has magic
that influences natural laws.
I thought Yami was
the only arcane-stage here.
Excellent.
[VANESSA gasps]
Heh. Hm?
Your fight is with me!
My, aren't you
a lively little nuisance?
Fair enough, then.
I can spare you some attention.
[chuckles]
[ASTA yells]
[ASTA]
Black Slash!
[DANTE] Gravity Magic:
Presence of the Demon King.
[gasps]
He canceled out my magic,
then made his move.
Not half bad.
But I'm not done.
[ASTA gasps]
[ASTA screams]
[DANTE chuckles]
[gasps]
[BOTH yell]
That magic may
modify natural laws,
but I didn't realize it could
overturn death, as well.
[ASTA grunts]
[GROUP gasps]
Let me guess,
this cat belongs to you.
Stay behind Rouge, okay, guys?
[ASTA]
Forget them, fight me!
Asta!
[VANESSA]
His magic's overwhelming.
And it's got
such a wide range, too!
Hah.
Not only can you manipulate
the laws of nature,
you're also
strikingly beautiful.
Dante of the Dark Triad.
The pleasure is all mine.
[VANESSA] The Dark Triad?
Like, the ones from Spade?
[GAUCHE] Those jerks are
the reason our kingdom
got wrapped up in this mess!
Now, come.
You're going to be my woman.
Ugh.
You can't just take possession
of someone like that!
I would love to see you
try to stop me.
So you're the guy
who's in charge, huh?!
What a delicious surprise.
I didn't know Clover had
a devil-possessed, as well.
[ASTA]
Black Divider!
[ASTA yells]
Black Meteorite!
I can't hit him!
That Anti-magic technique
is made to track mana.
So how did he dodge it?
And what do we do?
[gasps]
[GAUCHE]
If he can side-step that,
then we'll keep attacking
until he screws up!
How nice of him to come
straight to our doorstep.
If we can win this fight,
then the whole stupid
mess'll be over with!
Hey, Asta!
Yeah? What's up?
New plan! Look here!
Mirror Magic: Mirror Brigade!
[ASTA, GAUCHE]
Mirror Meteorites!
[gasps]
--[yells]
--[ASTA CLONES yelling]
This'll scatter
Asta's Anti-magic.
And it moves incredibly fast,
so if all goes well...
...he won't be able to evade it!
[DANTE]
Fifty percent.
[ASTA gasps]
You're kidding!
Did he just warp space?
What happened?
[DANTE] I'd like us
to have a discussion.
True, we may have
different ranks,
but we're both devil-possessed.
I'm sure we can find
some common ground.
[ASTA groans]
We are nothing alike! Nothing!
You're doing such terrible
things to your own people.
How could I ever
get along with you?
[chuckles] I don't understand
all your melodramatic nonsense,
but if I disgust you, then
that's quite the compliment.
So thanks for that.
Malice is an emotion that's
unique to human beings.
It distinguishes us
from all other animals.
[ASTA grunts]
But what am I saying?
I'm sure you're familiar.
Rage.
Hatred.
Revenge.
Destruction.
Malice has power!
Because, whenever you let those
feelings of malice take over,
that's when you're
at your most human.
After all, humanity's
truest form is evil!
[ASTA]
You're wrong!
I'll admit, I have bad thoughts
every once in a while, too.
Sometimes, they even
give me more power to fight!
Thing is, I have a heart
that's really strong,
so I can control those
feelings and use them
to do good things instead!
That's what makes me human!
Is that so?
It seems that you're quite
unique among those
who are possessed by devils.
Meow.
As long as I'm here, I won't
let any of my friends die!
[DANTE]
Naughty girl.
You're my woman now, remember?
And that means you
can't use your power
to help anyone except for me.
[growls]
Let's move to 60%.
[ROUGE meows]
[grunts] This is awful.
I worked so hard to improve...
To become stronger...
And he just undid everything
in the blink of an eye!
[panting]
[HENRY]
My mana's depleted.
I can't... operate
the Black Bull anymore.
[GAUCHE]
I can't control my body!
This guy's got us pinned down!
We're sitting ducks!
[GREY]
I have to do something!
[DANTE] Gravity Magic:
Evil God's Pressure Craft.
Have it your way.
[gasps]
Perhaps you'll be more driven...
if I appeal to your feelings.
No, wait.
Stop it, now!
[ASTA]
Stop!
[DANTE chuckles]
Don't do it!
--[VANESSA] Oh, no!
--[GREY] He hurt Gauche!
[ASTA'S MOM] I'm here with you,
my precious little boy.
[ASTA snarls]
[laughs]
[ASTA growls]
[DANTE]
There it is.
That's human nature!
[GROUP gasps]
[VANESSA] Asta's attack was
able to erase this guy's magic
from the whole area!
[GREY whimpers]
Now, then. Let's find out
what you can really do.
[ASTA snarls]
[ASTA growls]
You'll never damage me
with those techniques.
You'll have to
adjust your strategy.
[ASTA growling]
[DANTE] I was hoping
to chat with you a bit,
but you appear to be lost inside
yourself at the moment.
Perhaps you can
tell me who that devil is...
...Lucifero.
I do not know.
If any high-ranking devils
are in the mortal realm now,
it would probably be Zagred,
who left the underworld,
but I don't believe
that's the case.
Erasing magic is a parlor trick.
It must be the work of
a being that possesses
only a paltry amount of mana.
[DANTE] In other words,
the boy is no match for us.
We are possessed
by the mightiest of devils.
That's what makes us
the Dark Triad!
[shouts]
[ASTA grunts]
[ASTA snarling]
[yells]
[VANESSA]
What's going on here?
Something's off.
It's like Asta's powers
are going berserk!
Still, we have to rely on him.
At this rate, Gauche won't
survive much longer.
If only Nero were here
to seal his wounds!
But even that
might not be enough.
Hang in there, Gauche.
Please don't leave us!
[sobs]
I'm so weak...
I couldn't do anything...!
[whimpers]
My Transformation Magic...
It doesn't help at all...
It's useless!
[roars]
[DANTE chuckles]
I'm impressed that you can still
fight that hard.
But I suppose I'll end this now.
[roars]
[DANTE]
Not giving up?
How foolish.
Anything you do is futile.
[ASTA growls]
[ASTA roars]
[DANTE] He predicted
where I'd show up next.
Interesting...
[ASTA growls]
It seems you've
left a small scratch.
You'll regret that.
[GREY]
Please don't die, Gauche!
You're my... my...
[ASTA]
Your what?
[GREY]
Ah, nothing at all!
Black Clover , Page 163:
"Dante VS The Captain
of the Black Bulls."
[ASTA]
C'mon, tell me!
[GREY]
I'm so embarrassed!