[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[ASTA] Check that out!
It's a floating castle!
This is it.
We're at the Eye of the
Midnight Sun's hideout.
[NARRATOR] The Royal Knights,
an elite team of fighters
chosen to defeat the
Eye of the Midnight Sun,
were finally putting
their plan into action.
[ASTA] Yeah, that's Licht.
No doubt about it.
So we'll divide into
five teams of four
and make our move.
Team One will charge in
from the upper left!
[BOTH]
Yes, ma'am!
[MEREOLEONA]
Team Two, take the lower left!
[GROUP]
Yes, ma'am!
[MEREOLEONA] Team Three,
cover the upper right!
[ALL]
Yes, ma'am!
[MEREOLEONA]
Team Four, take the lower right!
[ALL]
Yes, ma'am!
And we three members
of Team Five
will attack them head on.
Ma'am!
All that matters is whether
you're strong or weak.
And the two of you are here
because you're strong,
isn't that correct?
[MEREOLEONA]
Two fools, chosen by Yami.
I hope for your sakes
you do not disappoint me.
Yes, ma'am!
Yeah, we'll do our best
to come back in one piece.
Is that good enough for ya?
A team like you shouldn't need
a fully detailed battle plan.
Eliminate any who dare
to get in your way
as you head toward the center.
And of course, the
method is up to you!
[NARRATOR] Once they arrived
in the strong magic region
known as Gravito Stones,
the heroes invaded
the floating dungeon that
served as the enemy's hideout
and headed for the center.
Their ultimate goal
was to eliminate Licht,
the terrorist organization's
elusive leader.
Whoa! Crazy!
I feel like she doesn't
even need our help!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
at the Black Bulls' hideout,
the mood was more relaxed.
[YAMI]
Ugh...
[SHEEP bleat]
[YAMI]
Well, I guess I'm headin' out.
What's going on, Captain?
I just got this
letter from Goldiguts
askin' to speak with me.
Sounds like he wants to
apologize for the Langris thing.
So, I'm off to their
HQ. Although...
I'm not sure why I'm the one
that has to go where he is.
Seems like the apologizer
should have to make the trip.
Does this mean I can
go and visit Marie
while you're away?
I can't believe you
just asked me that.
You stay put in case
a mission comes in.
Ugh.
I wanted to go
check on Finral,
so I'll be out for a bit, too.
How long can that
boy stay asleep?
Maybe if he senses I'm
there, he'll wake up.
[MAGNA] And I've got
some training to do!
I'm gonna get crazy strong,
you wait and see!
Good luck, Magna!
I know you didn't get
into the Royal Knights,
but try not to let
it get you down,
you little troublemaker!
I know there's an insult
in there somewhere.
I just can't tell where!
[CHARMY] I'm going out to
hunt for delicious goodies!
I'll dig up a
smorgasbord! See ya!
Um. Come back soon,
okay, you guys?
[mumbling]
I get so lonely without
all of your smiling faces here.
All right, I'll be
back in a while.
Do me a favor and
don't let the place
get overrun by robbers
while I'm gone.
Oh, boy. This is
gonna be a drag.
Well, when you see
that old quack,
ask him how Finral's holdin' up.
You got it, Captain Yami!
Here goes! Trainin' time!
[CHARMY] Hope you're ready,
my scrumptious little sweets!
The moment I've been growing
you for is finally here!
Charmy and the Sheep Cooks
are on the way to harvest
every last one of
you for snacking!
[mumbling] What a nice
intimate gathering
with two of my best friends.
[GAUCHE]
What's with this?
Grey and Gordon are both
sitting here staring me
right in the face,
but they're not saying
or doing anything at all!
Maybe it's because all the
usual loudmouths are gone,
but the silence
is kinda deafening!
[whimpering]
[mumbling] It'll be great for
the three of us to spend some
quality time together.
A lively conversation
such as this
can really lift the spirits!
[GAUCHE]
Hey!
I'm sorry!
[mumbling] I know,
let's take turns
revealing our darkest secrets.
Though, I already know yours.
If a mission request
comes our way,
I'll handle it myself.
You two feel free to go to
your rooms and get some rest.
[yelps] Oh, no, please don't
trouble yourself on my account.
I would rather die!
[mumbling] Obviously, if a
mission request did come in,
I would be more than
happy to accompany you
as your best friend.
[GAUCHE] I can't understand
a word they're saying!
Just take some time to relax.
Besides, I need all the work
I can get so I'll have
extra money to pay tribute
to my darling sister!
[whimpering]
[mumbling] If that's what
you prefer. Then fine.
[GREY] I'm too shy to go
without Transformation Magic
and let people see
my true self anyway!
[mumbling] I was looking
forward to a chance
to deepen friendships
with everyone
at the Underwater Temple.
[GREY] Then again,
all the other Black Bulls
do think of me as a friend.
And if that's the case,
then I should at least
be myself in front
of them, right?
[mumbling] I was hoping
to strengthen our bonds
during the Star
Festival as well.
[GREY]
Besides.
Gauche even complimented
this version of me!
[mumbling] I'll use this time
to the fullest and build
a deeper relationship with them,
deeper than the deepest sea!
[GAUCHE]
All right, that's enough.
I'm going to my room
so I can concentrate
on making a doll
of my sweet goddess.
Let me know if anything happens.
--[GREY whimpers]
--[mumbling] But wait...
It's bad enough to be
in a group of three,
but if you leave us alone,
it'll be a one-on-one,
and everyone knows
that's the most
uncomfortable thing of all!
I mean, Gordon's
pretty quiet, too,
but it doesn't even
really matter who it is.
If I have to be alone
with another person,
I'm gonna melt into a
puddle of humiliation!
[GAUCHE] What is the
matter with these two?
[GREY]
Muster up your courage!
Try to make some
casual conversation!
Hey, G-Gauche, that's
an interesting project
you're working on there.
What exactly is it?
Oh, this?
Uh, yeah!
I'm glad you asked.
You see, when I was a nerd,
my eyes were opened to
the wonder of figurines.
So I'm making one depicting
Marie in one-eighth scale!
[GREY]
Wow. That's, uh...
[GAUCHE] I'll let you worship
her once I finish it.
Um. Should I be grateful? Sorry.
[mumbling] As I suspected,
my dear friend Gauche
does have an interest in dolls.
It appears the time
has finally come
to show you my own collection.
Oh no, please don't.
I'd rather not see that!
Peek.
[screams]
[GORDON mumbling]
These are my homemade
Black Bulls replica dolls.
Dead ringers, aren't they?
[GREY] Does this mean
his cloak's been full
of voodoo dolls
this entire time?
[mumbling] Aw,
so cute, so cute...
[GREY]
Ew, I don't like this at all!
Do you have any clue
how scary you are?
I know I've got no room to talk,
but if building friendships
is that important to you,
that means you have
to be more approachable!
And you can start
with your face!
[mumbling] What? My face?
[GAUCHE]
Try smiling for once.
[mumbling] If you say so.
[GAUCHE]
Go on.
[GREY]
Uh-oh.
--[GAUCHE] That's even worse!
--[GREY screams]
[mumbling] So painful.
You've broken my heart, Gauche.
There's no need
to be that harsh.
Well, anyway. Nature's calling.
[GAUCHE]
Don't touch her.
[GREY]
I got it!
Oh, wait. Where is it?
[mumbling] It's on the
second floor today,
down the hall to the right.
Gotcha.
I still don't understand why
this building has to change
its layout all the time--
it's really annoying
to keep track of.
[GORDON mumbles] Not sure.
It's been that way as long
as I've been here, so.
[GAUCHE]
Ugh, what a headache.
I'm sure it's some
kind of spell,
but what's the point
of having it?
Please come back as quickly
as you can, okay, Gauche?
Like I said before,
I'm extremely
uncomfortable with this!
What were Charmy and Vanessa
gossiping about earlier?
I saw something creepy!
It was hard to make out,
but it was definitely fluffy!
And it wasn't a
Sheep Cook either,
it was way more spooky
and mysterious than that!
I swear, it's not
the alcohol talking.
I'm telling the truth.
I saw a ghost.
A real-life ghost!
Hic! I'm serious.
[GAUCHE]
What if it's not a spell
and our hideout
really is haunted?
Come on.
You know it's not
funny to joke around
about things like that--
[screams]
[GREY screams]
Monsters!
[GAUCHE]
What the--? We're surrounded!
Oh, no, this is terrible.
Please try not to look at me,
it's too humiliating!
We have bigger problems here!
Hurry and transform already!
[mumbling] I can't believe so
many of you gathered together
so we could become friends.
No, you idiot!
I don't know what's
going on, but these people
are the opposite of our friends!
Get ready for battle!
[GAUCHE] What do you
think you're doing?
[SALLY]
So this place is Asta's hideout.
But I guess Asta
isn't around today, huh?
That's too bad.
I was looking forward
to dissecting him alive.
Sally.
For the last time,
he isn't your plaything,
because he belongs to me.
I was excited to have some
fun with him today, too.
Sally. Rades. Look.
You'd do well to remember
our current objective.
Huh. I guess if this is the
Black Bulls' secret hideout,
I'll probably find plenty of
toys just begging to be mine.
I can't wait for it.
Yay, experiments!
I want to cut them open!
Rearrange their innards!
Watch them bleed out!
[ZOMBIES groan]
Lookie!
[GAUCHE]
All right, intruders, listen up.
I don't know whose
stupid decision it was
to break in here like this.
[GREY growls]
[mumbles] Foolish.
But you will pay!
[RADES]
Ah, here they are.
Those rotten Magic Knights.
You guys again?
[mumbling] Does that mean
you know them, Gauche?
[GAUCHE]
Of course I know them.
They're all terrorists from
the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
[mumbles] Those villains!
[GREY growls]
[GAUCHE]
So, what do you want?
Did you come here to get
another beating from us?
I noticed you're controlling
a bunch of wraiths,
so I'm guessing you're
the one they call Rades.
[cackles] This guy gets it.
We're on the hunt for something.
Is that right?
In this rundown old
mess of a hideout?
[RADES] Ha! You may
not know about it,
but it's definitely here.
And it's something good, too.
[mumbling] Is it friendship?
'Cause we have lots of that.
Would you shut up?
You idiots!
Don't worry, we'll find it,
and we might as well
tear this place to pieces
while we're at it!
[cackles]
[GAUCHE]
Not if I kill you first.
Now, Mirror Magic: Reflect Ray!
Gel Magic! Go,
Sticky Salamander!
There it goes!
[GAUCHE]
I forgot.
My kind of magic is
useless against hers.
Tch!
There's no need to get upset!
Gauche is your name, isn't it?
You're not my target.
In fact, I was specifically
instructed to leave you alive,
so you've got nothing
to worry about!
Huh? What do you mean?
[SALLY]
To be honest, I'm not too sure.
You'd have to ask Master Licht.
[GAUCHE]
Their leader really said that?
Come to think of it...
I'm sorry. I should
never have hurt you.
Me? What're you talking about?
[YAMI] Oh, didn't know
you guys were friends
or I wouldn'ta beat him up.
Of course I'm not friends
with this monster.
One day you'll understand.
[GAUCHE]
Why did he say that?
[RADES]
Come on, let's play!
--[GAUCHE gasps]
--This might hurt a bit.
So say your prayers,
you Black Bull boneheads!
[GAUCHE]
No time to ask questions.
We've gotta do something
about these guys!
The captain and
the others probably
won't be getting
back for a while.
Which means it's up
to the three of us!
[GREY growls]
[SALLY]
Here! Dark Magic Item...
Properties Boost: Reinforce!
Ta-dah! You're all
set! Let's go!
[growls]
Go!
[mumbling] The Eye
of the Midnight Sun.
You're an awful organization
that's hurt so many.
I'm not going to let
you set one foot
inside of the
Black Bulls' hideout!
[GORDON] Poison Curse Magic:
Aufwachen Dachs!
[ZOMBIE 89D groans]
[mumbling] Since
they're all corpses.
I believe my ability will be
especially effective
against them.
Good work!
Oh, neat!
That's some nasty poison
you've got there!
Doesn't matter, though.
Because my gel can
neutralize it easily!
Um, I should've told you, but...
What?
[GREY] I actually learned a new
spell that might be helpful!
Er, Transformation Magic:
Magic Conversion!
Changing Gel Magic
into Crystal Magic?
That's a surprise.
Uh. There you go.
Your turn, Gauche!
I see! Now I should
be able to break it!
With Mirror Magic:
Reflect Refrain!
Nice job!
That was great!
Your technique can change
the very essence of a spell.
You've really
piqued my interest!
I bet I could learn a lot by
doing some experiments on you!
[GREY yelps] D-D-D-Don't
look at me, it was nothing!
[RADES cackles]
That'll just make it even more
satisfying to crush you! Valtos!
Right.
[RADES]
This guy's next. Number Zero:
Mikael Caesar!
What the hell?
What's this creepy thing?
You'll see.
[MIKAEL CAESAR growls]
[GAUCHE] He can use two spells
with different attributes
at the same time?
And with such an incredible
amount of force!
Putting this big fella together
really took a lot out of me!
Yeah, but you never
would have pulled it off
without the help of my
Dark Magic Items, remember?
Some thanks would be nice.
He's made out of two
different corpses.
And that's not even
the best part of it!
Both of them were
Magic Knight Captains!
--[GAUCHE gasps]
--[GREY gasps]
[MIKAEL CAESAR growls]
[GREY yelps]
[RADES] Those cute little
spells of yours may be
clever parlor tricks,
but they'll never be enough
to defeat the perfect
wraith I've created!
[GAUCHE grunts]
[RADES cackles] This pathetic
Magic Knight hideout is only
getting in our way. Go ahead
and decimate it for me!
Attack.
[GORDON]
Stop it now.
[GORDON] My family was
in the business of hexes.
Never given the opportunity
to make friends.
I grew into a poor communicator
with revolting Poison Magic.
Everyone I met despised
and shunned me.
[GREY]
Don't do this.
[GREY] At first, I lacked
the confidence to let others
see my true self,
so no one trusted me.
Everybody was so quick to assume
I was weird and creepy!
I was always by myself.
[GORDON]
But then, this place...
[GREY]
But then, these people...
[YAMI laughs]
You know what, I like you!
Come and join my squad!
[MAGNA laughs]
She's a bull, how cool is that?
[GREY]
You think it's cool?
[GORDON mumbling]
I'm glad you're all having fun.
My heart is filled with joy.
[CHARMY]
You should eat a good meal!
You'll need energy
to fight on our team!
[VANESSA] Maybe then
you'll start speaking up
a little more, too, eh?
[GORDON mumbling]
This is delicious.
Food that's made
with love satisfies
both the stomach and the soul.
[CHARMY]
Here, Grey! Happy birthday!
[VANESSA]
Go on, girl, have a drink!
[GREY] Oh, my goodness.
I don't know what to say!
Thank you so much!
[MAGNA chuckles]
He's out like a light!
[GAUCHE] That one's Asta,
and that one's Grey.
Or wait, maybe vice-versa.
Either way, those
muscles are hideous.
[GORDON]
My friends...
[GREY]
This place...
[GORDON, GREY] I finally
have somewhere I belong!
Ah! We're outnumbered and
their power's off the charts!
Damn! How are we gonna win this?
[GORDON]
Don't give up yet, Gauche.
[gasps]
[BOTH] No matter what,
we'll protect our hideout!
I see. You've been
quiet since I met you,
but now you're finally
raising your voices!
Turns out, it's not
just my sister.
I have all of
these people, too,
and I wanna make
sure they stay safe!
Besides, we've got Captain
Yami to worry about.
If he comes back and
we've let this place
go to the dogs,
there's no telling
what kind of
punishment we'll get.
Oh, wow. You're still
able to stand up.
Well, I think I'm about ready
to start dissecting you three!
Fancy speeches and good
intentions won't help you.
The truth is, you don't stand a
chance of surviving this battle.
Here comes the finishing blow!
Just don't kill them, okay?
I want them alive
when I dissect them.
I'm not making any promises.
It's time to shine,
Mikael Caesar!
[MIKAEL CAESAR growls]
[alarm rings]
[SALLY, RADES]
Uh?
[VOICE 89A]
Emergency. Emergency.
[GAUCHE]
That's odd.
It's shaking!
[mumbling] Wait, what's
happening to the hideout?
[VOICE 89A]
Emergency. Emergency.
[GREY, GAUCHE, GORDON gasp]
What is all this?
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[GREY whimpers]
C-C--
[GREY, GORDON] "Comedy with
Gordon and Grey"!
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[mumbling] Hello
there, everyone.
My name's Gordon
and this is Grey.
Oh, no! Don't look!
Don't listen, either!
Just cover your ears
till we're done, okay?
[mumbling] That's going
to put a damper
on our comedy routine, you know.
Maybe so, but at least
people can understand me.
You're always muttering under
your breath like a creeper!
[mumbling] Well, I guess I
can't argue with that, can I?
[BOTH] We've reached the
end of our comedy routine,
so we hope you all
had a good chuckle!
I don't know what that was,
but you guys owe
comedy an apology!
[GAUCHE]
What's going on around here?
Whoever you are,
you'd better start talking.
No, faster than that!
Black Clover , Page 90:
"Crazy Magic Battle."
Don't worry, Marie,
my goddess of a sister.
I'll take care of this quickly
so I can visit you soon!