[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] Soon after arriving
at the Underwater Temple
in search of the magic
stone, the Black Bulls
were roped into High
Priest Gifso's "game":
a high-stakes temple
battle royale.
[GIFSO laughs] All my Temple
Mages are more powerful
than intermediate-class
Magic Knights,
and they're out there
fighting a bunch of juniors?
They're losing?!
That's impossible!
Heh! It's gonna take more
than a few drops of water
to scare me off.
[NARRATOR] Magna and Luck
faced the same opponent,
vying for the chance
to defeat him.
[LUCK laughs]
First come, first served, sorry!
Lightning Magic:
Thunderbolt Destruction!
[GIO] Well, well. Aren't you
a spunky little fella.
I'll have you know,
my son is the most
powerful mage in the
Underwater Temple!
[LUCK]
He's got so much power.
Like a tidal wave. This guy
is the strongest one here.
[GIO]
I'll take you both on at once.
I'm not interested in
tormenting you any further.
Water Creation Magic:
Poseidon's Hammer!
You're not gonna
be ending anything!
Yeah, I'm nowhere near
done playing with you!
[MAGNA, LUCK yell]
[GIO groans]
[NARRATOR]
The game was interrupted
by the arrival of Vetto,
a top member
of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
[VETTO]
Well, it looks like you folks
are having quite a get-together.
How about... you guys
let me in the mix?
[MIMOSA] Oh, wow! The full
moon looks so gorgeous!
[MIMOSA]
Wherever Asta is,
I wonder if he's looking up
at the same moon right now?
[MIMOSA giggles]
Silly Mimosa!
[BEACH MAGES yelling]
Ha... ha...
I guess I must have
nodded off for a bit.
[groans]
[yells]
Ha, ha?!
[BEACH MAGES groaning, yelping]
[gasps]
Ha. Barely enough
for a decent warm-up.
That was like fighting
a bunch of puny mice.
[BEACH MAGE 44J groans]
Time to go.
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES]
Sir!
[SEKKE whimpers] They may not
have been expecting an attack,
but that's still a lot
of top-ranked mages.
It shouldn't have been
possible for one guy
to take them all out
in a matter of minutes!
These are the people we trust
to protect the kingdom.
How could this happen?
One thing's sure.
That was no human.
That thing was...
...a beast!
What's this guy
think he's doin',
crashin' our battle?
And why's he so hairy?
[LUCK]
Yeah, no fair.
Sharkhead totally
belonged to me.
[LUCK]
Maybe it's okay, though.
This guy's got more magic
power than Captain Yami.
[GIO] You made it through
the ocean currents,
and forced your way into
the Underwater Temple.
Your magic must be
formidable indeed.
Oh. I see you can still move.
Well, that hurt.
You and your buddies there sure
don't look like Magic Knights.
I know why they're here,
but what do you people
want with the Underwater Temple?
The same thing that they do.
We're here for the
magic stone, too.
Are you? Well, that's too bad.
We can't simply hand
it over, you know.
I'm sure.
I wouldn't want it to be
that effortless, anyway.
I'd much rather plunge
you all into to despair,
destroy this place,
and take the stone myself!
You what?
The rest of you, go!
Spread out through the temple.
[MIDNIGHT SUN MAGES]
Sir!
It's rude to drop in
uninvited like this.
I'm afraid I'll have to ask
you to leave, please.
[VETTO]
Silence, peon.
You really do need
to work on your manners.
It will take far
more powerful magic
than you possess to
make me leave this place
without that stone.
Oh, dear.
You clearly don't understand
who you're dealing with.
Of all the Underwater
Temple's mages,
I am the strongest by far.
Enough chitchat.
We can let our magic
do the talking.
Very well. Mine has
plenty to say.
Water Creation Magic:
Now, Poseidon's Hammer!
--[MAGNA] Nice!
--[LUCK] Whoa!
[GIO gasps]
That little hammer spell is no
match for my Rhinoceros Armor.
[GIO]
There's not a scratch on him!
[VETTO laughs]
Still, not a bad try
for a temple mouse.
You've earned a prize.
A prize?
That's right! A swift death!
In nature, the mighty
beasts get to devour
their prey as a reward
for their strength,
while the pathetic
vermin like you
only get destruction
and despair.
My Beast Magic: Bear Claw!
[GIO grunts]
--[MAGNA] Wha--
--[LUCK] Uh--
[grunts]
[MAGNA grunts]
[LUCK yelps]
Do you understand the situation?
You see the overwhelming
difference in our power?
You are insects.
I shall not allow you to
retain even a shred of hope.
[OCEAN DWELLERS
yelling, gasping]
[GIFSO] No. That shouldn't
have been possible.
Gio. He's the
strongest that we have.
He was beaten so easily.
I've never seen such power,
and I've seen much in my time.
Listen, old man,
playtime's over now.
Get me out there to my
people and do it fast.
This must be serious
if you're rattled.
Who is he? He looks more
like a beast than a man.
He's a high-rankin'
member of the group
I told ya about,
the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Eye of the Midnight Sun?
There's no time to explain.
Just get me outta
here, all right?
I'm sorry, Captain.
I'm afraid that
won't be possible.
We are stuck in here.
We can't leave until
the game is finished,
and I can't break
the spell, either.
That's the way it is.
We'll just have to wait and see.
Is that so?
[GIFSO]
What are you--?
Guess I'll just have
to let myself out.
[GIFSO]
Huh?
[YAMI]
Dark Magic: Lightless Slash!
Huh?
Hey! What happened to my temple?
Damn.
[YAMI]
What is this?
[ABARI] Spatial Magic:
Different Dimension Sphere.
Ha! Once somebody
has been ensnared
by my Spatial Magic,
they have no hope of escaping
unless I decide to release
them from its hold.
[VETTO] Dark swordsman
from a foreign land.
Yes, that's right, I can tell
you're here by the mana.
Watch from the sidelines
a little longer.
You're going to be my main dish.
You'll be steeped
in delicious despair
from having seen the deaths
of all your friends.
We must do something
to stop this beast.
Or else the temple is done for.
[YAMI]
All right, geezer.
[GIFSO]
What is it?
We can't get in there,
but can we still talk to 'em?
[GIFSO]
Well, yes. We can.
But how will that help them?
[YAMI]
Uh, testing one two. Test, test.
Oh, my gosh!
That's Captain Yami!
[YAMI]
All right, ya morons. Listen up!
[VANESSA] Hey, Captain!
I actually beat one of them!
[YAMI] A nasty character's
just crashed the party.
He's one of the Midnight Sun's
high-ranked members.
Real wild-lookin' SOB
who's as strong as
a Magic Knight captain.
[VETTO laughs]
[ASTA]
He's here?
[YAMI] Plus, he's got
four minions with him.
I'm gonna need another
helping, please...
[YAMI] But some things have
come up, so I can't get to 'em.
[FINRAL]
Huh?! What "things" exactly?
[YAMI] You block heads
are gonna hafta handle it.
You've gotta be kidding me!
[YAMI] Now, look.
It's time to get serious.
Push past your limits.
[YAMI] Die and I'll
kill ya. Over and out.
Great. We're basically doomed.
When I proposed
this game of mine,
I had no idea it would turn
out to be so exhilarating.
And now here we are,
with the fate
of the Underwater Temple
hanging in the balance.
Time for a rule change!
Knights and Mages.
In order to win the game,
you must defeat
Team Eye of the Midnight Sun!
All those who contribute
to this victory
will have their wishes granted,
insofar as my authority
as the high priest
of this temple allows!
[ASTA]
We have to fight that monster!
Yeah, he's scary. So what?
That's exactly what makes
a battle worth fighting.
I can do this.
I can take him down.
[KIATO]
Asta!
I guess this means that
our fight is on hold.
Guess so.
[ASTA]
All right! Let's go!
[KIATO]
Yeah!
[VETTO]
Too easy.
Now, who's going
to be my next prey?
[MAGNA, LUCK]
Where ya goin'?
[MAGNA]
Think you can move on
to the next fight
just like that?
[LUCK] Get back here.
We're not dead yet.
Captain Yami gave us
our marching orders.
And if our captain says
to take you down,
that's what we're gonna do.
[LUCK]
You got that?
--[LUCK] We're not done!
--[MAGNA] We're not done yet!
[BOTH]
We won't be broken!
Excellent.
I shall enjoy bringing you
despair that much more.
The longer the hunt continues,
the greater the anticipation
of the kill becomes.
[VETTO laughs]
[MAGNA]
I'm glad we're still goin'.
But how are we gonna fight
a monster like that?
If he lands one more square
hit on us, we're toast.
Hey, big guy.
Throw that last attack spell
at us again, will ya?
Huh?!
[LUCK]
Yeah! The super-fast one!
[MAGNA] Has all that lightning
finally fried his brain?
We barely survived that
one the first time!
How're we supposed to live
through a second round?
Well, well. We've
got a feisty one.
Delicious. Then I'll continue
feeding you despair...
...until you choke!
[LUCK laughs]
You leave yourself open
for just a second.
I thought I saw that before.
And you're fast enough
to take advantage of it.
You have keen perception
and incredible speed,
I'll grant you that.
Aw, man, my
Thunderbolt Destruction
didn't have any
effect on him at all!
I can play with you
a while longer.
[LUCK laughing]
[VETTO]
He's all over the place!
[LUCK growls]
[VETTO yells]
[LUCK yells]
[VETTO growls]
[MAGNA] That crazy
battle freak. Damn him.
[LUCK]
It's Magna, right?
You've got some
weird-looking hair.
What?
I'm Luck. Nice to meet you.
[MAGNA]
Oh, this guy?
I think he's that smiling maniac
they call Luck the
Cheery Berserker.
Looks like I'm gonna have
to show him what's what.
Yeah. Nice to meet ya,
too, ya jerk.
[MAGNA yells]
Oh, hey. That's a funny face.
[laughs]
[MAGNA] You've been messin'
around and annoying
the crap outta me ever
since the very first day
you joined the squad.
Everyone knows you've got more
than your share
of personality issues.
[laughs]
Hot, hot, hot...
--[LUCK] Ha!
--[MAGNA yelps]
[screams]
[MAGNA]
And half the time on missions,
you're more trouble
than you're worth.
--Ha!
--[MAGNA] Huh?
[yelps, screams]
--[MAGNA yelling]
--[LUCK] Ha!
[FOREST THUGS yelping]
[laughs] That's the
Crackling Magna Typhoon!
[FOREST THUGS yelping]
[MAGNA]
Still, your battle sense...
Gotta give it to you there.
[MAGNA] And ever since
that dungeon mission,
you've only been
gettin' stronger.
You're reckless,
immature, and insane.
I hate to admit it, but damn it,
you're my best friend.
That's it.
You better not even think about
leavin' me behind, ya jerk!
Flame Creation Magic:
Grand Slam!
Yeah! Right outta the park!
[MAGNA grunts]
[yells]
Hey, nice one, Magna!
Here, lemme help!
[LUCK] When we first met,
I didn't take you seriously.
A commoner, huh? Boring.
But something
told me that behind
the weird-looking hair,
there was somebody
truly dangerous.
And entertaining.
[LUCK] I kept messing with you
so I could meet that Magna.
Hey, thanks for the
flan. It was tasty!
Good, because that's the
last thing you'll ever eat!
[LUCK laughs]
[LUCK]
You always come right back at me
with everything you've got.
You never hold anything back.
And now, after all this time,
I finally realized...
You were the first
friend I ever made.
Hey, Magna! You can do
better than that, can't ya?
Shut up!
[VETTO yells]
That wasn't a bad catch,
fireball freak.
What? Who're you
callin' a freak?
Now get offa me, Lightnin' Boy.
If you two are done playing,
can we finish this?
That's it--let's kick
this guy's ass
Sure, sounds good to me.
We're ready whenever you are!
[VETTO chuckles]
[ASTA]
This way!
How do you know where to go
when you can't sense mana?
I can't sense mana,
but I can sense ki.
Ki? Anyway, you're right.
I sense magic power up ahead.
And there's a tremendous
amount of it, too.
I've never felt anything
like this before.
I agree with you that this
is a battle worth fighting.
Hey. I was trying to
read your ki earlier.
It was almost impossible
to pin you down.
How do you do that?
Oh, well my dancing
actually puts me
into a kind of trance,
which is a really big help
when it comes to fighting.
How does it work?
My body just sorta moves,
without any conscious
thought on my part.
That makes it hard
for my opponent
to predict what I'll do.
Okay, I get it.
That's really cool!
A trance...
What'cha doin'?
[ASTA]
Putting myself in a trance.
[laughs]
Whoa! I can see the magic
up ahead clearly now.
Flame mixed with Lightning,
and they're doing battle.
Flame and Lightning, huh?
That means Magna
and Luck are up there.
And as for the massive
power they're fighting...
What is this?
It's like hundreds
of wild animals
snarling and running crazy!
That's Vetto's magic!
Wait, how the heck can
you pick up on all that?
Our kind are
particularly skilled
at reading magic and the
different forms it can take.
But if that's what we're up
against, then I'm worried.
It's fine!
Those two may be a little
bit on the crazy side,
but you can always count on them
when things start to get tough.
We'll get outta this alive!
[groans]
[MAGNA groans]
[LUCK]
That hurt.
Now are you beginning
to understand?
Weak animals will be devoured.
Their lot in life is to despair.
[MAGNA]
Would you shut up?
The last thing I'm feelin'
right now is despair.
[LUCK]
That's right.
We can't give up. No way.
[BOTH]
If we quit that easily,
then we wouldn't deserve
to be his superiors anymore.
[MAGNA, LUCK grunt]
[growls]
[LUCK]
Not yet.
[LUCK yells]
[MAGNA]
Not yet.
[LUCK]
He's right. Fighting normally,
we wouldn't stand a
chance against this guy.
[MAGNA]
Not yet.
[VETTO laughs]
[MAGNA, LUCK]
Not yet. Not yet.
[yells]
[gasps]
[LUCK]
There it is!
That opening, a split
second after his attack.
[MAGNA, LUCK]
Now! We won't give up!
We're gonna fight with
everything we've got!
[VETTO] A simultaneous attack
at point-blank range,
aimed right for my weak point!
[MAGNA, LUCK yell]
[GIFSO gasps]
All right. You've got this.
So much mana!
[gasps]
This power's incredible.
[MAGNA, LUCK] Combo Spell: Flame
Lightning Exploding Cannon!
[MAGNA, LUCK yell]
Magna, Luck, we're coming!
Are you okay?
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[MAGNA, LUCK]
"Crackling Magna Typhoon"!
Hey, everyone! How's it going?
Where's your excitement, people?
Kick it up a notch
--or two already!
--[LUCK] Okay.
Today we're going to teach
you a fun and easy way
to pull off a
Crackling Magna Typhoon
in the comfort of your own home.
First, get a length of
lightning rope ready, like so.
Are you kidding?!
Then, you wrap it around
your very own Magna.
Quit zapping me!
Right. Now you try whipping
up a rope, Magna.
I can't do that!
You're doing great.
We're almost done!
Once the rope's nice and tight,
give him a push
to get him spinning.
Here we go!
There ya have it, folks!
A Crackling Magna Typhoon,
so easy anyone can do it!
No, you idiot!
You're the only one
who can do it!
I hate you!
Bye for now!
[ASTA] No matter how
tough the enemy may be,
I'm not giving up. Not ever!
I'm a Black Bull. We all are!
Black Clover , Page 45:
"The Guy Who Doesn't
Know When to Quit"!
That's right--my magic
is never giving up!