[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR]
In order to restore Asta's arms,
which were rendered useless
after the battle with Vetto,
Noelle and Finral went to visit
a certain group of exiles.
We'd like to talk!
Sure.
I was just getting
out of the bath, so--
[NOELLE screams]
Enough with the naked thing!
You're a grown man.
Keep your clothes on!
[NARRATOR] A former
Diamond Kingdom commander
named Fanzell Kruger.
His fiancée, Dominante Code,
magic items artisan.
And Mariella, who was
once an assassin.
Do you have any ideas?
We have to find a way
to heal Asta's arms.
Anything will be helpful.
So, Ancient Hex Magic, huh?
Well, there is one place.
[NOELLE, FINRAL gasp]
My homeland, the
Forest of Witches.
You think they'd help?
[DOMINANTE] The Queen of
the Witches' magic would.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
in the Forest of Witches...
Hey!
The smartest witch ever
to grace the Land of Witches
has come back to say hello.
I have business here,
so open up!
[NOELLE]
Domina.
What's the Forest
of Witches like?
Well, it's sort of
an independent area.
It lies east of
the Clover Kingdom,
close to the border
of the Diamond Kingdom.
Its inhabitants are all women
skilled in specialized spells
like Hex and Spirit magic.
In other words, witches.
Ooh! It's women only?
At last, I've found my utopia!
[DOMINANTE] I said they're
witches, remember?
Yeah, so?
I've heard tell
men who get too close
have been turned to bugs
and drowned in toilets.
[BOTH gasp]
Hold on. If they're witches...
Oh, right!
When Vanessa disappeared
out of nowhere,
maybe she was going
to ask their queen
to fix Asta's arms.
The thing is,
there's a strict rule
that witches must live in
the forest and nowhere else.
Which means that
women like Vanessa
and myself who decided to leave
are looked upon as fugitives.
You're fugitives?
[DOMINANTE] So she would
need incredible resolve
to go back there.
As for me, I'd fallen
head-over-heels in love
with my darling, so I had
no choice in the matter!
That's true, honeybear.
Both of us dove head-first
into a bottomless swamp
of pure devotion!
Oh, Zell. I love you!
And I love you, Domina!
Good grief.
They're so in love. I'm jealous!
And after I gave up
everything for you,
I'm still living in this damn
hovel, you worthless deadbeat!
[FANZELL yelps]
[DOMINANTE, FANZELL grunting]
[MARIELLA] She always aims
for his vital points.
Maybe she should've
been the assassin.
Okay.
You know what, true
love's overrated anyway.
Now, what were
we talking about?
Right, we should get
back to business.
Yeah.
If Vanessa really did
go back to those woods,
I'm worried.
I don't know all of the details,
but the rumors say that Vanessa
was of special importance
to the Queen of the Witches.
One thing's for certain, though.
Once she goes in, it's
going to be impossible
for her to escape again.
The queen is more deadly
than you can imagine.
So much so that
the Diamond Kingdom
won't even try to
stand against her.
And there's no hope of
reasoning with her, either.
So if you're planning to
enter the Forest of Witches,
it's only right
of me to warn you.
Angering the Queen will
destroy any chance you had
of returning with your lives.
[NOELLE]
We're going.
[DOMINANTE gasps]
Whatever it takes for
us to heal Asta's arms.
She's right.
Domina, please tell
us where it is.
[sighs] I'm going with you.
[FINRAL]
Huh?
But you just said that--
[FANZELL]
Count me in, too.
I'm not lettin' anyone lay
a finger on my sweet fiancée.
Asta helped me out a lot
when we first met
and showed me what I needed
to do to move forward,
so I owe him big-time.
I don't like the idea of
growing our debt, either.
Let's repay it.
[gasps]
Yeah. And besides all that,
I could never live
with myself if I left
my last student out to dry.
[ASTA yells]
If I can't use my arms,
I'll just work on my lower body
till it's perfect!
I'm not gonna stop jumping!
I want super-buff
legs like this!
[yelps] I got a cramp!
[ASTA]
Huh?
Long time no see, Asta.
Whoa, it's Old Man Zell!
[yelps]
Hold on! Where the heck
are you taking me?
Let's go, we can
explain on the way.
[NOELLE]
If we tell him...
There's no way I could
let you guys go somewhere
that dangerous for me!
He'll probably have
a fit, so we'll just
keep it a mystery for now.
Okay, we're off to
the Forest of W!
Wait, what's the W mean?
Please tell me it's
for "wonderful"!
[ASTA muffled yelp]
[ASTA muffled yelling]
Problem solved.
[NOELLE]
Good job, Zell!
Very wise, Master.
When I need to silence someone,
all I can think of
to do is kill them.
Uh, maybe you'd
better work on that.
We should hurry up!
[ASTA muffled] Hey! I still
don't know where we're goin'!
[WITCH 57A laughs] The other
day, there was this creepy guy
outside the forest,
he was staring at me
and going "ha, ha"
over and over!
Wow, seriously?
That's totally gross!
Oh, and by the way,
I'm pretty sure
I saw Vanessa around
here not long ago.
[WITCH 57B]
What? You're kidding!
If the queen finds out she's
here after what she did...
I don't even wanna think about
what's going to happen to her.
Imperfect.
And I don't just
mean you, Vanessa.
It's also true that my plans
failed to reach perfection
after you so selfishly fled
from the Forest of Witches.
If you had mastered
your Thread Magic
the way I instructed you,
you could have gained control
over destiny itself.
But no, you let that man
tempt you away instead.
Simply appalling.
To abandon your own people
for an ordinary human male?
We are perfect witches
with unlimited potential,
and you let him use you.
You should be ashamed!
Oh, dear. What an
imperfect room.
You're the one who's imperfect.
Here's the deal.
I'll come back to the
Forest on one condition.
Teach me to dispel
ancient hexes,
or never see me again!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES] It appears
you don't know your place.
So I'll show you, now.
[DOMINANTE]
The Forest of Witches.
There's witches here?!
Wait, what? Could
somebody fill me in?
Will you try to
keep your voice down--
we have to be extremely careful!
[whispering] That's it,
now I'm worried!
Why is everybody all
quiet and serious?
Is this like a
secret spy mission?
I'll tell you later.
But we're about to bust in,
there's only so much
"later" it can get
before it's too late!
Look, Asta, if you
don't hurry up
and shut your mouth...
[ALL but ASTA]
...then we'll shut it for you.
[quiet yell]
Now, what were you
saying, Domina?
[DOMINANTE]
The queen's used her tremendous
magic power to cordon off
this entire Forest.
So if we cast even
a small spell,
she'll immediately know
that we're here.
Sounds like my Spatial
Magic won't do us
a whole lot of good, then.
[DOMINANTE] She'll find us
even if you don't use it.
As soon as anyone with magic
goes inside the Forest,
the queen'll be alerted.
If she spots us,
that means we'll be...
...full of holes.
I don't have any magic,
so I'm good, right?
Shush!
That all makes sense.
But how are we gonna get in?
[DOMINANTE giggles] Luckily.
I have just the invention!
I call this one the Vanishawl!
[NOELLE]
Uh...
Slap one of these
babies on and poof!
Your body, magic, and presence
will disappear in a flash!
That's marvelous!
I'm sure it's expensive, though.
Of course not!
You can take one home
for just 30,000 yuls!
Really? Wow! What a great price!
But wait, there's more.
Buy now and you'll get another
Vanishawl, absolutely free!
[STUDIO AUDIENCE applause]
♪ D-O-M-I-N-A, just for you! ♪
Ooh, ooh!
♪ I've got everything you want,
and at a bargain, too! ♪
Whoo!
[gasps]
Is this enough money?
And then some!
I'm kidding, dear. I'll let
you use them for free.
You say that now,
but everyone saw you
think about taking her money.
I'm sure she was
just a bit startled
by how much it was.
Anyway, look, I think I see
another way in over there--
we should try it!
Cute Girl Paradise,
here we come!
I still don't know what's up!
Be quiet, Asta!
[ASTA]
Ugh!
[FANA]
Humans are so despicable.
They do nothing but hurt us.
And take things from us.
[CIDANE]
Mistress Fana.
The Black Bulls we're watching.
It appears they're up
to something strange.
I'll burn them to ashes.
I'm never going to forgive
them for killing Vetto
and for what they did to Licht.
They'll pay for it.
They'll all pay!
Last time I went to the
city, I got approached
out of nowhere by this creepy
guy who kept saying "ha, ha,"
and then he handed me
a bouquet of 100 roses!
[WITCH 57C]
That's so weird!
This is kind of crowded.
I could kill someone right now.
My apologies, you two,
the Vanishawls
were originally designed
to cover one person.
But, hey! Better than
getting shot at
till we look like
human honeycombs!
I guess we'll just
have to deal with it
till we make it to the queen.
At least we're faring
better than they are.
Sorry we gotta get all up
close and personal, guys.
Apparently she only made
two of these things.
Man, this place is
crawling with gorgeous
magical hotties and here I am
stuck in a dude sandwich!
Don't you think after all this,
I deserve to know what the heck
we're doin' here?
[WITCH 57E] Are sure you
can't sell this love potion
for a little cheaper?
Sorry. I can't.
There's love potions here?!
[WITCHES]
Hm?
[WITCH 57E] That almost
sounded like a man yelling.
You're imagining things.
There's no way a man could
get into this Forest.
[WITCH 57E]
I guess not.
Whew! That was close!
Sorry, I couldn't help myself.
I've only ever seen love potions
in my wildest of dreams.
Uh...
[GOLEM 57A]
Golly!
Hey, what's that thing?
It's weird, but
it's kind of cute.
[DOMINANTE]
That's a security golem.
They may look harmless,
but the second
they detect an intruder,
they start swarming
and firing off magical bullets.
Now I understand why you
said that about honeycombs.
Right.
If we let even one of those
things find out we're here,
they'll come fill us full
of holes till we drop dead.
[MARIELLA] A harmless-looking
façade, and a merciless attack.
They're the ideal assassins.
[NOELLE gasps]
Here it comes!
[DOMINANTE]
Don't worry.
If we're under the Vanishawl,
it can't see us.
[BOTH sigh]
[FANZELL, FINRAL, ASTA]
Okay. It's our turn now!
[laughs]
Whoopsie.
[ALL]
Are you kidding me?
Golly?
Beautiful day, isn't it?
What a nice place you got here!
Golly.
[ALL]
Huh?
[ALL scream]
[DOMINANTE]
You've done it now, Zell!
You are way too naked
to be this close to me!
Yeah, what are you
grabbing us for?
I promise it's not
on purpose. I'm sorry!
He's a degenerate.
That's just the kind of thing
that my Master's into.
Can't help yourself, can you?
No, that's not it! Don't
look at me like that.
Hey!
What's going on?
Huh? Intruders! Male intruders!
It looks like all we can do now
is try to blast our way through
to the queen's palace!
Leave it to me.
I can use my Spatial Magic
to make an instant shortcut!
[FINRAL]
Hi there!
Hey, this is no
time to socialize!
[shrieks]
It's a naked old man!
[FANZELL]
Uh...
[FINRAL]
Let's grab a coffee!
Cut it out, Finral!
[WITCH 57E yelps]
Creeper!
[sighs]
[FINRAL]
Hope to hear from you.
Take a hint, would ya?
[WITCH 57B yelps]
[WITCH 57G]
That's it, grandpa.
Time to go!
Worst part is, that
wasn't a shortcut.
No, the worst part is how
bad they shut me down.
I'm still in shock here.
I don't know what
the worst part is.
[ASTA]
Crap, we're surrounded!
[GOLEMS]
Golly.
They use Spew-Smoke.
I should've guessed it.
Spew-Smoke? What's that?
[DOMINANTE] A special item
that casts a smokescreen
with trace amounts of magic.
It'll clear out soon, though.
This is our chance
to head straight
to where the queen is!
[ASTA, FINRAL, FANZELL yelp]
[DOMINANTE]
Over there!
[ASTA]
Man, they should patch that!
[DOMINANTE]
This way, we can fly right in!
[ASTA. FINRAL,
FANZELL screaming]
I shoulda kept my shirt
on so I wouldn't
scrape up my back.
Couldn't resist your
urges. Shameful.
[FANZELL] It was an accident,
Mariella, I swear!
An accident!
[ASTA]
Ugh, that hurt--
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Imperfect.
She's got Vanessa!
[BOTH]
Vanessa!
[ASTA]
What do you think you're doing?
I don't care if you are
the queen or whatever,
get your foot off
our friend, right now!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
You dare barge into my home
and address me that way?
Perhaps you aren't
aware of this.
I am the all-powerful
queen of this forest,
and the mother of
every witch here.
Some of you recognize me.
Your friend there,
as well as little Vanessa,
are my descendants.
I have more daughters
than you could ever count.
And children need
to be disciplined.
What do you mean?
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
This is a private family matter.
You ought to mind
your own business.
I am free to treat my children
in any way I see fit.
I dunno what's going on,
but it seems like
you're the boss here.
And you may be their
mom or whatever.
But... you can't hurt her!
Imperfect.
[ASTA yelps]
Asta!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Hm. That's bizarre.
Do you not have any magic?
What a pitiful, imperfect
little brat you are.
[ASTA] You're right,
I don't have any powers.
And now, I guess I can't even
fight you with my swords.
But still!
Unlike you, I'd never
step on my own family!
You must be that upstart
Vanessa talked about.
I honestly don't understand
why she'd bother
trying to repair trash like you.
She sacrificed everything.
What a foolish girl I've raised.
She told me she would
become my slave
and live out the
rest of her days here.
All for restoring those
silly arms of yours.
She really did that?
We're here... for me?
When we first met,
you told me about
the dream you had.
You still have to become
the Wizard King, right?
Let us help.
Once you have people
who care about you,
none of your problems
or decisions you make
are solely your own anymore.
That is what you said,
isn't it, Noelle?
Of course.
You guys...
And on that note.
That's impressive.
I was hiding my
intent to strike.
However...
[ASTA yelps]
[ASTA]
Old man! You saved me!
Indeed.
All I needed to do
was create a diversion
while the old man
was rescuing Asta.
Yeah, yeah. The old
man did real good.
Now stop calling me that!
Here goes.
Wind Creation Magic:
Emperor of Slashing Winds.
Take your foot off of her!
She's one of us!
So leave her alone!
Pitiful fools.
What could such
imperfect creatures
possibly hope to do for her?
Vanessa, much like you all,
is powerless to
escape her destiny.
This divination paints
a lovely picture
of the end that awaits
you in mere moments.
[gasps]
I didn't expect it
to happen so soon.
I knew they'd be coming,
but now of all times?
Then again, of course they'd
choose a moment like this.
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
The Eye of the Midnight Sun.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[SEKKE]
"The Forest of G"!
Ha, ha!
You've gotta love the
Magic Shopping Network!
What a bargain!
This amazing Vanishawl
can make you
and your magic disappear!
It cost 5,000,000 yul, but I'll
have it paid off in 12 years!
Now I can enter that perfect
oasis of beautiful women
they call the Forest
of Witches! Ha, ha!
But this is always
the ha-hardest part.
I know it's around
here somewhere,
but I'm not sure
which way I need to go.
[GORDON mumbling]
Something wrong?
Ha, ha! Who's there?
[GORDON mumbling]
Let's be friends.
Ha, huh? Show yourself
now! You're scaring me!
[mumbling] I'm Gordon.
I'm Gordon, too.
What's good, yo. I'm Gordon!
We're all Gordons here.
What? But why?
[screams] It's the
Forest of Gordons!
[MARIELLA] The Eye of the
Midnight Sun just launched
an attack on the
Forest of Witches.
Oh, and it looks like
they're not the only ones.
Black Clover , Page 58:
"The Battlefield Decision."
And yes, my Master's magic
is taking his clothes off.