[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[JULIUS] I'm glad you were
all able to attend.
Without further ado,
I'd like to commence
with the Royal Knights
Selection Test.
[NARRATOR]
The exam to decide which Knights
would fight the Eye
of the Midnight Sun
had just gotten underway...
...when suddenly,
a mysterious man
appeared on the scene.
[ZORA] So sorry I'm late
for the party, everybody.
Who, me? I'm Xerx Lugner.
Pleasure's mine.
[NARRATOR] Despite Asta's
immediate distrust
of this "Xerx," the two of them
soon discovered
that they had been
placed on the same team
for the tournament.
[NARRATOR] And, so, in this
tense and menacing atmosphere,
the Royal Knights Selection
Test begins in earnest.
Magic Knights, it's time
to start the exam!
Now that the
explanations are done,
I hope our first
two teams are ready.
[yells]
I was born ready, Your Majesty!
[MAGNA]
Asta!
Give those guys a beatin'
they won't forget!
That's right, show them
what the Black Bulls
are all about!
Give it your best, okay?
Hurry up and take care of them
so you can spar with me later!
Don't be reckless!
[mumbling] I swear I won't
take my eyes off you
the entire battle.
I won't even blink.
Ah. What kind of
interesting spells
will I get to see today?
I can't wait to find out!
[CHARMY]
Here. Anything's more exciting
to watch with a snack.
Why thank you!
[ASTA yells]
I'm totally psyched now!
It's time to do this thing!
Quit shouting already.
This is an exam.
You need to stay calm and focus.
Look. The best tactic
is to study the terrain
and figure out what
each of us can offer.
[ASTA growls]
You're right! I hate it,
but you're so right!
[ZORA] Everything I say
is right, short stack,
so get used to it.
Settle down now, both of you.
[MIMOSA] Aw, Asta's cute even
when he's gritting his teeth!
I agree with Xerx, though.
Let's get familiar with
each other's abilities
and come up with a solid plan.
I'm sure that's what the other
team is doing right now.
Yeah! That's good thinking!
My Plant Magic is best suited
for support and recovery.
And Asta's anti-magic will
be useful at close range
to nullify the spells
our opponents cast.
What kind of magic
do you have, Xerx?
[ALL gasp]
What the--?
[MIMOSA]
They're already attacking?
So fast! And which direction
did it come from?
Either way, I've gotta
keep our crystal safe!
Oh, no!
That looked like a
long-distance strike.
But how was it so accurate?
I don't understand this!
Where's it coming from?
Looks like ten o'clock,
three meters.
Do you copy?
[FORTI]
Roger.
Thanks to a highly precise
Crystal Magic spell
called Crystal Scope,
their whereabouts
are as clear as well,
he, heh, you know.
I'll make you pay for ridiculing
the Wizard King, knave!
You don't deserve a chance
to shine after that stunt!
Flame Magic: Burst Javelin!
Combined with
Rock Magic: Strong Bow!
We're gonna lose!
Crap. What now?
If we work together we--
Seriously, what is the
matter with this guy?!
He's terrible!
He's... asleep?
Yup, he's out cold.
Sure looks like it.
Guess he needs a nap.
[mumbling] That's pathetic.
How could anybody fall asleep
with all of these
people watching them?
The shame! The embarrassment!
My, I never expected
a tournament like this
to devolve into naptime!
They must be worn out.
Unless... it's a trick.
What the heck are you layin'
on the ground for, huh?
If you don't get off
your lazy butt right now,
our team's crystal is gonna
be smashed to pieces!
Do you wanna win
this thing or not?
--[yawns]
--You're such a jerk!
Winning or losing doesn't
make a difference to me.
Nor do I care how
badly you wanna win.
So just direct all that
unchecked enthusiasm elsewhere.
Listen, I kinda pulled
an all-nighter last night.
I'd appreciate it if you two
would let me catch a few Zs.
[RICK] That Xerx fellow actually
has the nerve to sleep!
[FORTI] Do you think it's
some kind of strategy?
It's not.
My Crystal Scope can
identify not just location
but the physical state
of its targets.
There's no doubt--that
ruffian is fast asleep!
[FORTI]
How can one man be so arrogant,
especially after the way he
insulted the Wizard King
when he first arrived?
That's enough! He's dead!
Whatever his little plan may be,
if you don't move,
you can't win.
Let's put a stop to
this here and now!
Plant Creation Magic:
Magic Flower Guidepost!
[MIMOSA] Looks like two of them
are close to the crystal,
and the other one is 60 meters
in front up in a tree!
[MIMOSA gasps]
The pair's magic is inflated!
They must be casting
a combo spell!
From that far away?
Prepare for another attack!
Right!
[ASTA] The last couple
were pretty fast.
But if I can nail down
the direction and timing...
[ASTA]
Gotcha!
Aw, yeah!
[MIMOSA]
That blast was so quick,
I never could've
dodged it in time.
Asta really is amazing!
We don't stand
a chance of winning
without Xerx's help, though.
It's two against three!
Come on, our best
course of action
is to leave this guy behind
and do what we can on our own!
I can pinpoint the
enemies' positions
and distract them. You focus
on protecting the crystal.
The two of us are
going to charge toward
their crystal and hopefully
we can destroy it directly.
It's the only option now!
[ASTA]
Mimosa's good at thinkin' fast.
She's been through some
really tough battles,
that's for sure.
All right! That's what we'll do!
Our first team effort
is goin' great, huh?
It is our first! I'm glad!
Let's go!
Here it comes!
[ASTA yells]
[MAGIC KNIGHT 74A]
Look at that!
Those two are running
straight toward the target!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 74B]
That guy's got some guts!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 74C] Too bad
their teammate's takin' a nap.
Is he trying to pull somethin'?
[MAGIC KNIGHT 74D]
Maybe.
But whether it works
or not's gonna depend
on their abilities.
Do you actually find
this interesting?
A date with me would have
been a lot more fun,
but somebody couldn't
be bothered to go.
What's with that face?
Ugh, doesn't anything
get to you?
That's it, Mr. Grumpy.
I'm gonna force you to smile!
[NOELLE] You know, those two
actually make a good team.
I mean, not that it
matters to me whatsoever!
You can do this.
Both of you, be strong!
[RICK]
What's that boy thinking?
He's blocking all our combo
spells as he rushes in,
crystal in tow!
It would appear he's planning
to strike us head-on!
One of them must be tracking
our location, as well.
They're coming closer!
[ASTA] Up there! They're
guarding the crystal!
That's them!
We have nothing to fear.
After all, our crystal
is completely untouched,
and theirs is already
quite damaged.
[MIMOSA]
Plant Magic...
Huh? Rock Magic...
[MIMOSA]
...Magic Cannon Flower!
Rock Fortress!
[ASTA]
Oh, wow, Mimosa!
I didn't know you could do
any super-cool attack spells!
[MIMOSA] Asta. I'm going
to get stronger.
The next time we face
an enemy together,
I'll be able to
fight by your side.
I'll take the lead now, Asta.
Let's turn this around!
[MIMOSA] We may be down a
teammate, but we can still win!
[ASTA] Awesome, I can
really count on this girl!
I know just what to do!
Magic Cannon Flower!
Man, check her out!
So she's not just a pretty face,
but she's powerful, too?
Yeah! It's love!
She's the total package!
That's fantastic! She
sure knows her stuff!
I wonder if she'll
let me spar with her!
[VANESSA]
Hm. That cute little flower's
really starting to bloom!
It's probably because
she's working with Asta.
[GREY] I can't believe she's
able to fight so boldly
in front of such a huge
audience! Isn't she scared?
[mumbling] What a
wonderful teammate.
[NOELLE]
Wow, she's good.
[KLAUS] During my training,
I noticed your improvement,
but now that you're here,
I can see how much progress
you've made on your journey!
As your superior,
I'm very proud of you!
[NOELLE]
She's giving this all she's got.
I have to start taking
things more seriously!
I'm not losing to her!
[YUNO]
Nice work, Mimosa.
What was that? You smiled
for me, didn't you?
Woo-hoo, I finally
got what I wanted!
I'm not smiling. You're
just seeing things.
You have to have the
last word, don't you?
But, hey. I don't necessarily
dislike that about you.
Hmph.
Good!
And she's got a fair amount
of room to grow, as well.
Go, Asta! You can do it!
And if you win, I'll
give you a tasty snack!
[CURTIS]
They're missing their third man.
Perhaps it's best to approach
and overpower them.
Not yet.
The weapon that boy is holding
is an anti-magic sword.
I saw its power.
There will be no
defeating it in
close-quarters combat.
What? Anti-magic?
I'd heard rumors, but he's
the one who wields it?
It would be foolish to
engage him too casually.
Well, then.
They split up! But which
one has the crystal?
Magic Flower Guidepost!
Judging from this...
Aim for the left!
[ASTA]
You got it!
That's it, boy!
You're no match for me!
That's a huge
power concentration!
Careful, the next attack
will be enormous!
Then I'll have to
slice through that
and the crystal, too!
[gasps]
[MIMOSA]
What? Two identical reactions.
The other two are preparing
heavy midrange attacks!
[MIMOSA]
Which means we're surrounded!
If even one of those
spells hits our crystal,
it won't survive the damage!
Asta might be able to take
them on one at a time,
but we're done for if
they all strike at once!
Asta!
[ASTA gasps]
[ASTA screams]
No! They've got him!
[ALL]
Asta, no!
--[YUNO, KLAUS gasp]
--It's a trap!
Is that...?
[yelling]
[JULIUS]
Hm...
[MIMOSA] So one of them can
use paralyzing Trap magic?
Where did it come from?
[MIMOSA]
We can't be sure of anything!
This test is more
rigorous than I expected!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Do it now!
[MIMOSA]
From three directions?
[KLAUS] They can't dodge that,
they're trapped like rats!
Oh, dear. This
doesn't look good.
[ALL gasp]
[CURTIS]
What happened to our magic?
Whoa!
[FORTI yelps]
[CURTIS growls]
[ALL gasping]
[CURTIS, RICK, FORTI]
Our spells are being sent
straight back at us!
[gasps] What kind of
ability was that?
I-I'm not sure.
[MIMOSA]
Asta!
[ZORA laughs]
[yawns] Well, looks like
everything worked out okay.
But... I don't understand this!
Shoulda known.
I thought that last attack
would've shattered your crystal,
but I suppose you are a Senior
Magic Knight, after all.
So you managed to keep it
from crumbling apart
and stopped yourself
from going unconscious.
What a good boy!
Unfortunately though,
it seems you and your
precious crystal are
on your last legs.
And since you never
know what surprises
might be lurking
around the corner,
it's in my best interest
to destroy said crystal.
Stop it!
An impudent villain
like you could never
get the best of me!
Why you little--!
Funny you should say that,
because that's exactly
what I just did.
Pitiful.
Don't you have enough
imagination to handle a spell
you're not familiar with?
A good Magic Knight is
supposed to be prepared
for any possibility.
You should know you can't
win by throwing a tantrum
and firing off a bunch
of heavy-duty attacks.
Pal, if you lost to me,
you're no Magic Knight at all.
I'll kill you!
His magic... It's Ash type!
[MIMOSA] That means the
Trap magic that hit Asta
before must have been his doing!
This has been fun,
but I'm bored.
Better luck next time,
ya piece of garbage.
Damn it all!
You know what,
on second thought...
[ZORA]
I may not have come here to win,
but I do have a very
specific purpose in mind.
[gasps] What's the
meaning of this?
Just kidding, loser!
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[EMCEE MAGE] The crystal's
magic has been cut off!
Team B's the winner!
What kind of power does
that guy have, anyway?
It amplified his enemy's magic
and sent it right back at him!
I couldn't make
much sense of it,
but that was most impressive.
The masked man's
Royal Knights material.
He's my first pick.
I'm glad Asta's team
won the first match,
but I'm frustrated
at the same time!
Then again, all it takes
to make me feel better
is a little more food!
[ZORA laughs]
Hey! We were pretty
solid back there.
Teamwork really does make
the dream work, right?
You were the best decoys
a guy could ask for.
I mean, did you see his face?
He was so sure I wasn't
gonna break that thing.
[ASTA]
Thanks, Mimosa.
Uh, sure.
Look, mister! I've had
enough of your attitude!
You can't treat a fellow
Magic Knight like that!
Their team fought hard
and did a good job!
So what if they did,
a loss is a loss.
At the end of the day,
we had better teamwork,
so we wiped the floor with 'em.
Be happy, you little runt.
Oh really, teamwork?
Listen to you!
That trap I walked into
near the end was created
by your magic, wasn't it?
How could you do that
to your own teammate?
[ZORA]
I just needed you to serve
as the decoy to set it off.
You know what they say.
To trick your foes, you gotta
start with your friends.
[ASTA]
Who says that?!
Oh, and I've got one more
surprise for you in my collar.
Ow, why do you keep trickin' me?
You're the worst!
Jeez, my eyes feel
like they're burning!
--Asta!
--[ZORA laughs]
Man, I swear that
never gets old!
[MIMOSA]
I think I see now.
He draws a magic circle
somewhere on the terrain
or on an object and infuses
it with the power of a spell.
Then as soon as certain
conditions are met,
the trap is triggered.
[NARRATOR] Correct.
Near the end of the battle,
Asta inadvertently activated
a trap designed to target
any opposing spells
infiltrating that territory
within a predetermined
time period.
This ability is known
as Counter Trap Magic.
It doubles the speed and power
of any spells it reflects.
So, the stronger
the foe's attack,
the more deadly the result.
[MIMOSA] For such a
large-scale Trap Magic spell,
you'd need massive amounts
of time and magic power.
When did you manage to do it?
After all, you were sleeping
for most of the fight!
[laughs] I kinda prefer
to stay mysterious.
I'll give ya mysterious,
ya big jerk!
I'll knock that super cool
mask right off your face,
--you hear me?
--[MIMOSA] I think it'd be
more convincing if you
didn't compliment him.
[ASTA] Come back here and
tell us everything right now!
Or I'll punch ya!
[MAGNA]
Give it a rest, Asta.
Seriously, do you have
to be so loud 24/7?
You guys have had your fun,
and now it's our turn
to tear it up.
Move aside, would ya?
You know, you're kinda
cocky for a twerp
with ugly purple glasses.
They're not ugly, they're cool,
and you just wish
you had some, too!
I don't have to take this
crap from you, Giant Girl!
You only think I'm giant because
you're so short and wimpy.
Who're you callin' wimpy, huh?
I'll make you eat those words!
Oh, hey, it's Magna!
And Giant Girl!
Wait. Where's your third member?
[KIRSCH]
Honestly.
Every last one of you is
desperately devoid of style.
Ugh. Kill me.
My, what an eyesore.
I'll thank you not to
interfere with the splendor
of the magnificent
Kirsch Vermillion!
[ASTA]
Okay. Why is he sparkling?
[gasps]
Did he say "Vermillion"?
Sadly, this is my older brother.
For real?
I wish I wasn't.
I'm so beautiful!
I can't stand it!
[laughs]
He kinda brightens
everything up, doesn't he?
I'd be much happier
if he disappeared.
[KIRSCH laughing]
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[MIMOSA]
"The Next Time We Meet"!
Asta. I'm going to get stronger.
The next time we face
an enemy together,
I'll be able to
fight by your side.
I'm strong.
--Like the strongest!
--[KLAUS] You've got this,
--Mimosa!
[MIMOSA]
I'm strong. So strong!
[KLAUS]
You are! Keep pushing!
--[MIMOSA] Go! Fight! Win! Yeah!
--[KLAUS] Almost there, Mimosa!
[NARRATOR]
And so...
Asta, I've gotten much stronger.
Here I go. Watch!
[KLAUS]
You can--
Whoa, that was amazing!
Where did you learn to
serve like that, Mimosa?
[MIMOSA]
I did it!
[KIRSCH] I am the beautiful
Kirsch Vermillion,
Mimosa's beautiful
older brother.
Are you blinded by my beauty?
Terribly sorry--I can't help it.
Beautiful Black Clover ,
beautiful Page 75:
"Fierce Battle."
Don't hate me because
I'm beautiful.