[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[yelling]
[VALTOS]
Nice observation skills.
You really are quite the animal.
Regardless, it's
already over now.
Over?
What is?
[NOELLE, LEOPOLD, ASTA gasp]
[ASTA gasps]
[VALTOS] You've fulfilled
your purpose here.
Take your leave, Rades.
Before the other Knights arrive.
It's little Asta, right?
Don't worry, I promise
to kill you soon enough
and make a plaything
of your corpse!
Something we can both
look forward to, you brat!
[ASTA]
Spatial Magic is still magic.
And I've still got my sword.
I'm gonna hack that
spell to pieces!
The hell?
[VALTOS gasps]
[ASTA yells]
[screams]
That hurt!
You're gonna pay for that,
ya little wretch!
Unfortunate.
[RADES gasps]
You're whining about
a little cut?
After the pain you've caused?
You want pain?
I'll give ya pain!
[grunts]
[ASTA]
You tortured innocent people
and laughed the whole time.
[ASTA yells]
So, what should I do?
I can't afford to
lose Rades just yet.
[VALTOS]
How pitiful.
Huh?
[BOTH gasp]
[VALTOS] I come here after
receiving word from the master,
only to arrive and find
you fighting this?
Pitiful indeed.
[LEOPOLD]
So now there's five of them?
[ASTA]
This curse I've got on me.
None of these scrapes and
scratches will stop bleeding!
Looks like the tables
have finally turned!
[CITIZENS chattering]
It's gotten a lot
quieter out there.
Is the invasion over?
[CHARMY]
It's so good!
So good, so good,
so good. I can't move!
[CHARMY] Oh, my beautiful
savior of sustenance!
I wonder what happened to
those Knights who saved me.
I hope they're okay.
[laughs]
[ASTA yells]
Huh?
Asta!
What was that?
Small surgery.
Now I'm ready to fight again!
Watch. I'll prove it to you.
[RADES]
Seriously?
Did he just strike himself
with his own blades
to dispel the curse?
Unbelievable! Who would do that?
[SALLY giggles]
This kid's funny!
Can I pretty please
dissect him later?
Be quiet and focus.
Phooey. You're no fun.
[ASTA]
Here's the thing.
I've been fighting an uphill
battle since I was born.
No matter how many
guys you've got,
and no matter what you do to me,
I'll cut right through
every last one of you!
You hear me?
Let's see what you've got!
Has the threat of our
superior numbers
driven him mad?
What's it matter, anyway?
I can still dissect
a crazy person.
[gasps]
[yells]
Such pointless flailing about.
Hah! The brat doesn't
know when to give up.
[ASTA yelling]
Oh. I know who you are.
[GEORK]
This must be the Anti-Magic boy
the master mentioned.
[panting]
Your brash fearlessness may well
be the greatest weapon you have,
but you must learn
to remain calm.
That is, if you truly do
wish to be the Wizard King.
[gasps]
[ASTA panting]
You got it, Captain.
I can do calm.
I'm gonna calmly
tear you to pieces.
Not likely.
Flame Magic: Exploding Flames!
[SALLY]
Whoa!
[GEORK grunts]
You think I'm gonna
let you get away
with what you did to my brother?
One of us is going down today,
and it's not gonna be me.
How you doin', Asta?
You got room for one more?
Sure thing!
Feel free to jump in
whenever you want to.
[ASTA yells]
[yelling]
[GEORK]
They fight like wounded beasts--
cornered, with nothing
left to lose.
[BOTH yelling]
[GEORK]
They're fearless!
What are you waiting for?
Just get rid of these
idiots already!
What do you think we're doing?
This wasn't our
original objective.
But you've made
yourselves targets.
[SALLY, HOODED FIGURES grunt]
Thanks, Noelle!
If those fools
thought I'd let them
kill my friends that easily,
then they were sorely mistaken.
Hey, that's some pretty
spiffy defensive magic.
[GEORK]
Interesting.
This girl has the look
of the royal House Silva.
Well, in that case,
we should respond with
something appropriate
to her exalted station.
Tree Creation Magic:
Magic-Draining Roots.
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
Asta!
[ASTA]
I got it!
What are you planning to do?
Oh, no!
His counter spell
swallowed up the torrent.
Heh.
[TREE ROOT 26A belches]
[ASTA, LEOPOLD yell]
Admirable battle instincts.
But it won't be enough.
Wind Creation Magic:
death by Tornado Needles.
[BOTH grunt]
[gasps]
[LEOPOLD]
He was too fast.
Are you okay?
Please say something!
Now, to finish this for good.
[NOELLE]
I can't help.
[grunts]
Please, no!
[GEORK gasps]
[gasps]
Ooh! How fun!
I've never sensed
magic like this before.
What? You're back!
The rest of the Magic Knights!
No!
[ALECDORA]
Did you think a little distance
would be enough to save you?
You're back. How?
From so far.
We worked together
to affect our return.
Though cooperation doesn't
come naturally to us.
If I had to give the spell
a name, I'd call it,
Super Compound Magic.
[laughs] Merging our talents
rather than vying
for dominance--
what a novel idea.
Well, I guess we can't
write off men entirely, huh?
Yes.
It appears they can
be useful on occasion.
[scoffs] This cooperation
business leaves
a bad taste in my mouth.
We Silver Eagles have
never been known
for playing well with others.
[NOZEL]
And yet.
It is the duty of all Magic
Knights to protect the kingdom.
If we must work together
to do that, then so be it.
What happened here?
[NOELLE] He's badly hurt.
Do you think you can help?
How horrible!
Who could do this
to a man as strong
as Captain Fuegoleon?
Somebody check the others.
Are they still breathing?
Come on, Asta, wake up for me!
[grunting]
Good, he's alive!
To have brought down fighters
as strong as these three...
How powerful are they?
Our losses will be too high
if we continue
this fight. Retreat.
What, leaving so soon?
Mercury Magic: Rain of Silver.
Gel Magic:
Go, Sticky Salamander!
It will take a far more
powerful spell than that
to withstand my silver rain.
Think so?
Dark Magic Item.
Properties Boost: Absorb.
Woo-hoo!
That's impossible!
It's soaking up the captain's
magic like it's nothing.
[NOZEL]
But how?
What sort of magic item is that?
[KLAUS gasps]
Asta!
[SALLY]
And gotcha!
[GEORK]
What do you plan to do with him?
[SALLY]
It's a secret!
We'll leave you for now,
but remember this day,
Magic Knights.
We are the Eye
of the Midnight Sun,
and we will bring the
Clover Kingdom to its knees.
[NOELLE]
Asta!
Gel Magic:
Go, Sticky Salamander!
It will take a far more
powerful spell than that
to withstand my silver rain.
Think so?
Dark Magic Item.
Properties Boost: Absorb.
Woo-hoo!
That's impossible!
It's soaking up the captain's
magic like it's nothing.
[NOZEL]
But how?
What sort of magic item is that?
[KLAUS gasps]
Asta!
[SALLY]
And gotcha!
[GEORK]
What do plan to do with him?
[SALLY]
It's a secret!
We'll leave you for now,
but remember this day,
Magic Knights.
We are the Eye
of the Midnight Sun,
and we will bring the
Clover Kingdom to its knees.
[NOELLE]
Asta!
They took Asta. But he...
Let's follow them!
Stop, Noelle. It won't work.
Why not?
We have no means of
tracking them and no way
to know what awaits us
if they are found.
[NOELLE]
I don't care.
Let it go.
Our priority right
now is strengthening
the royal capital's defenses.
For all we know, there could
be more enemies about.
We have neither time
nor magic to waste
on somebody like him.
[NOZEL] How is Fuegoleon?
Will he survive?
[MIMOSA] I've done all
I can with my magic,
but it won't be enough.
We need to get him
to the medical ward
for more advanced healing
spells as soon as we can.
We don't have much time.
Ha. A one-armed squad captain.
Is there any sight more pitiful?
[laughs]
This is what House
Vermillion has become?
It almost makes me
ashamed to be a royal.
How could you say that?
The captain fought bravely.
[NOZEL]
Because we are Magic Knights.
If we do not win,
we may as well not exist.
Trying counts for nothing?
[SOLID]
Less than nothing!
The Crimson Lion Kings
are ruined--
[NOZEL]
Enough, Solid.
We weren't here to fight,
and that makes us
even less than him.
Now, see to the town's defenses.
This is no time for your
adolescent posturing.
Right.
There's some sort
of spell blocking
Transmission Magic.
The chain of command
is in chaos.
That explains why
outside reinforcements
never arrived.
Everyone stay sharp!
[CHARLOTTE] We need to
secure the perimeter.
Keep your eyes open.
[SOL]
You bet, Char.
Call me Captain, Sol.
[SOL] 'Kay! Securing the
perimeter, Captain Char.
At the rate things are
going, I don't know
when I'm ever going to have
time for that dessert.
Quick, Klaus. Go.
Return to HQ for backup.
Right!
[NOELLE]
Asta.
Rades!
You put your petty need for
revenge ahead of the mission,
and this is the result.
The master may have
taken a liking to you,
but don't get cocky.
Mucking about with those
creatures of yours.
Taking on the
captain by yourself.
You're an arrogant fool.
Give it a rest already.
If you had stuck to the plan
like you were supposed to,
things would have been
much less complicated.
I don't see what you
have to complain about
when it was my precious puppets
that were the victims
in all of this.
Let's not forget
about Catherine.
Things didn't turn out
too well for her, either.
As if I care about that old hag.
Quit squabbling.
I don't know why
everyone's so upset.
You got what you wanted, right?
Oh, and, Sally. One thing.
This little prize of yours
can't come with us.
Kill him.
[SALLY]
What?! You've got to be kidding!
I can't just throw away
a prime specimen like him.
We're not talking about
simple magic-weakening spells.
This kid has actual Anti-Magic!
[ASTA]
Where am I? What is this stuff?
It feels sorta nice.
Only those people who
have been acknowledged
by the master may go
where we are headed.
We don't need more
unnecessary trouble.
Kill him before the
master comes for us.
[ASTA]
Huh?
[SALLY]
Aw!
You know, I'd be happy
to kill him for you.
The brat would make a good
addition to my playthings.
[ASTA]
Uh-oh. Not good.
[RADES]
No fair.
[ASTA] Looks like I've
gotten myself captured.
Oh! Goodie, goodie!
You're awake!
[ASTA]
A girl?
[SALLY] C'mon, you should
help me convince them!
It'll be great!
I'll study everything about
you and your grimoire,
and do some experiments,
and then I'll dissect you!
You want to help with
my research, don't you?
I'll analyze every last cell.
Nothing will go
to waste, I swear!
Just think of how
much we can learn!
[ASTA]
This girl is completely nuts!
I am in seriously deep trouble.
Crap, I can't move.
There's no getting out of here!
[SALLY] Are you gonna
make me beg, Geork?
Because I will. Pretty,
pretty, pretty please?
[GEORK sighs] Whatever you do,
just leave me out of it.
[RADES]
Give him to me!
[SALLY]
No way!
[JULIUS] Hi there.
You've kept me waiting.
[ASTA gasps]
[GEORK]
What?
[SALLY]
Ooh!
[RADES]
No, it can't be.
[GEORK] The Wizard King,
Julius Novochrono.
How did he find us?
Why is he here?
Did you have a pleasant
visit to the capital?
Kill him now!
[RADES, VALTOS gasp]
[GEORK, SALLY gasp]
They're gone. How did you--?
[JULIUS]
Yes, sorry about that.
It would have been too difficult
to restrain all of you.
Much easier for me this way.
[grunts]
[GEORGK yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[gasping]
You started this.
It was your choice
to attack the capital.
And now you're nervous?
Don't tell me you came to kill
without being prepared
to die yourselves.
[VALTOS] So strong.
But what did I expect?
He is the Wizard King.
And with my magic
power drained...
Tell you what.
You're skilled enough to make
this a bit of a challenge,
but I'd rather not
go to the trouble.
So, let's make a deal.
I'll let the first person
to surrender survive.
Well, do we have any
takers? Don't be shy.
[RADES growls]
[ALL]
Not happening.
[GEORK grunts]
[laughing]
[GEORK]
How is he moving like that?
He's so fast,
I can't even see him!
[gasps]
[JULIUS]
A test, then.
We'll see if it will
work on this many.
Time Binding Magic:
Chrono Stasis!
[RADES]
What... did... he... do?
[GEORK]
Body's frozen.
[VALTOS]
Can't move.
Well, would you look at that!
I got you all. Guess I
overestimated your skills.
I hope you enjoyed this moment
because you're going to be
stuck like that for a while.
[grunts] Ow, ow, ow.
Oh, Asta, there you are.
It's nice to see you again.
We keep running into each other.
Uh, yeah.
[ASTA]
That many powerful mages,
and he captured them all?
[ASTA] It shouldn't be possible,
but he pulled it off.
Amazing.
You wanna be the
Wizard King someday,
isn't that right?
[ASTA gasps]
Then I suggest you
carefully consider
everything you've seen here.
This was only the smallest
example of the sort of power
you'll have to outmatch.
[ASTA]
This is who I'm chasing.
The strongest man I've ever met.
The most powerful mage
in the kingdom,
and the one I have to surpass.
[JULIUS]
Can you stand?
[ASTA growls]
[ASTA] The Wizard King
and all his power,
right here in front of me.
[ASTA]
Idiot! Stop shaking!
Don't look weak!
[ASTA grunts, pants]
[JULIUS] Well, it would seem
you don't need help after all.
As much as I hate to admit it,
you folks have some
pretty neat magic.
It surprised me. Now, then.
There are a quite few questions
I'd like for you to answer.
[ASTA]
Huh?
This tablet you have
here with the jewels.
What is it for?
I've never seen
writing like this,
nor such a pattern.
What exactly were you trying
to accomplish with it?
[JULIUS]
Actually, hold that thought.
You can't very well answer
while caught up in my spell,
now can you?
We'll have a nice
chat about it later,
back in the Clover Kingdom.
[JULIUS]
Get ready. Something's coming.
So bright!
Where is this light coming from?
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[SALLY]
"Salamander on Rice: So Nice!"
Gel Magic:
Go, Sticky Salamander!
'Mander!
Aw, it's so adorable!
I suppose, but Nero here
is obviously much cuter.
[NERO]
Co, co!
You should try it
over rice some time.
Totally delicious!
[gasps]
This girl is crazy!
Yum, I want a bowl!
That one is, too!
[SALLY]
Wow!
I can't believe the Wizard
King himself showed up!
I wonder if I could get
him to be the subject
for my next experiment.
Black Clover ,
Page 27: "Light."
I'm always looking
for new specimens.
Just ask for Sally!