[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Why don't we show them
what you really are?
[heartbeats]
[ASTA]
My magic is never giving up!
[NARRATOR] The Queen of Witches
removed the limiter
on Asta's anti-magic energy,
awakening him to
his true potential.
[ASTA] What's happening?
My body's chilled to the bone.
Like I'm floating
in a freezing lake.
My mind feels clearer than ever.
And my physical strength...
...is overflowing!
[LADROS groans]
[QUEEN OF WITCHES] I'd suspected
you were of a certain bloodline,
but I was wrong.
Due to your body's mutation,
the mana did not
dwell within you.
Simply put, you're defective.
But because of that,
you're able to hold the sword.
You aren't anything special.
Not in the slightest.
And that is precisely what
makes you extraordinary.
[ASTA]
Black Meteorite!
[LADROS screams]
[NARRATOR] Asta defeated Ladros
with his newfound power,
and Ladros turned
over a new leaf.
But then...
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Yes, my magic allows me
to manipulate blood as I please.
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
So, for as long as you live,
you're going to carry this
weapon as though it were mine.
[NARRATOR] The Queen
of Witches revealed that
she'd been after Asta's
anti-magic ability
from the start, taking
control over his body.
And now for your first order.
I want you to kill every
one of these weaklings
with your own hands.
[growling]
Asta, no.
Asta! Don't do this!
Wake up!
Now then, which one of them
would I like to slaughter first?
Ah, yes.
It's only proper to
start with royalty.
Kill her.
[ASTA growls]
[gasps]
Don't hurt her!
Hey, get ahold of yourself!
This isn't you, Asta!
No use. I can't get
through to him.
It's me! Noelle!
I know you remember!
Now this is justice.
How fitting.
To think that a
Clover Kingdom royal
would be vanquished
by their blade.
You can't.
Asta.
[VANESSA]
Snap out of it!
[NOELLE]
No! Please stop!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
It's time to say farewell.
Asta!
Don't listen to her!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Do it.
[ASTA grunting]
[gasps]
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Curses. He isn't even conscious!
Thank God.
So, despite all of that,
she still doesn't
have total control over him.
I won't die.
No matter what, I won't
let you kill me!
Don't even try!
Once I get myself free,
I can undo this stupid spell!
Like it's nothing!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES] Puppet's
Blood binds to the blood
in his body, bending
him to my will.
He can fight it, but
he can never undo it.
A magicless neophyte like
him cannot escape its hold.
Asta!
Oh, dear. So stubborn.
[ASTA grunting, growling]
Don't do it!
Stop this! I'll make you a deal!
You let him go, and I'll
stay here for good.
I will never disobey
you again! So, please!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
No.
[VANESSA gasps]
[QUEEN OF WITCHES] He's going
to kill each of them perfectly,
here and now, so that I can
put an end to your defiance.
Vanessa, my scrying foretold
that you would someday
come back here alive
with something I wanted.
That's why I didn't
search for you.
However, I must admit, I had
not anticipated that this
"something I wanted"
would reveal itself to be
a human boy wielding
an anti-magic weapon.
What did you gain by
fleeing from this forest?
You may have shared
a fleeting bond
with these imperfect
worms, but in the end,
it only led them
to their deaths.
No matter where you run,
your ties to me
cannot be broken.
To you?
You are my daughter, after all,
and family lasts forever.
We're family? What do
you mean by that?
[QUEEN OF WITCHES] I'm saying
that you belong to me.
[WITCH 64A]
No way!
[WITCH 64B]
I'm serious!
[WITCH 64A]
Wow!
[WITCHES laughing]
I just remembered, there's
a place in that village
that has really good cake!
Cool, we should go check it out!
Hey, wait up! I wanna go!
Please take me with you!
Don't leave me here alone.
I need a way out!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Vanessa.
[VANESSA] Your Majesty!
Can you please let me go?
I'm sick of this place! It's so
lonely being trapped here.
How long do I have to stay?
I'm begging you!
I'm trying really hard,
but I just don't think
my Thread Magic has the kind
of power you say it does!
Can I go now?
No. I'm certain that you possess
the ability to control destiny.
My divinations have
confirmed as much.
[VANESSA]
Yes, but--!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
How long I keep you here
depends on you.
It's simple, really.
Find a spell that
controls destiny.
At that time, you may leave.
Remember, Vanessa,
we are family.
[VANESSA] If you're my
family, then let me go!
Out of the question.
You belong to me, and I
will choose your fate.
[VANESSA]
Your Majesty! Come back!
Please get me out of this place!
I don't wanna be all by myself!
I told you. I can't do it.
[WITCHES laughing]
I heard that cute little
cake shop in the village
ended up closing down for good.
That's too bad!
[VANESSA]
Hey, did you know?
There's a big town
outside this forest,
and I've heard there are
tons of people living there
who aren't witches!
[BIRD]
Silly Vanessa.
You must have told us
about that place
a thousand times now.
Isn't that where all the
other witches have gone?
To have fun and find boyfriends
and stuff like that?
[DOLL] Why not escape this
cage and join them?
You want to, right?
[VANESSA]
What? No! That's impossible.
I mean...
[VANESSA] I could never
defy the Queen of Witches.
[BIRD] Hey, it's all right.
Don't look so sad.
[DOLL]
I know!
Want me to ask the
Queen of Witches for you?
That won't work.
You're nothing more than a
doll I made using my magic.
So if I can't do something,
you certainly can't, either.
[DOLL]
That's right.
And this whole conversation
is just you talking to yourself.
[BIRD] Someday, it would be nice
to have real friends to talk to.
Yes, it would.
But it'll never happen.
I'm stuck here.
Inside this cage, forever.
I'll never be free.
[WITCHES shouting, screaming]
[VANESSA] I wonder what
all the chaos is about.
[WITCH 64E]
It's a man!
[WITCH 64F]
Intruder!
[VANESSA]
What did they say?
[gasps]
--Jeez, relax...
--[VANESSA] Is that a...?
Are they really gonna
chase me outta here
for bein' a man?
[VANESSA gasps]
[VANESSA] I've never seen
one of them before.
I'll give that hysterical
old hag one thing, though.
She really knows how to fight.
[VANESSA] Wait, is he saying
he fought the Queen?
Now then, where am I?
Uh... And what's your story? Why
are you sittin' in a birdcage?
Well, sir. I, uh...
You see, this is my home.
The Queen of Witches locked
me in and I can't get out.
Like a pet bird.
But you gotta go outside
every once in a while, right?
[VANESSA]
I've never left the cage.
Not once? Sounds
like a tough life.
But hey, it's your lucky day.
There's a hole in the wall.
Now you can sneak out.
Oh. Thanks, but...
I can't run away
from Her Majesty.
I have to stay here.
This cage is my fate.
Your fate? Really?
You're sayin' you ended up
here because it's your fate?
Yeah, yeah, old
Mr. Fate, I know.
Man. I'm not a fan of that guy.
Why would anyone obey him?
I live how I want, even if
it means kickin' fate's ass.
[VANESSA gasps]
But at the moment, I don't
stand a chance in hell
against that crazy old bat
who's got you trapped here.
Which means I probably
oughtta make a run for it
while I can. Hope it
works out, little birdie.
Wait. Don't go!
What should I do now?
Well. That's up to you.
[VANESSA]
If I really am a bird in a cage,
then I have wings
like a bird, too!
If I want to,
I can fly away from all this!
It's my choice!
[VANESSA]
You wanted to know what I gained
from the outside world.
Well, I learned something.
Which is?
[VANESSA] You're not my
family, and you never were!
'Cause the Black Bulls
are my family!
And now... I'm about to have
them taken away from me,
right before my eyes!
[VANESSA]
If I can't put a stop to this,
then what good am I to them?
Please, if that power
really does exist...
Magic of mine, change this fate!
What is that?
Incredible. She's done it.
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
At last, the red thread of fate!
[meows]
In all these years,
I never imagined that
it would look like this. A cat?
[CAT meows]
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
So, she's discovered the spell.
She really can
manipulate destiny.
In that case,
let's give it a try.
[grunts]
Asta!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Is that all?
It touched him, but nothing
seemed to happen.
It's time to pay
for underestimating
the great Queen of Witches.
No!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES] It appears
you are still imperfect.
But not to worry.
In my infinite perfection,
I shall see that you
receive proper training
from this point forward!
Asta!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES gasps]
She lives?
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Impossible.
I was certain he'd slashed
that girl in two!
It's time to pay
for underestimating
the great Queen of Witches.
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
How strange!
Did I not say the same
thing moments ago?
He missed!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
This must be a mistake!
Don't hurt her!
[NOELLE grunts]
It's over for you.
Don't hurt her!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES gasps]
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
No, this cannot be!
Kill that one!
[meows]
[QUEEN OF WITCHES] Perhaps
striking the cat directly.
[QUEEN OF WITCHES gasps]
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
It dispelled Puppet's Blood?
But my manipulation
should've been unstoppable!
I see.
This is the power that
can control destiny!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES] When someone
is touched by that animal,
it would seem the spell takes
over that person's fate,
altering its course to work
in the caster's advantage!
Vanessa must not
be able to visualize
an outcome in which
her friends are killed,
so she imagines scenarios
where my attacks fail
by a narrow margin.
The cat is harmless
and unstoppable.
Well. How about that?
I'm impressed that you've
realized this power.
[gasps]
Vanessa. You've done so well.
How I've waited for this day!
Blood Magic: Puppet's Blood!
[NOELLE]
Vanessa!
Now both you and
your newfound ability
will be mine to
command as I please.
It'll be the perfect
enhancement to an already
perfect entity such as myself!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
Listen well, fate!
I am your master now!
What the hell?
It worked. We're safe.
Zell, my love!
You two. Thank goodness.
I was so worried!
But how? Why?
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
My magic is perfect!
There was no possible way
I could have failed
to seize control
of that boy! How?
[meows]
[VANESSA] So, this is what
you meant when you said
that I could control destiny.
I don't know too much
yet about this power
or how to use it.
But, one thing's for certain.
[VANESSA] I can already tell
it'll always side with me
and those I hold dear.
Which means you and I
don't have any ties.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES]
"Vanessa Saw!"
[PUPPET PRINCE]
Princess!
Please do me the honor
of being my bride!
[PUPPET PRINCESS]
Yes, my prince.
I'd be glad to marry you,
if you'll have me!
[PUPPET PRINCE]
Indeed, my love!
Why, you are as beautiful
as the Queen of Witches
who dwells within the Forest!
[PRINCESS VOICE]
Oh, my goodness, gracious me!
You couldn't possibly
mean such a thing!
The graceful and benevolent
Queen of Witches
is loved by all who know her,
in kingdoms near and far!
[PRINCE VOICE]
Of course I do!
You are a most noble,
kind, and elegant lady,
just like the Queen!
[PRINCESS VOICE]
Oh, I'm so happy, my prince!
[PRINCE VOICE]
Let us embrace!
[QUEEN OF WITCHES laughs]
[VANESSA laughs]
[YAMI groans] Sure is quiet
around the ol' hideout
when those
knuckleheads are gone.
I mean, I'm glad I can
take a dump in peace,
but this is just too quiet!
I think I'm 'bout ready
for 'em to come back!
Black Clover ,
Page 65: "We're Home."
Oh, hey, there you are!