[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
The hero's name was
Lumiere Silvamillion Clover.
[NARRATOR] He was later hailed
as the First Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
I'm one of the
Black Bulls now. Me.
[SECRÉ] Oh, Prince. So many
things have happened.
So much has changed
since the day we
met 500 years ago.
Why, hello there.
You must be Secré,
right? I'm sorry.
I would have come to you,
but I've been totally buried
in my research lately.
So tell me about
this magic of yours.
Sealing Magic?
I've never heard of that before!
It must be rare.
You're so lucky!
How can we put it to use?
Thinking about it
is so exciting!
[SECRÉ]
Magical tools?
[LUMIERE]
That's right.
With these, even someone
born without any magic
can use all kinds of spells.
I think it'll be
a good way to make
our society more
equal in the future.
Equal? You're dreaming.
It can be done, with the
help of my magic items.
I'm sure your ability will be
a huge help in making them!
I know. Can you seal
magic into objects?
[SECRÉ]
Um, yes.
[LUMIERE]
Wow, really? That's perfect!
[SECRÉ]
And so... I helped the prince
with his magical inventions.
I'd never met anyone else
like him in my whole life.
There were some
members of his family
who resented him because
of the progressive ideas
that he championed.
But he didn't let
that bother him.
He remained strong and honest,
never compromising his beliefs.
[SECRÉ] I didn't know
it then, but the prince
associated with a group that
was different than humans.
They were the elves,
a race who was loved
and blessed by mana,
and who lived their lives
in quiet peace.
[ELVES clammoring]
[ELF VILLAGER 95A]
Wow, I can't believe it!
[ELF VILLAGER 95B]
Licht and his Sword Magic
have been chosen by the
four-leaf clover grimoire!
[PATRY]
What's so exciting, Mom?
Well, you see, darling,
only a select few
are given a grimoire
just like he got.
It even comes with
an extra helping of luck!
[PATRY]
Oh.
Licht and his
four-leaf grimoire.
He's so cool!
[SECRÉ]
The three leaves of the clover
each stand for something.
One is integrity, one
is hope, and one is love.
Good luck dwells within
the fourth leaf.
And in the fifth leaf,
there lives the devil.
Back then, we all assumed
that was nothing
but an old saying.
[PATRY] What do you
think about all this?
[LICHT]
Hm?
You know.
There's been a lot
of talk about humans
planning to attack us.
I'm sure it's a rumor.
It's still a possibility
though, isn't it?
I mean, think.
The human race is so wicked
and mean-spirited,
they slaughter helpless animals
just for the sport of it,
without giving it
a second thought.
[rumbling]
What's that thing?
[TETIA screams]
What's he doing?
[LICHT]
Sword Magic: now, Origin Flash!
[LUMIERE]
Light Magic: Lamp of Avior!
You're not hurt, are you?
No. I'm fine!
Thank you for saving me!
[LUMIERE] Tetia, don't
leave the castle like that!
I'm sorry.
[LUMIERE] Besides,
a Wind Magic user like you
isn't supposed to be
getting herself caught
in a mana tornado.
What were you thinking?
Thank you for helping my sister.
It's no--
[gasps]
[SECRÉ] Phenomenal magic
talent, similar ideals,
the same four-leaf grimoires.
For the first time,
the prince had found a peer
in Licht, the
leader of the elves.
Let's foster understanding.
Your elvish mana really
is a remarkable thing!
If we combine that with our
own magic-item technology,
this land will be safer
and more prosperous!
Let's all work together,
hand in hand!
[ELVES chattering]
[SECRÉ] By combining his work
with the elves' resources,
the prince developed magic-item
technology ever further.
And the world he'd
dreamed of, where both races
could live in harmony,
was becoming a reality.
He and Licht were best friends.
And soon, they would
become family as well.
[VETTO]
Is it true? You're with child?
[FANA] Ah! With you for parents,
it'll be a lovely baby!
Hey, congrats, Tetia!
And you, too, I guess.
[laughs] Well, thank you
for including me, Rhya.
[RHYA] What are you
pouting about, tiny?
It's nothing.
You're still little;
you'll understand one day.
Would you shut up?
Stop talking down to me
like I'm some stupid baby!
[RHYA]
Excuse me then, big man!
[LICHT] Lumiere. Once I marry
Tetia, our families will be one,
and you and I will
become brothers.
I'm sure some humans
won't approve of that.
Probably. But, still.
With your help, we can
create a new world
of peace and equality.
I truly believe that.
I believe it, too. I know...
[LUMIERE] ...that you and I were
brought together by destiny.
[LUMIERE] I'm sorry, Tetia,
but it looks like I might
have to arrive late
to your wedding.
Father has summoned me
to the palace that day,
and I can't refuse.
I know you're disappointed
that he and the others
don't approve of this,
but please, don't worry.
I'm sure they'll come
to understand someday.
[TETIA] Yes. And it's
all right, even if you're late
to the ceremony,
Licht and his family
will be so pleased
to see you there.
[SECRÉ]
But, it's likely that even then,
his plot was already in motion.
[LUMIERE]
Why did Father call me here?
We didn't mention
the wedding to anyone,
so it must be coincidence.
I should hurry, or I'll miss it.
[ELVES cheering, chattering]
[ELF VILLAGER 95AA]
Good luck!
[ELF VILLAGER 95BB]
We wish you the best!
[ELF VILLAGER 95CC]
Congratulations!
Thank you all very much.
How sweet! I wanna be a bride.
I'm sure you'll meet your
soulmate one day, too, Fana.
Yeah, and hopefully soon.
May the rest of your
days be happy ones.
[TETIA]
Thank you!
[PATRY] I wonder, can we really
come to understand each other
like he said we could?
Licht believes it's possible.
Maybe they're right.
Elves and human beings
living side by side.
I'm here, Father. You
wanted to speak with me?
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Now "Bind!"
What's this? I'm trapped!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL cackles]
Good day, my prince.
[LUMIERE]
Minister? No.
That villainous mana
doesn't belong to him.
Who are you?
[KOTODAMA DEVIL cackles]
Who, me?
Despair, hatred,
disloyalty, death,
any number of
awful things, really.
Use whatever name you prefer.
[LUMIERE gasps]
[LUMIERE]
I've read about this being.
A soul from the other
world with evil mana.
A devil!
[LUMIERE]
Where's my family?
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Who knows?
Perhaps they've gone
to confront that other race
that's plotting to use
your unwitting princess
to topple this entire kingdom,
but that's only a guess.
Imagine how surprised the elves
will be when a monstrous
act of human violence
befalls that little
wedding ceremony
that only you were supposed
to know was happening.
No, let go! Now!
As soon as I obtain
my body and grimoire,
I promise I'll come back
to play with you again.
[LUMIERE]
Wait!
Help me! Isn't
anyone here? Please!
[SECRÉ]
Prince!
Thank goodness!
Oh, no! What's that?
[LUMIERE]
I've been trapped by a devil!
I knew you would
never do such a thing.
I'm not sure why,
but the magic item
we created was stolen!
[LUMIERE]
Quick. Use your Sealing Magic!
Of course! Sealing Magic:
Inverse Release!
[LUMIERE]
Come on, fly faster!
Tetia, Licht, hold on!
[ELVES screaming]
[PATRY]
What's going on?
It's the humans!
They're attacking us!
[ELVES screaming]
Everyone, this way! Let's hurry!
My spells won't work.
Our magic... It's
been sealed away!
Get down!
[VETTO groans]
[PATRY] This is Light Magic.
Does that mean...?
[PATRY] This is a mistake.
It's not true!
[PATRY] No way, no way,
no way, no way, no way!
I won't accept it! I'll never...
...forgive you for...
[PATRY]
Is that you, Licht?
[LICHT sobbing]
[LUMIERE, SECRÉ gasp]
[LUMIERE]
There's the device we made!
[SECRÉ] His items stored
and distributed magic,
and their magic stones
amplified spells
by linking to another world.
No.
[SECRÉ]
That's a five-leaf grimoire.
[LICHT]
I knew it.
Knew what?
Deep inside. I knew you
weren't responsible.
Please forgive me.
I should never have harbored
any suspicion of you,
not for a second.
You are the future
we all believed in.
You represent hope.
What are you--?
[LICHT] Right now,
my body is filled with
an overwhelming amount
of negative mana.
I can't control myself,
but we mustn't let
that devil succeed.
No, Licht.
[LICHT] In order to
keep my body and power
from falling under
the influence of evil,
I've absorbed even
more negative magic.
[LUMIERE]
Stop it. You can't do this!
[LICHT] I'm sorry, but I have
one last selfish request,
and only you can
grant it. I beg of you.
There has to be another way!
[LICHT]
Lumiere.
I need you to kill me!
[SECRÉ] The devil manipulated
Prince Lumiere and the elves
in order to throw the owner
of the four-leaf grimoire
into a deep pit of despair.
He did so because
it's the way
a five-leaf grimoire is born.
Which, in turn, allows the
devil to manifest itself
in this world, along
with his true form
and ultimate powers.
[CITIZENS screaming]
[CITIZEN 118A] Where did
that creature come from?
[CITIZEN 118B]
Run away!
[CITIZEN 118BB]
Oh, no.
[CITIZEN 118C] This must
be the end of the world!
[BABY 118A cries]
[LUMIERE]
Now I understand why I was born
with such a massive
amount of magic power.
[LUMIERE]
Don't worry.
I won't let you
become a murderer!
[CITIZEN 118D]
Who's that?
[CITIZEN 118E]
Look!
[CITIZEN 118F]
It's Prince Lumiere!
[SECRÉ] They stole
something I helped create
and used it to take away
the elves' magic!
We built that item to make
everyone's lives better!
I'm sorry, Prince. Lady Tetia.
Is there anything
left that I can do?
[LICHT growls]
[LUMIERE grunts]
[SECRÉ]
My prince!
This item is our legacy!
We can still make it a good one!
[LUMIERE] I'll use the item
we built to absorb his attack!
[LUMIERE grunts]
[LUMIERE]
I should've known,
it couldn't withstand
that much magic!
The beam stopped.
[SECRÉ]
That evil mana's fading.
[LICHT]
Lu... miere.
[gasps]
[LICHT]
This is your chance. Do it now.
I can't.
[LUMIERE]
You're right. I have to!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL cackles]
You may have prevented me
from possessing him,
but you put on a good show.
For the time being, I suppose
I'll have to be satisfied
with taking his grimoire.
[SECRÉ]
Don't you dare!
Stay away! I won't
let you have it!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Magic stones.
[cackles]
You saw what happened
to the elf, didn't you?
You're a mere human.
If you used those,
you wouldn't be able
to keep your form
for even a tiny spell.
Give up!
[SECRÉ]
Never!
I'll use these stones
to maximize my power!
[SECRÉ]
Sealing Magic: Eternal Prison!
Wait, I know what you're doing!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Sealing Magic, eh?
Her seal presents
a bit of a problem,
but I can use the magic
stones for reincarnation.
"Come here."
What's happening?
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] There's
even more despair and pain
in store for the soul who
possesses the four-leaf.
So I'll go ahead and
sow the seeds for him.
Forbidden Magic:
Noad Nepesh.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] I'll be sure
to work much more slowly
and carefully next time,
in an era where you
two don't exist.
[LUMIERE]
Secré! Are you hurt?
[SECRÉ]
You're alive!
[LUMIERE] You managed
to seal that devil away.
Yes, it should contain
him for a little while,
but it won't hold out
forever, so we--
[SECRÉ]
No! Prince.
This is the way it should be.
I kept my promise to
Licht, so it's okay.
[SECRÉ]
Don't worry.
I'm going to use the
magic stones to seal you.
It probably won't be perfect,
but it should at least
keep you alive.
If the devil's seal is broken,
then the peaceful future
we fought so hard for
will be taken away!
Think about what
you're doing, Secré.
If you use any more of
that forbidden magic,
your humanity's going
to be lost forever!
That's better than letting
you die here, Your Highness.
It's just as he said.
You're our hope
for a brighter future!
[SECRÉ] When I finally woke up,
several centuries had passed.
[SECRÉ] So, the prince began
his long slumber as a statue.
And for some reason,
I was turned into a bird.
[SECRÉ] I've been spared,
but in this small form.
I'll need help from
the future mages.
[SECRÉ]
That day,
I felt the presence
of a powerful hope.
A hope that could stand
against that fearsome devil.
[ASTA, YUNO crying]
[HIGH PRIEST]
Two more for us, eh?
[YUNO crying]
[HIGH PRIEST]
Aw, sh. There's a good boy.
Are you brothers?
Same age, so possibly
twins, as well.
No, they're neither.
This one here is sweet
and well behaved.
And, this one, well,
he's a bit spirited.
Then there's the fact that
they don't look a thing alike.
[HIGH PRIEST]
Hm... "Yuno."
Now, for this spirited
little fell--
Ow!
Ow! A bit too spirited.
[HIGH PRIEST]
"Asta," eh?
Well, you've had
a tough beginning,
but your worries are over.
As of today, boys,
this will be your home.
Asta and Yuno.
[SECRÉ] Hope that can
stand against the devil.
I wagered everything
on that wish.
Black Clover , Page 124:
"Nero Reminisces... Part Two."