[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] The devil possessing
Ronne took on its true form.
It then revealed its role
in the massacre
and resurrection of the elves.
Patry and The Eye of
the Midnight Sun were
its unwitting pawns in a plot
500 years in the making.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Rampage as you please,
allow your fear and
despair to be your guides.
[chuckles]
[NARRATOR] After breaking Patry,
both in body and spirit,
this Devil turned him
into a dark elf.
[PATRY]
Hatred.
[gasps]
[YAMI grunts]
Oh, no.
This spell...
[BOTH]
I know this magic.
[ASTA]
I've seen this before.
It's the spell that almost took
out me and Captain Yami.
Only this time,
it's even stronger.
Gauche came in and saved us
with his mirror magic back then.
But...
[RHYA]
Patry...
[YUNO] He's concentrating
so much magic.
How?
Hatred.
Demon Light Magic:
Ray of Divine Punishment!
Perish.
[ASTA growls]
[yells]
But still, together,
we've got this!
[ASTA, YUNO yell]
[ASTA panting]
Okay. We managed
to survive somehow.
[gasps]
Asta!
'Preciate the save, Yuno.
That was a close call.
That spell was strong.
Casting it should've
depleted his mana.
[PATRY]
Hate.
[gasps]
I hate you!
[ASTA]
There's no way.
How can this be?
That sinister magic...
It just keeps welling up.
[ASTA] Okay. Even if
I can't take my dark form...
[gulps]
...there's too much
at stake for me to lose.
He's attacking! Be careful!
Now die.
[MIMOSA grunts]
Your complexion has changed,
but I'll never forget that face.
[BOTH gasp]
[NOZEL]
Leave him to me.
Captain Nozel!
[gasps]
How did he do that?
Fair warning...
...I'm not as kind as Fuegoleon.
Hatred.
You have no chance
of besting me alone.
[NARRATOR] A conflict
between wizards is decided
by more than raw power.
Some types of magic have
intrinsic advantages
over others.
This is why Magic Knights
work in teams,
to cover for each
other's weaknesses.
But Nozel Silva is an exception.
His all-purpose magic makes
him a team unto himself.
With his ever-changing mercury,
he's able to adapt
to any situation,
and compete with any foe.
[PATRY]
I hate you.
[NOZEL]
Your Light Magic is formidable.
But my mercury
counters it perfectly.
[NARRATOR] Nozel's magic is both
powerful and sophisticated.
He creates a vast
amount of mercury,
then hardens it into
mirror-like shields.
That being said,
I don't exactly plan
on losing to the man
whose magic
counters mine, either.
In the meantime, I've been
sharpening my skills,
waiting for the chance
to avenge him.
Captain Nozel's winning.
He might be a cold-hearted
jerk, but he's captain
of the Silver
Eagles for a reason.
His technique's incredible!
Still though, something's
up with that elf guy.
How is he able to move
that quickly after unleashing
all of that power?
You're certainly a slippery rat.
But...
[NOZEL]
My preparations are complete.
This spell requires all the
power and focus I can muster.
I couldn't use it in
the last battle because
my magic was being disrupted.
[PATRY gasps]
[NOZEL] Mercury Creation Magic:
Silver Star of Execution.
[MIMOSA whimpers]
Hatred.
Hatred!
This spell will contain
you and your Light Magic
while letting me
attack from any angle.
It's an inescapable prison.
[PATRY]
I hate you.
Die!
[yells]
[NOZEL grunts]
Just die, Human!
Let your unseeing
rage... be your end.
[groans]
He deflected every
last blade of light.
Such incredible precision.
[ASTA]
Whoa...
Asta. Yuno.
Those are your names?
The next Wizard King
is going to be me.
[FUEGOLEON]
Earlier...
...you said you planned to
become the Wizard King, Asta.
It seems that I am
your rival as well.
Cool. Then I guess
you're my rival, too!
The title of
Wizard King is still mine.
--[ASTA] Nuh-uh, mine!
--[YUNO] Mine!
[ASTA]
Yeah, keep talkin', you'll see!
[RHYA whimpers]
Patry...
If I had just spoken up...
about everything...
...then maybe your fate
would've been different.
Hey. Patry?
Can you hear me?
It's too late.
I think I'm done for.
[RHYA]
Goodbye, Patry.
Licht.
[RHYA]
It's so warm.
Why?
I don't need a reason
to save somebody's life,
even if you're my enemy!
When it comes down to it,
our differences don't matter!
[RHYA groans]
Damn it...
After all this, I end up
saved by human royalty?
[RHYA] That's why I didn't
want to get involved with them.
They've always been like this,
and they always will be.
Well. You were chosen,
that's true.
But not by the four-leaf clover.
By me, my little puppet!
[PATRY screams]
Now, then. Time to die.
Hold up!
I don't feel like that's how
this is supposed to play out!
There's gotta be another way
--to set things straight!
--[YUNO] The idiot's right.
And how do you suggest
we settle the matter?
That villain is the leader of
the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
His actions have thrown the
Clover Kingdom into a state
of chaos and confusion,
resulting in a multitude
of senseless casualties.
[ASTA]
Yeah, I know that, but--
[YUNO]
Please wait!
This sounds odd,
but that isn't his own body.
It's actually Vangeance's!
That can't be possible.
His appearance and his magic
power are completely different.
I can't explain why, but
I'm positive that I'm right.
I can sense Captain
Vangeance's presence.
So, this is my suggestion.
Let this absolute fool
save the captain's life.
Yeah! I can do that, easy!
What? That's ludicrous.
He'll destroy you.
[ASTA]
Did you not hear a word of that?
Man, you must really
wanna kill him, huh?
Can't I at least try?
Come on, please?
Be my guest.
Thank you!
[ASTA]
Whoa!
I've never felt this much
Anti-magic in one place before!
[grunts]
[GAUCHE] For every action
taken in this life,
there must always
be consequences.
You should do your best
to remember that, Human.
Wait. This...
Asta!
--[PATRY] Hate.
--[YOUNG PATRY] Hate.
--Hate... Hate...
[ASTA gasps]
Where am I?!
[ASTA] I must be
inside his memories
or his soul, or
somethin' like that!
Maybe everything the sword
sucked out is flowin' into me!
--[PATRY] Hate...
--[YOUNG PATRY] Hate...
So loud.
[groans]
[YOUNG PATRY]
Unforgivable!
[ASTA]
My head's killin' me!
[PATRY] Your Time Magic
was enough to save them.
Impressive.
Though, it would appear you've
used all the time and power
you had saved up.
You would have seen
this attack of mine coming.
But, unfortunately,
you weren't able to call off
that final Time Magic spell
in order to get out of the way.
Because you're the Wizard King.
Wizard King.
Wizard King!
--[YOUNG PATRY] Hate.
--[ASTRA groans]
--Hate.
--[PATRY] Hate.
--Hopelessness.
--Hate.
--[gasps]
--[YOUNG PATRY] Sadness.
--[PATRY] Hopelessness.
--[YOUNG PATRY] Pain.
[YOUNG PATRY]
Frustration.
It hurts!
[ASTA groans, screams]
[PATRY] I allowed myself to
be deceived for Licht's sake.
It was a mistake
to resurrect the elves!
So many sacrifices
that he didn't even want.
I made a mistake.
I was never chosen
in the first place!
"Humans are evil."
Or, is that just what
I wanted to believe?
If it's true, then that means...
No, William and I
understood each other!
[PATRY]
We can't have understanding!
Humans did this!
That's why I hate them!
We won't forgive them!
All humans are monsters!
That's right.
Everything is their fault!
[footsteps]
[ASTA]
I knew I'd find you eventually.
You and I need
to talk, okay, pal?
Name's Asta.
I'm surprised.
On the inside, you're just
a kid who's about my age.
I never woulda guessed it.
Stay back, you human!
What do you want?
I get it.
You were tricked.
You couldn't protect
the ones you loved,
and everything you once
believed in was lost.
You're dealin' with
so many crazy feelings,
you can't stand it anymore!
But that's why I have
to tell you this!
Don't you dare give up again!
[gasps]
All you've ever done is give up!
Instead of facing your problems,
you locked yourself away
and hid in the darkness,
because you thought
it was the easiest thing to do!
[PATRY gasps]
No. Stop.
Don't talk to me!
Shut up!
I don't have to listen
to a thing you say!
You could never understand!
Stupid human!
[ASTA snarls]
Enough with this "human" crap!
I told you, my name's Asta!
--[PATRY gasps]
--Answer me!
How dare you kill
the Wizard King?!
He was a great man
and everyone respected him!
I wanted to be like him one day.
We all did!
[PATRY groans]
[ASTA] And you took control
of all those Magic Knights!
When you brought back the elves,
you hurt tons of
innocent people!
You say you can't
forgive humans?
Well, I can never forgive you!
[PATRY]
But that's why... we...
And now, after all you did,
you're acting like this?
Huh?
[ASTA] Just because you made
a mistake that you can't fix,
that doesn't mean you're
allowed to run away and cry!
Think about it!
Shouldn't you be
tryin' to defeat
that creepy devil guy, too?!
You had the guts to make
everything else happen, right?!
You did that!
Maybe you weren't chosen,
maybe no one wanted you,
and maybe you can't be forgiven,
but you still have to
stand your ground without
making excuses for yourself!
What? I don't
understand you at all.
Why are you trying
so hard to change my mind?
I know you're wrong!
Leave me alone!
[gasps]
I wasn't chosen.
No one wanted me.
I've screwed some stuff up.
But I made up my mind.
[gasps]
[ASTA]
I'm gonna be the Wizard King!
That's why...
...as long as you're alive,
I won't give up on you!
You sound like... him.
Let's foster understanding.
[PATRY whimpers]
[PATRY sobbing]
Asta!
--[RHYA gasps]
--You're okay!
Barely! That was so close!
[RHYA]
I-I don't believe it.
That runt brought Patry back!
Honestly.
You must be the most
foolish human I've ever met.
Say that again, I dare ya!
[NOZEL]
Hmph.
[YUNO]
Okay.
Looks like we'll have to wait
to bring Captain Vangeance out.
[PATRY] Right now,
there's one thing I can do.
If you help me,
we can end this
once and for all.
I'm in!
No way am I lettin' that evil
lunatic get what he wants!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL chuckling]
I guess this is it.
The door to the outside.
Now, then.
Heh, heh.
Not yet.
Face me, demon.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] Look at you,
lobbing threats at me
when you're not
even fully awakened.
Seems somebody's
holding a grudge.
[laughs]
I suppose I can't blame you.
We have quite a tumultuous
history, and now I've taken
the grimoire of someone very
dear to you and made it my own.
Ooh! I didn't expect you to have
so much fight left in you,
since your soul's still unstable
after spawning that demon.
[laughs]
I'm impressed!
As a reward
for your hard work...
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] ...I'm going
to give you a proper death!
"Lightning Lance"!
And "Earth Shield"!
Hah!
Now "Tempest of Blades"!
"Split him open."
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Next up, a-here's "Bind"!
That sword can
absorb magic, but sadly,
I imagine it doesn't
offer much protection
against more concrete attacks!
Like this "Iron Lance."
With the use of Word Soul Magic,
I can make anything happen
by speaking it into existence,
and I can also summon
physical matter!
Look at you with
your little sword.
You're no threat to me at all!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Goodbye, leader of the elves!
Oh, my. Seems we have an elf
who wasn't an
Apostle of Sephira.
[CHARLOTTE] I noticed Baval
heading into the Shadow Palace,
so I decided to follow him.
When I got inside and
found him unconscious,
I knew that something
must have gone wrong.
Devil! I'll stop you!
[YAMI]
Did you say devil?
I'm not so sure.
I mean, if devils are even
a real thing, he's not one.
He's way too wimpy.
[cackles]
[YAMI] Looks like Nozel went
toward that other strong magic
I sensed, so I'm glad
I came this way.
Somethin' crazy's goin'
on with his ki.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL chuckles]
So many of you!
We've got ourselves
a party. [laughs]
[YAMI]
Man, this guy reeks of malice!
Human.
You came this far
just to get in my way?
[YAMI] Can we skip the playful
banter and get this done?
I don't have time to listen
to you flatter yourself.
You're obviously not the
biggest baddie in the room.
[CHARLOTTE]
Hmph.
If you can't keep up
with me, I'm letting you die.
[YAMI] Hey, now you're
startin' to sound like
the prickly princess I remember.
Try to keep her body in one
piece till she gets back.
Now, "Wave of Flame"!
Hah!
[YAMI]
Dark Magic: Black Hole.
Dark Cloaked Lightless Slash!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
"Tempest of Blades."
[CHARLOTTE growls]
"Wither, vines"!
[YAMI]
Dark Cloaked.
Dimension Slash!
My! [laughs]
What masterful teamwork!
And here I thought
you two wouldn't be
on the best of terms right now.
I'm as shocked as you are.
[FINRAL]
Here we go!
Clover Cli--!
No, no, I keep
telling you ladies,
we're supposed to do it
in unison! Here goes!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 116A]
Yeah. I think he's fine.
He's our savior. We need
to be careful with him.
Hm? What's with that bird?
[screams]
'Kay, okay, we can
take a quick break!
Huh? Nero?
The old demon's bones.
Take me there.
[FINRAL]
Nero can talk?!
Then again, I was out cold,
so maybe I was just dreaming.
Can somebody please
pinch my cheek really hard?
Black Clover , Page 117:
"Breaking the Seal."
Ow! Nope, not a dream!
Nero can talk!