[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[FINRAL] Captain Vangeance
of the Golden Dawn?
That's right.
He and Licht were sharing the
same body and nobody knew.
What? How does that even happen?
Licht said that William
was asleep inside of him.
Somethin' like that.
So, technically, it's more
like he was possessed?
[YAMI]
How should I know?
Anyway, Goldiguts
wasn't the only knight
that started behavin' like
a lunatic outta nowhere.
Marx and the doctor did, too.
Even the Prickly
Princess is different.
No way! Captain Charlotte?
Obviously, a whole lotta
crazy stuff went down
while you were in
here takin' a nap.
[FINRAL] You do know
I almost died, right?!
[YAMI]
You could say that.
[FINRAL]
I am saying that!
[YAMI]
I was worried.
[FINRAL]
Oh, sure, I can tell!
[YAMI]
No, I'm serious.
I couldn't sleep
a wink for days.
[FINRAL grumbles]
We're lucky they didn't
take control of you, too.
[gasps] Hey, wait!
I wonder if that's what
happened to Langris?
Probably.
[gasps]
[FINRAL]
That ominous mana I felt.
The way he tried to kill
me with no hesitation.
[YAMI]
Hey, Finral.
You ready?
[FINRAL]
Yes, sir!
[FINRAL] Langris.
I'll stop you this time.
I swear I will!
[MAGNA] Flame Magic:
Explosive Scattershot!
[clapping]
Not half bad, for a delinquent!
[MAGNA] Tch. Why are
you out here, Vanessa?
I just got done visiting
Finral, and I figured
you would be crying your
eyes out from loneliness,
so I stopped by to
make you feel better.
Cryin'? Me? Yeah right!
And who said you could sit
on my Crazy Cyclone, huh?
Look. Just don't
interrupt my training.
[MAGNA] Asta, Luck, and Noelle
are out there destroyin'
the Midnight Sun with the
Royal Knights right now.
Most likely.
I outrank those three,
so I'll be an
embarrassment to them
if I'm not as good as they are.
That's why...
...I have to become stronger!
I promise you I'll
come back alive, okay?
Go ahead without me!
What's wrong with you? Tell me!
Please.
Can't you see you're nothing
but strangers to us now?
No!
[KLAUS]
I told you, it's pointless.
Stop screaming or we'll
silence you ourselves.
Klaus, listen to me!
You can't do this!
Be careful!
[ASTA gasps]
[ASTA grunts, yells]
I'm begging you, stop it!
We're all Magic Knights--
don't you remember that?
[KLAUS] This body...
It's responding to his words!
You fool!
Regardless of what
we were in the past,
our grudge is far deeper
than any bond we shared!
[ASTA grunting]
Easy.
Don't go overboard or
you'll wind up dead.
[RHYA]
What a pain. Though...
...I guess as soon as we get
the grimoire and the swords,
you won't be of any
more use to us.
[panting]
Doesn't look like you're
plannin' to give up.
Well, if you're set on dyin'
to protect your royal pal...
[RHYA]
By all means, have at it.
Asta. No.
[ASTA]
Not yet.
Huh?
[ASTA]
I'm not dyin'. Not yet!
I made a promise to my friend
that I would get out
of this place alive!
I won't let teammates
kill each other!
I'll survive. I'll
get through this!
And one day...
...I'll become the Wizard King!
[YUNO]
You showed me it was possible.
Gave me hope. That even
though we're poor orphans...
Commoners...
We can still make
something of ourselves
in this world.
And to prove that...
[ASTA] To make Sister Lily
and everybody else happy...
[ASTA, YUNO] We'll fight to see
who will be the Wizard King,
whatever it takes.
[YUNO gasps]
That was quite an
impressive speech
coming from someone who's
too weak to move his body.
[HAMON]
We've heard enough.
This is where you die...
[BOTH]
...human!
[KLAUS, HAMON gasp]
Save your breath, Asta.
The next Wizard King is me.
Yuno?
Wait, I'm confused!
Is that you? Or not?
I mean, you knew my name, so!
Yeah, it's me.
[ASTA]
What? Are you sure?
You got pointy ears and stuff!
[YUNO]
So what if I do? Who cares?
[ASTA]
It's just, you're actin' normal!
I'm here, too! And look!
We even have matching ears now!
Bell. Please stop talking.
[BELL]
Ugh!
Yeah, we're kinda in the
middle of somethin' here!
[BELL whines]
That's so rude!
Forget the shorty,
why don't you start
complimenting me on my
cuteness or something?
[ASTA]
Who are you callin' shorty?!
At least I'm more than
three inches tall!
[BELL]
Five inches!
[YUNO]
Quiet, both of you.
[MIMOSA]
I'm glad they're not possessed,
but I do wish they'd get
me down from here already.
[sighs]
I'm the same me.
Ya got a problem with that?
No way. It's great!
Oh, so you two
are buddies again?
I told you, pay
attention to me--!
[KLAUS]
You've awakened!
It's good to have
you on our side.
Come stand over here.
Excuse me? I was
talking, thank you!
[RHYA]
Judging by that mana,
the reincarnation
must've been a success.
He's not quite ready, though.
And even with his
swords and grimoire
right in front of him,
Licht isn't responding at all.
Maybe it's because he just
used the highest order
of forbidden magic
to bring his elven friends
back from the dead.
We're definitely gonna
need some more time.
For Licht, and for you.
[BELL yelps]
[YUNO] I'm not sure
exactly what's happening,
but I can sense that
there are different souls
moving within their bodies.
Klaus and Hamon as we know them
are lying dormant
somewhere on the inside.
Whoa, really?
So, how are we gonna
bring 'em back?
Um, Thank you so much
for rescuing me, Asta.
[YUNO]
And, inside my body...
What's up?
[YUNO]
Still!
I am Yuno, one of
the Magic Knights
of the Clover Kingdom!
And no one else!
[KLAUS]
This is a shame.
That human vessel
is awfully stubborn.
It's clear now. He
hasn't fully awakened.
The humans have tainted him!
Very well, we'll slay
those vermin behind you
and exorcise you from that body!
What?
[YUNO] Those bodies
belong to my squadmates.
Leave them now, or I
will force you out!
Well, if this is the
way you want to behave.
You've left us no choice!
[ASTA]
Whoa!
They're makin' the room shake
just by glarin' at us!
Not good!
I know I can't fix this.
But I can stun and capture them.
I'll stop them.
You and Mimosa stand back.
[ASTA laughs]
[MIMOSA]
Um, Asta?
[ASTA laughing]
Yeah, right! I want
in on this, too!
Save some fun for me!
Yuno doesn't need you, Shorty!
He's got me with him!
Mimosa!
Could you give us a little
extra room to work here?
Okay!
[KLAUS] With new developments
and improved grimoires,
magic is significantly
more refined
than it was during our time!
I agree.
[KLAUS, HAMON] Combo Magic:
Le Château de Verre!
[KLAUS]
You're finished.
Man! That is a
tough-lookin' spell!
You're not scared, right?
Their power is outrageous.
I can't protect us both
this time. Good luck.
[ASTA, YUNO]
Here we go!
[BOTH]
Onward, Le Château de Verre!
[YUNO]
It's over!
[ASTA]
You're goin' down!
[BOTH yelling]
Wow, that was amazing, you two!
[RHYA] The anti-magic
brat's enough of a pain,
but now this one gets the
magic boost from reincarnation,
even though he's not
completely awakened yet?
[gasps]
[RHYA]
Licht...
[YUNO]
He should be out of power.
How's he able to
make things levitate?
The mana's extremely dense.
This is impossible!
Now we have to
defeat their leader?
What's with the sword?
[ASTA]
Nero?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, cut
that out, it really hurts!
Ow, now is not the time!
[ASTA]
His ki...
[YUNO]
That sword's got massive power!
[ASTA] Uh-oh. I can't stay
in this form much longer.
Come on, just a little more!
Asta. Careful, all right?
Yeah. I know that...
[ASTA]
He's fast!
No, it's more like he's
melted into the air.
I can't read his ki now!
[YUNO]
Why can't I pick up his mana?
Did he somehow become
one with the natural
mana around him?
[ASTA gasps]
[YUNO]
Asta!
[ASTA yells]
[MIMOSA grunting]
[YUNO] Wind Spirit Binding
Magic: Liable Tempest!
Please don't miss.
Where did all that
confidence go?
[ASTA]
Got 'im!
Asta! Look out!
[ASTA yelps]
[YUNO] He's casting Fast
Movement. Now what?
This is where we push
past our limits!
That's your big plan?
[gasps]
Wind Spirit Magic:
[YUNO]
Spirit Storm!
[yells]
[YUNO] It's drawing
my magic towards it!
[RHYA] That's just one
of the fun little perks
that comes with the original
demon-dweller sword.
[yelps]
[ASTA]
This guy is strong.
And what the heck did
he do to my sword?
I don't know what's
goin' on anymore!
I hate this!
Come on, body, you can't
give out on me, not now!
[RHYA] That runt should be
reaching his limit any second.
I'm pretty worn out myself.
But hey, good job
gettin' this far.
[MIMOSA]
Asta. Yuno!
I can't heal them
right now. My magic is...
[YUNO]
I can't find an opening!
Time to change my approach.
[yells]
[YUNO]
Not yet.
Not yet!
[RHYA] I'm surprised he can
handle attacks that fast.
Nice moves.
[YUNO]
Not yet!
All right. My turn!
Mana Zone:
[RHYA] That's what
that fire chick used!
Watch out!
[YUNO]
Spirit Storm!
[laughs]
[RHYA] Look at that,
he's only partway through
the reincarnation process
and he still managed
to catch him off guard.
Well, I guess he
and Licht are...
[gasps]
[RHYA] Wait. I thought
he couldn't move?
[YUNO] This is it. Asta's
pushing past his limits!
I'm not done yet!
[RHYA] The timing's perfect,
like they planned it that way!
[RHYA]
Who are these two?
You're not killin' Yuno!
Or Asta, either!
[ASTA, YUNO]
He's my rival!
[ASTA gasps]
He blocked it with that sword?
[YUNO] He's condensing
a huge amount of magic!
Is this Yuno's spell?
[gasps]
[BOTH yelling]
[ASTA] The leader of the
Eye of the Midnight Sun.
He's so powerful!
But I promised Zora I
would make it back alive.
And besides,
Yuno's here with me!
Black Clover , Page 101,
"The Lives of the
Village in the Sticks."
What's gonna happen to them?