[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] Driven by rage,
the elves who'd been reborn
as Magic Knights continued
their vicious attack.
As the Black Bulls hurried
to defend the royal capital,
they crossed paths with
Sally, Rades, and Valtos,
who had narrowly escaped
death when Licht
unexpectedly used
them as a sacrifice
to resurrect his elven brethren.
[RADES]
You get on my nerves, too.
But my first priority is
killing off that bastard, Licht.
[NARRATOR] After some
convincing, the trio found
common ground with
the Black Bulls
and joined their cause.
Meanwhile, at the castle,
Noelle's determination
to save her siblings
and protect the capital
motivated her to learn
an awe-inspiring new technique.
[NOELLE]
It's over!
Langris, no!
[NARRATOR]
As for Finral...
Your brother! Wake up!
Fallen Angel's Wingbeat!
[FINRAL]
This is my last chance!
Your big brother really shines
when it comes to
speed and accuracy.
So I'll stop you,
whatever it takes!
I hope you're ready. Wake up!
[NARRATOR]
He finally found a way to quell
the destructive rampage of
his possessed brother, Langris.
But, once Patry returned
to the hideout,
he began to put a
terrifying plan into motion.
[PATRY] Now all that's left
is to fit the final magic stone
into the pedestal
within the castle,
and initiate the spell that
will destroy the Clover Kingdom.
After humanity is snuffed
out, we will reclaim
this world, making it a peaceful
place for elves alone.
Roger that.
As soon as these two wake up,
all the actors'll be on stage.
Hey there.
How do you feel after
that nice long nap?
So, do you two remember?
What your old names were?
Who you worked for?
Yeah. We made up the
Third Eye, as I recall.
Fana the Hateful,
and Vetto the Despair,
and you were called Rhya the
Disloyal, isn't that right?
How funny.
[NARRATOR]
As the Eye of the Midnight Sun's
most formidable warriors,
the Third Eye had fought
multiple battles against Asta
and his friends in the past.
Vetto was killed,
and Fana's soul
became separated from the
body it had been inhabiting,
which, in turn, allowed that
body to begin a new life.
Rhya preserved the
general characteristics
of the human bodies the
other two had been using,
and prepared two new vessels
for their souls to possess.
[RHYA]
Welcome back, guys.
I could only incubate
you for so long,
so your bodies are
about 15 years old.
Which means you're smaller
than me for a change, Vetto.
Well, seeing as how
I've already died twice,
this'll do fine.
Agreed.
Creating near-identical bodies
with the same mana
as the originals.
I gotta say,
Sally's really outdone herself
with her research on this one.
I'd compliment her,
but she's probably
been dead for a while now.
[FANA] My mind is a lot
clearer this time around, too.
Oh, I can explain that.
See, last round, we used the
evil eye to bring you back,
so I'm sure your malice
was a lot stronger before.
Evil eye? That's right.
I did feel
half-asleep back then.
It was almost like I was having
some terrible nightmare.
Salamander!
There's no response.
I guess I must not
have it anymore.
[RHYA] That means
it found somebody else
who was qualified
while Fana was gone
and partnered up
with them instead.
[RHYA] Eh, it's fine.
Even without Salamander,
you're strong enough
as you are now.
Yeah, that's true.
There's no way I'd let
those humans beat me!
[VETTO gasps]
'Kay, the next step
is to take you
over to the Grimoire Tower.
The sooner you let one
pick you out, the better.
Before that,
we need some clothes.
Especially for her. And quick.
He's right. Now that
I take a good look,
I think you're more
developed than last time.
Good for y--
Before too long,
this false royal capital
constructed by the humans
will be no more.
[FRAGIL] They've finally
gathered up above.
[KLAUS] Then they must've
received the revelation
in preparation for this moment.
[ELVES]
Those who guide the elves.
The Apostles of Sephira!
Licht, it's you!
He's not saying much,
but I can guarantee
you he's in there
somewhere, deep down.
Trust me, Patry, as soon
as the reincarnation
is complete, you'll see
the old Licht again.
I understand. Wait,
what about that boy?
[RHYA]
Oh, yeah, that was weird.
He was reincarnated
like us, but somehow,
he still kept the
human's personality.
Are you serious?
[RHYA]
Don't sweat it.
He'll come around, too,
when everything's finished.
Let's go and wait over there.
[PATRY]
Okay.
[RHYA]
Man, get a load of this view!
The party's in full swing.
Now then, let's get started.
[RHYA] By infusing
Gravito Stones with magic,
we'll open the door
below Clover Castle,
and release the seal
on the underworld!
[gasps]
What the hell is that?
This doesn't look good.
[NOELLE] Nozel, what's
happening to the castle?
[MIMOSA]
I don't understand this at all!
[BAVAL] This is a magic space
that serves as a border
between this world and
the next, which the elves
entrusted to the humans
through an ancient pact.
It's called the Shadow Palace.
It can only be opened by
the Apostles of Sephira.
Ten elves who can receive
divine messages. See?
When we place the
final magic stone
into its pedestal
inside the palace,
the elves' great reincarnation
will be complete!
Of course, a price must be paid
for our use of these bodies.
Sadly, their human souls will
be sent to the underworld!
Think again!
As an envoy of beauty,
I won't allow such ugliness!
[MIMOSA]
David's Dice Magic gives him
various advantages,
with higher rolls
being the most devastating!
But, getting this
much power from a two?
It doesn't make sense!
It won't do you any
good to attack me,
but you might as well
give it a shot.
[MIMOSA gasps]
How are we going to fix this?
[YAMI]
'Kay, so there's a magical
space growin' over there.
I don't really get the details,
but it's definitely bad news.
[cackles] Sounds like our
cue to head that way.
Huh?
[KLAUS] You won't stop
the Apostles of Sephira!
I get the feelin'
they're not plannin'
to cooperate with us.
Show me what you've got, then!
I'll shred you all
to smithereens!
[YAMI] Hang on, we can't
fight that many
without Finral's Spatial Magic!
[JACK]
Dammit!
It's one thing after another.
Can't these jerks
just give us a break?
[NOELLE]
Now what?
[gasps]
Hey! Is that...?
[BLACK BULLS]
Here we are!
--[BLACK BULLS yell]
--[ASTA] You guys okay?
[YAMI]
'Kay, so there's a magical
space growin' over there.
I don't really get the details,
but it's definitely bad news.
[cackles] Sounds like our
cue to head that way.
Huh?
[KLAUS] You won't stop
the Apostles of Sephira!
I get the feelin'
they're not plannin'
to cooperate with us.
Show me what you've got, then!
I'll shred you all
to smithereens!
[YAMI] Hang on, we can't
fight that many
without Finral's Spatial Magic!
[JACK]
Dammit!
It's one thing after another.
Can't these jerks
just give us a break?
[NOELLE]
Now what?
[gasps]
Hey! Is that...?
[ASTA] I know this thing
looks scary, but it's just us!
Also, don't freak out
when you see
who we brought with us;
it's kind of a long story,
but it's fine, I promise!
Hey, look.
What's with... that black...
castle... back there?
Looks like Gauche is chillin'
on top of the enemy base!
Our best friend needs us!
[GREY] You guys!
This is so overwhelming!
Tell me where
Licht is right now!
[PATRY gasps]
A huge bull? No way!
[YAMI]
There's our Henry.
[laughs] Ya buncha dumbasses!
Better work on that entrance!
Captain! Sorry to make you wait!
Whoa, Finral's behind him,
totally passed out!
Oh, no! I didn't even know
you woke up the first time--
you can't turn around and go
back to sleep already, Finral!
You'd better not
make us check you
into the infirmary again
after you just got out!
My cooking'll get everybody
back in tip-top shape,
so I want all of you to pile
your plates up with
some yummy food!
What took you guys so long?
The next words out of
your mouth better be
"Thank you for picking up
our slack!" you lazy idiots!
[NOELLE]
Ugh, it was terrifying!
[ASTA] Whoa, what's with
the new outfit, Noelle?
You look extra cool now!
[MAGNA]
Hey, you're the ones who almost
got your butts kicked!
You should be
thankin' us, princess!
You care to explain
the walking house
full of loud people?
I wish I could, but this
is new for me, too.
It seems like our squad
gets weirder every day.
But everything's
gonna be okay now,
because all of the
Black Bulls are here!
[KLAUS]
Curse you, humans!
Bring in whatever
reinforcements you like,
you're still no match
for the elves!
Ready?
[LUCK] This spell gauges
the strength of their attack,
and then together...
[LUCK, MAGNA, GORDON, SALLY]
...we intercept it!
[KLAUS groans]
So cool!
[RADES]
Now where's your leader?
That's enough! Take this!
C'mon, Rouge!
[meows]
[KLAUS gasps] What happened?
Our attacks aren't landing!
Here... goes!
[BOTH yelling]
Good, now hurry and chow down
so you can replenish all
the mana you just used!
[ASTA] I can't use magic,
but I'm gonna eat anyway!
[RADES]
I don't see Licht anywhere!
Ha! Look at 'em,
havin' a snack
in the middle of a fight!
So what do you think of my team?
Pretty tough, aren't they?
I wanna cut them.
[YAMI]
Whoa. Well, don't!
Really? The Black Bulls?
Even here, they stand in my way.
That one's magic interferes
with the very laws of nature.
So she's a witch!
It would appear their defense
largely depends on her.
[DOROTHY]
I'm going now. Goodbye.
Oh, Reve!
Ah. I see, so you're
finally awake.
I can't believe it--you sleep
even more than Rhya does.
You gonna be okay?
This'll be your first
spell in centuries,
your past life included.
Who, me? Yes. I'm fine.
[MIMOSA]
Black Bulls, can you hear me?
[ASTA]
Mimosa's here, with her brother
and that mushroom guy.
If we don't do something,
all of the Magic Knights
who've been possessed
are going to lose
their souls forever!
We're running out of time, Asta!
Seriously?
[BLACK BULLS gasp]
My! Such magnificent magic!
Don't tell me this ki
is what I think it is.
[ASTA gasps]
I know her!
That's the captain
of the Coral Peacocks!
Did she get possessed, too?
[DOROTHY]
Dream Magic: Glamour World.
No way! What did she do?
[HENRY] I can sense the magic
of the pieces that vanished,
but they don't exist anywhere.
[ASTA]
Hey, we're missing some people!
Vanessa, Magna,
Luck, Charmy, Sally!
What did she do with everyone?
It's gorgeous!
But the moment she activates it,
her targets will cease
to exist in this world!
They've been whisked away
to the World of Dreams.
And once you're in,
there's nothing
you can do to get out!
There is. There must be!
Well, I suppose that takes
care of their defense.
All right, let's wrap
things up then.
[BLACK BULLS gasp]
[PATRY, GAUCHE]
Combo Spell:
Light Sword Storm of
Imperial Conviction.
[BLACK BULLS yelling]
Ha! There you are,
Licht! Fight me!
And there's Gauche, too!
Hey, Gordon, could you please
do that one thing now?
Okay!
Poison Curse Magic:
Dwelling of the Poison Cloud!
[ASTA] Whoa, wait! I don't see
how this is gonna help!
[GREY]
Don't worry, I can fix it!
Conversion Magic:
Poison to Cotton!
[ASTA yelps]
[ASTA]
Whew, that was close!
Thanks for savin'
everyone, Grey!
[GREY whimpering]
What, were you tryin' to do,
poison the whole squad?
[mumbling] I was using
teamwork to help my friends
in their time of need.
[GAUCHE]
We can handle things here.
Why don't you go ahead and meet
up with your precious Licht?
I wish you wouldn't
say it like that.
But yes, I'm counting
on you, Droit.
Sure. I'll catch ya later.
Ugh! Hey, Valtos!
Make me a portal!
Man, they're such jerks!
[HENRY] Everyone...! You
should... get away... from me!
[ASTA]
Henry! He got too far away
from the Raging Black Bull!
And without Charmy,
nobody can recharge
their mana if it runs out!
[NOELLE]
You guys!
My armor. It vanished!
Well, that crazy spell of
yours was kind of a doozy.
Your body probably can't
keep up with it just yet.
[ZORA]
Now that I think of it,
I'm runnin' pretty
low on juice myself.
Oh, Asta.
Goodness, you look even
more feeble than usual!
[YAMI] I know the Black
Bulls need my help,
but I can't let the bossman
slip through my fingers.
Don't screw this up,
you hear me?
I want you to surpass
your damn limits!
--[GREY] Uh, okay sir!
--[ASTA] Yeah!
Sounds good! I'll see ya
in a little bit, then!
Time to go, Jack!
[JACK] Since when am I
taking orders from you?
[MARIE] Look, Brother,
some of them are gone.
[GAUCHE] Then we need to kill
the rest of them quickly
and hurry after
the ones who left.
That's where you come in, Eclat.
It's time for a fun
game of hide-and-seek.
Right.
[GAUCHE] Willpower won't be
enough to save them now.
[MARIE] I found them.
Look at me, humans.
[GAUCHE]
Mirror Magic...
[MARIE]
Eye Magic...
[GAUCHE, MARIE]
Combo Spell: Reflect Iris.
[gasps]
[ASTA]
What's happening?
[GREY]
Why can't I move?
[GORDON]
We're stuck!
[MIMOSA]
How is this possible?
[NOELLE]
My magic...
[ZORA grunts]
Little Eclat has the
ability to immobilize
anybody who looks into her eyes.
It renders your magic
useless, as well.
[ASTA]
What?
But Marie doesn't even
have her grimoire yet!
I guess the elves are
just that powerful!
There's no hope for you.
Now die, helpless worms.
[ASTA]
Not yet. I refuse to give up!
This is not the end!
I still have to turn Gauche
and Marie back to normal,
not to mention everyone else!
I'll set things right.
No matter what it takes!
[ASTA growls, yells]
[gasps]
Hey, look at that. I can move!
He must've nullified the spell!
Asta... you... did it!
Okay, you guys! Everyone ready?
--[GORDON] All set!
--[GREY] Yes!
Hold on. That blade.
Why does he have Licht's
Demon Destroyer Sword?
You don't deserve that weapon!
Give it back and die!
[GREY]
I'll use Transformation Magic...
Here!
[GREY]
...to make more mirrors!
[GORDON]
Poison Magic: Forbidden Fruit!
[ASTA growls, yells]
[ASTA]
It may be stronger now,
but I still understand
Gauche's magic really well!
Actually, he kinda ticks me off!
The way he used to shoot
those weird beams at me.
You know, gettin'
possessed didn't change
his personality much!
Yes, I agree,
and after we save him,
he'll go right back
to insulting us.
That's exactly what'll happen,
plus he'll keep showing us
pictures of his sister
and making dolls of her
and getting nosebleeds
when he thinks about her.
He's really not a fun
person to be around!
He's... always...
been... creepy!
[ALL] That's why we need
to bring back the Gauche
we all know, so we can
complain to his face!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[RHYA]
"Revival."
Part 1.
There's not much time.
I was in a bit of a
rush to take you out,
which means your bodies are
gonna be pretty puny now.
[BOTH crying]
[RHYA] Okay, I probably
shouldn't have jumped the gun.
Part 2.
[RHYA] I had plenty of time
to spare, so I let 'em steep.
Vetto and Fana should be more
mature this time around.
[VETTO] I don't know what
happened to me before...
[RHYA] We gotta find some
kinda happy medium here!
[GORDON]
My best friend, Gauche Adlai.
Your little sister is
basically my little sister.
That's right! Marie
is my actual sister!
Black Clover , Page 111:
"The Eyes in the Mirror."