[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[BLACK BULLS]
Let's go!
[NARRATOR]
Aboard the Raging Black Bull,
Asta's team charged
toward the capital.
[VANESSA]
Rescue!
[CHARMY]
I gotcha!
[VILLAGERS yelping]
[GREY]
Magic Conversion!
[NARRATOR]
They rescued the townspeople...
[ALL]
Asta Cannon!
[yells]
[NARRATOR]
...and returned the possessed
Magic Knights to normal.
[BLACK BULLS]
All right!
[NARRATOR] After that,
the Black Bulls were greeted
once again by Rades,
Valtos, and Sally,
who were now burning
with hatred for Licht.
[RADES] You're on your way
to the royal capital,
too, aren't you?
It sounds like we all have
the same objective here,
so we might as--
No way!
[RADES]
Huh?!
You need to make up
for what you did!
And you can start off
by helpin' us
save the Clover Kingdom!
[yelps] Are you kidding me?
There's no way
I'm gonna do that!
Does it look like I'm
playin' around to you?
[NARRATOR]
After some convincing from Asta,
they agreed to cooperate.
[RADES]
Fine, you win!
We'll go with your squad
to the royal capital!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
Langris appeared before
several members
of the Golden Dawn
who had fallen under
the possession of elves.
[LANGRIS] Birds of a twisted
feather flock together,
I suppose. I know I'm
itching to get my hands
around the throats of those
despicable royal scum!
The Midnight Sun has set.
It's time to show
humankind the wrath
of a brand-new Golden Dawn!
Not much longer now,
you worthless humans.
Vaude. Am I going insane?
Because I don't understand.
Apparently, your son, who
engaged in violent behavior
during my Royal
Knights Selection Exam,
is now under
suspicion of treason?
I assume there's been some
sort of miscommunication.
We agree, Your Majesty,
it's not true!
No one from the House of Vaude
would do such a vile thing!
Please believe us!
My dear little Langris
is no traitor!
I give you my word, sir!
That may be so, but
even if it is a rumor,
I can't let my bloodline mix
with a man of such ill repute!
[FINNES]
Great Uncle.
I know Lord Langris
and don't have any
misgivings about him.
Please don't judge
him too harshly.
Be silent, Finnes, your opinion
is of no concern in this matter!
And you two should be ashamed
that she even felt
the need to defend you!
[LEDIOR, LILIANE gasp]
[FINNES gasps]
[LEDIOR]
Yes. This is Lady Finnes.
She will marry the next head
of the House of Vaude.
[clears throat]
Nice to meet you.
[LANGRIS]
Hmph.
Pardon the interruption,
Your Majesty,
but I bring urgent news!
It's a development regarding
the mage attacks.
Don't bother!
I'm sure the Magic
Knights have already
gathered in the capital!
Until I get there, they can do
whatever they want
for all I care!
So many Golden Dawn mages.
Why are you in this area?
We're the Castle Knights.
We've got this place
under control.
Your group should hurry
and help the townspeople.
Actually, we have some business
with the humans on the
other side of that door.
How dare you make such
jokes at a time like this?
Beyond this gate are the castles
of the three royal families.
Even Magic Knights
need permission
to proceed past this point!
[LANGRIS]
A stupid rule made by humans
is meaningless
and easily broken.
What are you--?
[CASTLE KNIGHTS yelp]
Clearing the way.
That's treason! We'll stop you!
Now, Compass Magic:
Willful Compass.
[CASTLE KNIGHT 107A]
No! Don't let them advance!
This is in your hands.
Understood.
My group and I will
focus on the right side.
Sounds good, we'll take
care of the left, then.
Which leaves me
to charge in from
the front and
slaughter them all!
Stop right there!
Actually, I believe
you're the ones
who will be stopping.
So Langris did make that
hole in the castle gate!
Honestly, I'm not too
worried about helpin'
the royals out, but this ki...
Judgin' by that, some
pretty tough contenders
have weaseled their
way into the castle.
We'll have to let
the others take care
of the town and
fix this ourselves!
Yes, sir!
[BOTH gasp]
--[FINRAL yelps]
--[YAMI grunts]
Here! I got you!
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked
Lightless Blunt Strike!
Man, every one of these guys
is overflowing with magic power!
Two of us against
dozens of them!
It doesn't look good!
Not trying to kill us?
You're awfully naive.
[YAMI] Oh, no, I fully
intend to kill you.
And by "you,"
I mean the freeloader
who took control of that body.
Enough chit-chat!
Dark Magic: Black Hole!
[YAMI] It's gonna be tricky
to beat four of 'em.
It doesn't matter how
many of you there are,
you'll never overpower us!
I recognize that weird magic!
[JACK] Great job getting
possessed, you useless bastards.
But I got to admit, it's pretty
entertainin'! [cackles]
You're exactly the ones
I want to slice up.
So thanks for coming out!
Oh, perfect,
it's Jack the Ripper,
Captain of the Green
Praying Mantises
and all-around psychopath!
Good grief. It's nice
to have reinforcements,
but did it have to be this guy?
What's wrong, Yami?
Do you want to be the
first one to get fileted?
[YAMI] You almost got me that
last time, so watch it.
We're lucky they didn't take
control of you, string bean,
or we'd all be reduced
to shreds by now!
If you think I'd get
myself possessed
and miss out on the fun,
then you're even
dumber than I thought!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 107A]
Humans.
[GOLEM ARMOR] We won't allow
any of you to leave alive.
Say goodbye!
[JACK]
Severing Magic: Death Scythe!
[GOLEM ARMOR]
Corundum Magic: Ideal Closer!
Those weak blades can't
cut through my armor! Die!
[cackles]
[JACK]
Death Scythe!
That won't help you.
Your attacks are
all so predictable!
You pain in the ass.
[YAMI] Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked
Lightless Blade Storm!
It's takin' all I got
to stay one step ahead!
[YAMI] Watch where you're
swingin' those things!
[JACK cackles]
Death Scythe! Death Scythe!
Ah! This is a real blast!
[YAMI] Sounds like Jack's
bringin' a little extra crazy.
[FINRAL] They're both captains
and they're still struggling!
[YAMI, JACK grunting]
Hey, Jack.
What's the next idea in
that sick ol head o' yours?
Keh. Same thing you're thinkin',
and that's Severing
Magic: Death Scythe!
I already told you, your
spells won't work on me--
[GOLEM ARMOR screams]
There's nothing in the
world that I can't sever.
But are you even
worth slashing up?
Prove it to me!
Wait, what?
The property of the
magic changed somehow!
Somebody's distracted.
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked
Lightless Blunt Strike!
[YAMI laughs]
That's a big mistake.
Finral!
Yes, sir!
[FINRAL] Spatial Magic:
Fallen Angel Gate!
What?
But how?
[FINRAL] All right!
Great job as always, you two!
You're really gettin' the hang
of this stuff, aren't ya?
Not too shabby, Finral.
If you can back
me up in a fight,
you must not be
completely incompetent.
Uh. Thanks a lot.
[FINRAL]
Man, this guy's scary.
Hey, that kid's my ride,
so try not to freak
him out. Jerk.
[FINRAL]
They both are!
[JACK] Come on, let me
borrow him sometime.
No way, get your own door guy.
This is super fun and all,
but we should get going.
Uh! Look over there!
Keh, keh.
[ROYAL 107A gasps] Why would
the Golden Dawn do this?
[ROYAL 107B]
You're the Magic Knights!
It's your duty to protect
the people of the upper class!
[groans]
[ROYAL 107A]
What is the meaning of this?
Don't they know they're
in the royal palace?
We gathered here to curry favor
with the House of Silva
to see if they would grant
us a share of their power!
Must they cause trouble now?
[ROYAL 107A] You there!
Lowly servant! Stand still!
Commoners like you only
exist for our benefit.
Now act as my shie--!
[screams]
Hiding yourself won't work.
My needles will never miss you.
Doesn't matter where
you run; you're dead.
[SERVANT 107AA screams]
Makes no difference;
we intend on killing
every human in this castle.
Damn it all! It's not fair!
You really lost to Noelle?
That's pathetic, Solid.
It sounds like you let your
guard down for a moment.
[SOLID] Noelle isn't capable
of anything that powerful!
[NOELLE]
Hey, Solid.
You might wanna block.
Just try to hit me,
you pipsqueak!
Do your worst, you
good-for-nothing girl!
Sea Dragon's Roar!
[screams]
Curse you, Noelle!
I'll make you pay
dearly for this!
Hold on. Who's out there?
I suddenly feel uneasy.
[SOLID, NEBRA gasp]
[SOLID]
A Knight from the Golden Dawn?
This is our castle!
You aren't allowed in here!
That magic power. You're royals.
Which means you're of
that tainted bloodline.
I've come to dispose of you.
[gasps]
[NEBRA]
Her power's incredible!
Oh, my goodness,
you don't have
any manners at all!
Let us teach you!
[MIST CLONES]
Mist Magic: Solid Mist Clones!
Care to have a bit of fun?
Mist Spider's Threads!
[MIST CLONES] Marvel at
the strength of a royal!
That's a commoner for you.
[MIST CLONES gasp]
[KIVN]
Compass Magic: Useless North.
I lost? How?
The clones did nothing
to distract her.
She located me effortlessly!
[KIVN] Human techniques
are so underhanded.
Oh, no, Nebra! How dare you?
You just attacked a Silva--
you won't get away with that!
Funny. With royal blood,
I thought you'd be more astute.
[SOLID]
Wait. I'm sensing an even more
powerful presence outside!
The end of all humanity
is close at hand.
[CLOVER CITIZENS screaming]
[JACK cackles] I wonder what's
inside the big mystery ball.
Whatever it is, I'm ready
to liven things up!
I appreciate your
positivity and all,
but I promise it's bad!
In fact, I'm pretty sure
it's the enemy base,
filled with even more people
who wanna kill us,
because that's the
kind of day it's been!
Well, that's great.
Who the hell thought
it'd be a good idea
to invite the giant floating
boulder to the party?
But, look, a pretty little
birdie just showed up, too.
No matter what, the
castle will not fall!
The royal family!
Welcome home, fancypants.
[FINRAL]
Hey! Noelle!
Look who's down there!
It's the captain!
And wait. Finral, too?
Captain Jack, as well.
Good to see ya!
Sorry to make you
worry about me!
I know it must have been
lonely for you when I wasn't--
I wouldn't be worried about you
if you were missing for 100
years! You're so wimpy!
And I hope you enjoyed your nap
while the rest of us were
trying to save the kingdom!
Idiot.
Phew. I'm really glad
he pulled through.
Oh, you poor things.
Waiting for beautiful me to
make my spectacular return.
Well, don't worry,
the wait is over!
No one missed you. Now shut up.
Huh. I know you.
[laughs] It's been a while,
hasn't it, Captain Crazy?
I decided I would join,
since you seemed
to be having so much trouble
keepin' it together.
What was your name again?
[MIMOSA giggles]
[ZORA]
Yeah, yeah, that's real cute.
But like it or not, I'm a
member of your ragtag crew!
And you're the one who gave me
this cloak, so get used to it!
There's nobody for you
to blame but yourself!
[YAMI] It sure took ya
long enough, dumbass.
I was gettin' tired of waitin'.
[YAMI] You better make
up for wastin' time!
And where have you been,
Mr. Silver Eagles?
Did you get held up at a
hair appointment or somethin'?
Your house is a mess,
so you might wanna
go take care of that.
[cackles] Get your butts
inside or we're going to hog
all the carnage for ourselves!
Such nerve from those
without royal blood!
Don't mind them.
For what it's worth,
you're one of the few people
I've always considered
to be beautiful!
Silence. That does not help.
Do whatever you need
to do to fix your house.
We're gonna go find
ol' King Clover!
They're strong,
so don't be a hero
and try to take 'em
down on your own.
Your only goal is to
rescue and retreat!
[JACK] Who the hell died
and made you boss?
[YAMI]
Oh, shut up!
None of you idiots is
allowed to get killed!
You're the last person I
needed to hear that from.
[NOELLE]
I'm home again.
I never thought
it would be under
these circumstances though.
[NOZEL grunts]
So cruel!
How dare those monsters
taint our castle with blood?
They will regret this day.
[gasps]
In case you forgot,
I don't give a crap
about you stuck-up royals
and your fancy digs,
so I'm gonna do what I want!
[ZORA] Considering how
many we're up against,
we gotta move smart.
Hey, wait!
Nobody said you could do that!
Just let him go.
He was selected to become
one of the Royal Knights,
so I'm sure he has
his own fighting style.
Ready yourself.
There you are, royals!
You ready for your punishment?
[NOZEL] I'd ask you
the same, but it appears
you're incapacitated.
[NOELLE] With fine mana
control, he can make
free-transforming mercury
magic work for attack
and defense at the same time.
Nozel really is talented.
[NOELLE]
Mother.
We're going to take down
the strongest first.
That's Solid's room!
[yells]
[SOLID] The magic coming
off of those compasses
is blocking me from
landing a hit!
What do I do? This
can't be happening!
[yells]
[SOLID] Water Creation Magic:
Sea Serpent's Coils!
[yelps, groans]
This is getting me
nowhere! Now what?
Be careful.
[SOLID]
We are royalty, you know!
You mentioned that.
Face your fate.
No!
Nozel, it's you!
[gasps]
[SOLID]
And Noelle!
[NOELLE]
Mana Skin!
Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Roar!
[NOELLE]
I've got her!
Now Compass Magic:
Willful Compass!
[NOELLE]
She deflected it!
[SOLID]
Not even the spell Noelle used
to defeat me could
break through that mana.
I knew you would come.
Thank you, Nozel. Sincerely.
[NEBRA] I can't believe Noelle
managed a spell like that.
But it still wasn't enough.
I hate to admit it,
but in my state,
I'd only hold them back.
It's better if I just retreat.
Mist Magic: Bewildering
Forest of Mist!
All of you will die here.
[KIVN]
Compass Magic: Another Atlas!
The only way you're
escaping this room alive
is if you can defeat me first!
[NOZEL] What? I don't have
control of my magic!
This technique
forcibly disturbs any
and all magic in a given area.
No matter how powerful
your own abilities may be,
human, you will never be
able to put a scratch on me!
And yet...
[yelps]
My spells will hit you.
Without fail!
Stop her, Nozel! Please!
Stay there, Solid.
You'd only hold us
back as you are now.
I will handle this.
[NOELLE]
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
I went through
all that training.
I'll succeed. I can do it!
I won't let you hurt
my family anymore!
Let's show her
our power, Noelle.
The House Silva stands strong!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[JACK]
"Jack the Amazing."
There's nothing that
I can't sever.
But are you worth cutting up?
You've got to prove it!
With meat like this,
you want to cut it
into strips of just
the right size.
Death Scythe.
All right, what to cut next?
Show me you're worth it!
The best way to
prepare tofu is diced!
Into nice, scrumptious
little cubes!
Oh, hey. That's how
I like my victims, too.
Death Scythe.
I'm on a roll! I could
carve up stuff all day!
They're supposed to be
"bite-sized" pieces,
but I've got a big mouth,
so it's tricky!
Death Scythe.
Don't let it boil over
when you add the miso.
Ta-dah! It's Jack the Ripper's
famous pork miso soup!
Ah!
[JACK] Oh, no! I forgot
to put in the soup stock!
[NARRATOR]
Once, there was a girl called
the Steel Warrior Princess,
known for dancing
gracefully through combat.
Black Clover , Page 108:
"Battlefield Dancer."
Now, it is Noelle Silva's turn
to dance across the battlefield.