[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] Vetto's sudden
appearance shocked
the Black Bulls and
temple mages alike.
Water Creation Magic:
Now, Poseidon's Hammer!
--[MAGNA] Nice!
--[LUCK] Whoa!
[GIO gasps]
That little hammer
spell is no match
for my Rhinoceros Armor.
[GIO]
There's not a scratch on him!
[VETTO laughs]
Still, not a bad try
for a temple mouse.
You've earned a prize.
My Beast Magic: Bear Claw!
[GIO grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
[VETTO]
You are insects.
I shall not allow you to
retain even a shred of hope.
[YAMI]
Dark Magic: Lightless Slash!
Huh? What is this?
All right, ya morons. Listen up!
[GREY]
Oh, my gosh!
[YAMI] A nasty character's
just crashed the party.
But some... things have come up,
so I can't get to 'em.
You block heads are
gonna hafta handle it.
Now look. It's time
to get serious.
Push past yer limits.
[NARRATOR] It seemed the fate
of the Underwater Temple
was in the Black Bulls'
hands. And then...
[MAGNA, LUCK]
Now! We won't give up!
We're gonna fight with
everything we've got!
Combo Spell:
Flame Lightning
Exploding Cannon!
[MAGNA, LUCK yell]
[KIATO] Your friends
are a lot more powerful
than I expected.
Oh, man.
[ASTA gasps]
[VETTO laughs]
That Combo Spell was
unbelievably powerful,
and he survived it
without a scratch on him.
[YAMI] Magna, Luck, that
was a real manly effort.
All right, kid.
Stand your ground!
[VETTO]
You pathetic weaklings.
I gave you a chance, and
that was all you could do?
Accept your despair.
[VETTO] Ah, the puny knight
with the anti-magic sword.
We meet again, brat.
It's one of them.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun!
This is a stroke of luck.
Since you're here,
I can repay you
for all the pain
you caused Licht.
You'll wind up just like
these insects at my feet.
[ASTA]
They're not insects.
They're my superiors!
[VETTO grunts]
Listen! Their job
was to take you down.
And now that job
has passed to me.
[VETTO] So this scratch
is the result of a blow
from an anti-magic sword.
To be fair, if it had
been anybody else,
it would've sliced
right through.
And it accomplished
more than those
other mages' special combo move.
Yeah, well, that's
just the beginning!
Now, let's talk about
those magic stones
you people want so bad.
That's right, we know
what you're after!
I don't have to tell
you anything, runt.
You're just garbage to me.
A piece of trash
unloved by mana.
I'm garbage, huh?
Now come on, take
another swipe at me.
You won't fare any better
than your feeble friends did.
This beast man
even took out Dad?
His power reserves
are like nothing
I've ever seen before.
He's surrounded by
waves of magic,
his body constantly
guarded by them.
[VETTO]
These fools.
I'll have plenty of time
to look for the magic stone
after I massacre every
last person here.
That goes for the
people outside, too.
I can only hope such
pitiful specimens will be
sufficiently amusing to destroy.
[KIATO growls]
[KIATO] My family lives here.
My friends live here.
I love them all, and I
won't let you kill them!
[growls]
Ready, Kiato?
--[KIATO] Yeah!
--[ASTA yells]
[VETTO yells]
[yells]
[BOTH panting
Such power, and he
barely touched us!
[ASTA] The way he's attacking...
Is he reading our ki?
He's so fast, reading
his is almost pointless.
Wow, that was awesome.
I didn't realize how powerful
your Dance Magic was
when we were fighting earlier.
You must've been
really holding back.
And so were you.
I didn't know that you
had a second sword.
How tedious. Sluggish
moves, glancing blows.
But what should I expect
from magicless trash
and underwater scum?
You're pathetic.
Hm. Now you're askin' for it,
you overgrown furball.
[BOTH]
We'll do whatever we have to,
to bring you down!
[ASTA, KIATO yell]
That's my boy, Kiato!
Give that beastman
everything that you've got!
[YAMI]
Look at that kid.
Still actin' like
nothin' scares him.
[VANESSA] Even from here,
I can feel the magic.
The air is practically
on fire with it.
[YAMI] Now, look.
It's time to get serious.
Push past your limits.
All right, Captain.
I guess you mean
business. Too bad.
I'll have to put the
wine away for now.
[FINRAL] This is getting
worse by the second.
If I run into that monster and
try to fight him, he'll kill me.
But... if I run off
and hide somewhere,
like I want to do,
Yami'll kill me.
What do I do?!
I'll take the flan. A bucketful.
Yummy. So much flan.
Tch. Damn it.
I was trying to get
this over with quickly
so I could go see Marie.
This delay is
absolutely unacceptable.
[ZARIK laughs] Hello, Magic
Knight. You're in for it now.
Unfortunately, you're about
to be pitted against
the Eye of the Midnight
Sun's top Chain Mage.
Whoever this Marie is,
I'll make sure
you never see her again.
Making a threat like
that is a good way
to end up dead.
That's it.
Mirror Magic: Reflect Refrai--
[ZARIK]
Nice try.
But my chain magic immediately
senses when attack spells
have been cast
and counters them.
Chain Magic: Scorpio Chain!
[laughs]
Come on, move faster!
At this rate, you're not
going to last very long.
You think pretty
highly of yourself
for a damn minion.
Mirror Magic: Real Double!
Oh, no, whatever shall I do?
With an extra target, my one
chain can't possibly keep up.
It's a good thing I've got two.
[BOTH]
In that case...
Reflect Refrain!
Whoa, hey.
What're you gonna
do with those things?
[GAUCHES]
Die.
I told you what threats
like that would get you.
[GAUCHE groans]
[ZARIK laughs]
Phew! You had me worried
for a second there.
You irritate me.
Now, Chain Magic: Heavy Chain!
[ZARIK]
To pay you back,
these lovelies will
crush you into nothing!
[gasps]
[grunts]
Damn he's fast.
[ZARIK laughs] There's no use
running away, weakling.
[GAUCHE]
Dammit.
He looks and talks like
an idiot, so I thought
he'd be easy to deal with,
but he's strong.
[gasps]
[ZARIK laughs]
[ZARIK]
So, where are you hiding now?
[GAUCHE panting]
[GAUCHE]
I hate to say it, but his magic
is solid on both
attack and defense.
If there's any opening here,
it's with the caster himself.
He's underestimating me,
letting his guard down.
But I've already played
my Real Double card.
So what now?
Huh?
[ZARIK] Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
I can tell you're
a Black Bull just from
the pathetic resistance
you're putting up.
Your squad is
a bunch of pitiful,
cowardly little misfits.
[GAUCHE]
Shut your mouth.
Dumb-looking jerk!
There you are!
[GAUCHES grunt]
Thought you could play the
same trick twice, didja?
[yelps] So scary! Save me!
Your brilliant plan failed.
Ya idiot. And now you'll die.
You're the idiot here.
There's another one?
Now, Mirror Magic:
Large Reflect Ray!
[ZARIK yelps]
[ZARIK] But, how? I already
defeated your clone.
Well, too bad for you.
That wasn't my clone.
Yeah, ya dummy! You fell
for it! You fell for it!
I used my Transformation
Magic to trick you
by turning into Gauche,
and it totally worked!
[GAUCHE]
He was a tough opponent.
Too tough. It's a good
thing Grey showed up.
So thank me already!
[laughs]
Quit acting like a freak while
you look like me! Or die.
[GAUCHE] I don't have as much
power left as I'd like.
But we still have to defeat
the remaining enemies.
Yes, sir!
Ah...
[GAUCHE]
Hm?
[GREY]
I'm so super sorry about this!
Guess I twisted my ankle.
This is ridiculous.
At least change into
something that isn't me!
I know. A crab, they
have plenty of legs.
Oh, no! If I transform so soon,
it would use up magic power.
Can't waste that, can we?
[gasps]
[GREY]
Hold on.
[GAUCHE]
Why?
[GREY] I'm sure it was
right around here.
Aha! Thataway!
[CHARMY]
Who needs a fork?
The best way to eat cake
is with your hands.
[GAUCHE] Domehead!
Why the hell's she sleeping?
[GREY] Dunno. She was like
that when I found her.
Even that greedy glutton
could be a help
against the Eye of
the Midnight Sun.
Let's wake her up.
[GAUCHE gasps]
What? Oh, no! We're gonna die!
[sighs]
[GAUCHE] These vines are
draining away my magic power!
[GREY] Ah! I'm getting
weaker by the second!
[ZUTA]
My Vine Trap Magic: Bind Vine.
--[GREY yelps]
--[ZUTA] Two identical faces.
Someone's using
transformation magic.
You bastard.
[GREY] Oh, no, oh, no,
oh, no! Another one!
Heh. Well, lucky me!
Two of you knights
for the price of one!
It won't be long now
before my Vine Magic
renders you just as useless
as this poor fellow here.
[GREY] No, stop!
Please, don't! Let us go!
[ZUTA]
My goodness. How easy.
Simply cast my Trap Magic,
and let you dimwits
wander blindly into them
with no help from me.
That's it.
I just wait until you're
drained of power.
And then you're all mine.
Couldn't be more effortless.
[GAUCHE]
Damn. He's got my grimoire, too.
I can't produce any mirrors.
Was he using her as bait?
[GAUCHE]
Hey, Fivehead! Wake up!
Another bowl?
Don't mind if I do...
[GAUCHE] We're trapped here,
and she's taking a catnap!
[GREY]
No! Let go! Please! Stop!
I don't wanna die!
[GAUCHE]
Even if we could fight back,
this one can only use
Transformation Magic.
Useless, both of them!
I'll just have to do something
before I run out of magic.
All by myself.
We're squadmates and
friends, aren't we?
And that means when we fight,
I protect you and
you protect me!
Then nobody can take
either of us down!
[GAUCHE]
That's right.
I can't forget what I
learned on that mission.
[GREY] Gauche, this jerk
is stealing my magic power
and I'll never get it back!
Why are you just hanging there?
Do something already
or we're gonna die!
[GAUCHE]
Will you shut up?
Think. How do we fight this guy?
I've got a chameleon
with zero offense,
and a bottomless pit
who's dead to the world.
Oh, yeah, there's
nothing I like better
than a big ol' hunk of meat.
[GAUCHE]
Hey, Grey!
I have an idea.
[ZUTA laughs]
You don't stand a chance.
I doubt you could have
defeated me before,
and now that my vines
have drained away
more than half your power,
you're even less equipped
to challenge me.
You know what? I gotta admit,
I'm kinda impressed.
You're pretty strong
for an old man.
What?! I'll have you
know, I'm only 20!
There's no time to
hesitate. Let's do this!
Okay, here goes!
[ZUTA]
What is that?
Hey, domehead, wake up!
Somebody's trying to
steal your dinner!
What are you gonna do about it?
What would I want
with that thing?
I don't even eat meat.
[CHARMY]
You. Step away from the food.
[ZUTA]
Huh?
Such power from
someone so small?
[ZUTA]
On the inside, she's a beast!
All right. I'll just suck away
your magic power, too.
Luckily, I've already set
Trap Magic over there.
[CHARMY]
Cotton Creation Magic:
Strike of the Sleeping
Sheep! Strike One!
[CHARMY]
Strike Two!
You're out!
[groaning]
[GAUCHE, GREY grunt]
[GREY]
We're saved!
[CHARMY] Meat, meat, meat,
meat, meat, meat, meat!
Hold on! Not cool!
This isn't meat!
I hate to admit it, but
when she actually focuses,
her attacks are unreal.
And you. You can do a lot
more than I thought.
Huh?
You aren't the first
person I've seen
with the power to
transform themselves.
But that rock--I've
never known anybody
who could transform
objects, too.
Seems like you could maybe
do a bit more with it.
Well... What?
I used more magic
than I realized!
My transformation's breaking up.
What? Grey's
transformation's fading?
[yelps]
[CHARMY]
That's right!
We've never seen Grey's
true form before!
I wonder what it'll look like.
[GAUCHE] Not the big guy
with the smoke?
[GREY yelping]
[whimpers]
[CHARMY] What?! You're a
tiny little girl?
Oh, my gosh, how
could this happen?
It's even worse than those
creepy vine things!
I'm so embarrassed!
Don't look at me, please!
Why would I look at
you when I can gaze
upon the face of
my angel, Marie?
The sight of her face
will restore my strength.
[CHARMY] Seriously? He's not
even a little interested?
Wow, so that's
what you look like.
Not what I expected.
I hate letting anyone
see my real self.
I wish the meanie with the
vines had just killed me!
I can't stay like this!
Please help!
Aw, c'mon, what's the matter?
You're so cute. Stop. Now.
I've always wanted to ask:
how old are you, really?
[GREY]
Um. I'm 24.
Huh?! You're five years
older than me? No way!
I simply refuse to
believe that you and I
are the same age, glutton.
What? You mean you're 19, too?
[GAUCHE]
I'm almost out of magic power.
I wonder how that feisty
brat is coming along.
[BOTH yell]
[ASTA, KIATO]
Almost there!
[ASTA yells]
--[ASTA yelps]
--[KIATO yelps]
[ASTA, KIATO groan]
You had some hope left?
An attack like that
is child's play to me.
You'll have to do a lot better.
[ASTA]
Not yet.
[panting]
[VETTO cackles]
Looking at you disgusts me.
Fighting with objects you
aren't even worthy to touch.
You don't have so much
as a sliver of hope.
And do you know why?
One, you're weak to
long-distance attacks,
such as throws.
Especially when it comes
to non-magical objects.
Two, you're physically strong,
but still outmatched by
one whose strength
has been magically enhanced.
[ASTA]
Get to the point already!
[VETTO]
And three...
[ASTA grunts]
You don't know when to give up.
You think if you
hang on long enough,
you're bound to find some way
of turning the fight
in your favor.
So you persist in
your reckless attacks
against foes you can't defeat.
And leave yourself open
to mortal wounds.
[ASTA grunts]
It makes me sick to see
the demon-slayer sword
and the demon-dweller
sword in the hands
of undeserving filth like you!
[ASTA]
Talk all you want.
It won't change anything.
You and your worthless friends
never had a chance
of defeating me.
[ASTA grunts]
[VETTO] Go on. Howl!
Embrace your despair!
[yelling]
[ASTA muffled] No one ever
protected anybody by giving up!
What?
[KAHONO sings]
[VETTO]
Hm?
[NOELLE] And I thought
animals were supposed
to have good hearing.
[NOELLE, KAHONO]
What he said was,
"No one ever protected
anybody by giving up!"
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[CHARMY]
"Magical Sleuth Charmy"!
Hello, everyone.
The great Magical
Sleuth Charmy here.
You're joining me just in time
to help me solve a mystery
and uncover what dastardly
villain ate my cake.
On my honor as
a master detective,
I will determine whodunit!
That's easy--you did it.
[CHARMY]
The scene of the crime: my room!
This is a brazen thief!
Look, it's you, okay?
[CHARMY] But the scoundrel
made a big mistake:
They left this handprint behind!
That looks a lot
like your handprint.
The thieving cake eater.
Yeah, that's you.
[gasps] It was me!
[GROUP]
Well, yeah.
[CHARMY] The ocean is
a marvelous restaurant!
Let's finish this up
already and get to eating
all those yummy fish.
Black Clover ,
Page 46: "Awakening."
My magic is gobbling up
the bounty of the sea!