[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[pants] Terrible news!
Sir, the royal capital--
it's under attack!
[CITIZENS screaming]
[NARRATOR]
While the Wizard King was away,
invaders launched an attack
on the capital of
the Clover Kingdom.
The capital burns,
its people besieged
by an army of corpses.
[cackles]
You're so sure you're
stronger than me.
Right? Right?
Then come on and show
yourselves, Magic Knights!
People are getting killed,
and standing around talking's
not gonna help them.
I'm outta here!
Asta, wait!
Just where do you
think you're going?
We still don't have a grip
on the situation, and besides,
what will you do when you
can't even detect magic power?
I'm just gonna go
wherever it's loudest!
What are you,
some kind of animal?
[laughs]
Now we're talking!
Wait up, Asta.
I'm not gonna miss seeing
my rival in action!
It may chafe taking
orders from me.
Still, we must act now.
I'll go after Leo and
the Black Bull boy,
and then once I've secured them,
we'll head to the north.
Silver Eagles, take
the central district,
where the enemy is strongest.
Blue Rose Knights,
you head east.
As loathe as I am to take
a man's orders, we must.
[FUEGOLEON] Golden Dawn,
split into two teams.
One heads northwest,
the other west.
Let's hurry!
I hate to leave before dessert,
but I suppose we can
come back for it later.
[FUEGOLEON]
Failure today will bring shame
to the Magic Knights.
Do not let the enemy get away!
[MAGIC KNIGHTS]
Right!
[whimpering]
Tell me, little girl.
Do you like it in
the Clover Kingdom?
Yes, I do. I love it.
So please, sir.
Please! You need to stop!
I can't! I hate
the Clover Kingdom!
So I'm going to take
this town, its people...
[whimpers]
[RADES] ...and you, little girl.
And destroy you all!
[whimpering]
[NARRATOR] The strongest
of the Magic Knights
are on the move, and Asta has
run headlong into the fray.
All right. Then I'm
gonna protect them!
[screaming]
Why? Why are you doing this?
[CITIZEN 21E whimpering]
--[CITIZENS screaming]
--[CORPSES growling]
I knew some Magic
Knight would show up.
But a Black Bull, really?
And an undergrown one, at that.
Get away from her, you psycho!
She's just a kid!
Hah! You're joking.
A Black Bull with
a rusty old sword?
You really believe you can
stand against my army?
Hold on. Did he...?
[GIRL 21A]
I was so scared!
[ASTA]
I know, but you did great!
I need you to get behind me now.
[GIRL 21A]
Okay!
[RADES]
Oh, I see.
You must be that supposed
"Anti-Magic freak."
Heard of me?
[RADES] Mm... Honestly,
though, this can't be right.
The Black Bulls might
be the disgrace
of the Magic Knights,
but even they
wouldn't take on
somebody like you.
Pathetic, magicless scum!
[CORPSES moan]
Kill 'im!
[ASTA yells]
[CITIZEN 21F] You--
You won't get away with this!
[CITIZEN 21F screams]
[CITIZEN 21G]
What do you want?
Whatever it is, you can have it!
[CITIZEN 22A]
Look! It's the Silver Eagles!
[CITIZEN 21F]
The Magic Knights are here!
They'll save us!
[CITIZEN 21D]
And do you see that?
The captain himself came.
[CITIZEN 22E]
Sir Nozel! Sir Solid!
[CITIZEN 22A]
Lady Nebra!
We're here. Now,
everyone step aside.
What are these things?
Nothing we do seems
to keep them down.
Unfortunately, it appears
I shall have to pass
on dessert after all.
I find these creatures
have ruined my appetite.
Oh, wow!
Whatever these are, they're
really gross, huh, Char?
Yes, they are.
Just looking at them makes
me sick to my stomach.
And, call me Captain, Sol.
Uh. Oh, yeah, sorry!
Stay back, filthy wretches.
There are just so many of them!
A corpse army.
I wonder if they
have any weaknesses.
So cautious. If you're
strong enough,
the enemy's weaknesses
don't matter.
They're really creepy.
I hope my rival's all right.
You can worry about looking
for the Black Bull
boy later, Leo.
These fiends.
There's magic power inside them,
but while they can move,
they aren't living beings.
Which means...
[MAGIC KNIGHTS]
To make sure they stay down,
we must destroy them!
Let's see how you
like this spell.
My Flame Magic: Spiral Flames!
[yells]
Go, Flame Magic: Sol Linea!
That's incredible.
Steel Creation Magic.
Go, Spiral Lance!
[HAMON]
Oh, dear, this won't do.
You needn't fight like savages.
Though, I suppose
that's what you are.
At least you can die
with grace and beauty.
Glass Creation Magic:
Fleur de Verre.
[HAMON laughs]
I'll rip these mindless
sacks of flesh to pieces.
Feel my wrath, you filth!
Sand Creation Magic:
Sand Armored Guard.
Wind Magic: Towering Tornado!
My Dream-Healing
Flower Cradle spell
can help if you've been injured.
Any wounded, please come see me!
Is there no end to
these vile creatures?
You creeps had better keep
your hands off of Char!
Earth Creation Magic:
Raging Mother Goddess!
[RAGING MOTHER GODDESS roars]
That's "Captain"!
Not one step further.
No one is permitted to touch me.
Briar Creation Magic:
Corpse-Hunting Briar Trees!
How revolting.
Water Creation Magic:
Slashing Sea Serpent!
[ALL]
Mist Magic: Solid Mist Clones.
[NEBRAS]
Too bad.
These dumb brutes are
hardly worth the effort.
[CORPSES growling]
[NOZEL]
Receive your punishment.
Mercury Magic: Rain of Silver!
[NOZEL] This is what
happens to those who dare
to rise up against
our land. We crush them.
Flame Creation Magic:
Leo Rugiens!
Burn to ash!
That was amazing!
They're so powerful!
Is there anything they can't do?
Wow, they're incredible!
[panting]
[LEOPOLD]
Yeah, I've got you now!
[ASTA yells]
Hey, I know that yell.
[ASTA yelling]
[LEOPOLD]
What's he doing?
Mowing down hordes
of those things
with only that sword of his?
So much raw physical power.
And what a straightforward
way to fight.
[laughs]
You're almost too entertaining.
And that's exactly what
I'm looking for in a rival!
[LEOPOLD grunts]
[yells]
[RADES] My Wraith Magic
allows me to channel my mana
into corpses and control
them however I wish.
My very own puppets.
[RADES]
But this boy's attacks instantly
cut through the mana,
making it disappear
and severing my
puppets' strings.
Is that all of 'em?
Yo-You saved me. Thank you!
I wouldn't thank me just yet.
[RADES]
Heh!
[ASTA] You've gotta be
a real monster to attack
innocent people like that!
Huh?!
Well, I'm gonna make sure
you don't do it again!
[yells]
[yelps]
[RADES]
Number Four: Jimmy.
Innocent, you say?
These people fail to
see how powerful I am.
[yelps]
So, they're guilty to me!
[RADES]
Heh!
[ASTA] You've gotta be
a real monster to attack
innocent people like that!
Huh?!
Well, I'm gonna make sure
you don't do it again!
[yells]
[yelps]
[RADES]
Number Four: Jimmy.
Innocent, you say?
These people fail to see
how powerful I am.
[yelps]
So, they're guilty to me!
[grunts]
The corpses just keep coming.
Problem is, they're
not the true enemy.
Almost done.
There you go.
You're as good as new.
[HAMON laughs]
There's just no end to them.
They almost had you there.
But lucky for me,
you came to the rescue.
I'll treat you both to a gelato
later, as a thank you.
Yeah!
Go, go, go, go, go!
The loveliest flowers
are those with thorns.
Mist Spider's Threads.
Water Creation Magic:
Holy Water Bullet!
[RADES]
Here you go, Jimmy.
This little brat
is your prey. Enjoy.
[JIMMY growls]
Hey!
I'm gettin' kinda tired
of all the creepy stuff
you've been springing on
us today, so chill out!
[gasps]
[ASTA]
This wound--it's getting bigger.
Excellent, it seems
you're finally
starting to notice
the unique effects
of Jimmy's special curse shells.
You'll find even a simple
scrape won't stop bleeding.
So I'd be careful if I were you.
Jimmy!
[JIMMY roars]
[ASTA]
The big sword is too slow.
[ASTA yells]
For someone without any magic,
you certainly are a nuisance.
Still, Jimmy has
enough curse power
to swat you like
the fly you are.
[JIMMY growls]
[ASTA growls]
But, first things first.
[ASTA gasps]
[RADES]
Jimmy!
Take care of that little
pest he's protecting.
[gasps]
[JIMMY roars]
[screams]
You stay away from her!
Oh, yes, the noble
Magic Knights.
Gladly risking themselves
to safeguard the people.
[ASTA yells]
--[JIMMY growling]
--[ASTA grunting]
[laughs]
Why are you even
bothering with her?
There, see?
Defending all these
so-called innocents
will only get you hurt,
you self-righteous fool.
Please, I'm scared!
The little brat is
gonna die anyway,
sooner or later.
So what's the point
of protecting her?
I don't need a reason
to save someone's life!
Really?
All right, then.
If that's how you feel.
You can stand there
and swing your sword
like an idiot until
your blood runs dry.
[yelling]
There he is!
[NOELLE]
I have to help him!
[gasps]
[SOLID] You can't even
control your magic properly.
Could there be any greater
disgrace than you?
You were as good as
banished from House Silva
for being an abject failure.
How dare you come waltzing
back into the Noble Realm
as if you belong?
This is no place for a
pathetic creature like you.
Now leave.
Wasn't killing
our mother enough?
No. I would just be in the way.
Please help! Anyone!
Asta's in trouble.
[NOELLE gasps]
Thank you so--
[FUEGOLEON]
Concentrate!
[whimpers] Ow. What'd
you do that for?
Tell me, Black Bull girl.
You aren't hesitating because
of your siblings'
taunting. Are you?
There's no time for that
on the battlefield!
[NOELLE gasps]
[FUEGOLEON] One bad decision
out here could mean lives lost!
Forget your insecurities.
You stand here today as a
member of the Magic Knights.
If you joined the order
of your own accord,
you must be determined
to grow stronger!
Stronger.
There isn't any shame
in being weak, girl.
The shame is in staying weak.
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
That's right.
He's been proving that
all along, hasn't he?
[NOELLE]
He can do it. And so can I.
We can grow stronger!
[ASTA grunts]
Are you okay?
The weak will die weak
while the strong live
to grow stronger.
--[ASTA yells]
--[JIMMY roars]
[gasps]
[ASTA]
Oh, no! I'm too late!
[yelps]
Huh?
[RADES]
And who the hell are you?
Noelle!
What mess have you
gotten yourself into now?
I can't leave you alone
for five minutes!
How about a "thank you"
for bailing you out again?
Thank you!
[NOELLE]
Now that you can move freely,
he won't be able to stop you.
So get going!
[laughs] I guess somebody's
feeling better, huh?
I'm just fine.
It's not like I was that upset.
Brats, both of you!
Now, you'll die!
[ASTA grunts]
Don't worry, Asta,
your new rival's got your back.
Now go give that brute
a taste of your blade.
Get out there and show
me what you can do!
Oh, hey.
That was good timing, thank you.
There's no need to thank me.
It's my turn!
I'm gonna take this guy down!
[JIMMY growls]
[ASTA yells]
[ASTA yelling]
[yelling]
[JIMMY groaning]
[ASTA]
I'm not done yet!
[ASTA yelling]
Whoops, gonna fall.
He did it!
You're amazing!
I don't think I've ever seen
such an unmage-like
fighting style.
You're just fascinating!
[laughs]
[RADES groans]
Huh?
A ridiculous attack like that
shouldn't have been
able to bring him down.
Hey, Jimmy! Can you hear me?
[ASTA]
Your sidekick is done.
This time you're gonna have
to come after me yourself!
[RADES]
Huh? Ooh!
Think you've got me
beat now, do you?
No way, boy!
Come forth, Alfred!
[ALFRED groaning]
Now, Number Two.
Say "hi" to Alfred.
Go and get him, Alfred.
He's all yours.
[ASTA grunts]
[laughs]
Asta.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[RADES]
"Justrades"!
Hello, there!
Hello to you!
It's nice to meet you. I'm Asta.
You were so busy
trying to kill me,
you never introduced yourself.
So, do you think you could
tell me your name, corpse guy?
Sure, no problem.
The name is Rades, see?
That's a pretty
unusual name, huh?
I don't think I've ever met
anybody called Radessy before.
No, you've got it wrong.
Not Rades-see,
it's just "Rades."
Justrades, okay! Well,
it's nice to meet you!
Wrong again!
But that's what you
said: "Justrades."
Come on, listen. It's Rades.
Just "Rades," see?
Okay then, Rades Justradessy.
There, I think I finally
got it that time. Huh?
C'mon! Just how stupid are you?
The name's Rades!
Ya hear me?
You can't get one
simple name right?
I'm really looking forward
to killing you now!
[RADES]
The Magic Knights?
Please. They're no match for me.
I'm Rades, the strongest mage
in the Clover Kingdom!
Black Clover , Page 23:
"The King of the Crimson Lions."
My magic is commanding
the dead to do my bidding.