[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] Round Two, Match One
of the Royal Knights
Selection Exam.
Team B was at a
distinct disadvantage
against Kirsch's
overwhelming magic might.
Black Hurricane!
[NARRATOR] But Asta channeled
his dark power to nullify
Kirsch's spells in one fell
swoop--along with some
traps the mysterious mage Xerx
had set up before the exam.
Now, they're back to square one.
[ASTA] There's only one
way to beat a team
as strong as that,
n' guess what?
It's by makin' a team
that's stronger!
So I guess that leaves
me with no choice
but to put you to use.
[NARRATOR] Working together
for the first time,
Zora and Asta set up
an ingenious snare
that successfully lured in
the self-absorbed Kirsch
and removed him from
the battlefield.
I told ya that you and me
could make a good team.
[MIMOSA] Okay. According to
my Magic Flower Guidepost,
the enemy hid their crystal
inside of Sol's golem.
[MIMOSA] If I use this seed to
plant my Magic-Controlling Weeds
inside of Sol's spell,
we can win this.
It'll let me take control
of her little mud pet
long enough to expose
the gem and shatter it.
The problem is,
that spell needs time to
sprout and put down roots.
And I'd have to fight as though
I didn't know the seed was sown.
Will I be able to pull
off a feint like that?
Plant Magic: Magic Canon Flower!
You're not as weak as I thought.
But not good enough.
Earth Magic: Clod Seal!
[MIMOSA gasps, yelps]
I wanna win, but I'm
not into hurting women.
How about you stay outta this?
I have to warn the others!
[SOL]
Now, then.
I wonder how far that
hothead can get on his own.
It was only a matter
of time before
your overconfidence
led to your downfall.
And now look at you.
I can't believe you fell
for such a primitive trap.
Are you really a vice captain?
Save some face and quit already.
Egotistical morons like
you make me sick.
By the way, your precious
face is all scratched up.
[ASTA] Why are ya pilin'
the insults on a guy
who's totally out cold?
Still, this was a great idea!
May have been a bit risky,
but that pitfall worked
out in the end.
See? I knew you'd come up
with somethin' crafty.
Never thought my sword
would double as a shovel,
but it got the job done way
faster than I thought it would.
[ZORA] I have to admit your
speed was impressive.
And you barely broke a sweat.
You pack a lot of muscle
in that tiny frame.
Hey, thanks, man,
I've been training!
Now. This guy may be
a fool, but he's strong.
No telling what he'll
do when he wakes up.
I'll put a magic circle near
the entrance just in case.
[ASTA] Whoa! So that's
how you lay traps!
And they just disappear!
[ZORA] If anyone shows up
and tries to rescue the fool:
kaboom. [chuckles]
Might as well bury
him while I'm at it.
Can't be too careful.
[ASTA]
Hey! That's overkill!
Not to mention my sword's
down there with him!
[MAGNA]
Hear that? This way!
[ASTA]
I know that voice!
[MAGNA] Flame Reinforcement
Magic: Risky Stolen Base!
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on...
Aw, yeah. I found ya, crystal!
Wow, you're really bringin'
the heat, huh, Magna!
I know better than
to get close enough
for you to attack me, Asta.
But at this distance,
I'm sure to win this match.
Call it revenge
for what happened
during your stupid baptism!
Don't think that I haven't
grown into a more
powerful wizard than
I was back then!
You gotta prove it. Bring it on!
Take this!
All right!
I can hit this back. No problem!
You're not gonna get
this crystal, Magna!
Uh-oh!
[laughs] Now that's
a swing and a miss.
My new Annihilation
Massacre Fireball
vanishes before it
ever hits its target.
There's no way can
you stop something
that disappears right
before your eyes.
[ASTA]
That's an awesome spell.
I shouldn't be surprised,
coming from Magna.
Oh. Quite impressive!
Turns out he's more
skilled than he looks.
You should see him
fire up the grill
whenever we have a big barbecue.
[ASTA] If I try to get close to
Magna, he'll just sprint away
with that speedy
spell from earlier.
Plus, I'd be leavin'
the crystal wide open.
I'd need to go all Black Asta
to get close to him quickly.
But that power's
still cooling down.
Dang it.
[ASTA] Mimosa! Where are
you? I need your help!
[ZORA]
Hey, runt. Hold out for ten.
No. Make that five minutes.
Sure. I'm on it.
[BAKER 79A]
Hey! Wait up, ya thievin' brat!
[KIRSCH]
You see that, Mimosa?
Such a young child already
devoted to a life of crime.
Take note: the poor are
poor to their very souls.
Ugly outside and within.
Those who're revolting
in childhood are destined
to be just as hideous
when they're adults.
[SOL] Hey? You okay?
Time to rise and shine.
[KIRSCH grunts]
[SOL]
I said. Wake up!
Good, you finally
decided to join us.
[KIRSCH] I'm afraid
I can never forgive you
for laying a hand
on my glorious face.
Hate to tell ya this,
but it was pretty
messed up before I got here.
My beautiful visage
shall survive.
[SOL]
You are not beautiful.
[gasps]
You're not deserving of
that word; it should only
be used to describe
people like Char!
Now then, we'll be back soon.
Take care of the village
while we're gone.
You can count on me.
No reason to worry when
I'm watching over things.
You focus on making money
and I'll make sure
everyone here's safe.
Just as I expected,
you're still a heck
of a spitfire, Sol.
[VILLAGER 79B] But this
village is full of promising,
reliable young men.
They'll handle things for us.
That's right. We'll take
care of everything.
[VILLAGER 79D]
Yeah.
We'll guard the village
while our fathers are away.
You be a good girl and go help
our mothers out, why dontcha?
What? Aren't you
the baby who just
spent the afternoon
running around crying
because a scary-looking stray
dog wanted to lick him?
[BOTH]
Uh--
I'm way stronger than any
of you little boys in town,
everyone knows it's true.
[VILLAGER 79D]
Maybe, but...
Even if you are kinda
strong for a girl,
you're still just
a woman, and us men
are the ones who should
be doing the protecting.
Wait. Huh? You really
think that matters?
[OLD WOMAN 79A]
I am worried, though.
We've heard reports
that there are bandits
wandering about
targeting villages
far from the royal capital.
[VILLAGER 79E]
They attacked a rural village
to the east not too long ago.
There's no need to panic.
Those bandits you heard about
were all but destroyed
thanks to the Magic Knights
going after them.
[SOL'S FATHER] If anything
happens, you should contact
the Magic Knights right away.
Goodbye for now. We'll be
back before you know it.
[gasps]
[VILLAGERS yelling]
Grab anything that
looks valuable.
And any woman who looks
like she might sell.
And be quick about it.
We gotta be gone before
those damn knights show up.
Everyone needs to get
to the church right now!
I know what you're thinking.
But you can't stay out here--
you have to come, too.
I'll be fine on my own, just go!
Our guards, huh?
[gasps]
Hey, now, missy.
This area is dangerous.
Especially for a
beauty like you.
I'm betting you'll grow
into a fine woman soon.
You're gonna be joining us now.
If you come quietly,
I'll guarantee you only
get bruised up a little bit.
Leave this village immediately
or I'll force you out!
Heh! She's a real
wild one, isn't she?
That's good. And I think that
we're just the men to tame her.
Looks like we found
a mouse in the alley.
[BANDIT 79B]
What's wrong, kid?
You so scared you
can't even run?
You wanna impress her?
Here's a little tip,
you'll have to do more
than just stare.
Why don't you c'mere
and try to save your friend?
I mean, unless you
value your life.
And us men are the ones who
should be doing the protecting.
Sorry, Sol.
Welp, so much for bein' rescued.
[BANDIT 79B] Not that he ever
stood a chance against us.
Forget about that
hopeless kid, girly.
I'll teach you how to
play like a grownup.
Ah--
[gasps]
[KIRSCH] Captain Charlotte
really went out of her way
to protect a poor
village like that?
You remember what
the Wizard King said.
We fight for people regardless
of their rank or status.
And Char. Not only
did she save my life,
she gave me a goal
for the future, too.
[CHARLOTTE]
Can you stand?
There's no need to be afraid.
I wasn't. I swear it.
[SOL] I really was planning
to fight them and win.
Somehow. Some way. This is home.
I wanted to protect
everyone here.
But...
[SOL]
I couldn't do anything.
I was too weak.
I'm so mad at myself.
I believed what those
boys said about me,
even if it was just for
a second. I'm a failure.
[SOL]
What does it take?
How do I become
a powerful person?
Please, tell me!
How do I become strong and
beautiful like you are?
You are plenty
beautiful already.
Moving forward,
you should focus on
training your body
and your magic.
You'll grow up to be powerful.
I'm sure of it.
When that happens,
I hope you'll join
the Magic Knights.
You think that I
could? Seriously?
I'll be waiting with
the Blue Rose Knights.
They didn't take you.
You're fine!
[SOL]
You!
Oh, Sol. I'm sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
I wasn't ever relying on you
to save me, you idiot.
I'm sorry you had to
see me looking so pitiful.
I thought I could finish
that bandit guy off
with a single shot, but I
guess I let my guard down.
Don't worry about it, though.
If they show up again,
I swear I'll keep you
and this village safe,
no matter what.
Of course.
Then it's decided. I'll get
stronger and stronger.
And I'll join the Magic Knights.
And then...
What was her name?
Ah, never mind.
Wait for me. Whoever you are!
Don't you have a reason
to overcome your narcissism
and win this fight?
Or are you weak?
[KIRSCH gasps]
[ASTA]
Crap! Missed again!
Hitting a tiny target is hard
enough, but at that speed,
I can't even sense their ki!
[MAGNA] I don't have some
kinda fancy schmancy
anti-magic sword like he does.
And I'm definitely no noble.
If I was, this
wouldn't be a problem
'cause I could fire off a
million high-powered spells.
But I do have this
sure-to-hit technical magic.
The blasts might be small.
But this is how I can
overcome him in a fight!
[ASTA yells]
Wait, wha--?
Finally. 'Bout time
I stopped one.
What's the matter?
Keep 'em comin', Magna!
Oh, you asked for it.
Feel the heat!
[MAGNA] Dang. He's putting
up a heck of a fight.
I'm barely scorin' any hits now.
[ASTA] I'm still letting
too many of them through.
Our crystal's not
looking too good.
Magna really is amazing!
That's such an intense matchup,
I can't take my eyes off them!
And it's only
going to get better.
Neither of those two
knows how to hold back.
Oh, man, I bet they're
having so much fun!
I can't wait to get
back out there!
Come on, guys,
finish up your match!
[MAGNA]
Asta.
You really are somethin',
ya stupid twerp.
Thank you.
For makin' not just me,
but all of us stronger,
ya little jerkwad!
But just so you know,
the final isn't gonna be
between you and that Yuno guy.
It's between me and Luck!
Seems you're forgetting
about this dashing mage!
Aw, man, I thought we
were done with this guy!
There we are.
It's criminal to mar
such a beautiful face.
And punishable by death!
[ASTA]
Yikes! Two against one?
Not good.
It looks like our crystal
could shatter any second!
What do I do?
Go after the flower guy.
Do it. Now!
[MAGNA]
[ZORA] It true that I
can't see your fireballs
until it's too late.
But a magic circle
on our crystal
means that doesn't matter.
[MAGNA] Ah! Think you can
defeat my magic, huh?
Well I'll just hit that
spell right back atcha.
[MAGNA yelps] Aw, man, not
again. Hit by my own spell!
Well, this just proves
that my magic is awesome.
Magic is the essence of beauty,
and that sword wipes it out.
This is appalling.
His power is an
afront to my senses!
I shall no longer
simply scorn you,
lowly commoner.
Instead, I shall destroy
every trace of you
and your crystal.
[ASTA]
Uh-oh!
If he goes any higher, forget
fighting off his blossoms.
I won't be able
to land any attack!
Our crystal will be history!
[KIRSCH]
I don't care how unseemly it is.
I'm using all my power!
What?
[KIRSCH]
Ensnared by some kind of magic?
[ZORA]
Bingo.
I set plenty of traps up
in the sky, too, by the way.
Maybe you should have
focused on your trademark
"magic sensing" instead
of talking trash.
[gasps] This will only
slow me for a moment.
[ASTA]
That's all I need to beat you!
[KIRSCH yelps]
Jeez, man. Knocked out
twice in one match?
[ZORA] You're gonna feel so
humiliated when you wake up.
[GOLEM growls]
[SOL]
It's payback time.
This is the end
of the line for you!
[gasps] Oh, no. The crystal!
[SOL] Uh... Huh? Hey!
What's goin' on, stupid?
We almost got them!
I did it. Just in time!
Whoa, nice one, Mimosa!
Hey! Wake up!
Do what I tell you to.
[yells]
[SOL]
Huh? No!
That's the opposite
of what I want!
Here we go!
[EMCEE MAGE]
Crystal destroyed!
[MAGIC KNIGHTS
gasping, murmuring]
[EMCEE MAGE]
Team B wins!
Whoa. Now that was a fun match.
Magna and Asta are both so cool!
Our boys really
hustled out there!
I guess, we'll have
to drink a toast to them
when this is all wrapped up.
[mumbling] Only real friends
can fight so earnestly.
Magna and Asta
are fight-friends!
Oh, heck yeah! We did it!
Nice job, snazzymask.
Not that I'm surprised,
because teamwork
always gets the job
done in a fight.
Aw, yeah, bring it in
for a high five.
[ZORA] So it all played out
like he thought it would.
Whatever.
It would've been
much easier to win
if you hadn't destroyed my
traps in the beginning, moron.
You're mad about that?
Can't we just high-five
this out, huh?
Please?
[ZORA]
You three.
Maybe you'd like a little
advice from the victors.
Let's see.
The Azure Amazon.
You're good, but you
got sloppy out there.
If you'd been a little more
attuned to the subtleties
of magic power, you
might not have lost.
This detonating delinquent
spent way too much
of his mana during the warm-up.
Maybe it's a habit
for commoners but,
you've gotta learn
how to say "when."
And there's you,
the royal narcissist.
You were far too arrogant
the entire time.
Falling to pieces just
because you got punched
by someone you see
as lower than you?
That makes you the
ugliest one of all.
What is with you?!
You're going way too far
with these burns again.
Wouldn't kill ya to be nicer.
[MIMOSA]
Brother.
Mimosa.
What you said back then.
Sometimes it is true
that a commoner's
impoverished condition can
lead their soul to ruin.
I agree.
[MIMOSA]
But, true beauty is something
even poverty can't take away.
It lives inside of them.
Avert your eyes.
You mustn't look
at me. I'm hideous.
[MIMOSA giggles] You did lose
in a rather unsightly manner.
But think about it:
not only did you accept
that commoners can be mighty,
you fought beside them,
getting yourself dirty.
Honestly, this is the most
beautiful you've ever been!
[KIRSCH gasps]
[KIRSCH] I certainly don't want
to admit this, but it's true.
[KIRSCH]
They really were gorgeous.
[growls] Royalty,
losing to these peasants?
How downright deplorable.
[EMCEE MAGE]
Next up. Round Two, Match Two.
Prepare yourselves!
[FINRAL]
It's my turn. And I won't lose.
You got that, Langris?!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[SOL]
"A Lover for Char."
Now. Let's see, which one
of these guys would I pick
to go on a romantic
date with Char.
Well, no one who's
shorter than her,
that's for sure.
And no lame gutter punks.
Can't be pairing her up with
anybody who's that gaudy.
Narcissists are a hard pass.
Quiet people wouldn't suit her.
And she'd never be able
to accept such a wimp.
The Wizard King does
seem like that rare,
acceptable man, but
he loves everybody.
Char needs someone
who'll love only her.
So, someone who's
taller than Char,
not a punk or gaudy
or a narcissist,
who can pleasantly chat
with her, is stronger,
and will love her and
her alone. Let's see,
there's got to be someone
I know who matches
that description perfectly.
The obvious choice
has gotta be me!
C'mere, Char!
[VANESSA] Finral's up
against his little brother,
Langris, in the next match.
Come on, Finral.
Believe in yourself!
Black Clover , Page 80:
"Special Little Brother
vs. Failed Big Brother."
Finral, you are not
gonna lose this one.