[DAZU]
Sorry to drop in on you.
You made all of these?
Wow, that's amazing!
[BOW]
It's nothing special, really.
It is! You're so talented!
Thank you, Dazu.
You're too kind.
[sighs] That's about the
extent of my magic power.
I think it's
wonderful! Be proud!
Thanks for having me.
Of course. I enjoyed it.
Goodbye, then.
Goodbye.
[DAZU, BOW]
Listen. We could do this again.
If you don't--
[DAZU giggles]
[BOTH]
All right.
[BOW]
Only one more ingredient.
Could you take over
for a moment, Dazu?
[BOW]
Here we are.
Just a dash of
mogro leaf powder.
[DAZU laughs nervously]
Stir it more gently.
Take your time. 'Kay?
Okay.
[BOW]
Much better.
Now they won't get chapped.
Thanks a lot, Bow.
Here. Your turn.
That should be good.
What would I do
without you, Dazu?
[BOTH laugh]
[BOW]
What happened?
It was their fault.
They kept asking me to show
them my Catalyst Magic.
They wanted me to fail
so they could laugh.
He looked worried
and asked if I was okay,
but I know he found it amusing.
That's how they are,
every one of them.
But you're different!
And so are you.
Ow.
Try to be strong.
It should heal up soon.
[DAZU]
Thank you.
[BOW]
Sure thing.
Hey. It's all right.
[DAZU] I always thought
I was alone in life.
But now, I realize
that's not true.
[DAZU] Since birth, I had lived
in a world where people like me
never saw the sunlight.
All of us were so weak,
and fragile, but...
Even so, we existed!
Great, now you're here!
Huh? You're the backup?
Well, yeah, I was
able to get here quicker
than anyone else,
so you're welcome.
[ASTA]
Thank you, sir!
Gotta say.
They've rounded up a bigger
crowd than I was expecting.
Listen up, Devil Believers.
We need to have a little chat.
[DAZU]
A chat?
[BOW]
We have nothing to say to you.
Aw, c'mon, don't be like that.
[MAN 147A] Isn't that guy
a Magic Knights Captain?
[MAN 147B]
I bet he's here to arrest us!
[WOMAN 147A]
We're right on the border,
does he have the
power to do that?
No way! I won't
let them take me!
Not now! I have to
make it into Spade!
So do I!
Keep moving!
[FOLLOWER 148A]
You'll never catch us!
[FOLLOWER 148B]
We're defecting to Spade!
Wait a sec. We're not
here to arrest you--
[BOW]
There's no time to delay.
[DAZU]
Right.
[DEMON MASK 142B]
C'mon!
Ow, that hurt.
[ASTA]
Noelle!
Nero!
[ASTA yells]
[DEMON MASK 142B]
After them!
[DAZU]
No.
[DEMON MASK 142B]
But...
[DAZU]
It's all right.
We still have the
five-leaf grimoire.
With this, we'll be fine.
Hey, Captain Yami!
[YAMI]
Gimme your hands.
[ASTA, NOELLE]
Huh?
So, boss. Are we gonna
go stop 'em or?
I don't see any
reason to hurry.
Oh, hey. Look up there.
A couple of little birdies
have come to our rescue.
[ASTA]
It's Captain Fuegoleon!
And, uh, that nice,
chubby guy who makes doors!
[NOELLE]
And there's my brother!
We're just in time.
Their numbers have increased.
[FUEGOLEON]
Everyone!
Please listen to
what we have to say!
[DAZU]
Listen to the Magic Knights?
Everyone, send me all your mana!
Concentrate!
Okay, Dazu!
Right! For Dazu!
Take mine, as well!
[DEMON MASK 142B]
To Dazu!
[DEMON MASK 142A]
[DEMON MASK 144AA]
To Dazu!
I had thought we might
get through to them,
but it seems not.
After the things
they've been through,
they're not likely to
trust the Magic Knights.
What now?
[BOW, DAZU gasp]
[roars]
What the hell?
[FUEGOLEON]
She's using Catalyst Magic.
It probably has an effect on the
mana in the surrounding area.
We're close to a
strong magic region.
Gathering everyone's
power must've summoned
this beast from there.
Thanks for the explanation.
Now. What to do?
[DAZU] I can't believe I was
able to bring that monster here.
If I can do that, then--!
[BOW]
Dazu!
[MAGNA]
Flame Magic: Exploding Fireball!
[yells]
[DAZU gasps]
[ASTA yells]
Are you okay?
[DAZU]
Um, yes.
[FOLLOWER 148BB grunts]
[SECREÉ]
Sealing Magic: Closed Sorrow.
You healed me!
[DAZU] They didn't rush toward
us to grab the grimoire.
They were trying
to save our lives!
Flame Magic: Ignis Columna!
Mercury Magic: Silver Bullets!
[ICE GIANT roars]
[YAMI]
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked,
Lightless Slash!
Mercury Magic:
Silver Shining Regal Spear!
Fall.
Flame Spirit Magic:
Salamander's Breath!
[YAMI]
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked,
Black Blade!
Well, looks like
he's had enough.
[FOLLOWER 148A]
Wow, they're so powerful!
[FOLLOWER 148B] So this is
what the Magic Knights can do.
[DAZU]
I don't believe it.
After all the magic
power I collected.
[FOLLOWER 148E]
It's over.
[FOLLOWER 148CC]
We've failed!
[FOLLOWER 148F]
We can't stand up to them!
[FOLLOWER 148DD]
All this for nothing!
[FOLLOWER 148G] How do you
think we'll be punished?
[YAMI]
Listen.
You guys have got
the wrong idea here.
[NOZEL] He's right,
it's not our intention
to take you into custody.
We just want to talk with you.
[FOLLOWER 148H]
Talk with us?
Roger-dodger, sir, I'll get
things rolling right away!
[FOLLOWER 148I]
Hey, wait a second.
Is that who I think it is?
[FOLLOWER 148J]
The Captain of the Golden Dawn!
[FOLLOWER 148EE]
That's him, William Vangeance!
The hero himself!
[DAMNATIO] Those who live
their lives in shadow.
[YAMI]
There's the man of the hour.
Thanks for fittin' us into
your busy schedule, hotshot.
I'll do anything
to aid this kingdom.
After all. I still
need to atone.
I'm glad you're here.
But did you really have to bring
the Honorable Judge
Stick-in-the-Mud, too?
You're one of our best.
Good thing you're safe.
[WILLIAM] We didn't come
here to punish anyone.
If I'm correct, you are heading
toward the Spade Kingdom.
But you haven't yet
crossed the border.
Which means that,
as of this moment,
you haven't committed a crime.
That said. If we asked
you to turn around
and go home,
I'm sure you'd refuse.
You may not realize it,
but we Magic Knights do
understand your plight.
So please, will you allow us
a bit of time to help you?
We'll do what we can
to assuage your doubts.
I don't know what to say.
[FOLLOWER 148GG]
We shouldn't trust them!
[FOLLOWER 148K] Tch. Why
would they care about us?
[FOLLOWER 148L]
He's right, they're just
a bunch of nobles and royalty!
But that's not--
[YAMI]
True, as you can see.
The Magic Knights have
got plenty of high-class,
highfalutin snobs on the
roster, but we're actually
a lot more of a mixed bag
than you might expect.
Just look at the Black Bulls.
We got an ex-con,
a guy whose folks
disowned him, a creepy loner,
a royal family's black sheep,
someone who was alone
for a real long time,
some commoners,
and don't forget me,
the foreigner.
When I came to this kingdom,
I couldn't even
speak the language.
I was totally cut off.
The point is,
I understand where you
guys are comin' from.
You've endured great injustice,
and that is what pushed
you over the edge.
We regret that we weren't able
to help you more in the past.
It wasn't because
we didn't care.
[NOELLE]
Nozel.
I swear to you all upon
the House of Vermillion.
If I can rid the world of this
imbalance, then I will do so!
Now, please return to your
homes and await the day
when we have fulfilled
this solemn promise.
Mark my words, the Magic
Knights will strive to shine
the light of hope
into the darkness!
[FOLLOWERS murmuring]
[FOLLOWER 148M]
Captain Vangeance!
[FOLLOWER 148HH]
Look at his face!
I am not so different from you.
I was treated terribly
because of my face.
Then I met the man we know
as the Wizard King.
Julius Novachrono.
He was kind enough
to take me in
and look past my
unsightly appearance.
He accepted me
just the way I was,
and gave me a place where
I could truly belong.
I owe all that I have
to Lord Julius,
and I'll follow his example!
We'll create a place
you can live happily,
where you can see the sunlight.
So, please, if you're
able to, just this one time,
I want you to believe
in the Magic Knights.
[BOTH gasp]
[FOLLOWER 148N]
That does sound good.
[FOLLOWER 148II]
If they're really going to help
make life better for us...
[FOLLOWER 148JJ]
Can't hurt to try.
[FOLLOWER 148O]
Yeah. I say we listen.
Let's trust them.
[FOLLOWER 148KK]
Okay.
[WILLIAM]
Now, then.
Dazu Tayak, Bow Nocde, and the
rest of the Devil Believers.
You're a separate matter.
You abducted two people.
Incited a riot in the capital.
[WILLIAM] And let's not
forget Kabwe Carillon,
Onoby Sinho, and Siona Caverly.
We suspect you may
have killed those three.
All right. That's
your cue, buddy.
[DAMNATIO]
For all these transgressions,
you are to be judged.
[GROUP gasps]
There's a heavy price for
the things you've done.
Very well. If you
want to arrest us...
...then I'll blow you all away!
[gasps]
Don't even waste your time.
But we came so far!
Yes, we did.
[DEMON MASK 142A]
Dazu.
I'm sorry, but who said anything
about arresting you two?
You think we'll simply
throw you in jail?
Foolish. As I told you,
my intention is to judge you.
Therefore, by my
righteous power...
I exile you from this land!
[BOTH gasp]
[GROUP gasps]
Ah! Righty-o, sir,
leave it to me!
Both of you, leave the
Clover Kingdom at once!
[DEMON MASK 144AA]
Dazu.
Where we go next is up to us.
It's our path.
We're done letting other people
decide our fate for us.
[DAMNATIO]
As you wish.
Does that mean...?
[DAZU]
Asta.
[ASTA]
My grimoire.
Hey! Wait up!
One day, I'm gonna
be the Wizard King!
And then I'll create
a new Clover Kingdom!
Better than what we have now!
A place where everyone
can understand each other
and laugh together!
So if you leave, promise me.
That whether you're near,
or far away, you'll be watching.
That way you'll know.
[DAZU]
Goodbye, Asta.
I wish that I could've
been more like you.
[DEMON MASK 144AA]
We're sorry.
Please tell Marie that, as well.
So, we're left with no
grimoire and no hostages.
All we have now is each other.
If we're being honest,
there's almost no chance of us
coming out of this alive.
But...
...despite all that, I...
[DEMON MASK 142A]
We should go.
[DEMON MASK 142B]
Right.
Yes.
We'll be joining them.
We're leaving this
kingdom. But still...
In the future,
if you fail to
create real change...
...this will happen again.
Other groups like us will rise
from the shadows. Over and over.
[DAZU]
Bow.
[BOW]
Dazu.
[DAMNATIO] The scales that
have tipped into darkness
must be balanced back
toward the light.
Isn't that right, Kabwe?
Justice should reign
supreme in this kingdom.
C'mon.
Okay.
[DAZU]
I have committed a sin.
Several, actually. That night,
I killed my husband
and my mother-in-law.
They were awful people.
In their hearts,
they always mocked me
and looked down upon me.
But, they never said
anything outwardly,
or let it show on their faces.
Truthfully, I could've
lived my whole life
pretending that I didn't notice.
But then...
[DAZU] Don't worry!
I'll save you, I swear!
Please, get us out.
And hurry, or we'll die!
Come on, Dazu.
Good-for-nothing wench!
[MESHU]
Dazu!
[DAZU]
I've had enough.
Just die.
[DAZU] I never felt an ounce
of regret over what happened.
I gave those two exactly
what they deserved.
[DAZU] I'm sure the burn
scar that I got from him
will fade as time goes by.
But, the scars on my heart from
enduring years of ridicule...
I'll probably have
those for life.
More than that, even
now that they're dead,
the flames of vengeance
that engulf my soul
will burn forever.
Which is why I--or, rather,
we must reach the
Spade Kingdom at any cost,
so that we can obtain
the devil's power.
[SECREÉ] This kingdom
is embroiled in chaos,
and the threat of
the devil still looms.
Black Clover , Page 149:
"Two Things We Need to Find."
It's always darkest
before the dawn.
Isn't that right, my prince?