[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[FUEGOLEON] Flame Creation
Magic: Leo Rugiens!
[cackles] Aw, is that
all you've got?
I have to say, Captain,
I'm very disappointed in you.
[RADES gasps]
[ASTA gasps]
[FUEGOLEON] When you attacked,
the mana grew thin
in some places across the
barrier for the briefest moment.
Those were the spots
I aimed for.
[ASTA]
Man, he's awesome!
[FUEGOLEON]
Listen to me, Rades.
You have incredible talent,
as well as powerful magic.
But wielded without
a just spirit,
they are no more than savagery.
You're a monster.
They were right to
have expelled you!
[RADES gasps]
[YUNO] I need to get
stronger so I can handle
something like this more easily.
[CATHERINE] It's a bit early
to be celebrating.
The preparations must be
nearly complete by now.
Time for a feast.
Such lively, young mana.
Absolutely, delicious.
[RADES]
What went wrong?
My power is great enough
to rival the strongest
mages in the kingdom.
[RADES] I've honed my magic,
studied the enemy,
made meticulous preparations.
Years of work, countless
hours of planning.
For this day. For this moment.
[RADES]
All wasted.
How did this happen?
[LEOPOLD yells]
Nice work. Thanks
for the shield.
Keep your thanks and
take care of him, already!
[LEOPOLD]
I'm on it!
[LEOPOLD yells]
[LEOPOLD]
Flame Magic: Spiral Flames!
[yells]
[pants]
It's over!
That pile of ash won't
give us any trouble now.
[laughs]
[groans]
Very well done, both of you!
You've shown your worth as
Magic Knights and as royalty.
[BOTH]
Sir!
What am I doing saluting him?
No. Impossible.
I'm stronger.
Royalty or not, nobody is
more powerful than I am!
You'll see!
Now, Flame Creation
Magic: Leo Palma.
Get these flames
off of me, damn you!
This isn't fair! It's
not over! I'll show you!
There are a great many
questions I would like to ask.
And you will answer.
But first, I'm going to take
a look at your grimoire.
[gasps] Wait, no!
[RADES]
That's mine! Don't touch it.
You have no right!
Interesting. It seems
unusually thin.
No! Leave it alone!
Unbelievable. It only
has one page!
Quit looking! Put it down now!
--That's mine!
--[FUEGOLEON] One page...
Does this mean he can
only wield a single spell?
[RADES] Give it back!
Haven't you done enough?
I don't need your mockery, too!
[ASTA] Mockery? I don't
hear anyone laughing.
I get that you wanted people
to take you seriously.
But I don't understand why
you had to do it like this.
You're strong, and you've
got a ton of magic power.
But now, all that strength
and power mean nothing.
You threw them away!
Come here. But try not
to get me all dirty.
Thanks, I'll do my best.
Perhaps you could have
become a great man
if you had gone down
a different path.
This is where the lack of
a just heart has led you.
You must atone.
[VALTOS]
Well? Are you satisfied.
[ASTA]
A voice?
What is it? What's wrong?
[VALTOS] I hope you've
at least learned a lesson.
Clearly, your might
alone was not enough
to defeat a squad captain.
No. I almost won. Really.
[VALTOS]
Sometimes you cannot win,
no matter how great your power.
My power, too, nears its limit.
No more acting on your own.
From now on, we proceed
according to plan.
For the Master's sake.
[CITIZEN 24A] Three cheers
for the Magic Knights!
[CITIZEN 24B] I knew you
would save us, thank you!
Now, then.
I can practically hear
dessert calling my name.
Would you care to
come along? [giggles]
I'll pass, thank you.
A nice, hot bath sounds awesome
right about now, huh, Char?
Heavenly.
[CITIZEN 24C] Good job,
Blue Rose Knights! Thank you!
Captain Charlotte is
just so amazing!
Not to mention beautiful, too!
Sol is cooler, though.
[laughs]
[NOZEL] I have a feeling
this isn't over.
What do they want?
[sighs]
[VALTOS] Excellent. They're
all in the designated areas.
[gasps]
[YUNO]
My grimoire.
[gasps]
Magic?
[VALTOS] Allow me to
thank you for your service,
Magic Knights.
What the--
Look out!
[yelps] How?
Where did the Magic Knights go?
They disappeared
completely. But how?
Sol's gone!
[HAMON]
Oh, heavens. Where are we?
I would estimate that
we're at least a few
hundred kilometers from
the royal capital,
judging by the terrain here.
They sent us away?
That's not nice!
Our enemy has taken
things a step further.
I knew there was a
strong Spatial Magic user
working with them,
but even so...
To do this?
Transporting us all would
require great skill.
[ALECDORA]
We have failed!
Something's wrong.
Where'd the other
Magic Knights' mana go?
I don't know, but I
can't sense it either.
[FUEGOLEON]
I want to know how
you carried out this attack.
Where are the others
you're working with?
[RADES chuckles]
Um, does anyone know
what's happening?
Something is definitely wrong.
Those idiots fell for it
hook, line, and sinker.
It was almost too easy.
And these are the greatest
mages in the country?
How utterly pathetic.
I was going to play
with any of the Knights
who escaped, but I suppose
I won't get to now.
Oh, well.
This place is full
of young mana.
Time to start harvesting.
Ash Curse Magic:
Ash Absorbing Formation.
[CITIZENS gasp, yelp]
What is happening?
[CITIZENS screaming]
[giggles] Much better.
Thanks to your
generous donations,
I can feel myself
growing younger already.
Who knew that skin
could be this smooth?
[CITIZENS panting, yelping]
No, please!
Just let us go!
You think you're so
sweet and cute, don't you?
Well, you're not. Sow!
[CITIZENS screaming]
[yelping]
[laughs]
Eliza! No! Eliza!
Oh, my.
Now there's a
fine-looking specimen.
Tell me, my dear,
am I beautiful?
Care to take a guess
at my age? I'm waiting.
Uh. What have you done?
You're some kind of monster!
No one calls me
a monster. No one!
What have we here?
It looks like one of the
Knights managed to escape
the Spatial Magic after all.
Ooh, and lucky for me,
this one's a beauty.
What do you say we have
some fun together, lovely?
I'm not gonna let you hurt
any more of these
people. You old hag.
[CATHERINE]
You're dead.
Ooh, and lucky for me,
this one's a beauty.
What do you say we have
some fun together, lovely?
I'm not gonna let you hurt
any more of these
people. You old hag.
[CATHERINE]
You're dead.
How dare you call me an old hag?
Ash Curse Magic:
Cheerful Ash Destruction.
These little shells
contain all kinds
of lovely curses.
The best part is you won't know
what they'll do
until they hit you.
Who are you and
why are you here?
What are you people
hoping to accomplish?
[CATHERINE] Ah, so you have
enough breath to chat,
do you? Very well.
Your pretty face has
earned you an answer.
Our mission is
relatively simple.
There's a certain someone
we mean to get rid of.
And who would that be?
Oh, come now, you
don't honestly think
I would tell you.
Right! Good looks
only get you so far.
[FUEGOLEON] There's at least
one other involved
in this plot besides you.
This invasion required
the use of Spatial Magic
on an immense scale.
So, tell me, where
is your partner?
Have they escaped already?
[FUEGOLEON]
They may have managed to send
the Magic Knights away
from the capital,
but that doesn't mean they
have the power necessary
to capture it.
Nor do I believe this
to be something as simple
as a feint to reach the king.
You've made it clear
your personal motive
is revenge, but I sense that
there was a larger purpose
behind the attack.
[laughs]
You want to know
what we're after?
You, Fuegoleon Vermillion.
We came for you.
For me?
But why him?
Yes, why?
Spatial Magic again,
eh? Very well.
Maybe now we'll get
to the bottom of this.
[LEOPOLD]
Fuegoleon!
[FUEGOLEON]
Strange. What is this place?
[grunts]
[YUNO grunts]
[YUNO]
Her attacks just keep coming,
and she isn't tiring at all.
The shells themselves
don't do much damage,
but what's inside them...
[YUNO grunting]
Oh, dear! Look at you flail.
Which of my curses has its
grip on you now, I wonder?
You don't seem to be
so chatty anymore.
Damn you.
[YUNO]
My eyes. I can barely see now.
It's not just my vision.
All of my senses are fading.
Say, can you hear me? Hello?
[laughs]
[YUNO]
My hearing's almost gone now.
What kind of power
does this woman have?
Are you enjoying my
Cheerful Ash Destruction spell?
It works slowly but
quite effectively.
It looks like you've
lost your vision,
and your hearing too,
I would guess.
Soon you won't even be
able to move. [laughs]
Sensory deprivation and
the fear that comes with it.
That's your punishment
for calling me an old hag.
[YUNO]
The four-leaf clover.
I joined the Golden Dawn to
live up to the expectations
that came with this grimoire.
[CATHERINE laughing]
[YUNO] But, what happens
if I never can?
[GOLDEN DAWN MEMBER 24A]
Four-leaf clover or not,
you're still just a
commoner. Don't get cocky.
[ALECDORA] Hmph. Your skills
merit little attention
in the Golden Dawn, village boy.
[GOLDEN DAWN MEMBER 24B]
Soon enough,
no one will remember your name.
[YUNO] I ignored the
people who doubted me.
Instead, I honed my skills
and worked to make myself
unbeatable. Except...
I couldn't win. It wasn't
me who defeated him.
It was a power buried
in that dungeon.
One I just happened
to stumble across.
A power I can't control.
No matter what I do,
I can't get it to listen to me.
I couldn't even evade the
Spatial Magic on my own.
I escaped because
the power reacted.
A power I can
hardly call my own.
[ALECDORA]
His work may be sub-par,
but it's not as if we
expect much of a commoner.
[YUNO]
No, that's not it.
I don't care what they say.
That's not what
really frustrates me.
[YUNO yells]
[laughs] Was that supposed
to be aimed at me?
Here, let me show you how
to aim a spell properly.
I'll make you a deal.
Grovel for me.
I might let you live
if it's good enough.
Let's see how prettily
you beg. Well?
Not a chance.
[YUNO]
Blind. I can't see anything.
[YUNO] Numb, too.
I can't feel anything.
[YUNO]
Is this the manastream?
[NARRATOR]
Mages who wield wind-based magic
are particularly skilled
at sensing mana.
The enemy's attack deprived
Yuno of his senses.
However, with all other
distractions taken away,
his sensitivity to mana
became even more heightened,
and made possible
what came next.
Come on now, open that
stubborn mouth of yours.
I'm not going to wait
forever, you know.
Hurry up, or I'll have
to kill you. [laughs]
There are so many things
I want to know about you.
So, let's hear you beg.
Well? Well?
I don't hear you.
[YUNO]
Please. Just shut up.
I don't care about you
or what you want.
Only one thing
matters to me now.
I can't lose.
[YUNO gasps]
[YUNO]
Not to Asta.
I'm not done!
[CATHERINE]
Is that what I think it is?
The legendary four-leaf
clover grimoire?
[CATHERINE]
The mana. It's gathering.
It feels like...
No, impossible.
Is he... controlling the mana?
[YUNO]
I see now.
The spirit has been
sending out mana signals
this whole time.
But I relied too much
on my vision and hearing,
so I wasn't able to sense them.
There's just one
very important thing
to know about me.
The truth is...
I would rather give
my life than lose!
Wind Spirit Magic:
Sylph's Breath!
[CATHERINE] One chance.
I have to use the power I stole.
[CATHERINE screams]
It's you!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[YUNO]
"Birthday."
I finally figured out how
to command the wind spirit.
I've decided to name you Bell
and make today your birthday.
I got you a cake and everything.
Yay!
[YUNO]
There's just one candle.
I hope that's okay.
Hooray. Happy birthday, Bell.
Pretty!
Go on, make a wish,
then blow it out.
[BELL]
Well, um.
Ah!
[BELL]
Huh? Where did the cake go?
I found it.
[LEOPOLD]
Where did you send my brother?
Answer me if you wanna live.
[LEOPOLD gasps] Fuegoleon,
what happened to you?
Brother!
Black Clover ,
Page 25: "Adversity."
Always remember to
stay calm. [screams]