[NARRATOR] Asta, Noelle,
and Magna travelled
to Saussy Village to
rid the area of boar.
There, they encountered
a mysterious foe.
Though the three Magic Knights
fight bravely to
protect the villagers
from the enemy's
vicious attacks,
his magic power is far too great
for even their
strongest efforts.
So, it can not
only cancel magic--
that sword of yours can
reflect it, as well.
But you're a fool if you
think that will defeat me.
I can create wave after
wave of icy fangs.
Go on. Let's see
you protect them.
[yells]
[MAGNA]
Damn this guy!
Asta and I have our hands full
keeping the villagers safe.
What's more, my magic
is startin' to run out.
This is turning out to be
a hell of a first
mission for those two.
Things are goin' south quick.
But if all that was enough
to make me give up,
I wouldn't be a man! Here we go!
Your fellow commoner
is gonna keep you
safe and sound!
[NOELLE]
What's wrong with me?
Even though I'm royalty...
Even though I have more
magic power than anyone here...
Stay behind us, Noelle!
[NOELLE] I'm only
holding the others back.
[LOU] Miss Magic Knight,
please help us!
We need you!
[gasps]
[NOELLE] This little girl
is looking me in the eye
and begging for help.
I have to protect her!
I won't run! Never!
[NOELLE]
That looks like... a new spell?
[NOELLE] Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Lair!
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[NARRATOR] A grimoire evolves
along with its owner,
new spells appearing as
the mage grows stronger.
This growth chiefly
refers to an increase
in magic power through training
or to improved handling
of said magic power.
However, it may also occur
in cases of heightened
or altered emotions, or
accompany great determination.
[NOELLE] I will protect
them. I am royalty.
What's more,
I am a member
of the Black Bulls!
[gasps]
[LOU]
You're amazing!
[VILLAGERS gasping, yelling]
Well, that wasn't
so difficult, after all.
[MAGNA]
That is one serious spell.
There, see?
You'll never know
what you're capable of
until you're willing
to give it a try.
That's impossible.
How can she have so much power?
[NARRATOR] On the sidelines,
the beast was watching.
Waiting for his
chance to strike.
To seize the enemy
by the throat.
[ASTA yells]
[NARRATOR]
And in that moment...
[HEATH]
Consider yourself.
You have enough magic power to
have joined the Magic Knights.
I don't have a single
drop of magic power.
But that doesn't matter.
I'll still destroy you!
[BOTH]
No! Master Heath!
That's what I'm talkin' 'bout!
Did... he get him?
[gasps]
[HEATH chuckles]
[ASTA] Oh, no. I slipped on his
ice and killed my momentum!
That sword of yours may
be able to nullify magic,
but that can only go so far
when it's wielded
by an ordinary human.
Now it's my turn to
take a stab at you.
[gasps]
[HEATH] Sleep, little fool.
For all eternity.
[MAGNA gasps]
Asta.
[HEATH] There is tremendous
magic power behind this spell.
Still, it's just
a matter of time.
I ought to be able
to create an entrance
wide enough for at least
one person to pass through.
[NOELLE gasps]
This should take
approximately 25 seconds.
[HEATH] You pesky creatures
certainly do enjoy
wasting my time, don't you?
But, oh, the price you will pay.
[pants]
[MAGNA] I don't have
much magic power left,
but I can't give up.
Flame and ice.
Going by our magics' attributes,
I have the upper hand.
Still...
The difference in
our power is enough
to flip that on its head.
We picked the wrong
guy to take on.
Sorry, Yami, sir,
but I think this may be
one fight that I can't win.
I'm not done yet!
Too late.
[gasps]
Asta!
So, that last strike
didn't kill you off.
You're a tough little idiot.
However, your wounds
will make swinging
that sword difficult.
[ASTA]
I'm not done!
And I'm no boar to be pinned.
[ASTA screams]
[grunting]
[ASTA]
I'm not done yet! Got that?
Hmph. How persistent.
But you're gonna regret
wasting my time.
[FRIEND 10A]
You're amazing, Magna!
[VILLAGERS laughing]
[FRIEND 10B]
Never thought I'd see the day!
I can't believe there's gonna be
a real Magic Knight from
sleepy little Rayaka.
From street thug to the
village's golden boy!
[FRIEND 10A]
Let's give 'im a cheer!
[VILLAGERS]
Magna! Magna! Magna!
[SEIHI]
Really? You did it, huh?
Wonderful! I knew that
you could make the cut.
Yeah.
This means you're not just
some street punk anymore.
Well, go on, take it.
Uh, thanks.
Whatcha think?
[SEIHI] Mm-hm. It looks
good on you, all right.
Now, go be the man
I know you can be.
Right!
I've got this.
I'll do it, Seihi.
I'm not going to give up yet.
[MAGNA grunts]
[MAGNA] A real man hangs on
till the bitter end.
Noelle. This spell of yours.
We can get outside of it
easily enough, right?
Well, yes, I would imagine so.
You stay here and look after
the villagers, got it?
Hey! What are you doing?
You stand no chance
of prevailing against me.
Why not accept that and give up?
If I gave up now, then who
would protect them?
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[ASTA]
I realized something.
[HEATH]
Hm?
Sooner or later, I'm going
to be the Wizard King.
But it's not just about
keeping a promise.
It's about keeping people safe!
You think you'll be
the Wizard King?
What an utterly
ridiculous dream.
Especially considering that
you'll be dead in one minute.
[MAGNA]
That's not gonna happen, Frosty.
If you wanna go
after him, just try it.
I'll give ya fair
warning, though.
In order to do that,
you gotta go through me!
What are you doing, Magna?
[MAGNA laughs]
You and me--
we're the real men here, Asta.
Reckless fool.
Going out of your way
to die an early death.
You have 30 seconds.
[MAGNA]
Bring it on! You ready, Asta?
Time for a baptism.
[gasps]
[MAGNA]
Here we go.
All the magic power
I've got left!
Now, my Soul Ball.
[MAGNA] Flame Magic:
Prison Death Scattershot!
[MAGNA yells]
[HEATH] This is the final
spell of your pathetic life?
What a complete waste.
[MAGNA grunts]
[HEATH]
Your time is up.
[ASTA]
You wish!
[HEATH]
That wasn't the real attack.
He's reflecting the spell.
I'm alive.
[NOELLE] Hmph. You can
thank me for it later,
lowly street punk.
[NOELLE]
Oh, my gosh, I did it!
I actually controlled
my magic power!
Never can keep your
mouth shut, can ya?
[gasps]
[HEATH]
These flames...
They aren't going out.
No matter. I'll
just freeze them.
[yells]
[ASTA]
Not done yet!
[HEATH gasps]
[ASTA] As long as I can
still move, I'm not done!
No. You can't.
Like hell!
[ASTA yells]
[gasps]
[HEATH]
These flames...
They aren't going out.
No matter. I'll
just freeze them.
[yells]
[ASTA]
Not done yet.
[HEATH gasps]
[ASTA] As long as I can
still move, I'm not done!
No. You can't.
[ASTA]
Like hell!
[ASTA yells]
[HEATH]
No... Impossible...
Me? Bested?
And by this... boy?
If only I could have been
more use to the master, but...
[VILLAGERS gasping]
He did it.
[LOU]
Are we safe?
[NOELLE]
Yes. He can't hurt you now.
It's over.
What started as Flame Magic:
Prison Death Scattershot,
will now become
Flame Binding Magic:
Flame Bondage Formation!
You're better at this than
you look like you'd be,
I can give you
that much, anyway.
How 'bout you shut that
royal mouth of yours
and quit looking down
on your superior!
Once again, you just
happen to be below me, so...
[ASTA]
Magna, sir!
[MAGNA, NOELLE gasp]
[growls]
[NOELLE]
Seems, your follow-through
leaves much to be desired, sir.
Uh--
[VILLAGERS yelp]
It's freezing!
[MAGNA laughs] Oh, ho-ho! What
was that about follow-through?
I can't believe
one of 'em got away!
How'd that happen? Dammit!
[ASTA]
How do ya like that?
I may be a commoner, but I won!
Yeah! How do you like that, huh?
[VILLAGERS gasp]
Hey, man, are you all right?
[snoring]
[MAGNA]
Sleeping? Seriously?
He is such a fool,
and a reckless one, at that.
An idiotic, obnoxiously
loud commoner.
But, he's also kind of amazing.
[ASTA snoring]
He saved us.
I thought we were done for.
He's still just a kid, too.
[VILLAGER 9A]
Do ya think he's really
just a commoner like us?
Thanks, Magna.
And you, miss. For everything.
Sure, that's why we're here.
We're simply doing our duty.
[VILLAGER 9C] Still, we'll never
forget what you did for us.
[VILLAGER 9C]
Wha--? An anti-bird?
[NOELLE]
Huh?
[MAGNA] Hey, about time you
woke up, you sadistic jerks.
And now...
We just gotta wait till
my power comes back.
When it does, Crazy Cyclone's
hauling you to the capital.
Hmph.
You're gonna pay, I promise you.
You'll spend the
rest of your lives
makin' up for what
you did today.
[HEATH] This spell of his
appears to be blocking my magic.
Just wait, you're gonna
spill everything.
Who you people are,
what you're after.
The Magic Knights'll
get every last
scrap of information outta you!
[HEATH]
They will not.
The end times are upon us.
[NOELLE, ASTA gasp]
[MAGNA] He's got a
Magic Item inside him?
Engage Ice Magic: Ice Burial.
[ASTA, MAGNA, NOELLE gasp]
They were willing
to go that far?
Must've sworn some serious
loyalty to someone.
[growls] What was he thinking?
[MAGNA] To sacrifice
them all like that...
What was his game, anyway?
[ASTA]
How could they?
Treating life like it's
something to throw away.
Like death is nothing.
I'll never understand
these people.
Not in a million years!
[NICK]
Grandpa...
We should go home
now. Please, Nick.
[NICK]
In a bit, okay?
Grandpa always liked
the view from up here.
Yeah. I heard what
happened. What Seihi did.
He fought those men.
He did what he could
to protect the village.
[NICK]
Uh-huh.
[SEIHI grunts]
[yells]
[panting]
Your grandpa was amazing.
He was a real man.
[NICK] You should've heard
him tell the story
about gambling in the capital.
He was so happy, 'cause he
had beaten some Magic Knights.
Yeah.
He even used some of the
money to buy presents,
and he brought lots
of yummy food
for everyone in the
village to share.
[NICK]
He never got to become one,
but Grandpa would've loved
to be a Magic Knight
more than anything in the world.
Yeah, I know.
[NICK] And, he regretted
it his whole life.
What did he regret?
[NICK] He said he should've
worked harder when he was young,
then maybe his dream
would've come true.
Nick...
[NICK sniffles] But, even
though he didn't make it in,
he was happy 'cause
you worked hard enough
for the both of you.
Yeah.
Magna.
Could I...
Do you think...
Can I be a Magic Knight,
too, someday?
Of course you can!
[gasps]
Just remember,
nothing's impossible.
You can do anything, Nick.
Your future's what
you make of it.
He's totally right.
I mean, I'm a commoner
with no magic power,
and look at me now.
A knight! It won't be easy.
Get ready to sweat!
You're gonna have to work hard.
And always do your best.
Just wait, by the time you
get into the Magic Knights,
I'll have worked even harder,
accomplished even more,
and gotten even closer to
becoming the Wizard King.
Please, let's not get
into that nonsense again.
But, hey, point is, dream big.
That's what a real man does.
We'll be waiting
for you. Got it?
Yeah!
Good!
[BOTH chuckle]
[ASTA grunts]
[screams]
[ASTA] Just what do you have
against my head, featherbrain?
Oh, it's on now! I'll get you!
[ASTA]
What's that stone?
Hey, I recognize that.
It's the charm Grandpa used
to carry around with him.
Give it back, you,
this is something special.
Come on, bird, just let it go.
What d'you even need a rock for?
[laughs]
It's okay.
Your bird can keep
it if he wants to.
It's the least I can do
after how you saved us.
Yeah? Okay, thanks.
[NOELLE]
Just look at those hateful eyes.
He is so adorable!
You could sit on me
if you'd like.
[ASTA]
Hm?
[ASTA yelling]
Not again!
Quit pecking me, psycho-bird!
What'd I do to you?
Hey, get back here!
I'm gonna fry you up for dinner!
[ALL chuckle]
[ASTA screams]
Just leave me alone!
[LOU, NICK, NOELLE, MAGNA laugh]
[FIGURE]
So that's what Heath chose.
Very well.
And the magic stone is now in
the hands of the Black Bulls?
Yes, sir.
No matter.
The Black Bulls
won't be an issue.
We can deal with
them at any time.
They can keep the magic stone
until we are ready
to retrieve it.
[FIGURE]
Not long now.
The resurrection
is close at hand.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[NARRATOR]
"The Spitting-est Image"! Go!
And the winner is...
[NARRATOR]
This anti-bird!
[NOELLE, ASTA, MAGNA]
What?!
[SEIHI] Just look how far
you've come, Magna!
You're not just some punk
anymore, you're a man!
You're on fire, shining bright!
Black Clover , Page 11:
"What Happened on a Certain
Day in the Castle Town."
My magic is never giving up!