[NARRATOR] Within the clover's
fifth leaf there lives a devil.
Asta, born unable
to harness mana,
was granted the power
of Anti-magic
from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability
to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members
of Spade Kingdom's
Dark Triad also possess
powers from the devils
of the underworld and used them
to launch an invasion on
the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from
his belief in himself
and from the support
of his friends,
Asta continues to fight
for the safety of this world.
Don't flatter yourself.
The key to the underworld
isn't you, per se.
It's a magical channel
that's known as
the Tree of Qliphoth.
[NARRATOR] Dante revealed that
creating the Tree of Qliphoth
would require the use of both
Dark Magic and World Tree Magic.
[YAMI]
No more chit-chat.
I'm taking you down
here and now!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
all over the Heart Kingdom,
the battles against Vanica's
Dark Disciples raged on.
[LUCK]
True Lightning Magic: Ceranos!
[NARRATOR] First, Luck defeated
the Skin Magic user, Svenkin.
Next...
[CHARMY]
Food Magic: Glutton's Banquet!
[WOLF growls]
--[WOLF] Down the hatch!
--[HALBET screams]
[NARRATOR] Using the Mana Method
to give her Food Magic a boost,
Charmy brought down Halbet,
wielder of Hair Magic.
The only way to get
true beauty and strength
is from a balanced diet!
[SIVOIR]
What?
Where did that enormous
array come from?
[LEOPOLD]
I endured you so that I could
take my time creating it!
True Flame Magic:
Crimson Eruption!
[NARRATOR] Leopold, who had
obtained True Flame Magic
thanks to the Mana Method,
defeated the Eye Magic
user named Sivoir.
[LEOPOLD] If you're not tough
enough to handle getting burned,
then don't play with an inferno!
[SIVOIR screams]
[NARRATOR] Hischer and his
Nail Magic were eliminated
by the Spirit Guardian Gaja.
[GAJA] You're finished
here, Dark Disciple.
[ROBERO cackles]
[ROBERO grunts]
[MIMOSA] Plant Magic:
Magic Cannon Flower!
Serves you right
for being creepy!
[NARRATOR]
Queen Loropechika was confronted
by Tongue Magic user Robero.
And, just as Mimosa
stopped him...
[VANICA]
Yoo-hoo!
Happy to see me,
little Loropechika?
I've gotta say, this is
getting really dull.
With the Dark Triad
out there on the offensive,
it's been pretty quiet here.
Yeah. Oh, there is one thing!
I'm not sure if you heard
this already, but apparently
we may have a spy from the
Clover Kingdom in our midst.
[laughs] Don't be ridiculous!
There's nobody stupid
enough to try that!
[GUARD 165B laughs]
You're right.
[GUARD 165C]
You there.
These are Lord Dante's quarters.
You shouldn't be here.
Unless... you were the spy
I've heard so much about.
What do you say you and I
have a little chat downstairs?
[GUARD 165C]
What?
Where did you go?
[GUARD 165C gasps]
[GUARD 165C screams]
There's my Loropechika!
Oh, and there's no reason
for you girls to be so guarded,
she and I go way back.
I only cursed you last time
because Megicula said to.
Anyway, this should
be a fun visit!
[NOELLE]
She's possessed by Megicula.
That must mean she's
Vanica of the Dark Triad!
She's the one who
killed my mother!
If it's just me you're after,
then why attack Heart?
You didn't have to get
innocent people
involved in all this chaos!
Oh, it's simple, really.
I knew that would make you
want to fight me even more!
[LOROPECHIKA gasps]
[NOELLE]
She's heartless!
[NOELLE] Well, you'd better
be prepared to deal with us,
because we wiped
out your minions!
You're the only one left!
Yeah? So, you defeated
all of them?
[ROBERO giggles]
Oh, boy.
That sure was a great warm-up!
[ALL gasp]
[MIMOSA]
What? My magic should've
rendered him unconscious!
I don't think I'll ever be able
to thank you
enough, Lady Vanica.
Because of you, I feel
neverending pleasure--
[ROBERO screams]
[BOTH gasp]
Shut up already.
Take care of these
annoying little bugs
so I can be alone
with Loropechika.
--[ROBERO whimpering]
--[thudding]
[gasps]
[ROBERO giggles]
I beg you.
Please step on me
more, Lady Vanica!
See that?
Thanks to the curse
I put on them,
no matter how many times you
kill them, they just won't die!
[HISCHER] Where do you
think you're going?
You're still alive?
[HISCHER]
Of course.
We've only just begun trampling
your poor little kingdom.
Long live Lady Vanica!
[gasps]
[LOROPECHIKA]
So, the rest of them!
[laughs] That's the
power of love!
All hail Lady Vanica!
[SIVOIR]
You little rat.
How dare you make me suffer
the first pain of my life?
After I was hand-selected
by Lady Vanica herself!
I am a woman of beauty!
I should never have
been put through
such a disgraceful
ordeal as that!
And so, with the
eternal gorgeousness
given to me by Lady Vanica,
I shall destroy everything!
Why does it take them so long
to do their dumb speeches?
He, he.
[ALL]
Okay, bring on round two!
As I told you,
you will be stopped.
[VANICA]
Sorry, but unless you defeat me,
they'll keep coming
back to life forever.
And they won't lay off until
your whole kingdom is dead.
So, you are ready to play!
Took long enough.
Loropechika! Let's go!
Right!
Noelle! That's our cue!
Let's do it!
Water Creation Magic:
Valkyrie Armor!
[ALL]
We're going to take you down!
[NOELLE] Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Roar!
[VANICA]
Blood Magic: Red Beast.
That's your best technique?
It's just a worm.
[MIMOSA screams]
[ROBERO laughs]
Just let me play with you.
I promise it'll be lots of fun!
I snuck in a few seeds for
my magic-controlling weeds
when I threw that
last attack at you!
[ROBERO] So I can't move, but
then again, neither can you!
Mimosa!
Leave the toad to me--
you guys focus on taking down
the devil-possessed one!
[BOTH gasp]
[ROBERO groans]
[ROBERO laughs]
Oh, Lady Vanica, both of your
magic abilities are great!
Curse-Warding and Blood Magic.
It's just like Loropechika
told us before!
[NOELLE]
Loropechika! Anyone home?
Oh, yes, hello, I'm here!
Apologies, everyone.
I was checking on something.
[NOELLE]
Seriously?
Because it looked like
you were spacing out.
Now what was that about Spade?
Right, I was just
getting to that!
Each member of the Dark Triad
has a combination
of two different
magic attributes.
Their own and the one
their devil has.
When it comes to Vanica,
I've fought her
and Megicula before,
so I will come up with
a perfect strategy.
[LOROPECHIKA]
We'll train with that in mind!
[VANICA giggles]
Nice one, Loropechika!
I wonder if Dante and Zenon
are having as much fun as me!
Nah, whatever those two are
doing, this is ten times better!
'Cause Loropechika's here,
and I can kill her if I want to!
Sorry, that won't
be happening today.
Because I'm here, too!
[gasps]
I guess it'd be cool
to have Dark Magic
and World Tree Magic.
But if you ask me, it sounds
like it'd be too much of a pain
to drag those two
back alive! [laughs]
[NOELLE]
Wait, Dark Magic?
What do you mean by
"dragging them back?"
What are you guys
plotting? Tell me now!
Ugh. Do you honestly believe
I'm going to tell you anything?
[LOROPECHIKA]
World Tree Magic.
Dark Magic.
[NARRATOR] The Queen of
the Heart Kingdom inherits
the previous queens' powers,
as well as their knowledge
and experiences.
Here, inside
Loropechika's mind,
is where that colossal mountain
of information materializes.
It is because of this place
that the queen is called
the "All-Knowing Priestess."
[LOROPECHIKA gasps]
It's so cruel.
Loropechika!
[LOROPECHIKA]
Listen, Noelle.
If we let the Dark Triad
have their way,
they're going to open
the door to the underworld
and release the devils,
killing more
than 90 percent of the
people on this continent.
And the world will end!
But that's insane!
[gasps]
It's so cruel.
Loropechika!
[LOROPECHIKA]
Listen, Noelle.
If we let the Dark Triad
have their way,
they're going to open
the door to the underworld
and release the devils,
killing more
than 90 percent of the
people on this continent.
And the world will end!
But that's insane!
How can you do
something like this?
So many people will die!
Yes, but the ones left
behind will be strong,
and my blood will boil
along with theirs!
What's the big deal if
the weaker ones die off?
Anyway, forget about the
future--let's enjoy the now!
Enough!
We can't allow monsters like you
to roam free in this land!
Which is why we will defeat
you once and for all!
[LOROPECHIKA]
The fate of existence itself
is in our hands.
Mana Zone plus Mana Method.
Water Spirit Magic...
[LOROPECHIKA]
...Ludic Sanctuary!
With this technique,
your Blood Magic's efficacy
will be cut in half.
And Noelle's water-based attacks
will increase in power!
Stronger. I need to be stronger!
What now?
The lighter your armor is,
the more easily
you can become one
with the water!
[gasps]
[LOROPECHIKA] This should also
help you move more fluidly!
You'll be swifter
than ever before!
[NOELLE]
Valkyrie Armor: Mermaid Form!
You've destroyed so much.
But the damage stops
right here and now!
[LOROPECHIKA gasps]
[giggles] Well,
just look at you!
It's so cute that little
Loropechika found a buddy!
This'll be double
the fun for me!
[gasps]
[VANICA]
Try not to die too fast.
Devil Power,
50-percent strength!
[LOROPECHIKA] Her blood
can't harden as easily,
but that's not slowing her down!
I knew it. We can't win
with normal attacks!
Noelle!
[giggles]
[laughing]
All right, now things
are getting real!
Fifty-one percent!
[NOELLE]
She only went up by one percent,
but she's so much stronger!
All you think about
is satisfying
your own twisted desires!
[laughing] Fifty-two percent!
You don't even think about
the people you've hurt!
You killed my mother, Acier
Silva of the Clover Kingdom!
[VANICA]
Fifty-three percent!
Yeah, who's that?
Talking about the past
is pointless and boring!
Let's enjoy the
moment, shall we?
[ROBERO laughs]
I wish you'd give up
and take your licks
already, pretty girl.
Thanks to Lady Vanica, we're
never gonna die, remember?
We've trained so hard.
Trust me, there's no way we'll
be defeated by the likes of you!
[MIMOSA]
Not just for the world.
[NOELLE] Not just to avenge
the death of my mother.
[MIMOSA grunts]
[MIMOSA] You really are
incredible, Loropechika!
With your help, our magic
will be unstoppable!
[NOELLE]
Uh, yeah, sure.
I guess you had
something to do with it.
Well, what did you expect?
Loropechika's that amazing!
Oh, no, not at all!
I'm not special.
Forget the modesty,
it comes off as fake.
But I'm only this capable
because I inherited
all of my abilities and
mana from the queens
who ruled the Heart
Kingdom before me.
Even so, your powers
are unbelievably great!
They can't be inherited
by just anyone, dear.
[LOROPECHIKA] Because
I'm so clumsy and goofy,
I can't help but wonder
to myself sometimes.
Am I really worthy
of the crown I wear?
[LOROPECHIKA]
Last time, when I fought Vanica
and the devil Megicula,
I was scared.
And because of that,
I was cursed.
I'm unfit to be a queen.
[LOROPECHIKA laughs]
But when I'm with you,
I forget about my status
and things like that.
I feel like I can be honest.
I wonder why.
What I'm about to tell you
will probably make me seem
even more undeserving.
[LOROPECHIKA]
But...
But I'm so afraid!
I don't want to die!
As the queen, I'm supposed
to be so much stronger
and more responsible,
but... I...
Ah! I do apologize.
A queen should never cry
in front of others.
[NOELLE] Oh, come on!
That's not true at all.
[gasps]
It's okay for you to cry.
Especially with friends.
Exactly.
Thank you, Noelle. Mimosa.
--[LOROPECHIKA yelps]
--[thud]
[NOELLE] How did you trip with
both of us holding you?
[MIMOSA laughs]
[MIMOSA] No matter what,
we're going to win this fight!
[MIMOSA]
For Loropechika!
[NOELLE]
For our precious friend!
We're at 65 percent!
Sixty-six percent!
Sixty-seven percent!
[laughs] Are you ready
for the big one?
Here we go!
You get my best! Lucky you!
Here's 70-percent power!
Do it, Noelle!
We were waiting for this!
We need Vanica to use
the highest percentage
of devil power that
she can muster.
As her Blood Magic ramps up,
she'll lose more and more blood
and deplete her mana.
That's when she'll start drawing
on Megicula's power
to keep on fighting.
After that, we should be able
to go head-to-head with her.
And when she runs
out of that, as well,
it'll be time to use
our ace in the hole.
That's you, our
arcane-stage fighter.
Nero!
[LOROPECHIKA]
With Nero's arcane-stage spells,
and your combative spirit
and fighting style,
if we train hard and
create a formidable team,
I'm confident with our
abilities combined,
we can overpower
Vanica and Megicula
when the time finally
comes to battle with them!
Well, Nero, can we
count you in, too?
I'm about to seal away
that devil's power
you seem so proud of!
[SECRÉ] Mana Method.
Sealing Magic: Eternal Prison!
[SECRÉ] I won't let Queen
Loropechika, or this world,
be harmed by scum like you!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[LOROPECHIKA] What the Queen of
the Heart Kingdom Inherited.
[NARRATOR] The Queen of
the Heart Kingdom inherits
the previous queens' powers,
as well as their
knowledge and experiences.
Here, inside
Loropechika's mind,
is where that colossal mountain
of information materializes.
[sighs] This isn't
the right one.
Not in here.
Nope, no good.
No.
Agh, darn it!
Why were the previous queens
so disorganized, huh?
They could've at least
put things in ABC order!
You're no better.
[NOELLE]
No matter how strong the enemy
or how dire the situation,
we will never give up!
We'll keep pushing
past our limits.
That's what the Black Bulls do!
Black Clover , Page 166:
"Captain: Yami Sukehiro."