[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[MAGNA]
Here ya go!
[gasps]
You earned this
fair and square, Asta.
What, you don't want it?
[ASTA]
No! I do! I do! I do!
This is really mine.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Let's see how it looks.
And now, the finishing touch.
Hey! It looks
pretty good on you.
Right, Yami?
I don't think it's his color.
It's official now:
you're one of us.
You're a member
of the Black Bulls.
Don't do anything
that would bring shame
to Yami or to the Black Bulls.
[ASTA]
Understood!
I'm so glad to be
a part of this team!
Yeah!
[ASTA laughs]
Shut up, kid.
[ASTA]
I'm sorry!
I'll be more careful
from now on, sir!
[MAGNA] What part of "shut up"
do you not understand?
[NOELLE] So, I guess that's
the other new recruit.
[sighs] Little insect.
[MAGNA]
Here it is: your room.
Dank, huh?
Not to mention oppressively
cramped and filthy.
[laughs]
[MAGNA]
You should see mine.
--It's twice this siz--
--[ASTA whimpers]
My room! No way!
Wait, you're actually happy?
This is the first time I've
ever had a space of my own.
Back at the church, everybody
crammed into one room.
We were all lined
up like sardines.
[ASTA]
So long, dust!
Dirt and grime, get outta here!
[ASTA laughs]
See ya, cobwebs!
[MAGNA]
Go on, scrub all ya want.
We're free till the
next mission, anyway.
[laughs]
Oh, hey, one more thing, Asta.
Yeah, what's up?
Make sure you take
some time to write.
The folks back at the
church deserve a letter.
They're your family, right?
So, they'll wanna know
that you're okay.
Right!
[MAGNA] You can't go
making anyone worry.
That's what bein' a real
man is all about. Later.
Just hit me up
if you need anything.
Will do! Thanks, Magna.
[ASTA] This is my first
castle, but not my last.
Someday, I'm gonna live in
the castle of the Wizard King.
[ASTA]
I won't lose. Got that, Yuno?
It's better than you deserve.
A room like this is wasted
on the likes of you.
Now, tomorrow I'll
explain your duties
as a Magic Knight.
I don't particularly
wish to be your tutor,
but since it's on Captain
Vangeance's orders, so be it.
Are you listening, boy?
My name is Yuno.
My name is Yuno, Klaus. Not boy.
Enough.
Watch your tone. I outrank you.
You are to address me as "sir."
[YUNO]
Yes, sir.
Better.
Don't be late tomorrow,
or I will be displeased.
[ARLU, HORO laughing]
Thank you.
[gasps]
I knew we were right
about you, Yuno!
The pride and joy of Hage,
making it into
the Magic Knights!
Not that I'm surprised.
Yuno can do anything!
Yeah, anything!
Everyone in the village
will be so excited
when they hear.
And what does Asta's letter say?
Can you even make out that
terrible chicken scratch of his?
[NASH] Yeah, he writes
like a five-year-old.
So does he say when
he's coming home?
When he does get here,
we'll have to cheer him up.
Even Asta will have a hard
time bouncing back from this.
Maybe a pop-potato party
will lift his spirits.
Actually, he says
that he got in.
[BOTH]
Huh?
--[HORO] What?
--[ARLU] Huh?
They both passed.
[HIGH PRIEST, REKKA, NASH,
ARLU, HORO] What?!
[BOTH]
Seriously?
[LILY]
Mm-hm.
Oh, wow.
You're not kidding, are you?
Really? He did it.
So, um. I guess, then...
Asta won't be
coming home, will he?
Right.
We'll go let everyone know
about our Magic Knights.
This will be the best news
--Hage Village has ever gotten.
--[ARLU, HORO] Yeah!
Amazing!
He's gonna be a Magic Knight,
just like he said.
He did it!
Asta. Yuno. Good job.
Just keep doing your best!
So, it's real.
I wasn't dreaming.
Right. Yeah!
I'm ready to--
Wait a second.
I'm pretty sure this column
wasn't here yesterday.
[MAGNA]
Hey, newbie! How's it hangin'?
Oh, uh. I'm good, thanks.
Can I ask you, though,
about this column?
Yeah, what about it?
Well, it's just,
I don't think it
was here yesterday.
Probably because it wasn't.
That's nothing, though.
This whole building shifts
around all the time.
[ASTA]
It does?!
[MAGNA]
Yeah. Eh, you'll get used to it.
I thought there was something
weird about this place.
Well, come on. Let's go.
[ASTA]
Sure thing!
You're lucky enough to have
me as your tour guide.
There's no one better
to show you all the secrets
of the Black Bulls' hideout.
Well, Rasta? Ready?
Yeah, I'm ready!
Let's go, Mr. Shades.
What? No. It's "sir," twerp!
[ASTA]
Right! Got it, Sir Twerp.
[MAGNA]
Drop the "twerp"!
This is the dining hall.
[ASTA]
Ooh!
[MAGNA] Eh? Whatcha think?
Ridiculously huge, huh?
No kidding! It's enormous.
And this is the communal bath.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
It's so hot.
I mean, maybe it is
for a normal person,
but this heat should be
nothing to a Black Bull.
What's wrong? You wanna
get out already?
[ASTA growls]
No, of course not.
I can stay in. I'm not done yet.
[mumbling] I wouldn't mind
adding a little cold water.
It's just really nice to hang
out with you guys like this.
[MAGNA] Over there's where
the women's rooms are.
If a guy goes in, the
trap magic'll kill him.
Wow, serious security.
[MAGNA]
And here is...
--[ASTA] Huh?
--...the bathroom.
[yelps]
You're dead.
[ASTA, MAGNA]
We're really sorry, sir!
[BEASTS growling]
[ASTA]
Whoa! What's in there?
[MAGNA]
That's the beast room.
[ASTA]
Uh, what for?
It's Yami's little
hobby. And, Asta?
Yeah, what's up?
I've decided to put you in
charge of our furry friends.
[ASTA]
What?
This job is an honor
to have, you know.
I hate to give it up,
but it's yours.
They get fed in the
morning and the evening.
Go on, give it a shot.
Um, okay. Nice little beasties.
Here you go. Eat up!
[ASTA yelps]
--[ASTA screaming]
--[MAGNA laughing]
The Black Bulls' library.
Got it!
And this beauty
here's the rec room.
You can have lots
of fun in here.
Uh, say what now?
[BOTH laughing]
What's the matter,
newbie? Can't keep up?
Just wait, you haven't
seen anything yet!
Hah! I'll show you!
[BOTH yelp]
Ow!
Jeez, give a guy some
warning. What the...?
Who is she?
[ASTA] A Black Bulls robe.
So that means...
Well, what do you know.
It's your fellow rookie.
She's our other new
member this year.
[ASTA]
Cool! Another newbie?
Glad to know I'm not alone.
How's it going?
I'm Asta from Hage Village.
Let's give this all
we've got. What do ya say?
Don't speak to me so casually.
You're a little insect of a
commoner with barely any mana.
"Little insect"?
Jeez. "Commoner"?
My name is Noelle Silva,
of the royal Silva house.
What? No way!
You're--? Are you--
Royalty...?
I, uh...
An insignificant insect like me
should never have presumed
to speak so informally
to an exalted royal
such as yourself!
As long as you understand.
[ASTA] Wait. Who are you
calling a little insect?
We joined the Magic Knights
at the same time, didn't we?
Who cares if you're royalty?
Yeah, that's right, Asta.
You tell her! Being royal
doesn't matter here!
It does, very much so.
[BOTH]
And what makes you so sure?
[sighs] Foolish commoners.
I suppose words aren't enough
to make you understand.
The difference in
our magic power
should get the point across.
[ASTA, MAGNA gasp]
Hey...
Wait a minute!
Don't forget your place again.
[ASTA]
There's no time!
[MAGNA yelps, gurgles]
Hmph.
[ASTA]
Uh...
[MAGNA] What were you
thinking? Entitled brat.
Obviously, you've got
more guts than sense.
You just attacked
a senior member!
It isn't my fault you
were in the wrong place.
I didn't tell you
to stand there.
You did that on your own.
[sputtering]
What kind of crazy are you?
I'm your superior here!
That's nice, but I'm royalty.
[MAGNA]
Yeah?
Well, I don't care
if you're royalty
or the sister of the
Silver Eagles' captain.
Huh?
[MAGNA] Yami's the only
person I know who would
ever take on a crazy
chick like you.
So you might wanna
show some gratitude.
I was holdin' off
'cause you're a woman,
but I think it's time
for your baptism.
Uh--
Don't bother. I quit
this stupid squad.
You--
Hey!
What do you think
you're doing, huh?
I'm leaving before the
filth of the Black Bulls
has a chance to rub off on me.
Everyone knows you're
the worst of the worst
Magic Knight squads.
This is hardly the place
for a royal like me.
How dare you!
Get back here and apologize
to the robe and Yami!
Apologize! Apologize!
I gave everything
to get that robe,
and she just threw it away...
[MAGNA]
Ya moron!
[ASTA] I don't get it.
What the hell just happened?
How did I wind up outside?
I was just looking
for the bathroom.
[explosion]
Huh?
[ASTA screams]
[ASTA] Jeez, what the
heck was that thing?
[gasps]
[NOELLE panting]
[ASTA]
What's she doing?
Oh.
[ASTA screams]
[pants]
Why won't it work?
Why can't I ever hit...
[NOELLE]
...what I'm aiming for?
[panting]
So it's true. Everything
they said about me.
[NOBLE 7A]
Have you heard?
Apparently, the youngest
Silva child has no control
over her magic power.
[NOBLE 7B]
Oh, no.
For someone like that to be
born into the royal family?
That sad grimoire of yours
is practically paper-thin.
Are you sure you're
really royalty?
Not being able to
control your own magic.
That's the most pitiful
thing I've ever heard.
And this wretch
is my little sister?
Embarrassing!
[pants]
[NOZEL] You will never
be a member of my squad.
There is no room in the Silver
Eagles for a disgrace like you.
A disgrace and a mistake.
Why wasn't it you who died
instead of our mother?
What an abject failure.
[NOELLE]
I am not a failure.
Somehow, I will
make you accept me!
[NOELLE yelling]
Poor Noelle.
I guess she doesn't
have it easy either.
[gasps]
Hey.
[NOELLE]
The little insect!
How long have you been there?
[NOELLE]
Here it comes, the mocking.
Are you...?
[NOZEL] You will never
be a member of my squad.
There is no room...
[NEBRA] Not being able
to control your own magic.
That's the most pitiful...
[SOLID] Are you sure
you're really royalty?
Nuh--
[ASTA]
"Nuh"?
[NOELLE]
No!
Take this!
[gasps]
[yelps]
Ah!
[YAMI sighs]
[YAMI]
Dump: taken.
Guess it's time for a catnap.
Huh?
What in the hell is that?
[NOELLE muffled grunting]
[screaming]
My goodness!
--Hey, cool!
--[GORDON] Whatever that thing
is, it looks like it's
some serious magic.
That's magic power
gone out of control.
And a whole hell
of a lot of it, too.
We're... gonna have
to do something.
[YAMI sighs] Well, attacking
the thing with magic is out.
She's gonna get hurt
if we try that.
Why not use your spatial magic
to pull her outta there?
[FINRAL]
Please, be reasonable.
I can't get close to that!
[YAMI]
Yeah, okay.
Man, if there were only
someone around here
who could cancel out magic.
[ASTA yelling]
You picked the right
time to drop in, kid.
Huh?
[YAMI]
See that?
Do somethin' about it.
[ASTA]
"Do something"?
Okay, I'll try.
Wait. How am I supposed
to get up there?
I can't exactly fly. So...
I don't wanna hear your excuses.
[ASTA yelps]
Just suck it up, newbie.
Dig deep, and push
past your limits!
[ASTA yelling]
[ASTA growling, yelling]
[gasps]
[screams]
[ASTA]
I'm dead.
[screaming]
Yeah! I didn't die!
[laughs]
That was so fun to watch!
--More! More!
--[VANESSA] Really?
I'm all wet now.
[ASTA]
Thanks for the portal.
I thought you might
appreciate it.
You pulled it off,
kid. Good job.
Thank you! Hey, Noelle!
[gasps]
[NOZEL]
What an abject failure.
[NOELLE]
Here it comes, the mocking.
You know...
You've got yourself
some crazy magic power!
I mean, it's freakin' amazing!
[ASTA] Really! I'm totally
jealous of you.
I don't have any
magic power, like, none.
All you need is some training
to get it under control.
You'll be strong. Unstoppable!
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
Little in--
A-Asta.
I'm screwed.
Man, I'll have to
work extra hard
if I'm gonna keep up with you.
[MAGNA]
What? Is that all?
You were running away
because you can't
control your magic power?
Shoulda said something sooner,
you royal failure.
I mean, come on.
This is the Black
Bulls, after all.
We're a whole squad of failures.
[VANESSA chuckles]
[gasps]
[MAGNA] So maybe you've
got a weakness or three.
That doesn't matter
to us, ya big dummy.
Anyway, we're glad
you're all right.
Oh, and, I know this place
that makes killer pasta.
You wanna check it out
with me sometime?
Forget about pasta.
You need to try a bite of this.
Here!
That was quite the
show you put on.
I happen to be
particularly gifted
at controlling my magic power,
so I can teach you.
Also, maybe give you
some womanly advice.
[GAUCHE]
I'll tell you all about
what an angel
my sister Marie is.
[mumbling] I think we should
just start as friends
and see where it
goes from there.
Now, come on.
We'll do our best together.
[NOELLE] I'm looking forward
to working with you.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[NOELLE]
"Show Some Respect"!
I am so regal,
it's beyond belief.
Wouldn't you agree?
An illegal mountain thief?
Who are you calling
a bandit, commoner?
I'm royalty! Did you mishear?
Oh! So you're a buccaneer.
Who are you calling
a pirate, peasant?
I'm of the royal family.
Wait, hold on. We're family?
[gasps] Just shut up.
[ASTA] My first mission
as a Magic Knight. Yes!
One step closer to
becoming the Wizard King.
What? Boar hunting?
That's the mission?
Black Clover , Page Eight:
"Go! Go! My First Mission."
My magic is never giving up!