[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives a magicless
boy named Asta.
This brave young hero devotes
blood, sweat, and tears
to becoming the
next Wizard King.
Though Asta's situation
is practically unheard of,
there are others
residing in this kingdom
who possess at least
a tiny amount of mana,
yet can barely
use spells at all.
They make up
a very small minority,
living their lives
in the shadows.
[NARRATOR]
But, like everyone else,
they do their best to survive.
[MAN 142A]
Run away!
[GIRL 142A]
Mommy!
[WOMAN 142A]
Somebody help us!
[NARRATOR]
On that fateful night,
the reincarnated elves
came seeking vengeance.
[DAZU] Don't worry!
I'll save you, I swear!
[NARRATOR]
In the town of Tiulyu.
Dazu lost her husband
and her mother-in-law.
[NARRATOR] With help from
Bow, another resident,
Dazu confronted a member of the
Magic Parliament named Kabwe.
Kabwe despised devils.
And after Damnatio delayed the
trial for Nero, Asta, and Marie,
who were facing judgment for
their involvement with one,
he believed the situation
was being handled poorly,
which caused him to
become even more enraged.
And so, the group took action.
Under the name
"Devil Banishers,"
they abducted Marie
from the church in Nean.
[SIONA] You won't be escaping
again, servant of the devil.
Why do you think I'm a
servant of the devil?
[ONOBY] The scale
is tilting to darkness.
We must push it
toward the light!
Let's go!
Someone. Help me, please!
Please, Gauche! Save me!
[NARRATOR] Around the same time,
the Devil Banishers attempted
to put Asta and Nero to sleep
and kidnap them as well.
Nero. Let her go!
Please help me, Asta.
[NOELLE] What do you people
think you're doing?
Get away from Asta
and Nero right now!
[SECRÉ] Sealing Magic:
Inverse Release!
[ASTA]
I can't move my body.
Oh, crap.
Am I gonna...
[KABWE]
We're out of time, let's go.
[NOELLE] Water Creation
Magic: Sea Dragon's--
[DEMON MASK 142AA] Plant Magic:
The Flower on the Roadside!
[NOELLE]
Water--
[KABWE]
Now, run!
Asta! Nero!
[DEMON MASK 142B]
She's fast!
[NOELLE]
Sea Dragon's Waterball!
[DEMON MASK 142B groans]
[NARRATOR]
Luckily, Noelle fought them off,
but the group still managed
to escape with Nero in tow.
As for Asta...
Don't you dare leave without
telling me who you are!
[DAZU]
We are the Devil Banishers.
[BOW] We will drive
the Devil to its demise.
You won't get away.
Not until Nero is safe!
Asta!
[NOELLE]
Please wake up!
Asta!
So, we all made it.
How did your mission go?
[SIONA]
We succeeded.
[ONOBY gasps]
Where's Asta?
[DEMON MASK 142B]
We apologize.
Someone got in our way.
I see.
But still, there is
some good news.
He should sleep
for a very long time.
Doctor. I need to know
that Asta's still alive!
Don't worry, he's alive.
Just sleeping.
If that's true, then why
won't he open his eyes?
I mean, what if they put him
under a spell that causes him
to sleep forever or something?
[OWEN]
No. I can confidently say
he's not sleeping
because of a spell.
[NOELLE gasps]
That makes sense!
Assuming that it's
what I think it is.
[MARX]
Let me go!
[grunts] What about
me suggested
that I needed to
be dragged here?
Asta.
Still snoozin', huh?
This is startin' to get fishy.
So, what did you
mean when you said
he wasn't sleeping
because of a spell?
Listen, quack,
you better not tell us
it's a sleeping potion or
something stupid like that.
Actually, yes, it is.
Trust me, I'm as
surprised as you are.
Not sure who made it,
but it was a ridiculously
powerful concoction.
But why would anybody have
something like that on them?
[OWEN]
That, I don't know.
In any case, he should
wake up on his own
after he rests for
a little while longer.
Thank goodness.
Well, I guess we can say
one thing for sure:
if they put him to sleep,
that probably means they weren't
out to murder the kid, right?
Makes sense.
First, we should find out
exactly what happened.
[GAUCHE] Dammit, you
incompetent old hag!
This is the third time!
The third time?
That's right. The third time
Marie's been put in danger!
Remember? First,
these bastards took her,
then there was this whole
trial thing, and now this!
That's three strikes, sister!
You're out of the game now!
Whoa, chill!
Please don't beat up
the elderly!
Shut your mouth, portal boy!
[FINRAL] Even if I didn't
outrank you, that's just mean!
I could say that it happened
while I was away
from the church,
but I know that's merely
an excuse. Either way.
I have to imagine there's
something you can do
that would be more proactive
than strangling an old woman.
[grunts] Marie.
Where did they go?
[GAUCHE]
Tell me! What happened to her?
Huh? It's you!
Answer me! Right now!
Uh. These masked people
calling themselves
the Devil Banishers.
They took her.
Who the hell are they?
I swear, I don't know!
I mean, they said something.
Then tell me what
it was, already!
Yeah, okay!
They said, "the scale
is tilting to darkness,
and we must turn it
back towards the light!"
A scale, huh?
[ASTA, SECRÉ coughing]
[ASTA]
What is this?
It's poison!
[KABWE]
That was impressive!
You're quite a
skilled potion-maker.
[BOW]
Thank you.
Those are some
creepy-looking masks
they got there.
[ASTA]
I can't move my body.
Oh, crap.
Am I gonna...
That was all.
Leave it to him to fall
for that obvious trick.
To tell the truth...
The spells they were using
weren't all that powerful.
Maybe they were trying to be
discreet so that the other
Black Bulls wouldn't pick up
on their mana or something.
That explains why
Henry didn't wake up
when they came to the hideout.
[crash, rumbling]
[OWEN] Honestly, Yami,
was that really necessary?
Not only did these
evil bastards attack the base
while I wasn't around,
but they had the balls
to kidnap a member of my squad!
I don't know who they they are,
but screwin' with me was the
biggest mistake of their lives.
[rumbling]
[MARX]
What was that noise out there?
What's wrong, sir?
Did you hear that? Uh...
I'm beginning to think doors
are a foreign concept
to the Black Bulls.
Where's my sister?
[DAMNATIO]
Whatever do you mean?
Has something happened to Marie?
Don't give me that!
You abducted her again,
I know you did!
You can't be serious.
Don't you dare
play dumb with me.
I assure you, I'm not.
Although... You've
been impertinent.
And for that,
you must be judged.
Gentlemen, I suggest
you step back.
[MAGES]
Yes, sir.
[gasps]
[GAUCHE]
He did this last time.
[DAMNATIO]
Scale Magic: Scale Regulate.
You were imprisoned once,
and it seems I'll have to
put you behind bars again.
[GAUCHE]
Try it and see what happens!
Mirror Magic: Reflect Ray!
Are you all right, sir?
[BOTH] Casting Mirror
Magic: Real Double!
[DAMNATIO] He used a mirror
to clone himself?
[GAUCHES]
I already saw you pull
that dumb little trick
during the trial.
It's not gonna work
for you this time, buddy.
It seems you've
underestimated me.
[DAMNATIO]
On your knees!
The hell is this?
Seize these two, immediately.
[MAGES]
Yes, sir!
[YAMI]
Are you trying to terrorize
every member of
my squad, or what?
I don't care how much
you despise the guy,
you can't just go rogue
on me like that!
What's worse, I don't recall
giving you permission
--to hijack my wheels!
--[FINRAL] Right, wheels.
Do you know how much
mana I had to waste
draggin' myself all
the way over here?
[NOELLE] I'm pretty sure
it was easy, but okay.
Why are you two accosting him?
Because this is the second time
this mole-faced freak
kidnapped my sister!
[ALL gasp]
Not true.
[GAUCHE]
Well, who the hell did, then?
I know what those guys
with the masks
were saying when they took her.
Something about
returning the scale
to the light after it
tipped into darkness.
That's exactly the kind of crap
that you talk about!
Wait a minute. Did you say
those guys were wearing masks?
What's the difference?
Were they or not?
[GAUCHE]
Well, I think so.
I wasn't there, but...
[GAUCHE]
So, they didn't just take Marie?
[YAMI] They didn't get
the kid, but Nero's gone.
[GAUCHE]
That means it was you!
What led you to that conclusion?
I'm not following your logic.
First Marie, then you
took Asta and Nero.
All the ones
who were on trial!
You were trying to take justice
into your own hands,
weren't you, creep?
Listen, I don't really care
what you do to Asta and Nero.
That's kinda messed up!
[GAUCHE]
Just give Marie back!
Now then, Marx.
If you would show them
my memories, please.
All right, I will.
Tch.
In a few moments,
my innocence will be proven,
and then you will pay severely
for the way you've insulted me.
It's clear from his memories.
He knew nothing
about any of this.
So obviously,
I couldn't possibly
have been involved
in the situation.
Not only did you attack me,
but you also accused me
of a heinous crime.
I hope you're prepared to
assume full responsibility.
[GAUCHE] Fine. Do
whatever you want to me.
But it'll have to wait until
Marie gets back safe.
[DAMNATIO] What makes you think
you have any right to negotiate?
Hold on, now.
The guy we saw
in your memories.
You know, the one you
were arguing with.
You'd think he would've popped
in durin' all this ruckus.
[DAMNATIO]
Hm.
[chiming]
I'm here, sir.
Is something wrong?
[JULIUS]
I'm sorry to interrupt you all,
but there's something I need
Yami and his group to see.
Listen, we're a little busy--
[JULIUS] He should
be arriving any moment.
[NOZEL]
Pardon me.
It's my brother.
[JULIUS] Remember,
at the start of this mess,
we put a special
communication bracelet on Asta
to keep track of his
location at all times.
[NOZEL] We're getting a signal
from the town of Tiulyu,
in the Common Realm.
What does that mean?
Did someone take it off of him?
The only ones who even
knew about that bracelet
are the people who were
in the room when we did it.
And the only person
I can think of
who'd be able to get that
thing off would be Nero
with her Sealing Magic.
Perhaps she did remove it,
and now she's trying
to use the signal to broadcast
her whereabouts to us.
And I bet if we find her,
we'll find Marie. Finra--
[YAMI]
Finral! Let's go!
Yeah, so I hate to tell ya this,
but I've actually
never been to Tiulyu.
Guess we'll just have to
travel there by broom then.
Captain.
Allow me to accompany you.
After all, my best friend's
sister is basically my sister.
Hell no!
Say that again, and you're dead!
This may be a trap.
Should we really take that risk?
No one asked you, fungus head!
I don't care if it is a trap,
it's the only clue we
have to go on right now!
[YAMI]
I agree with Gauche.
We gotta check it out.
Hold on.
[DAMNATIO] I haven't
finished my conversation
with this insufferable
criminal yet.
[GAUCHE]
Oh, yeah?
Get your head out of your ass!
There's more important
stuff goin' on here!
[JULIUS]
Yami.
Did I or did I not
order the Black Bulls
to keep an eye on Nero?
You did.
[JULIUS] They're called
the Devil Banishers, yes?
Well, you can't exactly
watch over her
until you get her back
from them, can you?
So, Damnatio, I'll have
to ask you to withhold
your judgment for
a while longer.
Is that all right?
Yes, I suppose so.
[JULIUS]
I'm counting on you, Yami.
Right.
[JULIUS] Oh, yes, and
there's one more thing.
We don't have all day here!
[JULIUS]
I understand tensions are high,
since one of your own
has been abducted.
But remember, this isn't
like what happened
with the Magic Parliament.
With this many unknowns,
one wrong move could put
your squad in grave peril.
No need to tell me.
Enough talk. Ready? Let's go!
[BLACK BULLS]
Yes, sir!
I'll go with you.
Huh?
Didn't see that coming.
Why are you taking
the time to help us out
when your squad's
so busy training?
We need every Magic
Knight in the kingdom
to help defeat the evil,
and I don't want to lose
anyone between now and then.
No more, no less.
Come on, we all know you're just
worried about your sister.
Stop trying to act
like Mr. Badass.
It's gettin' old.
If you say one more word,
then I won't hesitate
to send you plummeting
to your death, foreigner.
So much for that fancy speech
about not wantin'
to lose anyone.
[GAUCHE]
There it is.
It's destroyed.
It's probably one
of the many areas
that were attacked by the
Eye of the Midnight Sun.
[GAUCHE]
I'll be right there, Marie!
The signal.
Yeah, where is it?
[cuffs rattling]
I'm guessing that's
another magic item
that prevents mana tracking,
like the one I have?
Yes, just to be safe.
I doubt anyone'll find us way
out here, but it doesn't hurt.
[NOZEL] It appears they're doing
their best to block the signal.
Do you think they know
about the bracelet?
It's possible.
Either way, we'll be wise
to proceed with caution.
Did we really have to land
this far away from them?
Are you stupid?
Uh--
I doubt it'll just
be Nero and Marie.
I'm sure the kidnappers
are keeping an eye on them.
Do you honestly
think it would work
if we barge in there
without a plan?
Huh.
[YAMI]
Gauche.
[GAUCHE]
Yeah?
You got a picture of
your little sister on you?
What the hell do you
want it for?!
Relax, weirdo.
We need it to ask people
if they've seen her!
That makes sense.
[YAMI]
Mm-hm.
I need all of them back!
[YAMI] We don't know
what these guys might do.
So nobody go into town alone.
Remember to watch yourselves!
Tch.
The Double G Duo rides again!
You're not my sidekick.
Don't be embarrassed,
we work great together!
Let's go, Noelle.
Okay!
Well. I guess it's me and you.
Y'got a problem with that?
What? No, of course not.
No one's come to help them?
We only have so many forces
we can send to make repairs.
[GORDON]
It's strange.
This place obviously suffered
some serious damage.
And yet...
[FINRAL]
Wow.
I know, there's
so many graves here,
you can't count 'em all.
Wonder how many popped up
after the big attack.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[NOELLE]
"Devil Banishers."
We're gettin' Nero and Marie
back from those jerks,
whatever it takes!
Can't seem to remember what
they called themselves, though.
Let's see, it was
somethin' like...
Devil Tooth-Pullers!
[NOELLE]
Banishers.
[YAMI]
Devil Injectors!
[NOELLE]
Nope, Banishers.
Devil Fourth-Hitters!
[NOELLE]
Banishers .
Devil Night Train Passengers!
[NOELLE]
Banishers!
Devil News Reporters!
[NOELLE]
Banishers!
Devil Book Publishers!
[NOELLE]
I said, Banishers!
[YAMI]
Devil Banishers!
[NOELLE]
For the last--!
Oh, you got it.
[DAMNATIO] As much as I hate
to admit it, the kingdom
desperately needs Asta's
help to defeat the devil.
Black Clover , Page 144:
"Those Who Wish
for the Devil's Demise."
Someone is trying to throw
the scales of justice
out of balance.