[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] In the second
round of the Royal Knights
Selection Exam, Langris's
Team G won by a slim margin.
Finral, no!
[NARRATOR] However, even
after the match was over,
the crazed Langris
continued to attack
his older brother Finral.
[LANGRIS]
Disappear.
[NARRATOR]
The other Black Bulls stepped in
to save their wounded comrade.
[ASTA]
Hey!
Go on. Take one more
step toward him.
But you should know that
the second you do,
you're dead.
You Black Bulls
may be doing better
than expected, but you're
still worthless underlings.
You think you can
take the vice captain
of the Golden Dawn?
Your rank has nothing
to do with this.
All we care about is
protecting our friend.
[laughs] You may have
lucked out and failed upward
to get to this point,
but you're still a nobody
who's talking to someone
completely out of your league.
Wizard King.
Before the next teams
face off against each other,
allow me to put these Black
Bulls in their rightful place.
In fact, the fight
can start now.
Let the semifinals begin!
Wizard King, sir. You're
not going to stop them?
If this were an actual battle,
no one would be able
to control when the
fighting begins or ends.
[NARRATOR] Langris's sudden,
violent outburst forced
Teams B and G into an
impromptu semifinal faceoff.
But part of Julius's
plan for this test
was to expose an
"involuntary" traitor
working on behalf of the
Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Asta, no!
[NARRATOR]
In order to subdue Langris,
Asta called upon
his Black Asta form.
How about some help, Xerx?
[NARRATOR]
Focusing his might,
he put his trust in
the mage called Xerx.
[ZORA] Look at him, smirking
with all the confidence
in the world.
[NARRATOR]
Whose real name was Zora.
[ZORA]
Dammit.
I swear I'll use the power
I possess and protect
everyone who needs my help.
That's my duty
as a Magic Knight!
[NARRATOR] Zora's father
Zara was the first commoner
to become a Magic Knight.
however, he was
eventually betrayed
by his own squad
mates and murdered.
[ZORA]
You jerks.
My father knew what
a knight should be.
And you are no Magic Knight!
[MIMOSA gasps]
Begone. I am the true
Magic Knight here!
[MIMOSA]
It broke through the circle!
Careful, Xerx!
[gasps]
[ZORA] Congrats on being
the first one to hit me today,
snot-nosed royal.
What?
[LANGRIS]
A magic circle on his body?
[MAGIC KNIGHTS gasp]
I don't believe my eyes!
Casting a spell like
that over his own body--
that'll be a constant
drain of power!
Not to mention it's an
extremely risky strategy.
I agree, it is rash.
But then, that does appear
to be the way he operates.
Whoa, there's no way!
Impossible.
[XERX'S BODYGUARD]
Wh-What've you done?
Who the hell are you?
[yelps]
[ZORA]
Oh, no one in particular.
Just a living
embodiment of the anger
of a filthy brat from
some poor village.
Have a little taste of my rage.
Pathetic excuse for
a Magic Knight!
He just reflected
that Spatial Magic!
But that will only
double its power!
[gasps]
Whoa!
[LANGRIS] I refuse to let
some nobody toy with me!
He'll pay for this.
What happened to that attack
after he doubled its strength?
He made it go away!
The vice captain was
powerful before,
but this is something
else entirely!
Where is all this
magic coming from?
Your Highness.
[ZORA grunts]
[cackles]
As it turns out, not even
your little ace in the hole
was enough to slow me
down in the slightest!
All you did was give me
more to work with!
It's just as I've been
telling you all along.
I really am special!
Unlike my weak brother.
And unlike you, as well!
All of you are so pathetic!
Nothing you do will
amount to anything!
[ASTA]
Wanna bet?
[gasps]
How dare you!
Go away, royal.
I don't need your
stupid healing spell.
So stop!
That's out of the question!
Not only are we
on the same team,
you and I are both
Magic Knights!
What did you just do?
Your appearance changed!
Oh, it's really nothin' special.
This is just what happens
when a commoner
gets tired of hearing
all your trash talk!
Everywhere I turn, I see
yet another nuisance
to contend with!
So do try to stay
out of my portals
during the next battle.
It would be a shame if
you were to permanently
disappear somewhere.
Forget about what it would
do to Mother and Father.
I think a certain
someone would be
quite devastated as well.
Yeah, good point.
So if I wanna prevent that,
then I'll just have
to win, won't I?
Despite knowing
I'm a chosen one.
You would still dare
think you are my equal?
I am one of a kind!
You don't stand a chance
against my supreme greatness!
Yeah. Right. You are
somethin' else.
Even as nobles go, your
power is crazy intense.
Your Spatial Magic
is off the charts.
You were born incredible.
That was what I always wanted!
To be someone special.
[ZORA grunts]
I fought alongside
a real tough character
on the battlefield today.
He definitely knew impressive
ways to use Time Magic.
Your power may be awesome,
but you know what
really sets us apart?
I don't care whether you're
impressed with me or not.
I mean, I can't stand you.
[ASTA] Just don't take him
from us for nothing!
Unlike you, we don't wanna be
powerful just to get our way.
We use magic to
protect each other!
We compete so we
can all get better!
We fight as a team.
That's the only reason
we've made it this far!
I've heard enough.
If you wanted to live, you
should have groveled at my feet
or kept your
commoner mouth shut!
Good-for-nothing cur!
[ASTA] You can call me
names all day long,
but you won't be laughing
when you see my power!
I'll burn it into you!
[groans]
[LANGRIS]
My magic's not working!
[YUNO gasps]
Oh, Asta.
[yells]
[BOTH gasp]
Black Meteorite!
I've heard enough.
If you wanted to live, you
should have groveled at my feet
or kept your
commoner mouth shut!
Good-for-nothing cur!
[ASTA] You can call me
names all day long,
but you won't be laughing
when you see my power!
I'll burn it into you!
[groans]
[LANGRIS]
My magic's not working!
[LANGRIS yells]
Black Meteorite!
[MIMOSA gasps]
[EMCEE MAGE] Both crystals
broke at the same time!
This match is a draw!
Oh, my goodness!
[ZORA grunts]
[laughs]
[FRAGIL]
He's out cold!
That was a fla- ha wless defeat!
[ZORA] I see. As long as
you've got the advantage,
that means you're always
in the right, does it?
Mr. Fancypants Nobleman?
[FRAGIL, SEKKE gasp]
If so, now that you've
had your ass handed to you
by a commoner, I guess
that puts you in the wrong.
Anyway, after that
little tantrum,
nobody's ever gonna let you
be their vice captain again.
Hey, fluffy hat girl!
What were you even doing
during that last battle?
So scared of Portal-boy
that you had
to wait on the sidelines?
Must've been nice
to kick back huh?
Listen, there's no
reason for you
to be such a jerk about it.
Shut your trap!
Why would I care
what a no-talent
showoff like you thinks?
You types are the most
useless ones of the bunch
and we both know it's true!
[whimpers]
[ZORA] Quit the Magic Knights
and go home already, you trash!
And, Shorty!
You gotta stop putting
so much trust in everybody
who comes your way.
Not everyone's a good guy,
and the good ones
ain't that good!
You're gonna end up
gettin' yourself killed!
[gasps] Please don't say that!
[ZORA] As for you, you're
always trying to act according
to what's best for the
given circumstances.
But you'd better be careful--
don't throw thinking
out the window entirely
when there's a situation
you weren't anticipating,
Little Miss Royal.
And you. Yeah, you.
The devilishly handsome guy
with the awesome mask!
You should've depended
on your teammates
a whole lot more.
[ASTA]
A draw. We didn't win.
Man! I hate this!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 83A] Let's do our
best out there, everyone!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 83B]
No matter what,
we're all Magic Knights
of the Clover Kingdom!
The fight ended
in a draw between
your brother's and Asta's teams.
But our showing was better.
The newbie superstar of
the Black Bulls giving
the vice captain
of the Golden Dawn
a run for his money made
a pretty big impression!
Which is why
you need to hurry
and wake up soon!
While you've been
here catching Zs,
our friends have been
accomplishing some great things!
I've administered first aid,
but his wounds are too serious.
Let's take him to the infirmary.
Cob, do you mind?
Don't mind it one
itty-bitty-bit, sir!
Then I'll be going with you.
It looks like your
team is on deck!
Ya better not screw it up!
Yeah, I got this.
--[MAGNA screams]
--[laughs]
[EMCEE MAGE] Next, we'll
continue on with Team I:
Rill, Nils, and Ruben vs.
Team K: Puli, Klaus, and Luck.
Round two, match three
will begin momentarily!
Aw, yeah!
Let's hit them with
everything we've got, fellas!
Well, we're up
against the captain
of the Aqua Deer.
He'd just counter every attack
with its direct weakness.
What to do?
I think I might
have a good strategy.
Wanna hear it?
[laughs] I can't wait to see
what kind of masterpiece
I'm going to create this time!
[NILS, RUBEN] If we provide
enough backup, we might win!
Huh? That magic...
Someone's condensing it
and making it more refined!
[LUCK]
There's no point in countering
an ultra-fast attack spell.
One strike and he's toast!
[LUCK] I guess we're kind of
copying the Combo spells
those other guys were
using in the first round.
But I betcha this
technique is gonna have
a lot more oomph to it!
That looks bad!
We've got to get our
team's crystal to safety!
[LUCK] Don't bother
moving out of the way.
On a battlefield like this,
I'll always know exactly
where you're hiding.
[RILL] Oh, wow. I'm sure
it travels really fast!
Better get to drawing, then!
[LUCK] Whatever your next move
is, it won't help you at all!
'Cause this spell pierces
through everything!
[ALL]
Compound Magic: Lightning Arrow!
Nobody's gonna stop this attack!
[RILL laughs]
[RILL] He's right! Picture
Magic: Game of the Gods!
[RILL] Actually, I drew
a little inspiration
from the first round, myself!
The method's not quite the same,
but I'm still charging
up the enemy's spell...
[RILL]
...and reflecting it!
[KLAUS, PULI gasp]
Welp!
[EMCEE MAGE]
Crystal destroyed! Team I wins!
What in the world
just happened here?
Uh. Your guess is
as good as mine!
[laughing]
[RICK] Well, he's not
the captain for nothing.
[FORTI]
That's Rill Boismortier for you!
[RILL] And, I got a glimpse of
my great masterpiece! Woo-hoo!
Oh, boy. That didn't
last very long.
Shake it off, you guys!
[mumbling] Luck's come
so tremendously far
in this selection exam.
I'll be writing all of
this down in my diary.
Excellent work!
[MIMOSA]
Excuse me, Black Bulls?
[BLACK BULLS]
Huh?
It's Asta. He's
severely exhausted now.
We took him to the
infirmary downstairs.
I'm going to stay
with him for a while.
Please be here for
Noelle in my stead.
[EMCEE MAGE]
The next matchup is Team M:
Ben, Brad, and Eric vs.
Team P: En, Noelle, and Yuno.
Stand by for round
two, match four!
[NOELLE]
This is for Asta.
Uh, I'm gonna fight
for everyone who's lost
and definitely not
one specific person!
Of course, we are.
And we're going to win.
[EMCEE MAGE]
Round two, match four, begin!
[NOELLE gasps]
Hey! Don't just go without me!
[YUNO] I refuse to waste
my time standing still.
There they are!
Just him?
Who is this guy?
Begone!
Wind Magic: Towering Tornado!
[ALL]
What the--?
But, he's nothing
but a commoner!
[YUNO] Asta, you may be down,
but you'll get back up.
I've seen how quickly
you adapt and improve.
The more it hurts, the
further you push yourself.
Soon you'll be countless times
stronger than you are now.
[gasps]
[EMCEE MAGE]
Uh, crystal destroyed!
Team P wins!
What did he just do? And how?
Oh, man! That spell
was pretty damn sweet!
Yeah, I wish I could
fight him, too!
[sighs]
[JULIUS]
Yuno, I can see that you've got
much more to show us.
Yuno!
What's your problem, finishing
them all off by yourself?
I wish you'd use my power
every once in a while!
My talents are wasted on you!
Shut up.
Ugh, you sure stress me out!
I don't hate that
about you, though.
Next up, match two
of the semifinals.
But it will be much
more than that.
Since the first
match of this round
resulted in a draw,
this face-off between
Team I and Team P
is going to be the last bout
of our great tournament!
[YUNO]
Asta, I'm moving forward!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[ZORA, ASTA]
"Names."
Okay, so my name
is actually Zora,
and my dad's name was Zara.
What? That's too simple?
I think it makes it extra
clear that we're related.
Yeah, I agree! Imagine
if I was a quintuplet.
My name's Asta!
Basta.
Casta!
Dasta.
Fasta!
[ALL] Not a single one of us
has any magic ability.
But no matter what, we still
never give up on our dreams!
Sister Lily is so
gonna marry me!
[BASTA]
Me!
[CASTA]
--[DASTA] Me.
--[FASTA] Me!
[ALL]
We'll fight for it!
[ALL yelling]
[ALL panting]
[ALL]
Sure, we may argue sometimes,
but we'll always be a family!
[GROUP laughing]
One of him is a racket,
but five is enough
to drive ya up a damn wall.
Yeah, one is plenty.
[JULIUS] It's finally time
for the deciding match!
I really did enjoy
seeing all those
different spells in action.
I don't want it to end yet!
Black Clover , Page 84:
"The Victors."
Now, let's see which
team of Magic Knights
will take home the glory!