[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] The first round
of the Royal Knights
Selection Exam is heating up!
Asta's Team B...
[NARRATOR]
...Magna's Team C...
...Finral's Team E...
[NARRATOR] ...and Langris's
Team G have each been successful
in their initial matches
and secured their spots
in the second round.
It's too bad that you'll
never be anything more
than a means of transport.
But my magic is useful.
So do try to stay out of my
portals during the next battle.
It would be a shame
if you were to permanently
disappear somewhere.
Forget about what it would
do to Mother and Father.
I think a certain someone would
be quite devastated as well.
Yeah, good point.
So if I wanna prevent that,
then I'll just have
to win, won't I?
[FINRAL] Man. I can't
believe I said that.
Then I'll just have
to win, won't I?
That's my dear brother.
Still insolent as ever.
[FINRAL] I wasn't trying
to make him mad at me.
[sighs]
Now then! Let's move on to match
five of the starting round!
Sweet! Here we go!
Hurry up already.
Members of Team I and Team J:
approach!
May the best fighters win.
Let's have a fair match.
I agree.
This should be fun.
We plan to do our best.
[ASTA] Roland, Wainsley,
Nix, Nils, Ruben...
Why is there an X, though?
I guess somebody went home.
I'm fairly certain "X"
is someone's name.
Really?
Kinda unusual.
A pseudonym?
[KLAUS]
Hm...
I'm sorry. One question.
What is it?
We're supposed to be
on a team with this "X,"
but we don't know who that is.
Is that person even here?
Uh...
I don't understand
what the holdup is.
Find your third team member
or you'll be disqualified.
Er, right.
If the Magic Knight
"X" is present,
then please step forward
so that we can proceed!
"X?"
[X laughs]
Whoa! What's with this guy?
[RUBEN whimpers]
[ALL gasp]
[X]
I am the X you seek!
[ALL grunt]
Just kidding!
It was me, Captain
Rill Boismortier!
You guys should've
seen your faces!
It's Rill, the Aqua Deer
captain! Why's he here?
--[KLAUS gasps]
--I'm confused.
Isn't that the little
guy who can transform
other people's magic
power into paint
using his Picture Magic?
Yeah, why would there
be a captain here?
That's weird.
Wait.
Don't tell me there's
a rule against captains
participating in the exam!
That's not the case at all!
You are welcome here.
[JULIUS]
Perfect!
Now I get to see
Rill's magic as well!
Everyone's accounted for,
so get on with it!
No need to worry, competitors.
Think of this as your chance
to make a strong impression
by defeating a captain!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 76A]
He's right!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 76B] Yeah,
and the way this competition
is set up, we might actually
have a decent shot!
[laughs]
I'm doing this to give the
Aqua Deer a rankings boost
after we came in last
at the Star Festival,
so you'd better believe
I'm not gonna go down
without a fight today!
[WALTER]
Such determination!
You're a great
inspiration, young master.
I'm quite moved.
[ASTA] Now we got grandpas
flyin' in outta nowhere?
Everyone.
I implore you to
look kindly upon Rill
during this competition.
[laughs] Oh, Walt,
stop being so stuffy!
Hey, it's Asta!
[WALTER]
Hm?
[RILL]
Let's do our best!
Yeah! But I'm definitely
gonna beat ya!
Don't speak to a
captain so casually!
Are you guys friends
or something?
[WALTER]
Hm...
Okay, the old geezer's
startin' to scare me!
[whimpers]
[WALTER]
Ah.
And I assume you must be
the young master's
dear friend, Asta?
I must say, he has spoken
very highly of you.
[ASTA]
Where'd that cup come from?
It happened so fast!
Words cannot express
how deeply I appreciate
the companionship you
have shown Master Rill.
But forgive me, for I have
yet to introduce myself.
My name is Walter, his humble
and dedicated servant.
Please accept this.
Oh, okay, don't
mind if I do then.
[ASTA]
This is...!
What, Asta?
It's so fancy,
I can't even taste it!
Moron.
[KLAUS sighs]
Oh, my.
I'm so glad to see he's
finally found a friend.
Not long ago, such a thing
would've been unthinkable.
Wow, seriously?
I'm sorry, that sounds
like it would be rough.
Please do forgive my rudeness.
I cannot help it.
This is all so touching.
[RILL] Cut it out, Walt!
Don't talk about the past.
Don't you know
it's embarrassing?
[WALTER] Right! I beg
your pardon, master!
[EMCEE MAGE]
It's time to continue!
All right! I can't wait to
paint my next masterpiece!
[NILS, RUBEN] What does
he mean, "masterpiece"?
The fifth match of round one!
Team I: Rill, Nils, and Ruben
vs. Team J: Wainsley,
Roland, and Nix!
We're facing the captain
of the Aqua Deer.
I wonder what he's like?
Master Rill.
Begin the battle!
[RILL]
Hm...
I'm sorry, sir,
what are you doing?
They just said go.
[RILL]
The sky looks so pretty!
[NILS, RUBEN gasp]
I betcha I can get that exact
color if I use lapis lazuli!
You can create blue paint
by crushing up gemstones!
Interesting, right?
[BOTH]
Oh.
[RILL] Then, I'll add in a
little whitewash for the clouds.
Whitewash is a special
kind of paint that's made
out of seashells,
in case you didn't know.
Wow, I couldn't ask for
a more beautiful skyscape
for us to compete under today!
All right, team,
I'm ready when you are!
I'm about to paint a marvelous
picture on the inviting
blank canvas that
is our battlefield!
Follow my lead, okay?
Here we go!
He just up and left us.
I admire his initiative,
but that's too much.
Oh, no!
They captured me!
They're like five seconds in
and he already screwed up?
And this boy is a
captain? Oh, dear.
He was so busy
daydreaming about the sky
that he walked
directly into a trap.
Well, this match is
going to be fairly brief.
[chuckles]
I didn't expect him to
be that easy to catch.
I actually feel kinda guilty.
He is a captain, after all.
It doesn't matter,
a win is a win.
We should face our foes
with our full might,
no matter how
unthreatening they are!
Right.
Works for me.
Here goes!
[yells]
[ROLAND] I'll use Plant
Reinforcement Magic:
Magic Pollen! Your turn!
All right, Flame Magic:
Flame Spike technique!
I'll finish this!
Ice Magic: Icicle Bridge!
[ROLAND, NIX, WAINSLEY] Take
that, Captain of the Aqua Deer.
You're going down!
[RILL]
Wow. Their spells are exquisite,
and they know just
how to use them!
This battlefield really
is the ideal canvas.
I'm so inspired!
I feel my creativity
starting to flow, Walt!
Not again.
[VILLAGER 76B]
How many times is that today?
It's practically constant.
Ever since the Boismortier
child received his grimoire,
he's been holed up in his room,
allowing his magic to run wild.
[VILLAGERS gasp]
I know he's always been a
bit of a strange little boy,
but since the awarding ceremony,
he almost seems to be possessed.
[VILLAGER 76A]
Right.
And with that enormous amount
of power he's wielding,
he's impossible to control.
I hear his poor mother
is at her wit's end.
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[sobs] How could my
son have become
such a terror?
My lady, please calm yourself.
[RILL'S MOTHER]
I can't get him to listen
to a single word I say.
All he does is
paint all day long!
[sobs] My sweet boy.
--[explosion]
--[RILL'S MOTHER, MAID 76A gasp]
I don't even understand
him anymore. He's a monster!
It's wrong. Wrong, wrong,
wrong, wrong, wrong!
[RILL]
I hate this.
It isn't what I wanted
to paint at all!
[RILL]
It should be more. More!
[RILL'S MOTHER] Please stop
painting now, Rill!
How can you cause
me so much pain?
I almost wish...
No, I do wish...
I wish you'd never been born!
You don't understand my art,
and you never will!
Never, ever!
[footsteps]
[WALTER] Young master.
May I have a word with you?
[RILL]
Shut up, Walter! Get out!
[WALTER]
But, sir--
Just go!
Why can't I paint
the way I want?
Art's supposed to be
fun! This is boring!
Everybody, leave me alone!
[RILL] They have no idea
how much I'm suffering.
Not Walter. Not Mother. No one!
None of you understand me--
[RILL gasps]
That's good.
It's a relief that you're
finally able to see me properly,
young Master Rill.
Walt.
[WALTER]
Is your face hurting?
What?
When someone sustains
an injury, it causes pain.
That's the reason people are
so afraid of getting hurt.
We tend to be frightened of
what we fail to understand.
So we are reluctant to
draw close to such things.
That's why you should try
to understand others.
So that they can
understand you, too.
You love to make art.
Don't you want someone
else to see it as well?
Although, a tiny canvas
such as this cannot hope
to contain your outstanding
talent, young master.
Your abilities are
far too great.
It must be difficult to get
the people in your life
to understand you.
That's the way it is
for those who shine
as brightly as you do.
But I know of a canvas
where you can unleash
your colorful magic power
to your heart's content.
Huh? Where's that?
Join The Magic Knights.
The Magic Knights, huh?
Yes. Would you like
to give it a try?
After all, with impressive
abilities like yours,
you're sure to be accepted.
And then, you'll be
free to paint upon
the never-ending canvas that
spreads out along your path.
You'll create a
masterpiece like no other!
Do you really think
I can do that, Walt?
Indeed.
Well, then. I'm gonna go for it!
Oh! Sorry for hurting
you. Are you okay?
It's just a scratch, sir.
The right butler can make
anything look good as new.
[giggles]
[BOTH laughing]
Are you sure you'd prefer
not to say any goodbyes
before you depart, Master Rill?
[RILL]
Yeah. I won't be lonely, though.
[WALTER]
Hm?
[RILL] The people I love
will always be smiling
in the paintings in my heart.
Of course.
[laughs] I'm ready. Let's go!
Magic Knights test,
I'm on my way!
Please forgive me, son.
Goodbye.
[WALTER] Your talents have
blossomed immensely
during your time with
the Magic Knights.
And now you're
the youngest person
ever to become a captain.
You are the greatest pride
of the House Boismortier!
[RILL] Ah, this canvas
takes my breath away!
You know what, Walt?
I'm gonna show the
world my masterpiece,
but I want you to see it first!
[RILL] 'Cause you helped me
become who I want to be!
[WALTER]
The young master's Picture Magic
has a unique capability.
Picture Magic: Twin Storms
of Fire and Water!
[WALTER] It can recreate
any spell's attribute!
[WAINSLEY gasps]
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
He attacked both of
them with techniques
that they're weak against,
and at the exact same time!
[WALTER] The mightier his foes,
the greater his inspiration.
The young master's
creativity is infinite!
I knew you could do it!
Good show, sir!
But... how?
[laughs] Don't take it too hard,
you've got a lot of potential,
but you're a little far away
from becoming a masterpiece!
[giggles]
[RILL gasps]
Thanks a lot!
Not at all, sir! Um, that
spell was incredible, Captain.
I've never seen
anything like it.
[laughs]
Sandstone Magic: Rock Storm!
[ROLAND grunts]
[EMCEE MAGE]
Crystal destroyed! Team I wins!
[MAGIC KNIGHTS cheer]
Now that was an
interesting battle!
Eh. Just as I thought.
I'm relieved we made it
through the first round.
Guess so.
By the way, do you have any
idea what he's doing there?
Huh?
I could have gone with a
rougher hand on that side.
Oh, but that shade of cobalt
blue came out really pretty!
Hm, it's not quite perfect yet.
[BOTH]
Captain?
Shouldn't you be focused
on the tournament?
[RILL]
Hm...
[NILS, RUBEN] We'll have to
really be on our toes.
I see the young master's
letting his mind wander
to ensure his teammates
are giving it their best!
He truly is a talented leader!
[ASTA]
That makes no sense!
Now it's time to get
ready for the sixth match
of the first round!
Team K and Team L: approach!
Oh. It would appear
it's our turn.
Hm...
Captain Rill, let's go back.
[EMCEE MAGE] Please clear
the arena to make room
for the next contestants!
Oh! Right, we're so sorry!
We're working on it!
[RILL]
Hm...
[gasps]
Wait. What are you doing?
Stop, I need to look
at my art some more!
Let me go!
Hey, what's up? Is it over yet?
Yep! And you're up next!
Knock 'em dead!
Just try not to fail miserably.
[LUCK]
Right! Thanks, guys!
It's finally our turn to fight!
Yay! I can't wait!
[KLAUS]
Luck Voltia.
This contest will
decide your eligibility
for the Royal Knights.
So please take it seriously!
I'll be the leader.
No going solo,
do you understand me?
[LUCK] Aw, don't suck
all the fun out of it!
Listen here, you little ruffian.
Your foolishness
had better not...
[PULI] These two clowns
are my teammates?
A restless brat and
a fussy four-eyes.
I smell trouble!
My gut's telling me I'll have
to carry this team on my own!
[PULI]
Hm.
Well, I see no point in
getting mad about it now!
Let's crush that
crystal! You ready?
What the...?
[laughs] Who are you, lady?
Your third team member.
Puli. Puli Angel!
As I'm sure you've noticed,
my name suits me perfectly!
Oh! Okay, it's
nice to meet you!
[PULI]
We'll give them a performance
they'll never forget!
Yeah!
[KLAUS] Great, she's just as
carefree about this as he is!
In that case...
I'll have to work as
hard as possible.
We're rootin' for ya, Specs!
Good luck out there.
I know you can do it!
If you lose this, I'm never
calling you "sir" again.
Disrespectful as
always, aren't you?
Just wait and see;
you won't be disappointed.
[LUCK] Hey, we should
come up with a plan first.
Good thinking.
If there's one opponent
we need to be careful of...
...it's the Wind mage who's said
to be the swiftest in his squad.
Second Class Senior Magic Knight
from the Silver Eagles,
Rob Vitesse.
And with that,
it's time for match six!
Team K: Puli, Klaus, and Luck,
vs. Team L: Rob,
Francis, and Winston!
The battle begins now!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[RILL]
"Wrong!"
It's wrong.
Wrong, wrong, wrong,
wrong, wrong!
[RILL]
I hate this.
It isn't what I wanted
to paint at all!
It should be more.
More!
It's not beautiful enough.
You do realize that I'm
standing right here, do you not?
Something beautiful.
[RILL]
Yes, like that!
I wish he would
disappear forever.
Why am I even here?
[WALTER] It is I, Walter,
loving and devoted butler
to Rill Boismortier,
Captain of the Aqua Deer.
Ah, young master,
look at how far you've come!
Black Clover , Page 77:
"Bad Blood."
Your mother is beaming
with pride as well, sir!