[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] Yami had just
arrived at the Golden Dawn
headquarters for a meeting
with Vangeance when...
[YAMI] I thought ole' Goldiguts
called me here to apologize.
What's the big idea makin'
me wait around all day?
How much longer
is this gonna take?
I'm sure that he'll be here
as soon as possible!
You playin' me for
a fool, Golden Dawn?
[BOTH grunt]
[NARRATOR] Yami continued
to wait, trusting the man
who'd fought alongside him
on behalf of their nation,
and with whom he'd become
a Magic Knight captain.
But in the meantime,
Vangeance was revealing
his alternate identity
during a confrontation
with the Wizard King.
With two separate souls
inhabiting his body at once,
he was not only
Captain William Vangeance
of the Golden Dawn,
but also Licht,
the leader of the Eye
of the Midnight Sun.
[LICHT]
William, my only human friend,
I know this was hard for you.
I'm grateful.
Greetings to you.
Wizard King, Julius Novachrono.
I am the leader of the
Eye of the Midnight Sun
known as Licht.
I have dreaded this day.
Yet here we are.
[NARRATOR] Licht challenged
Julius to a battle,
hoping to steal the final
two magic stones he needed
to enact his revenge
against humankind.
But Julius used Time Magic
to predict and
block his attacks.
[LICHT]
It's over!
His predictions are improving!
[JULIUS]
I can already see your future.
And I can assure you,
it ends in defeat.
[CLOVER CITIZENS murmuring]
[VILLAGER 93A]
Hey, look!
[VILLAGER 93B]
The castle tower!
[VILLAGER 93C]
What are all those flashes?
[VILLAGER 93D]
Something's going on up there!
[MARX panting]
[MAGIC KNIGHT 93A]
Over here!
Look, sir!
[MARX]
That power--it's Julius!
He must be fighting someone!
A Light Magic user strong
enough to be holding
his own against the Wizard King.
Who else could it be
but the leader
of the Eye of the
Midnight Sun... Licht.
[MARX] Except, the Royal
Knights are supposed to be
out on a mission to
eliminate him right now!
[MARX]
How did he get to the castle?
Is the Midnight Sun to blame
for the communication
breakdown between
me and Julius?
[MARX]
There's so much we don't know.
[MAGIC KNIGHT 93B]
What's happening out there?
[MAGIC KNIGHT 93C] Is Sir Julius
fighting with somebody?
[MAGIC KNIGHT 93A]
What can we do to stop this?
[MARX]
Please remain calm.
Our mettle may be tested
in times like this,
but we'll never be able
to defend Clover Kingdom
if we let panic overtake us!
[MARX]
That's right, just stay calm.
Now, more than ever, my duty
is to keep a cool head.
If any of us got involved,
the difference in skill
would only hold Julius back!
[MARX] I don't expect
he'll be defeated.
If it came down to it,
the only knights
fit to join the fray
would be captain-caliber.
[MARX] I'll send an alert to all
the Magic Knight headquarters!
What the heck?
Hey, Char!
A Transmission Spell?
A call from the
Royal Capital, sir.
This is an urgent
message to all captains!
The Wizard King is at
Clover Castle fighting someone
who appears to be the leader
of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
As was the case with
the previous assault
on the capital, it's possible
that they're plotting
multiple attacks.
Knights, please follow
your captains' orders
on where to stand guard.
And, Captains, finish
organizing your guard squads
and assemble in
the Royal Capital!
I don't understand this!
Yeah, I thought
Captain Mereoleona
was infiltrating their hideout.
[LEOPOLD] Their leader is
attacking the Royal Capital?
This is the perfect chance
to avenge my brother! But...
What's with all
these pitiful faces?
You dare to call
yourselves members
of the Crimson Lion Kings?
[CRIMSON LIONS]
Sir!
Remember what my
brother said to you.
It's always best to stay calm!
Even though my
sister isn't here,
we will follow the
instructions from the capital
and attack the enemy on our own!
He's got a point!
This is no time
for us to falter!
[CRIMSON LION 71F] Yeah,
we're the Crimson Lion Kings!
[GOLDEN DAWN 92B]
It says we're to follow orders,
but the captain is
nowhere to be found.
[GOLDEN DAWN 92A]
I sure hope Captain Vangeance
gets back soon.
[YAMI]
Don't tell me...
I hope I'm wrong about this.
[JULIUS] Your attacks are
growing quite pedestrian.
Even without looking
into the future,
I don't think I'll have very
much trouble avoiding them.
[LICHT yells]
[LICHT] He can keep up
with me at this speed?
Just how far into the future
is this human able to see?
[LICHT yells]
Is this yours?
[LICHT] He sped up my spell
and threw it back?
[JULIUS]
Wow! Close call.
Despite my ability to see
what you're going to do next,
you're too quick on your feet
for me to catch up with you.
[LICHT]
But how? What is this strength?
He's only human.
He shouldn't be able to--
You know, you'd be
awfully helpful to me
if you'd surrender
right about now.
I wouldn't wanna cause any
damage to Vangeance's body.
[LICHT]
So he won't kill me.
He's trying to
capture me instead.
He's holding back!
Against me and my
four-leaf grimoire?
All right, then what
must his be like?
And where could it be?
I assume you must
be getting curious
about my grimoire.
You're welcome to
examine it for yourself.
It's right up there.
[LICHT gasps]
[LICHT]
It doesn't even have a cover!
What kind of grimoire has
a bizarre shape like that?
I'm a Time Magic user
with a coverless grimoire.
I never knew whether
that was good or bad,
but I could tell that it meant
I was something special.
I thought hard about it,
and I realized that
this grimoire and I
have a lot in common.
Neither of us fits into
a particular category.
So, who am I, really?
What am I meant to achieve?
I asked myself these
questions for years,
and the more I learned,
the more I wondered.
After I'd made it this far,
it was finally clear.
The path I'd walked
all this way; that is me.
[JULIUS]
I am the Wizard King.
[gasps]
[LICHT]
Yes, I understand now.
What we're planning
to do once we have
the magic stones will be
an attempt to violate
the natural laws of this world!
So, this man... This human...
He must have been placed
here by Fate itself
in order to thwart
our ambitions!
He is the final
bastion of reason!
And as the Wizard King,
I'll protect the people
of Clover. Come what may.
[LICHT]
I knew it.
That's all the more reason
why I must end his life!
Protect them? Go ahead and try!
[LICHT]
Sealing Magic: Release!
[JULIUS]
He's expanded his power!
Hey. What's that?
Look up in the sky!
Oh, dear, what's
going to happen now?
[JULIUS]
It's absolutely gargantuan.
Humans took away everything.
All of our happiness!
Our friends and loved ones.
Our peaceful days.
Just like that.
It may be an affront to reason,
but you'll atone for
your sins. Now, die!
[JULIUS] He's been holding
onto enough power
to cover the entire kingdom.
Is he going to release
all of that magic
and wipe out the whole populace?
[LICHT]
I may not be able to kill you.
But I can easily
exterminate everybody else.
Whoa, is that magic?
Swords of light--
thousands of them!
[CHILD 93AA] Look, Mama,
the sky's full of swords!
[CHILD 93A]
So bright!
[VILLAGER 93I]
Those blades could kill us all.
Is this how the world ends?
It's unbelievable.
[NASH] What's that bright light?
It's way over there.
I have a bad feeling.
It's all right.
Even if it turns out to be
something dangerous.
We'll always have
the brave Magic Knights
to guard the Clover Kingdom.
[YAMI] That's a big
hunk o' Light Magic.
Dammit! What the hell
is this, Julius?
I gotta hurry!
[JULIUS] His spell's already
covering everything in sight.
At this rate...
Now... Here is your
punishment, humans!
Light Magic: Arrows of Judgment!
[JULIUS]
I did have my doubts.
Honestly, why do
the regular folk
have such pathetic magic
compared to people like us?
I couldn't agree more.
To tell you the truth,
I'm not sure why
commoners exist
in the first place.
We shouldn't have to share
the same country with them!
[NOBLE 93A]
I'll drink to that!
[NOBLES laugh]
[JULIUS]
But is that really true?
What're you looking at?
Nothing.
[JULIUS] They had strong magic
power, and yet the only thing
they ever used it for
was to selfishly
line their own pockets.
Why did these
useless mages exist?
I see. You're that
Magic Knight, aren't you?
Yes, the one with
the strange grimoire.
Well, no matter.
Anyway, I was about to tell
you, there's a merchant
who wants me to give
his business a leg up.
[NOBLE 93B]
Really?
[NOBLE 93A]
Oh, we'll talk.
[NOBLE 93B laughs]
I can't wait to hear!
[JULIUS] I kept fighting
in my Magic Knight squad,
hoping I'd eventually
discover my calling.
Then, one day...
[gasps]
[BANDIT 93A cackles]
Gimme all your yul
or I'll bash your face in!
[ZARA]
Hold it!
You villains are always
disturbing the peace,
and I'm fed up with it!
[JULIUS]
...I met Zara.
The very first commoner
to be selected
as a member of
the Magic Knights.
We'll fight if you want.
But so you know, my magic's
about 100 times tougher
than anything you
can throw at me!
A Magic Knight, eh?
Am I s'posed to be scared
of you or somethin', pal?
That's a bad move.
Had enough?
Now, go find somewhere safe.
[VILLAGER 93L] Thank you.
We're so glad you showed up.
Hey, you, do me a favor!
Come down for a sec!
[JULIUS] His power itself
was weak, but his strategic
fighting style made
full use of Trap Magic.
It was clear he had
worked hard to master it.
What kind of crazy
spell is that?
It's almost like you're turning
back time or something!
It looks that way, but
that's not exactly the case.
Time Magic, huh?
That is impressive!
Seems like it would
be a sure-fire way
to prevent casualties.
You're Zara, aren't you?
It appears that you're
injured as well.
Sit down and rest
so I can take a look.
[ZARA]
Nah, I'll be all right.
When you're a Magic
Knight, you're supposed
to put the lives of
the civilians first!
You agree. Dontcha, Julius?
Okay, this guy seems fine.
[JULIUS]
Unlike all the knights
who were selfishly
seeking glory...
He was truly prioritizing the
lives of the people he saved.
I still didn't know
what a Magic Knight
was really supposed to be,
but even I saw that he
was the genuine article.
Later on, I learned
that Zara had died.
[JULIUS]
Hey. Are you--?
[JULIUS] Zara had carried out
his duty as a Magic Knight,
and I wanted to follow
in his footsteps.
I was finally sure
of my purpose in life.
To become the kind
of knight he was.
[MAGIC KNIGHT 93HA]
They're saying he was murdered
by one of his own squad members.
[MAGIC KNIGHT 93HB laughs]
Really?
Well, we can't have a nasty
rumor like that going around.
[MAGIC KNIGHT 93HC]
Word is he was prying
into things he shouldn't.
[MAGIC KNIGHT 93HD] What's one
dead commoner, anyway?
No one's going to miss him!
[MAGIC KNIGHTS laugh]
[JULIUS] How could this
possibly be right?
And it wasn't just among
the Magic Knights, either.
It was the way the
country had always been.
The class system made
the nobles prideful
and the commoners hopeless.
There had to be more,
on both sides of the coin.
Magic potential, human
potential, is infinite!
But to be heard, I needed
power, standing, and trust.
I devoted my efforts
to producing results
and became the Wizard King.
Surely magic, and people,
should be more free.
It hasn't happened overnight.
But I can see now that,
little by little,
this kingdom and its people
are finally beginning to change.
After all the ones I came
to trust and respect
combined their strength,
as well as the strength
of those who they trusted...
As the Wizard King,
I can't let it end here!
I refuse to!
[JULIUS] Time Reversal Magic:
Chrono Anastasis!
[VILLAGER 93N]
What's happening now?
[LICHT] Your Time Magic
was enough to save them.
Impressive. Though, it
would appear you've used
all the time and power
you had saved up.
You would have seen this
attack of mine coming.
But, unfortunately, you
weren't able to call off
that final Time Magic spell
in order to get out of the way.
Because you're...
the Wizard King.
[YAMI gasps]
[LICHT]
And being the Wizard King...
...is your one
and only weakness.
[YAMI] What happened here?
Tell me, Vangeance!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[MARX]
"Calm Yourselves!"
[MAGIC KNIGHT 93B]
What's happening out there?
[MAGIC KNIGHT 93C] Is Sir Julius
fighting with somebody?
[MAGIC KNIGHT 93A]
What can we do to stop this?
[MARX]
Please remain calm.
[MAGIC KNIGHTS gasp]
[MARX]
That's right, just stay calm.
Now, more than ever, my duty
is to keep a cool head.
I don't expect
he'll be defeated.
If it came down to it,
the only knights
fit to join the fray
would be captain-caliber.
I'll send an alert to all
the Magic Knight headquarters!
You've reached "My Magic is
Never Giving Up" Bar & Grill,
what's your order?
I'm sorry, I must've
called the wrong place!
[MARX] Okay, this time I'll
call the Magic Knights!
Thank you for calling the
Melty Mana Hot Spring Resort,
are you making a reservation?
No thanks, I'm fine!
[MARX]
One more try!
And who might this be?
Uh, hello there, ma'am,
is this a Magic
Knight headquarters?
I told you people
I don't want any!
[MARX]
Damn! I can't get through!
What the hell am I
doing wrong here?
[MAGIC KNIGHT 93B]
It's okay. Just stay calm.
[MARX]
Right.
[YAMI] What's gotten
into you, Vangeance?
You just betrayed Julius's
trust and my friendship.
And for that,
you deserve to die!
Black Clover ,
Page 94: "New Future."
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked
Dimension Slash!