[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[paper rustling]
[breathing heavily]
As you may be aware,
Asta's arms have been
repaired by the Queen
who resides within
the Forest of Witches.
That's good. I was
so worried about him,
I've had trouble slee-- Oh!
Wait! No, I haven't!
I've slept just like a baby!
Um, what I meant was...
I know you've all
been concerned,
so now you can rest easy!
Please, I'm not concerned
about him in the least.
[gasps] Nor am I!
But, sir, you've been
outside every night
dousing yourself with water
and saying prayers.
[KLAUS]
Please restore Asta's arms!
[gasps] How did you know?
I went out to do some
prayers of my own,
but I saw that you
were already there--
Ah-- On second thought,
forget everything I just said.
I didn't see you, I promise!
Yes, Precisely!
And I didn't do
anything absurd either!
I don't know--
[KLAUS] Eh-hem! At any rate,
I've called you here to discuss
something very important.
My, you're so serious now, sir.
It concerns that
terrorist group.
The Midnight Sun attacked
the Forest of Witches
to acquire the
Queen's magic stone.
Fortunately, they failed.
So Asta and his squad
obtained the stone themselves.
Asta really is one of a kind!
My point is, it's highly
likely we'll be forced
to contend with them
in the future.
So welcome to the Eye of the
Midnight Sun study session!
You! Tell us every single detail
you know about the organization!
Everything that
I know? Let me see.
There was that surprise
attack on the royal capital.
[CITIZENS screaming]
[RADES cackling]
[YUNO] We Magic Knights
were called to the scene.
Let's see how you
like this spell.
My Flame Magic: Spiral Flames!
Go, Flame Magic: Sol Linea!
Steel Creation Magic:
Go, Spiral Lance!
Glass Creation Magic:
Fleur de Verre.
[HAMON laughs]
Sand Creation Magic:
Sand-Armored Guard!
Anybody who's been wounded,
please come and
see me immediately!
[SOL] Earth Creation Magic:
Raging Mother Goddess!
[RAGING MOTHER GODDESS growls]
Not one step further.
No one is permitted to touch me.
Briar Creation Magic:
Corpse-Hunting Briar Trees!
Water Creation Magic:
Slashing Sea Serpent!
[ALL]
Mist Magic: Solid Mist Clones.
[NOZEL]
Receive your punishment.
Mercury Magic: Rain of Silver!
[NOZEL] This is what happens
to those who dare
to rise up against our
land. We crush them.
Flame Creation Magic:
Leo Rugiens!
Burn to ash!
Hey, look!
They're so powerful!
Is there anything they can't do?
There's just one very important
thing to know about me.
The truth is,
I would rather give
my life than lose!
Wind Spirit Magic:
Sylph's Breath!
[CATHERINE screams]
[YUNO] But, what they
were really after
belonged to Captain Fuegoleon
of the Crimson Lion Kings.
It's you!
[ASTA gasps]
[gasps]
[NOELLE screams]
[JULIUS]
I see.
And we don't know
when he'll wake up?
Losing a man like Fuegoleon
would be quite a blow.
The consequences
of my misjudgment.
No, it's our inexperience
that's to blame.
And there's something else.
We discovered that
the pendant Fuegoleon
was wearing has disappeared.
[JULIUS] The multicolored jewels
embedded in that tablet.
The next time they were spotted,
it was close to the
small village of Nean.
Asta's group saw them
while on a break.
How bizarre.
Asta must be connected
to them by fate!
That day, they faced the
group's leader called Licht.
And...
[LICHT]
I'll introduce you.
These three are the strongest
members of the Midnight Sun.
They are the Third Eye.
Antithetical to integrity,
we have Rhya the Disloyal.
As the antithesis to hope,
we have Vetto the Despair.
And, as the inverse of love,
we have Fana the Hateful.
Now, let's get this over with.
Hah!
Kill them.
Spirit Magic:
Salamander's Breath.
[KLAUS] Even Captain Yami
struggled against
that trio of powerful mages.
You're having way too much fun
on your own here, Yami.
You should let the
rest of us in on it.
Aw, man.
Just when I was about to have
some kinda awakening, too.
I would expect somebody who was
in your position to speak
with greater care.
How pitiful.
You couldn't handle a few
measly mages without us?
[KLAUS] But then,
Captain Jack the Ripper
of the Green Praying Mantises,
Captain Nozel Silva
of the Silver Eagles,
and Captain Charlotte Roselei
of the Blue Rose
Knights appeared.
Briar Creation Magic:
Corpse-Hunting Briar Trees.
Severing Magic: Death Scythe!
I've been waiting
for this. Finally!
Mercury Magic: Silver Spears!
[VETTO yells]
[CHARLOTTE grunts]
[YAMI] He's been weakened,
but I'm not gonna
risk letting him get away.
[LICHT] Ah, yes.
I expected this from you.
I'll end you this time.
[YAMI] You're goin' after
the boss, too, aren't ya?
All right. Bring it!
My magic is never giving up!
[YAMI yells]
[laughs] Gotcha.
So, what'd ya think about
my magic-free smash attack?
No!
This cannot be!
Why do you have that grimoire?
Why do you wield them?
The demon-slayer sword
and the demon-dweller sword.
Those swords belong
to the master!
This grimoire and
these swords are mine.
I don't care if
they're all beat up!
They're not yours.
Give them back to
their rightful owner!
His body isn't going to
hold out much longer.
We need to hurry!
[VETTO, RHYA, FANA]
Trinity Sealing Magic!
You pushed yourself
too hard this time, Licht.
Our boss is feeling
a bit under the weather.
So I'm afraid we're gonna
have to call it a day.
I promise, when we meet
again I won't leave
until you've tasted
true despair.
The next time we meet,
you'll draw your last breath.
Remember, wherever you go,
the Eye of the Midnight
Sun is watching.
Despite some difficulty,
the Captains fought off
Licht and the Third Eye.
[YUNO] If you ask me,
I could've accomplished
that on my own.
And I wouldn't get hurt, either.
After that was over,
an investigation revealed
why the Midnight Sun wanted
Fuegoleon's pendant
so desperately.
According to our captives,
they call the gems
embedded in that tablet
"magic stones."
They believe that gathering
them will allow them
to be reborn into their
"true forms" with close ties
to the mana, thereby granting
them immense power.
Apparently that was the reason
they targeted Fuegoleon--
because of the
magic stone he wore.
Four stones remain
to be gathered.
And from what our captives said,
it seems they know the
location of one of them.
[YAMI]
Where's that?
[JULIUS]
The Underwater Temple,
one of the "strong
magic regions."
Oh, yeah, I understand now.
So we have to get there before
the Eye of the Midnight Sun
does and make off with
this magic stone thingy?
Thank you, Yami.
I'm counting on you.
Oh, and Asta?
Yes, sir!
[ASTA screams]
I think I felt my heart stop!
[YAMI] Never seen someone injure
themselves givin' a salute.
And so, the Black Bulls headed
for the Underwater Temple.
Asta, again. Why didn't
he ask me instead?
The Wizard King
must've taken a liking
to Asta, too, and I can see why.
Well, I can't.
As soon as the
Black Bulls arrived
at the Underwater Temple,
trouble ensued.
They were confronted by a member
of the Third Eye,
the Midnight Sun's
three most vicious fighters.
Vetto the Despair.
Well, it looks like
you folks are having
quite a get-together.
How about... you guys
let me in the mix?
[BOTH]
We won't give up!
We're gonna fight with
everything we've got!
Combo Spell:
Flame Lightning
Exploding Cannon!
[MAGNA, LUCK yelling]
[ASTA groans]
[VETTO]
Go on. Howl!
--Embrace your despair!
--[screams]
[ASTA] No one ever protected
anybody by giving up!
What?
[KAHONO sings]
[NOELLE, KAHONO]
What he said was,
"No one ever protected
anybody by giving up!"
[yells]
[VETTO] A sparrow's song,
and a waltzing mouse.
I wouldn't expect them
to be so powerful.
They have some unique
spells for living
in such a remote location.
[KIATO]
That's right!
This place is what
shaped our magic!
It's been woven into the
very fabric of our lives.
Generations of our people
have praised the sea god
with their singing and dancing.
[KAHONO] We've been practicing
all of our lives.
Each song and each dance is
an offering to the sea god.
To him, and to everyone we love!
This magic bonds the people
of the Underwater Temple.
[KIATO yells]
[NOELLE]
There's no way!
[VETTO cackles]
Done with your
little speech now?
Kiato!
[VETTO]
Dreams? And bonds?
Don't speak such
words to me, girl!
Kahono!
[NOELLE gasps]
[VETTO] Where did all
this power come from?
Release my friend at once.
Or you'll regret it!
Hold on. Are you royalty?
[NOELLE] I am Noelle Silva
of the Black Bulls.
And I'm done standing by
and watching while you hurt
my friends and squadmates!
Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Roar!
Bear Claw!
[yells]
[panting]
How's that?
[yells]
[VETTO cackles]
[gasps]
You have my gratitude
for summoning me, human.
[NOELLE]
Where'd that eye come from?
Now begone, my little mouse!
Mythical Beast Magic:
Epohlla Puevig!
[VETTO cackles]
[ASTA panting]
Asta! You saved me!
[ASTA] Not yet. It's
not... It's not over.
You haven't won!
We haven't given up,
and we're not going to!
[yells]
Hey, Despair!
[screams]
[ASTA]
This is where you lose!
[KLAUS] At long last,
after an all-out war...
Take that, jerk.
--[FINRAL] Got you, Asta!
--[VANESSA] Got you, kiddo!
Jeez.
Do you have any idea how
incredible you were out there?
That was amazing!
Damn.
That shrimp's got
some serious guts.
[BOTH gasp]
His power's back?
[VETTO] I'm taking you
with me. All of you.
In fact, I'm going to blow
this entire temple away!
All right! Now come and get us!
[YAMI]
I miss anything?
Hey there, you dumbbells.
How's it goin'?
[ALL]
Captain Yami!
[YAMI]
Finral.
Vanessa.
Noelle.
Gauche.
Charmy.
Who're you?
Oh, uh, yeah, I'm Grey.
[YAMI]
You guys, too, Magna, Luck.
Real good work, all of you.
Since you've done
so much already,
I'll handle the clean-up.
Ha. Who am I kidding?
This is the best part.
I meant it, though.
You all did a fine job.
You may be knuckleheads,
but you guys pushed
me past my limits.
[BLACK BULLS gasp]
Don't waste your time!
You humans will taste despair!
Yes! Despair!
[YAMI] Would you shut up
about your damn
despair already, ya freak?
However strong your
magic might be now,
it doesn't matter!
'Cause this spell slashes
through dimensions!
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked.
Dimension Slash!
[VETTO gasps]
[YAMI] Thanks for
toughenin' up my squad.
Now goodbye, Mister Despair.
[KLAUS] And so, having
defeated Vetto and secured
the magic stone from
the Underwater Temple,
the Black Bulls had finally
completed their mission.
Now then, concerning the Queen.
That stone is a
type of magic item
that enhances the power of
the individual who wears it.
But only a member
of the Elf Tribe
is able to use it effectively.
This Midnight Sun
is a curious lot.
I wonder if they might be
descended from the Elf Tribe.
Listen well, Asta.
The two weapons you carry
are all that remain
of the pair of magic
swords once wielded
by the leader of the Elf Tribe.
The elves.
The ones from the legends.
So they were actually real?
Regardless of which
magic stones are held
by whom, we can't say for
certain what will take place.
But still!
Whatever the future may
hold, we Magic Knights
will always protect the Clover
Kingdom and its inhabitants!
Yuno, Mimosa,
I'm counting on you.
Right!
There's no need to worry.
I'll stop any foe who dares
to stand in our way.
Because I'm going
to be the Wizard King.
You got that, Asta?
You will never get
the best of me!
Take a look at that.
It's from that old broad who
runs the Forest of Witches.
Fighting off the Eye
of the Midnight Sun
and the Diamond army
at the same time!
It sounds like the
Black Bulls have done
yet another remarkable job.
Thank you, as always.
That's nice and all, but I
feel like my team and I
deserve a handful of stars
to go with that thank-you.
Come on, man. Don't hold out.
[coughs] Now then.
We've had a great deal of news.
Some good, some not so good.
The good news is that
we're close to locating
the Eye of the
Midnight Sun's hideout.
Yeah?
You're right, that's
really good news.
Now tell me the not-so-good.
It would appear as
though they're only
just getting started,
I'm afraid.
Very soon, we'll have
to fight them again.
Let's be ready.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[KLAUS, MIMOSA]
"Prayers."
Please restore Asta's arms!
...501, 502, 503...
Yuno! You try, too!
[YUNO]
Nope.
[KLAUS]
Don't be shy! Hurry!
[JULIUS]
Hey, This is kind of fun.
Can I leave now?
[JULIUS] Time to announce
the achievements
for all the Magic Knight
squads at the Star Festival!
Should be interesting!
Black Clover , Page 67:
"A Fun Festival Double Date!"
Ooh, a date! I remember
when I was young.
Time for a stroll
down memory lane.