[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward
and took up the fight.
The hero's name was
Lumiere Silvamillion Clover.
[NARRATOR] He was later hailed
as the First Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[SECRÉ] The devil was
sealed for 500 years,
but the day would soon come
when the seal would break.
Against all reason
in this world,
I was transformed into a bird,
and I continued to guard
Licht's grimoire.
[SECRÉ] In the present day, this
place is called Hage Village.
It's situated far away
from the royal capital
of the Clover Kingdom.
A hamlet in the Forsaken Realm.
[YUNO]
Asta! Hang in there.
I'm sorry. It's all
my fault. I'm so sorry.
[ASTA] This? Please.
Don't worry about it.
This is nothin'. After all,
I'm gonna be the
Wizard King, right?
I'm gonna be the Wizard King.
I'll keep you and
everybody else safe.
No more worrying
about food or money.
You'll have everything
you ever wanted.
[YUNO gasps]
[ASTA] I'll prove it.
I'll show them all.
Show them? Prove what?
That even if you're poor...
...a commoner and an orphan...
...you can still become
the Wizard King.
You really think so?
[ASTA]
Yeah!
Commoners? Orphans?
Anybody can do it.
As long as they're
willing to work hard.
[YUNO]
Anybody?
Even me, and even you.
[gasps]
I... I'm never going
to cry again.
I've decided.
Whatddya mean?
I'll do it, too.
I'm going to become
the Wizard King.
I'll work hard and get strong
so I can protect you
and everybody else.
I'll do whatever it takes,
and I'll never give up!
[PATRY gasps]
[PATRY]
What is this place?
What happened to me?
I thought... I was dead.
[gasps] I look like Licht!
[PATRY]
What is this?
Have I become him somehow?
Did my spirit implant
itself in his body?
That's not it.
Judging by how this mana feels,
the body I'm in is human!
A human that looks like Licht.
I see. So I really did die.
Whatever Licht unleashed
when our magic
was sealed away,
it must have been
some kind of forbidden spell,
and something
extremely powerful, too!
Like Reincarnation Magic!
This light.
[PATRY] I can sense them,
every single one!
I can feel Rhya's soul,
and the souls
of all the other elves
in this village!
Licht must have done this
in the final few
seconds of his life!
And all for the sake
of our people.
[PATRY] I have been chosen.
I'll become Licht!
No matter what it takes.
[PATRY] I'll revive all the
elves. As for the humans...
For going back on their word,
for killing the people
I loved, they must pay!
I swear, they will
all be annihilated!
[PATRY]
So, these three are the souls
I was able to restore
at this juncture.
It's as if they never died.
But I'll need greater power
to bring back the rest.
And that means supplying
even more sacrifices.
To that end, we will
gather the magic stones
that were once kept
within our village
but have since been
scattered far and wide.
And we'll use humans to do it.
Smart, don't you think?
Oh, yeah.
Agreed. Let's begin.
We'll get back at
those hateful scum.
I'll make sure they
suffer endless despair!
[PATRY]
Indeed. The great rebirth
will start with the humans.
[SECRÉ] Resurrecting the elves.
Getting revenge on humankind.
It was all a misunderstanding.
Sadly, they had no
way of knowing that.
[SECRÉ] Everything that
happened was orchestrated
by a deceitful devil.
Not only the capital,
but the entire kingdom,
was about to be
overrun by darkness.
However, at that same time,
I saw a glimmer of hope.
[ASTA]
Is that... a grimoire?
[SECRÉ]
My prince.
The time has come.
[SECRÉ] The leaves of the clover
represent three things.
One is integrity, one is hope,
and the third one
stands for love.
Within the fourth leaf
dwells good luck.
And in the fifth
lives the devil.
[SECRÉ] But, the devil inside
the grimoire happened
to be different from the one
who had attacked the elves.
This particular being would
later be of aid to Asta,
the boy with no magic.
As for Patry's group,
they named themselves
"The Eye of the Midnight Sun"
and searched for
the magic stones. By collecting
all of these stones,
they would be able to
resurrect the other elves.
Kill them.
[SECRÉ]
They ransacked a village.
[LEOPOLD]
No! Fuegoleon!
[SECRÉ]
Then the capital.
Then the Underwater Temple.
Until finally, every
magic stone was theirs.
[ALL gasp]
[CHILD 96A]
What is that, Marie?
It just never ends.
I'm so scared.
[YAMI]
Hm?
What the hell?
[RHYA]
Too bad.
What is?
Your worthless human
race is finished.
What's happening?
Why do you look...
Klaus, talk to me!
[MIMOSA gasps]
Don't use such a
familiar tone with us.
[gasps]
You should know.
We aren't teammates or friends.
[SECRÉ]
The resurrection was complete.
All the elves had returned.
[PATRY laughs]
[PATRY]
Begone, humans!
At last, the time
has come for revenge!
[ELVES]
Those who guide the elves.
The Apostles of Sephira!
[RHYA] By infusing
Gravito Stones with magic,
we'll open the door
below Clover Castle
and release the seal
on the underworld!
[gasps] What the hell is that?
[MIMOSA]
I don't understand this at all!
[BAVAL] This is a magic space
that serves as a border
between this world and the next,
which the elves
entrusted to the humans
through an ancient pact.
It's called the Shadow Palace.
[SECRÉ] Should they have
succeeded in placing the final
magic stone into the monument,
the reincarnation spell
would've become permanent,
and the souls
of the human hosts
would be lost forever.
So, Asta and the others
gathered at the Shadow Palace
for the final battle.
But something awaited them.
What is this?
A pitch-black magic?
And why is it so cold?!
[heartbeats]
[PATRY]
Don't tell me. Is he...?
[KOTODAMA DEVIL cackles]
[PATRY]
A devil?
This creature. What is he?
[KOTODAMA DEVIL laughs]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Though it's still incomplete,
it's been centuries since
I've been in my own body!
And it's such
a wonderful feeling.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
You've used your
four-leaf grimoire well,
elf. I commend you.
I praise you from the
bottom of my black heart,
for all that you've
done up to this moment,
and the results you've shown me.
And now...
You shall taste the
depths of despair,
just as another did
all those centuries ago!
[PATRY] Another? But, who?
What is going on here?
That day, the one
who tricked the humans
into betraying the elves
was none other than...
Why, me, of course!
And, then you lot
made it even easier,
letting me trick you
in the most amusing way!
The revenge went
exactly as planned.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL laughs]
I might have known.
You're nothing but
a bunch of fools!
Five centuries ago,
they got in my way.
And, though I came close,
my incarnation failed.
Rather than admit defeat,
I selected you to be
my next unwitting pawn.
A new sacrifice,
loved by mana, still young,
and oh-so-easily swayed.
Tragedy, a sense of purpose,
a mission to fulfill.
That's all it took to turn
you to forbidden magic
that would reincarnate the
elves' souls in human form.
No, you have it wrong. Not me.
Licht was the one who
reincarnated us in human bodies.
It's true, he delved
into forbidden magic,
but he did it for us.
He gave us a chance!
You're incorrect. Truth is,
he had nothing to do
with your reincarnation.
All me, I'm afraid.
[PATRY gasps]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] You don't
understand your leader's wishes.
He doesn't want to
exterminate humanity.
The restoration of the elves,
the revenge you so longed for:
false goals, all of them.
You merely followed the path
that I laid for you, and led
the other fools along the way.
You did a truly splendid job.
I couldn't have asked
for a more useful tool.
And, in the end,
it brought about a future
Licht would never want,
and my incarnation,
allowing my soul to return
to my body, at last.
It's not true. He's lying.
Well, you were chosen,
that's true.
But not by the four-leaf clover.
By me, my little puppet!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL cackles]
Excellent work.
[PATRY screams]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL chuckles]
Ah! It's so amusing!
Elves and humans, so alike.
Your dreams and ambitions
make the most excellent
playthings for
creatures like me!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] When the owner
of a four-leaf grimoire
is engulfed in deep despair,
a miracle happens:
a five-leaf grimoire is born
out of the darkness within!
At last.
I enjoy both my precious body
and my pitch-black grimoire.
Now I can rule this world,
a devil in possession
of my true form and full power!
[SECRÉ] However, we refused
to let that devil win.
I spent all this
time in solitude
to prevent that from happening.
Now that your seal
has finally been broken,
I'm assuming my own seal
will be released, as well.
[FINRAL]
Huh? Nero...
What a pathetic state you're in.
If only my spell had
worked more completely.
No. Without your help,
I couldn't return at all.
[FINRAL]
Huh?
It's good to see
you again, my prince.
At long last.
You're the First Wizard King.
That statue... It was
you the whole time?
And how did Nero--
[yelps] No way!
Nero, is that really you?
You look, um, kinda different.
[SECRÉ] Today, we will finally
put this conflict to rest!
And it's not just
us two anymore.
We have friends now
who feel the way we do!
[SECRÉ]
So please...
Win this, Asta.
[YUNO] I can feel this light
making me even stronger!
Looks like he's
maxed out, though.
Sorry, Asta, but if you can't
keep up, I'm ditching you.
[ASTA] You should know
that's never gonna happen!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
...that obnoxious fool is merely
letting himself be pulled
along by his partner's spell.
They're no danger to me.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Where's the Anti-magic boy?
Hiding in the severed magic?
[BOTH yelling]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
They're pulling each other in
with increasing speed!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
"Sto--"
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] "Weaken!"
"Go back!" "Hold back!"
[BOTH yelling]
[ASTA]
That's all I've got.
No, Asta!
Nice try!
[YAMI]
Mana Zone.
Dark Cloaked...
Dimension Slash, Equinox!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL groans]
[ALL gasp]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] Dark Magic can
interfere with the other world!
Curse that human!
[ASTA]
I know that ki!
Captain Yami.
[cackling]
I'll end you!
[SECRÉ]
Sealing Recovery Magic:
Heavenly Prison, Faint Omen.
I've sealed his physical damage.
Now he just needs to draw
out his Anti-magic power!
Asta!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Die! Perish! Disappear!
[yells]
You first!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL screams]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
You're nothing but trash!
[SECRÉ]
Asta.
Remember.
[ASTA gasps]
You're going to be
the Wizard King!
Yeah!
[ASTA]
Right here, right now.
I'm going to push
past my limits!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL screams]
[ASTA yells]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL screaming]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL groans]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Impossible! It can't be.
I won't have it!
[ANTI-MAGIC DEVIL chuckles]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL gasps]
You got a problem
there, comrade?
Don't give me that!
Who are you? Tell me!
[cackles] You don't
need to know that.
It doesn't matter
how powerful you are.
you've lost this fight,
and you're about
to disappear for good!
Farewell, you disgrace.
We... won.
I'm grateful.
[panting]
[SECRÉ]
We prevailed.
[LUMIERE gasps]
[gasps]
The time has come.
I don't have enough magic
to hold this body
together anymore.
My prince.
[LUMIERE]
Secré--or, Nero, I suppose--
will you watch their
futures play out,
watch them make the
world better, for my sake?
I've always been...
Well, um. I mean...
Anyway. Let me go
with you! Please, sir!
I gave everything 500 years ago.
I should have died that day.
But then, you helped
me protect the future.
Let me go.
Like I said, I can't let you
seal off your potential.
[LUMIERE] I think the path
ahead is a bright one.
Both for the Magic Knights
and for the kingdom
they'll fight to defend.
So do I, really!
Serving you for so long.
I-It was an honor!
I was honored to have you.
Secré. Thank you for everything.
You did well. Goodbye.
[SECRÉ]
My prince.
I'm sure there will be
many more challenges
for us to overcome.
But I know everything
will be all right.
Because, from now on,
I won't be alone.
[SECRÉ]
The Black Bulls return
to where their
hideout once stood.
As they attempt to rebuild it,
they all become
drained and collapse.
What's wrong with Asta
and his friends?
Black Clover ,
Page 125: "Return."