[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
The hero's name was
Lumiere Silvamillion Clover.
[NARRATOR] He was later hailed
as the First Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[GUELDRE] What was that
shaking sensation just now?
Did something happen up there?
[REVCHI] I'm more curious
about these dreadful
purple things crawling all over.
[REVCHI] If not for Gueldre's
Transparency Magic,
we'd be dead by now.
And worse than that,
this fortress
is practically infested
with strong mages.
I don't know what
I was thinking,
walking into a
situation like this.
Look at it this way.
There's always a little
bit of danger involved
in any decision a person makes.
[GUELDRE] That said,
we should probably escape
before I run out of mana.
Which way to the exit?
Licht's ultimate move
seems to be working.
They couldn't
withstand its power.
I still can't wrap
my head around
how killer that spell was.
It really saved
our asses, though.
Only problem is, we got sent
all the way down here.
And thanks for fixin' my arm;
you're kinda nice after all.
Huh. I just wanted
us to be even.
[YAMI] I might have one more
Dimension Slash in me.
[YAMI] But I can feel that
evil mana and ki from here.
Does that mean elf-boy's
best attack wasn't enough?
[YAMI]
I wanna jump back in there,
but until I have a plan,
I'd better wait.
For whatever reason,
my Darkness Magic
seemed to be a match
for that devil.
I guess all I need
to do now is land
one final hit on him.
[YAMI] The only other
contender we've got
is the one guy
with no magic at all.
The weapon he's using
belongs to Licht.
What happened?
After Licht's grimoire changed,
it became possible for
evil beings to use it.
And then, when it made
contact with a different devil,
it apparently gained
the power of Anti-magic.
[ASTA grunting]
[ASTA] Oh, crap.
I think I'm overdoin' it!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL cackles]
You clearly have no control
over that ability.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] He broke
a spear from the other world!
It's supposed to trap
Light Magic and warp space,
but none of that
worked against him!
[ASTA yelps]
Okay!
I don't know what devil
you got that
special talent from.
Regardless, I suggest
you learn your place!
[ASTA grunts]
Word Soul Magic:
"Voizuiinemidoren."
"Futogerueofu."
"Snoittnedeidoog."
[yelling]
[gasps]
[ASTA yelps]
Thanks for gettin'
me outta there--
[ASTA grunts]
Oh, crap! I didn't
mean to do that!
[PATRY] Light Magic:
Light Swords of Conviction!
Wind Magic: Tornado Fang!
Damn!
[PATRY]
Just as I thought:
our attacks are useless
against his abilities!
Even with the four-leaf
on our side, we can't win!
There's only one thing
left for me to do now.
Here I go.
And this time, it won't
be to hurt other people,
but to protect them!
[PATRY] Demon Light Magic:
Light Swords of Conviction!
It worked!
Ah, yes, the elf chosen
by the four-leaf!
You're on the
wrong side, though,
which means that your
efforts are utterly wasted.
[ASTA grunting]
[ASTA] Everyone else is pushing
their limits on their magic;
I need to be able
to do that, too!
Should I make it take shape
and try to hold it there?
Come on!
[SECRÉ] Are you all right,
Your Highness?
That really hurt.
Anti-magic is amazing!
I probably won't be able
to use my power for a while.
Sounds like you're
not all right, then.
It's not very likely to work,
but I can bind it using
my Sealing Magic, then maybe
I can get control of it--
[LUMIERE]
Secré. It'll be fine.
It takes you so long
to do everything, Asta.
Hurry up.
[gasps]
[YUNO] If you can't use your
power to its full potential,
then how can you ever be...
the Wizard King?
[LUMIERE] Our magic had
dispersed into the air,
but he used his wind
to condense it and made it
into a weapon that could
combat the devil's attacks.
He's grown
significantly stronger.
Over the course
of a single battle.
[YUNO] Wind Spirit Creation
Magic: Spirit of Zephyr!
[ASTA]
Yeah, yeah. I was gettin' there.
I just needed a sec!
See, you can do it if you try.
[ASTA]
Of course I can.
'Cause I'm the guy who's gonna
be the next Wizard King!
[ASTA] Anti-Magic Demon
Slayer Sword: Black Divider!
[PATRY]
That one, too?
They both evolved so quickly.
He's got a wind attribute
as well as sword magic.
[gasps]
Yes, that makes sense!
Amazing! But what about the boy
using the five-leaf grimoire?
Who is he?
[SECRÉ] He's a foolish boy
born with no magic.
And he's always barreling
into things head-on.
That said, he tries harder
than anyone in the kingdom.
And he will never give up!
Stubborn to a fault.
How do ya like me now,
ya big jerk?
I one-upped ya!
[ASTA] I finally gave it shape,
but I don't feel like
I can keep it goin'
for much longer!
Hang in there as
long as you can.
At least until we
cut this guy down!
[YUNO]
It'll only take a second!
[ASTA, YUNO grunt]
You're lively,
I'll give you that.
But at that speed, I'm not sure
you'll be able to reach me!
[gasps]
[ASTA growling]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL groans]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
That wretched Wind Magic:
it made him faster!
[LICHT]
The Anti-magic pursued the wind,
and the wind traveled
through the void.
That was a brilliant
combination!
They did it.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL gasping]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
You putrid trash.
How dare you?
--I'll kill you all!
--It's over!
Really, how dare you?
--How dare you?
--I'll kill you all!
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[cackling]
[ASTA] I pierced his heart
and then it just
popped up somewhere else?
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
"Voizuiinemidoren,"
"Futogerueofu,"
"Snoittnedeidoog."
I'm going to exterminate
every single one of you!
[gasps]
[CHARLOTTE] I think that
devil's getting serious now!
He's about to
swallow up everything!
So he's been holding
back this whole time?
[YAMI] But with all
this crap in the way,
we can't get close to him!
[PATRY] This is going poorly
even for the best of us!
I'm worried about our allies
on the lower floors.
[LICHT] Patry. Defend the
perimeter for now.
We'll handle this.
No matter what happens,
we can't let the people
of this era be killed.
We need the present-day
Magic Knights.
They're the future
of the Clover Kingdom!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] You're nothing
more than a lump of meat!
--I'll kill all of you.
--I'll slaughter you one by one!
--Humanity is finished.
--You're nothing more than...
Now, the finale.
Ha. You think it's over?
You don't get to
decide how this ends!
You ready, Yuno? Let's go!
Of course I'm ready, idiot.
[BOTH] Time to shut
this guy up for good!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
You're no better than vomit.
A mere insect that had
the nerve to bite me.
Die. The only atonement
is your deaths!
You're just maggots
hiding under a rock.
I'll twist off
your arms and legs.
--Die!
--I'll rot your mana
and life away, bit by bit!
Die!
[YUNO] The Anti-magic
is really affecting him!
That's why he avoided
that blow to his heart,
and why he's so furious
about getting hit!
So that means, if we
can get Asta's sword
to actually pierce his heart...!
[ASTA]
These things go on forever!
[ASTA] This sucks, my body's
starting to reach its limit!
[LUMIERE]
That Anti-magic boy.
He's fighting side-by-side
with the Wind Magic user
and trusting him completely.
They can do this.
[LUMIERE, LICHT] We'll leave it
to them and help their friends!
[JACK]
Severing Magic: Death Scythe!
[cackles] Almost time!
Soon I'll be able
to slice this girl's
healing magic into tiny pieces!
Wait a second!
[FANA] We really
shouldn't be fighting!
[rumbling]
[BOTH gasp]
[FANA yelps]
I thought you guys went
to a different floor!
No time to explain,
this place is about to
flood with inhuman magic!
Everyone evacuate, quickly!
[MEREOLEONA] Mana Zone:
Calidos Brachium, Barrage!
Captain Mereoleona's here, too?
[laughs] I've never seen
a spell like that!
This world is amazing!
Ew, gross! Where
the heck did this
nasty-looking purple
stuff come from?
[FUEGOLEON] Things are
getting dire! Oh, no!
[FUEGOLEON]
It's catching up!
[LICHT]
The Demon-Dweller Sword connects
those who have strong bonds,
allowing them to
share their power.
[LUMIERE] Since my magic has
a chance against the devil,
we'll use the sword
to send it to everyone!
[LUMIERE, LICHT] Combo Spell:
Demon-Dweller Sword,
Protecting Light!
[CHARMY gasps]
This power... What is it?
Looks like Licht and
that prince of yours
combined their abilities
into one big spell.
How do you know that?
[RHYA] My connection
with Licht shows me
what's going on above our heads.
Isn't that nice?
He got to have a little reunion
with his long-lost friend.
Heh. Aw. I gotta say,
it makes me feel kinda jealous.
[LUMIERE]
As long as this spell holds,
I won't let a single one die!
[gasps]
[PATRY]
Demon Light Creation Magic:
Light Whip of Judgment!
The bond they have...
This time, I'll trust it!
[ASTA gasps]
[YUNO] With this spell
acting as a shield,
we can focus on our attacks.
Hey! Where'dja get
that light from?
No fair, come on, I want one!
I know you get angry anytime
something proves
I'm better than you,
but we're in the
middle of something!
Heh! Fine, pretty boy.
Careful though, you might
mess up your hair!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL] It'll be so
much fun to watch you die.
Your sword still
hasn't reached me.
It's utterly useless.
Already.
Right here. Just like this.
Finally.
Keep your distance, human--
you're too close to me again.
Hey! If you didn't have me here,
you'd be eyeballs deep
in that purple crap.
Anyway, didn't you
say you could see
what's happening
on the upper floor?
I'm thinking going
by mana and ki alone
probably isn't the
safest strategy for us.
Keep me updated on what that
freak's doing, would ya?
And stop complaining so much.
You're kidding.
You think that'll
work from here?
Well, I'd prefer to be
asked more politely,
but I'll add momentum
to your strike.
You'd better not miss!
I won't.
[YUNO, ASTA, YAMI]
We'll finish off this battle
with an all-out attack!
[SECRÉ] At first,
I only got close to you
so that I could use you.
You had no magic,
but you happened to obtain
the five-leaf grimoire
that repelled magic.
And then, the more time
I spent around you,
the more times I saw you fight,
the more I wanted
to believe in you.
I wanted to cheer you on!
So please,
win this, Asta.
[ASTA growls]
[YUNO yells]
[YUNO] I can feel this light
making me even stronger!
Looks like he's
maxed out, though.
Sorry, Asta, but if you can't
keep up, I'm ditching you.
[ASTA] You should know that's
never gonna happen!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
You're just a human,
yet you're using elven and
spirit power to fight me.
They'll never pierce
through my heart
with a silly gust of wind!
Meanwhile, that
obnoxious fool is merely
letting himself be pulled
along by his partner's spell.
And poorly, I might add!
They're no danger to me.
Where's the Anti-magic boy?
Hiding in the severed magic?
He's approaching
from my blind spot!
[BOTH yelling]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
They're pulling each other in
with increasing speed!
--"Sto--"
--[ASTA, YUNO yell]
--[KOTODAMA DEVIL] "Stop!"
--"Weaken!" "Go back!"
[BOTH yelling]
[ASTA]
That's all I've got.
No, Asta!
Nice try!
[CHARLOTTE] His level of
concentration is astounding!
But there's no way he'll
succeed from this distance!
[YAMI]
You sure about this?
Putting a foreigner like me
in charge of a
Magic Knights squad?
[JULIUS] Don't worry.
I'm sure you'll do fine.
I mean, I'm sure I'll
do things my own way,
and I know some
of the higher-ups
won't be thrilled about it.
Yeah, my magic's kinda
rare and all, but still--
[JULIUS]
I know that.
Yami. I've watched
you for a while.
Trust me. You can
handle the job.
[YAMI]
Mana Zone!
Dark Cloaked:
Dimension Slash, Equinox!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL sputters]
[ALL gasp]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Dark Magic can interfere
with the other world!
Curse that human!
[ASTA]
I know that ki!
Captain Yami.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL cackles]
I'll end you!
[SECRÉ]
Sealing Recovery Magic:
Heavenly Prison, Faint Omen.
[SECRÉ]
I've sealed his physical damage.
Now he just needs to draw out
his Anti-magic power!
Asta!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Die! Perish!
Disappear!
[yells]
You first!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL screams]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL yells]
You're nothing but trash!
[SECRÉ]
Asta.
Remember.
[gasps]
You're going to be
the Wizard King!
Yeah!
[ASTA]
Right here, right now.
I'm going to push
past my limits!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL screams]
[ASTA yells]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL screaming]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL screams]
[YUNO]
Asta. We did it!
This is exactly why you're
the perfect rival for me!
Wait, is the Shadow Palace
starting to crumble?
Black Clover , Page 120: "Dawn."
The battle ends and
a new morning comes!