[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR]
Fanzell Kruger:
the former head of
Mage Knight education
for the Diamond Kingdom,
and, by an odd coincidence,
the man who taught
Asta the sword.
[FANZELL, ASTA grunting]
No! You're too slow.
Don't pause between hits.
What we're after is
rapid-fire attack.
Right! [yells]
[NARRATOR]
Some time after the two met,
the Black Bulls were sent out
on a dungeon-clearing mission.
They battled a Diamond
Kingdom mage named Mars,
and Asta was gravely injured.
Noelle had gone out to
gather restorative herbs
for her wounded squadmate.
[NOELLE]
Come on, where is it?
That's the one!
[FANZELL]
Excuse me.
You there, with the silver hair.
Yes, hello! Do you
have a second?
I'm sorry to bother you,
but it won't take long.
[yelps]
[FANZELL] I just wanted a closer
look at something of yours.
Like I said, it'll
only take a second.
Why, you...
--What?
--[NOELLE] You pervert!
[yelps]
[FANZELL]
Wait! No. It's not like that!
Please, I swear!
[NOELLE] Oh, yeah?
Then what is it like, huh?
How's a man supposed
to get a decent nap
with all this
screamin' goin' on?
Is that Noelle?
[growls]
[screams]
[NOELLE]
Don't let him touch me!
[YAMI]
Hm?
[FANZELL panting]
You've got it all wrong.
I'm not some kinda creep.
I just want a real quick look.
Please, I'm even
willing to pay you.
Just a peek, that's all.
Ah--
Oh...
Feel my wrath!
"Pan" is only one letter
away from "pain"!
Poor thing. It must have
been so frightening,
being set upon by
a vile man like that.
What were you tryin'
to do to her?
She came running in,
scared outta her mind.
You're lucky we busted you up
instead of killing you.
Please. It's not how it looks.
I was robbed, that's why--
Nobody wants to hear it, freak.
We should let him loose.
Then we can capture him again!
You don't deserve to live
in the same world as Marie.
Now die.
Yes, Knights Headquarters,
this is Finral,
reporting for the Black Bulls.
We have a pervert
in custody here
and will be bringing
him in at once.
No, please don't.
I can explain. This is
a misunderstanding!
Miss Understanding works
at the tavern I think.
I think we're having some
communication issues.
[ASTA]
Zell?
Hold on. Asta?
[ASTA] Whoa, you're not lookin'
so good. Are you okay?
Sort of.
But enough about me,
it seems you made it
into a Magic Knight
squad. Congratulations.
[YAMI]
Hm?
[GAUCHE] So it was all
a misunderstanding?
[VANESSA] You were robbed
and they took your clothes?
[MAGNA]
You coulda told us that earlier!
I tried, but you weren't
exactly in a listening mood.
Yeah, details,
details. Who cares?
Here you go.
It's like I always say,
"better bread than dead!"
Oh, sure, thanks.
[mumbling] We don't get
new friends very often.
I hope you'll tell me
more about yourself.
What's wrong?
Zell. I gotta say,
you look pretty familiar.
Have we met somewhere before?
Uh, no.
I think I would
remember meeting you.
How'd you end up at our
hideout anyway, old man?
[FANZELL]
Oh! I forgot!
Excuse me, but you're
Noelle, aren't you?
I'm really sorry for
frightening you like that.
I wanted to ask you about
your wand, that's all.
That's what you wanted to see?
Yes. I think I know its maker.
A woman named Domina I've
been seeking for a while now.
Domina?
I remember that name.
She's your fiancée, isn't she?
All right. But I don't
think she made this.
The person who gave it
to me was named Code.
Doesn't sound like this
"Domina" you're looking for.
It is, though. It's her!
You see, her full name
is actually Dominante Code.
Where did you get it?
From a stall in the castle
town's black market.
The castle town. Thank you.
[ASTA] Domina's alive!
That's awesome news, Zell.
Well, go get her!
What are you waiting for?
You're right. I should go.
Right now. Thank you.
I can take you there.
Noelle. Listen.
Because of you,
I'm going to be reunited
with the woman I love,
finally. Thank you.
I didn't do anything, though.
Captain, sir, am I
free to leave now?
Yeah. Sure, why not.
But don't go blabbin' about
how we falsely imprisoned you.
You're the one talking
about false imprisonment.
[YAMI] Shut it, Portal Boy.
Speakin' of which.
Use your Spatial Magic
to send 'em on their way.
Then we'll be square.
I need a dump and a nap.
[sighs]
[FANZELL]
I appreciate it.
I should get going,
or it's gonna be
too hard to say goodbye.
See ya, Asta.
I'm glad our paths
crossed again,
even if it wasn't for long.
Now, go out and
become the Wizard King.
Sure thing!
And you go and live
happily ever after!
Everyone, get down!
[CHARMY]
Ha!
Ooh, cool! Someone's
attacking us!
It's probably the people
who are after me.
So, sounds like it's
time to get outta here.
The hell is this?
Whoever woke me up just
earned themselves a killin'.
There's been no movement so far.
Strange Master Fanzell
didn't leave at once.
That's what I would've
expected him to do.
[GALLEO]
For now, let's watch and wait.
Squads one through four,
maintain your formation
and begin a steady advance.
Squads five and six, continue
to stand ready at the rear.
That building--it looks like
some sort of dormitory.
Yes. I ought to be
on my way now.
Commander Galleo, a portal,
if you wouldn't mind.
You want a little
insurance in case
our sneak attack fails?
I honestly don't know what
you're so worried about.
We'd be a real laughingstock
if we couldn't pull off
an operation like this.
I'm not sure I like
your attitude.
You remember who allowed
you to live, right?
I'm aware that I owe you
my life, Commander.
And don't forget it.
Since I'm in your debt,
I'll offer you a little advice.
Defeating my old
teacher won't be easy.
[DIAMOND KNIGHT SCOUT 56A]
Squad one scout reporting.
We are within 65 feet
of the building.
[GALLEO]
Good. Prepare to charge.
[GALLEO] The target's
on the move. After him!
Lightning Creation Magic:
Thunderbolt Destruction!
[DIAMOND MAGIC KNIGHTS groan]
Go Flame Magic:
Prison Death Scattershot!
[DIAMOND MAGIC KNIGHTS groan]
Well, all right, I didn't
see that comin'.
Our surprise attack worked!
Guess these guys aren't
so tough after all, huh?
[laughs] Yeah. Too bad.
But at least there
are lots of 'em,
so smashing their kneecaps
ought to keep us
entertained for a while.
[GALLEO] I want squads one
and two to stay on the target!
[GAUCHE]
So, you're in charge here?
[gasps]
The sooner this is over with,
the sooner I can visit Marie.
See how you like my Mirror
Magic. Reflect Refrain!
Wha... What's going on here?
I've got a nap to finish,
so let's make this quick.
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked.
Lightless Slash!
[DIAMOND KNIGHTS scream]
I don't care who you are.
Nobody ever lays
a hand on my food!
[DIAMOND MAGIC KNIGHTS groan]
[YAMI] Hey, numbskulls.
Save some of the fun for me.
[GALLEO]
That Water barrier.
It's not meant to block
attacks from out here,
but to keep their own spells
from destroying the place?
[grunts]
[GREY]
You're the C.O.?
Fanzell. That you?
If you care about
our hostage at all,
you better get your
traitor's hands off me.
[GREY]
A hostage? Who?
Dominante Code.
Mariella's on her way now.
Hah. You may not have
known where she had gone
into hiding, but we did.
Now, let me go or we'll--
Wow-ie! Captain Yami
is so amazing!
Everything's playing out
exactly like he said it would.
[GALLEO]
Uh, what?
My squadmates are going
via portal to visit
a lady by the name of Domina.
I don't think your hostage
will be a hostage
for much longer.
[GALLEO]
Who are you?
[GREY growls]
[DOMINANTE]
How long were you going to wait
to come and get me?
A poor, helpless woman hiding
from a bunch of killers,
and you just leave me here?
You're lucky I'm still
alive, you useless jerk!
I was so worried!
When you didn't come
looking for me,
I thought you might
have gotten hurt.
I'm a little more hurt now.
Thank you for bringing him!
I know I threw in
a little extra,
but I never thought
you'd do this!
I guess that means
Bruce was right
about you all along.
I should've known.
I'm not so sure.
[DOMINANTE]
And this young man must be Asta!
[ASTA]
You know about me?
I heard you were
a tough-looking kid,
and it seems like it's true.
From who?
Well...
[ASTA]
Ah--
What are you doing here?!
[NOELLE, FINRAL]
Hm?
I don't plan to hurt anyone.
Besides, how much
damage can one girl
possibly do on her own?
You beat up your teacher
and tried to kidnap him.
Why should we trust you?
My intentions are in
no way malicious.
I am simply using you.
[gasps]
What do you mean?
I recognize those robes.
You're the Black Bulls
squad, aren't you?
[GALLEO] Did Mariella know that
when she ordered us to attack?
Hold on, you're telling us
you sent your own men
to storm the
Black Bulls' hideout
hoping they'd get crushed?
Meanwhile, I came here
to the black market
and informed Domina
that Master Fanzell
would be arriving soon.
I wanted to ensure
she was prepared.
However, I didn't expect you
to get here so quickly.
This is a map.
I've researched escape routes
and plotted them on it.
I don't understand why you
would do this, though.
Nor I.
[MARIELLA] To strike a blow
against the Diamond Kingdom.
A number of their assassins
are now out of commission.
Master Fanzell and Domina
will be able to escape.
So, in other words,
I set a plan in motion
that would badly
damage the organization.
This is revenge.
Mine, against those
who have controlled me.
[ASTA]
Why now?
Much like my teacher, I'm tired.
I can't do what they
ask of me anymore.
That said,
I don't believe
I have the strength
to stay on the run
for my whole life.
It wasn't easy,
but I made a decision.
Exact my revenge and
then turn myself in
to the Clover Kingdom's
Magic Knights.
You were gonna turn yourself in?
[MARIELLA] I was nearby,
waiting for the circumstances
to properly align.
I watched as Master
Fanzell approached
the Black Bulls' hideout
and saw him dragged inside.
I thought, if I sent
those troops against you,
you would annihilate
them for me.
Thank you for consulting us.
She makes it sound so easy.
And now, will you please
take me into custody?
Then we all get what we want.
[FANZELL]
Think about this, Mariella.
Do you know what you're asking?
You could be subjected
to extreme punishment.
The Clover Kingdom won't
forget your past crimes.
And the organization
can still reach you
even if you're in
somebody else's custody.
I'm willing to accept that.
Yes. As long as
my life is spared.
[gasps]
I've been thinking
about what you said.
We have to find our own hope,
our own reason for living.
Right?
Yeah, what about it?
[MARIELLA] It was
obnoxious and overbearing.
Ah--
That said, it was also moving,
and sort of dashing.
Oh, you think so?
Whatever punishment
I might receive
is the price I have to pay
to atone for my crimes
and begin a new life.
So, no matter how severe it is,
I'll bear it without complaint.
I see.
[GALLEO]
I've had enough of this!
[gasps] Galleo, sir!
You're the assassin
corps commander,
and you've abandoned your
troops? That's horrible!
And what do you
call what you did?
If you want so desperately to
be executed, I can oblige you.
Everybody, run.
He may sound like a petty fool
who's just full of hot air,
but his magic's quite tricky.
That's right!
Spatial Creation Magic:
Unopening Red Room!
Asta!
Now, Spatial Creation
Magic: Go, Riftmen.
[ASTA]
What are these creepy red guys?
And why's the room all red?
[MARIELLA] Galleo's initial
spell created this place,
and those figures
are magic soldiers
that can only exist here.
They're not going
to be easy to beat.
But wait. Hold on.
You jumped in front of the spell
without knowing what it did?
If that had been offensive
magic he was using,
you could have died!
Are you stupid?
Well, maybe.
So what if I am?
I'd rather be stupid
than just stand back
and watch somebody die!
[gasps]
And besides.
Something's changed since the
last time we saw each other:
I'm Asta of the Black Bulls now!
But, I'm still your enemy?
I don't care. This is who I am.
If someone needs help, I'll
help 'em as much as I want!
You got it?
But, hey, if you wanna
give me some backup
while I'm at it, I won't mind.
[ASTA yells]
I may not be as
altruistic as he is,
but I can't stand by and
watch a student suffer.
So come on, let's work together
and get through this!
Get through this? How can we?
Easy! This is nothing!
[ASTA, FANZELL yell]
No! Impossible!
[YAMI]
Yeah, Knights Headquarters?
This is Yami of the Black Bulls.
We've got a bunch
of troublemakers
rounded up out here.
Come and get 'em, wouldja?
[GAUCHE] That's a lot of
mages to have hunting you.
Who is this Fanzell person
and what did he do
to get so many people
sicced on him?
Wait, hold on.
Don't you mean Zell?
Uh-- No, according to
Grey his full name
is actually Fanzell.
[GREY growls]
Ah! That's right.
He's Fanzell Kruger.
He was the commander
of the Diamond Kingdom's
invading army.
I met the guy on the battlefield
a really long time ago.
Seriously?
I heard he moved from
commanding the army
to training their soldiers,
but I guess he musta deserted,
which would explain
why everybody
and their mom was
tryin' to get to him.
I realize it isn't my
place to ask this, sir.
And, correct me if I'm wrong,
but did we just help
a high-ranking member of our
greatest enemy's
military escape?
[YAMI]
Sounds about right.
Hey, Gauche.
Yes, Captain?
Never speak of this again.
My lips are sealed.
Please give me a
week of Marie-leave.
You're only supposed to see
her once a month, aren't you?
I'll watch her
so surreptitiously
for all 168 hours
that nobody will know.
Man, you've got
some serious issues.
[NARRATOR] And so, the case
of the creepy naked man
and the mysterious attack
on the Black Bulls' hideout
was put to rest at last.
Are you sure it's okay
for us to leave like this?
I'm worried that it'll
only cause all of you
more trouble in the long run
if we just up and vanish.
Captain Yami didn't
have any problems
with you guys going,
so I'm sure it's fine.
Don't you think so?
Yes. Sure.
[FINRAL]
Not fine.
And it'll probably turn into
something extremely not fine.
Are you sure you're
okay with this, though?
Mariella isn't exactly
the nicest person.
All the terrible things
I did were under duress.
Galleo and his assassin
corps were going
to kidnap me and
hold me hostage.
She's the one who put
a stop to that, remember?
Besides, if you think
about it, Mariella here
is the reason my Zell
and I were reunited.
Honestly, there's such a thing
as being too nice, ya know?
You're one to talk--
you and your pushover squad.
Honestly, I manipulated
all of you so easily,
it was ridiculous.
I never asked for your help,
and I don't need it.
I can get by just fine
without anybody else.
The only person you need
in your life is you.
You've been telling yourself
that for a while, huh?
Taking on the burden
alone is actually
surprisingly easy, isn't it?
You just keep
saying to yourself,
as long as you can get
through it, you'll be fine.
There's no need to consider
the people around you,
so there's not really much
thinking involved at all.
I hate to tell you, but
that's off the table now.
Because once you have
people in your life
who care about you, your
problems and your decisions
aren't only your own anymore.
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
That's right.
Now you've gotta
think about them, too.
So you'd better get used to it.
I guess I'm not
the only one here
with personality issues.
Well, it's not like I care
what you think, anyway.
All right, we should get going,
or it's gonna be too hard--
Hey, there's nothin'
to cry about.
Remember, you and me are guys
who like to get things done.
And like you said, there's
no time for sittin' around.
So get to work, old man!
Go out there and make
Domina as happy as you can!
You're right.
I was given more time when
I thought I had none left,
and I won't waste it.
Together, Mariella, Domina and I
are going to live life
to the fullest.
That's the spirit!
I'll write once things
settle down a bit.
Great! Take care of yourself.
Uh, and, well, I hate
to ask this but, uh...
Remember how you all
thought I was a creep,
but then I told you
I was actually robbed
and my clothes were taken?
[chuckles]
You're kidding, right?
Do you think I could
borrow some money?
[meows]
We should've just let the
Diamond Kingdom have you!
[NARRATOR] And that's the
story of how Fanzell, Domina,
and Mariella met
the Black Bulls.
[NARRATOR] Back in the
present, Noelle and Finral
have called on Fanzell
hoping he might be able
to help them find a way
to heal Asta's arms.
[NOELLE]
Domina, Mariella! How have you--
Enough with the naked thing!
You're a grown man,
keep your clothes on!
[FANZELL]
Ow! Hey! Stop!
It's not my fault!
[MARIELLA] This house is
already run-down enough.
Don't contribute
to its sorry state.
Oh, wow. Poor Asta,
that's terrible.
He's had quite an eventful life
for someone who's
still so young.
His bad luck is inversely
proportional to his height.
Do you have any ideas?
We have to find
a way to heal him.
Anything will be helpful.
So, Ancient Hex Magic, huh?
Well, there is one place.
[NOELLE, FINRAL gasp]
My homeland, the
Forest of Witches.
You think they'd help?
[DOMINANTE] The Queen of
the Witches' magic would.
[inhales]
Hey!
The smartest witch ever
to grace the Land of Witches
has come back to say hello.
I have business here,
so open up!
[FINRAL] We might have found
a way to heal Asta's arms!
All right, time to infiltrate
the Forest of Witches.
Ooh! Look at all these
beautiful witch-girls!
Hello, ladies!
Black Clover ,
Page 57: "Infiltration."
Maybe I can infiltrate
a heart or two!