[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed
lost until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] Both Black Bulls
and Temple mages
battled against Vetto of
the Third Eye to prevent him
from staging a massacre and
obtaining the magic stone.
Ready, Kiato?!
Yeah!
[grunts]
[ASTA yells]
[yells]
How tedious.
Sluggish moves, glancing blows.
But what should I expect
from magicless trash
and underwater scum?
You're pathetic.
Now you're askin' for it,
you overgrown furball.
[ASTA, KIATO] We'll do whatever
we have to, to bring you down!
[BOTH yelling]
[NARRATOR] Though Asta and
Kiato put up a fierce fight,
Vetto's strength was
simply too great.
You had some hope left?
An attack like that
is child's play to me.
You'll have to do a lot better.
[ASTA]
Not yet.
[VETTO cackles]
Looking at you disgusts me.
Fighting with objects you
aren't even worthy to touch.
[ASTA]
Get to the point already!
[ASTA grunts]
[VETTO] You and your
worthless friends never
had a chance of defeating me.
[ASTA grunts]
[VETTO]
Go on. Howl!
--Embrace your despair!
--[yells]
[ASTA muffled] No one ever
protected anybody by giving up!
What?
[KAHONO singing]
[VETTO]
Hm?
[BOTH]
What he said was,
"No one ever protected
anybody by giving up!"
Noelle.
Kahono!
[VETTO]
So, you two are next.
At least try to entertain me.
No. Dad!
[NOELLE]
Magna and Luck are down, too.
Asta!
[NOELLE] All before we
could even get here.
What kind of monster
are we up against?
[laughs]
Not done!
Go away.
Insect!
[ASTA screams]
Asta!
Song Magic: Rhythm Cushion!
[NOELLE]
Thank you, Kahano!
A thousand yul should cover it.
Ha! I'll give you 100
times that if we survive.
[KAHONO giggles]
Now. We need to get the
others on their feet.
Can you use your Recovery Magic?
[KAHONO]
Well, I can.
But do you really
think he'll wait
until I'm done
singing to attack?
--[clattering]
--What's that?
[NOELLE]
Who's he?
[gasps]
Hey!
Big Brother! Why the
heck are you sleeping?!
We've got a promise
to keep, remember?!
We're never gonna get famous
if we let this
beast man kill us!
Did you forget about
our singing, dancing
brother-sister act?
No, of course I didn't!
Wait: "Big Brother"?
Yep, that good-for-nothin'
dum-dum over there
is my big brother Kiato.
Who are you calling
good-for-nothing?
[KIATO] If I hadn't deflected
the force of that punch
with my Dance Magic, I'd be
missing a head right now.
He'll be impossible
to beat. But...
My brother and I have a dream.
We're gonna go ashore someday!
Yeah, that's right!
We can't give up now.
We won't let our
dream die! Let's go!
Yeah!
[sings]
[gasps]
[NOELLE] I can feel it.
The mana's getting stronger!
[KIATO, KAHONO]
Combo Spell:
Now, Sea God Slash!
[KIATO] Compound Magic that
combines Song and Dance.
Kahano's singing enhances
my Dance Magic,
allowing me to release
enormous strikes
of magic power at the enemy.
[grunts]
Incredible!
[yells]
That's it! Come on!
You're doing well. You can
defeat him. I know you can!
Ever since you were little,
you've both worked
so hard to make your
dreams come true!
[KAHONO singing]
[KIATO]
Phew!
That oughta be enough
practicing for today,
don'tcha think?
Nuh-uh.
If you wanna be rich someday,
you gotta try harder than that.
I guess you're right.
Becoming a star dancer is tough.
[KAHONO]
Mm-hm. Yeah.
And besides, we don't
just wanna be famous.
We wanna please
the sea god, too.
[KIATO]
We've got a lot of work to do.
'Kay, you ready?
[KAHONO]
Mm-hm.
[KAHONO sings]
[GIFSO]
Hard work will never betray you!
[singing]
[grunts]
[singing continues]
[VETTO] A sparrow's song
and a waltzing mouse.
I wouldn't expect them
to be so powerful.
They have some unique
spells for living
in such a remote location.
[KIATO]
That's right!
This place is what
shaped our magic!
It's been woven into the
very fabric of our lives.
Generations of our people
have praised the sea god
with their singing and dancing.
[KAHONO] We've been practicing
all of our lives.
Each song and each dance is
an offering to the sea god.
To him, and to everyone we love!
This magic bonds the people
of the Underwater Temple.
[OCEAN DWELLERS cheering]
You've got him now, kids!
Take the beast down!
[KAHONO] We'll never let
that bond be broken!
[KIATO]
You won't defeat us!
[KIATO yelling]
[NOELLE]
Did it work?
[VETTO laughs] Done with
your little speech now?
[gasps]
[singing continues]
There's no way!
[OCEAN DWELLERS gasping]
Ha.
Keep trying!
[KIATO yells]
[yelps]
[laughs]
[screams]
Kiato!
[KIATO grunts]
Run, now! Kahono!
[VETTO]
Dreams? And bonds?
What do humans know of those?
[gasps]
[VETTO] Don't speak such
words to me, girl!
Kahono!
[GIFSO screams]
All right, you beast!
Now Game Magic: Monster Toy!
[MONSTER TOYS growl]
[VETTO]
Can't you muster anything
beyond a childish diversion?
[growling]
[groans]
How?!
We had those once, as well.
Our own dreams and bonds.
Until you humans destroyed them!
[VETTO]
We, the Eye of the Midnight Sun
had golden dreams
and bonds of blood!
I don't understand! What
is he babbling on about?
Damnable, rabid beast monster!
[VETTO] It looks like there
will be no more singing
and dancing for the two of you.
All it took was a couple
of well-timed strikes
to crush those silly
dreams of yours.
What good are you now?
You're a sparrow
without a voice.
The very essence of
despair. How delicious.
[KAHONO grunts]
So, there's still a scrap of
defiance left in you, is there?
Very well.
Let's see how you'll feel
after I tear your wings off.
Really. A sparrow
that can't sing
has no reason to live, anyway.
I think I'll just--
[NOELLE]
Don't touch her!
Put her down! Do it right now!
You truly think I'll stop
because you told me to?
[NOELLE]
If I miss, I might hit Kahono.
You and your worthless
friends never had a chance
of defeating me.
[VETTO]
Go on. Howl!
--Embrace your despair!
--[yells]
[NOELLE] I couldn't bring
myself to attack then, either.
Would my attacks
even do anything
against someone like that?
No one else's have.
[gasps]
[VETTO] If you're not
going to use that thing,
then just stand there
and watch. Watch her die.
[NOELLE gasps]
[laughs]
[NOELLE] Everyone else
has fought until they're
too exhausted or hurt to go on.
But I... I just can't.
[KAHONO]
It's all right.
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
Kahono?
[gasps]
[KAHONO] There's a great
power within you.
You're strong enough
to handle it now.
[KAHONO] Because you're
fighting to protect
what's precious to you.
You're fighting to win, Noelle!
[NOELLE]
What's precious to me...
[KAHONO] It will be
all right. Don't doubt it.
Because I say so,
and I'm your friend!
What's happening?
It's shaking!
What is this?
It's about time, Noelle.
Get 'im.
[NOELLE]
I won't tell you again.
[VETTO] Where did all
this power come from?
Release my friend at once.
Or you'll regret it!
Tell me, Black Bull girl.
You aren't hesitating because
of your siblings'
taunting, are you?
There's no time for
that on the battlefield!
[NOELLE gasps]
[FUEGOLEON] One bad decision
out here could mean lives lost!
Forget your insecurities.
You stand here today as a
member of the Magic Knights.
If you joined the order
of your own accord,
you must be determined
to grow stronger!
Stronger...
There isn't any shame
in being weak, girl.
[NOELLE]
Huh?
The shame is in staying weak.
[gasps]
Release my friend at once.
Or you'll regret it!
So strong.
Who is this girl?
Hold on. Are you royalty?
And what does it matter if I am?
That isn't what's important
to me right now!
I am Noelle Silva
of the Black Bulls.
And I'm done standing
by and watching while
you hurt my friends
and squadmates!
I see.
[VETTO]
So it's true.
A member of the humans'
most corrupt class.
Good!
I'll make an example of you.
Now, hit me with me
everything you've got,
you disgusting royal parasite.
Oh, I was planning on it!
I'll show you the power
of a "royal parasite"!
Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Roar!
[roars]
[yells]
Bear Claw!
--[VETTO yelling]
--[DRAGON roaring]
[yells]
[yelling]
[DRAGON growls, roars]
[OCEAN DWELLERS gasping]
Whoa!
Is... Is that the sea god?
[panting]
[VETTO panting]
My arm!
[panting]
How's that?
Some crazy power you've got.
You really did push
past those limits.
Maybe a little too far past 'em.
Who is that girl?
Is she the sea goddess?
[YAMI] I always figured
her latent abilities
were nothing to sneeze at.
But who knew she was an
attack mage all this time?
[VETTO grunting, groaning]
[screams]
[LICHT]
Let us live together.
It is not you who
should be despairing.
But the people of
the Clover Kingdom.
You must remember
your true self.
[ELVES chattering, laughing]
[ELF 46A] Congratulations
to the happy couple!
[ELVES screaming]
[ELVES scream]
[ELF 46CC]
Is this...?
[ELF 46C]
It can't be!
[ELF 46DD]
Humans?
[VETTO]
I'll kill you.
[yelling]
[VETTO pants]
[VETTO laughs]
[gasps]
You have my gratitude
for summoning me, human.
[NOELLE]
Where'd that eye come from?
I've never felt such sinister
magic power before!
Mythical Beast Magic:
Noita Nejair.
[VETTO yells]
His arm... grew back?
How is that possible?
It shouldn't be.
Not grown' back
a whole missin' arm.
There's no spell
that can do that.
Not even the strongest
Recovery Magic
can regenerate a limb.
At the very most, it could only
hope to close up the wound.
[YAMI] These people
aren't a terror group.
They're something much stranger
and much more horrifying.
Oh, my god. Get out
of there! Run, Noelle!
[panting]
[NOELLE]
Run away?
Leave them?
Not a chance!
You have a lot of
resolve, for a mouse.
And that's what will
kill you. Now, begone!
Mythical Beast Magic:
Epohlla Puevig!
Sea Dragon's--
[gasps]
[NOELLE] That last spell
drained all my power!
[OCEAN DWELLERS yelling]
[BOTH gasp]
[VETTO laughs]
[ASTA panting]
Asta! You saved me!
[laughs] That's our boy.
[ASTA]
Not yet. It's not...
It's not over.
You haven't won!
We haven't given up,
and we're not going to!
You're right. It isn't over yet.
The real despair starts now!
[VETTO laughs]
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[VETTO]
"Mythical Beast Magic!"
Mythical Beast Magic
spell was called?
Do you really wanna
know, bug? Fine then.
[NOELLE]
Who're you calling "bug"?!
I'm royalty, thank you!
[VETTO]
This is the spell.
Well, go ahead. Read it.
I can't.
--It's easy: Epohlla Puevig.
--Huh?
Come on! Epohlla Puevig.
Picky Peggy Piper picked a
peck of pickled persimmons?
Not even close.
Listen to me one more
time: Epohlla Puevig!
Whales and dolphins may
look like big fish,
but they're actually mammals.
Thickness is the only
difference between udon,
somen , and hiyamugi .
Hawks are smaller than eagles,
but they're also faster.
Really, I didn't know that!
Ha! Of course I knew
that sort of thing.
I am royalty, after all.
[VETTO] I have no idea
what just happened.
[VETTO] Insects, I have grown
tired of your incessant buzzing.
I shall crush each and every
one of you with my own hand!
Black Clover , Page 47:
"The Only Weapon."
My magic is devouring despair!