[NARRATOR] Within the clover's
fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
[NARRATOR] Asta, born
unable to harness mana,
was granted the power
of Anti-magic
from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability
to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members
of Spade Kingdom's
Dark Triad also possess
powers from the devils
of the underworld and
used them to launch
an invasion on the
neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from
his belief in himself
and from the support
of his friends,
Asta continues to fight for
the safety of this world.
[OWEN] While you were defending
your own headquarters,
the Golden Dawn's base
was attacked, as well.
They were almost wiped out.
I can't tell you
how relieved I am
to see you all survived.
That's because Asta
and Yami were around.
So, how bad is it?
He should pull
through, fortunately.
But... I'm not sure what we
can do for his right arm.
There's no telling
what'll come of it.
Excuse me!
But would you mind taking
a look at Gauche, too, please?
Was he injured as well?
The wound's all healed.
I feel fine now.
You should still let him
make sure, though!
Just in case!
[OWEN]
What do you mean?
Gauche was hit with
an enormous sword
that went right
through him, sir!
I used a spell to heal him
as fast as I could, but...
[OWEN]
I don't understand.
I thought you were a
Transformation Magic user.
Don't worry, Grey.
I'll take a look.
Wait. I'm sorry, did she say
the sword went all the way
through your body?
[GAUCHE]
Yeah.
[OWEN]
This goes beyond healing.
It looks as though the tissue's
been completely rebuilt!
[BOTH gasp]
Perhaps at the
core of your magic,
it's something much more
than Transformation.
Then what kind of magic is it?
I wish I could be of more help,
but I honestly have no idea.
I believe this is
something that Grey
needs to figure out for herself.
Yes, sir.
[OWEN] I'd like Asta
to stay here for a while
so that I can monitor him.
The rest of you can return
to the Black Bulls hideout.
The Squad Captains are holding
an emergency meeting
tomorrow morning.
The best thing you can do
is get some rest,
so you can be ready
for whatever comes next.
[ASTA gasps]
[pants]
[ASTA]
Huh? I can't move my body!
Are you going somewhere?
[ASTA]
Who is that?
Is he using magic
to hold me still?
You should go back inside now.
They took the captain.
I have to save him!
That won't work.
You'd be walking into
a fight against not only
the devil-possessed man
who defeated you before,
but two others who
are equally powerful.
Believe me, you don't
stand a chance.
[NACHT] On top of that,
your own devil's forsaken you
and you aren't sure what'll
happen to your right arm.
[ASTA]
How does he know that?
[NACHT] Challenging them in
your condition isn't brave.
In fact, it's foolish
and reckless.
I don't care.
I still have to go!
How could I just sit
around here and do nothing
when he's in trouble?
When he needs my help?
[NACHT] You might as well leave
that boorish brute to die.
Whoever you are,
shut your mouth,
because you don't know the first
thing about Captain Yami!
Oh, I know him quite well.
[NACHT]
He's a violent and vicious man,
not to mention he's
irresponsible and brash.
To tell the truth,
he's worthless.
I'm gonna need backup over here.
Asta!
You don't know him.
You've got no idea!
Captain Yami risked
his life to protect us!
And yet, he still
lost the battle,
which proves him to be a fool.
Destroyer!
[ASTA yells]
[ASTA]
Let me go, jerk!
If you can't even hold
your own against me,
there's no possibility
of you saving the captain.
[DEVIL] That's right.
Because you're weak.
This is all my fault.
I'm not strong enough.
You really are a fool.
But you do seem
like a good person.
Which is why I like you.
No need to worry.
Yami's still alive.
[ASTA]
Weg? Who are you?
Tell the truth!
I'm Vice Captain Nacht
of the Black Bulls.
A pleasure.
[NACHT] I can teach you
how to use your devil power.
If you would like
to learn, that is.
[ASTA] Did he just say he's the
vice captain of the Black Bulls?
[GIMODELO]
What'd I miss, Nacht?
And who's this puny guy
you're talking to?
[ASTA]
That ki. A devil!
I hate to tell you
this, Gimodelo,
but you're a whole lot
punier than he is.
[GIMODELO laughs]
Don't even start!
You're only saying that because
I'm not in my true form!
[ASTA] They're talking
like best buddies!
You're possessed
by a devil, too?
Precisely.
This little imp
right here is Gimodelo.
[GIMODELO laughs]
[ASTA gasps]
That's our crest. So it is true!
Are you really our vice captain?
Yes. Although, Yami basically
decided that himself.
[GIMODELO]
Aw, don't make me leave!
This whole thing is so crazy.
[NACHT] It's no surprise
you don't know about me.
After all, I've only
been to the hideout once.
And why is that?
It's because I despise Yami.
Huh?
I hate to admit it,
but stubborn people like him
tend to be very resilient.
He's still got some
time left to live.
But, how do you
know that for sure?
Well, I've been undercover
in the Spade Kingdom
for a long time now.
[ASTA gasps]
[ASTA]
I don't know much about you,
and I'm not even sure
if I can trust you.
But...
...you're the only person
who might know
how to get Captain Yami back!
So, please help me!
Teach me everything you can
about my devil power!
[NACHT]
Good.
I'm glad to see
you're straightforward.
I quite like that
trait in a person.
[ASTA]
Um, thank you!
But as of right now,
I can't say that I'm
sensing even a smidgeon
of talent within you.
Huh? Wow, tell me
how you really feel!
[NACHT] I'm sure it'll work out
if you learn to use your powers.
Yeah? Great, let's do it!
Oh, no, you need
to get some rest first.
[ASTA muffled]
Huh?
[NACHT] There's somewhere I'd
like to go with you tomorrow,
so take it easy tonight.
[ASTA muffled] You expect me to
be able to sleep right now?
[NACHT] Just do it.
I hate selfish people.
Excellent. It seems
you're all here.
[MARX] Now, then, let's begin
the emergency captains' meeting.
This concludes the report
from the Black Bulls
who witnessed the attack.
The Tree of Qliphoth.
It's supposed to connect
this world to the underworld.
And to create it,
they need the magic types
that William and Yami possess.
I see. I still can't believe
they kidnapped them!
I can.
Those two allowed themselves
to be caught off guard.
And they dare to call themselves
Magic Knight Squad Captains?
They're just a couple
of lousy men.
[CHARLOTTE] Oh, no!
My sweet Yami's been abducted!
Is he all right?
Ah! I hope they
haven't hurt him!
I haven't had a chance to
confess my love to him yet!
We did everything that we could.
And it still wasn't enough.
The enemy wasn't even
fighting us seriously.
Keh! Yeah, that's a real
likely story, kid.
It sounds to me like you
might've chickened
out on the guy.
Turns out the Golden Dawn's
got a sniveling coward
for a vice captain!
That's enough, Jack.
Those foul villains could
be linking this world
to the underworld
even as we speak.
Keh! Then it's all gonna be
fire and brimstone, I guess?
[FUEGOLEON] We must prevent
that outcome at all costs.
Sadly, we don't have
much information.
Great. So we're all gonna
sit around and talk about it?
Genius plan you've got there.
Forget it.
This stupid meeting obviously
isn't going anywhere.
I'm out!
Stop.
You'd better not
be thinking about
going to infiltrate
Spade on your own.
Yeah, right! Just to
rescue that idiot?
Besides, even if I did,
it's not like it would be
any of your business!
You're a fool!
It is our business!
I won't allow a fellow
captain to be so rash!
Because I wanna go
save Yami, too!
Kyeh! Well, it's better
than just sitting here
picking our noses all day.
Believe me, Jack, I want the
chance to kill that monster
just as badly as you do!
Everyone! Settle down right now!
Yeah or what?
Lord Julius.
[NACHT] Good to see you're
all motivated, at least.
Still, though.
I dislike those who can't
maintain proper civility.
Uh, hi, Captains!
I'd appreciate it if
you would quiet down.
Set a better example.
[YUNO]
Asta.
Who is this intruder?
Declare yourself!
Please.
I can assure you
that I have every right
to be included in this meeting.
[DEVIL 168A growls]
Whoa, you've got four devils?
I didn't expect that!
[FUEGOLEON] Devils?
So, he's possessed, as well.
Tell us. Who are you?
This man is with
the Black Bulls.
He's their vice captain.
Wait, seriously?
He'd been operating in
the Spade Kingdom as a spy.
However, I was unaware
that he was possessed.
So that's the vice captain
of the Black Bulls?
I didn't realize
we had sent a spy.
[FUEGOLEON] I suppose the
vice captain of Yami's squad
could be practically anyone.
[JACK]
Where've I seen this jerk?
Wait, I remember you!
Your magic is
different now, though.
That man is no more.
[NACHT]
Anyway, we're wasting time.
I suggest we get
straight to the point.
I'd like you all to have a seat.
As you know, the gate
to the underworld
is about to be opened
in the Spade Kingdom.
So, we can assume
they're already making
preparations for the ritual
of the advent of Qliphoth.
To do so, they'll
undoubtedly offer Yami
and Vangeance as sacrifices.
[ASTA]
Captain Yami.
[NACHT] When that's done, the
advent of Qliphoth will begin,
lasting for seven days.
Seven levels, with seven gates,
will open one by one.
Scattered throughout
these gates are ten devils,
each compatible
with the Qliphoth.
The deeper the level, the
stronger the enemies will be.
The upper ones are
about as powerful
as the Dark Triad members,
but as you descend,
they become much fiercer.
What's worse,
if the final devil, Lucifero,
emerges, this world is done for.
Yami and Vangeance will
be killed by this process.
But, as the catalysts,
they'll be kept alive
until the last gate opens.
[gasps]
[NOZEL]
Impressive.
He managed to gain this much
information on his own?
And from the very heart of
the enemy's country, no less.
But why would the
Dark Triad want to attempt
something that's so dangerous?
It isn't the kind of thing
we could ever understand.
As Magic Knights,
I'm sure you've met
more than your share
of people like them.
Those who care only
about themselves and hurt
without hesitation to
satisfy their own desire,
who feel no guilt or shame,
no matter how low they sink.
Personally, I would
never even want
to understand
what motivates them.
They are the worst
sort of trash imaginable.
Irrational evil. There's
nothing I hate more.
Perhaps God and the
devils will forgive them
for what they've done,
but I never will.
That being said, I can't defeat
the Dark Triad without help.
I'm aware of my own limitations.
I won't attempt something
beyond my abilities.
Which is why,
I'll make him
the warrior we need.
Huh?
[gasps]
We'll harness the potential
of his Anti-magic.
In three days, the gate
to the underworld
will be opened.
Before that happens, we're going
to take back Yami and Vangeance
and destroy the
Tree of Qliphoth.
Using my magic,
we'll be able to infiltrate
their castle without
being detected.
Once inside, we'll
attack the Dark Triad
and take each of them down.
Dante has gravity
and body magic.
Vanica has curse-warding
and blood magic.
Zenon has spatial
and bone magic.
[YUNO]
Zenon.
[NACHT] I won't be able to
take many people with me.
We need to select a group
that has the best chance
of success against the devils,
with Asta at its center.
Keh! No wonder
you're here, then.
Clearly, squad captains
are the ones you want
for this kinda thing.
[YUNO]
Let me go.
I know it's impudent to ask,
but please, let me join you.
Tch! Are you, stupid?
Like hell we're
gonna send anyone
who's already lost to them.
Yuno, I understand how
you feel right now,
but staying behind to
protect the Clover Kingdom
is also a vital task.
[ASTA]
Yuno.
[NACHT] Actually, I did
want to ask you something.
There's a resistance movement
in the Spade Kingdom
that seeks to undermine
the Dark Triad's rule.
Not long ago, a member
of this movement
snuck across the border
and into Clover.
He's at your hideout
now, isn't he?
What's this?
Tell me. Who are you, really?
[YUNO] Apparently, I'm the
prince of the Spade Kingdom.
[ALL gasp]
[screams]
Prince?! No freaking way!
Come on, you're not serious
about this, are you?
[YUNO]
Yes.
I was a newborn when the
royal family was overthrown.
Someone smuggled me out
and brought me to Clover.
[NOZEL]
I see. He's royalty,
that explains the tremendous
amount of mana he has.
The man that you
mentioned before,
he was loyal to the
previous rulers of Spade.
He should know a great deal
about the enemy and the castle.
[JACK]
Keh! That's even more reason
not to let you in on this.
For all we know, that
guy's an enemy spy!
And not just him, either.
Who says you're
not a spy, yourself?
If I don't save him,
then there's no point.
You don't understand.
Since the elves attacked,
you've been cautious.
You weren't sure you could
still trust Captain Vangeance.
And I can't blame you for that.
He couldn't choose between
the humans and the elves,
and our kingdom suffered.
But that's exactly why,
no matter how much he's hurting,
he continues to fight more
earnestly than anyone else.
I was defeated by Zenon,
but I remember...
As I was blacking out...
While he fought, Captain
Vangeance did his best
to keep the Golden Dawn safe.
If you rid yourself of
some of that baggage,
you'd be able to focus more
of your strength on our battle.
But you won't do that, will you?
And that's exactly why
you're going to lose.
Of course I won't
abandon them.
I made them walk a path of
thorns, but they rose again.
They forged ahead,
without resentment or regret.
They are all I could
ask them to be.
They are my dream!
He was only captured because
he was protecting us.
He could have saved
himself, but he didn't.
Maybe to you he's a traitor
who once turned his
back on this kingdom.
But to us, he's not.
He's everything a squad
captain should be!
Yuno.
[YUNO] That monster thinks
he annihilated the Golden Dawn.
He's wrong.
Thanks to the captain's magic,
we're alive and
ready to fight back!
This war is far from over.
The Golden Dawn
is still standing.
The greatest Magic Knight Squad
in the Clover Kingdom!
I'm going to prove that
he did the right thing
when he protected us.
They'll see just
how powerful we are!
I will be the one who
saves Captain Vangeance!
[JACK]
The hell's up with this mana?
Enough!
Just sit down and
shut up already, will ya?
[BELL]
Instead, how about you shut up?
I'm kinda busy
storing up mana, here.
We're gonna take down
that bony bastard!
Yuno won't lose to him again!
Very well, you're in.
I don't actually
hate people like you.
You may be the prince
of the Spade Kingdom
and the vice captain
of the Golden Dawn,
but you'll always be Yuno to me!
In three days, we'll depart
early in the morning
for the Spade Kingdom.
I'll send you a more
detailed plan later on.
This time, we're
on the offensive.
[ASTA] Now that I see
how Yuno's handling this,
I understand there's
no time to cry!
If I was too weak to win, that
means I need to be stronger!
No. I'll push past my limits
and become the strongest!
Let's go defeat the Dark Triad
and save both our captains!
Right!
In that case,
we'd better reach out
to Heart for
assistance, as well.
I've tried, but they haven't
answered me all day.
What?
Do you think something happened
to Charmy and everyone else?
Yesterday, each Dark Triad
member left their castle.
Knowing that,
I'd wager Vanica went off
to attack the Heart Kingdom.
You think so?
[gasps]
I don't believe it!
[ASTA]
No way!
So, the vice captain
of the Black Bulls
can use devil power, too?
Okay, what kind of training
are we gonna do to
make me the best?
[NACHT]
Black Clover , Page 169:
"The Devil-Binding Ritual."