[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] A brutal invasion
shattered the peace
of the Clover Kingdom's capital.
Fires blazed in five
areas of the city,
and the Magic Knights
mobilized immediately
to calm its panicking populace.
They soon found
themselves battling
hordes of unfamiliar foes.
[ASTA]
This time you're gonna have to
come after me yourself!
Think you've got me
beat now, do you?
No way, boy!
Come forth, Alfred!
Now, Number Two.
Say "hi" to Alfred.
Go and get him, Alfred.
He's all yours.
[ASTA grunts]
[RADES cackles]
[NOZEL]
That's odd.
They may be great in number,
but they are poor fighters.
Who is commanding them?
Why employ such a strategy?
What are they after?
[NOZEL]
The king?
[KING CLOVER] Why isn't the
Wizard King himself here?
These are the gravest
of circumstances,
and yet he fails
to do his sworn duty.
Whatever errand he was on,
he should have run
immediately to my side
at the first hint that the
capital was being threatened.
[KING CLOVER munching]
[KING CLOVER]
His primary task is to safeguard
the royal person from
any and all harm.
As our mightiest mage,
the Wizard King
is responsible for my
well-being above all else.
Has he forgotten that?
[MARX]
I assure you, he hasn't!
Sire.
We of the Wizard King's staff
will be here to guard you
until he can return.
[KING CLOVER]
Ah! That Julius.
We share authority
in military matters,
and he thinks that means
he can do whatever he pleases.
Arrogant pup.
Sometimes he seems to forget
that this kingdom
has but one ruler.
Augustus Kira Clover is king
here, not Julius Novochrono.
[CITIZENS screaming]
[whimpering]
[STAFF 23A] What are you
still doing here, Chef?
[STAFF 23B]
The capital is under attack.
We need to get
to safety quickly!
You fool!
I would never turn tail and run
during the middle of a dish.
I am a chef!
A little invasion won't stop
me from completing this feast.
All due respect, sir,
but I'm afraid
the banquet's over.
The Magic Knights have all gone
down to the city to fight.
There's no one for us to serve.
[HEAD CHEF 23A]
What?!
They had the nerve to leave
without even trying my entrée?
[STAFF 23B]
It is a national emergency.
[STAFF 23A]
Which means we need to get out.
[CHARMY screams]
[STAFF 23A]
Hey!
Wha--?
Where did this little
shortcake come from?
[CHARMY] You mentioned
a special entrée, Chef.
Huh?
I'd be honored if you'd
let me try it for you!
[STAFF 23A]
U-Uh...
[HEAD CHEF 23A]
A Magic Knight robe?
She must be one of the bigshots
from the Distinguished
Service Ceremony.
Look at her.
Those eyes, ablaze
with determination.
That drool, sparkling
with desperation.
This one is something special.
I hope you're hungry!
Just you wait.
I'll make you a dish that will
ruin you for all other food.
[STAFF 23A, STAFF 23B]
You can't be serious, sir!
[CHARMY]
Hooray!
We don't have time
for this. We'll die!
I'm not afraid of death.
Life is life, cooking is all!
[CHARMY squeals]
[ALFRED moans]
[ASTA grunts]
[cackles]
Poor little brat.
It looks like you're
having some trouble.
That rusty Anti-Magic sword
of yours is failing you.
[RADES] It's nothing more
than a hunk of metal
if you can't hit your target.
[growls]
[yelps]
Please don't get hit!
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
Quick, run!
Get away from there!
Okay!
But he needs help, too!
Everything will be all right.
Leave it to me. Don't worry.
I would never abandon
someone like that.
[yells]
[grunts]
[ASTA]
Come on! Get down here!
Did you really think
that would work?
He's not going to stand
still just because
you asked him to, you idiot.
[NOELLE] Back when we
were in the dungeon...
Yeah. I'll bring this guy down,
and I'll get one or two hits
in for you while I'm at it.
I may not have any magic power,
but what I do have
are my friends!
[NOELLE] When his sword
was imbued with my magic,
Asta defeated that mage.
If I lend him my power again,
even an enemy in mid-air
should be no problem.
[LEOPOLD]
Black Bull girl!
[LEOPOLD] If you're going
to step in and assist
your squad-mate,
I will accompany you.
I won't allow that coward
to harm my rival.
[NOELLE]
Great!
[WRAITH 23A growls]
A playmate for you.
That should keep you occupied.
[LEOPOLD]
Such muddy magic.
Not a good match with mine.
[NOELLE] Asta. That wound
he got earlier looks bad.
[RADES] Hey, brat. Remember
what you said earlier?
That stuff about me
coming after you myself.
[cackles]
Don't you get it?
Why would I bother
fighting you myself?
I've got plenty of others
to do it for me!
I just have to
sit back and watch.
That way I achieve
maximum results
with minimum risk.
The plus-side of not being
a musclebound moron.
I not only have a brain,
but I know how to use it.
Something you can't say.
[cackles]
[RADES]
Idiot!
[RADES cackles]
[ASTA]
What should I do?
This guy is more of a
monster than a human being.
I can't let him win!
What are you thinking
about over there?
How to defeat me?
Stop wasting your time.
Nothing's going to save you now.
Alfred!
[ALFRED growls]
[gasps] Asta!
[ASTA]
Damn it. Now what?
[RADES cackles]
Finish him!
[RADES]
No. Impossible.
My Alfred... Reduced to
cinders with one strike!
[RADES]
It was him.
[ASTA]
What's wrong with me?
Why couldn't I beat him?
I wanted to do it on my own.
I interfered in your fight.
It was necessary. I'm sorry.
I thought it a pity
for a Magic Knight
of your caliber to die here.
Forgive me.
I will say, though.
For a commoner with no magic,
you handled yourself well
against a difficult enemy.
You know, kid. I like you.
Come join our crew.
[FUEGOLEON]
He was right.
It pains me to admit it,
but Yami showed greater
foresight than the rest of us.
[FUEGOLEON]
Asta, was it?
Earlier.
You said you planned to
become the Wizard King.
Say what?
You think that you can
be the Wizard King?
Whatever Anti-Magic
abilities you have,
you're a brainless brat.
You'll never amount to anything.
[FUEGOLEON]
Asta.
It seems that I am
your rival as well.
[gasps]
Interesting turn of events.
The Black Bull boy
couldn't handle it,
so it looks like I've
got a new opponent.
[laughs] None other
than the captain
of the Crimson Lion Kings.
The great, Fuegoleon Vermillion.
[FUEGOLEON]
You've done enough.
You can leave
the rest to me now.
[WRAITH 23A growls]
He's all right!
My brother's got this.
[ASTA] Did he really mean
what he said before?
It seems that I am
your rival as well.
A captain's rival? No way!
[yells]
This is no time
to be giving up!
I'll fight with you.
I can keep going!
No, you can't.
[whimpers] Like I wasn't
already hurt enough?
[FUEGOLEON]
Exactly.
A warrior must always be aware
of his body's condition.
He must assess whether or not
he is truly able to fight.
[FUEGOLEON]
Right now I would say
that you most likely are not.
Your brash fearlessness
may well be
the greatest weapon you have,
but you must learn
to remain calm.
That is, if you truly do
wish to be the Wizard King.
[gasps]
Tell me. What is the
purpose of this attack?
Your actions are too
inconsistent for this
to be a true invasion,
and too organized
for it to be some
sort of terrorism.
Just who are you?
You really don't know?
Well. I can't say I'm surprised.
Though it's a shame I'm the only
one enjoying this reunion.
What's that?
Ha! I was a Magic Knight.
Inducted six years ago
as a top candidate.
[BOTH gasp]
One of us? No, that
can't be possible.
More than possible,
I assure you.
Though I suppose you took
little note of me at the time.
[gasps]
[FUEGOLEON]
He's a regular citizen.
But his power is incredible.
[STAFF 4A]
Do we have any hands, Captains?
It's been a long time,
but I remember you.
Your name?
[RADES huffs]
The name's Rades.
Rades, that's right.
You were chosen by
the Purple Orcas,
so why are you fighting
against us now?
Because those shortsighted
fools kicked me out.
You were expelled?
That doesn't make sense.
You were strong,
had so much potential.
They were frightened
by what I could do
with my Wraith Magic.
They said it was
dangerous. Forbidden.
I was exiled not
just from my squad,
but from the entire kingdom.
I'm only an average citizen.
No one cared enough
to stand up for me.
No one!
I was beneath them--
it didn't matter that
my skills were greater.
Greater than the nobles',
greater than anyone's!
Magic is supposed
to be everything,
and yet they cast me aside.
Fools!
There ya have it, Captain!
I'm here to use my cursed power
to get revenge on
the Magic Knights
and the kingdom rejected me.
That is the purpose
of this attack.
[VALTOS] Well, that's one
of the purposes, anyway.
All of this, just to
get your revenge?
Don't toy with me! You fool!
You doubt me? Ha!
That's the thing about reasons.
They're usually quite simple.
Leo!
Right here, Brother!
[FUEGOLEON]
Do you need any help?
Nope, we've got
this under control!
[NOELLE]
Uh...
[LEOPOLD]
Don't worry about us!
[NOELLE]
Hey!
[FUEGOLEON]
All right, then.
[NOELLE]
Hey!
You take care of that creature
while I handle the mage.
[LEOPOLD]
Yes, sir!
[ASTA]
Wow! These guys are hardcore!
Real warrior brothers!
You don't actually think
that's going to work?
Their magics are too mismatched
for a decent fight.
Not that I was going
to let you help.
They're on their own.
[gasps]
That's enough talking.
Time to fight.
Flame Creation Magic:
Leo Rugiens!
[gasps]
The wraith shielded itself.
[cackles] Meet my
Number One: Carl.
This fellow was extremely
good at defensive magic
back when he was alive.
With a dash of my
curse powers thrown in,
we're practically impervious.
Jeez! Another one?
How many does he have?
[FUEGOLEON]
Asta!
Uh, sir?
[FUEGOLEON]
Remember what I said before,
about staying calm?
Pay close attention.
You're so sure you'll
come out on top, aren't you?
Defensive magic isn't the
only area in which he excels.
[FUEGOLEON] Flame Creation
Magic: Ignis Columna!
So, you've got yourself
a magic barrier
just like Carl, huh?
[RADES] Fine, let's see
how well you hold up
when we combine
an ironclad defense
with a rapid-fire attack.
Indeed, I appear to
be quite helpless.
[cackles] Aw, is that
all you've got?
I have to say, Captain,
I'm very disappointed in you.
My Flame Magic: Sol Linea.
[FUEGOLEON] When you attacked,
the mana grew thin
in some places across the
barrier for the briefest moment.
Those were the spots
I aimed for.
You think I've never
been up against
that sort of attack before?
Listen up, you two!
[BOTH gasp]
[FUEGOLEON]
You are Magic Knights.
In the line of duty,
you will constantly face
strong foes and tricky magic.
You must calmly
judge your abilities
and those of your enemy.
Fight bravely, but keep a cool
head and maintain control.
It's not easy, but if you can
do that, you will not lose.
Understood?
[BOTH]
Yes, sir!
[ASTA] That quickly, he zeroed
in on the enemy's weakness
and managed to
reassure his allies.
So that's what it means to be
a Magic Knight squad captain.
Man, he's awesome!
No, it can't be.
He beat my Number One
wraith... so easily.
I should have won. Not him.
[FUEGOLEON]
Listen to me, Rades.
[RADES]
Huh?
You have incredible talent,
as well as powerful magic.
But wielded without
a just spirit,
they are no more than savagery.
You're a monster.
They were right to
have expelled you!
[RADES gasps]
[MARX]
I have a report, sire!
Almost all of the assailants
have now been neutralized.
Have they?
Well, it certainly
took them long enough.
The Magic Knights should
hone their skills.
[yawns] All right,
then. And Julius?
Is he still off gallivanting
about somewhere?
He's out on an
important mission, sire.
Honestly, now.
I can't imagine what he
could possibly be doing
that's more important
than protecting me.
It's over.
I'd still like to know
what those things were.
[SHIREN]
Mm...
[HAMON]
Whatever they were,
I find it highly unlikely that
they were our true enemy today.
[laughs]
[SOL] This is what happens to
people who dare to attack Char.
Serves you right!
The women of the
Blue Rose Knights
are the only ones who
can lay hands on her.
Enough.
You're just asking
to be misunderstood.
Only the Blue Rose Knights
can touch her tender skin!
Try again, Sol.
[SOL]
Hm?
[SOLID laughs] What's this?
Are we done already?
[NEBRA chuckles] Too bad.
I hardly got to play at all.
[NOZEL]
Something isn't right here.
[ALECDORA sighs]
I guess it's all but over.
[MIMOSA]
Ugh. Creepy. So very creepy.
[YUNO] I need to get
stronger so I can handle
something like this more easily.
[CITIZEN 23A] Amazing!
Such unbelievable strength!
Let's hear it for the
Magic Knights, everyone!
[CITIZENS]
Hip-hip hooray!
[CATHERINE] It's a bit
early to be celebrating.
The preparations must be
nearly complete by now.
[CATHERINE]
Time for a feast.
Such lively, young mana.
Absolutely delicious.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[HEAD CHEF 23A]
"3-Second Courtly Cooking."
Hello, everyone. Clover
Kingdom's royal chef here,
bringing you easy
three-second recipes
even a beginner can make.
Today we're whipping up
a three-second curry.
To keep it simple,
we'll start with a roux
purchased from the market.
Then carrots, onions,
and potatoes.
You can add mushrooms
or tomatoes if you like.
Flavoring your curry
with a touch
of chocolate or coffee
can give it more depth.
Now, simply take
your ingredients, and...
[yells]
Use magic to dice them
up and stew them.
The more passion
you put into it,
the better your curry will be.
Three seconds and done!
Wasn't that easy?
All right, come to Mama!
So good!
This has been Three-Second
Courtly Cooking,
with easy recipes
that anyone can make.
[BOTH]
See you later!
Impossible!
[KING CLOVER]
Will the Magic Knights
please hurry up and
do their jobs already?
Black Clover ,
Page 24: "Blackout."
As ruler of Clover Kingdom, I,
Augustus Kira Clover
the Thirteenth,
have some important tasks.
Namely, eating and napping.