[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy
who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
[NARRATOR]
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world
and to become the
next Wizard King!
[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
Much of the royal capital was
decimated during an attack
by the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
but repairs are
running smoothly.
As proof that
this ruthless enemy
is no longer a threat,
the residents have gathered
in the square, knowing that
the stalwart individuals
who watch over their nation
are working tirelessly
to restore peace and normalcy
as soon as possible.
[MAN 130A]
Captain Vangeance!
[GIRL 130A]
That's him! [squeals]
He's the hero who saved us all!
[MAN 130B]
The captains are so great!
[GIRL 130B]
Lord Fuegoleon!
[GIRL 130C]
Not only is he captain again,
but he controls
Salamander now, too!
[GIRL 130D]
And there's Lord Nozel.
His bangs are dreamy!
[MAN 130C] I heard that
he was on the front lines
during that last battle!
[MAN 130D]
Lady Charlotte!
[MAN 130E] They say every
rose has its thorns...
[CHARLOTTE]
I don't see Yami
or the Green Praying
Mantis Captain.
How dare they be late on an
important occasion such as this?
[GIRL 130E]
There's Rill!
[MAN 130F]
Uh, is he okay?
Looks like he's
spacing out there.
[MAN 130G]
Oh, yeah, I know that face.
He's definitely in love.
[RILL]
That wonderful girl.
I wonder where she is now.
[WALTER]
Master Rill's first love!
Great news, Madam!
Your precious little boy
is starting to become a man!
I'd say it's only
a matter of time
before you'll be a grandmother!
[MAN 130H]
Wow, look, it's Lady Dorothy!
[GIRL 130F]
She's awake!
Who knew she had
such pretty eyes?
Hey there! How is everybody?
[MAN 130I] Lord Kaiser looks
awfully dapper today!
[MAN 130J] Yeah, but he
seems a little down.
[sighs]
[GIRL 130G] Check it out!
The man of the hour!
[GIRL 130H]
Wizard King!
[GIRL 130I]
Oh, no, is he injured?
[MAN 130K] I guess so,
I heard he was the one
who stopped the
Eye of the Midnight Sun
back when they attacked
the royal capital.
[GIRL 130I] Goodness,
he must've been through
such a terrible ordeal
to protect all of us.
I hope he isn't
in too much pain.
[MAN 130K]
We'll never forget what he did!
Go, Wizard King!
[OWEN]
What?
You want me to pose as you?
That's ridiculous!
Perhaps, but I can't exactly
go marching into the capital
looking like a child.
There'd be trouble if
the king saw me this way.
And, of course, not appearing
at all would be suspicious.
True, but don't you think
they'll know the difference?
I've already thought
through the whole thing.
All you have to do is
stand up there and wave.
Here. Cover your
face with these.
Wha--?
[OWEN] Your appearance is
different now, but inside,
you're the same
as you ever were.
Just smile and wave and
pray they don't notice.
[WILLIAM clears throat]
We're sorry. The Wizard King
has a sore throat
today, so, sadly,
he won't be able
to speak to you all.
Please excuse him.
[GIRL 130K] Aw, I was looking
forward to hearing from him.
[MAN 130M]
Well, these things happen.
[GIRL 130L]
Yeah.
[WILLIAM] Now. I'd like everyone
to give a round of applause
to the valiant hero who
stood up to our enemies
and protected our
beloved kingdom.
Our illustrious ruler.
Augustus Kira Clover
the Thirteenth!
[GIRL 130M]
Oh, hey, he's here, too.
[MAN 130N]
He's okay, I guess.
[GIRL 130N murmurs]
Thanks for your help.
Why are you
dawdling back there?
Pick up the pace, knave!
This is my one moment
of glory, you know!
So- hah- ry!
[SEKKE]
How the heck did I end up
being errand boy to this king?
It turns out, going with
the flow is for chumps!
How dare you stand
in my royal bubble?
Same goes for you!
[KING CLOVER]
Curse you, Julius!
Now I'm responsible for
addressing the people,
all because you have a little
tickle in your pathetic throat?
Then again, this might be
the perfect opportunity
to demonstrate my superior
dignity and benevolence.
You poor fool.
I hope you enjoyed the
attention while it lasted!
[KING CLOVER]
A-hem! Greetings and salutations
to all my loyal subjects!
Your king, Augustus Kira
Clover the Thirteenth,
is gracing you
with his presence!
[KING CLOVER] Erm. What's this?
They're at a loss for words!
They must be stunned
by my immaculate visage!
[CITIZEN 130A]
Is he almost done, or...?
[CITIZEN 130AA]
Shh!
[WILLIAM]
Yes. As you can see,
the public awaits
your kingly wisdom
with bated breath, Majesty.
But please make it
as brief as possible,
lest the suspense kill them.
Er, of course.
[KING CLOVER]
Hmph! I beg your pardon!
The king takes
orders from no one!
[KING CLOVER]
A-hem! Thanks to my brave deeds,
with minimal assistance
from the Magic Knights,
the Eye of the
Midnight Sun has fled,
and peace has finally been
restored to the Clover Kingdom.
You're so welcome!
None of this would've
been possible
without the impressive things
I do on a daily basis!
However, I imagine some
of you are still concerned!
How will your lives change?
What if another enemy
tries to attack us?
But I promise, there's
no need for that!
Hark! Witness my
splendid Light Magic!
How majestic! How striking!
Light Magic:
Absolute Monarch
of Divine Brilliance!
[KING CLOVER]
Perfection.
And so, my adoring public!
As long as the Clover Kingdom
remains in my capable hands,
it shall always be safe!
Lay all your cares and
doubts upon my shoulders!
Huh?
--[KING CLOVER yelps]
--[CROWD screams]
Damnit. That's enough, beanpole.
Let's settle this feud
once and for all!
[cackles] You don't
have to ask me twice.
Time to put your money where
your mouth is, foreigner!
Hey, wait. What's going on?
What is this, a party?
Yami, Jack. I know
I told you two.
We had an important
event planned today.
We were supposed to
gather in the square
and tell everyone that
the enemy's been defeated.
Oh, was that today?
[cackles] Must've
slipped my mind.
Picking unnecessary fights
is not an acceptable
reason to show up late.
Trust me, he's the
one who started it.
That's a lie!
We were both there, you know
damn well what happened!
I think we've heard enough
from the two of you.
This is hardly
the time or place.
[YAMI, JACK]
Tch.
[CITIZEN 130B] Goodness, both
of those squads are so violent!
[CITIZEN 130BB]
You saw the paper, right?
They say one of the Black Bulls
is possessed by a devil!
[CITIZEN 130B]
That makes sense.
When they placed second
at the Star Festival,
I knew they must've
had outside help.
[CITIZEN 130BB]
Exactly! Everyone knows
they're the worst squad.
Why, you irreverent ingrates!
How dare you intrude upon my
invincible Light Magic spell?
[YAMI]
Huh?
Your what?
Don't test me!
You brutes stepped
right into my spotlight!
Your Highness.
Perhaps this is a chance to
show the people your leniency.
If they see how merciful
you are, they'll like you more.
Ah, is that so?
[KING CLOVER]
Who wants your opinion?
Just because you've
been hailed as a hero.
Give me a break!
[KING CLOVER]
Er, I mean...
I must applaud your fervor!
By all means, gentlemen,
keep being your raucous selves!
It's a symbol of your
passion for our great land!
[JACK, YAMI]
Sure.
And now, His Majesty
will take his leave.
Let's give him one more
round of applause.
[applause]
Um. Excuse me, Captain Jack?
Look, anytime you
want me to come back
to the Praying Mantises,
just give me a ha- hah- ller!
"Come back"?
Who the hell are you?
[SEKKE]
Ha, ha?!
Attend to me, servant boy!
Uh, be right there!
Is he one of your guys?
You really think I'd let
a wuss like that on my squad?
[WILLIAM sighs]
I suppose it's about time
for us to head out, as well.
Yeah, I guess.
'Kay, later!
[GIRL 130O]
Lord Vangeance!
[OWEN]
Thank goodness it's over.
[YAMI] You gonna explain
your outfit, doc?
Or do we have to guess?
[OWEN]
What?
[FINRAL] Yikes. All of
the Magic Knight Captains
in the same room.
Kind of hard not to feel like
we're under a lot of pressure.
Yeah, if this is
supposed to be a meeting
for captains, then I
wonder why they wanted
all of us to be a part of it.
I should apologize, Yami.
You and the Black Bulls are the
ones who deserve that praise,
and yet the audience
mostly cheered for me.
We're kinda used to
gettin' booed, actually.
Right, I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Just forget about it.
[CHARLOTTE]
Calm down.
Don't let your
heart go aflutter.
Just relax and breathe.
What's wrong, Prickly Princess?
Your face is all red.
Feelin' okay?
I'm perfectly all right!
[YAMI]
Listen.
[gasps]
If you need to take a dump,
it's not healthy
to hold it in, just go!
That's not the issue at all!
How can a person be
so utterly devoid of tact?
So I was wrong?
Dead wrong!
[JACK] You really don't
get it, do you, Yami?
No wonder everyone's calling
you a clueless idiot.
She needs to piss.
No!
[NOELLE]
And they're in charge.
[MIMOSA]
Are they like that all the time?
[FINRAL]
I wish this was shocking to me.
Forcing us to come to a meeting
and then being the
last person to show up.
If that's not typical Julius,
I don't know what is.
I bet you anything
he forgot about all this.
He's probably off goofin' around
somewhere like a little idiot.
Crazy old man.
Or crazy old kid, I guess.
I hate to say it,
but you're right.
[NOZEL]
Shameful.
Yeah, that's true!
He's so silly!
[CAPTAINS]
Agreed.
Any idea what his problem is?
Nope!
He's been stuck like that since
the curse broke, apparently.
[MARX] I'm sorry for
the wait, everyone.
Excellent. I see
you all made it.
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
Him again!
[MIMOSA]
Damnatio.
They asked him to come, too?
Pardon the delay.
Careful.
If you try to condemn one
of my squad members again,
I swear I will--
Yami.
I'm the one who
summoned him here,
so there's no need to fight.
Wait, you were invited?
So it would seem.
Apparently, the topic
in question involves me.
I was informed that my
presence was required.
Our meeting today
is about the devil residing
in the Spade Kingdom.
Recently, some of our
Magic Knights paid a visit
to the Heart Kingdom
hoping to gather
information about the devils.
I trust everyone's seen
the reports by now.
However, since you
all were there,
we would like
to hear it from you.
Please proceed.
Okay!
We'll do our best, sir.
[MIMOSA] In the Heart Kingdom,
the strength of a mage
is normally determined by
a system called magic stages.
[NOELLE] The ranking starts
at nine, then eight, seven,
and so on.
And the smaller the number,
the stronger the mage.
[FINRAL] According to Queen
Loropechika, it's extremely rare
and favorable to have
mages at stage zero.
So, whenever there's a battle,
the side with the most warriors
at that level is considered
the superior one.
And this is the
most important part
of what we've learned.
If we go up against a devil,
we won't stand a chance
unless everyone is
at least a stage one.
A stage one, eh?
Right.
Asta and his companions
traveled to the Heart Kingdom
to investigate a curse
that was cast by a devil.
We found that the victim
was the queen herself.
Apparently, she only
has a year left to live.
And the devil who
cursed her was...
...Megicula, yes.
[NOELLE gasps]
[MARX] Some of the other
Black Bulls also made a report.
It seems the Diamond Kingdom
is currently under attack
by the Spade Kingdom.
Over the past few years, Spade
has steadily become stronger.
It's likely...
...that they could
be receiving assistance
from the very devil
we're discussing, right?
So, to sum everything up,
I've called this meeting so
we can decide the best way
to provide aid to
the Heart Kingdom.
Queen Loropetchka plans
to invade the Spade Kingdom
in six months' time,
before she becomes too weak.
We're considering
deploying our own forces
to fight alongside them.
I'm asking each one of you
to make your squads
are as strong as you can.
We only have six months,
but please do
everything possible
to raise their stages to one.
We must defeat Spade to protect
the residents of Heart,
as well as our own land.
I've been informed
by Queen Loropetchka
that the Spirit Guardians
are also going to contribute.
Can I count on you?
Yes, Wizard King.
Of course.
As if you needed to ask me.
My team has already started.
I told the Black Bulls
they could do things
however they see fit
over the next half a year.
Yes, William?
I'll participate in the battle.
However, as you all know,
the things I did in the
past were unforgivable,
and I believe I am
no longer worthy
of facing my squad as Captain.
And so, with a heavy heart,
I request that you
relieve me of my position.
--[ASTA] Huh?
--[MIMOSA gasps]
Wait--
If you would, sir,
I'd like you to assign
me a new mission.
It would be an honor
to put my life on the line
to help overthrow this devil.
Captain Vangeance.
If he's to blame
in this, then so am I.
Although my body was possessed
by an elf at the time.
I have committed
unspeakable crimes.
I should be put to death.
I failed as well.
It isn't right to
call myself a captain.
Eh, I don't feel all that
bad about it, actually.
[YAMI]
Oh, really? 'Cause you should.
All right, I've heard enough.
I understand why some of you
may be feeling ashamed
of what happened.
That being said,
I cannot and will not
take away your
responsibilities as captains.
If I did,
I'd have to extend
the same treatment
to the other Magic Knights who
fell under control of the elves,
and that's a lot
of people to punish.
Without them,
we'd hardly have anyone
left to guard our land!
If you truly want to
atone for your actions,
your only option is
to forget your titles
and work together to
protect the Clover Kingdom!
I'm putting my complete
trust in you all.
[CHARLOTTE]
Sir!
[KAISER]
As you command.
Roger that!
For you, Wizard King.
So, Damnatio.
Does this arrangement
work for you?
How do you mean, sir?
[JULIUS]
As we established,
the Magic Knights need to
train for the next six months
in order to be successful in
their battle against the devil.
Asta's still waiting
to receive a sentence,
but surely you can
table that decision
until after this
is dealt with, yes?
I suppose I don't object.
But let me be quite clear.
I've chosen to cooperate
only because I believe
this is the most
beneficial strategy
for the Clover Kingdom at large.
Now, please excuse me.
Tch. I know where he can
shove those damn scales.
Wow, you really got me
off the hook, Wizard King,
thank you so much.
There's no need to thank me.
[ASTA]
Okay, but I'm super grateful!
Anyway, I'm expecting
great things from you.
[cackles] You can depend on me!
I can't wait to slice
up my subordinates.
That's one way to trim the fat!
[YAMI]
Not the point.
This'll be fun!
I'll start creating
our training
regimen immediately.
Actually, it might be best
if all the squads
do this together.
That's a good idea.
We could hold mock battles.
[cackles] I'm not holding back!
[YAMI]
That's my line, freak!
Perhaps we should go ahead
and enlist a few healing mages.
I'm sure we're
going to need them.
[laughs] Don't get
too carried away!
This is as good a time as any.
Marx, why don't you
bring him in now?
Yes, sir.
Oh?
[YAMI]
Hey, it's the ham hock again.
[JULIUS] Obviously,
all of you are familiar
with Gueldre Poizot, the former
captain of the Purple Orcas.
He was recently
caught in a crime,
robbing the Shadow Palace.
He and Revchi, the disgraced
former Magic Knight
who was once his superior,
managed to get away
with an enormous haul
of precious gems
and ancient magic items.
Scum.
Honestly, when will
you ever learn?
I can't wait any longer.
I'm going to slice this ham
into little bite-sized pieces!
I'd be doing the kingdom
a service, right?
[JULIUS]
That's not necessary.
Because I've been
thinking I might
like to pardon Gueldre instead.
Pardon him?
[GUELDRE]
What?
This man happens to have
a great talent for business.
I believe he's capable of
turning an impressive profit
by selling the very treasures
that he attempted to purloin.
[GUELDRE grunts]
[JULIUS] I'd like him
to use that extra money
for the benefit of
the Clover Kingdom.
The repairs we've been doing
are far from cheap, after all,
and we don't exactly have access
to infinite financial resources.
You'll lend us your
services, won't you?
Well... I don't know.
[GUELDRE] Suddenly my life
depends on whether or not
I can make a business deal?
Please?
Yes, Your Highness!
I swear, I'll do
everything I can!
[JULIUS]
Thank you, this is a big help.
[GUELDRE]
Ah. Of course!
[ASTA] He made him an offer
he couldn't refuse!
[FINRAL] He's pushy like
Yami, but way sneakier!
You better make sure
you fetch us a good price
at the market, little piggy!
That's right, 'cause if
you screw this up,
you're going straight
to the chopping block.
There's just one more thing.
As I explained to you all
a few moments ago,
we do have certain limitations
when it comes to our finances.
Therefore, in order to alleviate
the financial burden
caused by our situation,
I'll need to reduce your pay
by 50 percent.
[BOTH]
Huh?
A logical solution, indeed.
I can accept that.
It's fine with me.
Yeah, it's okay.
No sweat!
It's no problem at all.
That's the least
that I could do.
Well, that settles it, then!
[YAMI]
Uh, I don't think so!
Not happening!
Is something wrong?
Come on, man, I'm in debt,
you can't just cut my pay!
Do you want us to go broke?
Uh... Remember, your
subordinates are present.
Be an example!
This is my example!
[JULIUS] Well, we decide these
things based on majority, so...
Reduced pay, it is!
[MARX]
With that, we now conclude
the Magic Knights Squad
Captains' meeting.
[JACK, YAMI]
What a load of crap!
[crash]
How long do you plan
to act like drunken fools?
I can't endure this.
Fine, go home then, nerd!
We can't expect you to care.
Yeah, you nobles
are rich, anyway.
You probably won't even
notice the difference
when you lose half your pay!
This is nonsense.
[KAISER] I wish you'd learn
to drink in moderation.
Bye! Don't throw up!
I betcha old Goldiguts
can stick around.
Yeah, you got time.
Come on, hero who
saved the kingdom!
Do us a favor and join
us for a quick game.
[WILLIAM]
Game?
We'll get our salary back
by making you gamble it away!
Fine, I'll play.
[YAMI, JACK]
We're about to clean you out!
[YAMI, JACK snoring]
Typical.
I win again.
[YAMI]
I got three times my paycheck.
I'm truly grateful
to both of you.
Despite what happened,
you haven't treated me
the least bit differently.
You have my word.
I'm going to do everything in
my power to defeat that devil.
Goodnight, then.
Here you are, sir.
I'm sorry my friends
made such a racket.
[BARKEEP 130AA]
Thank you very much.
[NARRATOR] The Magic Knight
squads begin preparing
for their confrontation
with Megicula.
Meanwhile, Asta and Yuno
pay a visit to Hage Village.
Black Clover , Page 131:
"A New Resolve."
The road to becoming
Wizard King stretches on!