[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[ASTA grunts]
[ASTA]
So beautiful.
What is that? Where am I?
Am I... dead?
Hey, did I die?!
--[ASTA grunts]
--[MIMOSA] Oops! I'm sorry!
You're awake!
Quit babbling like an idiot.
[YUNO]
Stop being dramatic.
Yuno? Noelle, Mimosa.
Sir Spectacles, you, too?
Well, we were worried about you.
I'm so glad you're
back with us, Asta.
I thought we were
going to lose you.
[yelps] Okay, that's it!
This hug's gone on long enough!
That's not gonna help me heal.
I...
Hmph!
[ASTA]
What?!
I've seriously been
asleep for a whole day?
[NOELLE]
That's right.
And you had the nerve
to snore the entire time.
Loudly.
[KLAUS] That's the
exhaustion that comes from
fighting with
everything you have.
We wanted to help you as well,
but by the time we'd arrived,
the Eye of the Midnight
Sun had run away.
The word came awfully late.
At least we got to take
care of you afterwards,
even if we weren't able
to join the battle.
Your Recovery Magic
really helped.
Thank you!
[gasps] Oh, no.
It was nothing. Really.
Klaus actually did
most of the work.
He hardly ever left your side.
[KLAUS]
A-hem! Well, anyway.
Thanks to you,
the abducted children
all returned home safely.
And the one who took them--
Neige, I believe--
He's being questioned
back at HQ.
Although I doubt
he can tell us much
about the Eye of
the Midnight Sun.
Since he appears
genuinely remorseful
and has demonstrated
no malicious intent,
he'll be volunteering
here at the church
as restitution for his crimes.
Good! He felt so bad,
I was hoping
it would be something like that.
[KLAUS] In any case,
you did a fine job yet again.
[YUNO]
If it were me,
I wouldn't have allowed the
enemy to escape so easily.
Yeah, well now I'm
gonna catch them.
Yuno! I'm not lettin' you
get the better of me!
You'll see.
I'm just gonna keep getting
stronger and stronger.
Then I guess I'll just have
to keep getting stronger
and stronger and stronger.
Then I'll just keep getting
stronger and stronger
and stronger and stronger!
I'll work hard until
someday I become...
[BOTH]
...the Wizard King!
Oh, just look at you two!
You're obviously
really good friends.
--[YUNO] What?
--[ASTA] Yeah.
Ridiculous.
Now that Asta's awake,
we should be on our way.
Yes, sir.
Oh, right, I almost forgot.
I meant to tell you,
Sister Theresa just woke up.
What?
Gauche is in there with her now.
Thought I might as well
pay you a visit
since you're conscious,
you useless old crone.
That's not the proper way
to speak to someone
on her sickbed.
Why don't you try that
again, you delinquent?
[GAUCHE]
Why don't I just finish you off,
you half-dead old hag?
Go ahead.
You'll be right back in
prison the second you do,
you depraved ex-convict.
Hey! No fighting, big brother!
Of course, angel,
whatever you say.
Well, I suppose I can
bring myself to thank you
for taking care of Marie,
you withered old bat.
[SISTER THERESA] Hmph. So
you've matured just enough
to show gratitude when
it's warranted, then.
Also... I'm...
I'm glad you didn't die.
[gasps]
Is that right?
Well, my beautiful little angel.
Are you going to praise your
big brother for not fighting?
'Scuse me!
[giggles] It's Asta, yay!
[MARIE, ASTA laugh]
You slept so long,
I thought you were dead.
I'm never gonna die!
Oh, yeah? We'll see about that.
Still got a ways to go.
Sister. Your wounds
healin' up all right?
Do I look like some
fragile old lady to you?
I'm fine.
I bet you're anxious
to tell Sister Lily
about your latest exploits.
She'll be thrilled to hear
the story, I'm sure.
You're right! She's
gonna be so excited.
Don't worry, Sister Lily.
Soon I'll be the Wizard King,
and then I'll come back for you!
[NOELLE]
Come on, Asta.
It's time for us to
be getting back, too.
Fine. But I gotta
make a stop first.
Huh?
Ah!
I'm so glad you like it.
I figured you'd wake up hungry,
so I wanted to have
plenty of food.
But I might've made too much.
[NOELLE] I hate to say it, but
this is really, really tasty.
Kill him. Kill him.
[MARIE]
Come on, big brother!
I've still got room left!
--[GAUCHE] Die. Die. Die.
--[ASTA] This is so good!
[NOELLE] So, maybe men
really do prefer women
who know how to cook.
[MARCO]
Asta! Thank you for the robe!
Sure!
You kept it all clean
like you promised, right?
Yep!
The robe may be clean,
but that's a lot more
than I can say for you.
It looks like you really
do need me around, after all.
[ASTA] But I'm a mess
even when you are...
[REBECCA] So she's the
girl he fights beside.
Well... I'm no match for her.
[ASTA]
Hey, it's okay.
[REBECCA]
Asta!
Huh?
[yelps]
[REBECCA] Sorry, but I'm
taking this much, at least.
If it weren't for you,
I might have lost Luca
and Marco. Thank you!
I, uh. Um. Yeah,
sure, no problem.
Just glad I could help.
Hey, wha...?
Did she just...?
No!
[MAGNA] You done digesting
your lunch, there, L'il Rasta?
[ASTA]
Yes, sir!
[MAGNA] Good! 'Cause, to
celebrate your recovery,
it's time for the Black Bulls'
traditional eating contest!
This time we're feasting
on pop-potato pies!
Right!
Can we start eating now?
I'm starving.
Is this actually a
Black Bulls tradition?
It's not. Hey, wanna spar?
I gotta make up for missing
out on the big fight.
It's only been half a day,
but it feels like
forever, Marie.
[mumbling] I wanted to throw
Asta a surprise party,
but nobody listened.
[GREY growls]
Sorry, think I'll have to pass.
I'd rather not end up
in a food coma.
[NOELLE]
I'm passing, too.
A competition like this is
hardly suitable for royalty.
You can't just say no!
This competition
is mandatory, folks.
Yami, sir! If you would kindly
judge the event? Thank you!
Fine, cut the chit-chat
and let's get started.
Ready. Eat!
It's so yummy!
My mouth is totally dry now.
I haven't even taken a bite yet,
so how come my stomach's
full already?
[YAMI] I see what you're
doin' there, Finral.
Stop usin' Spatial Magic
to send your food
into Luck's stomach.
I'm busted.
Sir! I'm not very hungry.
If there were a pretty
woman to feed me...
[YAMI]
You're out!
Oh, yeah! Let's go!
Flame Magic:
Explosive Reheating!
[groans]
Thought it'd taste
better well-done,
but that's a bit much.
You're out, too.
I'm nowhere near full. Let's go!
Hi.
Jeez, Gordon! Don't sneak
up on people like that!
You're gonna make me choke!
[whispering] Don't
mind me, Asta.
You can keep on...
[YAMI]
That's kinda creepy, so, out.
[sighs] I won't have an appetite
until I see my precious...
[YAMI] And you two
aren't even eating. Out!
If I could just
have a sip of water.
[yelps]
Those losers over there
tapped out ages ago.
So who do we have left?
[CHARMY, ASTA munching]
[MAGNA] It's an Asta
and Charmy showdown!
[munching]
I'm not done yet!
I'll win this contest
without using magic!
Just wait and see!
[NARRATOR]
The results.
With no magic used,
the winner was Charmy!
Well, better luck
next time, kiddo.
[yells] But not using magic
is my whole identity!
[FINRAL, NOELLE, MAGNA]
Big surprise.
[ASTA] That crest! It's a
letter from the royal capital!
Did something happen?
Are we going?
Stop yappin' for
a second, will ya?
Yes, it's from the capital.
Looks like the Wizard King's
asking for you.
The Wizard King?
The squad captains
are getting together
for a meeting tomorrow,
says to drag you along, too.
[ASTA] Whoa! What's he
want me there for?
Like I know.
You're just gonna have to come
to the capital and find out.
[MARX]
Sir.
I've done as you asked.
The captains have been notified
about tomorrow's meeting.
[JULIUS]
Excellent, thank you.
As much as I don't
wanna believe it,
I can no longer deny that
there's a traitor in our midst
with ties to the Eye
of the Midnight Sun.
Tomorrow will be our
best opportunity
to find out who.
[MARX]
But...
Do you really think
it's going to work?
[JULIUS]
We'll know soon enough.
It all depends on Asta.
[MARX]
Thank you for waiting.
Welcome, Captain Yami Sukehiro
of the Black Bulls,
and Asta.
Sorry, um. What's your name?
Right, we've never
talked before.
I suppose I should have
introduced myself.
How rude.
This here's Mushroomhead.
Thank you, Captain.
I'm Mushroomhead--
That was both impolite
and uncalled for, sir!
My real name is Marx,
and it's my honor
to serve at the
Wizard King's side.
The Wizard King?
Wow, Mushroomhead,
that's amazing!
Well. It certainly
isn't dull anyway,
and your captain
was only joking.
My name is Marx,
not Mushroomhead.
It's been real fun chattin'
with ya, Mushroomhead.
Now where's the meeting?
My name is Marx, sir!
The preparations are going
to take a little bit longer.
Please wait with
the other captains.
Now, Asta, if you would
please come with me.
Huh?
[MARX] I understand you
had a particularly fine
showing the other day.
It's very rare for
the Wizard King
to give out ten stars at once.
No way! Ten whole stars?
That's awesome!
Uh, hey where are we, anyway?
[MARX]
A secret underground prison.
Hardly anyone in the
capital knows about it.
It's where we keep
the VIPs, so to speak.
VIPs? Like who?
[MARX]
You've heard about the members
of the Eye of the
Midnight Sun captured
for their part in the
attack on the capital?
So you've been keeping
them down here?
[MARX]
Yes.
They've had memory-protecting
magic cast on them,
so we haven't been
able to get any intel
on their organization.
But the Wizard King has an idea.
He believes that
your anti-magic sword
might be able to break
the Protect spell.
That's why you're here.
Throughout the attack,
they always seemed to
anticipate our next move.
That wouldn't be possible
unless they were working
with somebody inside
the capital.
I'm afraid that the
only explanation
is that there's
a traitor among us,
and somebody who's fairly
high-ranked, at that.
A Magic Knight captain,
for instance.
What? Seriously?
We don't want to
believe it, either.
That's why we need to
make absolutely certain.
[MARX]
We're here.
[ASTA]
Right.
Hello?
Hi! Come on in, Asta.
That was some good
work the other day.
Thanks a lot, Wizard King, sir.
I'll try to keep it up.
I'm sorry. I know
you must be tired.
But you're the only
one who can use
that anti-magic sword, so...
Incidentally,
I heard you fought some
of the Midnight Sun's
strongest mages.
And about their
magic--was it cool?
Um. Yeah I guess so.
[JULIUS]
Copy Magic?
It just copies another
mage's spell?
Simply amazing!
Ooh, and Beast Magic?
I've never even heard
of that before!
And Spirit Magic?
Flame Spirit Magic?
How marvelous!
I wish I could have been there!
Uh, sorry?
Sir. Calm yourself!
Uh. Right, sorry.
You've heard our plan, Asta.
I think it just
might work. Do you?
Absolutely.
Whatever you need,
I'm at your service!
Yay!
What'd they bring this
little brat here for?
You'll see. That's the kid
who uses anti-magic.
They'll have him try to
dispel the Protect magic
cast on our memories.
[gasps]
[ASTA chuckles]
[CATHERINE]
No, don't!
Keep that thing away
from us, you swine!
[ASTA]
Hai-yah!
Dink. Donk.
All right, Marx, it's your turn.
Sir!
Memory Exchange Magic:
Mémoire Absolue!
What's it doing?
[MARX] This spell lets us
communicate directly
with their minds,
allowing us to hear only
their truthful memories.
Which means they can't hide.
Whoa!
Yeah, amazing, right?
Poking around in people's
heads like that!
It's so cool!
Sure.
If you don't mind,
I'm trying to concentrate.
[BOTH]
'Kay.
[MARX] I'm going to ask
you some questions.
You are to answer them honestly.
Understood?
[BOTH]
Yes, sir.
I heard all about your little
rumble in Nean Village.
Four Magic Knight captains
and you let a terrorist
ring leader get away?
How embarrassing.
[cackles] They were a little
tougher than those nobodies
from the Diamond
and Spade Kingdoms
you and your squad
went up against.
We were in a real battle.
[GUELDRE chuckles]
That's awfully big talk
coming from a man whose squad
has fewer stars than mine.
[JACK cackles]
Only because we don't stoop
to doing sneaky
stuff on the sly.
[GUELDRE, JACK laugh]
[YAMI laughs] I don't know
about this new katana.
Just doesn't shine the same.
And with the ten-year payment
plan they have me on,
I'm gonna be in
debt for a while.
Anyway, you need to calm down,
Skinnybones Lineface.
Garbletron's actually
got a point.
It's Gueldre!
Like I'm interested in
the opinion of somebody
who doesn't have
any stars at all.
[YAMI] Hm? We got plenty
of stars--black ones.
[JACK] You really want to brag
about having negative stars?
Will you two be silent?
Foreigners and low-born fools
should hold their tongues.
[YAMI]
What's that?
You wanna join our crew,
Sir Stuffypants?
This is absurd.
We'll never accomplish anything.
Not with all these
men blathering on.
[CHARLOTTE] And why do I
have to be next to Yami?
Calm down, Charlotte.
Don't panic. Just be yourself.
[chuckles] We still need
an interim captain
for the Crimson Lion Kings.
Whoever it is will have
big shoes to fill.
If Fuegoleon were here,
he would've had
everything settled five minutes
after he walked
through the door.
[gasps]
[RILL]
Why's everyone so gloomy?
Some youthful charm
should lighten the mood!
Check it out, you guys!
I'm Captain
Fuegoleon Vermillion.
What exactly do you
think you're doing?
You may have become
a captain at a young age,
but you still need
to show some respect.
[RILL]
Aw.
[YAMI laughs]
You're a funny one, kid.
[WILLIAM]
I've kept you all waiting.
I apologize for my tardiness.
What were you doing, Vangeance?
[WILLIAM] Oh. Something
needed my attention.
[GUELDRE]
Heh. You're busy.
And who would expect
it to be otherwise?
The charismatic captain with
the most stars to his name
this term must have a lot to do.
So tell me, what is your secret?
How did the Golden Dawn
come to be the mightiest
of all the Magic Knight Squads,
and in record time, at that?
I hear every member
of your squad
is developing greater talents
than would have been
expected of them.
Do you perhaps have
magic that allows you
to see into someone's future?
Regrettably, I can
claim no such power.
The members of the Golden Dawn
are simply diligent workers.
As a matter of fact,
I've wanted to ask you,
the mighty tycoon,
the secret to
amassing a fortune.
[GUELDRE chuckles] That's a
trade secret, I'm afraid.
There's somethin' I've
noticed for a while now.
You've got one hell
of a creepy laugh.
And you thought today's meeting
would be a good time to tell me?
Also, it's scary how much
you look like a boneless ham.
Tell me, Vangeance.
What were you doing on the day
of the Distinguished
Service Ceremony?
When a captain has knights
who are taking part
in the ceremony, that captain
should also be in attendance.
Perhaps there was
something that needed
your attention that day, too.
Well?
I was playin' the
gentleman's game of chance.
Got cleaned out,
too. You get it.
[NOZEL]
Nobody asked.
[RILL]
The mood's slipping again.
I know!
And as for you.
If you intend to impersonate
me, then be prepared.
There will be consequences.
[gasps] I can't do it!
Turns out those braided bangs
are really tough to pull off.
[YAMI laughs] You are
seriously killin' me, kid.
Now stop givin' Goldie
here such a hard time.
Oh, and hey.
You don't happen to use
Light Magic, do ya?
No, I don't.
[RILL] Oh, man, it just
keeps getting worse.
[RILL]
Hey, check this out!
Hi, I'm Yami!
Okay!
Now you keep your darn
mouth shut, chuckles!
[RILL]
What?
I bet you were babied
a lot growing up,
but I'm not gonna
do that, got it?
Time to start acting
like a squad captain.
[RILL] I don't get it.
He was laughing a second ago.
And you!
Would you quit sleepin'
all the damn time?
Oh, okay, what is this?
Yo--okay, you're talking
with your snores?
Well, I have no idea
what you're saying! Gah!
And where the hell is Julius?
He's the one who called this
meeting in the first place!
Don't tell me he forgot
about dragging us all
down here today and went
runnin' off somewhere.
[CAPTAINS]
It could happen.
Thank you for waiting
patiently, everyone.
The preparations are
complete, however,
the captains' meeting will
be taking place elsewhere.
Get your ass over
here, Mushroomhead!
[MARX]
He is really mad!
So this is where
they stashed ya.
You doin' okay?
Yes, sir.
I'm doing fine, thank you
so much for asking.
Does he need to take
a dump or somethin'?
Excuse me, sir.
What is this about?
[CHARLOTTE] Those two.
They're from the Midnight Sun.
Have you learned
something from them?
Oh, yes, all kinds of things.
Thanks to Marx and Asta,
they've become very talkative.
But the juiciest tidbit
is probably this:
It seems...
One of you has been working with
the Eye of the Midnight Sun
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[MARX]
"Memory Exchange Magic."
Go, Mémoire Absolue!
Uh...
All right, I'm going to ask
you some questions now.
Answer them honestly.
Yes, sir.
If you had to be
either the Wizard King
or a magic geek, then which
of them would you choose?
Magic geek for sure.
I knew it! Okay then.
Next question: what do
you think about me?
Well, you can be
a henpecking nag
some of the time,
but you're a hard worker,
and I'm always grateful for you.
[gasps]
Do you mean that?
Of course I do.
You're why I can rush through
my Wizard King duties
and focus on being a magic geek.
[yelps, groans]
[ASTA] There's a traitor
in this dungeon?
But the Magic Knights
are supposed to be people
everyone in the
Clover Kingdom can trust.
Whoever you are, I'm
gonna teach you a lesson!
Black Clover , Page 39:
"Three-Leaf Salute."
I'll never forgive the traitor!