[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed
lost until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] Vetto infiltrated
the Underwater Temple,
seeking the magic stone
that would help
the Eye of the Midnight Sun
destroy the Clover Kingdom.
One by one,
Asta and his comrades
fell victim to Vetto's
overwhelming power.
--[VETTO grunts]
--[KIATO groans]
--[screams]
--[VETTO] Don't speak such
words to me, girl!
Kahono!
Put her down! Do it right now!
[NARRATOR]
However, Noelle faced Vetto
and confronted him with
everything she had
in order to protect
her companions.
[NOELLE] I am Noelle Silva
of the Black Bulls,
and I'm done standing
by and watching
while you hurt my
friends and squadmates!
Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Roar!
[yells]
[VETTO yells]
My arm!
[panting]
How's that?
[NARRATOR] At the time, it
appeared that Noelle's attack
had defeated Vetto,
but, regrettably,
the battle was far
from being concluded.
[gasps]
You have my gratitude
for summoning me, human.
[NOELLE]
Where'd that eye come from?
Mythical Beast Magic:
Noita Nejair!
[VETTO growls]
[VETTO yells]
[NOELLE]
His arm... grew back?
[rumbling]
What now?
[SEKKE] Ha, ha! I'll send
for assistance at once!
You two do everything you
can to help the injured.
[SEKKE]
What's this?
I'm sensing a dreadful
mana emanating
from somewhere deep
in the ocean.
Could that beast have returned?
[SEKKE]
Ha, ha?
That power couldn't
come from a mere beast.
He's something even
stronger now--a monster!
[VANESSA]
What? This can't be good.
I've never felt mana
so threatening before.
Curious about Vetto's power?
It's incredible.
You must be confident,
to let that divert you.
Huh? Vetto?
[VANESSA] That's right,
the captain mentioned him.
One of the Third Eye,
the mightiest
in the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
To think he's the one who
invaded this place.
[TEUKE] Contemplating
your fate, my dear?
Yes, you are destined
to wither away
right where you stand.
Now, I'll suck out your
delicious magic power!
And I'll enjoy
every second of it.
I hate to disappoint you.
But you're done.
My friends are counting
on me to join them.
[TEUKE cackles]
[NOELLE] He seems...
different. More evil.
He's like something
out of the fairy tales
Granny used to tell me
when I was a little girl.
[NOELLE'S GRANDMOTHER]
Once upon a time, long ago,
a clan of malicious fiends lived
here and haunted our world.
They wanted everything in it,
especially the magic,
to be theirs, and they would do
anything in their
power to get it.
The most formidable
of the fiends
turned into a demon. And,
wielding dark, forbidden spells,
he attempted to obliterate all
of humankind with his magic.
The one man who stood up
to fight this wickedness
went on to become our
very first Wizard King.
[NOELLE] This creature's
like them, the greedy fiends
Grandmother told me
about in the story!
Now, begone!
Mythical Beast Magic:
Epohlla Puevig!
Sea Dragon's--
[gasps]
[NOELLE] That last spell
drained all my power!
[OCEAN DWELLERS
gasping, yelping]
[BOTH gasp]
[VETTO laughs]
[panting]
Asta! You saved me!
[laughs] That's our boy.
[ASTA]
Not yet.
It's not...
It's not over.
You haven't won!
We haven't given up,
and we're not going to!
You're right.
It isn't over yet.
The real despair starts now!
[VETTO laughs]
Wait! What are you doing?
There's no way out.
We're trapped.
I can't just leave them to die!
You should give up.
You'll never escape.
I told you, don't you recall?
No poor soul ensnared by my
Different Dimension
Sphere Spatial Magic
has ever managed to break free!
[ABARI laughs]
Listen up!
You better let us out of here
quick or you are dead, got me?
Well? Ya hear that?!
Answer, damn it!
Or what?
Please don't! I'm scared!
No! [chuckles]
What're you laughin' at?
You think it's funny that
I'll beat you to a pulp?
Bastard! It's too late
for an apology now!
I spit on your grave!
[GIFSO] Is he brave or
just completely insane?
[TEUKE laughs]
[grunts]
Mosquito Magic: Mosquito Hum!
[high-pitched static]
Don't you understand?
You're fighting a losing battle!
[VANESSA] This is the
most unbearable sound
I've ever heard!
[TEUKE] Oh, no, are you
having a hard time?
Poor thing.
My hum seems to be
distressing you!
My Mosquito Magic: Mana Sucker!
You can't keep dodging
my attacks forever!
[TEUKE]
All Magic Knights must perish!
So that we, the Eye
of the Midnight Sun,
may see our deepest
desire fulfilled! [laughs]
Aw, done being chased? Perfect.
What's this? Why have
I lost control of my arm?
Sure it's just the one arm?
How about your other limbs?
[TEUKE whimpers]
[TEUKE] What have you
done to me, woman?!
[VANESSA] You did a great
deal of it yourself
by getting so close.
From farther away, the
ultrasonic waves would
simply have snapped
all my threads.
It's like I said.
I knew I'd defeat you.
My friends are
counting on me. 'Bye.
She beat me?
Thread Magic: My Dancing Doll!
[yelps]
[TEUKE]
My body is moving on its own!
I can't control it! Villainess!
Now you can suck out all
the magic power you want!
Yours, that is, Little Mosquito.
[TEUKE]
I can feel it.
My magic... draining... out.
Well, that was intense.
I depleted quite a bit
of my mana fighting him.
Time to replenish and head out.
Ah. There we go.
[VANESSA]
Hold tight.
[VETTO laughs]
Back for more, anti-magic brat?
I see you can stand,
but it will do you no good.
What use is a body in tatters
in the face of my true form?
I'll relish your destruction.
The mana whispers.
It urges me to plunge
you two insects
into the depths of pain
and utter despair!
[panting]
How can you even stand up
when you're so gravely injured?
[ASTA]
It was Kahono.
She used the last of her
strength to heal me a little.
[gasps]
[ASTA]
I could barely hear her.
But it was enough.
I'm grateful.
[ASTA]
We have to take him down.
And then we'll find a way
to heal Kahono's throat,
and Kiato's leg, too!
[NOELLE]
What?
[ASTA]
He grew his arm back, didn't he?
Someone else has gotta know
that kind of magic, surely!
Hey, that reminds me.
That insane spell you
pulled off before--
it totally psyched me up!
Uh--
Heh. I always knew
you could do it.
You're just as amazing
as I thought you were.
Guess it's my turn now.
Asta...
[FINRAL] Nope, nope, nope, nope,
nope, nope, nope, nope!
What the heck are you thinking?
[FINRAL] Nope, nope, nope, nope,
nope, nope, nope, nope!
What the heck are you thinking?
"Guess it's my turn now"?
You're totally insane!
Just what exactly do
you plan to do here?
Have you not noticed you're
battling an actual monster?
I'll introduce you.
These three are the strongest
members of the Midnight Sun.
They're the strongest?
[LICHT] Indeed. Their power
surpasses my own,
especially when
it comes to battle.
They are the Third Eye.
And they're more
powerful than you?
So, Third Eye, huh?
[FINRAL]
Stronger than a Light mage?
He's got to be bluffing
about that, right?
[FINRAL]
But he wasn't bluffing at all.
This guy's got more power
pouring off him then Licht,
the leader of the Midnight Sun!
I doubt our whole group
would stand a chance now,
even working together!
He's taken everyone
down, one by one.
Swatted them all like
they were flies.
That's it. I'm getting out,
before it's too late.
[FINRAL groans]
[FINRAL]
I can't save them.
Might as well save myself.
If I don't escape,
we'll be wiped out for sure.
[VETTO] You're nothing--
just a pitiful urchin.
What could you ever hope
to achieve in this fight?
[ASTA]
Shut your mouth!
Don't get even cockier because
you grew an ugly third eye!
[FINRAL] Nope, nope, nope, nope,
nope, nope, nope, nope--
he's not being cocky,
he's just honest!
This guy has unbelievable
levels of magic power!
You're never gonna win this one!
You should escape while you
can! Don't think, just go!
[ASTA] What you said before,
about how my biggest
weakness is not knowing
when to give up.
[ASTA]
That's no weakness.
The way I see it, not giving up
is the strongest
weapon I've got!
And there's no way
I'm gonna quit before
my wish comes true,
do you understand me?
Not ever!
[VETTO cackles]
[VETTO] You would call your
death wish a weapon?
You'll soon find out how
useless it is against me.
I'll teach you
a valuable lesson.
Ignorant whelp.
You've never known despair like
what I am about to show you.
But before I delight
more in your pain,
I think I'll clean up some of
the trash lying around here.
You can't!
Mythical Beast Magic.
Stop! No!
[VETTO]
Llewerafs Revolc!
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
[VANESSA]
Oh, dear.
Could this furry fellow
be the notorious Vetto
the captain has
told us all about?
It seems highly likely.
But you're much more
brutish and uglier
than I imagined.
Not really my type, sorry.
--[NOELLE] Vanessa!
--[ASTA] Vanessa, yay!
[VANESSA]
You know, I would've been
way better off getting
dead drunk today.
And as for you,
over there, kiddo.
You're even more
reckless than I thought.
And yet...
I'm here now solely
because of your refusal
to give up the fight.
Time for me to hitch a ride
on this train of yours,
don'tcha think?
Great timing!
[VANESSA] I finally
understand why everyone
in the Black Bulls
had their eyes on you.
Makes perfect sense.
Isn't that right, Captain?
[YAMI]
It's the damn truth, kid.
Just like Vanessa said.
You refused to give up,
and because of that...
Noelle, Gauche,
Magna, and Luck...
They all managed to push
past their own limits.
For that matter, so did I.
[VETTO] Hm. You think that being
persistent is enough to win?
Pitiful.
[VETTO] As if these cobwebs
could restrain me! Please.
You can't trap a Mythical Beast!
What fun would it be if you
actually stayed tied up?
[VETTO]
Keep talking.
Your confidence will
disappear quickly enough.
You're just one more
insect for me to destroy!
Mythical Beast Magic:
Epohlla Puevig!
[ASTA]
I'm too late!
It appears there was one
more mouse on the loose.
[FINRAL]
Aw, hey, wouldja look at that?
You guys sure are
on fire today, huh?
Finral, you're here!
Oh, my!
[FINRAL] Our juniors are
giving it all they've got.
Time for us to show off
our most advanced stuff.
[FINRAL]
No! What now? I'm toast!
What am I even
doing here? I'll die!
How nice of you to finally
show up, Finral,
you old incompetent so-and-so!
Hey! Who are you
calling incompetent?
Of course I'd show up, what do
you think I am, a coward?
[FINRAL]
Don't give up! Don't give up!
[VETTO chuckles]
These little mice.
No, they're not even worth that!
More like a swarm
of pitiful ants. Ha.
They can't even hope to
inflict the tiniest scratch
upon the likes of me.
Right, Noelle.
Do you still have enough
magic to protect everyone?
Uh. Yeah!
[VANESSA]
Then I'll leave you to it.
My goodness.
That's a stunning amount
of magic. Daunting.
[laughs nervously]
You're right about that.
You can't see it,
though, can you?
Well, no, I can't
actually see it.
But, I can definitely
feel his ki.
[VANESSA] You sustain one
direct hit from this guy,
and that's it. You're
down for the count.
[FINRAL whines]
We're starting this fight
with our backs to the wall!
I'm not saying that
I'm gonna cry, but...
I just might!
If you help us win this,
I'll give you a nice, long hug.
A hug?
[VANESSA]
Oh, you heard me.
I'll let you cry into
my bosom all you want.
Now you're talkin'!
[grunting]
[ASTA] Finral's ki just
went through the roof--
that's amazing!
Men are so predictable.
They're easy as pie to control.
Now, listen, Asta.
The usual magic attacks
aren't gonna do any good
against this guy.
It's going to be up to you
and your anti-magic.
Whatever happens, do not
let go of that sword.
[ASTA]
Ma'am!
All right, boys,
our lives depend on this.
You bet. Let's beat him!
We're not about to
let you die, Asta.
We'll be fighting beside you!
[VETTO laughs]
[NOELLE]
Good luck, all of you!
Mythical Beast Magic.
[ALL]
Let's do this!
[VETTO]
Epohlla Puevig!
[yells]
[ASTA yells]
[VETTO] I assumed the anti-magic
blade would slice through
my long-range attacks,
but the Spatial mage
is sending them
right back at me.
Springing quickly into action
with remarkable accuracy.
Not bad for mere humans.
[FINRAL]
I'm so scared!
But I have no choice!
I have to fight!
[VETTO]
In that case,
I'll have to take you
on at close range!
[yelling]
[laughs]
[VETTO]
Nice try, brat!
[VETTO] But the Spatial
spell's power and your aura
give away your every move!
[VETTO]
What?
The thread's trajectory shifted.
You insects and your
useless scurrying about!
[yelling]
[yells]
[ASTA]
This is my weapon.
Now watch. I will defeat you!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[FINRAL]
"Bonus Magic."
Ooh, what is that?
It sounds awesome!
Well, like the name implies,
it's magic that gives
you a little extra.
Now whaddaya say
I give it a whirl?
Yes, please!
That furry beast-guy
Vetto has gotten
more than his fair share of
screen time, if you ask me,
so how about a little
change of pace?
[FINRAL]
Okay, here goes.
[ASTA]
So, this is bonus magic...
Oh, hey, I wonder
how Mimosa's doing?
[FINRAL]
Woo-hoo! It worked perfectly!
Oh, man, curves in
all the right places,
you know what I'm sayin'?
You guys are the Babes of...
What the heck is going
on here, Dorksta?
You stupid jerk, How could you?!
--What are you even thinking?
--[ASTA] It was him!
[VANESSA] We're joining
forces to defeat Vetto!
Finral and I give Asta
a helping hand.
I think you can do it, kiddo.
No, I know you can!
Black Clover , Page 48:
"Despair vs. Hope."
Our magic is never giving up!