[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
So you finally made it here.
Once you do, you've got
the nerve to attack our guys.
I'm gonna need an
explanation for that.
[NARRATOR] Yami was under
attack by two elves
who had possessed the
bodies of Marx and Owen.
[MARX]
Memory Magic:
Torment Canceller attack!
[YAMI] Dark Cloaked,
Lightless Blunt Slash!
[NARRATOR] He'd just managed
to fend them off...
[YAMI]
What? Red roses?
[NARRATOR] ...when a
mysterious and powerful elf
resembling Charlotte Roselei
appeared on the scene.
I don't know you at all.
You seem capable for a human.
[CITIZENS screaming]
[SOL]
There.
It should be safe now.
That Black Bull. He acted
like it was important.
What did he say was inside?
[yelling]
--[CHARLOTTE] Briar Magic:
--[YAMI] Dark Magic:
[YAMI]
Dark Cloaked, Dimension Slash!
[CHARLOTTE]
Crimson Vine Spear!
[gasps]
Oh, no!
[CHARLOTTE] We cast our
spells at the same time.
Mine was clearly the
more devastating one,
yet his attack split it
in two, which slowed down
its momentum and
prevented the town
from being completely
decimated by the impact.
Even if it just hit my gauntlet,
his spell had enough
force left to reach me.
Despite the difference
in our might,
he was able to turn the tide
of battle in his favor.
How could a lowly human
have achieved this
level of mastery?
Though I suppose he
must be exceptional,
if he beat those two.
It seems I
underestimated humankind.
[CHARLOTTE] I used more magic
than planned, so I'll retreat.
It's best to wait for
Licht and the others
to arrive so that I can
ensure their safety.
Char!
What about the captain
of the Black Bulls?
What the--?
No. Did Char crush
him? She wouldn't!
Don't run away from me, woman!
I've still got a bone to
pick with you, you hear?
I coulda died from a stunt
like that! Where is she?
You're alive.
Uh, I mean, whatever,
I guess that's a good thing.
[YAMI] As soon as I snap
you outta this little
mean streak of yours,
I'm gonna make you
pay big for that!
You're not gettin' off the hook!
Oh. It's Tomboy.
What did you just call me?
[YAMI]
Why are you still here?
What about the thing I gave ya?
[SOL]
I hid it in a safe place.
[YAMI]
Oh, that's real reassuring.
You know, I'm
trusting you, right?
Well, back atcha!
I trusted you to save Char!
Who do you think I am?
[SOL] I can't help her
the way I am now.
Look, I trust you!
Wouldn't care if you didn't.
So, what's the next step?
I'm tryin' to figure
that out. All right?
I got it! You go take
care of the townspeople!
I'm sure there's more
Magic Knights here.
Find 'em and help
everyone you can!
Right!
As for my part, well...
[GUELDRE]
What happened here?
I haven't a clue what
the commotion is outside,
but I am detecting a colossal
amount of magic power,
apparently enough to destroy
the seal on this prison.
Whatever the cause may be,
it looks like today
is my lucky day.
Now I'll finally
be able to escape!
[footsteps]
Well, of all the degenerates
I could've run into down here!
Hello, Captain Gueldre.
I'm sorry. Ex-captain.
Believe me, I'm just as
surprised as you are.
I thought for certain I had seen
the last of Chain Magic Revchi.
How long has it been?
[REVCHI chuckles]
Unfortunately, I'm
in quite a hurry,
so we'll have to reserve the
reminiscing for another time.
That might be more
convenient for you,
but I'm afraid it simply
isn't going to work for me.
As you may recall, sir,
two years ago, you sent
me on the assignment
that left me with
this unsightly scar.
And after the mission
resulted in failure,
you placed the blame on me,
and my status as a member
of the Purple Orcas
was permanently revoked.
Oh, is that it?
It serves you right
that you were banished.
I believe your
squadmates weren't
terribly fond of you, anyway.
Not a single one of them was
willing to take your side,
if I remember correctly.
Isn't that rich.
It seems like you aren't
very popular, either.
Why else would the previous
captain of the Purple Orcas
have been locked away
to rot down here
in this underground prison?
You have no right to judge
the behavior of a captain,
seeing as how you were
always perfectly content
to let everyone around
you move up in rank
while you consistently
dodged any mission
that appeared to be
even remotely dangerous.
[REVCHI] You shouldn't
accuse me of dodging
when your Transparency Magic
is nothing but dodging.
[GUELDRE] It's far better than
your cowardly Chain Magic,
sealing the power
of any mage you meet
so that you don't have to fight.
[BOTH] If it weren't for
that impudent little upstart
and his Anti-magic abilities,
there wouldn't be anyone
in Clover Kingdom who
could stand in my way!
What, you, too?
It seems we feel the same.
[BOTH grunt]
[rumbling]
[REVCHI]
His magic power's enormous.
I can tell that without
using my chains!
There are humans here, as well.
[REVCHI] Is he one of the
people destroying the city?
[GUELDRE]
The Eye of the Midnight Sun
is behind all this chaos?
If so, it seems I may have
gotten myself involved
with a rather
deadly organization.
We've been instructed
to massacre
any humans we see. All of you!
Wait! I assure you,
I am not your enemy!
In fact, I may even be
able to aid your endeavor!
Please, let me speak
with your leader!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 97A]
We refuse to be fooled
by you wicked humans again.
You all die. Everyone,
no matter who you are!
Oh? We all die?
I suppose we have no
other choice then, Revchi.
It kills me to say this,
but you're right.
If he's threatening our lives,
there's only one thing to do.
[GUELDRE] Transparency
Magic: Invisible Seeker
plus Invisible
Traveling Companion.
They're gone!
And their magic power
disappeared with them?
In that case. I'll tear
apart this whole area!
[gasps]
[REVCHI]
Chain Creation Magic:
Magic-Binding Iron
Chain Formation!
[MAGIC KNIGHT 97A] Did he just
seal away my magic power?
Impossible, my strength
is far superior to theirs!
What kind of
techniques are those?
Now that he's taken care of,
we should be home free!
Finally, these poor eyes of mine
will see the light
of day once more!
Indeed.
I knew it wasn't my
fate to die in here.
Revchi, let us make haste
to clear our sullied names,
once and for all.
Excellent idea!
You guys, what's wrong?
It's just like with
Vetto and the others.
It feels so evil.
Why's that kind of magic
power coming from you?
[giggles]
Why's that kind of magic
power coming from you?
[KIRSCH]
Noelle's right.
There's something terribly
malicious at play here.
Much like that
House Vaude fellow.
An ominous aura, indeed!
[BEN]
Finally, we've made it back.
Let me kill them.
[BEN chuckles] You're energetic,
considering you just awakened.
Yeah, that's why I'm so pumped.
Extra-pumped, actually.
Oh, dear.
[LUCK]
This thing is in the way.
Luck. I don't get it.
What are you...?
[NOELLE gasps]
Eh. I was hoping they'd
be a challenge, but...
They are humans.
[NOELLE gasps]
I missed ya! Looks like
I've gotten a little rusty.
[BEN chuckles]
Let's try again.
[KIRSCH]
Cherry Blossom Magic:
Raging Magic Cherry
Blossom Storm of Petals!
I don't know what caused
this change in them,
but they certainly aren't
the people they were before.
You should prepare yourself
to fight beautifully, Noelle!
But... it's Luck.
He's a member of
the Black Bulls.
He's my friend!
Noelle!
[LUCK]
Hm... I can't see.
Which means there's no
point in trying to aim.
That's okay.
I'll try plan B.
His strength is growing.
Use a defensive spell!
Why, Luck? Stop this!
We're friends!
Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Lair!
[laughing]
[gasps]
[yells]
Brainwashing?
No, even the essence of
their power's changed!
[NOELLE] Luck's fighting on
a totally different level now!
[LUCK] Your spells have
a certain feel to them.
Let me guess, you're royalty?
You don't--?
What if we said yes?
Would you treat my lovely
self differently then?
I knew it.
This fight is getting
better by the second!
Is this guy pullin'
my leg or what?
[ZORA] He was overpowered
from the beginning,
but now it feels like he's
about to blow the roof off!
Like I said, deception
is kinda my thing.
And since I'm a liar,
I can tell when other
people are lying, too.
Look, Mr. Anti-magic.
What you said a
little while ago.
I just want a kingdom
where all of us
get along and laugh together.
And when I'm the Wizard
King, we'll have one.
You'll see!
[RHYA]
I know you meant every word.
Too bad, really.
For a split second,
I was actually moved.
[RHYA]
Just like the last time.
Let's foster understanding.
[RHYA] There were no lies
in anything that he said,
and so I trusted him.
And what did it get me? That.
[RHYA] So, you see,
I'm done with trusting.
And to make sure
you know I mean it,
I'll kill you!
[RHYA] Copy Light Magic:
Light Swords of Conviction.
Copy Dark Magic:
Lightless Slash!
[ASTA] Two different
techniques at the same time?
[MEREOLEONA]
Mana Zone: Calidos Brachium.
Barrage spell!
Do you see what I'm saying now?
To them, there is
no getting along,
no matter how badly you want it!
[MEREOLEONA] They're determined
to kill every one of us
and wipe out all
of Clover Kingdom!
Maybe they are.
But I'll still win!
And I'll make a way
for us to get along!
The road to mutual
understanding's closed, pal.
I don't care!
I'll open it back up!
Fine, fine. You can try.
But you'd better make it quick.
Otherwise, I'll kill him myself.
Right!
Now, Calidos Brachium!
[RHYA] If she manages to hit
me with that move of hers,
there's no way I'm gonna
make it out of this
place with my life.
I better be on my toes!
[MEREOLEONA] A combination
of Spatial and Light Magic.
[ZORA] He's usin' a Light spell
to make himself more agile.
[RHYA] Valty's Spatial Magic
is the perfect thing
to keep her from hitting
me with that attack.
It's sad the ol' codger's
not around anymore,
but at least I got
something good out of him.
[RHYA] Copy Spatial Magic:
Myriad Black!
Copy Light Magic:
Sky-Rending Flash!
You can't dodge forever!
Seriously, this jerk
is untouchable!
[rumbling]
Heh.
[gasps]
Rill? Is that you?
Hey, Rhya, good to see ya!
I'm so happy that you're awake!
[laughs]
Hey! Lira!
You're just as hyperactive
as I remember!
Why wouldn't I be?
And you've still got that goofy,
spaced-out look on your face!
[RHYA]
Can it, kid.
[RILL giggles]
[RILL]
Aw, Rhya, I missed you so much!
Would ya stop bein'
a little pain already?
I'm just really happy!
Well, go be happy over there!
Hey! Rill, why are you
huggin' that monster?
[RILL] You know what?
My ability has a fancy name now!
Picture Magic!
[RHYA]
Nice!
[ASTA] You do know he's tryin'
to murder us all, right?
Or did you forget?
Say what? I'm confused.
You are?! We were in
the middle of a fight,
and suddenly you bust in
and you guys are
all buddy-buddy!
Do I know you?
[gasps] What the--? Rill!
Who's Rill? Didn't you
hear? My name's Lira.
Huh? What's goin' on?
[ZORA]
The captain of the Aqua Deer.
His magic power's gone
from crazy to ludicrous,
just like Mr. Copycat
over there.
That Spatial mage
from the Golden Dawn.
His felt the same way.
Was that an omen?
[MEREOLEONA]
Whatever this is,
it must've boosted
their strength.
I can tell from the
change in their auras
that it's not brainwashing.
That little one
doesn't recognize
the rookie at all anymore.
Are they being possessed
by other people?
It's me, your old friend Asta!
You and I are both
Magic Knights, remember?
How could you possibly forget
about a big loudmouth like me?
[yells]
Yeah. You're loud
and super annoying.
And there's no way I would ever
have a human as a friend.
[gasps]
[RILL]
I know how to shut you up.
Check out this Picture
Magic technique.
Four-Headed Lindworm.
You're no match for me!
[ASTA yells]
He's obviously bein' controlled
by some enemy spell.
You should try smackin' him
with your Anti-magic sword!
Right. I'm on it.
Sorry, guys.
You can throw whatever
you want at us,
but it's never
gonna reach us now!
[ZORA]
We'll see about that.
You think I've
been standing here
twiddling my thumbs
this whole time?
[ZORA]
Ash Trap Magic, activate!
Oh, I see, you were
settin' somethin' up
for us, too, huh? Big deal.
A paralyzing trap isn't
gonna help ya much.
Agh! Can't see!
But we're good at picking up
on other people's power,
so I'm sure we can
still wipe the floor
with you guys either way!
Let's see if you feel
that way after this one
gets through with ya.
He's a magicless monster!
[ASTA yells]
He's got Anti-magic coursing
through his whole body!
Hey, where are you?
Now snap out of it, Rill!
[ASTA]
Grazed him!
It's not much, but it should
be enough to break the--
[ASTA]
Huh?
That hurt me, ya know.
What's your problem?
[ASTA]
It's no good!
Man. I thought for
sure that would work.
[RHYA] Sorry, but thanks
to Reincarnation Magic,
we elves have been awakened
in these human forms.
Isn't that somethin'.
Whether you
understand it or not,
the soul-transferring
process is complete,
which means that these
bodies belong to us now.
[ASTA]
Reincarnation? Elves?
Quit messin' around!
Bring Rill ba--
All of them, too?
[ZORA]
This is bad.
Every one of 'em's givin' off
crazy amounts of power!
We won't last five
minutes against them!
Time to go. Come on!
You wanna run? Really?
We can't just leave them!
No way! Not yet!
Moron.
There's nothin' we can do
to save them right now.
That's why we should retreat
and come up with a plan!
Bird-brained shorty.
Yeah. You're right.
You and your dumb cool mask!
What's the alternative?
I know you, and you can't
kill your buddies.
[RHYA]
Neither can you.
But you can't get away either,
so you two wimps
are out of options!
This is pitiful.
[BOTH gasp]
[ASTA yelps]
[ZORA yelps]
[BOTH yell]
[MEREOLEONA]
Run along home now. Children.
But, Captain--!
Ah. So you wanna stay
here and slow us down
so they can run back with
their tails between their legs.
You seem like a benevolent
leader, Madam Royal.
[MEREOLEONA] Fool. You don't
understand a thing, do you?
[RHYA]
Hm?
I sent those novices home
because they were
getting in my way.
Slow you down?
Don't make me laugh.
I wanted the chance
to obliterate all
of you personally!
[MEREOLEONA] Crimson Lion Kings,
let the fire of courage
set your hearts ablaze!
Never give up,
even when your back
is pressed against a wall!
Black Clover , Page 98:
"The Sleeping Lion."
How long will you slumber,
foolish brother?