[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy
who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
[NARRATOR]
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world,
and to become the
next Wizard King!
[mumbling] No.
I can never go home.
Damn, you're spooky.
The Prickly Princess brought
you up when we had dinner.
Your family's famous, right?
On account of the magic
curse they work with?
I need you to pick their brains
for info on forbidden curses.
[mumbling] You want me to ask
about forbidden curses?
Yeah.
It could help us
to clear Asta's name.
These are spells that warp
our world and ruin lives
through otherworldly power.
Specifically, power borrowed
from the world of devils.
We need to learn as much
about them as we possibly can.
[mumbling] If our
investigation into the devils
doesn't progress,
then Asta could be...
[GORDON]
I'll do it, Captain.
I'm expecting to fail,
but I'll try regardless.
For the sake of my best friend.
[GORDON] Most people are
wary of curse mages.
And I was born into a
distinguished family of them.
So I never had any friends.
And it's not like
I'm close to my family.
Back when Asta's arms
had been cursed
by a member of the Third Eye.
I wrote them asking
how to break the spell,
and they wouldn't say.
Still, things are different now.
I have my friends with me,
so I feel more confident.
[ASTA screaming] Both of
my arms're fallin' asleep!
But I'm not done yet, ya hear?
My muscles are screaming
in joy; they love the pain!
Nobody cares.
The only person who can
ride at my back is Marie.
So shut your mouth and hang on.
Wait, so we're
meeting new people?
I feel embarrassed already.
[GORDON]
My friends give me strength.
By the way, I want
you guys to know
how grateful I am that
you all agreed to do this.
What? Who says I "agreed"?
Noelle's makin' her way
to the royal capital,
and I'd say that you three
need a reason to wipe
the sleep from your eyes,
so go with your pal, Gordon.
I know I'm not gonna do it.
Refuse 'n I'll kill ya.
[GAUCHE]
Talk about an abuse of power.
So, Gordon, I hear that your
family's a pretty big deal,
like they're super famous
for their Curse Magic.
No offense, but I don't actually
know what a curse mage does.
Curse mages.
Well, they specialize
in suffering.
Their trade is the infliction of
pain and misfortune upon others.
I never wanted
any part of that.
I wanted to make
friends with people,
not to cast curses
on them. So...
I left that house behind me
and rarely looked back.
That's crazy. I had no idea.
You ran away from home?
Do you think they'll still
be willing to talk to you?
Oh, and how about some assurance
that we won't get cursed?
I could get cursed
by a total stranger?
How embarrassing.
It's the curse part you
should be worried about.
[GORDON]
It'll be okay. I think.
[ASTA, GREY, GAUCHE]
You think?
[GROUP]
I wanna go home.
Let's do this.
[GAUCHE] Their house
looks pretty haunted.
[GREY] Getting spied on by a
ghost would be so humiliating.
Damn it, Grey.
Get off me, will ya?
Now that I'm here,
I'm actually kind of excited
to see what your
family's like, Gordon.
[GORDON]
It's me. I'm home.
[ALL gasp]
[whispering] It's wonderful
to have you back, Gordon.
[muttering] Hello, Big Brother.
[muttering] Well, look at that.
You decided to come
home after all.
[NILENIA grunts]
[ASTA, GREY, GAUCHE]
They all look exactly the same!
Let me introduce you.
First, this is
my father, Nathan.
That's my mother, Jonna.
My grandmother, Nilenia.
My little sister, Roxanne.
And...
[ASTA screams]
We're under attack everyone!
[GORDON]
That's our dog, Nunnally.
[GAUCHE, GREY]
Even the dog looks like them.
[ALL]
No.
[JONNA]
She's mauling another guest.
--[GAUCHE] Whoa, back it up!
--[GREY] Please don't curse me.
Don't all of you come
over here at once.
I'm sorry. You okay?
Uh. Yeah.
Sorry about the
late introduction.
My name is Asta.
The girl with her
face covered is Grey,
and that's Gauche next to her.
We're all in the same
Magic Knight Squad.
They're the friends I mentioned
in the letter I sent.
[muttering] We weren't
expecting company tonight,
but since you came
all this way...
[mumbling] You and your friends
will just have
to stay for dinner.
[GAUCHE] Why do his
parents look the same?
They aren't related.
Or they shouldn't be.
Gordon. Your mother's cooking
must taste exquisite
after all this time.
The creepy-crawly snake eyes
are especially scrumptious.
Thanks, dear.
I recommend the paralyzed frog.
I want bread.
Anyone seen the bread?
[muttering] Look down, Grandma;
there's a whole
loaf in your hands.
Oh. So there is.
How'd it get off of the plate?
Say, where did the bread go?
It's in your mouth, Grandma.
There's something that
I wanted to ask you, Father.
[NATHAN]
You must be hungry for seconds.
No, it's something else.
[GREY] Everywhere I turn, it's
nothing but weird muttering.
I have no idea what
anyone's saying right now.
[GAUCHE]
The hell's going on here?
It's not easy to make me feel
awkward, but they found a way.
Hey, say something. Come on.
Ask them about forbidden curses.
[GREY]
Oh, I-I couldn't possibly.
Gordon's just shaking
while he stares at us.
Tell him to do it.
[grunting]
No. That's Gordon's grandmother.
Whoa, it wasn't
easy to get over
how gross this stuff looks,
but it's actually super tasty!
This is amazing!
[GAUCHE]
Of course.
Why wouldn't Asta be having fun?
Ah! Uh. Hello?
[mumbling] Please take this
as a token of my hope
that we'll become friends.
It's kinda hard to hear you,
but I guess you wanna
give me something?
[laughs]
[GREY screams]
What is this?!
[muttering] Oh, goodness,
is that actually you, Nathan?
My, just look at how
much you've grown.
You will protect the House of
Agrippa, won't you, my dear boy?
[GAUCHE]
This lady's lost it.
[JONNA]
There, there, Mother.
I think it's time we took
you to bed, all right?
[NILENIA] Yes, but tell
Nathan I'm counting on him.
For the sake of our ancestor
who made the contract,
the curse of Megicula must be--
[JONNA]
Right. Don't fret.
[ASTA]
Curse o' what?
[ALL gasp]
[ROXANNE]
Nice to meet you.
[NUNNALLY barks]
[GREY] Huh. It suddenly
got really quiet.
[laughs]
[GAUCHE]
Okay.
[ASTA]
Make your move, Gordon.
This is the perfect
chance to ask him!
Father? I need to talk to you.
I realize I basically
abandoned my family,
so I don't have much
right to ask. But still.
I have to ask, because I wanna
help my friend, no matter what.
It's about forbidden curses
and the devils behind them.
Can you tell us whatever
you know about them?
[NATHAN]
Sure.
[GREY, GAUCHE, ASTA, GORDON]
That was easy.
[mumbling] The Agrippa family
has practiced Curse Magic
and studied its enigmatic
secrets for centuries.
I'll show you the result.
In addition, I'll show
you the secret arts
that deal with poison,
plague, and death.
Are you and your
friends prepared?
[screams]
No way. The hell?
[laughs] Beautiful,
don't you agree?
This is the workshop where
I conduct all my research.
Along with curses, I study
every form of pain there is.
I knew that Curse
Magic was sinister,
but this is even worse
than I imagined.
My dear boy.
Rather than despair
that you were gone,
I've eagerly awaited
your inevitable return.
Thanks to your Poison Magic,
you are the perfect candidate
to inherit and
advance my research.
Sorry, Father,
but I only came here
to ask about devil-related
curses for Asta.
I have no intention of staying.
Don't be like that.
Death can be caused by poisons,
plagues, and curses.
If you stay, I can
teach you about
every cause of death there is.
[gasps] What is a
life worth to you?
Human life is both
fragile and brief.
Don't you understand me, son?
Perhaps I should demonstrate.
Black Oil Creation Magic:
Curse-Filled Nails.
Stay back!
[ASTA screams]
[ALL]
Asta!
Why do I feel fine?
Huh.
Your temperature's
in a normal range.
You seem healthy.
I'm not detecting a single
physical abnormality,
though it strikes me as odd
that you have no magic.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
[laughs] I'm working.
I took the family's vast
knowledge of curses,
combined it with my own
research on germs and poisons,
and applied that
knowledge to the subjects
of health management
and medical treatment.
That said, I am the first
to take the family business
in this new direction,
so I can only treat
normal ailments right now.
Hence why I had no help to offer
when I heard that your
limbs had been afflicted
with an ancient curse.
Say, is something the matter?
No, but, if you've been
using what you know
about poison and death
and horrible curses
to make medicine
and stuff like that,
then the Agrippa family
business isn't hurting people;
it's helping them get better.
That's right.
Has been ever since I took over.
I honestly had no idea.
All this time, I thought
you were cursing people
to die in agony.
You people need to
learn to communicate!
And you need to get rid
of all this creepy stuff!
This just goes to show,
you can't judge
a book by its cover!
So, Father, does this mean
that you really will
help me save my friend?
Why, of course I will.
But the subject of devils
and forbidden magic
is both varied and elusive,
so let's start by discussing
your specific situation.
Right!
[DOROTHY] Okay. There's
still work to be done,
but I've sent the largest chunks
of debris into my dreams.
[CITIZENS cheer]
She did it so quickly!
That's the captain of the
Coral Peacocks for ya!
Thank you, Captain Dorothy.
You're an inspiration!
[NOELLE]
I'm glad you're still awake.
Well, look at you.
If it isn't the youngest member
of the venerable House of Silva.
What can I help you with?
I hear that you can
tell me the truth.
Apparently it wasn't my
birth that killed my mother.
I came here to ask
you about what did.
I guess you must've
had a chat with Nozel.
Yeah.
We talked when we went to see
Solid and Nebra yesterday.
[NOELLE sighs]
Nozel.
Why would you say
something like that?
Of course our mother died
while giving birth to me;
everyone in our family knows it.
Everyone believing something
doesn't make it true.
The fact is, her
death was inevitable,
and it had nothing
to do with your birth.
[gasps]
[NOZEL] It wasn't injury
or illness either.
Lives shouldn't end
the way hers did.
Not in this world.
[NOELLE gasps] Then she
was killed by something
from a different world?
If what you're saying is true,
this could be related
to our investigation on devils--
I'll advise you
to stop right there.
Keep talking, and your life
will be in danger, too.
[gasps]
[NOZEL] If you still have
the courage to face the truth
despite being aware of the risk
it entails, then your next move
should be to seek out
Captain Dorothy Unsworth
of the Coral Peacocks
and ask her what she knows.
Please answer.
What was it that took
my mother from me
before I even got
a chance to know her?
I'll tell you.
I could never say no
to a cute girl in need.
[NOELLE]
Okay.
[DOROTHY] I'll leave the rest of
the cleanup to you guys, 'kay?
[MAGIC KNIGHTS]
Yes, Ma'am! Just leave it to us!
Not that there's
much left to do.
Yeah, the captain's amazing
when she's awake.
Listen. I don't know if
you're aware of this or not,
but if my mother's death
involved a devil--
[DOROTHY] Shh. Didn't Nozel
tell you to watch what you say?
It's dangerous. You can't
just speak of it carelessly.
Say too much, and
you'll be cursed.
That's the case in
this world, at least.
Huh?
[NOELLE screams]
Where am I?
[DOROTHY]
Welcome!
To my very own Dream Magic:
Glamour World!
You might've guessed
this from the name,
but it's a dream world,
completely isolated
from the normal world and
under my total control.
[DOROTHY]
Here! Have some tea!
Usually, I trap
bad people in here
for a smidge of light torture.
But also, on days like today,
I'll bring in rubble
from damaged buildings
and unfortunates
who've been injured.
[NOELLE] She was right
to call it glamour "world."
This place is enormous.
Is everything here really
under her control? Crazy.
Good tea.
[ASTA]
Noelle!
Hey.
Asta? Wait a minute,
how'd you end up here?
Eh, who cares about that?
What matters to me is
that you're lookin' good.
I beg your pardon?
Seriously, I could stare at
that cute face all day long!
This can't be real.
There's no way!
Correct.
The boy in front of you
is just an illusion
I created from
your thoughts.
Yeah! You think about me
all the time, Noelle!
Huh?! That's a lie, and
I'll kill anyone who argues!
[screams]
Why so violent?
You came here partially
for his sake, didn't you?
What? No way! That twerp's
a total non-factor!
I'm sure.
But just so you know,
this is the perfect place
to have secret conversations.
Wait a second.
Are you saying...?
[NOZEL] We can discuss
Mother safely here.
[NOELLE]
You made a fake Nozel, too?
The real Nozel is probably off
with his squad or something,
what do I care?
But I'm correct in
assuming it was him
who told you I had
the answers, right?
About the juicy little
secret that he's kept
from all of his siblings?
The truth is exactly
what you suspected.
Acier Silva lost her life
to a devil's curse.
[NOELLE]
So, why didn't Nozel say?
Why'd he let me think that
her death was my fault?
Because anyone who
speaks of Acier's fate
will share it with her.
That's the cruel nature of the
curse that befell your mother,
and within the real world,
there's no way around it.
But my dreamscape is a
unique plane of existence,
so you don't have to
worry about that here.
You can discuss the
curse all you want
without bringing it into effect.
You can finally
speak your minds.
I'm sorry that it took me
so long to tell you, Noelle.
I was afraid of putting you
in danger, so I held back.
Aw. You're so cute.
What'd you just say?
Noelle. Noelle. My sweet Noelle!
You're the cutest little
sister in the world.
And your big brother loves
you more than anything!
I love you so much, I don't
know what to do with myself.
--[NOELLE screams]
--Noelle. Noelle. Noelle!
[gasps] I'm sorry, Nozel.
Hey, Dorothy, quit making
my fake brother act weird!
Aw. Sorry about that,
but from my perspective,
that's just the way he is.
[NOZEL]
Why did I feel a sudden chill?
Well, seeing as you've
just sent your brother
flying off into the void,
I'll tell you the rest.
The devils of the other world
can't manifest in ours,
unless there's been some
kind of anomaly, that is.
Mages can use forbidden magic
to form contracts with devils,
paying some price to use
their powers in a limited way,
but that's it.
Or rather, that ought to be it.
But as we speak,
a devil's shadow
is slinking about in our world.
The shadow's owner
is called Megicula.
[NOELLE] Megicula.
That's the name of the devil
who killed my mother,
and the key to saving Asta!
[NATHAN] I'm sorry to
keep you all waiting.
After hearing about
your situation yesterday,
I did some digging.
I understand what you need,
and I think I have just
the spell to help you.
This should be fairly simple.
My ancestors collected curses,
so their magic is basically
designed to find them.
Black Oil Creation Magic:
Curse Candle Ritual Disk.
[gasps]
[GREY]
Whoa, it's a map.
[GAUCHE]
Of the whole Clover Kingdom.
So cool!
[NATHAN]
Each flame marks a curse,
with the flame's size indicating
the curse's strength.
This is a map of the sickness
eroding our kingdom.
Look at that one;
it's enormous. So fierce.
Wait. Isn't that flame
at the Black Bull's hideout?
It is.
So does that mean one of the
Black Bulls has been cursed?
Is there anybody in our squad
who seems a little off?
Uh. Let's see. Well...
Luck is almost supernaturally
obsessed with fighting,
but Finral's just about
equally obsessed with girls,
and if ya told me that
Vanessa's drinking was a curse,
I don't think I'd argue.
The captain takes a long
time in the bathroom.
So basically...
[GORDON, GAUCHE, GREY]
They're all kinda cursed.
Hang on a second,
what sorta evil curse
makes ya take longer
to use the bathroom?
And before ya go judgin'
the rest of the bulls,
look at yourselves!
You're all unique in
your own weird way!
Hey. Don't call me unique;
it's embarrassing.
[screams]
I feel like I'm normal.
Forget us.
You're the biggest weirdo here,
ya magic-less meathead!
[ASTA screams]
Oh. Hey, speakin' of magic...
Maybe Henry's the reason
there's a fire on our base.
[GAUCHE]
Could be.
That would explain his condition
that sucks away
everyone else's mana.
[GORDON]
Oh, yeah, he's cursed.
[GREY]
Very cursed.
There's a roaring flame
in the royal capital, as well.
This map can't
tell us who's cursed,
but it does show us the
scale of the problem.
I see quite a few small flames.
Is there a way for us
to see a bigger area?
It will be less accurate
at a distance, but yes.
Look there.
That's in the Heart Kingdom.
It's a lot bigger than
the one coming from our base.
[ASTA]
Huh. Maybe there's a clue
about the devils there.
[GORDON]
You're my dad, Nathan.
And you showed us where
to look for the devils!
Thanks Dad-Who's-Also-Nathan!
You made my friends
really happy!
Black Clover , Page 128:
"To the Heart Kingdom!"
Wait, I'm staying home?