[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed
lost until a lone mage
stepped forward
and took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[ASTA] Yuno. You and me,
we're family, right?
[YUNO]
Yeah, of course.
[ASTA] Not by blood
or anything, though.
[YUNO]
Right.
But we're closer
than a lot of people
who are related
by blood, aren't we?
I guess so. Why, what's up?
[ASTA]
I was thinking.
You and me, we don't
have any real relatives,
but we've got a lot
of great friends.
What I think is we
should take the friends
we have now, and the
ones we'll meet later,
and make them our family.
Yeah!
We're almost there now.
It should be just
through this hallway.
[MIMOSA gasps]
Isn't that simply marvelous?
[KLAUS]
Hmph. Some dungeon that was.
Not much to it at all.
So, what's your plan
for getting past this?
It doesn't appear
as if the Black Bulls
have managed to find it yet.
Of course they haven't.
Despite their bluster,
they never stood a chance
of beating us here.
[MIMOSA]
You're probably right.
[KLAUS, YUNO gasp]
[KLAUS]
Mimosa!
Such a keen mana sense,
but she never saw it coming!
This is no trap magic.
So, what is it?
Who goes there?
[MARS]
You're in my way.
Now move.
[LOTUS]
See, what you really need
are friends you know
you can count on.
Well, I sorry about this,
but I've got things to do.
You know how it is.
[panting]
[LUCK'S MOTHER]
Win.
Keep on winning, Luck.
Hold on.
It's been too long...
...since things've gotten
this interesting.
Oh, yeah! Let's do this.
Time to fight!
So much potential.
I'm almost sorry
to extinguish it.
--[LUCK'S MOTHER] Luck!
--[blow lands]
[LUCK'S MOTHER] Why can't you
just do what I ask?
How many times do I
have to tell you?
Stop smiling like that!
Get mad, cry.
Do something normal.
Why were you born
a defective freak?
[BOY 16A]
Whoa!
[BOY 16B]
No way!
[whimpering]
[NOBLE 16A whimpering]
[BOYS murmuring]
[TEACHER 16A]
I can't believe this!
An ordinary citizen
defeated a noble?
[TEACHER 16B] It's never
happened in all the time
our school's held
this tournament.
[BOY 16A] Regular people
don't win against nobles.
[BOY 16B]
Oh, man.
I've been giving that
kid a hard time, too.
What if he decides
to get me back?
[BOY 16C] It's so creepy
the way he smiles all the time.
[BOY 16A] Don't go near that
guy unless you want a beating.
[BOY 16D]
What a freak.
You actually beat a noble
using your magic?
Oh, Luck! That's fantastic!
Who knew you would turn
out to be so powerful?
Most people like us
don't stand a chance
against the nobles, but
obviously, you're special.
And you'll win again, won't you?
Use that power of yours to win
and win and keep on winning.
In this world, nobody's
going to help you.
You have to help yourself.
[LUCK'S MOTHER]
Use the power only you possess.
[LUCK] I'll do it, Mom.
If it'll make you happy.
[LUCK'S MOTHER]
Win.
[LUCK]
Hah!
Interesting boy.
In spite of my magic, he's only
gotten faster and sharper.
[LUCK'S MOTHER]
Win.
I'm going to keep on winning.
[LUCK]
That's what my power is for!
Terribly sorry.
I'm afraid that I can't
afford to lose, either.
[LOTUS] Smoke Creation Magic:
Binding Cross Prison.
[LUCK] This smoke is solid.
I can't move.
Oh, dear.
That particular spell
uses so much magic power--
I'd hoped I would be able
to avoid casting it.
I'm downright exhausted now.
But at least you won't
be hopping around
anymore, youngster.
You're dealt with,
and now it's time to see how
my own youngster is faring.
Ow, ow, ow.
Honestly, I have such
difficulty getting
through to him sometimes.
Maybe it's the generation gap?
[MIMOSA]
Plant Recovery Magic...
Dream-Healing Flower Cradle.
I am so sorry, sir.
I should've sensed something.
I'm the group's healer.
What use will I be to you now?
Don't worry about that, Mimosa.
You only need to focus
on your own recovery.
[KLAUS]
That insignia.
Is he a mage from the
wretched Diamond Kingdom?
[KLAUS] You there!
Attacking from behind?
What kind of warrior
would do such a thing?
I don't understand
what you're asking.
Who are you?
You are merely pebbles destined
to fall by the wayside.
Let's go, Yuno. Back me up!
Right!
When we get done
with this barbarian,
he won't soon forget the power
of Clover Kingdom's Golden Dawn.
Now we're talkin'!
No hidden trap spells
along this path.
[gasps]
[NOELLE] The mana just
keeps getting thicker.
[NOELLE] Is that really
the treasure hall up ahead?
[grunts]
What's up?
All this magic power...
There's a battle somewhere.
That's where Luck went.
[ASTA]
Who's he fighting?
Likely someone from
the Diamond Kingdom.
They're here?
Then we should go help Luck!
Should we?
Luck likes fighting.
We could leave it
to him, couldn't we?
And keep going?
If there are mages from
the Diamond Kingdom here,
you can bet they'll be headed
for the treasure hall.
And protecting it is
supposed to be our priority.
This mission has
to be carried out
swiftly and thoroughly.
We wanna keep
those Diamond guys'
paws off the good stuff.
If we don't hurry,
the Golden Dawn'll
get the credit.
[growls]
[LUCK]
Win. I have to keep on winning.
With my own power.
Huh, I'm guessing
something more than smoke
is tying you in knots.
[LUCK] I almost had it.
Where did it go?
[LUCK]
Wait. I can't remember.
What am I looking for, again?
[KLAUS] There's so much
strength behind his attacks,
and he's not even
using a grimoire.
No sign of his magic
power decreasing, either.
[KLAUS]
If this keeps up...
Right. Yuno!
I'll stay here and hold him off.
Go on ahead to
the treasure hall.
He's extremely strong.
Are you sure you can
handle him without backup?
Stop questioning me
and do as I say!
We're out of options.
I don't like leaving this task
in the hands of a commoner.
But for the good of our kingdom,
we will complete our mission!
[KLAUS]
It's about time, you brat.
[gasps]
No!
Here, boy.
I can take all
your worries away.
[ASTA yells]
[gasps]
[ASTA]
Yuno.
You and me, we're family, right?
[ASTA] We're closer
than a lot of people
who are related by blood.
[LOTUS] Another spirited fellow
come to join us, I see,
[YUNO]
I guess so. Why, what's up?
What are you doing,
you imbecile?
[ASTA]
I was thinking.
Well, hello, there.
And who are you?
Who am I?
[ASTA] You and me, we don't
have any real relatives,
but we've got a lot
of great friends.
The mission needs to be
your priority right now.
[ASTA] We should take
the friends we have now,
and the ones we'll meet later,
and make them our family.
No, sir.
--[YUNO] You are my friend!
--[ASTA] I am his friend!
Right. Yuno!
I'll stay here and hold him off.
Go on ahead to
the treasure hall.
[KLAUS]
It's about time, you brat.
[gasps]
No!
Here, boy. I can take
all your worries away.
[ASTA yells]
[panting]
What were you thinking
coming back here,
you imbecile? We have
a mission to complete.
And that means getting
to the treasure hall,
even if you must go alone.
[YUNO]
First, we defeat him.
Then we go to the hall together.
[running footsteps]
You're taking us
on now! You ready?
Ooh.
Your friends are coming
out to play, too?
How delightful.
[VILLAGER 16A]
From what they say,
sounds like she
just up and died.
[VILLAGER 16B] She did seem
to be under a lot of stress.
[VILLAGER 16C]
Left her kid behind, too.
Poor thing must be heartbroken.
[VILLAGER 16B]
Well, I don't know about that.
He's a strange one.
[VILLAGER 16A] His mother's
dead, and he's smiling.
He's mine.
[NOELLE gasps]
Luck, wait.
[LUCK]
He's my prey.
[LUCK'S MOTHER]
Win.
[LUCK] I will win, and dedicate
my victory to you, Mom.
I'll take him on
alone. Stay back!
I don't need friends
to help me win.
I'll use the power
only I possess.
Please, Luck! Let us help!
I have to do it by myself,
or I'll never earn
my mom's acceptance.
--Fine, have it your way.
--Asta!
Is that all? This really
isn't the time
to hold back, you know.
[LUCK]
I'll do it. I'll win.
I have to. For Mom!
[LUCK] I need her to accept
me. Or I'll be all alone.
[ASTA yells]
You go ahead and do
what you gotta do, Luck.
But so will I, got it?
I have to beat him on my own.
Sorry, but that just
isn't happening!
[yells]
[ASTA grunts]
[gasps]
I'm not done!
[LUCK]
In some way...
I don't know what
you think of me,
and it doesn't matter!
Do whatever you want!
[LUCK]
...I was trying not to notice.
But you're my friend.
You're our friend.
So let us help! Yah!
[LUCK] Trying not to see
that even I have friends
who I can count on.
[LUCK]
Sorry, Mom. It turns out...
...I'm not alone, after all.
[ASTA panting]
You're right.
It does sound a lot more
fun to fight together.
Sure does!
[NOELLE]
Hm.
[LOTUS] Well, this isn't
a good turn of events.
If that's how it's going to be,
I suppose it's time
to get serious.
[LOTUS]
Smoke Creation Magic:
Prison of the Fallen King!
Poor, foolish little children.
There's no escaping now.
[ASTA] The thing about
the Black Bulls is
we don't lose to anyone,
and that includes you!
Got it?
Time to go. This ends now.
What are you...?
[YUNO]
Wind Creation Magic:
Engaging Swift White Hawk,
paired with Wind Blade Shower.
[KLAUS]
He's performing a dual-casting?
And one with so much
magic power behind it!
Time to get out of
our way, Diamond mage.
The Golden Dawn will
reach the hall first.
[yelling]
I'm cutting and
cutting and cutting,
but it's just not cutting it.
Here!
[LUCK grunts]
[gasps, yelps]
[coughing]
Anyone else feeling kinda dizzy?
[NOELLE] This place is
filling up with smoke.
We'll wind up suffocating
at this rate.
Our only chance is to defeat
the spellcaster, and fast!
[LUCK]
I can sense his magic power,
so I have a good idea
of where he might be.
If we attack, he'll
most likely dodge it.
What do I know about his
fighting style so far?
[LUCK]
When he's inside the smoke,
he can move really fast,
and he can pick up on
magic power quickly, too.
[LUCK] Our best shot is to
find a way to blindside him.
But how, when he
can sense our magic?
[ASTA yelling]
[LOTUS] This spell is effective,
but it uses a very high
amount of magic power.
I may not be young
like you three,
but I can do this all day.
[LOTUS] Of course, it would
help if I could actually
see my opponents.
Don't get any foolish ideas.
I can sense your magic power,
so sneak attacks aren't
going to work on me.
Whoa, there!
Wow, rapid-fire!
Getting desperate, are we?
I'm afraid you won't be
able to hit me like that.
It won't clear
the smoke, either.
All you're doing now
is wasting your power.
I suppose it all comes
down to experience.
I've likely been in more battles
than all of you combined.
[grunts]
[groans]
[yells]
[LOTUS groans]
[LUCK]
First, I cornered him.
[NOELLE] Then, using
every drop of my magic,
and in a fraction of a second,
so he wouldn't notice.
Up you go!
[LUCK]
And Asta, with no magic power
to give him away, attacked!
[NOELLE]
That went really well.
You know, you were
right earlier.
Teamwork is vital.
What? How is that possible?
[panting]
[MARS]
Begone.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[YUNO]
"Family."
So. Yuno.
Is it true that when
you make new friends
you treasure them like
you would your own family?
What a lovely idea!
That sounds so wonderful.
Yeah.
Family...
So, does it look a little
something like this?
Hey, Big Brother Klaus!
[KLAUS]
Hm?
[giggles]
Aw, that tickles!
Little Brother Yuno.
I got something special for you.
[YUNO]
Ooh, my own glasses!
Wow, you're the best.
Thank you, Brother!
Yeah, no way.
[YUNO]
This guy's powerful, all right.
But I can't let myself
be defeated now.
Not if I'm going to
become the Wizard King.
Black Clover ,
Page 17: "Destroyer."
My magic is never giving up!