[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[ASTA, YUNO]
Here we go!
[YUNO, ASTA growling]
[BOTH]
Onward, Le Château de Verre!
[YUNO]
It's over!
[ASTA]
You're goin' down!
[YUNO yells]
[BOTH yelling]
[NARRATOR] Asta and Yuno
joined forces to drive back
the attacks of Klaus and Hamon.
[gasps]
[RHYA]
Licht?
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, the real
Licht had been preparing
to make his move.
[YUNO]
I can't find an opening!
Time to change my approach.
[yells]
[YUNO]
Not yet.
Not yet!
All right. My turn!
Mana Zone:
Spirit Storm!
I'm not done yet!
[RHYA]
Who are these two?
You're not killin' Yuno!
Or Asta, either!
[ASTA, YUNO]
He's my rival!
[ASTA]
He blocked it with that sword?
[YUNO] He's condensing
a huge amount of magic!
[MIMOSA]
Is this Yuno's spell?
[gasps]
[BOTH yelling]
The giant hole you just
made in the ceiling
does kinda brighten
up the place.
But you lost your grimoire,
and both of your swords with it.
You sure that was a good move?
[RHYA] Guess he's not
in a talkin' mood.
[gasps]
Well, never mind the grimoire.
It isn't mine anymore.
[RHYA]
What?
[LICHT]
Rhya. Let's go.
[RHYA] Licht is finally
here for real now.
That's all that matters.
Asta!
Ugh! What is that
weirdo's problem?
Yuno's soaking wet now! Achoo!
You better not have
given me a cold.
Next time we meet,
I'm gonna sneeze on you!
[rustling]
[MIMOSA]
Zora!
[ZORA] This way. There's
another captain here.
Ah. They're fine,
they're just unconscious.
Hello there, Rhya.
Hey, Ado.
How's everything been?
Not bad, thanks.
Is he still...?
[RHYA]
Yeah.
Looks like all we can
do is wait for him
to awaken the rest of the way.
I suppose.
So, where are the others?
One moment.
Ha!
It's been quite a
while, hasn't it?
Five whole centuries!
But all of you look great.
Well. 'Bout that time.
Let's go pay the rest
of our friends a visit,
and then, we'll wipe
out all humankind!
[screams] I blacked out!
Whoa, for some weird reason,
my whole body hurts and
I'm drippin' wet, too!
What's wrong with me?
[YUNO] I liked it better
when you were knocked out.
[BELL] You're gonna burst my
eardrums, you big, dumb idiot!
Who you callin'--
Gah! My ears hurt, too!
--This is the worst!
--[BELL] Dummy.
You survived! I'm so relieved!
[ASTA]
Yeah! I'm glad we're all oka--
[screams]
Hey, where'd the hideout go?
Crazy as it may sound,
it took off toward
the royal capital while
you were out cold.
[ASTA]
What do you mean "it took off"?
Like, how-ow-ow-ow-ow?
You came back alive,
just like you promised.
You're the luckiest
damn half-pint I know.
[ASTA]
How's the captai--
[ASTA screams]
She's unconscious,
but she'll pull through.
[ASTA]
That's good news, at least!
She won't be up any
time soon, though.
I'd wake her, but I
don't have a death wish.
[EN]
You made it! This is wonderful!
[ASTA] Mushroom Man and the
Silver Eagles capta-- [groans]
Two of our comrades seem
to have changed sides.
Fortunately, we were
able to escape using
my mushroom smokescreen
and the mobility boost
from Nozel's magic.
Really? Them, too?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
[NOZEL]
Asta of the Black Bulls.
He survived a battle
terrible enough
to put Mereoleona
in that condition.
Herbs'll fix ya!
No prob! You guys eat, too!
Sure.
Nah, I'll pass.
You really shouldn't
eat those raw.
[BELL]
You'll get a tummy-ache.
[MIMOSA] I know these'll
probably make me sick,
but Asta gave them to me.
I can't let 'em go to waste!
[NOZEL]
Here, use this.
Magic Item: Eilia's Booth.
This tool provides
an enormous enhancement
to the body's natural
healing abilities,
which you three
desperately need.
Oh! That's great, thank you!
Awesome, the pain's
already goin' away!
What a useful magic item!
Thank you so much for your help!
Nozel's a pretty decent guy,
but I don't know how he
can see with that haircut.
Hold still, Yuno, let me
take away your pain,
and give it to you!
Hey, I don't want it!
Are you feeling
better, my darling?
Yeah.
Oh, thank goodness!
You guys! You're all okay!
Noelle!
And she brought that.
It's your big brother!
What happened to you, Kirsch?
Man, you look like crap!
[KIRSCH sighs] Even spattered
with blood, I'm still beautiful.
[MIMOSA]
Ugh, I don't think so!
[KIRSCH groans] I'm such
a gorgeously fragile flower.
Okay, who is this nutball?
Noelle! Where's the team?
I don't know how
to explain all this,
but Luck turned on us.
Aw, that sucks!
[KIRSCH]
That Crimson Lion, as well.
Same with Klaus and Hamon.
It was out of nowhere!
Don't forget Rill.
This is bad.
[sighs] They're pitiful.
Hey!
You have markings
on your face, too!
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm the same person I was.
My magic's just
been boosted a bit.
[gasps]
All right, fine. I guess
I can spell it out.
How dare you condescend me?
I'm royalty, after all!
Oh, yeah, well,
I'm the Wind Spirit,
so you're nothin'
special, missy!
No one asked you!
[NOZEL] The Spatial mage who
was on standby isn't here.
He must've changed
sides like they did.
[SILVER EAGLE 101A]
Captain Nozel!
Come in, can you hear me?
[NOZEL]
What's wrong?
[SILVER EAGLE 101A]
Oh, good, you're there!
I thought I would
never get through!
What's that?
A magic transmission device
that all of the captains have.
[SILVER EAGLE 101A]
Several of our squad members
have suddenly become violent!
They're acting strange
and claiming to be elves!
The worst part is,
their magic power
is much stronger than usual!
We can't handle them alone!
Apparently the other squads
are experiencing the same thing!
Something must be taking
over the kingdo-- [screams]
[NOZEL]
What was that? Answer me!
Is this happenin'
all over the place?
It's not lookin' good,
I know that much.
Come what may, we're
still Magic Knights.
Which means our
number-one responsibility
is to protect the Clover
Kingdom, even if doing so
means we have to eliminate
some of our own comrades
in the process.
[NOZEL] And even if it comes
at the cost of our lives.
But, Luck...
When he attacked me before,
his spell didn't hit me.
I missed ya!
Looks like I've
gotten a little rusty.
Let's try again.
[NOELLE]
He was moving extremely quickly,
but we were still able
to get away from him.
I think Luck made that happen!
Well then, why did he hit me?
I'm sure you deserved it.
That means Luck's soul
is fighting to resist!
Just like Yuno
still has control!
[NOELLE] And since we
know that's possible,
we should be able to restore
everyone's free will!
There has to be a way!
As Magic Knights,
we can save our squadmates
and the Clover Kingdom!
Yeah!
Let's do it!
[NOZEL chuckles]
All right! Go!
[VILLAGER 101A]
What do you think that is?
[VILLAGER 101B] As soon as
those light swords go away,
now this happens?
[VILLAGER 101C]
Why is the demon skull glowing?
[VILLAGER 101AA]
It's frightening.
Hey! See that?
[VILLAGER 101BB]
Huh?
What's happening this time?
It looks like daybreak.
Nuh-uh. Not that!
Something's coming.
[gasps]
[ARLU gasps]
[VILLAGER 101E]
It's headed for the capital.
[VILLAGER 101F]
But what is it?
[DIGIT]
Those are my friends, of course.
[VILLAGER 101CC]
His "friends"?
Look at his clothes.
He's dressed like a...
Your robe tells me
you're a Magic Knight?
[DIGIT] It would appear that
you humans have rapidly
increased in number over
the last several centuries.
[PRIEST]
Sir...
The people who possess
the least magic power
make their homes in
this area, and then,
as you reach the center,
you begin to encounter
the stronger inhabitants.
I see your kind continues
to discriminate in petty ways.
So, Magic Knight? Or not?
Kinda looks like he is.
[DIGIT] And you weaklings are
the target of this prejudice.
You humans. So arbitrary.
What?
Hold on. Who are you, exactly?
We do not discriminate.
We slaughter all humans,
equally and swiftly.
Poison Plant Magic:
Now, Zofnir's Garden
of Lingering Burns.
[PRIEST yells]
Aw, yeah! I'm as good as new!
Hey! Where'd your shirt go?
I had to get a good look
and make sure my
injuries are healed!
Okay, now you know,
so get dressed already!
Now that I've recovered,
my beauty can shine
to the fullest!
I kinda wish you hadn't
recovered at all.
The captain should
be better, too, right?
I don't understand why
she's not waking up.
Just let her rest.
Oh, yeah! You can
have this back now!
Throw it out.
It only works once.
Whoa, seriously?
I mean, it's kinda cool-looking,
so I think I'll hang onto it.
Do what you want.
We're almost to
the Forsaken Realm.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Someone's attacking that area.
But, that's...
[BOTH]
...the Village!
[ASTA] Yuno and I grew up
there! We have to help!
[NOZEL]
No.
[YUNO, ASTA gasp]
We must proceed directly
to the capital
as quickly as possible.
The best way to
protect Clover Kingdom
is to secure the most
populated area first.
My hometown is part
of this kingdom!
You two may do as you
see fit, but we press on.
That said, you're both crucial
to our fighting strength.
Finish quickly and
meet us in the capital.
[BOTH]
Right!
Let me go with them!
[NOZEL]
You'll remain with us, Noelle.
You're forcing me?
[NOZEL]
You are royalty.
I order you to accompany me
to safeguard the castle.
You want my help? Really?
Although, if we're being honest,
your very existence
is pointless.
This is no place for a
pathetic creature like you.
Now leave.
[gasps]
Right! Then I'll go!
[DIGIT]
I had always found it strange.
Why did I possess
Poison Plant Magic?
It didn't seem logical, but...
One day, I understood.
[VILLAGERS whimpering]
[VILLAGER 101G]
It hurts so much.
Help me, please.
It feels like my whole body
is being burned alive.
That's what this magic is for.
Eradicating insignificant
lives like yours.
[LILY] Water Creation Magic:
Holy Fist of Love!
[panting]
No life is insignificant.
Not one!
No, Father!
Hang in there!
So, some of you are able to
use a little magic, at least.
Or is it only you?
Are you of noble blood?
Well, no matter.
Even the mightiest of humans
are powerless against the elves.
Who is this guy? He's a monster!
You're so cruel.
Hurting a priest like that!
Listen. I don't know what
happened in your past,
but what did the residents
of this poor village
ever do to you?
We live simple, peaceful
lives, like anyone else!
You'll be okay!
I'll make all the
owwies disappear!
[LILY]
We cry.
Gah! This is way too confusing!
[LILY]
We struggle.
At this rate, I don't know
how we'll make it
through the winter.
[LILY]
We worry, and yet!
Pop-potatoes again?
At least we have enough food.
Yeah, I love pop-potatoes!
You make the tastiest
dishes out of these, Sister!
I don't mind eating yours, Nash!
No way, I still want 'em!
Food is food!
Need water!
[ALL laugh]
[LILY] We find a way
to laugh and dream.
And live life with
everything we've got!
We don't deserve
to die like this.
Nobody in the kingdom does!
[gasps]
[NASH]
Yeah!
You're poor like the rest of us.
Orphaned cast-off. Kids like
us don't get to have dreams.
Hey, Nash.
No giving up, you hear me?!
We can dream as
much as we want to!
Even if you're a poor orphan,
you can become great,
just like anyone else.
You can do anything you want.
Make your dreams come true
and make the people
you care about happy.
That's exactly what
I'm going to prove.
If by some chance,
some very small one,
you actually manage to
join the Magic Knights.
Yeah, what?
Then I'll start believing
dreams really can come true.
That I can be anything I want.
And maybe one day, I'll
become a Magic Knight, too!
Or, you know, whatever.
Without me and Yuno here,
guess you're gonna
be the biggest brother
from now on.
Keep these guys safe.
We're countin' on you, Nash!
I agree.
No one's life should
have to end in sadness.
Therefore, I'll wipe out
the source of that sadness.
Your kind.
[LILY gasps]
[DIGIT]
Poison Plant Magic:
Zofnir's Garden
of Lingering Burns.
No! Leave her alone! Stop!
[gasps] Oh, no! Stay back!
[yells]
[ALL gasp]
[LILY gasps]
[LILY]
Asta. Yuno.
[REKKA] Father, wake up!
It's Asta, he's back!
[ARLU]
And Yuno, too!
You're really brave, Nash!
Good job!
You mean it? Thanks a lot, guys.
[BOTH]
Stay back, it's our turn now!
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[KIRSCH, MIMOSA] "Exploring
the Vowels with Kirsch."
The first vowel. A.
As in awfully gorgeous.
[MIMOSA]
I.
As in intense beauty!
U.
Um, ultra chic!
E.
Eek! Exquisite!
[MIMOSA]
O.
Oh, ornate!
As in, observe the ornateness
of my overwhelmingly opulent...
[MIMOSA] O as in
overly obnoxious oaf.
[YUNO]
I'll take it from here.
I don't know who you
are, but I'll never
let you put the people of
Hage Village in harm's way.
Your time is up.
Black Clover , Page 102:
"Two Miracles."
When are these weird
markings gonna go away?