[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives a magicless
boy named Asta.
This brave young hero devotes
blood, sweat, and tears
to becoming the
next Wizard King.
Though Asta's situation
is practically unheard of,
there are others residing
in this kingdom who possess
at least a tiny amount of mana,
yet can barely
use spells at all.
They make up a very
small minority,
living their lives
in the shadows.
[NARRATOR]
But, like everyone else,
they do their best to survive.
[DAZU gasps]
So, is that a "no" then?
[mumbling] Are you
sure I'm enough?
I'm sorry, I can't hear you!
Could you repeat that?
I said, are you sure
I'm good enough for you?
What? Don't be silly!
Dazu. I love you.
And I want you to become
my wife one day!
[DAZU gasps]
[MESHU]
Excellent work, Dazu!
[DAZU]
Hello, ma'am.
You don't use any magic.
And yet, somehow, you do just
as much as everyone else does.
[FINRAL]
Wow.
I know.
There's so many graves here,
you can't count 'em all.
Wonder how many popped up
after the big attack.
[FINRAL]
Um, hello, miss.
Pardon me.
Would you mind if
I asked you a question?
Sure, that's all right.
[FINRAL]
Have you seen this little girl?
We're also trying to find
a beautiful young lady
with a pair of
horns on her head.
[DAZU] Horns? I'm sorry,
I don't understand.
[YAMI]
No dice?
This might ring a bell.
You know anything about a group
that's got a grudge
against devils?
I would assume everyone
has something against devils.
You know about
the one that caused
all the destruction
here, don't you?
Yeah, I do.
[DAZU] Judging by your cloaks,
I take it you're Magic Knights.
[YAMI]
We are.
I lost my husband in
that attack and his mother.
Why didn't any of you
show up to help us?
Our numbers were
stretched way too thin.
The whole kingdom was in chaos!
[YAMI]
I'm sorry.
Because we weren't here,
your loved ones died.
[DAZU]
Excuse me.
[VILLAGER 144A]
That cross and that silver hair.
Are they Silvas?
[VILLAGER 144B] What are a
couple of royals doin' out here?
[VILLAGER 144C]
Hey, cut it out, stop staring!
[NOELLE]
I have a question.
Does this girl look
familiar to you?
[MAN 144A]
Uh... I don't think so.
Cute kid, though.
[NOELLE] We're here looking
for her and another girl
who has horns on her head.
Please let us know
if you see them anywhere.
Hang on, did you say horns?
[NOELLE]
So you haven't seen them.
Thanks!
Uh, no problem.
[NOELLE]
Excuse me, sir!
Have you seen this person?
[MAN 144B]
Nope, can't say that I have.
Sorry.
But you didn't even look!
Sorry, but I'm a little
busy right now.
My house was just
torn to pieces recently.
And no one came
to help us rebuild.
Hey, don't go!
[NOZEL]
Let him.
[NOELLE]
What's wrong with them?
They're being indirect.
But it's obvious that the people
in this village are angry
at the Magic Knights for
the way things were handled
after what happened
to their home.
We can't blame them.
It's our job to protect
the Clover Kingdom,
and we weren't able to be here
when they needed us the most.
You're right. We failed them.
[NOZEL] We won't get any useful
information by being forceful.
But Nero and Marie--
we have to save them!
I agree that time
is of the essence,
but panicking never
produces results.
If you are a true Magic Knight,
then you'll learn how
to keep a level head.
Right.
[NOZEL] Since questioning
people isn't working,
perhaps we should
try something else.
Okay!
Marie!
What is wrong with you?!
[GAUCHE gasps]
[LITTLE GIRL cries]
I guess you're not Marie.
You'd better stay away
from my daughter!
[GAUCHE] Excuse me!
I'm a little tense, here!
[MAN 144C sputtering]
[GORDON] As the other
half of the Double G Duo,
it's my job to back him up!
How about a nice treat
from your new friends?
[LITTLE GIRL screams]
I said don't touch my little
girl or I'll kill you both!
You should probably look
a bit more closely next time.
I don't need advice from you!
If I even think
it might be Marie,
then I'm running straight
over to save her!
Dammit.
Marie!
Where did they take you?
I'll find you, angel!
Please wait for me!
Let's try not to attract more
attention to ourselves, okay?
[MAGGIE]
Did you call me?
Wait, what?
[MAGGIE] I could've sworn
I heard you shout my name.
On top of that, you
called me an angel. My!
I don't think I've
ever been called that,
even when I was
a spring chicken!
What the hell are you
yapping about, you crone?
[GORDON] I'm sorry, ma'am,
but what is your name?
[MAGGIE] It's Maggie,
but Angel's fine, too.
[GAUCHE]
Didn't you hear us?
We said Marie!
[MAGGIE] Oh, dear.
Well, that's different.
[GORDON]
Just a little.
[knocking]
[door creaks]
Did something go wrong, Dazu?
[DAZU]
Yes.
[BOW]
We'll talk down there.
[trap door creaks]
[DEMON MASK 142A]
Dazu. Welcome back.
[DEMON MASK 142B]
You did well.
Thank you, everyone.
How much longer do we plan
to keep hiding in this cellar?
I think it's better to go ahead
and execute these two.
[DAZU] It seems we have an even
bigger problem on our hands now.
The Magic Knights
have just arrived.
[KABWE]
What?
[DEMON MASK 142C]
Did they track our location?
[DEMON MASK 142B]
No, they couldn't have.
Master Kabwe's
Transparency Magic
is concealing our
presence completely.
But they still might have
planted something ahead of time.
[ALL gasp]
[KABWE] Transparency Magic:
Detection Decoder.
That must be it!
What the hell?
That thing tracks people
who are possessed by devils!
How did it get here?
I can't believe they
pulled a stunt like this!
[DAZU]
Wait, not yet. I have an idea.
Please tell me you guys
got some good info.
No, unfortunately,
the townspeople
weren't being very cooperative.
We tried to figure out where
their hideout might be,
but no luck as of yet.
And, despite my best efforts
to track their mana,
we still can't
pinpoint the target.
Look at this.
The signal still seems
pretty unstable.
It's also troubling that
we don't know how much time
we have left before they
notice that magic item.
If we don't find them
before that happens,
things could get worse!
Well, what'd you learn?
We mostly just talked
to an elderly woman.
She was an interesting person.
[YAMI]
So, basically nothing. Got it.
[GAUCHE] Look, I'm not
here to screw around!
I'll do whatever it takes
to hunt down those monsters
who took my sister.
Once I get my hands
on them, it's over!
What's wrong, rich boy?
[NOZEL]
They're on the move.
Yeah, where?
You think they know
we're onto them?
I dunno, but something
real weird's goin' on.
[NOZEL]
I'm sure they realize by now
that Magic Knights
are in the area.
Perhaps they're creating
some type of diversion.
All right, then I
think Gordon and I
oughtta take another quick
look around the town.
I'll let you guys borrow
my wheels for a while.
[NOZEL]
Thank you.
That'll make it
easier to get back.
[FINRAL] Even Captain Nozel's
using me as a chauffeur!
Get on and hurry!
[BOW]
That worked like a charm.
Hopefully, it'll buy us
a little extra time.
I can't believe we have
to contend with them!
When the Eye of the Midnight
Sun ransacked our kingdom,
many of the Magic Knights
were directly involved
in the chaos that ensued!
Possessed or not, they should've
been held responsible!
[DEMON MASK 142C]
I couldn't agree with you more.
[DEMON MASK 144A] And yet,
all they're doing right now
is trying to protect
each other!
[DEMON MASK 144B]
They're a joke.
We obviously don't
mean a thing to them!
[DEMON MASK 142A]
It is our responsibility
to show them what the true
meaning of justice is!
Yes, that's right.
We have to stand up for
the people of this kingdom,
and make sure anyone
who threatens them
is severely punished!
Now. I say the first step
to exacting justice
is to execute these two
servants of the devil!
[ONOBY]
I agree!
Then we can put their corpses
on display as a symbol
of the negligence,
arrogance, and deceit
that the Magic Knights displayed
when we needed their assistance!
[SIONA]
They showed their true colors
when they sided with the devil,
and now they must be stopped!
[KABWE]
Exactly!
From this day forward,
the Devil Banishers
will be the ones to keep
the Clover Kingdom safe!
Perhaps it's better if we hold
off on the executions for now.
How can you possibly
believe that's better?
I feel just as strongly as you.
I can't forgive anyone who
communes with a devil.
[DAZU] But if we hang onto
them for a little longer,
we may be able to lure out
Asta--the boy who's possessed.
If we killed all three
at the same time,
we could make an even stronger
case for Master Kabwe's cause.
[KABWE]
Hm.
[DEMON MASK 142A]
That's a good point.
If we use these two as bait,
the Black Bulls are sure to act.
[DEMON MASK 144A]
Asta's possessed.
He's the one we really want!
That makes sense.
After all, he's practically
a devil himself!
We can't hope to bring justice
to the Clover Kingdom
until that monstrous
villain is dead!
Yes. I'm glad you agree.
So, now, we should determine
the best way to capture him.
Let me think here.
[NOZEL]
They've stopped moving.
No one's around.
Let's check in there.
[GAUCHE]
Marie! We're here for you!
Just tell me where you are!
[NOELLE]
Well, great.
They deceived us.
That was the only lead we had.
How are we supposed
to find them now?
[GAUCHE]
Damn it!
[NOZEL]
We need a new plan.
Let's regroup with
Yami and Gordon
and head back to the capital.
[BOW]
We'll be all right.
[DAZU]
You really think this'll work?
We made it through that night,
and our luck hasn't
run out since then.
[DAZU]
All thanks to you, Bow.
[BOW]
It isn't just me.
If I hadn't met you.
I wouldn't have any
purpose right now.
I'd just be wandering
aimlessly through my life.
[DAZU] And if not for you,
I would've felt nothing
but despair after being left
alone to suffer in this world.
[BOW]
You give me hope, Dazu.
I believe in you,
with all my heart.
[DAZU]
If you're by my side,
I'm sure everything
will be fine.
[ASTA grunts]
What's goin' on? Where am I?
[OWEN]
So, you're awake.
This is a breakroom
inside the palace.
Is that you, Owen?
Oh, yeah! Nero!
Hold on! Don't leave!
[gasps]
Don't you think you oughtta
find out what's happenin'
before you hightail
it out of here, kid?
[ASTA]
I'm sorry!
[OWEN] I was able to rid
your body of the drug,
so you should be fine now.
[ASTA]
Thanks a lot, doc!
Let me get this straight.
Nero and Marie were kidnapped
by a group called
the Devil Panickers?
It's Banishers, genius.
And if things had
gone differently,
they would've taken you, too.
Yeah, I heard that you saved
my life in the nick of time.
You're the best, Noelle.
Well, it's not like I saved you
because I care about
you or anything.
I just didn't wanna
let them get away
with whatever they were doing.
I wish I could've stopped
them from kidnapping Nero.
That's not your fault, though.
If I had just been
a little bit stronger.
I know it hurts,
but there's no use in
cryin' over spilled milk.
Now. Owen says you're
healthy enough to leave,
so why don't you guys
head to the hideout?
No. I'm gonna go out there
and look for those two!
Did you not hear
anything I just said,
or are you really that stupid?
We don't have any clues
as to where they took them,
which means all you'd be
doin' is runnin' around
on a wild goose chase!
[ASTA grunting]
[YAMI]
Well, good luck, everybody.
What are you gonna do,
Captain Yami?
[YAMI]
Sometimes, a captain's gotta
tend to his business,
you know? Oh, yeah.
I already talked to
Gauche about this,
but if he freaks out, don't be
afraid to rough him up some.
Try not to kill him, all right?
That sound fair?
Yeah. I guess so.
It looks like everyone's here.
The Golden Dawn and Aqua Deer
are guarding the borders.
And the Coral Peacocks
and Purple Orcas have some
important restoration
work to attend to.
We certainly shouldn't
expect them to walk away
from those responsibilities
right now. So, hopefully
we'll be able to take
care of this matter
with only the people
we have present.
[DAMNATIO] If it's all right,
I have something to say first.
It's a distinct possibility
that my subordinates
are the ones who orchestrated
this whole scheme.
Therefore, I'm willing
to provide you
with any information
you require.
[JULIUS]
Thank you for your cooperation.
As of right now,
our top priority
should be rescuing the two
people who were kidnapped.
We can delay the punishments.
At the moment, it'd be
helpful if you could share
some background on your team.
Yes, a good idea.
Well then, Chairman Damnatio.
Please tell us
everything you can.
[DAMNATIO]
This is Kabwe Carillon.
He's 38 years of age.
His Transparency Magic
allows him to make himself
and the people around
him disappear.
He can't hide his mana,
so he doesn't have
the same skill
as the former
Purple Orcas Captain.
Besides him, there's a man
named Onoby Sinho,
31 years old.
His Barrier Magic
creates a barricade
whose radius is about
five times his height.
The structure promptly explodes
if anyone tries to tear it down.
Third, there's Siona Caverly,
29 years old.
Siona is a Paper Magic user,
meaning she's able to control
any thickness or length
of paper at will.
I could slice up
all three, easy-peasy.
We shouldn't do anything
to them until we know for sure
that they're involved with
the Devil Banishers.
Once there's proof,
you can slice and dice
as much as you want.
But for now, we need
to put our heads together
and find those two girls.
You got it, Beanpole?
It's also important to note
that the Black Bull
happens to be a wielder
of arcane-stage magic.
That makes her essential
to our strategy
for defeating the devil.
We cannot afford to
lose her at any cost.
They're both important.
The other girl's part
of our kingdom, as well.
So it's imperative that we
bring her back unharmed.
[YAMI] Hey, that was a pretty
good speech, Prickly Princess!
You're a lot smarter than
that Stick-Bug over there.
[JACK]
You shut it!
[CHARLOTTE]
Yami complimented me.
Wait, no!
Now's not the time
to be giddy about that!
Even if it was an ambush,
it's hard to believe
Asta was overpowered by
someone who's not a fighter.
[YAMI] They used somethin'
he's never dealt with before.
Apparently, the
assailants subdued him
with a sleeping potion.
Are you kidding me?
That's what I call a dirty,
underhanded trick!
[YAMI] The kid's had
training, so he can negate
just about any spell
someone throws at him.
And of course he can handle
a physical attack, no problem.
Up until now, he's
basically only had to fight
people in a way he understands,
which is face-to-face.
[NOZEL] Clearly, this
group has quite a gifted
strategist in their ranks.
Let's not forget,
they also managed
to use our own magic
item against us.
If these guys are going
around calling themselves
Devil Banishers, then
it's probably safe to say
that they're trying to
get rid of devils, right?
[MARX]
Yes.
[JACK] Then why haven't they
offed their hostages yet?
It's not like they
haven't had a chance.
[DAMNATIO]
Provided that my subordinates
are the responsible
party in this matter...
Out of those three,
Kabwe is the one with the most
enduring sense of justice.
And after the incident with
the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
his hatred of devils
became even more intense.
In fact, Kabwe was
extremely displeased
when the execution of the
devil-possessed was postponed.
Then why not kill
them even quicker?
If it were me, I would've
skipped right past
the sleeping potions and
slaughtered them all!
I'm sure they had their reasons.
Stupid ones.
[DAMNATIO]
Assuming Kabwe's in charge,
I'm certain that he would
prefer a proper execution
to murdering them on sight.
Most likely, he will attempt
to take their lives
in front of the
biggest audience he can.
He hopes to gain
the public's approval,
which will help him to
justify taking the law
into his own hands.
Like some kind of vigilante.
If I know my subordinates,
this is the method
they'll probably use.
Keh! Hell of a team
you've got there, pal.
Fortunately, if your
assumptions are accurate,
then it stands to reason
that both of the hostages
are still alive.
[YAMI]
Good.
[CHARLOTTE] But, if there
was a public execution...
There would likely
be a few citizens
who were in favor of it.
As I've seen firsthand,
many people are resentful
of the kingdom's
decision-making
since the Eye of the
Midnight Sun attacked us.
The wounds from that incident
have yet to be healed.
That devil committed
unspeakable acts,
and our people are still
reeling from the shock of it.
If we don't correct
this quickly,
we might just find
ourselves dealing
with a large-scale rebellion.
Right now, we're preparing
to face a threat from outside.
The last thing we need is
an additional conflict inside.
We have to nip
this in the bud
before it becomes
uncontrollable.
If they do decide to go through
with this public execution,
then they won't be able
to do it without us knowing.
Question is, what do we
do when the time comes?
Well, I trust you'll all
proceed with caution. Yes?
I wish I could give you
better instruction,
but I don't know
what else to say.
I can't help feeling
we're missing
an important piece of
the puzzle somehow.
[GAUCHE]
Execution?!
There's no way I'll
let that happen!
If those psychos hurt Marie
or even make her cry,
I'll be the one executing them!
Black Clover ,
Page 145: "Rescue."
Hold on, angel! Big Brother's
coming to get you!