[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[BANDITS groaning]
[groans]
[BANDIT 30A]
So strong.
[BANDIT 30B]
What kind of magic is this?
Now, how should you die?
[BANDIT 30A]
Please, please spare us!
We'll never attack another
village again. I swear!
[GAUCHE] Maybe I won't
kill you this time.
Huh?
Since it is a special day.
The day that an angel was born.
[BANDIT 30A gasps]
[GAUCHE]
Go on.
I want to hear you wish
her a happy birthday.
[BANDIT 30A]
Who is that?
[GAUCHE] Celebrate her with
every fiber of your being,
before you die.
[BANDIT 30A]
So you are gonna kill us?
[LILY] Look, Father!
We got our monthly delivery.
[ALL gasp]
That's wonderful!
[NASH]
Sounds like he's doing okay.
[REKKA] Looks like we're
in for a pop-potato feast.
[HORO, ARLU]
Hooray!
[LILY]
Amazing!
Yuno's become a Junior
Magic Knight, First Class.
[NASH]
No way!
He's only been there two months.
Yuno is the hope
of Hage Village!
And Asta?
Knowing him, he's being reckless
and getting into all
kinds of trouble.
But it's all right!
You can come home
any time, Asta!
Let's see.
He says "Dear Sister,
fellow church orphans,
and Hage Village Chief..."
What am I, chopped liver?
[gasps]
[LILY] Asta's made it
to Junior Magic Knight,
Third Class!
[KIDS, HIGH PRIEST]
What?
[NASH]
Good job, Asta.
Glad you're not slackin' off.
I knew you could do it, Asta!
You boys take care of yourselves
and keep doing
us proud, you hear?
[KLAUS]
Yuno.
I've heard that
you've been promoted
to Magic Knight, First Class.
Congratulations!
It's not really a big deal.
[KLAUS]
Exactly right.
We can't have you
getting a big head.
Never forget that
I am your better
in both rank and experience.
Is everything all right, sir?
[KLAUS]
Take it.
[gasps]
[KLAUS] A promotion gift
from your superior.
You keep that for yourself.
I know where all
your earnings go.
He doesn't always know how
to express his emotions.
I wish you'd gotten
to see it, though.
He was so happy when he
heard about your promotion,
I think his glasses
were sparkling.
That's pathetic.
Uh?
[YAMI]
All right.
I need everyone to listen up.
Our wages have come in.
So there's no work today.
[BLACK BULLS cheer]
Okay! Time to get training!
[yells]
Yami, sir! I thank you!
Great call, as usual!
Time for a drink, or three.
Well, you know
what that calls for?
Second breakfast!
All right, it's
time to get busy!
Ladies. Hey, there.
Who's your guy? Me!
[growls]
Oh, yeah, Gauche.
That bandit thing
yesterday. Good job.
Today is my little
sister Marie's birthday.
Do you think I could
extend my time off
until her next birthday?
Hell no.
Free time?
Man, I hope somebody
attacks the capital again!
Oh, hey! Maybe I should do it.
That's an even bigger no.
[mumbling] Money is nice,
but true happiness comes from...
I guess nobody
feels like working.
Cotton Creation Magic:
Feed me, Sheep Cook!
Stuff my face! Yeah!
[gasps] Pop-potatoes!
Ah, no way!
They're a specialty
of Hage Village.
That's where my darling prince
of provisions is from.
Give 'em a try.
So good! Mm. Thank you!
They're pretty dense.
Must be really high in fiber.
Wow, it's super crumbly.
Amazing how it sucks
all the moisture
outta your mouth.
These would make for
a pretty good bar snack.
[growls]
[CHARMY] The love I feel
for my savior of sustenance
knows no bounds.
It will not be denied!
[GAUCHE] What present would
be a worthy tribute
to my little goddess
on her birthday?
It's time.
Ladies of the Clover
Kingdom, get ready!
--Here comes--
--[YAMI] Wait.
Oh, right, of course.
You'll be wanting me
to take you into town
for another match, huh, Captain?
Yup, but first...
[stomach gurgling]
[YAMI]
All that fiber musta kicked in.
I might push past
my limits right here.
[FINRAL]
That's one limit you do not need
to push past, sir! So gross!
[NOELLE]
What now?
I get a day off out of nowhere
and there's nothing to do.
--[ASTA] Magna, sir!
--[NOELLE] Hm?
Sorry to bother you, sir.
But if you have time, will you
please take me somewhere
on your awesome broom?
Oh. How can I say
no when you ask
all sweet and polite
like that, Rasta?
Where to?
[ASTA]
Nean, sir!
[NOELLE]
Wait. I know that place.
It's where the boys went
for that stupid mixer.
Sure. So, whatcha
goin' there for?
Well, uh...
[NOELLE]
"Well," what?
Think we could talk on the way?
[NOELLE]
Oh, come on!
Not that I care what he does,
or who he may or may
not be going to see.
It's simple curiosity,
that's all.
Well? Are you comin'?
Wha--? Like, now?
Now or never,
it's your call, dude.
Now is good!
[MAGNA]
Get ready to hold on tight!
[gasps]
[MAGNA]
Hell yeah!
Okay. So, maybe I do care!
[GAUCHE] Greetings,
my darling sister Marie.
I've just arrived in the
village where you live.
Being a Magic Knight isn't easy,
but I don't mind,
because I'm doing it for you.
And with my wages,
I can buy you the
presents you deserve.
[GAUCHE]
Me, a former prisoner,
living a life on the
straight and narrow.
It's thanks to you, Marie,
my angel made flesh.
I do it for you.
[GAUCHE]
Ah, my nose won't stop bleeding.
[SHOPKEEPER 30A]
Gauche, sir!
We've been waiting for you!
If you would please step inside.
We have presents ready
for your perusal.
Show me immediately.
Right away.
First up, these!
Perfect for a little girl.
They all just love
stuffed animals!
One of these would be sure
to put a smile on her face.
[gasps]
They're perfect! Thanks so much!
[GAUCHE groans]
[GAUCHE]
Yes! I'll take them all!
Certainly, sir!
Our next item.
She'll be playing
with this for hours,
imagining herself living
in such a place.
A perfect home she'd share
with her brother, naturally.
[gasps]
Big brother! I'm so
glad you're home!
[GAUCHE groans]
[GAUCHE]
I'll take that, too.
Excellent, sir!
Last but not least,
with this costume,
your sister can be a real angel.
[gasps]
You know, Gauche. I love you!
[GAUCHE groans]
[GAUCHE]
The whole store. I want it all.
[SHOPKEEPER 30A]
Always a pleasure, sir.
[MAGNA]
What?
You're visiting some girl
you met at a mixer?
Sure am. I promised
Rebecca I'd come play
with her brothers
and sisters sometime.
Go, Asta. You're a fast mover,
already bringin' the whole
family in on your date.
I'm proud of you, buddy.
Yeah!
Hey. Look, Nean's up ahead.
[ASTA]
All right!
I'm gonna play so hard,
they won't know what hit 'em!
[MAGNA]
Whoa, heh, take it easy, boy.
[GAUCHE] Greetings, my beloved
little sister Marie.
Please forgive your brother,
whose blood loss
has made him tardy.
I've bought you so
many birthday presents.
I hope they will
bring you great joy.
[GAUCHE]
All my wages are gone now,
but no price is too high
for your happiness.
Soon I'll see my
precious angel again,
and that smiling face of hers.
Ah! My darling Marie!
Marie, Marie, Ma--
[giggling]
[laughing]
[ASTA]
You like that, huh, Marie?
[MARIE] So fun! You're
really strong, Asta!
I want a turn!
Me, too!
'Kay, come on and-- [yelps]
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
Get away from her
right now, you scum.
Oh, it's the bloody-nosed
sister-lover!
[GAUCHE] Call me a bloody-nosed
sister-lover again, meathead.
I'll squash you!
That isn't gonna happen--
not the way I've been training!
[laughs]
[GAUCHE]
Shut up.
[GAUCHE] I only get to see
my sister once a month,
which means these
visits are sacrosanct.
Today I set aside
all other thoughts,
ready to dote on my Marie
in every way possible.
It was supposed to be flirty
and fun and perfect.
So how is it that you
showed up here before me?
[ASTA]
So you do have a sister complex
and get nose bleeds.
And how was I supposed to know
she was your sister?
[GAUCHE] Stop pointing your
grubby little finger
at my angel!
I know I showed you
her picture, don't lie!
Did you? I don't remember.
I met her today when
I came over to Rebecca's
to play with her
brothers and sisters.
Uh, hi.
[PIM]
He's really scary!
What's "flirty" mean?
I don't know that word.
Shh!
Well, Marie's cute,
that's for sure.
Of course she's cute,
but that doesn't mean
you have permission to make
eyes at my sister, you filth!
Stop, big brother!
I don't want you doing
mean things to him! Please!
Asta's going to be
my husband someday!
[echoing] Asta's going to
be my husband someday!
Asta's going to be
my husband someday...!
[NOELLE]
Her husband?!
When I tagged along with them,
that was not what
I was expecting!
Uh, the fare, miss?
[NOELLE]
Will this be enough?
[DRIVER 30A]
Heck yeah!
[GAUCHE]
Kill. Kill. Kill...
Uh. You okay?
[GAUCHE]
Kill. Kill...
Kill now!
[ASTA screams]
[GAUCHE]
Mirror Magic: Reflect Ray!
[yelps]
Hey? What are you doing
with that mirror?
Now die!
Whoa. Hey! Stop! Ah!
Please stop! Don't hurt him!
[SISTER THERESA] Oh, my.
It's awfully noisy out here.
Marie, it's time to go.
You need to get back
to the church now.
[MARIE]
Sister!
I see. So you're here, Gauche.
That's right, hag.
[SISTER THERESA]
That's "Sister" to you.
Mind your manners.
[GAUCHE]
Marie and I are going on a date.
You can head back to
the church on your own.
No, Gauche. She's coming.
The sooner you accept that,
the better for us all.
When are you going to realize
that you're no good for
an impressionable young girl
like Marie?
She deserves to be around
somebody better than you,
with your bad attitude
and nasty tongue.
What was that, you old crone?
[SISTER THERESA]
There, see?
Just drop dead.
A nice thing to say
to an old woman
nearing the end of her life,
thoughtless fool.
Says the demon witch who'll
live for another 100 years.
Or two, or three.
Only a thug would resort
to that sort of name calling.
Shut up, you worthless bag!
Hold on a sec!
You can't just talk
to an elderly woman
of the cloth like that!
It's just wrong!
[GAUCHE] Nobody asked
you to get involved.
Now back off!
[SISTER THERESA] Just go home.
Come along now, Marie.
[MARIE] Bye, Gauche!
Bye, Asta! I had fun!
[groans] No. Marie!
--[KIDS] See you later!
--[ASTA] Bye, Marie!
[ASTA]
Hey, uh, you gonna be okay?
[GAUCHE]
Marie...
He's really weird.
You hungry?
We could go and grab
some food at the restaurant
while your knight
friend recovers.
You could, um,
stay the night at our
place if you want.
You mean it?
--[MARCO] Yeah!
--[PIM] Stay! Stay!
[NOELLE] Spend the night?
Are you kidding?
Sleeping at the house
of a woman he just met?
That's madness! Madness!
[MARIE]
I had a great time today!
Asta's really funny.
The obnoxiously loud boy?
[MARIE]
Yeah!
[ASTA]
Aw, yeah!
Have some more!
Here, would you like some
moguro berries, birdie?
[LUCA]
Whoa.
Man, every bite I take
is better than the last one!
Really? Thank you.
[laughs] Yeah! You know?
You'd make a great wife
with these cooking skills!
Huh? I wasn't going for that.
[NOELLE]
This is ridiculous!
Cooking skills aren't
the only thing
that make someone a good wife.
[yelps]
Uh?
Hey, sis.
Are you gonna
marry Asta someday?
[REBECCA]
No! Why would you say that?
[NOELLE]
Yeah right. Over my dead body!
So, sis.
Are you gonna make
a move while he's here?
Huh?!
[NOELLE groans]
No! Where did that
come from, Luca?
Pem? You, too?
I don't need all of you
ganging up on me.
[REBECCA]
Make a move on him?
No, that would just be crazy.
[NOELLE]
I never thought I would miss
Magna's Exploding Fireball.
Why is it so cold?
It's not even winter.
[NEIGE chuckling]
[snoring]
Are you gonna make
a move while he's here?
Pem? You, too?
[REBECCA]
Stupid! Ridiculous! Insane!
I would never do
anything like that!
I'll just check to make sure
Luca and Marco are asleep.
Maybe then I can get some rest.
[ASTA snoring]
It's time...
...for you to die.
Mirror Magic: Reflect Ray.
Ah-choo!
[screams]
What the heck is going on here?
[GAUCHE]
Die, Asta.
Who, me? But, I didn't do--
Wha--? Why?
I will never allow
you to marry Marie.
And there's one foolproof
way of preventing it.
[yelps]
Come on, it's just
something that kids say!
Also, you jerk, I was asleep!
[yells]
You can call me
whatever you want,
as long as I get to kill you.
Mirror Magic:
[BOTH]
My Real Double.
[ASTA]
Two Gauches?
And mirrors shooting
death beams?
What's up with this
guy's magic, anyway?
You have been found guilty...
[BOTH] ...of the crime
of meeting my little sister.
Aren't a lot of people
guilty of that?
[BOTH]
Just shut up and die.
[ASTA screams]
We don't even live here!
What?
[ASTA]
There's snow everywhere.
Where'd it all come from?
It's not even winter yet.
That's not important
right now. Die!
Hey! Stop it!
What are you doing out here?
I'm sorry! Things
got out of hand.
Never mind! It's the children.
They're missing!
What?
[MOTHER 30A]
Uriah! Where are you?
Christopher!
Von is missing, too!
No.
[NEIGE] How exciting. I just
love making new friends.
[laughs]
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[GAUCHE]
"Double Gauche."
Big Brother!
[GAUCHE]
Hm?
Will you swing me
around like Asta?
[ASTA, MARIE laughing]
Swing you around like him?
Are you okay?
I can't bring myself
to disappoint her.
I'll just have
my clone handle it.
Mirror Magic: My Real Double!
Now, swing her around.
I could never put
Marie in any danger.
You're so right!
Let's try this instead!
[GAUCHES]
Here we go! Around and around!
Aw.
[NOELLE]
Let's see, the ABCs of cooking.
All you underlings,
bow to my royal magnificence,
and cower before me.
Black Clover , Page 31:
"Pursuit Over the Snow."
Wait! This is no time
for word games!
Those children are in danger!