[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] The Black Bulls
have finally made it
to the Underwater Temple.
However, when they arrived...
You came to my temple to seek
the magic stone, didn't you?
If you want it,
you'll have to play
a game with me first.
[NARRATOR] A mysterious
old man, the high priest,
and his nine Temple Mages
were waiting for them.
The high priest separated
the Black Bulls,
telling them they must fight
the mages, nine-on-nine,
if they want to leave
with the magic stone.
[GIFSO] The team that wipes
out all of their opponents
or the one with the most
players left standing
when the game concludes
will be the winner.
Oh, yeah! I'm so there!
This is gonna be
a total bloodbath!
Hold on.
Did he say it was going
to be a nine-on-nine battle?
But there should be ten of us.
All right, I got it!
Now, let's go! I'm ready!
[OCTOPUS MAGE]
How interesting.
I'm not sensing so much
as a scrap of magic
coming from you.
Too bad. Looks like I got a dud.
[ASTA]
You think I'm a dud, huh?
Just try me and find out.
[GIFSO laughs]
Perfect! Now I can
sit back, relax,
and watch how the game unfolds.
Got a nice little spread
laid out and everything.
Listen up, you whacko.
There's no way I'm gonna
sit on the sidelines.
Let me play or I won't
be a happy camper.
[laughs] I'm afraid
that won't work.
You're too strong.
I've been looking forward
to this, and so have
all the good people who
are watching from outside.
Can't have the fun end
too quickly, now can we?
Well, hell, looks like
you've got a good eye
for fightin' skill, old man.
This geezer knows
a thing or two!
[BOTH laugh]
[GIFSO] Oh, looks like
some of the competitors
have crossed paths.
[YAMI] Those idiots better
not lose, or I'll kill 'em.
I'm so cold.
I'm gonna make that
crazy old bastard pay.
[SEAHORSE MAGE laughs]
That's priceless!
Fire magic in an
underwater temple.
This should be
very entertaining.
[MORAY MAGE] Hm. So small
and fragile looking.
I'll almost feel ashamed
when I tear you apart.
Ooh, are you the
one I get to fight?
[PUFFER MAGE]
I've heard of you people.
You're the Black Bulls.
They say you're the weakest
of all the Magic Knight squads.
[PUFFER MAGE laughs]
Marie is waiting. Let's
just get this over with.
[OCTOPUS MAGE]
So you know, waving around
that rusty old sword
is a waste of your time.
I can dodge any attack
you throw at me
with my Mollusk Magic.
Oh, yeah?
[GIFSO laughs] My toes are
practically tingling!
Out of curiosity, Captain,
how are those mages
of yours ranked?
They're all still
at the junior level.
I'm surprised ya know about
ranks, livin' down here.
[laughs] All my Temple Mages
are more powerful
than intermediate-class
Magic Knights,
and they're out there
fighting a bunch of juniors?
Your poor shmucks don't stand
a chance in this battle!
[YAMI]
Wow. That's bad.
Guess we're in trouble.
Unless those poor shmucks
are actually stronger
than their ranks suggest.
They're losing?
That's impossible!
Heh. It's gonna take more
than a few drops of water
to scare me off.
I say we turn this little
battle into a fish fry!
I guess that musta been
one of their weaker guys.
How boring. Wonder where
the tough ones are.
There, now that's done,
we can move on to much
more important things.
Like getting back to Marie.
[OCTOPUS MAGE grunting]
I don't understand.
My Mollusk Magic should
be able to deflect
any kind of physical attack.
That stuff's not
gonna work on me.
This is an anti-magic sword.
[ASTA]
Who's up next?
[ASTA yells]
[laughs] Yeah! Beat the
crap outta those fish!
[GIFSO growls] Idiots! Letting
them get the drop on you!
Hey, how 'bout we
bet on which team's
gonna win this game of yours?
I'm puttin' 10,000 yul
on the Bulls.
Please! This is
just the beginning.
The mages who're
left won't go down
as easily as those others.
In fact, my three great
mages rival senior-ranked
Magic Knights in terms of power.
[FINRAL]
Don't see me.
Phew. That was a close one.
I have no desire to fight
someone that scary looking.
I've been trying
to get back to where
this all started, but I can't
seem to for some reason.
Looks like for now
I can only use magic
to get to places that I can see.
[GIFSO] Oh, yes, there's one
thing I neglected to tell you.
Until the game is over,
you won't be able to leave.
[FINRAL] Hey, are you
watching me, old man?
[YAMI] Finral! Quit hidin'
and fight already. You wuss!
[FINRAL] Wait! You're
watching, too, Yami?
But how? Don't tell me
you're with the crazy priest!
[YAMI]
We're havin' a feast,
with your fights as
the entertainment.
[FINRAL]
What?! If you're with him,
can't you get him
to call off this game?
It's brutal!
[YAMI] Well, yeah. The brutal
part's what makes it fun.
[GIFSO]
I couldn't've said it better.
[FINRAL]
Great, they're buddies now?
You know,
this'll be a lot less
fun if your knights
are just gonna run away.
[YAMI]
Yeah. We gotta make 'im fight.
Well, it's time for
some nuisance magic.
Game Magic: Monster Toy!
[growls]
[screams]
[FINRAL screaming]
[laughs] Look at 'im go!
I should give him a few
more to play with.
Listen up, geezer.
That didn't look deadly enough.
Can you whip up somethin'
more like this?
[GIFSO] Just to clarify--you're
on their side, aren't you?
Nice drawing, though!
Now, let's see how the
rest of those little idiots
are holdin' up.
Grey's turned into a crab
and scuttled off somewhere.
Gonna kill the moron later.
Oh, looks like
Charmy's fighting.
[panting]
Wow. I've never seen
anything like this before.
Yes, the Underwater Temple's
denizens are truly yummy!
So awesome!
If I'd known the seafood
was so magnificent here,
I'd've come to visit
a long time ago,
strong magic region or not.
Ah, if only my
prince of provisions
were here to savor
this feast with me.
That's it!
I hereby claim this ecosystem
in the name of Charmy!
And I'm gonna keep
eatin' till it's empty!
[CHARMY laughs]
What, uh, is she doing, exactly?
Oh, yeah! Here we go!
--And it's all for me. Yay!
--[DOLPHIN MAGE] Found you!
Huh?
[DOLPHIN MAGE] Aw! Look at
what a cutie you are.
Too bad I'm gonna
have to squash you.
[CHARMY]
Heh. Is that right?
Well, right now, I'm full
of mana from all those
tasty little sea
creatures I ate.
You want to see if you'll
manage any better
against my teeth than they did?
Then let's dance!
[yells]
[DOLPHIN MAGE giggles]
Song Magic: Mother Lullaby.
[singing]
Wow. I feel really
good all of a sudden.
[CHARMY]
No, wait. I can eat more.
[DOLPHIN MAGE]
That's one down!
[laughs] Oh, I should've
mentioned that sleeping
counts as a knock out.
Well, what do you think,
now that you've seen
one of my great mages in action?
When we get back, she's on
short rations for a week.
[DOLPHIN MAGE]
That was fun.
Maybe I'll run into
my new friends next.
Nice.
My clothes are finally dry
after that dousing earlier.
I wonder who my next
victim's gonna be.
--[MAGNA] Eh?
--[LUCK] Uh--
Well, it looks like
you're still alive
and kickin', Lightning Boy.
Yep! And I knocked
out a temple mage.
I headed this way 'cause
I thought I was picking up
on something pretty strong.
And oh, goodie, it looks
like I was right.
Hell, yeah.
Now we just gotta decide
which one of us is gonna--
Hey, Luck, no fair!
Come back here, ya jerk!
[laughs] First come,
first served, sorry!
Lightning Magic:
Thunderbolt Destruction!
[GIO] Water Creation Magic:
Sea God's Shield.
[LUCK]
He's tough!
Lightning and Water should
be a good match, too!
[GIO] Well, well, aren't you a
spunky little fella. He, he, he.
[ASTA panting]
[growling]
[yells]
Gotcha, Slimy!
[ASTA]
That ki. Someone's there.
[MONSTER TOYS groan]
[TEMPLE MAGE 42A]
Aw, come on, Grandpa.
Can't you save the nuisance
spells for the other team?
Well, whatever. It was
a good warm-up, I guess.
[ASTA] He beat that
huge thing? Who is he?
[TEMPLE MAGE 42A]
Huh? Oh, hey there.
You're Asta, aren'tcha?
Uh, yeah, that's me.
[TEMPLE MAGE 42A]
I've heard about you!
You wield a strange sword
that cancels out magic.
Sure, that's right.
Wait, heard what, from who?
[TEMPLE MAGE 42A laughs] Never
mind that. Check out this dance.
[ASTA] But, we're
supposed to be fighting.
[ASTA] Still, that's
a pretty awesome dance!
[TEMPLE MAGE 42A] How do you
think it'd go over on land?
They would love it!
[KIATO]
I'm Kiato!
My dream is to captivate
the entire kingdom
with my dancing!
[ASTA] Now he's talking
about his dreams?
[KIATO] Except, while we
Underwater Temple folk,
can go to the kingdom's
beaches if we want,
we're not allowed to visit
any of the cities.
But that could change soon,
because, if I win this
fight, then Grandpa--
Oh yeah, the high priest is
my grandfather, by the way.
Anyhow, he said he'll use his
authority to let me go ashore.
Yes!
I'm going to make it big
as a star dancer!
[ASTA]
That's a huge dream, all right.
Hey. Wait.
Where have I heard something
like that before?
[KIATO]
So, I must apologize
But for the sake of my dream,
you must lose this fight!
[ASTA]
So fast!
[ASTA] Yeah, well, you're not
the only one with a dream.
[KIATO]
Huh?
That's right.
I wanna become the strongest
mage--the Wizard King.
The protector of the kingdom!
So, sorry.
But for the sake of my dream,
I'm gonna take you down!
[KIATO]
All right!
We'll both put our dreams
on the line and fight
without holding anything back!
[ASTA] I wouldn't have
it any other way!
[NOELLE]
Great.
What am I supposed to do?
How can I fight when I
haven't learned a single
proper attack spell yet?
[gasps]
[DOLPHIN MAGE]
Awesome! I finally found you!
[NOELLE]
Oh, no! A Temple Mage!
Well, I suppose it's
only fair to warn you
I am royalty.
Fight at your own risk.
Now's your last chance to run.
[DOLPHIN MAGE laughs] How cute!
I'm so glad you came, Noelle!
Uh, wait a sec.
How do you know my name?
[DOLPHIN MAGE]
Oh, silly me!
I forgot about the
whole mask thing.
[gasps]
[NOELLE]
Kahono!
I've been waiting
for you! Hiyah!
You live here?
You're one of the Temple Mages
we're supposed to fight.
Then why were you
so eager to help me
learn how to control my magic?
Yeah, about that.
I wasn't just practicing
up by the beach,
I was also looking for people
who wanted to come
down and visit us.
When we have visitors, Grandpa--
um, the high priest--always
wants to play this game.
And if I win, then I
get to go ashore.
Which means that I can
finally become an idol!
That's why?
So, then, you were
using me the whole time!
What? No, I wasn't.
When I saw how hard
you were trying,
I really did wanna help you.
And I totally still wanna
be your friend, too.
But...
Now we're facing off
against each other
in this game, and we hafta
fight fair and square!
But why?
You just said we were
friends, didn't you?
Yep!
But real friends can fight
for what's most important
to them and still
be able to laugh
with each other afterwards.
Song Magic: Mother Lullaby.
[singing]
[NOELLE] What's this spell?
It's making me...
[NOELLE] Water Creation Magic:
Sea Dragon's Lair!
Oh? So you are ready to fight.
[KAHONO]
Song Magic: Destructive Beat!
[KAHONO sings]
[NOELLE grunts]
Oh, come on, Noelle.
You've gotta use some
attack spells, too!
I really didn't wanna do this!
Wow.
That's just from releasing
her magic power? Jeez.
Really?
What the heck are
you doing, Noelle?
There's no point attacking
if you're just gonna miss.
You need to aim correctly
if you wanna beat me.
[NOELLE]
Shut up!
I still can't
control my attacks,
but you don't have to be
such a jerk about it, okay?
Sure you can.
What're you talking about?
You're controlling
your magic just fine.
Huh?
[KAHONO] You're unconsciously
trying to avoid
attacking me. You don't
wanna hurt people.
[gasps]
Now, that works out fine for me,
but think about the
reason that you're here.
Didn't you come
because you wanted
to see a dream fulfilled?
[NOELLE gasps]
Well, that isn't
going to happen unless
you fight me and win!
[NOELLE]
Why did I come?
Because I wanna
help the others!
Fine, let's fight.
[ASTA grunting]
[ASTA]
This guy's really strong.
And the way he moves is crazy.
It's like his mind's not here,
but off somewhere else.
His ki's so hard to read!
[ASTA] Feels like he's
scrambling my senses.
Is that his magic?
As I thought.
Against my real blades,
your anti-magic sword is nothing
more than a chunk of steel.
With my Dance Magic
as an added bonus,
you can't track my
movements at all!
[laughs] My grandson's pretty
powerful, don't you think?
Nice swordsmanship,
I'll give 'im that.
But still...
[KIATO]
Well, Asta? Come on!
Aren't you ready
to surrender yet?
[ASTA] Not good. If he keeps
this up, I'm in trouble.
It's like trying to grab water.
[ASTA]
Wait a second.
Maybe strength's not
what I need.
Water's shapeless.
So grabbing it's impossible.
[ASTA]
Stay calm.
I know!
[ASTA yells]
[ASTA] If I wanna beat him,
I have to be like water, too!
Monkey see, monkey do.
Now that's amusing.
Ooh! Ah! Watch what
this monkey can do!
I may not have any magic.
Who cares? I can just use
my body to mimic it instead.
Without magic, there are
limits to what you can do!
What?
[ASTA]
Oh, yeah? Well, in that case...
[ASTA] This is where
I push past my limits!
[KIATO] Impressive.
How strong is this kid?
[laughs] My guy's magic-suckin'
skill is even more powerful!
[yawns] Secretly setting
a trap for a poor,
defenseless woman like me.
You should be
ashamed of yourself.
[ANGLERFISH MAGE sputters]
[VANESSA]
Now, now.
You can't complain just because
you got caught instead.
Seriously?
Vanessa's usually either
too drunk or hungover
to manage much
of anything useful.
The Bulls are killin' it today.
I really shoulda bet more.
[growls] You said
that your knights
were junior-ranked mages.
There's certainly nothing junior
about the chest on that woman.
[YAMI] Better get that magic
stone ready, old man.
There's a real
nasty group called
the Eye of the Midnight Sun
that's after it, too.
I can promise you
that you're better off
handing it over to us.
Ha. You're only saying that
because my mages are
making a comeback.
At this point,
that kinda bluster
makes you sound
desperate, geezer.
[GIFSO]
I'm telling you, we'll win!
The tables will turn in
no time once my top mages
are able to show
what they can do.
I'll have you know, my son
is the most powerful mage
in the Underwater Temple!
[LUCK, MAGNA panting]
This is fun.
You look like you're
getting tired, though.
Wanna take a break?
Yeah, right.
I could keep goin'
all day if I needed to.
But if you need
a break, go ahead.
[GIO laughs]
Sorry about this.
My old man sure does
like his games, though.
Hold on a second.
That crazy old coot
is your father?
[LUCK]
He's got so much power.
Like a tidal wave.
No doubt about it.
This guy is the
strongest one here.
[GIO]
I'll take you both on at once.
I'm not interested in
tormenting you any further.
The least I can do for
you is end this quickly.
Water Creation Magic:
Poseidon's Hammer!
You're not gonna
be ending anything!
Yeah, I'm nowhere near
done playing with you!
[LUCK, MAGNA yell]
[GIO groans]
[BOTH gasp]
[KIATO]
Huh?
Um, why's everything shaking?
That's not part of the game!
What's going on here?
Well, it looks like you folks
are having quite a get-together.
[VETTO]
How about...
...you guys let me in the mix?
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[VETTO]
"Let Me In the Mix"!
Well, it looks like you folks
are having quite a get-together.
How about...
...you guys let me in the mix?
Huh?
Ah-- Um. I don't understand.
Did I get the wrong
place or something?
Wanna try?
[VETTO]
Huh?
Want to try some?
[stomach growls]
[sighs] I am kinda hungry.
Since I'm here, anyway,
I might as well get in the mix.
Thanks.
Then what are you waiting for?
Get mixing. Go on.
Like I always say,
those who do not
work shall not nom.
[VETTO]
Mix, mix.
It's not about sheer strength!
Cooking takes knowledge,
skill, and patience.
Right. I see now, thank you.
[ASTA] And so, Vetto, his eyes
opened to the joy of cooking,
left without retrieving
the magic stone.
And everyone lived
happily ever after.
I mean, it could happen, right?
No way.
[VETTO] I, Vetto, of the
Third Eye, will recover
the magic stone for the
Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Black Clover , Page 44:
"The Pointlessly Direct Fireball
and the Wild Lightning."
My beast magic will
crush everything.