[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[YAMI] So much for that
super powerful spell
of yours, Lineface.
[NARRATOR]
It seemed the Magic Knights
had finally bested the Eye of
the Midnight Sun's leader.
Until the Third Eye appeared--
the organization's
three strongest members.
Oh, man.
Looks like something
didn't go as planned.
Do you know what we do to
people who harm our friends?
I detest anybody
who hurts Licht.
--I hate them.
--[NARRATOR] Rhya the Disloyal.
Vetto the Despair.
And Fana Hateful.
I know you'll succeed
where I failed.
Thank you, my friends.
[NARRATOR]
The Black Bulls swiftly
found themselves outmatched.
Now, let's get this over with.
Hah!
Spirit Magic:
Salamander's Breath.
[NARRATOR] But then, the captain
of the Green Praying Mantises,
Jack the Ripper,
Blue Rose Knights captain
Charlotte Roselei,
and Silver Eagles captain
Nozel Silva arrived, turning
the tide of battle once again.
You're having way too much fun
on your own here, Yami.
You should let the
rest of us in on it.
Get some rest. I'm so
glad you're home.
And then, that woman
turned Baro into a giant,
living mass of mud.
I see.
It sounds to me like the
Eye of the Midnight Sun
was using you and your brother
for their own purposes.
I guess.
But we were still the ones who
abducted all of those children.
We were the ones who
stole their magic.
And so now,
I'm going to take
responsibility for my actions
as well as my brother's.
I'll turn myself in
to the Magic Knights.
Uh--
That's right.
Earlier, back in the cave,
Asta said something.
Good, and once you get
that outta the way,
you and I should be friends.
With all the cool
magic you can do,
I bet you're gonna be
a pretty popular guy.
We'll be friends.
I am truly sorry.
[NOELLE] Ugh! There's hardly
any point apologizing to me!
Once you're done
paying your dues,
you're going to be
Asta's friend, right?
So if I were you,
I would start praying
for your new buddy
to win his fight
and get back here in one piece.
Honestly, Asta.
What are you doing out there?
Finish it up already.
[NEIGE]
Asta. Please stay safe.
[gasps]
[NOELLE] I mean...
Not that it matters to me
what happens to that insect,
because it totally doesn't.
Not in the slightest.
Ugh! Why does this
keep happening?
And who am I even talking to?
[REBECCA]
She likes Asta, too?
Is that the someone special
he's got his heart set on?
There's no way he'd notice me
with someone like her around.
No.
This isn't the time to
be thinking about that.
I should be getting
things ready here
for when they get back.
Everything else can wait. Right!
Ooh, a second course. Yum.
Shame on you. Getting greedy.
It's not polite to hog
all the interesting
battles for yourself, you know.
I've gotta wonder.
How's it going to feel
to tear them apart?
Probably not very satisfying.
Kinda like rippin' up
a sheet of paper.
I was just about
to finish 'em off
when you morons
decided to show up.
[JACK cackles]
Yeah, I'm sure you were.
Looking more ragged
than usual over there.
[YAMI]
Pft. Me? Please.
[cackles] How about...
...I work out some
of my anger issues
by cutting you into tiny pieces?
[YAMI]
And there it is. You're nuts.
My sincerest apologies.
Forgive me.
[cackles] Scared now? I wasn't
really going to do it.
I'd much rather wait until
you're back in fighting shape
before our next little skirmish.
There isn't any point
if it's not a challenge.
Must we always come to get
you out of trouble?
You can't even stand up,
you miserable man
[YAMI]
Hey, it's not like that.
The ground just loves
my ass so much
it doesn't ever wanna let me go.
[CHARLOTTE]
Don't be an idiot.
The earth has no love
for an unwashed
miscreant like yourself.
[YAMI]
Ooh, burn!
That's some mouth you got on ya.
Not gonna be easy to find
yourself a husband, huh?
Now she's angry.
I don't need any
man to marry me.
The battlefield is my partner.
I get that you're
a warrior woman and all,
but even for you,
that's pretty sad.
[CHARLOTTE grunts]
[CHARLOTTE] Does he have
no regard for my feelings?
Why? Why did I have
to fall for him?
It's like some
kind of cruel joke.
But as hard as I try, I can't
keep him out of my head.
Well, I certainly can't
tell him anything now.
But if I did tell him someday,
what would my squad think?
You've gotta be
kidding me, Char!
You know he's a man,
right? A gross man!
[CHARLOTTE] What am I doing?
Now isn't the time for this!
So the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
its leader, and his top brass.
The highest-ranking members
of the organization
that attacked our kingdom.
I won't waste this chance.
I'll bury you with my own hands.
Ooh, Nozel, you are so cool!
You just sit there and try to
stay out of trouble, foreigner.
[YAMI] Your concern for my
well-being is truly touching,
O Great and Mighty Captain.
Hey.
How do you guys think
he gets his hair
to do that braid thing?
He's royal, so I figure
he has a servant
take care of it for him,
dontcha think?
Honestly, I wouldn't
be surprised
if he had his own
personal hairstylist.
I think that would qualify
as the worst job ever.
[ASTA]
What?
You think he takes the time
to braid his own bangs?
[YAMI] Oh, yeah, he probably
has lots of time on his hands.
Loser.
No, on second thought,
perhaps I ought to bury you
before those other four.
[YAMI] You don't wanna waste
your magic on some foreigner.
Show no mercy.
[JACK cackles]
Oh, yeah, let's do this, guys!
I'm totally ready to go!
We'll take these
jerks down, no problem!
You won't be joining this fight.
Huh?
[NOZEL] The captains have
taken to the battlefield.
Anybody who interferes now
will only get in our way.
Especially a pathetic,
magicless commoner like you.
[VETTO]
Excellent!
What better place
to find true despair
than at the end
of an endless battle?
And no despair is more delicious
than that of the mighty
when they face certain death.
The hell's he talkin' about?
Looks like we've got
some rat catching to do!
Jeez, Vetto is way too
excited about this fight.
Sounds boring to me.
[yawns]
Well, whatever.
I guess I can put forth
some effort for Licht's sake.
[RHYA]
And by the way, I'm calling dibs
on this beautiful young lady.
When I win, you and I are going
out for a drink, gorgeous.
When you win?
I'm afraid we're never going
to be clinking glasses, then.
Briar Creation Magic:
Corpse-Hunting Briar Trees.
Severing Magic: Death Scythe!
Someone's eager for a fight.
You're mine, beastie.
Well, well. The
Praying Mantis Squad.
Then I'll just squash you
like the insignificant
bugs that you are.
You think so? Well, we'll see!
You're confident
for a bug. Fine.
Let's see your smile while I'm
ripping you limb from limb.
Go, Bear Claw!
I've been waiting for this.
Finally!
Mercury Magic: Silver Spears!
Yet another foolish person
attempting to harm Licht.
For that, you'll die.
[cackles] Looks like
salamander girl's flames
are melting your mercury.
Wanna swap opponents, Silverboy?
I don't think so.
Those flames are hardly
enough to best me.
You have no idea what
I had to do to get where I am.
[JACK yells]
[yells]
[FINRAL yelps]
All this magic flying around--
it looks like some
kinda natural disaster.
I can't see through
all this dust.
Jeez, they're really
fightin' hard.
Better be careful, Jack.
You talk a good game,
but you cut it kinda close.
Looks like Charlotte's
doin' well, though.
And Nozel's bangs
haven't budged at all.
You can see?
Remember? Ki? I can sense 'em.
Yeah.
Finral. You ready?
[FINRAL]
For what, sir?
You've been restin' up
for a while now.
You oughta have enough
mana for a Spatial spell.
You mean we're leaving?
Sure, I'm ready!
Let the other captains
handle this, we can just--
[cackles]
[LICHT] The Magic Knight
captains are as powerful
as I expected them to be.
However, they are no match
for the Third Eye.
Our people are much loved
by the mana of this world.
And that is why there
must be some mistake.
How could an ordinary human,
one who's magicless,
clearly shunned by the mana,
possess that grimoire?
I must retrieve it from
his unworthy hands at once.
[YAMI] He's been weakened,
but I'm not gonna risk
letting him get away.
[LICHT] Ah, yes.
I expected this from you.
[FINRAL]
He's countering? Not good!
Look out, sir!
Oh, dear. You misjudged
our boss, I see.
[gasps]
I'll end you this time.
[VETTO yells]
Finish him, Licht.
[YAMI] You're goin' after
the boss, too, aren't ya?
All right. Bring it!
[ALL]
How did he get over there?
[NOZEL] It shouldn't have been
possible in all this confusion!
[YAMI] That's the kinda
thing you can do
when you learn to read ki.
[LICHT]
No one noticed. No one!
None of us could sense this boy,
because he has no magic!
We're gonna get you this time!
Thanks for trustin'
that I was gonna
take one last shot at you
while I had the chance.
As for me, I put my trust
in our magicless freak, here.
[ASTA]
My magic is never giving up!
[gasps]
[YAMI yells]
[ASTA grunts]
[ASTA pants]
[laughs] Gotcha.
So, what'd you think about
my magic-free smash attack?
You trying to take
all the credit, kid?
Sorry, Captain!
Not bad.
You really pushed past
your limits that time.
Thank you!
[gasps]
Where's Licht?
[BOTH]
Oh, no!
Eyes forward, beastie.
That little runt.
He left us in the dust.
[cackles] So much for
getting all the glory.
We're Magic Knight captains,
we can't fall behind!
It's up to us to take
care of the rest.
[FINRAL]
Captain Yami?
Wonder if any more of their
friends are gonna show up.
--I guess we'll see.
--[ASTA] That would be so cool!
Now's your chance
to finish him while
the other captains keep
the rest of them busy.
[YAMI grumbles]
[ASTA]
He's glowing.
[GAUCHE]
What the--?
No!
When that brat hit Licht
with his anti-magic attack,
it broke the spell of Sealing
that was cast on him.
That's not good.
That power had been set aside
for a day still to come.
This cannot be! Why do
you have that grimoire?
[LICHT]
Why do you wield them?
The demon-slayer sword and
the demon-dweller sword.
What's he saying?
[LICHT] Those swords
belong to the master!
[NOZEL]
The master?
According to our intel,
"the master" is the leader
of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Does this mean he
isn't the master?
You keep sayin' this crap.
Well, I'm sick of it.
It doesn't matter who this
"master" guy is, okay?
This grimoire and
these swords are mine.
I don't care if
they're all beat up!
Now quit with all
the accusations!
They're not yours.
Give them back.
That grimoire could
never belong to you.
The master's grimoire could
never be yours, filthy human.
Oh, boy!
What now, Captain?
Things aren't lookin'
so good, huh?
[cackles] Well,
this should be fun!
Death Scythe!
No way! It absorbed
my Severing Magic
like it was nothing.
That's an enormous mass
of pure magic power.
If he releases it,
we're all dead.
It'll destroy everything
in the surrounding area.
But what do we do?
Even we cannot stop this.
How much mana
is he channeling?
He's been holding back.
He could've obliterated us
anytime he wanted to.
[screams] I should have never
come on this stupid mission!
Actually, scratch that.
I should never have joined
this squad to begin with!
Stop runnin' your mouth.
Nobody wants to hear it.
Besides, this could
be our chance.
Just think of all the
limits we can push past.
We'll be up against
some real power!
[yells] Let's go!
[FINRAL]
No way!
Seriously, have you people
gone crazy here?!
[GAUCHE]
Hey!
Shut up and pull it
together, Finral!
I'm still your superior!
[GAUCHE] My magic's not
fully recovered yet.
Can I reflect his strike
with what I have?
That's too bad.
I'll need a raincheck
on that drink.
His body isn't going
to hold out much longer.
We need to hurry!
[VETTO, FANA, RHYA]
Trinity Sealing Magic!
[NOZEL]
They mean to seal away that?
All that magic...
Incredible.
You pushed yourself
just a little too hard
this time, Licht. We've got you.
Now get some rest.
It will be all right.
For now.
It's time to go, Valty.
Our boss is feeling
a bit under the weather.
So we're gonna have
to call it a day.
We may have lost to you
people this time around.
Just wait.
I promise, when we meet
again, I won't leave
until you've tasted
true despair.
We carnivores live to feast
on bottom-feeding
vermin like you.
The next time we meet,
you'll draw your last breath.
Remember, wherever you go,
the Eye of the
Midnight Sun is watching.
[CHARLOTTE]
That much magic power,
and they were able to seal
it with a single spell.
So, then, they were
toying with us.
[JACK]
The Third Eye.
Not only do they have a
tremendous amount of mana,
they are singularly
skilled at using it.
"Much loved by the mana"
is right. [cackles]
I'd like another chance
to rip them apart.
[NOZEL]
We let them get away.
But it won't happen again.
I will avenge you. I swear it
So, did we win?
It's less that we won,
and more like the
other guys ran off.
[YAMI] Huh. From where I'm
standing, them runnin' off
like that is as good as a win.
Besides, Beast Boy
said they lost.
Yeah!
Finral, Gauche.
You heard the captain! We won!
Yep! We totally did!
[GAUCHE]
You didn't do anything.
Dude, chill out.
We did it!
Yami, we're waiting.
Is there something you'd
like to say to us?
I'm hungry.
[cackles] I don't care
about your stomach.
I thought a "thank you"
might be in order.
What would you have done
if the other captains
and I hadn't shown up?
You can bet your
Scythe I wouldn't have
let 'em get away.
I would've taken 'em all down.
[cackles] You don't really think
that would've been possible?
You foolish man.
Fighting enemies
that strong alone
would be nothing
short of reckless.
Would it kill you to be
nice for once, woman?
[CHARLOTTE]
Still.
The idea that he would take
on all of them by himself...
I didn't fall in love
with him for nothing.
You should try to control
that tongue of yours.
Otherwise, you're
gonna die single.
[CHARLOTTE]
I told you, I don't care!
The battlefield is my husband!
Worry about finding your own
partner and leave me be!
[laughs] I'll make a deal
with you, Charlotte:
if we're both still single
when we're old and gray,
we can look after each other.
What? You're joking!
Who would want to be
with someone like you?
[CHARLOTTE]
Why can't I just be honest
and tell him how I really feel?
[ASTA laughing]
Asta's down!
Pushed past his limits
and then some.
All right. Get him healed up.
--Go on.
--[FINRAL] Who, me?
Yeah, make yourself useful.
[FINRAL] Like I've been
doing all day, you mean?
--[GAUCHE] Tch.
--[FINRAL] Oh, shut up!
[NOZEL]
I'll have to remember this one.
Asta, was it?
They sure got the best
of you this time, huh?
Sorry, Licht.
Well, you can rest a bit now.
I detest them.
Well, that was a
pathetic showing.
And you're our
strongest members?
What did you say?
Uh... Just. What do we do next?
The Wizard King will get
a report about Licht.
And soon, he'll start
pushing even harder.
On top of that,
Geork and Catherine
are still in custody.
If they talk, the Magic Knights
could find this place.
They could even discover
Licht's true identit--
Easy. Rades does have a point.
It's too soon.
We don't wanna put all
our cards on the table.
Well, not yet, anyway.
[yawns]
'Kay. Hm. What to do,
what to do.
I don't really wanna go,
but it doesn't appear
that we have much of
a choice. What a pain.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[SOL]
"Char's Acting Weird"!
[sighs] Honestly.
Why did I have to fall
for a man who smokes
like a chimney, has the
manners of a boar,
and absolutely does not look 28?
I just wanna wrap
him up in briars.
Yami!
Hey, Char, what were you
saying about Captain Yami?
[gasps] Um. I wasn't
saying anything!
And don't call me "Captain,"
call me "Char."
Wait, scratch that. Reverse it!
I swear I heard you say
something about briars, too.
Briars? Of course! Briars!
I was just thinking
about how much
I'd like to tie Yami up with
some of those, you know?
Okay, I get it now!
You're talking about
torturing him.
Wow, if you wanna do
something like that,
you must really hate
Captain Yami a lot, huh, Char?
Yes! I hate him so much!
Yes, I mean, he is a man!
Who'd ever wanna see
that guy's ugly face?
Exactly! Not even his face.
Right! And I'd like to smack
him with a briar whip!
Oh, why can't I just be honest
and tell him how I really feel?
[FANA]
Hurting Licht like that.
How despicable.
I will never forgive
the Magic Knights.
Black Clover , Page 38:
"The Magic Knight
Captain Conference."
Clover Kingdom, the end is near.