[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
[NARRATOR] All seemed lost
until a lone mage
stepped forward and
took up the fight.
[NARRATOR]
After his triumph, he was hailed
as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[NARRATOR] Asta joined
forces with his friends
to take on Vetto,
the strongest opponent
they had ever faced.
However, the beast soon
began to overpower
even these attacks.
[VETTO] I'm impressed.
You aren't half bad.
If even one of you
slips up, you'll be dead,
and you'll take the
other two with you.
[NARRATOR] With his back to
the wall, Asta brandished
his sword, putting his trust in
his friends and their victory.
Then, suddenly...
[GAUCHE]
It's not just two!
Looks like we made it in time.
Mirror Magic: Reflect Refrain!
Cotton Creation Magic:
Strike of the Sleeping Sheep!
Strike one!
Strike two! You're out!
[ASTAS yelling]
But how?
I used my Transformation Magic
to make some doubles.
I've had enough!
Time to plunge you
insects into despair!
Yeah, right! Who has time
to waste on despair?
[VETTO growls]
[yells]
Wow!
He did it!
[GAUCHE, CHARMY]
Yeah!
It's over.
[BLACK BULLS]
We won!
[VETTO]
Oh? Are you sure?
[crack]
[ASTA screams]
Did you truly believe that
your pitiful human power
would have any effect on me?
That was a fatal mistake!
I took that blow
on purpose, you fool,
in a place that
wouldn't kill me.
All so I could
steal your weapon.
[BOTH gasp]
What? No way.
[VETTO]
I know full well
when all hope is lost,
that is when despair sets in,
profound and unshakable.
Now the time has come at last,
to plunge into its depths.
[screams]
Please, no.
Asta!
[ASTA screams]
There it is!
The scream I've been waiting
to tear from your fragile body.
Yes! Wallow in
your despair, boy!
Despair! Despair!
Despair! Despair! Despair!
[NOELLE]
No... No...
[VETTO laughs]
So, how do you feel now?
Ha, ha! You'll never recover!
Not yet.
I'm not done!
[ASTA]
It's not over.
I won't give up!
[VETTO gasps]
[gasps]
That's incredible.
How is he standing?
That's right.
You tell him, kiddo.
[ALL]
We can still fight!
[yells]
Now, go!
[VANESSA grunts]
[VETTO]
You can't run from me!
[VETTO laughs]
Who's despairing now?
That's it-- the last
of our magic power!
No!
[NOELLE] Asta's right.
We're not giving up.
And we'll never lose.
Not to you!
[VETTO gasps]
Hey, Asta, are you okay?
[VANESSA]
This boy--he's not like us.
Born with no magic at all
into a world where
magic is everything.
And yet...
Maybe the fates chose
him to go without
because of who he is and
what he's capable of.
[VANESSA]
Whatever the case,
he's destined to
do great things.
We have to help him fight and
guide him when he needs it.
Here you go, kiddo!
I've made you a sling
for that broken arm!
Thanks, Vanessa. That's
exactly what I needed.
I may have a busted arm,
but, I can still fight!
[VANESSA]
Finral, get ready to go again!
Huh? Yeah!
[FINRAL]
I can do this!
Right! I'm ready.
[ASTA]
I've still got one sword left!
Why, human?
Why do you not despair?
[ASTA] I already told you.
I don't have time for despair.
There's someone I can't
lose to, no matter what.
We made a promise!
One that I won't break!
You and your despair
are getting in the way!
That's enough talking!
Pathetic human parasite!
It doesn't matter what you do.
I can read your every--
[VETTO] His movements are
too fast for me to follow!
[VETTO] The demon-dweller
sword still inside me must
be weakening the magic that
enhanced my physical abilities.
I had intended
to take his weapon,
but has he stolen mine
from me instead?
[VETTO groans, yells]
[VETTO]
I won't lose to you humans!
Your lives belong to me!
You've been losing this
whole time, Vetto!
Not one of us who went
against you has given up.
You tried to make us despair,
but you failed!
Silence!
[NOELLE]
Asta!
[VETTO]
My magic... No matter.
It won't stop me
from killing you!
[ASTA] Not yet.
I'm still... not giving up!
[gasps]
[VETTO]
This boy is just like me.
No. That's not true.
He's no beast.
[NARRATOR]
The leaves of a clover are said
to each contain one thing.
In the first three dwell
integrity, hope, and love.
The fourth leaf is
given over to good luck.
And in the fifth...
[VETTO] This one--he feeds
on despair. He's a devil!
[VETTO growls]
[yells]
[ASTA grunts]
[VETTO growls, yells]
[gasps]
[yells]
Hey, Despair!
[screams]
[ASTA]
This is where you lose!
[VETTO groans]
[VETTO sputters]
[NOELLE]
His magic is gone.
So... It's over. We won!
[ASTA laughs]
Take that, jerk.
--[VANESSA] Got you, kiddo!
--[FINRAL] Got you, Asta!
Jeez. Do you have any idea how
incredible you were out there?
I never doubted you,
not for a single second!
That was amazing!
I'm so glad you didn't
let the despair get you!
Damn. That shrimp's
got some serious guts.
[ASTA] Hey, um, you guys.
Please, stop!
I'm super hurt everywhere!
[VANESSA, FINRAL]
Oh. Sorry.
[laughs] They really did it!
They defeated that monster!
[YAMI] What the hell
kinda power was that?
[OCEAN DWELLER 49A]
Did you see what that kid did?
[OCEAN DWELLER 49B]
I thought we were done for!
[OCEAN DWELLER 49AA]
You saved us, Magic Knights!
[OCEAN DWELLER 49C]
Thank you!
So, how do everyone's
injuries look, Vanessa?
They're serious, but fortunately
not life-threatening.
Can you transport them with
a Spatial spell, Finral?
Sorry, not yet.
It's still going to be a while
before my magic's recovered.
[GAUCHE] Thanks a lot,
gutless good-for-nothing.
[yelps] You can't talk
to me like that.
I'm your superior!
Poor Kiato. Kahono, too.
I really hope they'll be okay.
[FINRAL]
Don't you think you should
be worrying about yourself?
Look how beat up you are.
You trusted us and
got torn to shreds.
Seriously, Asta,
what were you thinking?
Yeah, especially when
you're counting
on somebody as unreliable
as Finral here to back you up.
--[NOELLE] Yeah. Right.
--[GAUCHE, CHARMY] Right. Right.
Oh, wow. That's harsh.
I mean, sure, of course
I wanted to run away.
But once I saw you
out there, Asta,
my body moved on its own.
It was all you. You
refused to quit fighting.
You trusted us to keep you safe,
and because of that, we won.
Please, I don't know what
you guys are talking about.
You're senior squadmates,
handpicked by Yami himself.
'Course I trust you.
It really means a lot
to us that you do.
Yeah. I'm actually
tearing up here.
Your senior squadmates
are pretty awesome.
Personally, I think
we're lucky that Yami
picked you to be our new rookie.
Well... It's Yami.
Who else would pick him?
A kid with no magic.
Hey, Dorksta isn't the only
rookie he chose, you know.
Of course, Noelle!
I hear you were
pretty amazing, too!
Something about an incredibly
powerful attack spell.
Oh, yeah, it was awesome!
I've never seen anything
like your Sea Dragon's Roar!
Good. Now keep the
compliments coming.
[FINRAL]
Ooh, and you're cute, too!
[CHARMY]
A perfect royal!
Well, that has nothing to do
with my role in the battle,
but it's accurate, so I
suppose it's acceptable.
[NOELLE]
One more, maybe?
Hey.
[screams]
Stop it!
What sort of twisted
thoughts were you thinking?
[ASTA]
I wasn't thinking anything!
Oh. Sorry.
All right, everybody,
I say it's time to raise
a glass and celebrate
our glorious victory!
Now is not the time
to start drinking!
We've gotta find a way
to tie this guy up
and haul him outta here.
He's got a freaky
eye on his forehead,
he said some stuff
about my sword,
and he's a big shot in the
Eye of the Midnight Sun!
There's a lot we
need to ask him!
[VETTO whimpering]
[LICHT]
Vetto. Vetto.
Don't cry. It'll be all right.
[VETTO]
Did you see what they did?
Those humans tortured this
little bird. It's unforgivable!
[LICHT]
I chased those children away.
Let's head back and
patch this fellow up.
[VETTO]
Okay. I'm sorry, Licht.
You're always rescuing me.
Well, we're friends, right?
So I'm happy to.
Whenever you need me.
We're like this bird.
It's not strong, but it can
do something special--
it can fly.
As for us...
We have special magic powers
that the humans envy,
so they want to cause us pain.
Still, I think we may
be able to understand
each other better someday.
Okay. Then I think
so, too, Licht.
[VETTO] Hope. Such a fragile
thing, and so sweet.
That's what Licht was:
the personification of hope.
[VETTO]
And who stole that hope?
You filthy humans!
His power's back?
No way. We won!
[VETTO]
I'm taking you with me.
All of you. In fact,
I'm going to blow this
entire temple away!
No! What's going on?
[YAMI]
Damnit!
There's no way they're gonna
be able to stop
that monster now.
That does it! I'm
bustin' outta here!
Why bother trying?
[laughs]
[yelps]
[FINRAL]
We've seen this before.
Not even the Magic Knight
captains could stop it then.
It's like their leader's power,
except even more savage!
Is he going to self-destruct?
My threads are
already burning up,
and the power is
only increasing.
Damn. We can't get closer.
Listen, guys. This doesn't
change anything, okay?
Come on, send me at him.
No, no, no, no, no!
Never mind. Ignore me.
I almost chickened out again.
We've come this far.
We've got to see it through.
I'll tell you what, Finral:
help us pull this off,
and I'll go on a date with you.
A date, really?!
Now you're talkin'!
There must be something
left we can try!
I'm in.
No one keeps me from Marie
and gets away with it.
We're gonna destroy him,
and then I'm gonna
eat all the seafood
in this place!
I'm basically terrified.
But I'll do my best!
All right! Now come and get us!
[YAMI]
I miss anything?
Hey there, you dumbbells.
How's it goin?
[BLACK BULLS]
Captain Yami!
You-You really came for us!
How, though? Weren't you trapped
somewhere this entire time?
Some mage had me trapped
with Spatial Magic,
but I managed to
bust through it.
[YAMI]
Had to get a little forceful.
What do you mean by forceful?
It woulda been better if
you could've gotten here
a little bit earlier, though.
Shut up!
I've got my reasons,
thank you very much.
I can leave if I'm not wanted.
[BLACK BULLS]
Wha...?!
[ASTA]
Is Yami pouting?
Kiato! Kahono!
You poor things! It's all
my fault. That idiotic game!
And Gio.
You got dragged into
this mess just to humor
a foolish old man.
[GIFSO] I knew he was strong,
but using that kind of magic?
It's beyond what I'd expected.
He's some kind of
monster himself.
It's a good thing that
I decided to follow
my intuition and not let him
participate in the game.
Well, we don't exactly
have a lotta time, here.
Let's get this over with.
All right!
With Captain Yami here,
we're 100 times stronger!
No! A million times stronger!
Let's beat the snot
out of that guy!
Hey, where's this cockiness
coming from all of a sudden?
You gettin' a big head
now 'cause you thought
you could beat that guy?
What cockiness?
[YAMI] I can handle
this one on my own, kid.
[ASTA]
Huh?
[YAMI] You guys have already
risked your lives fighting him.
It's about time for your
captain to take a turn.
Finral.
Vanessa.
Noelle.
Gauche.
--[YAMI] Charmy.
--[CHARMY] Yay!
Who're you?
Yeah, hi, I'm Grey.
You guys, too, Magna, Luck.
Real good work, all of you.
[FINRAL]
Yami actually praised me!
[YAMI] Since you've
done so much already,
I'll handle the clean-up.
Ha. Who am I kidding?
This is the best part.
[YAMI] I meant it, though.
You all did a fine job.
You may be a bunch
of knuckleheads,
but you're the reason I
could push past my limits.
[BLACK BULLS gasp]
[YAMI] Made being stuck in
a little room with my back
against the wall worth it.
This spell reminds me
of something that freaky
beanpole guy would do, so I
can't say I'm a fan, but...
Don't waste your time!
You humans will taste despair!
Yes! Despair!
[YAMI] Would you shut up
about your damn
despair already, you freak?
However strong your magic might
be now, it doesn't matter!
'Cause this spell slashes
through dimensions!
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked.
Dimension Slash!
[VETTO gasps]
[YAMI] Thanks for
toughening up my squad.
Now goodbye, Mister Despair.
[FULL CAST]
Clover Clips!
[NARRATOR]
Yami Sukehiro.
The captain of the Black Bulls
Magic Knight squad
does most of his thinking
here, in the bathroom.
Our investigative team had
one question for him.
Well, because that's
where the toilet is.
But there's one important
thing to remember:
before you go, make sure
there's toilet paper.
People who go into a bathroom
with no toilet paper...
Well, they're like birds
with their wings clipped.
They will never
again venture out
into the wild blue yonder.
The boy's supposed to
be in charge of keeping
my paper well stocked,
but, he forgets a lot.
I've seen my share
of hell because of him,
but I've made sure to give him
even worse hell than that.
[NARRATOR] He went on
to speak at some length
about the importance of toilets.
Before we ended
our interview, however,
there was just one more thing
we had to ask the captain.
Captain! Please hurry!
How much longer are you
gonna be in there?
[YAMI] Shut up! You didn't
put in a new roll,
so now I can't leave!
That's it! I'm busting out!
[YAMI]
Please.
I can't sit back and do nothing
after you all fought so hard.
Black Clover , Page 50:
"End of the Battle,
End of Despair."
Now goodbye, Mister Despair.
It's so important,
I said it twice!