[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives a magicless
boy named Asta.
This brave young hero
devotes blood, sweat, and tears
to becoming the
next Wizard King.
Though Asta's situation
is practically unheard of,
there are others
residing in this kingdom
who possess at least
a tiny amount of mana,
yet can barely
use spells at all.
They make up a very
small minority,
living their lives
in the shadows.
[NARRATOR]
But, like everyone else,
they do their best to survive.
[NARRATOR] Let's turn
back time for a moment.
[SIONA grunting]
Poor girl. Damn those
Magic Knights.
What's her condition?
She appears to have
cracked several ribs.
[BOW] Shall I prepare
some pain medication?
Yes, she could use some.
[BOW]
Here you are.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
Here. Drink.
[KABWE] The pain should
eventually subside.
Okay.
So what should our
next move be?
Master Kabwe?
What exactly do you plan to do?
I'm going to kill the prisoner.
[gasps]
[DAZU]
No, not yet!
We have more important things
to worry about right now!
Like that book?
It needs to be dealt with, too,
lest our sacrifices be in vain.
Wait. "Dealt with" how?
[KABWE] They say that the devil
dwells in the five-leaf clover.
Let us be rid of this
accursed book at once.
Master Kabwe, please!
Why are you trying to stop me?
This wretched thing.
It couldn't possibly be
of further use to us.
[SECREÉ]
Wait.
I don't really care about
what you do to me,
but Asta needs that
book, so give it back.
[KABWE]
What a selfless request.
But when such words
come from lips
tainted by forbidden
magic, well...
I'd be a fool to listen.
[SIONA screams]
Siona. What's going on?
[KABWE]
Siona! Is she dead?
[thud]
[gasps] Onoby!
[KABWE]
No.
Damn you! Why betray us?
Have you still not
put it together?
I'll say it plainly.
The last thing we would want
is to see the devil banished.
We are the Devil Believers.
We're an order that
worships the devil.
That can't be true.
How can anyone worship
such pure evil?
No. You asked us to help
you destroy the devil!
If not that, then what
did you need us for?
[DAZU] You speak like we came
to you as supplicants in need,
but we simply took advantage
of your hatred for the devil.
In what way?
Well, seeing as you have access
to the Magic Parliament,
you've been privy to knowledge
that was kept from us peasants.
In addition to that,
it's helpful to have someone
who can actually use magic,
since we're dealing
with the Magic Knights.
[KABWE]
Someone who can use magic?
What are you talking about?
[DAZU]
Right. For somebody like you,
it must be difficult to fathom
that there are people like us
who are all but spurned by mana.
[DAZU] One hot summer day,
the neighborhood kids
asked me to do a favor for them.
[DAZU] They asked me to use
my catalyst magic to mix
both of their magics together
so we could all cool off.
[laughs]
[DAZU]
They seemed truly happy.
And seeing their faces
made me feel happy, too.
[DAZU] But then I overheard them
talking behind my back.
They said they were only acting
like my friends to impress
the adults, since I didn't
have any real friends.
[DAZU] They said it was because
I could barely use magic.
She's so creepy.
[CHILD 146A giggles]
[DAZU]
Then they just laughed.
People like us have
no place in this kingdom.
We've been told that
since we were children.
[grunts] You think
this will help you?
We do. Before now, it's been
like we didn't even exist.
But no more.
Despite the fact that he
doesn't have a single drop
of magic in his blood,
Asta wields power equal
to that of any great mage
by means of a grimoire
that hosts a devil.
So we'll imitate him.
We'll do whatever
we must to obtain
the devil's might for ourselves.
I will not allow that to happen!
Why, you...
[BOW]
Let's go.
Right.
[KABWE] No. I can't
let it end like this.
I'll find a way.
We're listening.
Where are you?
[KABWE groaning]
It's a lie.
These people aren't trying to
bring about the devil's demise.
Not at all.
The truth is that...
...they're after
the devil's power!
[ALL gasp]
What do you mean?
[KABWE] This organization
actually worships the devil.
They're called Devil Believers!
[KABWE]
Chairman Damnatio. I'm sorry.
I was a fool.
You must stop them.
Please, sir. For all of us.
What's wrong, Kabwe? Report!
Do you mind filling
us in on the details?
[JULIUS]
A devil-worshipping cult, huh?
Called the Devil Believers.
I don't think your
subordinates would help
that kind of group knowingly.
[DAMNATIO]
It's safe to assume
that they were being used
under false pretenses.
Those gullible idiots.
[YAMI] I get wantin'
to destroy a devil.
But who the hell would
decide to worship one?
These people are a bunch
of sickos if you ask me.
[knocking]
Excuse me.
We traced the Communication
Magic back to its source,
and it would appear
to have come from Tiulyu.
Well, that's a surprise.
Julius?
I order the Black Bulls
to travel to Tiulyu,
apprehend these
"Devil Believers,"
and save Nero
from their clutches.
You got it.
[YAMI] He must've used
the last of his strength
to grab that thing so he could
contact his former boss.
Was it an argument gone bad?
Nah, there'd be
signs of a struggle.
These guys didn't have
a chance to fight back.
So they just slaughtered
their own people?
S'like Chairman Chin-mole said,
they were bein'
played for fools.
They thought they
were fighting a devil.
Guess they must've
outlived their usefulness.
[GORDON]
Captain.
So creepy.
[GORDON]
A venomless viper.
Powdered long-necked
softshell turtle,
and the root of
a gorikabuto plant.
These ingredients are all
quite difficult to come by.
And knowing that...
[GORDON] We can assume that the
potion which put my best friend
Asta to sleep was
likely made here,
as were the potions used
at the execution site.
I would love to get more
information on the person
who lives here,
but the local villagers
seem to be pretty wary of us.
I can help you with that, sir.
[GORDON]
Granny Maggie? It's me.
Oh, hi, Gordon!
You brought some friends, eh?
This is Granny Maggie, everyone.
We got to know each other
and became friends
the last time we were here.
How goes it, Granny?
My name is Asta, ma'am!
It's an honor to meet you!
[MAGNA]
You're way too loud!
So are you, Magna.
Hold on.
Where is that mean-looking boy
who called me an angel?
Don't tell me you came all
this way and didn't bring him.
An angel?
[GORDON] Oh, if you mean
my best friend Gauche,
he's back at the capital
watching over his little sister.
Ah, well it's a relief to hear
he was able to
find the poor girl.
[GORDON]
Right?
[YAMI] I hate to rush
this cute little reunion,
but can we pick your
brain for a bit, granny?
We need info on the person
who lives in the forest
on the outskirts of town.
You talking about Bow?
[YAMI]
Yeah, prob'ly.
We need you to tell us
everything you know about Bow;
it's real important.
I can do that.
But next time you come around,
you bring that broody young
Gauche fellow with you.
[YAMI]
Oh, you got it.
[NOELLE]
She can barely use magic?
It's not actually all that rare.
Though I bet it seemed
that way to you, Noelle.
You can't really blame her.
I mean every single member
of her family's good at magic.
And Asta can't use it at all,
and she knows he's a freak.
This is all your fault.
My fault?!
[MAGGIE]
But...
Bow is also a wonderfully
skilled apothecary.
We don't go to a mage
with recovery magic
when we fall ill in this town.
Here in Tiulyu, the sickly
go straight to Bow,
with her expertly made medicine.
I could tell she was skilled
just by looking at her shelves.
I hear she worked hard
to become that good.
Perhaps we're all lucky
she couldn't use magic,
because that's what drove
her to develop such a skill.
Kind of sounds like a
certain meathead I know.
Uh--
Come to think of it,
you might want to hear about
Bow's good friend, Dazu.
She lost both her husband
and her mother-in-law
when those devil servants
attacked the town.
Where can we find her?
[MAGGIE] Like Bow,
Dazu can't really use magic.
But she never let
that get her down.
She's a wonderful girl
who's been through a lot.
You had better be nice
to her if you meet.
She got along very well
with her husband, Vide.
The two of them were as happy
as any couple I've seen.
Her husband's mother,
Meshu, would always talk
about what a wonderful
daughter-in-law she was.
[FINRAL]
Yami!
I think you should take
a look at this, sir.
[YAMI]
This woman.
Oh, yeah, I've seen her before.
Something's not
right about this.
Well, think about it.
The old lady was just going
on and on about how Dazu
and her husband
were deeply happy,
but that face looks
pretty dead inside.
Hang on.
Why would someone whose
family was killed by a devil
become one of the creeps
who worships a devil?
[JULIUS]
Nice work.
You're on the right path--
just keep flipping over rocks
until you find some worms.
[YAMI] Yeah, about that.
Honestly, I have my doubts.
And why is that?
The trail's gettin'
kinda cold is all.
I don't suppose you have any
other intel we can go off of.
[JULIUS]
Nothing solid.
I will say that the Devil
Believers sought out people
with the Magic Parliament
in the hopes of getting
sensitive information from them.
With that in mind, they
likely know that the devil
Megicula is in
the Spade Kingdom,
and that information probably
factors into their plans.
So what, you think they might
wanna offer Nero as a gift? Huh.
That reminds me, they still
have the kid's grimoire, too.
How could you forget
something that important?
Right. They probably wanted
to give you and the grimoire
to Megicula as some
kinda package deal.
[JULIUS]
Once they pay tribute,
they'll defect to
the Spade Kingdom.
Or rather, the devil inside it.
Okay, buy why?
[JULIUS] I doubt we can
answer that question
without asking these
people in person.
But in any case, we can
expect these cultists
to start moving north.
To reach the border,
they'll have to cut across
the Forsaken Realm.
Right. Good luck.
[YAMI]
Thanks.
Look sharp, dumbasses!
We're movin' out.
[BLACK BULLS]
Yes, sir!
[GAUCHE]
A mission?
That's right.
I can't.
[SISTER THERESA]
Neglecting your duties?
You must enjoy
disappointing your sister.
[GAUCHE]
Old hag?
Just what do you think
you're doing here?
[SISTER THERESA]
I think you know.
I'm here to rescue Marie
from her obsessive,
good-for-nothing brother.
No. My angel stays here.
What happened to her
before was a fluke.
I can guarantee
Marie's safety now.
Now get over yourself
and go do your job.
Shut your mouth, old hag!
There's no job
that's more important
than watching over Marie!
[SISTER THERESA]
And have you given any thought
to what would make Marie happy?
[MARIE]
Magic Knights are supposed
to keep people safe, right?
I was proud when I
found out my big brother
was going to be a Magic Knight,
and I wanna keep being proud
of you. So please, Gauche!
[GAUCHE] Tch. I'll listen
to you this time,
but don't get used to it.
I'm trusting you,
so you had better not
put Marie in danger again.
Get your ass over here.
She'll be safe with me.
[NARRATOR] And so, the Black
Bulls began their pursuit
of the Devil Believers,
who were thought to have fled
into the Forsaken Realm.
In case this thinking
had been in error,
the other Magic Knight
squads were sent out
to search the Common
Realm, far and wide.
[NARRATOR] But no matter how
diligently the Magic Knights
searched, they had no luck
finding the Devil Believers,
and several days passed
with no progress.
[YAMI] We've trekked through
half the Forsaken Realm
chasin' these jerks,
but we haven't caught
so much as a whiff
of their mana yet.
It's possible that they're using
some kind of devices to
keep their mana concealed.
The other squads haven't found
anything noteworthy either.
At this point,
I would assume they've
past the Forsaken Realm
and are bound for the
Spade Kingdom's border.
Sounds about right.
We've come across a few signs
that they passed
through ahead of us.
[JULIUS]
Signs?
[YAMI]
Yeah. Bunch'a weird crap.
[panting]
The locals at this village
say a bunch of their
people disappeared, too.
It's happening everywhere we go.
Do you think these Devil
Whatevers are behind it?
That'll be my guess
until I hear a better one.
[MAGNA] Hey! I got a
question for you guys.
Why the hell is everybody
so determined to avoid us?
It's due to what happened
with the Eye of
the Midnight Sun.
The people of the Forsaken Realm
have had it quite rough.
Almost everyone here feels
like the Magic Knights
left them high and dry.
And at least a few
of these people believe
that the Magic Knights
were behind the attacks.
[BOY 146A] I'll do what I want!
You can't make me stay!
[MOM 146A]
Please, don't do this!
[BOY 146A]
Stop trying to keep me here.
You've already made me
late to the meet-up!
Everyone else is already there.
I have to leave right now!
You think they'll heal your leg
with the devil's power?
Do you know how
ridiculous that sounds?
Why would you think
that's possible?
[BOY 146A] I don't "think"
it is, I know it is!
I mean, there's a guy who
doesn't have any magic at all,
and with the devil's powers,
he was able to get into
the Magic Knights!
[MOM 146A] But the boy was put
on trial for using those powers.
[BOY 146A]
What do I care?
Once I have the devil's powers,
I won't have to be scared
of trials or anything else!
Now let me go!
[MOM 146A] No, don't!
Someone stop him! Please!
[DAD 146A]
What the--?
Hold it right there! Hey!
You had better explain why your
mother's on the ground. Now.
Just let go of me.
I have to leave right now,
no matter what!
They're all waiting for me
just outside of town!
[MAGNA]
Yup. We're makin' our way
from Hecairo straight
up to the border.
[YAMI]
There are two big rivers
that flow into each other
there, is that right?
Yeah.
I don't see any people though.
[MAGNA]
Well...
This is proof that we're still
on their trail, at least.
Hey, you're not lettin'
what that kid said
bug you, right?
Oh, come on, Magna.
Do I look like I'm upset?
Yeah, you do.
Uh, how do I put this?
That poor kid's really
struggling with his leg,
so it makes sense that he would
do anything to try and heal it.
Right?
And these Devil Believers
are preying on that.
They're at least pretending
to be a ray of hope
for people like him.
These people have
nowhere left to turn.
They've run out of options,
so they'll take a deal
too good to be true.
Yeah, well, anyway.
We've gotta do something
about them, fast.
[YAMI] The area past Breed
Mountain heading toward
the Spade Kingdom has
some volatile mana.
The weather tends
to get real rough.
Odds are they'll probably
have to stop and wait it out.
[MAGNA]
Roger that.
[YAMI]
There's backup on the way.
But I want you three to race
ahead and scout 'em out.
We can't let 'em
cross the border.
Understood?
[GROUP]
Sir!
[ASTA]
Nero...
Ah, crap!
[ASTA]
Whoa!
Come on, Magna, can't you
fly this thing any steadier?
You're kiddin' me, right?
[MAGNA] It's gonna be pretty
difficult to catch them
if they managed to make it past
Breed Mountain in this weather.
[gasps] Look down there.
I think I see them!
How are there so many?
This is insane.
[ASTA]
We finally caught up with them!
And they really are heading
to the Spade Kingdom!
Black Clover , Page 147:
"Prepared to Die."
We can't wait
for reinforcements!
Don't worry, Nero.
We'll save you!