[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until
a lone mage stepped forward
and took up the fight.
[NARRATOR] The hero's name was
Lumiere Silvamillion Clover.
He was later hailed
as the First Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
[ASTA grunting]
Sorry, Asta, but if you can't
keep up, I'm ditching you.
[ASTA] You should know
that's never gonna happen!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
You're just a human,
yet you're using elven and
spirit power to fight me.
[BOTH yelling]
"Sto--"
[YAMI]
Mana Zone:
Dark Cloaked Dimension
Slash, Equinox!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL groans]
[ALL gasp]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL groaning]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Dark Magic can interfere
with the other world!
Curse that human!
[ASTA]
Right here, right now.
I'm going to push
past my limits!
[KOTODAMA DEVIL screams]
[KOTODAMA DEVIL]
Impossible!
This can't be. Inconceivable!
It can't be. I won't have it!
--[ANTI-MAGIC DEVIL cackles]
--[KOTODAMA DEVIL gasps]
[ANTI-MAGIC DEVIL] You got
a problem there, comrade?
Don't give me that!
Who are you? Tell me!
[cackles] You don't
need to know that.
It doesn't matter
how powerful you are,
you've lost this fight,
and you're about
to disappear for good!
Farewell, you disgrace.
[KOTODAMA DEVIL
gasping, groaning]
We... won.
[gasps]
I'm grateful.
[panting]
[CHARLOTTE]
That terrible magic...
It vanished! Did they stop him?
[YAMI grunts]
It looks like somebody
beat me to the punch,
but I'm glad to see
the job got done.
[CHARLOTTE]
You did well, human.
Actually, the name's
Yami Sukehiro.
Prickly Princess Two.
For the last time,
call me Charla.
[BOTH gasp]
[PATRY] Oh, no! His magic's
not completely gone.
It's consuming everything!
This place is about to crumble!
[BOTH gasp]
[YUNO]
We have to get out, now!
But what about everyone else?
[LUMIERE] I think my body
is reaching its limit.
There's not much time!
The light is starting
to grow dimmer.
What gives? I feel
all creepy-crawly!
My connection to
Licht tells me...
...the only way out is on
the top floor! Let's go!
[YAMI]
We can't get up there!
If we don't figure this
out quick, then we're screwed.
That ki.
[LICHT]
Lumiere?
The light, it's fading!
[yelps]
This is bad.
[gasps]
You guys!
[ALL yelling]
[NOELLE gasps]
Hey, it's you!
You're all okay!
And, man, talk
about good timing!
[NOELLE] Stop clinging to me
like that, you idiot!
Back off!
[ASTA]
I'm sorry!
[VALTOS] It seems the
person I put my faith in
was nothing but a pitiful
sinner, just as I am.
Now, I must make amends
for the wrong I've done.
If such a thing
is even possible.
You two again?
Well this guy
doesn't speak for me!
I've never been wrong
once in my life!
If you were here, you could've
at least helped us out!
Hey, don't you judge me!
I do whatever I want,
when I want!
[PATRY]
There's one more thing
I need to do before
this is over.
What d'ya know?
Just when I least expected it,
a boneless ham goes flyin' by.
That little spell of yours
might make your body
invisible to the naked eye,
but I can sense your
ki plain as day.
We gotcha now.
It's Captain Yami!
And the Blue Rose
Knights captain!
And that guy.
He used to lead
the Purple Orcas!
How dare you treat me
like this after
all the suffering
I've had to endure?
[ASTA]
Hey, wait, you're that jerk
who stole my grimoire
forever ago!
Revchi!
[ASTA] What the heck are
you two clowns doin' here?
[REVCHI]
At least we have magic power!
How impressive!
So many mages with so many
different types of spells!
I think the Clover Kingdom
is in good hands.
Enough chit-chat--
let's get going!
I'll never let you out
of my sight again, Yuno!
Hands off him,
Little Miss Fivehead!
Oh. Charmy, you changed
back to your normal self.
That was so cool when you turned
all tall and tough before.
And your powers
were super awesome!
Huh? I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm sexy, tall,
and long-legged 24/7!
What?
Wait. She didn't
notice what happened?
Better question, why
is Charmy here at all?
'Cause wherever there's
Yuno and yummy nummies,
I'm bound to pop up eventually!
Just so you know, lady,
I'm still going to slash you up!
Kyah!
What's wrong with
this guy? He's creepy!
Settle down.
There's no time
for idle chatter.
Remember, this isn't over yet.
[ASTA grunts, gasps]
[NOZEL] We have to stop the
elves from destroying
the kingdom.
They're still being driven
by deep-seated hatred,
completely detached
from their real souls.
There are so many.
How can we overpower them all?
I'll knock them out
with one good punch.
[YAMI] Somethin' tells me
she actually could, too.
Oh, man.
[ASTA] I won't be able
to get to everybody
with just one sword.
Not to mention,
my power's running low.
[PATRY]
Licht is here now.
There's a way.
William is still lying
dormant within me.
With his World Tree Magic,
we can gather mana and life
force from people all over.
To make that happen, we're
going to need his grimoire.
[growls]
Take it.
This is the one.
Valtos, thank you.
It doesn't matter who you are.
You're still the
person who found me
that day and saved my life.
Hang on. Are you saying that...?
[PATRY]
Yes. Asta.
Use that weapon to
destroy me for good.
Sure that's what you want?
I've already lived twice now.
I have regrets, but no fear.
After all that I did,
I'm not sure this is
enough to atone for it.
Patry...
I'll be the first one
to leave, then.
Forgive me, Licht.
Please finish this.
I will.
[PATRY] In the end, I got
to fight alongside Licht
and all my friends.
That's enough.
It's Captain Vangeance.
Patry.
[WILLIAM] The lonely soul
who's been with me
ever since I was a child.
It seems your rage and suffering
have finally reached an end.
But, the story's not over yet.
This time, it's my turn.
This mark that was carved
upon my face without reason.
The curse that brought me
so much mistreatment and hatred.
Because of it, his warped
feelings for the kingdom
and the suffering
he went through
were undoubtably real to me.
This battle happened
because I was too weak
to believe in Julius's strength,
or in the future
I was meant to protect.
Therefore...
I should be the one who puts
a stop to this violence!
[LICHT] I'll connect to their
souls and tell them the truth.
[MAGIC KNIGHTS gasping]
[gasps]
[WILLIAM] We need to lure
the connected souls
to the World Tree
and bind them together!
[WILLIAM, LICHT]
Combo Spell:
Demon-Dweller Sword
Spirit Light Tree.
[BOTH gasp]
Now, Anti-magic wielder!
Use the Demon-Destroyer Sword!
[NOZEL] The power of that blade
is reaching all of the elves.
[VILLAGER 120A]
Look! Up there!
That's the magic of the
Golden Dawn's captain!
[VILLAGER 120AA]
Beautiful.
[VILLAGER 120B] Does this mean
that they saved the kingdom?
I shoulda known.
Apparently, the three of us
won't be going with you.
See, after we got reincarnated
the second time,
our souls became bound
to these bodies.
There's no way we can go
back to our original forms.
I see. That's a shame.
After a journey filled
with pain and hatred,
it'd be nice if we could talk.
But, nothing to be done now.
Perhaps there's a reason our
destinies played out this way.
Live on in this world,
for all of our sakes.
Goodbye.
Take care.
That figures. We missed
each other again.
But if this is what
you want, then okay.
I guess I'll live this
life to the fullest,
no matter how much
of a pain it is.
[CHARLOTTE] I wish I'd seen
my younger brother again.
But I enjoyed fighting
with you, Yami Sukehiro.
Well, look at you, Charla,
turnin' all nice and
honest at the end.
That's sweet.
I admit, I may be
a little awkward,
but not as awkward as she is.
I suppose I'd better
be going now.
I wouldn't want to keep my
dear Tetia waiting any longer.
[LUMIERE]
Right.
[LICHT] I'm happy we got to see
a glimpse of the ideal future
that we'd always hoped for.
Me, too.
The elf that's in my body.
Is he your...?
[LICHT]
With you here,
it felt like I got to
fight alongside my son.
Thank you, wielder of
the four-leaf grimoire.
May good luck always follow you.
This is yours, right? Take it.
Actually, the five-leaf grimoire
belongs to you now, Asta.
Hold on tight to it.
It will prove helpful
on your journey.
[BOTH gasp]
[LICHT]
Farewell.
And thank you, mages
of the Clover Kingdom.
[RADES] Not so fast!
Hold on a damn second!
Wraith Magic: Soul Abductor.
[RADES] I can only use
this spell on somebody
who's been a part of
my life for a long time.
And, ironic as it is,
you fall into that category.
[gasps]
[RHYA]
The body that held Licht's soul
has magic in it again?
But wait, that mana... Patry?
Am I... reborn? No, reanimated!
That body was only a
duplicate that Sally created
to look like your
original one, anyway.
I'm sure you'll feel
right at home in it.
Hey, what the heck
are you doing?
Shut up, would you?!
This is... I, uh...
Look, I don't understand
it either, all right?
Anyway, Licht, or,
Patry, or whoever!
I'm not just gonna
let you disappear
and live happily
ever after! No way!
I won't ever forgive what
you did! That's why...
...I want you to spend
the rest of eternity
thinking about all the
humans you trampled on!
--Including me!
--[gasps]
[ASTA] Uh, hey, that might
come back to bite you later.
[RADES]
Quiet!
Rades. I feel like
I should thank you,
since you've given me
the chance to atone.
Shut your mouth!
I'll have your head if
it's the last thing I do.
And until that day,
I want you to spend your
life in constant fear!
Let's go, Valtos!
[RHYA] Wow. So, after
all that, you didn't even
get to go back with
Licht like you wanted.
Ain't that just the way.
It's only fair, though.
Rhya.
[PATRY gasps]
It's you.
I never expected we'd see
each other face to face.
Neither did I.
[WILLIAM] My closest companion
who shares my sin.
There was so much that
I wanted to tell you.
But first, this.
He may not listen, but I
owe someone an apology.
I know this is a selfish
thing to ask you,
but, Yami, please take me
to see Julius at once.
Of course.
[gasps]
[ASTA]
The Wizard King.
[LUMIERE]
The long battle is finally over.
Ow, ow! I've been in so
much pain this whole time!
I'm gonna die!
Oh, you poor thing,
that sounds terrible!
Maybe you'll remember
this next time
you're about to do something
reckless and stupid.
From the bottom of my heart,
I can't thank you all enough.
The spell has been lifted,
despite that devil's
best efforts.
And with another
devil's power, no less!
[ASTA]
...it hurts like crazy!
[SECRÉ]
You broke the seal a while ago,
and you're just now
starting to feel the pain?
Quite impressive.
By the way, Asta,
who are those two people?
Who is that man?
I know it sounds crazy,
but he almost looks like
the statue of the
First Wizard King
come to life or something.
Well, I think that's pretty much
what happened, actually.
[BOTH]
Really?
[ASTA] You were awakened
by magic, right?
Oh, man, I can't wait
to be a super-awesome
Wizard King just
like you someday!
And guess what else?
That's Nero!
[NOELLE]
The bird?
Wow, Asta, you must
have hit your head
--pretty hard if you think that.
--[SECRÉ] It's true.
[NOELLE, MIMOSA]
What?!
You know...
I always thought you were
a pretty cool little bird,
but now that I know you can
turn yourself into a human,
I think you might be the
coolest bird that ever lived!
I didn't transform
into a human.
I was a human to begin with.
Then why didn't you
tell me before?
Because up until the
Shadow Palace appeared,
I wasn't able to talk.
[SECRÉ] Now, I have a
question to ask you.
What makes you
think you can ever
hold a candle to His Highness?
Look, I know we're old pals,
but please cut that out!
[NOELLE] So, the spunky,
adorable Nero is...
Well, she's spunky and adorable.
[sighs] Well, to me,
"Wizard King"
is nothing but a simple phrase.
But thanks to you
and your rival,
it's become clear to me
that our ideals
live on with this
generation, as well.
Now then.
Which one of you
will take my place?
[ASTA]
Ooh, ooh, that'll be me, sir!
[SECRÉ] You're nothing
compared to him, Asta.
[ASTA]
You're mean!
[laughs]
[gasps]
The time has come.
I don't have enough magic
to hold this body
together anymore.
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
[MIMOSA] My Recovery Magic
can't fix this!
My prince.
[LUMIERE]
Secré. Or, Nero, I suppose.
Will you watch their
futures play out?
Watch them make the
world better, for my sake?
I've always been...
Well, um... I mean...
Anyway. Let me go
with you! Please, sir!
I gave everything 500 years ago.
I should have died that day.
But then, you helped
me protect the future.
Let me go.
Like I said, I can't let you
seal off your potential.
[LUMIERE] I think the path
ahead is a bright one.
Both for the Magic Knights
and for the kingdom
they'll fight to defend.
I even met my descendants.
I'm happy.
So am I, really!
Serving you for so long...
It... It was an honor!
I was honored
to have you. Secré.
Thank you for everything.
You did well. Goodbye.
What the hell is this?
Julius's body is missing!
[YAMI] But I know it
was hidden in there.
[gasps]
[YAMI]
That magic!
[YAMI gasps]
What? No way! Are you Julius?
[YAMI]
The long night's finally over.
Look at that gorgeous sunrise!
It's the new dawn
of the Clover Kingdom.
Black Clover , Page 121:
"Three Problems."
Damn, this old dude's
off his rocker.