[NARRATOR]
Threatened by a ruthless demon,
humanity was on the
brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone
mage stepped forward
and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was
hailed as the Wizard King,
and his story became legend.
The names of those who had
passed the Royal Knights
Selection Exam
were finally announced.
Zora, who'd also passed,
was late to the ceremony.
With the inclusion of three
additional members,
Shiren Tium, Cob Portaport,
and Nozel Silva,
Captain of the Silver Eagles,
the ranks of the Royal Knights
would now boast a total
of 20 elite warriors.
[MEREOLEONA]
Victory is all we need!
The Eye of the Midnight Sun
is a contemptible
terrorist organization!
If we don't pull it up
by the roots ourselves,
our nation will
never know peace!
Rest assured, we will
be making our way
to their base immediately!
Listen up!
It lies in the floating
dungeon found within
the strong magic region
called Gravito Stones!
[LEOPOLD]
It's nice of you to stop by,
even though we're rivals.
According to my sister,
you two were scrappy enough
to be selected for the
Royal Knights, very impressive!
Yeah! And we're
about to take down
the Eye of the Midnight Sun!
We're departing in three days.
Until then, we're staying
in the capital to keep info
from leaking.
Gotcha.
[NOELLE]
So, um...
How's Fuegoleon doing?
He's still unconscious.
After the capital was attacked,
he was abducted.
They must've done
something to him,
but we never figured
out what it was.
Whatever it is, it's bad.
Though, if he were conscious,
I know exactly how he'd react.
He'd say, "I failed to
overpower my opponent
because I'm lacking experience."
Either way, it's not
the end for me.
I'll train harder and
surpass you both.
Watch me!
Wow, Leopold.
I'll get revenge for
Captain Fuegoleon.
Don't worry about that!
Unlike most people,
he didn't laugh at my dream
of becoming the
next Wizard King.
He even called me a rival!
I am who I am now 'cause Captain
Fuegoleon believed in me.
And so am I.
There isn't any shame
in being weak, girl.
The shame is in staying weak.
What he said helped
me to grow stronger.
Asta. Noelle.
I'm counting on you.
Trust me! We're gonna bring
peace to the Clover Kingdom!
By stopping the Eye
of the Midnight Sun!
[ASTA] We gotta fight
together soon too, Leo!
[LEOPOLD]
You're on, pal!
Careful out there.
--[ASTA] Right!
--[NOELLE] We'll be back.
So Captain Fuegoleon and
Finral are both unconscious now.
I hope they wake up
before too much longer.
Actually, the way
that mana felt before...
It might have had something
to do with the Eye of the
Midnight Sun.
We've got to defeat them fast.
You're right.
But you know, there's somethin'
that's been buggin' me
for a long time now.
[NOELLE]
Huh?
Well, back when I was
fighting that big hairy guy.
He said they'd never forgive us.
That we're fighting because
we have a grudge.
So, does that mean if
we forgave each other
we wouldn't have to fight?
But who is "we"?
I don't know! It feels like
the more I talk about this,
the more I confuse myself!
That's because you're an
idiot who's trying to be deep.
[ASTA]
I'm not an idiot!
Hey, wait, come to think
of it, Captain Yami
said the exact same thing!
Okay, I'll clear my head
with some strength training!
Crunches!
[grunting]
And I gotta do a few
back extensions too!
You stupid brute.
[ASTA yells]
Ow, so many cramps!
[yelling]
[YUNO]
Unbelievable.
[ASTA]
Huh? Oh, look!
Yuno, Mimosa,
and Specs are here!
Did all of you come here to
visit Captain Fuegoleon too?
No. I'm afraid not.
Oh, Asta!
Are you all right?
[ASTA laughs]
Yup, don't worry about me.
I've trained every
last muscle in my body
so I'd be ready for anything!
Well, you obviously
forgot to strengthen your brain.
Yeah, you're right, my brain's
still pretty weak and flabby.
Hey! That's not fair!
If there's a spell that
makes a person smarter,
can somebody cast it on Asta?
[BELL]
You're so thoughtful, Yuno!
[ASTA] Don't ask people
to do stuff for me!
I'm sorry.
I don't know one.
[ASTA]
Aw, that's too bad.
Back to business.
The decisive battle is at hand,
but you don't seem
nervous at all.
What'll we do if an enemy
spy happens to find us out?
[BOTH gasp]
A spy, huh?
[gasping]
It's certainly a
possibility, after all.
Think of the individuals
who bribed the Captain
of the Purple Orcas
and opened up
the royal capital to attack.
No amount of caution
would be unwarranted.
I guess not.
We'll be on guard.
Anyway, if all of us are
headed into the capital,
want a lift?
We'll take my vessel.
[ASTA gasps]
Are you sure you don't mind?
[NOELLE]
If you insist.
[ASTA]
Yummy!
The food really is way
better in the capital, huh?
[MIMOSA]
Oops. You silly.
There's some sauce on your face.
[gasps]
I'm so sorry, that was far
too presumptuous!
It's cool. Thanks a lot!
Don't stuff your face.
You're supposed to be
on alert, remember?
And you're definitely not
supposed to be getting
your face wiped by a--
I mean, not like I care.
Do whatever you want,
stupid dorksta!
Look, I promise you guys,
I'm totally on the ball!
I'm not piggin' out.
I normally eat twice this much!
[choking]
Unbelievable.
I'm concerned.
It's not just Asta.
They may be talented,
but some of the Royal Knights
have... issues.
[LUCK laughs]
I can't wait to start fighting!
I'll pulverize those
Midnight Sun guys
till they're black and blue!
[RILL]
Huh?
Zora's all by himself!
He's probably too shy
to strike up a conversation.
Maybe I can bring him
out of his shell!
Look what I can do!
Hey, I'm Zora Ideale!
[RILL]
Huh?
[yells]
Ew! Gross! [groans]
Oh, no, Captain Rill!
Do none of you worms
have any manners?
When you're eating a meal,
you're supposed to enjoy it
in the most graceful
and beautiful fashion
you possibly can.
Running away from my fork
because you do not desire
for me to consume you?
What a decidedly
unbeautiful thing you are.
That's my brethren, you monster!
[HAMON chuckles]
Ladies and gentlemen,
it seems Puli would like
to entertain us with
an original song!
♪ Ha... ha! ♪
♪ Puli, Puli Puli,
beautiful and sweet! ♪
My ears! What's happening?!
This is the worst song
I've ever heard!
I hate to be rude,
but I'm filled with the urge
to kill someone.
[ASTA]
Ugh! Shut up already!
[MALE SPY MAGE]
Argh!
I'll never get any valuable
intel as long as I'm
stuck to him!
♪ Puli Puli yay! ♪
Nozel, what is it you'd
like to discuss with me?
The fact that we're
taking three days
to set our plan into motion.
Isn't that too cautious?
What are you implying?
Do you think I'm some
kind of paranoid coward?
No.
It appears that my
reservations were unfounded.
Heh. Somebody's a fast learner.
I've set a trap to find out the
extent to which the enemy
knows our movements.
Everything's under control.
Now then.
I have a question, too.
Did you really believe
you could deceive me
with such an insipid spell?
[MALE SPY MAGE gasps]
[MALE SPY MAGE grunts]
Damn it! [grunting]
End of the line, spy.
[ASTA gasps] He's from the
Eye of the Midnight Sun?
Wow, so they did have spies!
What a rotten trick!
Hey, you. Newbie!
Apparently, he chose
you to be his conduit
so he could tail us
on our mission.
I can't believe I never noticed
that there was something amiss!
What an absolute disgrace.
[MEREOLEONA] I've questioned
this rodent within an inch
of his life,
and I've concluded that
the enemy is not yet
aware of our activities.
Therefore...
I have moved up
the date of departure.
Which means we storm
their hideout first thing
in the morning!
Wait. So soon?
But I thought we had three days!
No way. I don't want to let
Yuno see what I look like
as soon as I wake up!
I want everyone at their best,
so get plenty of rest tonight.
That is all.
If you ask me, it seems
like Captain Mereoleona
must've been planning
from the very beginning
for us to leave immediately
if she caught an enemy
sneaking around.
Well, they do say that
to fool your enemies,
sometimes you must begin
by fooling your friends.
But still, we head
out in the morning?
[ZORA chuckles] That Captain's
really somethin' else.
What's got you so
upset, little fella?
Are you startin' to get scared?
It's the opposite.
I want to become
the Wizard King.
So that I can bring peace and
freedom to the Clover Kingdom.
I want everybody to smile!
They can't wreck our country.
I won't let them!
Make sure you don't wreck our
country by messing things up.
You won't get the best
of me either, Yuno!
Heh. I'm going to win.
Well, here we go.
Right.
Tomorrow's the day.
We'll finally put
an end to all this.
The Royal Knights...
...will defeat the Eye
of the Midnight Sun!
[ASTA] Check that out!
It's a floating castle!
[NOELLE]
This is it.
We're at the Eye of the
Midnight Sun's hideout.
[MEREOLEONA] There are few
people who would venture into
a strong magic area
like this in the first place.
And with the added obscurity
from that magical mist,
even those brave enough to
seek it would have a hard time
finding it.
Let me guess, that line of
thinking was what helped you
pinpoint the location,
wasn't it,
Captain of the Silver Eagles?
I must say, I'm impressed.
The discovery was nothing but
a stroke of luck, I'm afraid.
I was investigating a dungeon
when I discovered the location
of their hideout.
Really?
And would you care to
tell me your reasoning
for coming out here with us?
There's hardly time
for chit-chat.
Shiren, I believe your usual
spell will work from here.
Of course.
Stone Creation Magic.
Stone Model of the
World, materialize!
Awesome!
Yes, I see.
This place is structured like
an anthill that we can enter
from any angle.
It should be fairly
easy to invade.
There are mages wielding
senior-level magic power
scattered throughout.
And someone more powerful
in the larger, central space.
I would assume
that's their leader.
Yeah, that's Licht.
No doubt about it.
Nozel, sir.
What is our battle
strategy going to be?
I'm the Captain of the Silver
Eagles, not the Royal Knights.
That's a question
for Mereoleona.
Oh. Right, I'm sorry.
Listen carefully!
The best way to beat them
is to cause confusion
with a surprise attack.
Usually, we'd enter
separately to keep them
from anticipating our moves.
But, having so many points
of entry means the opponent
is likely to be confident
in their defenses.
The more spread out we are,
the easier it will be
for them to overpower
us instead.
Which means, the most
logical tactic is--
[ASTA]
I know!
We just have to psych ourselves
up so we can fight these guys
even harder!
I can take care of them myself.
No psyching up necessary.
I'll beat 'em senseless and
crush their bones into powder!
I shall use my immaculate
power to clear them out
in one beautiful swoop!
Please just disappear.
I'm surrounded by morons.
Balance is key.
If the idea is to break up their
numbers and still be able
to overcome them, then the
best plan is to split into
teams of four.
Don't you agree, Captain?
Wholeheartedly.
So we'll divide into five teams
of four and make our move.
As long as I'm not
stuck on the same team
as this obnoxious rugrat,
I guess I'll be all right
with anything.
Look, just because
your mask is cool
doesn't mean you get to be rude!
Plus, you're the obnoxious
one around here!
Oh. Then again, I don't think
anybody's gonna wanna work
with you anyway, so I
guess I'll be a nice person
and let you be
a part of my team.
You'll change your tune
when I save your weak ass
from certain death.
You problem children
are on my team.
Behave yourselves.
At your service, Lady Royal.
In fact, I hope you'll accept
this rainbow stinkbug
as a token of our acquaintance.
Don't do it!
[ZORA grunts]
Such a feeble odor isn't
nearly enough to disarm me.
[ASTA whimpers]
Great, but are you
sure commoners like us
would be fit to accompany
a lady of your noble status?
Whoa, I didn't know you
were a commoner just like me!
Whether a person is
a royal or a commoner,
social status doesn't make the
least bit of difference to me.
What does matter is whether
you're strong or weak.
And you're both here because
you're strong, are you not?
[MEREOLEONA]
Two fools, chosen by Yami.
I hope for your sakes
you do not disappoint me.
Yes, ma'am!
Yeah, we'll do our best
to come back in one piece.
Is that good enough for ya?
You should all be proud
that you were selected
to be our Royal Knights.
Now go use your
skills to the fullest!
I've assigned your teams.
Team One will charge in
from the upper left!
Yes, ma'am!
Of course.
[MEREOLEONA]
Team Two, take the lower left!
Yes, ma'am!
[MEREOLEONA] Team Three,
cover the upper right!
Yes, ma'am!
[MEREOLEONA]
Team Four, take the lower right!
Yes, ma'am!
And we three members of Team
Five will attack them head on.
Ma'am!
[ZORA chuckles]
[MEREOLEONA]
Spatial mage, remain on standby!
Absolu-lu-lutely, that
won't be a problem at all!
Give it everything
you've got, Knights.
Here we go!
[FEMALE PRISONER 88A whimpering]
[MALE MAGE 88A]
You foolish girl.
You do know how you got
into this mess, don't you?
The thing is...
You're a resident of
the Clover Kingdom.
And up until recently,
that applied to me too.
But me...
I was a bit different.
You see, I had my true
name bestowed upon me
by Master Licht.
What I mean is...
We're special, and you're not.
[FEMALE PRISONER 88A whines]
[MALE MAGE 88A]
In other words...
You're nothing but trash.
And so we can treat
you how we want.
[stones rumble]
[LUCK sighs]
That was way too easy.
They have stronger
guys here, right?
I have some
beautiful work to do,
so try not to pick them
all off on your own.
Are you all right?
I can't thank you enough.
A team like you shouldn't need
a fully detailed battle plan.
Eliminate any who
dare get in your way
as you head toward the center.
And of course...
The method is up to you!
As long as you win, I couldn't
care less how you do it.
[MEREOLEONA] The ants are
coming out of the woodwork.
[ASTA coughing]
You've got some nerve.
Swooping in when I wasn't around
and rampaging all over
the royal capital.
You may have managed
to escape from us
during that encounter
in the cave,
but this time is different.
Eye of the Midnight Sun,
this is the end for you.
You'll pay, right now!
This is for my rival.
[MEREOLEONA]
This is for my brother!
[NOZEL, MEREOLEONA]
Fuegoleon!
Make no mistake,
your leader's head will be mine!
[MAGES yelling]
Whoa! Crazy!
I feel like she doesn't
even need our help!
[RHYA groans]
Apparently, we have a real
tricky bunch on our hands.
Seeing as Licht isn't around.
This is gonna be a pain.
Guess I'll have to suck it up.
[GROUP]
Clover Clips!
[RHYA]
"Pain-ful Rhya!"
[MALE MAGE 88B]
Master Rhya, Master Rhya!
[RHYA yawns]
Yeah, what are you
so freaked out over?
Intruders!
[RHYA]
Seems that way, doesn't it?
But fighting them off
would be a huge pain,
so I'm just gonna stay here.
Stay here?
Sir, we need you!
Getting up is a pain, though.
Then I'll help you to your feet!
Putting on my shoes is a pain.
[MALE MAGE 88B]
I'll take care of it!
[RHYA]
Standing's a pain, too.
Allow me.
Walking's even more of a pain.
All right, forget it.
I'm not going out.
Really?
Please reconsider, sir!
[RHYA yawns]
I must've slept
with my mouth open,
because my throat is
feeling kinda scratchy now.
Here's a sucker for you.
What flavor is it?
Uh, it's apple...?
This fight'll be a pain,
but guess I'll suck it up.
[MALE MAGE 88B] What would've
happened if it were
orange-flavored?
[RHYA]
You know...
I wonder how Valtos and
the others are doing right now.
Black Clover. Page 89.
"The Black Bulls' Hideout."
Make sure you find what
you're looking for, okay, Valty?
[yawns]