[NARRATOR]
The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where
magic is everything,
there lives one boy
who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
[NARRATOR]
His strength and determination
helped him become
a Magic Knight.
And despite the many
challenges he faces,
he aims for the top
and refuses to give up!
Rich or poor,
royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove
that to the whole world,
and to become the
next Wizard King!
[ASTA]
Yuno.
You and me: we're family, right?
[YUNO]
Yeah, of course.
[ASTA] Not by blood
or anything, though.
[YUNO]
Right.
But we're closer
than a lot of people
who are related
by blood, aren't we?
I guess so.
Why, what's up?
[ASTA]
I was thinking.
You and me: we don't
have any real relatives,
but we've got a lot
of great friends.
I say we take all
the friends we meet,
and we make them
our family instead!
Yeah!
[KLAUS]
Hmph.
Tch.
[HAMON] I take it you three
are here to give reports, too.
[KLAUS]
Indeed.
We just finished
a mission in Kiten.
Ah, yes!
Kiten borders the Diamond
Kingdom, so the cultural
juxtaposition makes it
a popular spot for gourmets.
You're lucky!
I wish I could've gone there
instead of patrolling
the capital.
[LETOILE]
We're not on vacation, David.
[LETOILE] All these missions
must be wearing you down.
[YUNO]
I'm fine.
[HAMON laughs]
In times like this,
it's important to
get enough calories!
Would you like a snack?
[YUNO]
No thanks.
[MIMOSA] Why are we
just making small talk?
[ALECDORA] There's that
cocky attitude again.
He always said he'd
become the Wizard King,
but after his success
in that last battle,
he became even more arrogant.
If only I hadn't been
possessed by that elf,
I could've been useful
to Lord Vangeance!
Yuno just got lucky,
that was all!
[LETOILE]
The Captain's waiting.
Let's go in.
[DAVID]
Sounds good!
Yuno. I think you need to try
being a little bit friendlier.
What? I'm friendly.
[KLAUS]
He doesn't know.
Well, sure, there's
nothing wrong
with the way you are now,
but it might be nice
if you'd consider smiling
every now and then,
or throw in a joke
here and there.
But I can't even picture
what that would be like,
so just forget I brought it up.
Sure.
We'll go one step at a time.
I suppose.
[BELL] But that's what
makes Yuno so cool!
[WILLIAM] Thank you all
for your reports.
Klaus, Mimosa, Yuno.
The residents of Kiten
have expressed
their thanks to us again.
You obviously did quite well.
Sir!
We're honored to
hear that, Captain.
[ALECDORA grunts]
[WILLIAM] Now, I realize
you've only just returned,
but I have another
mission for you.
Apparently, a herd of wild boars
came down from the mountains,
posing a threat
to Saussy Village.
I'd ask another squad
to take care of it instead,
but no one's available.
I'll do it myself, sir!
A few wild boars would
be nothing for me!
These aren't normal boars.
According to the reports
we got from Saussy Village,
they're actually magical
beasts covered in flames.
[WILLIAM]
The villagers are terrified.
I'd like you all to go there
as a squad and eliminate
the herd before too
much damage is done.
Alecdora will lead this mission.
Yes, sir!
[WILLIAM] And remember,
I'm counting on you.
[MAGIC KNIGHTS]
Right!
[ALECDORA] No matter
what we're up against,
I swear, I'll outdo you!
[MAYOR 141A] I can't
believe the Golden Dawn
was sent here to rescue us!
[LOU]
I wish it was the Black Bulls.
[NICK]
Yeah. I wanna see Asta again.
[YUNO]
You know Asta?
Sure do!
Asta, Noelle, and Magna
protected our village
from some really bad guys!
That's right, it was
a while ago now,
but Saussy Village
is the place where
the Eye of the Midnight
Sun was first seen.
Uh-huh!
The Black Bulls defeated
some wild boars
when they were here, too!
Oh, yeah?
Then why don't we make
a game out of it?
Let's see if we can
take out even more.
I'm sure the Golden Dawn will--
No, David.
[ALECDORA] We're told the
boars are covered in flames,
that sounds dangerous.
They are, and they seem
to be even more violent
than they were last time.
We just don't know what
we're going to do anymore.
[BEAST BOARS growling]
[DAVID]
Oh, man. You guys feel that?
[MIMOSA] It's the kind of mana
that only magical beasts have.
[KLAUS] The villagers
can't defeat these.
[ALECDORA]
Shiren.
Think you can give us
a closer look?
[SHIREN]
Yes, of course.
Stone Creation Magic:
Stone Model of the World.
[ALECDORA]
Let's split up and stop them
before they hurt anyone.
[MAGIC KNIGHTS]
Right!
[YUNO]
Wait a second.
If we don't figure out
what made them so violent
in the first place,
the same thing
will just happen again.
I see. He does bring
up a valid point.
[ALECDORA] You'd better
learn your place, Yuno!
Lord Vangeance put me
in charge of this task,
so I should make the decisions!
If defeating the
boars was enough,
they might as well have
sent the Black Bulls!
How dare you?
Easy, Yuno.
Since you're so confident,
you can go ahead and execute
your plan on your own!
Everyone else, ready
yourselves for attack!
--[LETOILE] Sir!
--[DAVID] Roger that!
[HAMON] Those beasts won't
know what hit them! [laughs]
Sorry, what is your plan?
I need to find something.
Mimosa?
Um, yes?
Time for Sand Magic:
Suppressing Sand Mass technique!
[BEAST BOAR 141A growls]
I'll bet, with the
right seasonings,
these would make
a delightful roast!
[BEAST BOAR 141B growls]
[LETOILE]
There.
Now, Dice Magic:
The Gambler's Fallacy!
[DAVID]
A one? Too bad.
But that's still good enough
to beat a bunch
of overgrown pigs.
Wind Magic:
Crescent Moon Sickle!
[KLAUS] Steel Magic:
Blazing Spiral Lance!
Up ahead!
There's an area with
a high magical presence!
Let's take a look.
All right.
[BEAST BOARS grunting, growling]
[MIMOSA] I think that fruit
is what caused all this.
[KLAUS]
Interesting.
So that's why they're
on a rampage.
Then we'll need
to eradicate all of it,
along with the trees
it's growing on.
Good plan. You and
I can cover that.
Mimosa, you find out what other
areas have trees like this.
Yes, sir!
He was really outspoken earlier!
[KLAUS]
If it's to protect someone,
he won't hesitate
to defy his superiors.
I doubt he even
realizes he overstepped.
[MAYOR 141A] Thank you,
Knights of the Golden Dawn,
we are forever in your debt!
[VILLAGER 141A]
Not only did you stop them,
but you figured out what was
causing them to go berserk!
And now that it's fixed,
we shouldn't need to
trouble the Magic Knights
with this issue again!
[ALECDORA] I'm glad
we could put you at ease.
[ALECDORA] I bet you're
really proud of yourself
for proving me wrong.
[KLAUS]
What's with all the flowers?
Aw, they're adorable,
don't you think?
Since the boars
have calmed down,
the villagers are keeping
a few as their pets!
[NICK]
When you see Asta,
tell him I've been working
on my spells, okay?
Because if he's gonna
become the Wizard King,
then I wanna be on
a Magic Knight squad
so he and I can work together!
Okay. I'll make sure he knows.
[NICK giggles]
[YUNO] But the next Wizard King
is actually going to be me.
[NICK]
What? Really?
[WILLIAM] Excellent job
once again, everyone.
Now the villagers won't
have to live in fear.
I wish I could let you relax,
but we've just received
word that a new dungeon
has been discovered,
and there seem to be
suspicious people inside.
[MAGIC KNIGHTS gasp]
It's located right at the border
of Diamond and Clover.
It's near Kiten, actually.
[GROUP gasps]
[LANGRIS] Apparently, people
have seen Spade Kingdom soldiers
fighting in that area.
So whatever's happening,
Spade is likely involved.
This is a dire situation,
but with everything
that's going on here,
it's unwise for me to leave.
Langris.
I'd like you to take the
lead this time, if possible.
I wish I could be of
service to you, Captain,
but at the moment,
I'm still waiting
for my injuries to heal.
Surely one of the other knights
would be up to the task.
Of course.
If you think that'd be
best, then, let's see.
I'll send Alecdora.
[ALECDORA]
Sir!
This is my chance.
Time to prove once and
for all that I'm the one
who's the most useful
to Lord Vangeance!
[LANGRIS] Are you sure
he was the right choice?
Was he the wrong choice?
No, I just think
there was probably
a more qualified candidate who
could've been chosen instead.
I'm listening.
[LANGRIS]
During the battle against
the Eye of the Midnight Sun, he
managed to command Magic Knights
from all over the Kingdom
with no time to plan.
I think he has what
it takes to lead.
Though, his impertinence
can be irritating.
What's the matter, sir?
You're different these days.
And I mean that in a good way.
I didn't do anything.
I just want to make
sure this works out.
Yes, that's my goal, as well.
After seeing the
way you've changed,
I want that for him, too.
[HAMON] Ah, I see we have
some bandits on our hands!
[LETOILE]
They're not from Spade,
so this shouldn't be too hard.
Do you want me to get
rid of 'em real quick?
You can leave that to me.
Sand Binding Magic: Sand Box!
[MAGES groaning]
Way to go!
Mimosa. Show us the layout.
Sir! Looks like the treasure
room is right here.
There are two paths
that lead to it.
[LETOILE] So we can either come
in from the front or the top.
Then we'll split off
into two teams.
I'm going in via
the front entrance
with Shiren, Hamon, and Letoile.
That leaves Klaus,
Mimosa, David, and...
...Yuno.
You guys take the top.
Understood.
[BANDIT 141A]
Magic Knights?
[BANDIT 141B]
Damn, so much for the lookouts.
[YUNO] Wind Magic:
Crescent Moon Sickle!
Don't bother!
He deflected Yuno's spell?
[BANDIT 141A]
Have some more!
[KLAUS] Steel Creation Magic:
Full Metal Fortress!
[DAVID] Wow, these are some
sophisticated techniques
for a bunch of bandits.
Hey, wait. Look at those!
They're using magic
items to get a boost.
Smart move.
Wind Creation Magic:
Wind Blade Shower!
[BANDITS groaning]
Nice try, but even that won't
be enough to defeat us.
[BANDIT 141D]
We'll cut them off here!
[BANDIT 141E]
Take this!
[SHIREN] Stone Creation Magic:
Pursuing Crushed Rock!
What's that do?
[BANDIT 141E] This dungeon's
treasure is ours, you got that?
[laughs] Don't you know that
there's nothing delicious
about taking something
that isn't yours?
Glass Creation Magic:
Épée de Verre!
Now, Letoile!
[BANDIT 141H]
Die!
[LETOILE]
Willful Compass!
[BANDIT 141H yelping]
[ALECDORA] How dare you use
Wind Magic in front of me?
Sand Magic: Sand-Armored Guard!
[ALECDORA] No matter how many
bandits I have to face,
I'm getting all of those
magic items back!
[MAGIC KNIGHTS]
Huh?
[laughs] Excellent timing!
Aw, man!
I tried to get here first
so you'd owe me snacks.
[ALECDORA growls]
[GEWALT]
Oh, you're already here, eh?
[GEWALT] I guess I shouldn't
have expected too much
from a group of
low-rate bandits.
And even with the magic
items I lent them!
Though, compared to mine,
all those trinkets
are nothing but trash.
That's bold of you to say.
You're the only trash
I see in here.
And it's bold of you to insult
a former senior Magic Knight.
Not that you amateurs
would know the difference.
I'd watch my tongue.
You have no chance of winning!
You'd be wise to cooperate!
Think so? 'Cause I
have my doubts.
[ALECDORA] Sand Binding Magic:
Sand-Armored Heavy Guard!
Sand? Well, that's interesting.
[GEWALT]
It happens to be a perfect match
for the spells that I use!
[GEWALT] Black Earth Creation
Magic: Sludge Erosion!
[MIMOSA]
Alecdora!
[MIMOSA] Plant Recovery Magic:
Dream-Healing Flower Cradle!
Guess you're tougher
than you look.
But we'll see how you do
now that I've knocked out
one of your men.
Well, this is
certainly a predicament.
Not only does he have the
strength to be a Magic Knight,
he's also amplifying his
power with a magic item.
Yes, but he's just one man.
So we still have the advantage.
He has to be aware of that fact.
[KLAUS] He's confident.
What could he be hiding?
There's no use in thinking
about it too hard, right?
[HAMON]
Whatever the enemy throws at us,
we'll respond with a
delectable counterattack!
Glass Creation Magic:
Verre Fleur!
[GEWALT]
That's cute.
[KLAUS] Steel Creation Magic:
Fierce Spiral Lance!
Come on.
This can't be what passes for
a Magic Knight squad these days.
[LETOILE]
Compass Magic: Willful Compass!
There!
That one was
interesting, at least.
[DAVID]
How's this for interesting?
Dice Magic:
The Gambler's Fallacy!
My luck's finally
turning around now.
Unfortunately, I can't
say the same for you!
[DAVID gasps]
[GEWALT] This is the greatest
treasure in the whole dungeon.
No matter how powerful
a spell you cast,
I can use this magic item
to suck it right up.
Are you kidding me?
Bell.
I thought you'd
never ask, Yuno!
[YUNO]
Wind Magic: Swift White Bow!
Did you seriously
think that would work?
That felt like a gentle
breeze from over here.
[BELL]
Ugh! That's so annoying!
[GEWALT]
So, what's your next move?
You guys get the message
by now, don't you?
[YUNO]
It's crystal clear.
Between the necklace and the
urn, you've already shown us
every trick you've
got up your sleeve.
And now we can say for certain
that you're no match
for the Golden Dawn.
I should've helped them
fight those wild boars.
At least that would've
been more fun.
[GEWALT]
If you're trying to provoke me,
it's not going
to work, stupid brat.
I dunno, you look
pretty salty over there.
It's just as Yuno said.
Our squad'll never
lose to a weakling
who has to rely
on two magic items.
If we gave up,
it would dishonor
the proud name of
the Golden Dawn!
[HAMON] Let the scrumptious
battle begin!
If that's what you want,
then be my guest!
I'll absorb all your mana!
[YUNO grunts]
[KLAUS grunts]
[DAVID]
Luck's on our side!
[HAMON laughs]
Morons.
You don't know when
to give up, do you?
You probably shouldn't
be moving around.
Don't worry, Mimosa, I'm fine.
Help Shiren. He needs you more.
Find us a place
with fainter mana.
I will try my best to pinpoint
some weak spots in the walls.
Okay!
Wind Magic: Tornado Fang!
[GEWALT grunts]
You almost had me that time!
[GEWALT]
No, it can't be!
Dammit. He's persistent!
[KLAUS]
I'll finish this now!
Steel Magic:
Blazing Spiral Lance!
[DAVID] Dice Magic:
The Gambler's Fallacy!
There, that should be
enough to settle it.
[GEWALT] Looks like it's
a test of endurance!
You'd better hope
your mana reserves
don't run out before
my magic items break!
[YUNO]
We're not aiming for you.
[LETOILE]
Compass Magic: Willful Compass!
[GEWALT grunts]
[GEWALT]
A pitfall?
That's what they were
planning all along?
[BELL] Thanks for leaving me
with the heavy lifting.
[GEWALT]
Don't forget. I still have this!
[ALECDORA] You've reached
the end of the line!
[GEWALT]
You fool! I already told you,
my type of magic has
the advantage over yours!
[gasps]
Yes, and I told you.
[GEWALT gasping]
[screams]
You can try, but you're
simply no match
for the knights
of the Golden Dawn.
[WILLIAM] Thank you for leading
this mission, Alecdora.
[ALECDORA] You should know,
sir, at one point,
I was unable to fight after
sustaining an injury.
Without my squadmates,
there would've been
no hope of success.
I see. And what's
your view, Yuno?
Alecdora commanded
our team perfectly.
Why are you trying
to make me look good?
I'm only telling them the truth.
[ALECDORA] Then allow me
to be honest, as well.
When you came to the Golden
Dawn, some of our squad
looked down on you
for being a commoner.
They resented you and were
jealous of your powers.
And I was no exception.
What could possibly possess you
to stand up for a group
of people like us?
[YUNO] We're comrades.
I don't need another reason.
Just that I care.
In the past, I was also
guilty of thinking someone's
low social status made them
less worthy of respect.
But after being
rescued by a commoner
with no magic or manners,
I reconsidered my prejudices.
Don't you dare
compare me to him.
Yuno, please!
Apologies.
What?
Okay, but I'm not sure
what you're sorry about.
I wouldn't expect
you to understand,
but I'd be wrong
to let it go unsaid.
Even so, I still
don't acknowledge you
as one of us!
[gasps]
[ALECDORA, HAMON gasp]
[ALECDORA]
Are you here to give a report?
[YUNO]
Yes.
[HAMON]
When we're finished,
let's all go out
to eat together!
[gasps]
[KLAUS] This is Yuno's chance
to bond with the squad!
[KLAUS]
That sounds wonderful!
Hey, come back!
[SHIREN]
Yuno.
[HAMON]
You're invited.
In fact, we specifically
invited you.
Oh, I didn't...
[LETOILE] Hamon knows
some great restaurants
around the royal capital.
[DAVID] Yeah, we thought it
might be fun to hit the town
with the whole squad and party!
[ASTA] You and me, we don't
have any real relatives,
but we've got a lot
of great friends.
Let's take all
the friends we meet
and make them
our family instead!
Are you coming with us, Yuno?
Hold on. Are you blushing?
[YUNO]
Of course not.
Looks like you are.
[YUNO]
I'm not.
[BELL]
Ooh, I wanna see!
[YUNO]
I said no!
[ASTA] We're gonna train hard
and get even stronger
so we can fight the Spade
Kingdom and defeat the devil!
Black Clover , Page 142:
"Those Remaining."
Wait, who are you guys?
Do you want the
devil to die, too?