The year.
2148.
It was supposed to
have been a time of peace.
The Festum, our enemy
from far distant skies,
had been driven back after
humanity's decisive victory
in the battle
at the North Pole.
For most of us,
the end of the fighting
came as a welcome relief.
Still, amongst the world powers,
there were some who
could not be satisfied
until the enemy
had been wiped out completely.
And thus a new battle
was begun.
Heads up!
Alright, here we are.
Two Kazuki Curries.
Are we ready to order here?
Sure, uh.
Got an order up!
Two for Table B!
Got it.
Keep 'em coming!
That's two more
Kazuki Curry plates!
Mr. Mizoguchi, from
now on could you please
stop naming dishes after me?
Oh, gimme a break.
You're our main draw here, kid.
Another delivery order.
To Alvis again.
Huh?
Jeez, and we've still got
the festival tonight too.
This meeting will cover
the final checklist
for the school's annual U
Project, as well as the changes
to this year's Bone dance.
But first, there's something
we need to address.
I'll have a melon soda
and Kazuki Cake.
Lemon tea and a Kazuki Flan!
I'll have the Kazuki Curry
plate with green tea!
Slow down, not all at once.
We're really busy today,
you know.
Couldn't you do this at school?
Student Council always
holds official meetings here.
But Kondo's not even with you.
As the Vice President,
I have been entrusted
to run the proceedings.
Yeah, President Kondo's off
at the usual place again.
I've been handling
the secretary duties
to make sure
everything's organized.
That's pretty impressive,
don't you think, Maya?
Yes, Rina,
you're very responsible.
What about you, Akira?
Would you like something?
He'll have what I'm having.
Straight espresso, huh?
A bold choice.
You're a moron.
Did you want to order,
too, Chocolat?
Hey, Boss!
Are you ready, the festival
prep's already started!
I thought you weren't
gonna drink today.
Naaaaw.
Come on, Kenji.
This ain't drinkin'.
Still no Tamotsu.
The man's been drunk ever since
he finished work on the Fafners.
Perhaps, but it's thanks to
Mr. Kodate's work that we have
nine operational Nothung
Models ready to deploy.
Even Mark Fünf
is running perfectly,
and it was the most
heavily damaged of all.
The unit his son piloted.
He clearly put his heart
into those repairs.
Tsubaki Minashiro.
Hatred is not the way;
there must be another path.
Help him search for it.
I beg you.
Fumihiko.
Commander Makabe?
Hmm?
Systems operation proficiency
has also reached stipulated
values for all staff.
Former U.N. troops included.
Then we've determined the issue
is with the Brunhilde System.
That's correct.
Our core has entered her growth
stage, which means for a time,
she'll be drawing more energy.
Since the core also acts as our
environmental management system,
the resulting power drain
is likely to affect
the entire island.
Ecosystem, food supply,
disease rates, everything.
And meanwhile, we've been seeing
signs of activity from Solomon.
Destroying the Mir at
the North Pole should have
crippled their forces.
How can they be
on the move again?
It's possible that their Mir
has taken on a different form.
Perhaps in the same way our
Mir became the island's air.
But wouldn't that
require the enemy
to have a core similar to ours?
That's speculation.
We'll see what the
Solomon analysis tells us.
Until then.
We'll have to pray
this peace continues.
Ta-da!
Here's this morning's catch!
The saw-tooth stag beetle,
Miyama stag beetle,
and the Mulberry Borer!
We'll all be here
waiting for you, Tsubaki.
Hurry, okay?
I have so much to
tell you when you get back.
Finally, all done.
You still need
to get ready, don't you?
Why don't you
just head on home?
And what about you?
I should probably
wait here for Mr. Mizoguchi.
I'll be alright; I can still
see okay while it's light out.
'Kay, then.
Maya?
Thank you for--
Well, for everything.
It's alright; don't mention it.
I'll see you later.
The last glimmers
of hope have gone dark.
They are filled
with suffering and hatred.
I'm so sorry, Kazuki.
This is a gamble.
I'll tell you what
our last resort will be.
If anything should
go wrong, take Door Eleven.
Okay.
Thank you, Soshi.
I will return to you someday.
No matter what.
And I'll wait for you.
Right here.
As long as it takes.
Hey Kazuki.
Were you talkin' to yourself?
What?
No.
Was I saying something?
'Kay, all done!
See?
It's the great big boat!
Oh, yes.
That's nice!
Good job, Miwa.
And there's another boat
that's even bigger!
And a mountain, too!
You don't say.
And what do they look like?
This one's got
a big thingy on top.
See?
And it's all white and shiny!
Miwa?
Come inside and change, sweetie.
No, please.
Please don't take my baby.
I'm begging you!
And see?
The great big boat
is coming to talk to us!
You ready?
Grandma already left.
I mean, you are coming,
aren't you?
Will you say something?
Say something!
Fine, be that way!
You moron!
Hey, sorry I'm so late, Mom.
No, it's fine Canon.
I've laid out
your things for you.
Hey Sakura.
'Bout time.
Yeah, sorry.
Are you sure you should be
up on your feet like that?
I feel good today.
So I was thinking
I would try walking.
There's no need
to push too hard.
Come on.
I'll getcha there.
Fine.
Whoa.
Hey, are you gaining weight?
That's it.
I'm walking.
Hey!
C'mon, I didn't mean it!
It was a joke!
Funny!
Ha ha!
Now isn't that just lovely.
Yeah, Tamotsu was
in charge of the set-up.
Festival lanterns are
riding out on the tide.
They're partially
lifting the shield.
It really is a
beautiful tradition, isn't it?
I only hope our names will be
recorded like that one day.
Uh- Unknown object
detected inside our shield!
Wait.
What?
There!
It's coming from the west!
This is a gamble, Kazuki.
Kazuki?
What's he doing?
He can barely see!
Kazuki!
Wait!
No girls, it's not safe!
Stay back!
Soshi!
What did you say?
Hold on, is that--
Is that a Core?
Right, "Take Door Eleven".
Where are you going?
Data verified.
Neo U.N. B-29 military
transport submarine.
Zero response to our scan.
'Kay.
Whadda we got here?
"Kurusu", huh?
What the hell's going on?
Alright, I'll do it.
If that's what you want.
Soshi.
An aurora?
But what could be causing it?
Look, there.
They're on standby?
You don't think--
It's a Festum.
Are you there?
Enemy confirmed:
Sphinx type A.
I want all Fafners on standby!
The Brunhilde System
is not responding!
We're losing the shield.
Breach imminent!
Did they deliberately target
the Core's growth stage?
Mark Sein standing by
to sortie!
Is that Kazuki?
The enemy has reached the
Tatsumiya Island mainland!
Go, Mark Sein!
Launch now!
Opening Neidhöle
gates one through six.
Mark Sein, clear for launch.
Why?
Why is it you?
Why isn't it Soshi?
A new Festum?
Gimme a break.
Since when do the Festum
use human weaponry?
It's displaying a completely
different chemical profile!
Pilot is experiencing
rapid assimilation!
Send reinforcements!
All Fafners--
Commander Makabe?
It's still alive.
It's right on top a' me!
Eat this!
The enemy has been terminated.
Hey, it's alright.
You just keep still and rest.
But the siren.
No, it's not an attack.
They're moving the island.
Shield in place.
Disengaging camouflage mirror.
Entering course data.
T-minus two minutes
to autopilot engage.
The Com is open, sir.
May I have your
attention, please.
Tatsumiya Island will
soon leave her moorings,
as we attempt to distance
ourselves from the phenomenon
in the skies.
Effective immediately, we
will maintain our war footing
to prepare for
further enemy attacks.
Oh, please, no.
I'll be counting on every
one of you to do your part.
Listen up.
When you're piloting a Fafner,
don't think about it;
just move naturally.
Be one with your machine.
In body and mind.
And accept that you are not
the same in here as outside.
Hey, are you paying
attention, Mark Fünf?
Yes, sir!
We all go by
our unit names here.
You are your Fafners now,
and the Fafners are you.
You think you got
all that, Mark Neun?
Oh.
Uh.
Roger.
Mark Zehn?
Uh, right.
Mark Zehn--
reporting-- ma'am.
He's talking?
Can you-- hear me?
Mhmm.
Loud and clear.
No way.
Zwölf, you ready?
Akira did--
Did you just speak?
Mark Zwölf.
Respond.
Roger!
Now, maintain your
crossing with each other.
Shoulder any pain
or fear you feel as a team.
And don't forget.
The longer you pilot,
the more you've gotta
worry about assimilation.
But hey, unlike in the past,
at least your Fafner shouldn't
just stop moving on you.
Got it?
Then let's do this!
Pilot aptitude scores
are all in line.
I'll use these new tests
to determine the most
suitable equipment for her.
This feels so good!
Sakura.
Why would you choose
this for yourself?
You gonna be okay?
I never thought I would have
to worry like this again.
Hey Mom!
Don't forget, here I'm an
officer and instructor first.
Of course, Ms. Hazama.
I'm sorry about that.
Now let me show you
why I called you.
The thirteenth unit:
Mark Dreizehn.
You'll be the first pilot
ever assigned to it;
we've had it configured
especially for you.
A machine of my very own.
Seriously?
Who attacks by head-butting?
Maybe a result of her
altered consciousness?
Well, if so, she'll need some
equipment I didn't plan on.
So he's crossing over.
That's correct.
Based on these latest tests,
I've determined that Kazuki
is in a continuous
state of crossing.
So what you're saying is
that he's still connected to
Soshi Minamiro and most likely
has been for the last two years.
Yes?
We're not sure
who's on the other end.
All we can say for certain
is this appears to be linked
with a different heavy strain.
A different strain, huh?
Does that have
something to do with Sein?
That's my guess.
The thing's a walking
assimilation phenomenon.
And Kazuki is the only pilot
that can even handle it.
We cannot let him get back
into that machine.
It's obviously killing him;
it's a miracle he hasn't
been assimilated already.
What of this unmanned ship?
We've finished analyzing the
entity we discovered aboard.
Solomon confirmed
that it's a Sphinx type.
Its body composition closely
resembles a Core type,
but it has no chromosomes.
It's clearly attempting
to mimic a human.
Does that mean it's
the same as the enemy
that attacked the island?
There are no abnormalities
in the ship itself.
And according to
the autopilot record,
it was coming straight for us.
So in other words,
someone sent it here.
Most of the data we recovered
involved the Neo U.N's analysis
of a new type of Festum.
It has powerful
assimilation abilities,
and employs weapons
modeled after ours.
They named it the "Eurus" type,
after a mythological god
who summoned storms.
So what the hell
are they saying?
"You're gonna be fighting
these, now study up"?
We also discovered
this bit of data.
It's a recommendation
that we publicly disclose
SC Code-level intel
to this unidentified craft.
SC code.
It's telling us to disclose
info on our island's core
or the Mir to someone?
Or, more precisely,
on something akin to a Mir.
Do we know what
it's referring to?
Not at this time.
I can only assume that
was unknown to whoever created
this data, as well.
The phenomenon in our skies,
the enemy attack,
and the auto-piloted ship.
Right now, we have to figure out
how these things are connected.
I didn't think President Kondo
would be so weak.
He's not.
I think he lost on purpose,
as a way to help
build up our confidence.
This is so weird.
You're talking again.
I guess, I always knew I'd be
able to if I piloted a Fafner.
I want to be assigned to the
one Mom and Dad were piloting
when they disappeared.
The Zero Fafner.
You'll just get in the way no
matter what unit you're in.
I'll do it.
You should resign.
Stop it, Rina, you know
that isn't going to happen.
Here's what I know.
You're just a moron who
only thinks about himself!
Ah.
Man, that hurts.
Well you were a good sport,
taking one for
the team out there.
How'd it go?
None of them help each other.
They'll get themselves
killed like that.
Then we'll just have
to make sure they don't.
You know.
You really don't have to--
Yes I do.
I'm still a pilot, Kenji.
Besides, you already spend
so much time looking after
me and Mr. Kodate.
I think you've got
enough to worry about.
Hey, c'mon.
It isn't like it's any trouble.
You realize that it wasn't your
fault that Mamoru got killed.
And what happened to me
isn't anyone's fault, either.
Still, I do understand
why you feel responsible.
And so--
That's why I'm asking you
to let me share the burden.
I will not lose you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Then promise!
Promise you'll live,
no matter what!
Then this must be
what's causing my symptoms.
But I was exposed
to nuclear fallout, what--
Thirty years ago?
The island's Mir has been
suppressing your illness
all this time.
But after this latest
enemy attack, with our core
still in its growth stage,
it's severely weakened
its biosphere functions.
Perhaps when the core
finishes its growth then-- No!
I'll find a way to cure you even
before that, whatever it takes!
So the island has
allowed me to live.
It seems that
I've been truly blessed.
Air strikes and naval strikes.
They must be clearing
the way for a landing force.
So they're attacking
like humans would.
In that case,
let's show them how it's done.
Bastards.
Roger.
Reinforcement Fafners
prepare to sortie.
Nibeloong System now active.
Siegfried System
connections are stable.
Auto-calibration
sequence initiated.
Goubain!
They're beautiful.
I'm alive?
You're in a Nothung model,
it can take it.
That's what it was
designed to do, you know.
It's coming!
So hold it off!
No, no, no, no!
You're gonna be all right.
Just calm down.
Your Fafner's Mir core
resists the enemy's power!
Be quick, and they
can't touch you!
Believe in yourself, be one
with your machine, and fight!
One's breaking away, you guys!
Everybody look sharp!
'Kay, I'm on it.
Wha?
Is it-- Is it trying
to say something?
Nice work out there.
Keep it up, Mark Zehn.
Right!
He's about to wake up.
Solomon's responding!
There's a Festum inside Alvis!
It seems our guest has awakened.
So this is air.
Life.
The pain is multiplying.
It's sad.
Tears.
Please go home, everyone.
Give me some time
to talk to them.
The enemy is retreating?
Wait.
What just happened?
Did we win?
We-- We won?
Hell yeah!
They'll be back soon.
I advise surrender.
Kazuki.
Who are you?
And how do you know my name?
Kazuki!
What is this strange creature?
Help me, please!
I told you not
to charge off on your own!
Somebody's gonna get
taken out because of you!
You can't stop me!
I'm gonna fight
just like Mamoru did!
I swear.
I think that poor thing was
trying to tell me something.
It was awful!
Almost like it was
begging me for help!
And so what if it was,
it's still the enemy, right?
They're trying to kill
all of us, remember?
Just take 'em out;
that'll shut 'em up.
But I know Tsubaki
would want me to listen!
Tsubaki's gone, so get over it!
No.
How could you say
something like that?
What's with them?
They're all acting crazy.
It's their first fight; they're
just a little bit on edge.
Not me; I took out
four 'a those things!
I probably could'a
gotten a hundred
or so if they hadn't run away.
Uh huh.
Hey.
Maybe there'll be even more
of 'em next time, you think?
Would that be your idea of fun?
Suck it, Kenji!
I'm tougher than
you'll ever be!
Such enthusiasm.
I am so tearing them
all new ones when we get back.
No, we'll say they did great.
Y'know, "carrot and stick".
Assuming the fight
is really over.
They haven't called us in yet.
Something isn't right.
You may refer to me as,
Misao Kurusu.
Wait, isn't that--?
I can't believe
he's broadcasting this
to the whole island.
Shouldn't he be worried about
causing some kind of riot?
That's always been
Commander Fumihiko's style;
he's free with
information to a fault.
But much as I hate to admit it,
it's pretty damn effective.
"Misao Kurusu".
Is that the name of
a human you assimilated?
I chose it.
Based on Soshi Minashiro's
knowledge of your language,
these words seemed a suitable
way to identify my existence.
I needed a name to speak
with your kind, did I not?
And was it Soshi Minashiro
that put you on that boat?
No, that was my own desire.
However, he did want you
to have certain information.
You found his words
on the boat, correct?
You're telling me that data
came directly from Soshi?
Why doesn't he come
to the island himself?
It is because
of the great fire.
A fire that was
ignited by you humans.
It has caused much
suffering amongst my kind.
You mean the nuclear
strike by the Neo U.N?
Correct.
The pain of the initial
shock was unbearable,
so much so that our Mir
did not wish to be reborn.
Though perhaps that is why I
was allowed to be born instead?
What do you mean?
Did your Mir survive
the attack and now exists
in a different form?
Is he feeling alright?
Why's he grabbing
his chest like that?
Yes.
Mir split into pieces, but
did not disappear entirely.
Will you please answer
a question for me now?
Within reason, yes.
Then tell me, have you ever
looked up into the sky
and thought it beautiful?
The sky?
I suppose.
I knew it!
I really can
understand your kind!
And what?
You somehow find
this thought surprising?
You have the power to read
our thoughts, do you not?
We certainly do.
But it's often hard
to make sense of them.
Which is why I'm happy
to know that you think
the sky is beautiful, too!
And what is it
you're after, exactly?
I want to make
the fighting stop.
I don't want
the pain to multiply.
Are you saying
you've come seeking peace?
Yes.
Specifically, I wish
to assimilate your Core.
Excuse me?
Is this not
a reasonable request?
It would allow our Mir
to assimilate your Mir without
any further fighting.
After all, it was Tatsumiya
Island that gave us pain
and fear of death.
So what you want is to erase
your pain, and us along with it.
I don't want to erase you.
I want to join forces.
"Join forces"?
Against whom?
Other humans.
Other groups of my kind.
We'll take away
everyone's ability to fight,
so that they can't anymore.
And once we have succeeded,
then everyone will have peace.
Do you expect me to respond
to this immediately?
I'm prepared to wait.
I know your people
make decisions as a group.
But I hope you hurry.
The others will not stay gone
for much longer and your Core
will not survive another attack.
How do you know this?
I know because our Mir
has already stolen your sky.
And the Core
will die without it.
Although, it looks like
you might die even sooner.
Will you agree to remain right
here until I'm able to return?
Of course.
Then did you have
any other questions?
What is this "Kazuki Curry"?
You heard his offer.
He wishes to form
an alliance with us.
Whether or not it's genuine,
this is an unprecedented move.
It's also a sure-fire way
to turn the rest of
the world against us.
The kid said that
we'd be joinin' up to
fight other Festum, too.
So does that mean all these
special "Eurus-types"
or whatever they're
called have somehow split off
into their own group?
It does suggest that the enemy
has divided into factions.
How much of what
he said is true, though?
We can't verify
that data came from Soshi.
All we have's
his word for it.
We can't ignore the
possibility that this is all
an elaborate ruse to trick us
into divulging our SC Code.
Clearly, the part about the
enemy causing the phenomenon
in our skies was true.
But the assertion that these
aurora are killing our Core?
Also true.
Unfortunately.
And if the strain is
compounded by further attacks,
catastrophic failure
becomes even more likely.
We need to put this decision
before the whole island.
They're trying to
return to the soil?
Festum's bodies are made
of silicon--so they are soil.
They're just looking for a place
to come home to, same as us.
Akane!
I finally found
my home, you know.
Even if I did lose it
for a while.
And it's wherever I'm with you.
Have you told Mr. Mizoguchi
that you're sick?
I have.
So how did you find out?
Maya told me that you
looked like you weren't
feeling too well.
Right, I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
We'll protect the island, Dad.
So you can, you know,
try and take it easy.
And what might that entail?
I dunno, maybe living here
with-- Well, with Dr. Tomi.
Huh?
Hey, c'mon, I'm just
trying to help!
And where would
that leave you, then?
Huh?
There're places I can go.
Like where,
the cockpit of Mark Sein?
Yeah, sure I guess, I mean
if that's what I need to do.
Lemme tell you what I want.
I want this house to be a place
that you will always able
to come home to.
I can't leave the island
to you just yet.
I'm sorry, son.
Well, like I said, I was
just trying to help out.
So this "Misao Kurusu".
What do you make of him?
I don't know.
He is still an enemy.
But the way he came to us.
I just feel like Soshi's
gambling something on him.
Soshi sent that boat to
the island because he believed
doing so would protect us.
Is that the sense
you're getting?
I don't know how I know.
I just do somehow.
Not every war is won
on the battlefield.
Now go have a dialogue
with that creature.
If you're right,
perhaps you can find another
way to save this island.
What is this?
Go!
Just take the bastards down!
Hang on, they're
protecting each other?
Whoa!
Mark Zehn, no!
Let's take out their shields.
Roger that.
You and Soshi are here.
I've so wanted to see it.
The place Soshi Minashiro lived.
I want to understand him more.
So is that why you're
wearing Soshi's uniform?
I wore it because it fits.
What about Soshi, where is he?
He's nowhere.
But his existence
has not yet been lost.
So what else?
I'm very happy
we can talk like this.
Everyone on this island
is suffering because of you.
You do not get to act
like we're friends.
Are you feeling
hatred for me, Kazuki?
No, I-- I'm just angry,
that's all.
It seems I don't really
understand anger or hatred.
But if you don't
want your people to suffer,
then just do what I say.
If you want our Core,
why not take it?
Because I have no desire
to fight with you.
Then stop your Mir
from attacking us!
That's impossible.
I don't have
that kind of power.
You did it once!
I requested that the others
go home to give us time.
My existence is--
Well, you might say
it's analogous to one
of your fingers.
Your fingers don't
give your body orders.
Now do they.
So where is "home"?
The ship.
It's like my island.
And is that where your Mir
is located, aboard that ship?
Yes, it is.
And you have just thought about
attacking it, haven't you.
If that's what it takes
to save our island, yes.
Is that what Soshi Minashiro
has told you to do?
What do you mean?
Can you still
hear Soshi's voice?
I can't anymore.
It takes everything
I have just
to make sure his existence
doesn't disappear completely!
That was you.
You protected Soshi.
Now!
Finish it off!
Enemy kill is confirmed!
Whatever these latest enemies
have been dropping on us,
it seems designed to put
maximum strain on our system.
They're using
"Core Killers", huh?
Let her talk to them, Fumihiko.
You can create a path together.
Let her try.
"Her" who?
Commander!
So the SC Code.
Life being allowed
by the island.
And an existence akin to Mir.
Ms. Kaname?
I'll be okay.
Just feeling a little dizzy.
Mom!
Someone get the medical team
over here, hurry!
On it!
Medical Team
to the hanger, stat!
The past Mir,
nuclear contamination.
At this rate.
I predict that most of
the islanders will
become symptomatic soon.
This medicine aids
Pilot/Fafner integration.
It deliberately accelerates
the assimilation process.
It's our last option.
I don't have any other way
to suppress your symptoms.
I know the risks.
It's alright.
I just can't help thinking.
Maybe we should take
our chances with the Festum
and do what he says.
I know it's wrong,
but if it means you can live!
We haven't run out
of hope just yet.
Let's follow the
guidance of our core.
We'll see where that leads us.
We're going to live at Alvis?
Just for a little while.
Until it's safe to come back.
Yeah okay, I guess.
But why do I have to go
to the hospital, Mom?
I don't feel hurt anywhere.
I don't know, sweetie.
Why would you want
to save Soshi?
I had been looking forever.
For another existence who
thought the sky was beautiful.
And suddenly there he was.
So you decided
that for yourself?
That the sky is beautiful?
Yes.
Don't you think that, too?
I can't see the sky anymore.
And soon I won't be able
to see anything at all.
I just have to go by feel,
so my fingers have
to become my eyes now.
I've asked myself,
over and over again,
what it could be that
Soshi wants from you.
I don't know.
But my guess is that
there are things he hopes
you'll go back
and tell your Mir.
"Tell my Mir"?
Things like what?
That you can't
find peace this way.
Blaming humans for all of your
suffering isn't the answer.
Erasing us won't
erase your pain.
But I told you
I don't want that!
That's why I gave
your people a choice!
You're the one
who has to choose!
You can decide,
"Are you there?"
Seri!
You okay?
I finally figured it out.
What it is they're saying.
The Festum?
"Help me. Stop the pain."
Help me to stop the pain!
Fine, then we put 'em
outta their misery!
Hey.
Come on.
Don't cry!
I want to see
a blue sky again!
All of my information is
already being passed on to Mir.
What more could
I possibly tell?
Have you told your
Mir your feelings?
That you don't want to fight?
I can't.
To me, Mir is like what
your people call a "god".
You can't defy
the will of God, can you?
So please.
Please, just do what I ask.
But we don't want
to fight with other humans.
So how can you expect us
to agree to fight
the entire world with you?
If I did that,
I wouldn't be me anymore.
And likewise.
If I did as you suggest,
I wouldn't be me
anymore, either.
You surprise me.
I've known people who wanted
to talk with the enemy before.
But you're the first I've seen
who's made graves for them.
Tsubaki tried to tell the
Festum how sad we all felt.
And now they're suffering, too.
I dunno, I just
felt sorry for them.
Guess that's pretty strange.
You can say it.
No.
Just as we remember the
friends we've lost in battle,
we should never
forget our fallen foes.
The cost of war.
I can't imagine.
You've had to fight humans
before, haven't you?
I have.
Is there something you
came here to ask me?
Yes.
Something I believe
only you can do.
It's okay.
I'm not scared, Tsubaki.
This substitute can only
relieve the strain on our Core
for a few weeks.
The enemy is assembling
a large strike force,
mostly of Eurus type.
It would seem they've also
repurposed a number of units
that to this point have been
considered "noncombatant".
Hold on, you're saying they've
even rounded up
their own civilians?
So this is what these
Eurus types must have
in store for us from now on.
They're not going to hold
anything back, are they?
But with an army of that size.
Can we win?
Even if we do,
another wave will come.
Our only hope is to
take out the Festum's Mir.
We do have a proposal
we think might help.
Based on our data and
Misao Kurusu's statements,
there is a high probability that
this vessel is the enemy Mir.
Still, we just don't
have the resources
to launch a direct assault.
No, that's not what
we're suggesting at all.
You ran an operation here three
years ago that was codenamed,
"L Project."
As former U.N. military,
we can commandeer
the auto-piloted craft.
We'll infiltrate the enemy
lines, and destroy their Mir.
Just like that, huh?
We'll try to evacuate
as many personnel as possible
before setting off
the ship's Fenrir.
Should be enough
to wipe the enemy out.
You have to know that's suicide.
You can't evacuate, you'll
be completely surrounded.
Why would anyone
volunteer for this?
Because the Neo U.N. strike
that created this enemy!
And because we still
have a debt to repay.
You people saved our lives
after our government
basically abandoned us.
This is our duty!
I'll grant you permission
to use the submarine.
Commander!
But I am not going to allow you
to sacrifice yourselves.
The mistakes of the L Project
will not be repeated.
This time, it's our turn
to seek dialogue.
The first natural
conception on this island.
The first child born after the
Mir learned of life and death
from Tsubaki Minashiro.
She's an existence akin to Mir;
an unknown quantity,
even to Soshi Minashiro.
We have also determined
that Miwa is in a constant
state of crossing.
What's more, she's crossing
with the island's Mir itself.
Mama.
I'm not scared.
Can I talk to 'em?
Pretty please?
Oh, Miwa.
Let's go!
Please, surrender!
Or everyone will be gone!
Go and tell your Mir
to call them back.
But Mir would never
listen to my voice!
So then you tell it,
"The sky is beautiful!"
You weren't ordered
to think that.
You thought it on your own,
like a human, right?
Make it listen!
Make your god understand
what it means to have
that taken from you!
So even Mama's mama
isn't able to fix it?
You can speak our language?
But how?
They said if you stay
with me, you can talk, too.
She is our hope,
Commander Makabe.
So- Soshi?
No!
Hey, Rina!
You okay?
Kenji!
No!
Okay.
I guess it's up to me now.
Hang on, Akira!
What the hell?
Please.
Only she can make
their Mir understand.
She can tell them
in their own language.
Stop it, Soshi!
You're going to disappear!
I'm sorry.
Kazuki.
I tried.
What is it?
The nothingness we sealed.
They're about to reach it.
Will you please just stop it!
Why do you suffer?
Is your Mir ordering you
to endure this?
We do whatever we have to do
to protect our home!
We make the decision!
Did you only protect Soshi
because your Mir ordered you to?
No.
I-- I just didn't want
to see him disappear.
It's no use.
Mir is calling me!
Defy your god, Kurusu!
Say no!
Mark Nicht?
So this must be it.
The reason for my human form.
Kazuki!
You know, I can still
talk more if you want me to.
Yes.
I'm counting on that.
Stop!
Don't move!
You're going to take her
away from me, aren't you?
I won't let you steal my baby!
That's right.
You and I have kept it
sealed away together.
All this time, Soshi.
And I'll do it.
I will.
If that's what you want.
Synchronize support fluid
with the Core, stat!
Yes ma'am!
I see.
So this is it.
This is hate.
Stop.
Please don't do this!
You don't have to
obey your Mir!
You know this isn't the answer!
Make your own choice!
Let's plug these leaks!
Hurry!
Now, dammit!
You okay, Kenji?
You hang onto that, okay?
Now go back up Canon.
Got it?
And from now on use
our unit names!
But you weren't using them ei--
Wait, what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna teach these bastards
to stay the hell off my island!
Go!
Go protect our friends!
Right!
Assimilation.
Boot authentication for Fenrir.
To continue, please enter
the authentication key.
Continue?
No.
They haven't got me yet.
I'm still here, dammit!
Fight it, Akira!
It's too late!
Go!
Leave me!
I can-- already feel
myself slipping away.
Tell Rina I'll be with--
Mom and-- Dad.
No!
Fight it!
Is that?
Mark Vier?
Koyo?
Look, Festum!
The possibility,
who was born among my people.
This girl is the final hope.
For both our kinds!
Kazuki?
What're you doing?
Mark Sein's too dangerous!
Canon, no!
Hang on!
You're staying right here.
I'm the only one here who--
who has to do this.
Stop it!
You're going to
disappear, Kazuki!
What?
Why are you letting me
escape, Kazuki?
Your kind are the only ones
who wanted this fight!
It's up to you now!
Only you can stop it!
Kurusu!
Kazuki!
No!
I didn't want this.
I don't want your people
to disappear, but--!
What of my kind?
There's still
nothing being born.
And until then,
I have no choice.
I have fulfilled
all of my duties.
Holding me here will generate
no further possibility.
But you can still
show us how to fight.
Can't you?
I have given up
the means to do battle.
That Mir's condition is not
the possibility truly sought.
The pain is still multiplying!
I can't bear it alone.
It's too much!
I'm sorry Soshi.
I'm just not strong enough.
But I tried.
"Pain" is Soshi
Minashiro's blessing.
"Life" is Tsubaki
What blessing will you
bestow upon the world?
What can I do?
I'm powerless!
You are the first among
your kind to desire existence
while the Mir was absent.
Ask yourself,
"Why are you there?"
I only went there
so I could see the sky.
But all I've found is sadness.
I can't bear this
existence anymore!
I'm going to try
to erase the pain.
And then Soshi, and Kazuki,
and finally my own existence.
I saw it, Rina.
Nothingness inside the Festum.
It was just like when
Mom and Dad disappeared.
I thought they'd
be somewhere, but--
There's nowhere to go.
Well no duh, you moron!
I've told you a hundred times
they're never coming back,
but you still leave the front
lights on for them at night,
and you never want
to float lanterns for them.
Grandma's getting old,
you know.
If you leave me, pretty soon,
I'll be all alone!
In a house nobody
ever comes home to!
I'm sorry, sis.
Moron.
I don't understand.
This data stream.
It's coming from
the unit's core,
even though there
isn't a pilot on board.
Mark Vier has no core.
Your old U.N. pals stole it and
used it to create Mark Nicht.
Well something
moved this machine.
It shows the pilot ID
is still Koyo's.
Koyo Kasugai has come home.
Somehow he's transformed
himself into the unit's core,
so he could continue
to protect the island.
We talked about lots n' lots
of different things.
That's very good, dear.
Now what sorts of things?
It was so sad.
They told me
they're all hurting.
She's your precious little girl.
You only did what any
other mother would do.
I'm sure that's not
the way Miwa would see it.
She knows you were
trying to protect her;
and that's all that matters.
But what about Kazuki?
Do you think what
Miwa said is true?
That he didn't
actually disappear?
That he can still come home.
I do believe that, yes.
This is going to end, right?
What's the point of living
if everything we love
is just taken away from us?
We will stop them.
Even if it costs me my life.
See, they wanted to know more
about the girl holding the baby.
They wanted to know if she was
hurting as much as they were.
I can talk to them more and
tell them if you want me to!
Is all this makin'
sense to anyone else?
She's talking about Tsubaki
Minashiro and the enemy Mir.
It seems she wishes
to act as a go-between.
And we're sure.
She's the reason
the Festum pulled back?
Solomon confirms a massive
data exchange via crossing,
just minutes before
the end of the last attack.
A complex code sequence
based on an unknown type
of transfinite number.
The human race still hasn't
learned all the numbers
that exist in this universe.
This is one we don't know.
And yet, young Miwa Hino
deciphered it intuitively,
just as naturally as she
learned her first words.
What's more, she displayed a
level of influence over them
that even Tsubaki
Minashiro couldn't.
If Solomon's developer
were here right now,
she'd probably
be jumping for joy.
So, what?
She figured out the
enemy's chain of command
and was somehow
able to overwrite
the Eurus type's orders?
Putting it in those terms
fails to capture the full
scope of what's happening.
She insists on calling their
communication "talking",
but it's more like
she's appealing directly
to their sensibilities.
So she's teaching them empathy.
Is that what you're saying?
Do you really believe that will
be enough to end the fighting?
That's right, and I'm betting
everything on that fact.
So you wanna use the
auto-piloted sub to slip
behind enemy lines the
next time they attack.
And what happens
once you get there?
Miwa Hino will open
a dialog with their Mir.
I'll command the ship myself,
so you'll be in charge
here while I'm gone.
And what did Yumiko
have to say about this plan?
She agreed, as long as she
was able to join her daughter
on the boat.
She knows the risks.
But we believe
everyone will return.
If we cannot stop these enemy
attacks, our Core will soon die,
and our island will
be stolen from us.
This is our last,
best hope for survival.
We must succeed at all costs!
You're stronger
than I am, Tomotsu.
You never once turned
your back on the Fafners.
No, Ma'am.
This machine erased
my daughter and son-in-law
from this world and
I've avoided it ever since.
Logarithm Spiral Model.
Start-up initiated.
This is something their mother
and father left behind for them.
I have to believe it
will protect them for me.
The following are going
to be your team selections.
Mobile force:
Kenji Kondo, Sakura Kaname,
Rina and Akira Nishio.
Defense force: Maya Tomi,
Canon Hazama, Hiroto Doma,
and Koyo Kasugai.
Mobile Force's objective
will be to infiltrate
the enemy's home base.
With luck, we can
take them by surprise.
We'll only have
one shot at this.
Let's do our best
to make it count.
It's time to erase the pain.
I show Mark Vier is requesting
permission to sortie.
Open up the gate.
Mark Vier is going out.
Commence
"Operation Azure, Mark 2"!
Keep the camouflage
mirror up in roam mode.
Stand by to
activate control program.
All units engage!
He's here.
No sign of the enemy vessel.
Where are they?
If we're in the wrong place,
that means the island will be--!
Prepare to fire torpedoes.
At what, sir?
Our intel came to us
from Soshi Minashiro.
That ship is out there.
Craft identified as Neo
U.N. carrier Bollearios!
A camouflage mirror
and Welle Shields?
It's copied our defense system.
So in order to defeat us,
they've learned to become us.
Maintain course!
Ready the Fafners!
Distance to the enemy
shield is two hundred!
Zero Fafner, go!
Bring it down!
It isn't breaking!
Quick, tune in to
the shield's wavelength!
Quiet!
I know my job!
Sir!
The shield has been breached!
Mark Drei, take off!
Torpedo batteries, T-1
through T-3, covering fire!
Mark Acht, you're
clear for take off!
Covering fire!
Picking up a new energy pattern
in the sky above the carrier.
It's the enemy Mir.
Get the Hino family
on the phone, please.
What?
Our island?
So much hatred.
Stop it, Mir!
Don't make me carry
a burden like that!
Eat this!
Enemy field,
descending from above!
Do not let it reach us!
Go!
Dodge it!
Release all remaining shields!
Take the island
full speed ahead!
Don't cry, Tsubaki.
I'm not scared.
The Assimilation.
It's beginning.
I couldn't stop it.
Why can't I save anyone?
I've got to protect my friends!
Where's Kazuki?
Give him back!
You want to go outside?
Can we?
I can't talk from in here.
Miwa!
No.
It's far too dangerous!
Perhaps.
But it might just be our
only way to break through.
Alert our Fafner pilots.
We're coming up.
We'll surface
behind the enemy ship.
It's time to clear the path.
Is that Kazuki's mother?
Please Synchronize me
with your Mir.
You may Use me to
keep the core alive.
Akane!
Why are you doing this?
It is because this
is my final possibility.
No.
Because of something
the former core told me.
That this island was the place
I should come home to.
There are no enemies
detected overhead.
Then take us up!
Are you alright?
Don't worry.
For now, I'm still right here.
Huh?
Hey, you're doing great.
Are you ready for more?
Yeah!
Why won't you just stop this?
What're you gonna do now?
Erase everything in
the world you don't like?
Don't you see; Mir was
supposed to be reborn!
The fire you humans brought
down on us changed everything!
So then you try
to change it again!
Soshi gambled
everything on you!
He sent you to meet us!
He believed that
you were different!
My choice has
already been forced!
I've made your kind suffer.
How can I change after that?
Listen.
I've hurt people, too.
People like Soshi
I have caused him so much pain.
But still, he always
believed in me.
Don't you see?
You are me.
And I?
I am you.
Wait!
There's always another choice.
And even if it's
painful sometimes.
You just have to
keep choosing to be there!
Kazuki!
No!
Don't disappear!
Mir.
Please, I-- I don't
want to fight anymore!
The sky.
See?
The sky is beautiful.
Yes, we're both here.
And I'm happy, too.
Neo U.N. bombers.
Enola 512's, inbound!
Sending hails, but no answer!
So they wanna wipe out the
enemy and us along with 'em.
You assholes.
We're humans, too!
And we're right here!
Mama!
I'm scared!
Miwa, no!
No, don't erase her!
Stop, Mir!
I think the sky
is beautiful, too.
Let us be born together.
It's time for us
to say goodbye, Seri.
Mama, that was scary!
My baby!
They sacrificed
themselves to shield us.
"Help me. Stop the pain."
It's finished.
The core has
completed its growth phase.
Oh, Akane.
Shield output and biosphere
functions are all still normal.
And radioactivity
readings are-- are zero!
It's a miracle!
No, it's not a miracle.
The island just protected
us to the very last.
The pain.
It's fading.
It's the Mir.
It's become air.
Look!
They're going away!
All the fighting.
Does this mean
it's finally over?
That is a choice we'll
hope they continue to make.
All that's certain is that
our planet has just become
their homeland as well.
We finally have a blue sky.
Seri.
Kazuki.
I can't see you.
Is that you, Kurusu?
I wanted to at least erase
the thing that kept you
from seeing the sky.
I'm sorry to do it
without asking.
But it makes me happy to know
you'll get to see it again.
And he's gone.
One day, you might come to the
place where he'll be born anew.
And if you can't look at
the sky together, he'll be sad.
That was his final thought.
Is it really you?
He was protecting
my existence that whole time.
He fought against Mir
even as he obeyed.
Instead of assimilation, he led
us to a peaceful coexistence.
I can see you.
I can really see you, Soshi.
Thank you, Kazuki.
Thank you, for protecting
my place to come home to.
Welcome home.
Welcome home, Soshi!
The boundless pain
that fills our world.
Does it all have
some place to go home to?
For now.
I choose to believe that
supreme serenity awaits us
when we finally make it home and
that that is why we're here.