Eternal father, strong to save.
Whose arm hath bound
the restless wave
Who bids the mighty ocean deep,
its own appointed limits keep...
Oh, hear us when we cry to thee,
for those who peril on the sea.
Most holy trinity
of love and power,
please shield our brothers
in danger's hour.
From rock and tempest, fire
or foe, protect them please;
wherever they go.
Thus evermore
shall rise to thee...
glad hymns of praise -
from land...
and sea.
We are departing immediately
for the operation zone.
Departure stations!
These brain waves
in the 30 to 50 hertz range
are called gamma rays.
A Lambda Driver is
capable of generating
a repulsive force field
only when the strength
of these waves exceeds
a certain set level.
However, research up to
this point indicates that it is
difficult for an individual
to generate powerful
gamma waves intentionally,
not to mention continuously.
There is a method
for producing a similar
response artificially...
by administering the drug
T-i-970, which is synthesized
in very limited quantities.
What does that mean?
It means, sergeant that
deploying a Lambda Driver
for long periods of time
is next to impossible.
Excluding certain cases like
the Behemoth, of course.
In other words, the enemy
will get away with using it
and that makes us
shit out of luck.
Yeah, it doesn't even make
sense to talk about it.
Now hang on a sec, we still
have the Arbalest on our side.
Yeah, but we can't afford
another startup failure
like we had in Nanking.
Hi, Al.
Confirming:
Sergeant Sousuke Sagara.
Initialized.
How are you today?
Today's PMCS at 1730 hours
was rated as satisfactory.
Lieutenant Sachs
was the duty officer.
The maintenance record number
is 051021-01B-F-001.
Would you like
to view this record?
If you would like to perform
an additional check,
you will need to change
the current settings.
End the current
training mode, connect to
an external power source,
then engage the secondary.
Okay, I get it.
I only woke you up on a whim.
Training message:
Explanation needed regarding
the word "whim."
Try deducing it on your own, Al.
Roger.
Complete.
Shall I show you the results?
Go ahead.
Regarding the meaning of
"whim." Most likely match:
A concept similar to
"discretion" or "doubt."
Second possible match: A
concept similar to "enthusiasm"
or "diligence."
Third possible match: A
concept similar to "disorder"
or "erratic."
Fourth possible match: A
concept similar to "play."
You know what "playing" is?
Affirmative.
Is that the concept of "whim"?
It's close to
"play" and "erratic."
Roger.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Who taught you
what "playing" is?
It was Senior engineer
Bani Morauta.
And he was the
engineer who made you?
Affirmative.
Your lousy father, huh?
Training message.
What is the meaning of "lousy"?
Stop saying "training message"
every time you have a question.
"Lousy" is a weapon system
that only works when it wants.
In other words, you.
Affirmative.
The ARX system is incomplete.
You agree with me?
Affirmative.
You are a component
of the failure.
What did you say?
The ARX system cannot
fully function without
your complete cooperation.
You are part of
the system, Sergeant.
If you can explain your
current problem to me,
I may be able to
give you advice.
Please proceed.
Advice?
From an A.I.?
Affirmative.
I am not experiencing
any problem.
I do not agree, Sergeant.
Why not?
My intuition says otherwise.
Intuition?
Who the hell even taught you
the word "intuition?"
Maybe you should tell your
"intuition" its accusations
are off-base.
Your order is nonsense.
"Intuition"
cannot be controlled,
ordered or persuaded.
It comes from within the soul.
It's quite obvious that
you're the one who's
and full of nonsense.
Stop kidding around!
Sousuke?
Hey Sousuke, are you up there?
Yeah, What is it?
Commander Kalinin wants us
for a mission briefing.
A Mission.
I believe you've already
heard about this, but an AS
of unknown affiliation
has appeared in Hong Kong.
This lone, renegade unit has
caused widespread destruction
and we believe it's
hiding within city limits.
Both the North and South Chinese
armies have taken casualties.
This, in addition to the Nanking
incident, has pushed tensions
to a breaking point.
If conditions keep
deteriorating, it could lead
to the dissolution
of the peace treaty.
And Hong Kong would become
the inevitable battleground.
Lieutenant Clouseau
will take it from here.
Take a look at that.
This photograph was taken
26 hours ago near Yau Ma Tei
on the Kowloon peninsula.
We believe it's probably
the same machine we
fought in Helmajistan.
After destroying a South Chinese
tank, it used a smoke bomb
to cover its escape.
Since then, it's appeared then
disappeared in various places
in Hong Kong and Kowloon,
continuing to destroy
anything in its path.
Close to 10 AS units
have been destroyed,
and there have been
numerous casualties.
The bottom line is
they can't find it
and they can't kill it, either.
Considering what
we've seen in the past,
we believe this machine probably
has an ECS that's as good
as ours if not superior.
What's this terrorist after?
Unknown.
And no one's talking.
An educated guess says
wrecking the peace treaty,
or Hong Kong's economy.
But then, this whole thing
could be directed at us.
Regardless of what
kind of AS it is...
it can't run
longer than 24 hours.
The machine
requires maintenance,
the weapons need to be
reloaded with fresh rounds,
and the operator needs to rest.
We have to find this arm
slave quickly then send in
an M9 platoon in stealth mode
to pacify the situation.
And I'll need every one of
you to run reconnaissance.
Reconnaissance?
We're coordinating with
the Intelligence Division
in Hong Kong.
They know the politics
and the lay of the land,
so consider them an asset.
You'll leave by helicopter
under cover of night.
We need to get you
there before the M9s.
Does that include Sousuke?
It does.
Sir, but don't you think we
should have him standing by
with the Arbalest?
The plan for this mission
doesn't call for deployment
of the Arbalest, Major Mao.
But why?
It's not reliable!
When I look at it from up here,
it really hasn't
changed that much.
You've been here before?
A few times before
the mainland took over.
Some of the relatives
on my mom's side used to
live in this part of town.
I freeloaded off of 'em
for a couple months before
I hooked up with Mithril.
Total slacker.
You?
A slacker?
For starters, I got myself
kicked out of the Marines.
And the thought of going to
work in New York so I could live
with my parents was
out of the question.
My dad was always on my ass.
That Air Force bastard...
Your father was a military man?
Yep.
A chickenshit bomber pilot.
But he retired and
he's running a company now.
He's a tightwad, cocky bastard,
and on top of that...
he's always plotting something.
Like what?
Well, when I graduated high
school and was looking for work,
he pulled a bunch of strings
to try to get me married
to some rich jackass who'd
just graduated from Harvard.
That really pissed
me off, ya know?!
So on the day that I was
supposed to get married,
I ran away and joined
the Marines instead.
No way!
Yeah...
I'm serious!
I snuck out of the chapel
and ran to the recruiter...
I was still wearing
my wedding dress.
The guy behind the desk got this
goofy look on face and said...
"are you serious?"
"You're god damn right!" I said!
And of course, they all
tried to talk me out of it.
"Come on now,
you'd be happier if
you got married instead!"
"Won't your mom and dad
be worried about you?"
So I then told them, "Nah... "
My dad's in the Air Force.
"When they heard that,
they had a change of heart!
"Why didn't you say that
in the first place?
Sign right here, honey!"
So, how does that grab ya?
Oh God!
That's freakin' awesome!
I love 'er?!
Unbelievable!
Isn't that great?
All things considered,
it really was a great time...
The moment I made
that decision I felt like
the whole world
opened up to me.
It felt like
I could do anything,
and go anywhere, you know?
Why didn't you?
Well, a lot's happened
since then, Sousuke.
Frustration, danger,
disappointment...
But I really think I did
the right thing back then...
I can definitely say I like
myself more than I used to.
So there, that's my story.
Anyway, coming back to the
city triggered a few memories,
but don't read
too much into it, okay?
Phew!
Apologies for the wait.
I'm Mr. Hunter with Hong
Kong's Intelligence Division.
Now this goes
without saying, but...
both the Northern and
Southern armies have been
getting downright nervous.
We'll have to move covertly
and avoid provoking
anyone from either side.
Security's tight and both
armies have stopped traffic
at the border.
The harbor is closed and most
flights have been cancelled.
And let me tell you,
it's playing hell
with their stock market.
People are feeling a little
trapped at the moment.
what about the AS
causing this mess?
Well, we haven't been able
to observe it long enough
to get a fix on it yet.
It's last appearance was
at 1015 hours, in the town
of Shau Kei Wan in Hong Kong.
And you're absolutely sure
it's hiding somewhere
in Hong Kong, correct?
I really can't confirm anything,
but our analysts and artificial
intelligence seem to think so.
And a lifetime of using
THIS doesn't hurt!
We took the liberty of
pinpointing possible locations.
So what do you think?
Excluding the suburbs
and small islands,
we'll get aerial recon
using the choppers.
Anti-ECS sensors are going
to be useless in urban areas
so we'll have to go
street by street.
And we can cross off
any place that has a lot
of doves and crows.
Why birds?
It seems that birds can
still see a cloaked AS unit.
Most likely because the
ECS system can't mask out
the ultraviolet light.
Crows start screeching
like hell they're near one.
And dogs go nuts.
They're sensitive
to the ECS's ozone smell.
I see.
Anything else?
Well, that's all I can think of.
Hey, Sousuke?!
Do you have anything?
No.
Not really.
Hmmm, this looks
a lot more promising.
That narrows it down to
49 locations in Hong Kong
plus another 78
locations in Kowloon.
If we divide the search equally,
we could get it done in a day.
If conditions are
favorable, of course.
Man...
Hunter sure has his hand in a
lot of businesses around here.
Okay, time to start moving out.
Martial law's in effect,
so watch it.
What if the police or the
army stop us at a checkpoint?
That Hunter guy can't be
in everyone's back pocket...
That's true.
So if you can run, run away.
But no firefights
with the locals.
It's not their fault
they're in this mess.
If they catch you,
you're probably in for
a tough interrogation until
Hunter pulls some strings.
And you better keep your mouth
shut even if they torture you.
Got it?
Man, you're pretty harsh.
And another thing,
you better think about
what you're going to
do if you spot the enemy.
I won't allow anyone
dying out there without
getting my permission.
Understood?
Roger that.
Look at that...
I've never seen this
street so barren before.
Damn, you think they're
gonna hassle us, too?
Hunter's contacts
better be good.
It's up to you, Mao.
My Chinese is fine,
roll it down.
This is crazy.
I didn't think I'd ever
see this tunnel so empty.
Really...
Anyone who knew what
Hong Kong was like before this
would be shocked.
Think about it for a minute.
What if Tokyo
ended up like this?
Shinjuku and Ginza,
split right down the middle,
and right on the brink
of war with each other.
Like, instead of shopping
arcades filled with kids eating
ice cream and stuff, they'd
be lined from stem to stern
with tanks and arm slaves.
And instead of taking
quiet walks on the bayside,
you'd be ducking and dodging
through pillboxes and bunkers.
I mean, THIS is not the
Hong Kong that I know and love.
It's...
just insane.
Hey, Sousuke?
What's wrong?
It's...
nothing really.
I'm impressed.
The Southern Army's
letting us pass, also.
I guess Hunter
really is a big shot, huh?
We're almost at
the destination.
What should we do if we hit
the jackpot right off the bat?
Not a problem.
We can handle it.
Sagara, calm down!
You're confused
and having delusions!
Sagara!
Yo, Sagara!
Just let me take care of this
and don't you say a word!
I'm sorry...
I told you to shut
your mouth, didn't I?!
Souske!
Lucky for us, the local army
found bigger fish to fry.
Let's move it.
What the hell were you thinking?
Tryin' to get us killed?
Sorry.
You're still thinking
about Kaname, aren't you?
All right, that's enough!
Either you pull your
head out of your ass
or you get the hell
out of the van!
I know it bugs you.
But right now I can't play
the "big sister"
role for you, okay?!
I am NOT ready to die out here!
I mean, with the state
you're in, I'm better off alone!
You're right.
Sousuke?
Sorry.
but I can't do this anymore.
Continue the mission.
Abandoning my mission.
Having lost sight of everything,
I wander the streets
of Hong Kong.
I don't have any place to go,
or even the skill to
take refuge in depravity.
Next time...
"His Problem" I feel nothing...
except this escalating tension.