The scene here in
Taboli City is chaotic.
The Balic Republic's army,
anti-government guerrillas,
and armed militias from other
factions have been fighting
since the breakdown of the
ceasefire agreement yesterday.
Witnesses report nurmerous
shootings and acts of cruelty,
making life in
the city very tense.
Also, we've received reports
of nearly 100 refugees stranded
in a medical facility just
outside of the c--
All right,
that should do it.
Al, test the data links.
Roger.
ADM, on.
PCL, contact.
Opening from 403 to 412.
Commencing TAC transfer.
Complete.
Check backup.
Roger.
The observation team
says we're running late
for this little party.
Hey, no biggie!
The hero's supposed
to arrive late.
I'm not gonna help if you start
getting shot up, you idiot!
Man, that's cold.
Colonel Maress,
there are only the sick,
elderly, and women
and children here.
If you have even the
slightest human compassion,
please let us go.
Gebo 4 to all units.
We've arrived at Point Echo.
Activating ECS.
Now in stealth mode.
Opening cargo bay hatches.
I, I'm begging you.
Perhaps if you reconsider,
God will find it in
his heart--
Urzu 2, roger.
Let's move!
I don't give a damn about you
or the god you believe in.
Colonel Maress...
This is Urzu 6.
I'm good to go!
Urzu 7- ready to drop.
Now die!
What the hell?
This is Urzu 6.
I'm in firing position.
It's time to party!
All units to
defensive positions!
Red 1 is...
Dammit!
Radio and sensors are down.
What's going on?
Are they jamming us?
Arm slave!
AS spotted!
Gunner, fire at will!
Stay focused!
Close formation!
There aren't that many of them.
Colonel Maress, who in the
living hell are those guys?
They couldn't
possibly be the rebels!
They're Mithril.
Mithril?
Heard of 'em before?
There's rumors about an
elusive mercenary force which
doesn't align itself
with any governing body.
They have extraordinary
personnel and weaponry that's
10 years in advance
of the rest of the world.
Apparently they're "wannabe"
international peacekeepers.
But I never
thought I'D see 'em...
But why would
they help the refugees?
No idea.
But you saw those
AS units, didn't you?
Not even the Americans have
that kind of machinery yet.
It has to be those
Mithril bastards!
We should call
in reinforcements.
Do it now!
Throw everything
we've got at them.
And don't let 'em
get out alive!
OR those heathen refugees!
Mike 13 destroyed.
All hostile targets
have been neutralized.
Master mode 6.
Keep watching
with active sensors.
Roger.
Urzu 6, Urzu 7, this is Urzu 2.
Defend the perimeter around
the camp and secure a landing
area for the choppers.
Urzu 7, wilco.
Urzu 6, wilco.
This is Gebo 4.
I'm setting down on the L.Z.
And you better
watch my ass, Weber.
Heh!
I don't go for GUYs' asses!
Just get movin' and
load up, truck driver!
Yeah, whatever.
We're taking the
wounded onboard first!
All men, help out!
Women and children,
get together and stay there
until further instructions!
Man, they're nothing but
old men, old ladies, and kids.
So why does a government's
army waste time attacking them?
Ethnic conflicts can
be like that, Urzu 6.
But in this case,
there are probably
more complicated issues.
Like politics?
Economics, too.
A state like this
deliberately violates
international peace treaties,
giving major world powers an
excuse to "investigate" - and
then decide whom to approach
for under-the-table
deals as to mineral rights,
other natural
resources or whatever.
And now we're
a part of that, too...
Absolutely disgusting, isn't it?
But it's still worth it.
Exactly.
Teiwaz 12, situation?
This is Teiwaz 12.
We've got two combined-arms
companies approaching from
the northwest.
Near coordinates 36A, 87A.
12 AS units, 12 MBTs,
and a lot more out there.
Looks like ya still
got some time, but...
Shit!
It's Triple A!
They fired from the hill
10K to the southwest.
I'm hit with damage to the
engine and pressure gauge.
Unable to restart.
I'm going in
for a crash landing.
Teiwaz 12, you okay?
Teiwaz 12, respond!
Yeah, I...
I'm still here...
I'll send you data on
the Triple A position.
And we'll scuttle the
chopper and head back...
It's an Anti-ECS missile?
Impossible, I didn't know these
guys had that kind of firepower!
Yeah, this is bad.
They're all gonna get shot down.
Urzu 2, we can't take off now!
We reach 150 feet,
and a missile will take us
and the refugees down!
I know, but we have units
advancing on our position.
How are your NOE skills?
Stay low along
alternate route two,
and we'll provide the escort...
DON'T, Sousuke!
I'll take out the
anti-air missiles.
What about the rendezvous?
Handle it!
We can argue about it later.
Understood.
We'll escort the choppers
to coordinates 34B, 99A.
Be careful.
Roger.
We better move it.
Or we'll be boxed-in
and dead in no time.
Report from the
anti-air missile squad.
We've shot down
an enemy chopper.
Good.
Keep them pinned down.
If we can attack them while
they're still on the ground,
we'll crush them
with our main troops.
Relay their position
to artillery!
Urzu 7.
I'm near the enemy
triple A battery.
Five more minutes.
This is Urzu 2.
Moving away from L.Z.
Distance from destination is...
Whoa!
That was close.
That was just a greeting.
If we don't move our asses,
they're gonna rain down
artillery on those choppers.
If we don't hurry,
WE'RE gonna be surrounded!
Even our M-9s aren't powerful
enough to handle two companies.
I know.
Doesn't look good...
Two enemy AS units spotted.
Bearing 048.
Distance 15.
Damn!
They really are here!
All units, stop.
We've got enemy AS units!
Urzu 6, watch 4 o'clock.
Urzu 6, roger!
Warning: Two RF missiles
locked on Gebo 4.
ECM ON!
Set the blip enhancer
to maximum power!
Roger.
We're getting our butts
shot off out here!
How are things over there?
Almost done.
All that's left is...
Contact!
Enemy batteries and
radar have been destroyed.
Escape through the hole
in their anti-air net.
All Gebo units,
did you hear that?
We're pulling
out of here immediately.
Roger.
Urzu 2 and Urzu 6, hurry up and
dock for transport choppers.
What about Urzu 7?
We don't have the fuel
or the time for that!
And their anti-air radar
could be back up any minute!
Continue the extraction
and don't worry about me.
I'm heading to the
alternate escape route
and I'll get out on my own.
You can handle it, right?
Affirmative.
I have to hand in a homework
assignment tomorrow.
So I can't die now.
Okay.
We'll meet at the Danaan.
Roger.
Listen up!
We're pulling out!
We always end up
dropping our pants,
mooning them and
then running away.
How uncool.
Gold 2 to all units.
The enemy AS is heading
South down Revolution Street.
Set up a blockade at
Point oh-three-twenty one.
Blue 1, acknowledged.
Blue 1 to all Blue Team units.
Form two lines and
await further orders.
Permission to fire at will.
Perfect.
Don't let that
white arm slave get away!
Shot cannon ammunition: zero.
I know that.
Missile warning.
Bearing one-two-eight.
Warning.
Main Battle Tank.
What in the hell was that?
Success.
The Lambda Driver is...
Talk later.
Damage report!
Now!
Class B damage to
the right shoulder.
Stabilizers have malfunctioned.
Critical errors in
the targeting system.
Urzu 2, this is Urzu 7.
Due to enemy presence,
I've abandoned the
alternate escape route.
I've taken only minor damage,
but I'm getting surrounded.
I don't have much
ammo left, either.
Urzu 2, do you copy?
This is Urzu 7.
Please respond...
This is the Tuatha de Danaan.
Teletha Testerossa speaking.
Urzu 7, do you read me?
The Captain?
I have transport
helicopters standing by
under a communications blackout.
Please follow my directions
to the escape route, Mr. Sagara.
Roger.
I must apologize, ma'am.
Enemy troops are stronger
than my assessment and
I'm cut off from escape.
No, I don't think
that's quite true...
I've transmitted
the data to you.
Please move to
the marked position.
That position?
That's running
right into the enemy!
It's okay, hurry up!
Roger.
Over and out.
8 knots.
Depth, one-hundred.
We've reached
the target location.
Very well.
Put the EMFC into "active" mode.
Pivot 180 degrees and hold.
Aye, ma'am.
EMFC active.
Helmsman, make
your course 1-2-7.
Answering EMFC active; Coming
about to course 1-2-7, aye.
Please brace for impact.
Mr. Mardukas, all ahead
full - on my signal.
Aye, Captain.
Enemy AS is heading from
Anton Street to Uthro Bridge.
Trapped like a rat.
It's payback time for destroying
all my precious weapons.
TDDHQ, this is Urzu 7.
2 minutes from target location.
Playing cat-and-mouse...
Warning.
Arm slave and fighting
vehicle dead ahead.
Distance 5.
Chain gun ammunition zero.
Target location reached.
This is the 3rd
Combined Armored Company.
Silver Team and Copper Team,
Green Team and Yellow Team,
formation complete!
Ready and waiting.
This is the 8th
Combined Armored Company.
Gold Team and Platinum Team,
Blue Team and Purple Team,
formation complete!
Sniping team in position.
All troops are
in position, Colonel.
Good!
This is Urzu 7.
I am surrounded
by enemy forces.
No ammo.
Escape impossible.
Abandonment and self-destruct
protocol recommended.
Denied.
I'll lose my school credits.
Attention Arm Slave Pilot.
You are completely surrounded!
Emergency blow!
Aye, Ma'am.
Emergency Blow.
Main Ballast Tank!
Uptrim 5 degrees.
Counting down!
Ten!
Nine!
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
What?!
The Arbalest has been recovered.
Let's shake them up a little.
SUBLAR batteries engage!
Roger.
Launch all SUBLARS!
Launching all SUBLARS.
Aye!
Hold speed for crash dive!
Aye, Captain.
Set for crash dive!
Is that an...
amphibious submarine?!
Impossible!
Who the hell ARE those guys?
"Ii kuni tsukurou."
Muromachi shogunate...
It's the Kamakura!
That's a junior
high school question!
How do you expect to pass
the class like that, Sousuke?
I'm bad at Japanese history.
...and Modern
Literature and Classics.
And for Pete's sake, stop doing
your homework after a mission!
Come on!
You just did something like
straight out of a Bond movie
and now you wanna study?
That's lame!
I'd fail otherwise.
Just do what I used to do!
Slap that homework together
at the last minute.
Kurz.
You sure talk
pretty big for someone
who hasn't written
his OWN report!
Oh, you mean this week's?
And last week's too.
The logistics unit
keeps bugging me about it.
Try putting yourself
in my shoes for once.
Oh, yeah...
It must be difficult
for "Big Sis" Mao...
It's your fault they're
riding my ass, so DO IT!
That tickles...
We've just passed
15 degrees North latitude.
No ships spotted
within a 30 mile radius.
Set the alert condition
to Yellow Three.
Executive Officer,
you have the watch.
Yes, ma'am.
Setting alert
condition to Yellow 3.
X-O now on watch.
Mr. Sagara?
Oh, Captain!
Oh, no, you don't
have to get up.
I only stopped by
to eat some dinner.
But I...
Don't worry about it.
Ma'am.
Homework?
Yes, ma'am.
So is it difficult?
To me anyway.
Well, you know
I could tutor you...
NO!
I could never ask the
captain to do such a thing!
Just kidding.
I knew that you would
say something like that.
But it does look difficult.
It's...
part of my mission.
Mission...
Captain.
Thank you for what
you did for me.
You saved my life today.
That's...
part of MY mission.
HE'S LATE!!!
What is that idiot thinking,
being completely out of
reach two days straight?!
He still has the
notes I let him borrow!
I couldn't do my homework!
I'm gonna KILL him!
Take it easy, Kaname!
I'm sure Sousuke
has his reasons.
We should give him
a warm welcome back.
Not a chance!
He does this every time!
Oh, hello Sousuke.
Sousuke!
Give me my notes back now!
What?
I'm sorry, Chidori.
I forgot to bring them back.
Forgot?
AGAIN?!
Then go back and get them!
They're in your room, right?
I can't.
Why not?!
Because I left them in a
submarine 2000 kilometers from--
This is what Balic forces
shot down Teiwaz 12 with.
It's an improved
version of the Patriot.
And it's loaded
with a powerful ECCS.
This means that
all things being equal,
our systems will be
ineffective against them.
As of right now, only a limited
number of advanced countries
have this kind of missile.
But the Army of the Balic
Government had those missiles.
So how do you think we should
interpret this development,
Commander Kalinin?
The assumption is that a very
powerful outside organization
independently supplied
them with the missiles.
Impressive resources
for an independent.
Right.
And there's also a distinct
possibility that they acquired
the missile system anticipating
our intervention in this matter.
So they have an
intelligence network?
Correct.
And the seajacking incident
may have been a source.
Of course, I doubt the
enemy is in a position
to freely detect all of
our movements, but still...
They're dangerous.
Indeed.
Essentially, we've got to
be more diligent and cautious
in future operations.
Or otherwise...
I know.
The alternative is...
we all die.
A typical day in Tokyo.
But I didn't yet know
that in the shadows
of that ephemeral peace, the
wheels of a vast conspiracy
had started to move.
Next time: "The Situation
Beneath the Surface."
Dangerous people gather,
drawn by the smell of gunpowder.