Chidori
Chidori is
She's dead.
Sousuke.
Sorry, but we had to
follow you out here.
Mao and the others
are fighting the Venom,
without countermeasures
to the Lambda Driver.
We just sent our
coordinates to the Danaan.
And they're going to be sending
the Arbalest out here shortly.
We need you.
Come on!
You're the only guy
who can do this, man!
They don't stand
a chance out there!
She's dead.
It's his damned curse.
I let her die; then I kill him.
There's nothing left for me now.
Kaname's dead?
I never had
a future to begin with.
Have fun killing yourselves.
Die for all I care.
In the end we're nothing.
just chunks of meat.
Have you lost your mind?
You sound just like
those terrorists!
What, you don't realize that?
Fine, then.
You wanna talk
like a terrorist?
Then I'm gonna
treat you like one.
Corporal, wait!
A soldier who's lost his soul
is nothing but a killer.
We can't just leave him here.
You don't even
have a clue, do you?
More than you do.
Is that right?
Piece of shit.
It was useless
to send this thing.
I can't even use it anyway.
And I don't WANT to.
That's right.
Just lie there and rust away.
So where are you going?
I said, "where
are you going?"
Huh?
Don't have an answer for me?
Chidori?
What?
Cat got your tongue?
Chidori you're alive?
What?
Is that all you have to say?
Ya know, I've been through hell
and back trying to get here!
I was about to jump into your
arms all dramatic-like just
a second ago, and lucky me
what do I get instead?
And I quote.
"Chidori, you're alive."
THAT'S the best you can do?
You completely
ruined the moment!
So what are you going to do?
How are you
going to take responsibility
for this, Sousuke?
Now, wait, Chidori.
I don't understand
what you're talking.
SHUT UP!
Does it hurt?
I hope so!
That's for the pain
you've caused to my heart!
And THIS is for
the pain in my body!
And this one's for
the PAIN IN MY SOUL!
It-It's a monster.
Wha'd you say?
What are you doing?
I'm taking you back with me,
Sergeant Dumb-ass!
I mean I almost get killed,
and you're nowhere around!
And it actually made me
realize that... I mean,
I'm trying to tell you
that I... Um, that is, I...
You what?
I, uh, you see.
I mean.
It's my responsibility
as class rep!
Huh?
Looks like all my determination
petered out after only one day.
So, what did you want to say?
Never mind!
This old guy named "Hunter"
or something told me that Mao
and the others
are fighting, right?
So what in the world
are you doing HERE?
I just can't do it.
Why's that?
'Cause I can't
operate my machine.
And what's worse is...
I deserted YOU.
And that's why
you're all depressed?
I don't know.
Is it really worth
throwing everything away?
I just don't know!
I understand.
You got worn out, right?
And then you
couldn't tell anyone.
And because you're so
self-conscious and hard-working
you just reached your limit.
Am I right?
Well, I don't know
Pathetic.
Coward.
Good-for-nothing.
But you're strong,
and you're kind to people.
You still get things done
even though you're useless.
At least that's the kind
of guy I thought you were.
Huh?
Weak people are parasites
who feed on the strong.
So am I?
Do you really like being around
a bunch of goddamn weaklings?
So I'm useless?
Come on aren't you?
I'm sorry, Chidori.
I...
What... what did I do?
Shut up!
Everyone's in danger, right?!
Not to mention.
your CLASS CREDITS!
Now MOVE your ass!
Perth 1 to Urzu 1.
Fall back three
blocks to the south.
Try to lure him.
Roger.
The enemy has to be
getting tired.
You're better off if
you drag out the fight.
Provided we can hold out.
Dammit!
That's quite enough of you
Perth 1 this is Urzu 1.
What is it, Urzu 1?
We've got guests.
Five Venoms acquired.
Well, it looks like we finally
caught up with you, kitten.
Going berserk in an unauthorized
theatre of operations.
What am I going to do with you?
Remember, terrorist activity
without company approval
is a NO-NO!
And what that means
You, little girl, have
JUST PISSED DADDY OFF!
Then I'm glad I did it.
Huh?
I know that Amalgam caused
the civil war that
destroyed our hometown.
My sister and I will
have achieved our goal
if we get revenge on you.
Really?
Your sister, you say?
Oh yeah, that's right!
I forgot about
our special guest!
HERE SHE IS!
Direct from a rooftop in the
middle of "Who-Gives-a-Damn"
Japan, your little sister!
Ooooh!
Seems a little out
of sorts to me.
Hey!
Yu Lan!
Are you okay!
Say something!
Oh, that big, strong, sexy
Mister Gates caught me Big Sis!
It's so sad!
But now I'm so happy
Yes, I'm so happy that we're
finally TOGETHER again!
Gosh.
All this brings
a fucking tear to my eye.
Stop fighting, Big Sister!
Nothing good
ever comes from war!
And after all, Mister Gates
has won my heart!
Oopsie!
Goddamn thing broke.
BASTARD!!!
You make this too easy, bitch!
Say good niiiiiight!
Ooh this is fun!
Hey, you over there.
You're one of those Mithril
assholes, aren't you?
You know I didn't plan on
killing any of you today but
Ehh!
Shit happens.
Ben!
Get out!
Stay away!
You won't make it in time!
So, my poor little
helpless sheep,
are you done saying
your prayers yet?
Because it's sleepy time!
What was that?
Did YOU take that shot, Urzu 6?
Nope.
Wasn't me.
But it looks like HE finally
decided to grace us with
his presence.
He showed up right
in the nick of time!
You were just waiting to make
a big entrance, weren'tcha?!
Yeah, whatever.
Uruz 7 to all units.
Sorry about the wait.
Let me handle
the rest from here.
So, it's the Arbalest
We have activation, Al?
Affirmative.
Lambda Driver
activation confirmed.
Sometimes it works,
sometimes it doesn't.
What a piece of junk.
Agreed.
Total garbage.
Oh, so now you're
getting cute on me.
Huh, funny guy?
Affirmative.
You need new material.
Urzu 7, are you all right?
Affirmative.
Engage at will.
Roger.
Five Venoms, Al.
Normally, we should be
retreating at this point.
No, we can defeat them,
Sergeant.
You're right!
Let's go!
Roger.
Target the first machine.
Scatter!
You piece of shit!
Wha?
No way!
That's impossible!
Two!
Enemy inbound.
You miserable piece of SHIT!
That makes three.
Hey, that's my line!
No!
That's four!
Damn!
Back off!
Back the fuck off!
I'll kill him
with one little slice!
Don't move!
Ben, NO!
What the hell is going on here?
I thought Mithril's
Lambda Driver was unstable!
So how can it be so strong?!
You little shit
Who in the hell do
you think you are?
Who, me?
I'll tell you exactly who I am.
I really couldn't
care less about Mithril.
I'm from Class 2-4 at Jindai
Tokyo Municipal High School.
Hey, now!
I've still got a hostage here.
I am student number 41
I'm in charge of waste
disposal and umbrellas.
Hell-OOOOOO!
Shit!
I'm Sousuke Sagara!!!
You know,
I could use a haircut.
I know I told you to believe
in your own abilities and all.
But that was overkill, Sergeant.
My apologies, Lieutenant.
All hostile targets destroyed.
Sergeant, I have a question.
Go ahead.
We just fought a battle
against all odds to a startling
and very decisive victory.
Could you please explain
the reason for our success?
Well, I recently
solved a problem.
I guess that must be it.
A personal problem?
No.
More like OUR problem.
I cannot comprehend
your response.
It's something for you
to think about, then.
Urzu 7 to all units.
All Venoms have been destroyed.
I will be returning to
the Tuatha de Danaan now.
Correction.
Uruz 7 is now proceeding
to his next mission.
I'm leaving the Arbalest here.
Retrieve it whenever you wish.
But pick it up before
the local authorities do.
"Next mission"?
What are you
talking about, Urzu 7?
She's waiting for me.
That is all.
Urzu 7 out.
Wait, Sagara!
Are you going AWOL again?
All right, I'm confused.
Whats his deal?
Oh, it must be THAT.
Yeah, if it's THAT,
it must be okay
No one could have
predicted this.
We can't afford to ignore
the Arbalest's potential.
Oh yes, she was
definitely a factor
Helping that soldier,
and that beautiful machine.
Thank goodness we brought
this to a close without
destroying the entire
city of Hong Kong.
What about Sagara and Chidori?
Looks like they
went back to Tokyo.
Hmph.
Disobeying orders again.
Well if that's true then
you disobeyed orders by
bringing her here, didn't you?
So I guess it's up to the
brass to make a decision then.
I never would have expected you
to defy us in such
a threatening manner.
Sergeant Sagara, I don't think
you quite understand how angry
I am with you right now.
But General Amit.
He is the only soldier
who can handle the Arbalest.
At ease, Captain!
I've already determined
that this man's request
is completely out of line.
General, Sir.
I am only suggesting that
we make a change in the terms
of my enlistment contract.
If this unsatisfactory to you I
will simply pay the penalty fee
and give Mithril my resignation.
How dare you say
such a thing, Sergeant.
Do you really think I'm going
to let you live a normal life
after you've made an enemy
of me and Mithril Intelligence?
Let me ask you this.
General, do you
really think that I haven't
fully prepared myself
to do exactly that?
What's that?!
Listen carefully, General.
I don't remember agreeing
to sell my soul to Mithril.
I have to continue
to do things my own way.
That's all.
I intend to keep on
piloting the Arbalest.
I will keep on attending Jindai
High just like I have been.
You can cut my pay
in half if you wish.
Do you have a problem with that?
Watch your tone
with me, Sergeant!
Sergeant?
I'm just a mercenary, sir.
Nothing but a soldier for hire.
I refuse to be ranked beneath
you as your lap dog, "General."
You punk!
Lord Mallory, what?
Looks like you've lost, General.
This SRT member has
highly valuable skills
and he has just offered
to work for half of his pay.
You're out of
reasons to be angry.
Don't you gree gentlemen?
Yes, I suppose so.
But I'd rather not
let the cat out of the bag.
Well then, is that all?
It looks like it's settled,
Captain Testarossa.
I imagine it's difficult
having personalities like
these in your command?
Not really.
My people are
the best out there.
And you, Sergeant
Your name is
Sousuke Sagara, correct?
Sir!
I will make sure
I remember your name.
This meeting is done.
Farewell and take care.
Sergeant, you had me
sweating bullets.
You almost gave me a coronary.
Yes sir.
I apologize for that.
Honestly...
Yes, sir.
You're behaving
more like a man, now.
Sir?
I knew that you had it in you.
I still need to tell you...
Ma'am?
I'm sorry about
what I said before.
No.
I should have apologized
to you for my conduct.
No, it's okay.
I wasn't very dignified.
I guess I behaved like
a spoiled brat back then.
But...
Anyway...
I was wondering are we,
are you and I still friends?
Friends, Ma'am?
Well, Captain.
Sergeant?
If you really do acknowledge me
as a friend, Madame Captain,
would it be possible
for you to forgive me
for making a blunt remark?
Go ahead
Tessa, I'm really sorry.
You are an incredible person.
To me, you are not just
a superior officer. I...
to me you're more
important than that.
And, if something ever
happens I'll be there for you
Please remember that
Forgive me, I'm sorry
about that, okay?
It was impertinent,
but that's how I really
feel and I had to say so!
Well I'm going now...!
Tessa Tessa He called
me "Tessa!" Oh my gosh!
Oh my gosh!
What do I do now?!
He thinks I'm IMPORTANT!
Seriously If you even think of
doing something like this again,
I'm not going to be
able to cover for you.
Ma'am!
I'm grateful.
Honestly It's a good thing
I decided to keep
that letter in my desk.
And don't think I've forgotten
about that incident with my car.
I don't...
Mr. Sagara!
What are you doing?!!!
You're in danger!
There's a laser sight
targeting you!!!
What in the world
are you talking about?
Hey!
What are you doing Sousuke?!
Take cover!
We're under attack!
Serves you right.
I'm the one doing surveillance
out here in the cold.
So you can entertain me.
Looks like it's going
to be a lovely winter.
I can't believe
you're already causing trouble!
I don't even think
you're taking this seriously!
But Chidori, I...
Quiet, you!
You haven't made any
progress whatsoever!
And you're always,
always, always, always
Always, always, always, always
Always, always, always...
So it's like things
haven't changed at all.
Chidori?
How could you just run away
and leave me here like that
What were you thinking?
I'll never forgive you for that.
Sorry.
"Sorry" isn't going to cut it.
You.
Stupid.
Jerk!
I was frightened!
I was so scared,
because you weren't there!
Don't ever do anything
like that again!
You idiot!
Because I won't
forgive you next time.
Huh?
Kaname and Sousuke?
What are the two of you
doing all alone out here?
We weren't really
doing anything, Kyoko
Oh no, he didn't make
you cry, did he?
Oh you know Sousuke
Sousuke!
Did you think a terrorist
was after her and knock her
on the floor again?!
What?
That's not it
It's not very manly to
make excuses, you big jerk!
Yeah!
Say you're sorry, lame-o!
It's not like that at all.
OH YEAH?!
I'll just give up.
What?
Nothing.
it's not a problem.
And just what do
you mean by THAT, Sousuke?
Huh?
Where do you get off
treating her like that?!
You think you're gonna
get away with making her cry,
you better think again, mister!
I can't believe you'd be
so insensitive, Sousuke.
Gosh, you're such a jerk!
What's wrong with you?
I just remembered.
Hm?
You were trying to tell me
something back in Hong Kong,
right?
What exactly was it?
Well, it was just...
it was nothing.
Oh... I see.