Ancient Greece.
Mediterranean Sea.
Wei, Wu, Shu.
Jin dynasty unified the Northern
and Southern dynasties.
I swear he's
gonna get held back!
I'm sorry...
I'm late...
Oh, Sagara!
So you finally decided to
grace us with your presence.
That nonchalant attitude
is gonna get you in
a heap of trouble, mister!
Yes, sir!
Unfortunately,
circumstances kept me from...
Uh--huh, that's enough!
Just take your seat
and get started!
Right away, sir.
Vincent Bruno.
At the Cross--Yangtze
River Tunnel operation,
you were charged with
communications security,
but you decided to
feed that information
to another organization.
Am I correct?
Answer him!
You know?
The last couple of days
are kinda blurry.
Do it.
Yes, sir!
Don't worry.
This will be over soon.
If you ask me, breaking
his fingers isn't enough.
Oh GOD!
Please don't do any more!
Okay, okay, I understand,
I'll tell you anything you want!
Just don't do any more!
Fine!
Then you WERE responsible
for compromising our security
on that operation? Right?
Yeah! Yeah!
That was me! I did it, OK?!
And who hired you?
I don't know!
Stop lying!
No, it's the truth, dammit!
I swear to God they
wouldn't tell me their names!
All they said is that
they were from...
umm...
Amalgam, yeah, Amalgam!
Amalgam?
They didn't let me
in on any more than THAT.
It's the truth!
I thought maybe those
jokers were from the KGB,
the GRU or something.
I-- I, just didn't
take it too seriously!
But then they paid me
200,000 dollars in advance...
An easy 200, 000
right up front!
I just couldn't refuse it!
I'm sorry!
We've seen enough.
A mercury alloy...
Interesting choice,
wouldn't you say so?
Does the name "Amalgam"
mean anything to you?
A threat that
their caustic properties
could destroy even
fictional metals?
Like Mithril.
But still...
...was all of that necessary?
The interrogation?
It's definitely
unpleasant and painful,
but they weren't
going to kill him.
Yes, it IS unpleasant.
Besides, if it were me, I would
have cut his fingers off.
The admiral's taking
a phone call at the moment,
but you're still welcome
to go inside, Captain.
Mister Jackson, you don't have
to call me "Captain" here.
With all the brass around here,
I'm sure not going to call you
"young lady" like I used to.
Yeah, I know.
It's our mess and
we're gonna clean it up.
Well, of course!
We're keeping a record
of the interrogation.
What's that?
Yeah, well, we'll have to
talk about that issue again
some other time because I have
a meeting that just walked in.
Now then, can I offer
the two of you a drink?
Thank you.
A bottled water will be fine.
And you?
The same, please.
Come on now,
you're gettin' soft on me.
That call was from
my friend, General Amit.
Does Intelligence want us
to hand over Bruno, sir?
I refused, of course.
But it seems like they're
bent out of shape that we went
and got him without
their say--so.
By the way, did you come
to see the interrogation?
Yes.
Being Mithril's fleet
captain isn't an easy task.
You need to see the uglier side
of how our business gets done
and learn something from it.
That's just the
kind of path you're on.
Don't let it get you down.
You'll understand.
We're taking his
statement right now.
Who is it?
"Amalgam." Another
independent group.
Did you say Amalgam?
Have you heard of it before?
No, but it makes sense...
Some sort of shadow organization
that's flown under our radar
ends up being behind
the Perio Islands incident.
And then, months later,
rears its ugly head
to pester us in Nanking.
We're probably going to have to
re--think how we do
things around here.
Sir, what exactly do you mean?
First off, Kaname Chidori.
The girl Intelligence
mentioned the other day.
We just can't do it anymore.
The "Whispered" incident has
demonstrated to us quite clearly
that she's well beyond the
"matter of concern" stage.
And that's the
problem with Wraith.
It comes down to the fact
that we're not using
our resources correctly.
I couldn't agree
with you more, but...
But what?
Well, Sergeant Sagara, sir...
I think Sagara's talents
would be better served looking
after the ARX--7, Captain.
And right now is the time
to make it happen.
Do you have any objections?
No, I agree.
Did you apologize
to Ms. Kagurazaka?
Yes.
I promised I would
reassemble her car.
Ya know -- even if
you pass, you might end up
getting expelled for pulling
stunts like that, Sousuke!
Understood.
Understood?
I don't think so!!!
So where did you have
to go when the rest of us
were in the middle of taking
our mid--terms, Sousuke?
Something work--related.
It sounded like
a pretty rough deal.
Did everything go
all right out there?
Not a problem.
Okay, then...
By the way...
it looks like someone hasn't
had a haircut in a while.
I'd say she's RIGHT
about that one.
Is it strange?
No, it's not really
too strange...
But don't you normally
take yourself to a hair
salon to get your hair cut?
What is a hair salon?
A barber.
No, I always cut my hair myself.
That explains a lot, actually.
Wait a minute, I just
thought of something!
Why don't we take Sousuke over
to one of those super--fancy,
metro--licious beauty shops?
And we can get him a
complete makeover, Kaname!
A beauty shop?!
Why don't we just
take him to a barber?
Well, if Sousuke were a little
more fashion--conscious like the
rest of us, he might look pretty
handsome, don't you think?
Uhhh...
I'm not so sure...
You have to get him to agree
to it first, you know!
Right, then let's try it.
You just said that's where
normal high school students
get their hair cut, didn't you?
Well, looks like
somebody needs a makeover.
Haircut, please.
Follow me this way.
Gosh, it's strange seeing
Sousuke actually take the time
to do something about
his appearance, isn't it?
I'm trying to talk to you
about your life and your FUTURE!
You're only seventeen!
Haven't you even given
a little bit of thought
to the rest of your life?
All right, let's lather you up!
W--Wait!
Never mind.
Go ahead...
Kaname!
Look!
I found an article
on Daikitsuba!
Wow, well look at that...
You all comfy--cozy, sweetie?
No I'm not.
I'm completely vulnerable.
No, it's not a problem.
The soap isn't poisoned.
He's an ordinary civilian.
Well, ordinary for THIS
profession, anyway.
I'll remain calm...
Okay, it's just a towel.
Towel.
Regular towel.
Calm down.
Just a towel.
I'm not gonna be
strangled with it.
Just a towel.
Okay, now let's make
some magic, honey!
He tied this cloth around me
to keep the hair clippings
off my clothes,
NOT as a tactic to restrict
my freedom of movement.
That's all there is to it,
nothing more.
And I'm sure these are just
ordinary, everyday scisso...
Don't even twitch!
Jesus!
You're manhandling me!
I did it again...
SOUSUKE!
Don't worry,
getting him back on the
Arbalest will be good for him.
It's all my fault.
You asked me to take you
in the first place
so why did you flip out
like that, Sousuke?
I'm sorry.
They kicked us out of
the beauty parlor...
and they even treated ME
like I was a crazy delinquent!
I understand, Kaname, but it's
too dangerous for me to let
my guard down in front of
someone holding a blade.
Oh, well fine!
Then don't go to the beauty
shop in the first place!
You use a knife on your own
hair but you didn't think
you'd freak out when someone
else was cutting it?
One wrong move and you
easily could have KILLED
a completely innocent
hairdresser!
COME ON!
Why don't you stop thinking
everyone's an "assassin"
or an "enemy" once in a while?!
I can't do that because
Mithril's enemies are still
out there in force.
It wouldn't surprise me if
they attacked you at any time.
They'd attack me?
And that's why
you're my top priority.
I'll always be here
to protect you.
However...
I've been here six months...
and even still my
instincts often fail me.
In all this time,
I really don't think
I've adapted to this place.
All I do is cause
a lot of trouble.
For you, and everyone else.
So...
it's been 6 months, has it?
Well, Sousuke, you haven't
made any progress at all,
that's for sure.
Is that true?
Yeah, it is!
Hey, Sousuke...
Why don't you just
come over to my place?
I bet I can take care of that
crazy "bird's nest" of yours
in no time flat!
How 'bout it?
I don't know...
You're not afraid
of me, are you?
No, not at all.
You're in no way
a threat to me.
All righty, sir!
How are we getting it
cut today?
Is this too tight?
No, not a problem.
All right, let's do this!
Kaname?
What?
Do you have any experience
giving haircuts?
Of course I don't!
Well, I've played around
with Kyoko's hair,
but this'll be my first
time actually cutting.
Relax...
This has to be better
than cutting it yourself.
Please be sure not
to cut off my ears.
I'll see what I can do...
So, Sousuke...
What is it?
You kept on missing the
mid-terms because of your work,
right?
Yes.
And did you wind up
in combat again?
Is...
that a problem?
Not really.
You didn't get hurt
out there, did you?
Just some minor injuries.
They should heal quickly.
Oh...
So, Mr. Sousuke,
anyone seem a little
"on edge" to you lately?
Who would that be?
I meant YOU.
Who, me?
Yes, you.
You were doing it again today.
No, you're imagining things...
Oh, well...
You're probably being cautious
because of all the fuss about
that stalker the other day...
Or, am I still an enemy target?
Why do you ask that?
No particular reason...
It's just that a lot of strange
stuff has happened lately.
Well, the problem isn't
a stalker, Chidori.
There's another Mithril
operative out there assigned
to you as a backup unit.
Is it someone I know?
Like Kurz?
No, it's not anyone you know.
We've never met.
Oh, I see...
His true identity
remains unknown...
That's because he
never shows himself.
Does that mean I'd just be on
my own if I got attacked again?
The truth is...
when I really think about it...
I feel safest with you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Would you turn your head a
little to the right for me?
Hm?
Sure.
NO, no! Not THAT way!
I said turn RIGHT!
Hmm, I think I'm actually
getting the hang of this.
Okay, we're all done!
Oh, wait a second,
I forgot to RINSE, didn't I?
Hey, you two aren't scheduled
to sortie today, are you?
Whoa, wait a minute...
whaddya think you're...
What's goin' on?
You're getting all frisky on me!
Sure!
I'll meet you
there in a minute.
Whaa?
My little kittens left me?
What in the hell kind of problem
did they ever have with me?
Sure, they're half my age,
but I never slacked off
and I always satisfied them!
I'd rather not know
about THAT, sir!
But they've taken a model
M Codarl and I think they're...
Huh?
What was that?
Oh, what the hell am I
talking to you for?
Put them on the damn line!
Y--Yes sir!
I'll switch you over.
You two little darlings,
can hear me, can't you?
Just what do you
think you're doing?
What do you want?
That's an expensive toy,
sweetie!
You can't just trot off
and "frolic around" in it!
It's not your business anymore.
From now on, the two of us
will do as we please.
Well, not without
orders, kitten.
You're not taking that
thing to drop in for tea
with our friends from
Mithril, now, are you?
Of course we are.
They're all going to die,
for what they did to Sensei.
Arrgghhh!
Hey, I'm sorry
I only had leftovers.
No, I like it.
Thank you.
Is something wrong?
What?
No...
Well, you know...
how you're always walking around
with a bunch of scary
weapons hidden all over you?
Yeah.
Do you have anything
in that collection that's
not made to kill people?
You see, I was kind of
thinking of getting a weapon.
I believe I may have exactly
what you're looking for.
Now, keep the tear gas,
handcuffs, flashlight,
mini-baton, taser, brass
knuckles and the disposable
stun gun with you at all times,
and that should be a good start.
I have no idea where you
keep all that stuff...
But even something like
this looks so dangerous that
I think I'd end up
killing somebody.
It sends a high-powered electric
shock through the wires,
but it lasts only for
a small fraction of a second.
It won't kill a healthy man.
Okay, that's a normal man,
but what about women,
children or old people, Sousuke?
Chidori, you cannot afford
to have mercy in
a situation like that.
Remaining idle in front of your
attacker is not a wise decision.
You must always
put yourself first
in a life or death situation.
I'm very grateful
for everything today.
I'd be glad to pay you back
by cutting your hair sometime.
Absolutely not!
You should surprise Kyoko with
your new--and--improved look.
I think you're right.
And please don't forget
to return my notebook, okay?
Yes, of course.
And thanks again for everything.
I'm serious, if you forget it
like you've done before,
you have to go back
and get it, Sousuke.
No, I promise I won't
forget it this time.
I should probably be going.
Mm--hmm.
Talk to ya later.
See you tomorrow.
Maybe I should pick out some
clothes for him next time.
The truth is I feel
safest with you.
All right.
I didn't want to leave.
And I didn't mean
to abandon you either.
An ominous order.
Plus a bitter exchange
of words with a ghost.
Next time: "Left Behind." I
can't dispute this direct order.
I just feel...
powerless.