So it's Wraith...
that bastard.
Where are you?!
Get out here and
talk to me NOW, Wraith!
I know you can hear me!
Show yourself, dammit!
I am Sergeant Sousuke Sagara
of Mithril's Tactical Division
from the West Pacific Fleet
flagship Tuatha De Danaan!
As of 20 April,
I have been assigned
to guard a certain person.
My superiors have reason
to believe that this person
has been targeted for
the following reasons!
First!
This person is a special kind of
individual known as a Whispered.
Second!
The Whispered possess advanced,
hidden knowledge of interest
to worldwide military powers.
Are you insane?
Is sabotaging this mission by
screaming top-secret information
at the top of your lungs your
idea of keeping Chidori safe?
Then I guess you
shouldn't have ignored me.
Urzu 7, forcing this
discourse between us
is dangerous to our objective.
It's hard for me to believe
that you don't get it.
Answer me quickly, then.
Is your mission to guard Kaname
Chidori, or to observe her?
I have no comment.
Then, having already
been relieved of duty,
I could just spend
the rest of the evening
telling the neighborhood
everything, couldn't I?
And now you're
threatening me, Urzu 7?
I will have to report this
to the Tactical Division.
Fine by me.
But you will
answer the question.
My mission is to guard.
I don't trust you.
It's not your place to say.
The mission I was given clearly
states that Kaname Chidori
will not fall into the hands
of another organization.
Nothing more, nothing less.
You haven't performed that duty.
She's been surrounded by
a gang of delinquents...
and kidnapped by
a band of thugs,
she's been in danger
numerous times.
The acts of insignificant
hoodlums and children are not
the same as enemy
operations, sergeant.
Unsatisfactory, Wraith.
If you were truly
upholding your stated mission,
then why didn't you intervene
in the A21 incident?
Can you answer that?
Well?
Let's hear it!
My initial intention had been
to leave the enemy at large
however the situation
got out of my control.
Even I broke into a cold sweat
during that hostage exchange
but my decision to stand
down proved to be correct.
Those terrorists failed to
grasp how important she is,
so they didn't
compromise the information
she was carrying inside of her.
They were barely better
than hoodlums themselves...
Revisionist thinking.
Spin it in any way you like.
The fact remains that
Kaname Chidori's knowledge
as a Whispered is safe.
As long as her information is in
no danger of being compromised,
I do not have any
outstanding obligations
to act in this matter.
So you admit it, then.
If you let her die it would
be a tremendous loss to us.
At the very least,
I am bound to protect
her knowledge and her life.
I don't believe you.
I'm not expecting you to believe
anything I've said anyway.
Go worry yourself to death.
Intelligence was to have
taken over this surveillance
after the
Khanka Airport Incident.
But Tactical demanded that
you remain on--objective.
They believed you'd
be an effective decoy.
But to me you have
been nothing more than
an unwelcome distraction.
Sagara, you have no idea
how many times...
I've wanted to kill you off and
make it look like one of your
"accidents." It's never too late
to try if you're up for it.
It was a JOKE, Sagara.
I doubt I could eliminate you
without getting MYSELF hurt.
And actually you're
pretty amusing!
What?
Your soldier's instincts are
both your greatest blessing
and your deepest curse.
Just aiming a rifle at you
from sniping distance is enough
to make you dance like
a cat on a hot tin roof.
And your performance at the
beauty shop today was priceless.
You bastard!
Come on now,
don't get so angry.
As of today your fun with the
high school children is done
and you should be heading back
to your original mission,
don't you think?
We're both professionals, here.
Let's play the part.
I can't do that.
Chidori's safety...
Is no longer your concern
now that Mithril has
given you orders to
withdraw, sergeant.
Surely, you're not planning
on disobeying those orders?
Guess we'll see...
Could it be you've forgotten
that your life here is nothing
but a cover provided by Mithril?
Get it through
your head, Sagara!
You're not
a high school student.
You're a professional killer!
Your family records and
registration at the school
are a ruse...
all part of a disguise.
Do you think you're fooling
anyone when you have to run off
on missions outside
of your duties...
as my decoy?
Who do you think
you're protecting when you're
playing soldier-boy instead
of covering her full-time?
It sounds to me like you
want the best of both worlds,
playing the mercenary hero when
you get "orders" one moment
and playing the
hapless student the next.
So tell me, why aren't you
willing to follow your orders?
No answer, Sagara?
Maybe you just don't
want to know the answer.
Not that I care, mind you.
You gripes and complaints,
whether they're with me or with
your orders, make no difference.
You still have to entrust her
care to me and leave Tokyo.
Your being out of the picture
simply means I've lost my decoy
and I will spend more time
observing our subject.
Nothing more.
Nothing less.
It's funny you've found fault
with my performance, Sagara,
but do you really think someone
like you can protect her?
Remember that the time
I spend watching her
means watching YOU, too.
In the last six months,
you haven't been able to adjust
to Japanese society at all.
And you can't deny you've put
her in danger countless times...
through your own mistakes.
It seems that your idea
of being a bodyguard
could use some revision.
Calling you "third rate"
would be a compliment.
And that's putting it
rather nicely.
You're a pompous son of a bitch!
Well, I must have pushed
the right buttons, eh Sagara?
Either way, Urzu 7, you're done
playing house with that girl.
Follow your instructions.
Quack!
It's morning!
Get up, Kaname!
Quack!
Good morning, Kyoko!
Good morning, Kaname!
Wow, you certainly
look cheerful today!
I do?
Mm--hm!
So did something good
happen to you or what?
No, not really.
Well, maybe.
But I wonder if it's even
worth mentioning, though?
You're acting weird.
Anyway, Sousuke was back to
his normal self yesterday,
wasn't he?
I swear, Kyoko,
he's always embarrassing me!
It makes me wanna put a shock
collar around his neck--
you know, try and train him!
And every time he crosses
that line, it's "Zap!
BAD Sousuke! "I guess
that's totally evil of me,
but he DOES deserve it, right?
He's not a dog, Kaname!
Oh, by the way, what happened
after the beauty parlor?
Huh?!
Oh, we went home.
Why do you ask?
I just wondered what he's
going to do about a haircut.
Yeah, really.
He'll probably
just cut it himself.
No!
It'll look all sloppy again!
Great, I'll have to make sure
our stories match up later.
But still,
I think someone is looking
more chipper than usual.
Who's that?
YOU, of course!
What?
You're just imagining things!
So, what happened, huh?
I'm serious!
Nothing happened, okay?
Hey, did you catch
the latest Kumodoshin?
Yeah, I saw it.
What'd ya think?
Honestly, it wasn't that great.
Huh?
Why not?
Just because...
Well, okay, the octopus
samurai thing was good, but...
Yeah it was!
When all those tentacles and
stuff came out of his back!
That was INSANE!
Right.
And then it was over...
I didn't know about it either...
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing.
Oh, yeah, no kidding!
I can't wait til...
Good morning, Shinji.
Hey, good morning, Kaname.
Where's Sousuke?
Ummm...
You know, I haven't
seen him come in yet.
Then I guess he
still hasn't made it.
Okay, good.
What happened?
Oh, nothing!
Hey, Kyoko, what'd I miss?
Good morning!
Oh, good morning!
Oh man!
That was close!
I wonder what he's doing?
Rise!
And...
Bow!
Good morning, sir!
Good morning.
Be seated.
Listen for your name.
Igarashi...
Here.
Ishihara?
Here!
Isoumura?
Here.
Uozumi?
Fujida?
Here.
Oumi?
Ogata?
Here.
Hmmm, no answer?
No, but it didn't go to
voicemail, so it must be on...
I wonder what's wrong?
Heck if I know -- that
idiot could be anywhere!
Orders.
Damn.
KANAME!
Now my future
is totally hopeless!
It couldn't have been that bad.
Yes it could!
I did lousy on that
Math II test we got back!
It's okay!
It's not like
your life depends on it.
So how did you do, Kaname?
Well, I guess I did...
a little bit better
than average, I suppose.
You're a traitor.
You know that?
Hey, I just remembered --
you got the top scores
in last year's science and
math finals too, didn't you?
Mmhmm...
Well, it's just one of
those things, you know?
Or could being
one of the Whispered
have something to do with it?
Hey, can you help me
get better scores?
Look!
I don't do
anything special, okay?
Okay but could you at least
tell me your study secrets?
Could you be cheating?
Oh, I don't care
what it is Kaname,
you just gotta tell me
how you're doing it!
I could tell you...
but then I might
have to kill you.
Just kidding!
And by the way,
you know, Sousuke never
made it to class today.
Yeah, I noticed.
I honestly wonder if
he's trying to fail.
He's already in
big trouble, that idiot.
Well, why don't you try
calling Sousuke one more time?
He might pick up, you know.
Hmmm...
Apparently, he's gone off and
gotten lost again, as usual,
so I say we oughtta just
move on and forget the doofus!
You sure?
Well I guess if that's what
you really wanna do, Kaname...
Uh--huh.
I do!
And while we're at it, finals
are over so let's have a little
FUN while we still have the
chance, you know what I mean?
Like a karaoke party!
Yeah, that sounds fun!
A careless karaoke
free--for--all...
a ten--hour marathon!
Oh...
not again, Kaname!
What?
You had fun last time,
didn't you?
Well of course I did,
but after all that, we were
worn out the next day.
You gotta go for it!
What good is karoke night if
you don't do it till your ribs
are sore and you
get that feeling of...
Are you okay?
It's official!
10--hour karaoke marathon!
And you WILL be singing, Kyoko!
Okay, so who are we
inviting to this thing?
Shiori and Maya and
Ren and Mizuki and...
Huh?
What...
was that?
Kaname?
Hey, what's going on?
What is it, Kaname?
Hey!
Talk to me!
Kaname...
It's okay, it's okay.
The number you have
dialed cannot be reached,
as it is out of the service area
or the phone is powered off.
The number you have
dialed cannot be reached,
as it is out of the service
area or the phone is powered--
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, I have to go home.
No way!
I can't just let you go when
you're all shaken up like this!
I'm fine.
But you're...
Drop it!
I'm sorry.
See you tomorrow.
All right, welcome, everyone!
Let's introduce the
guest of the week!
The Encores!
Oh, you're looking very fit.
And you look like
you're having a fit!
Oooh, he gotcha
that time, Kenny!
What did you say?
Take this!
Aw, man!
Yeah, how ya like that?
It's okay, nothing's happening.
Kaname Chidori speaking.
Hello?
Who is this?
Hey!
Who's there?
Sousuke...
The number you have dialed
cannot be...
Shut up!
How...
How am I supposed
to reach you, Sousuke?
Oh!
The radio setup!
Mithril uses a satellite with
spectrum diffusion modulation
and a unique quantum code.
Thanks to the time I spent
on the Tuatha de Danaan,
I know how it all works and
what frequencies they use!
I can do this...
I know I can!
Sousuke!
Are you in there?!
My notebook...
Why was it left here
on the floor?
Huh?
But it can't be...
Frustration,
arguments and tears.
Unmitigated hatred rises
within me for the machine
that tore me apart from her.
Little do I know that it will
become a curse on myself.
Next time...
"Jungle Groove" Black
and white flashes pierce
through the jungle.