Balance is the key
We'll be there shortly,
Mister Gates.
Fine, but balance
is still important;
for people and for countries.
Sir?
Lean too far and you end up
falling off the beam
like a drunken gymnast!
And if you lose your balance...!
you might lose your head.
When you have the kinds
of customers we serve,
you can't afford NOT to
have balance on BOTH sides
of the equation.
Referring to North
and South China?
Well! We should be catching up
to our little stray
pussycat any time now!
Pussycat?
Oh come on!
Do I have to do all
your thinkin' for you?
I'm talking about
little Yui Lan!
And what exactly do you
intend to do with her body?
A beautiful young
body like that?
Oh, there's still plenty
of uses for THAT body.
Not exactly a local, are ya?
So are ya Korean or Japanese?
I don't have a
nationality to speak of.
Huh?
Well if you don't have any
business here, please leave.
I'm busy right now.
Are you evacuating?
Like everyone else.
May I take this?
Weren't you leaving?
At least let me pay you for it.
I don't give a damn!
Take it!
You must have some
kind of death wish.
Get outta here!
Death wish?
That's pretty close, actually.
All units, Urzu 9.
Now investigating Point 28.
Tighten your search perimeter
if we don't contact
within fifteen minutes.
Urzu 2, Wilco.
Wangfu headquarters copies.
Be careful out there.
Is something the matter,
Corporal?
Nothing, but it's been
a while since we've heard
from Sergeant Sagara.
So did the sergeant
major give you a reason
to think there
might be trouble?
No, I don't think so.
But anyway, we've got our
own work to worry about,
so let's go.
Yeah, we should get going.
Nothing here.
That leaves us 12
more points to go.
He must've been
a worker here, huh?
Probably.
Looks like he's been
dead for about two days.
Guess he stumbled on
their hideout by mistake.
No way to tell for sure.
But even if it was, they sure as
hell ain't comin' back to this.
It looks like somebody wrote
something on his chest, huh?
Yeah...
The Son of Bdakshon's Tiger.
Meet Hamidra at Tsim Sha Tsui?
Okay, What in the hell
is that supposed to mean?
Well, your guess is
as good as mine.
Do we have any reports of a
Venom sighting yet, Tessa?
60 percent of the
search points on the list
have been eliminated, Admiral.
We're working as quickly
as we can, but nothing yet.
Have we had any success
in convincing the Chinese
governments not to take action?
No shots fired,
if that's what you mean.
But they're hardly in a mood
to let go of their suspicions
and reinstate the cease-fire.
Both sides have been holding
grudges against each other
for years and this
just dials up the tension.
Of course,
we're still negotiating.
But at this rate, we've
only got about 3 hours left.
Only three hours?
Well, I'm hoping to hear good
news from you before then.
That is all.
Captain, Urzu 2 is on line G1.
Put her on.
Aye-aye, Ma'am.
Urzu 2 to TDD HQ.
Urzu 9 has discovered
a suspicious corpse,
and it has a message
inscribed on the body.
Please continue...
Roger.
Our victim was a middle-aged
man who was shot to death.
He was discovered
at Search Point 28.
The message states: "To the
son of Badahkshone's Tiger.
Meet Hamidra
at Tsim Sha Tsui.
"Also, Intelligence
confirms there have been
two other instances
of the same message,
and three reports of printings
in the local classifieds.
They sure are going to a lot
of trouble to find this guy.
Is that all?
That's it, Commander.
Fine.
Cover the rest of
the search area.
Roger.
Urzu 2 out.
I wonder what that
message could have meant...
Well, speaking of Bdakshon,
Commander Kalinin has
an outstanding working knowledge
of that area of the world.
Call Commander Kalinin
to the bridge and run
a cryptographic
analysis on the message.
Yes, Ma'am.
I'm puzzled, Madame Captain.
There's nothing in that
message that would throw us off
of Venom's trail.
Any idea what this means?
"Bdakshon's Tiger" is
a man, Madame Captain.
A legendary guerilla
commander in Hellmajistan.
His name is Majid.
Helmajistan?
I engaged him in battle
on several occasions.
My comrades in the Soviet
Army sent numerous assassins
into Helmajistan, trying to
eliminate Majid without success.
One of the assassins they
sent was a boy not even
8 years old at the time.
It was a child?
Majid had a reputation for
compassion that didn't change
even when he captured this
would-be assassin and gave him
a new name as his "son."
And that name was Kashim.
Then that means...
Kashim!
We're not friends,
YOU SHITHEAD!!!
Mister Sagara...
Captain, we need to
inform Sergeant Sagara.
Right...
Get me Urzu 2.
Yes, ma'am.
Go ahead.
TDD HQ to Urzu 2.
Please put Urzu 7 on the line.
Ma'am, this is Uruz 2.
Umm...
Is something wrong?
I'm sorry, but
Urzu 7 isn't here.
You're not Chinese, huh?
That's affirmative.
Well okay Mister "Affirmative."
So ya got any money on ya,
or what?
I have a little.
Well how about it,
are you free right now?
Yes.
Then would you like to
have a little fun with me
back at my place?
What, are you queer
or something?
Sure, whatever...
Let's head back to your place.
You little letch!
What are you doing
playing hard to get?
You know you wanna!
Come on--it's
just down the street.
What do you mean Sousuke
abandoned the mission?
You're not serious, are ya?
That's right.
I heard that he got
into a traffic accident
and just wandered off somewhere.
Hmmm...
But that's not
something he would do...
Did you hear anything,
Lieutenant?
Just some bits and pieces
here and there.
Not enough to make
a judgment call.
And Kalinin seems
to agree with me...
Regardless, we can't count on
having Sagara or the Arbalest
on our side in this battle.
He was good for a while, but
a seventeen-year-old punk
like that was bound to crack up
out there and lose his nerve
on a mission
sometime or another.
That doesn't matter, you idiot!
I still can't
believe it myself.
Sagara was always a straight
arrow and he never woulda
thought about bailing out
on a mission like this.
It's that girl.
Chidori.
C'mon, think about it
for a minute.
Ever since he came back
from that assignment to guard
that Whispered kid,
his brain's been AWOL.
Yeah.
Now that you mention it,
that's gotta be it.
What do you think, Roger?
I think I don't
know Sagara that well.
But I do know that what a man
carries deep down in his soul
doesn't change that easily.
And if it's in his nature to be
a hawk, then what do you think?
A hawk stays a hawk.
Right.
So, you want yours with
water or on the rocks?
You decide.
Okay, on the rocks then.
You know something?
You look like this guy
I dated a while back.
We only went out
for a little while,
cuz I had to
dump his sorry ass.
Yep, turned out
to be a total poseur.
You know what I mean?
I mean when he was around me
he'd act like he was a big shot,
but when he got around other
people acted so spineless
that I just wanted to rip his
face off and feed it to him!
Kinda funny that I'd end up
hanging out with you,
seeing as how you look like him.
Well, except that he wasn't
always frowning like you!
Hey.
You gotta have a smile
in there somewhere.
Come on!
I'm sure you'd feel
a lot better if you just
loosened up and relaxed.
I never really had
a reason to smile.
Fighting is all I know.
But you're a frickin janitor!
Whattya do?
Shoot people with your broom?
Oh, God!
You are too much!
And the way you said it with
a straight face
made it even funnier!
Oh really?
I'm sorry, but you weren't
actually serious about
all that fighting stuff?
I was joking.
So, Mister Fighting Janitor,
were you on a secret mission
when I met you out there?
I was working.
All by yourself?
No.
I had comrades with me.
So where are
these comrades now?
I guess they're still working.
Oh!
So you bailed out on 'em, huh?
Affirmative.
Well, that's okay.
When shit gets crazy,
it's okay to just
walk away if you have to.
Is that right?
Yeah that's right.
The real idiots in this world
are the ones who take life
too seriously and
never loosen up...
I thought I could
bear anything...
as long as you
were here with me.
I mean, they can always get
somebody else to clean up
the messes if you
skip out on the job, right?
I won't burden you anymore...
What?
Is something wrong?
You're not having
second thoughts are you?
Well I don't know.
One thing's for sure.
I can't return to my comrades.
Oh come on, you're not the first
guy to play hooky from work!
Why don't you just
tell 'em you're sorry
and they'll get over it.
No, I can't.
I've already violated the
faith they placed in me.
Oh, big frickin deal!
I mean, sure, they say they're
your comrades but you never know
when they're gonna
stab you in the back.
Keep your eyes open and
keep a safe distance,
and then they can't get to you.
The truth is...
I feel safest with you...
Here's what I've learned...
Just lean on everyone else,
and get as much as you can
out of 'em, cuz that's all
they're really good for,
you know?
And once the
relationship is over, BAM!
You just toss 'em
to the side...
Hey, Mr. Fighting Janitor,
why don't you join the party
and start drinking with me, huh?
I've never had alcohol before.
You gotta be kidding.
The effects would only
hinder my abilities.
Whatever, honey.
If you don't wanna drink,
I have a suggestion for you.
Have a little fun and forget
all your troubles with me.
And if that doesn't help you
forget your comrades,
we can get drunk off our
asses and do it some more.
I'll make you happy.
Sousuke...
Sousuke!
Sousuke.
Just relax, okay?
What was that for?
I changed my mind.
What?
I've decided not to do it.
What in the hell
is wrong with you?!
Thanks anyway.
Hey, garbage man!
Take this with you!
Now get the hell out!
It's time.
Are you ready, Teletha?
Deploy all your M9s.
Engage Venom
wherever it shows up next,
and take it down
with all you've got.
However, I don't want
the Arbalest out there.
We can't afford to expose
that machine to any danger.
But we need more time, Admiral.
My pilots haven't finalized
their countermeasures
against Venom, yet!
If we send them now, we're
risking excessive casualties!
Please give me
at least two more hours...
Lord Mallory and I
have already conferred
on this matter, Captain.
Admiral...
Tensions between the North and
South are at the breaking point.
And every time Venom appears,
the body count goes up and
we can't allow that anymore.
The situation is urgent.
How many more people
are going to die while
you're sitting there
"getting ready?"
But I just...
I've heard that Venom has
a short operating time
when it's out in the field.
You can use that
to your advantage.
Have faith in the people
under your command.
Nobody else in the world
can do what they can.
I know this is
hard for you, Teletha.
But I told you
you'd face these choices.
And you still chose
to retain your command
in spite of all that,
didn't you?
Yes, that is true, sir.
Then it's in your hands,
Captain Testarossa.
Do it quickly.
Understood.
X-O, take us up to periscope
depth and flood all
the underwater launch
hatches on the double.
Aye, Ma'am.
Ahead one-third, set your uptrim
five degrees and begin rise
to periscope depth.
They've called off the search?
Affirmative.
Head to the extraction point
and board your M9.
Join up with Urzu 1 at point
Echo at oh-four-thirty hours.
You will receive
your next orders there.
Urzu 2, Roger.
That's it.
TDD-HQ out.
Begin flooding
underwater launch hatches.
Flooding all
Aye, sir.
So you're telling me we've
run out of time, General?
That's right.
It's in the hands of the
Tactical Division now.
I understand, General.
Goodbye.
Shit!
We're at periscope depth
and trim is level.
Stop engines!
All engines stop.
Hatch flooding complete.
Open all hatches.
Opening hatches, aye.
Preparations for launch are
now complete, Madame Captain.
Launch all units.
Aye, Captain.
Urzu 1 copies.
All units, you are
now clear for launch!
Urzu 3, Roger.
Urzu 5, Roger.
Urzu 8, Roger.
Uruz 6, Roger that.
People actually drink this?
"To the son of Bdakshon's Tiger.
Meet Hamidra at Tsim Sha Tsui."
Time is almost up.
A deserted city echoes with a
message from the underworld.
A mastermind behind the scenes.
Is this who's calling me?
Next time:
"Burning Hong Kong."
A corpse taunts me from
the darkness, beckoning me
back to my desolate past.