[SHINTARO]
The 96 model has a weak joint
on its right arm.
They've accurately recreated
even the weakness.
Of course, when
Ban Presto's making it...
[SHINTARO sighs]
Shinji...
[thunder]
Summer!
Ocean!
And... sweet...
summer... memories...
[yelps]
Please don't tell me
this is supposed to be the
highlight of the summer?
Hey, at least we're
still in Chiba, right?
Listen to me!
We were supposed to go
swimming in Kujukuri,
or walk the white
sands of Onjuku!
Haven't you ever listened
to the Beach Boys?
That's what a summer's
supposed to be!
Okay, we can go in now!
I've checked out the security!
So stop goofing around!
You! It's your fault.
It's all because of you!
You shouldn't have come with us
if it bothered you this much.
She's right. You shoulda
opened your mouth
and told them that when Sousuke
agreed with Shinji's idea.
Besides, you're in
high schol now,
so stop trying to ruin
the fun for the rest of us
just 'cause you
didn't get your way.
It could even be more
exciting than swimming,
like if a really hot
BS pilot asked me out.
Ooh, what do ya
think I should do
if one of them comes up and
asks me to play BS with him?
I think the term you're
looking for is AS.
[SHINTARO] We need to break
our losing streak here
at the Post Festival.
Those guys from
Nerima have taken
to calling themselves
the "Red Dragon"
in their latest and most
ridiculous challenge
We need to give
these jokers hell!
I want to wish you all,
the best of luck!
Start boarding your mechs!
[MEN]
Yeah!
[VENDORS shouting]
Check this out! I got the
very best Nerima daikon.
Go ahead, mister.
Try some of this radish.
[MAN IN COSTUME] The big battle
of the machine troops
is gonna start soon.
You kids don't wanna
miss the action.
Wow, it looks really stupid.
Duh. It's just a cardboard box.
[MAN IN COSTUME] Aw, but the
real ones look super cool.
[CHILD A] You're gonna lose
again this year, huh?
Let's go.
[SHINJI] Aw man. Even the
little kids call him stupid.
[SOUSUKE]
Hm?
The real AS trooper's
here. Super weak.
[SOUSUKE] Are there problems
with the equipment?
[SHINJI] Uh-uh, the
equipment's supposed to be
some of the best in Japan.
They're paratroopers.
Okay, so why are they weak?
Well, their equipment
is the only thing they
have goin' for 'em.
Huh...
[SHINTARO]
Shinji!
[SHINJI]
Huh?
Dad?
Heh. And you must be Mr. Sagara.
Sir! Sergeant
Sousuke Sagara, sir!
[SHINTARO]
Hm?
[SOUSUKE]
I-I mean, it's nice to meet you.
Hi. Shintaro Kazama's the name.
I work as a secretary
on the base.
I admit I'm surprised,
because Shinji's never brought
his friends to the
festival before.
Geez, Dad. Could you
put a lid on it?
See? It's things like that
which make me worry
about him sometimes.
Come on, Dad. Cut it out.
Anyway, I hope you
have a good time here.
Yes, sir. I will,
Mr. Secretary, sir.
[SHINTARO]
What an unusual kid.
He's got real military manners.
Hm?
[KYOKO]
That's gotta take some skill.
[MIZUKI] I'm really wishing
I hadn't ordered something
with seaweed in it.
Get that stuck in my teeth,
no one will ask me out.
[KYOKO] Hey, do you
want anything, Kaname?
[laughs]
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hi there.
So, where're you girls from?
Uh, we came in from Sengawa.
What a coincidence!
My group just got
here from Nerima...
[KANAME]
What's his deal?
[MIZUKI]
Weird sunglasses.
[KYOKO]
Cosplayer?
How'd you like to check out
an AS from the inside?
[GIRLS]
Huh?
I'll let you feel the power
of the Nerima Red Dragon
up close and personal.
The Nerima Daikon?
No! I said, "Nerima Red Dragon."
A red colored dragon, okay?
What d'ya say?
Oh, yes!
I'd love to try it out with you!
My name: Ryonosuke Akagi.
And you are?
Eh?
Someone who's not big on AS
or the raving idiots
who go gaga over them.
Don't you worry, baby.
I'll teach you AS from A to Z.
[KANAME]
No, thank you.
Heh. She's even cuter
when she's angry.
Captain Akagi, it's time for
us to start boarding now.
Roger that.
If you girls will excuse me.
[MIZUKI]
Urg... What is going on here?
How come you pick
her and not me?
You wait, Kaname.
I'll have my revenge.
Well, I don't think
it's her fault.
Why does everyone
look so depressed?
Did something happen?
[KANAME, MIZUKI]
Shut up and die!
Uh...
[ANNOUNCEMENT] All right!
Now we're gonna start today's
main event here at
the Post Festival,
the battle of the
machine assault troops,
featuring Team Narashino
vs. Team Nerima.
Will the players please
enter the ring?
Akagi! Watch out 'cause
we're gonna win this year!
Hah! What are ya talkin' about?
The Nerima Red Dragon is gonna
fry you all nice and crispy.
--[KANAME] Huh?
--[KYOKO] Must be Daikon.
I won't forgive him.
[SHINJI, SOUSUKE]
Huh?
[gunshot]
[MACHINE TROOPS]
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Hah! We can do this In one shot.
Divert maximum power
to the right arm.
Diverting maximum power
to the right arm!
Now pull!
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
Oh, ho, ho!
Team Nerima shows its
strength once again.
It seems that Team
Narashino is rather weak.
Weak doesn't even begin
to describe it.
Another weak show.
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
Narashino's not giving up.
It looks like they're
couching on their anchors.
Let's take the lead!
But we've already
reached top speed, sir.
Don't be soft on them.
Cancel the power limiter.
Canceling!
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
Wow, what a hit!
It looks like Nerima wins again!
Hey! Why don't you
jerks stop cheating?!
Calm down, Shinji.
Huh? Uh...
Looks like they're
sitting in tandem.
There should be a gap
in their synchronization.
I say we take advantage of that.
Uh, we're sitting
in tandem too, sir.
Tactical plan b; get ready.
Plan b. Roger.
Ah! Here it comes,
Captain. This is it.
The world famous
Red Dragon Drive Smash!
[gasps]
[KOSUGE]
What?
Damn! It's a feint!
Quick, go forward.
Not a chance.
Oh my god!
Where's the ref?!
Why's he letting them do that?!
It's all over now.
Nothing to do but wait.
[beeping]
Captain! Unknown AS, nine
o'clcock and closing in!
And it isn't Narashino's?
[SUBORDINATE C]
Can't be!
This AS is three times
faster than normal.
What the hell?
Dammit!
Ah! Kickass!
Hey, where did Sousuke go?
Huh?
No way.
[SOUSUKE]
Can you hear me, Nerima Daikon?
[RYUNOSUKE]
That's Nerima Red Dragon.
[SOUSUKE] This is supposed
to be a contest.
Not a war.
You shouldn't use such
underhanded tactics.
[RYUNOSUKE] Hmph. Let's talk
where I can see you.
It certainly was a
beautiful smash.
Huh? Who the hell are you?
Let's see your face.
Oh, so an AS pilot
needs no name?
Very well.
I challenge you!
[SOUSUKE]
No problems here.
Sousuke, just what do
you think you're doing?
[SOUSUKE]
How did you know it was me?
You're the only one
who would do something
this ridiculous.
[SOUSUKE]
But the contest should be
about conforming to the
spirit of fair play.
Ugh! You...! Ah!
Why did I have to
come to this place?
Give me back my fun
time by the seaside.
[MIZUKI]
Here.
Huh?
I hope you're a big
orage tangerine fan.
Did someone say tambourine man?
Uh, bad Shinji.
No cookie for you.
Mizuki, what exactly
are you doing?
Wouldn't you rather play TS
with me than that little kid?
[KANAME growls]
Even though you're
wearing this outfit,
I bet you're a
really handsome guy.
What do ya say we
take off that mask
and see that face of yours?
Stop bothering Mr. AS Pilot.
Come on. We're going.
Good luck!
Kaname, wait!
Well, well, so her
name's Kaname...
What a hottie.
Miss Kaname! Miss Kaname!
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
Well, after some discussion,
the judges have decided
to call the ping pong game
a draw due to
outside interference.
What do you want?
I never knew we had
such a skilled AS pilot
here in Narashino
right under our noses.
I know this may be a bit sudden,
but I'd like to ask you a favor.
[SHINTARO] That's it. We have
nothing else that can help us.
[KOSUGE]
But, Mr. Secretary...
[SHINTARO] And you, Kosuge.
Are you trying to kill us?
Hiding the secret
weapon from me...
[gasps]
[SHINTARO]
Please! We're begging you!
We need to beat Nerima!
Please command our troops!
[SOUSUKE]
Um, excuse me?
[SHINJI] What the hell
are you doing, Dad?
[SOUSUKE]
Shinji?
Is it part of your regular
job to bow and scrape
untill someone feels
sorry for you?
Come on, Dad.
Why don't you tell him
how you had no choice
but to become a secretary?
It's because you were no good
at piloting the AS, right?
[SOUSUKE]
Is that true?
He has no clue
what his father does.
[SHINJI]
You wanna know why
I started reading AS fan
in the first place?
I wanted to find out
how difficult it was
to opperate an AS
and I hoped that would
help me figure out
why you could never
hack it as a pilot,
when the other guys
make it look easy.
I wanted you to be
able to operate it.
I wanted to brag to my friends
that my dad was an AS pilot.
But please, Shinji--
Please nothing, Dad. I hate you.
[slap]
[SOUSUKE]
Sorry.
But you're forgetting
something important.
The background support team
plays an important
role in the battle,
even if they're
not on the field.
Soldiers on the front lines
can't show their abilities
without that support.
It's crucial to have someone
like your father at the helm.
[SOUSUKE]
So, shall we go out there
and chop up some Nerima daikon?
[MEN]
Yeah!
Did you have a fight
with your boyfriend,
the secret weapon?
That jerk isn't my boyfriend.
I guess that means I still
have a chance, don't I?
Would you like to
challenge him with me?
Huh?
[RYUNOSUKE] I only fought with
him once, and briefly at that,
but I could feel that he
was a skilled AS pilot.
Of course, I don't think I'd
lose if I had you with me.
We would win for certain.
I think it's time for you and
me to kick some AS together.
What d'ya say?
[KANAME]
Hm...
And we'll win?
Definitely. I'm not one
to let a lady feel regret.
Then let's do it.
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
Ladies and gentlemen,
the time has come
for the final match.
The cavalry battle!
The festival championship has
come down to the final fight.
Winner take all!
[KYOKO]
Where'd everybody go?
[MIZUKI]
I don't know. Come on, BS Pilot!
Kick that loser's
ass into orbit!
[KOSUGE] Don't worry,
I'm not gonna bother asking
who you are right now.
Let's just do our best, okay?
Thank you, sir.
[KOSUGE] Remember, we're the
ones who let the Kazamas
join the team and they'll
be blamed if we lose
so we need to win.
[SOUSUKE] The unexpected
attack of an amatuer
can sometimes be deadlier than
an expert's calculated move.
We'll win.
[KANAME]
What's that smell?
You should get used
to it soon enough.
Just pretend like you're
in gym class, okay?
I'm here if you need anything.
Please do not touch me.
[ANNOUNCEMENT] The cavalry
battle is about to start!
Players, take your positions!
[KOSUGE]
He used to be such a good kid.
[KOSUGE] But they haven't been
getting along too well lately.
I heard they were arguing
like that just the other day
when the secretary broke
that plastic model
Shinji gave him.
The Kazamas' teamwork
is in bad shape.
Teamwork will often
times get formed
during the heat of the battle.
You never know untill
you're actually there.
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
Ready!
[SHINTARO]
How did you talk me into this?
[SHINJI] Don't worry, Dad.
I've got it under control.
What do ya mean?
Since when do yo--
One of the assistants
gave me this disc to use.
[KANAME]
What do I do?
Tell me what to do!
It's quite simple.
Just imagine you're punching
someone you really, really hate.
No problem.
Take this!
Ah!
Quick! Block with your arm!
Hey, this OS is awesome!
They blocked me.
It's all right, babe.
You're a natural.
Try it one more time.
You think so?
Then watch this.
The Captain's machine moves
in a totally different
way than the others.
Miss Kaname, he's got to be
the one piloting it.
Gotcha!
Hey, Sousuke!
We can't afford to
underestimate their captain.
He's rather adept, you know.
You think so?
I don't know.
Most of their punchs were
looking a little funny to me.
Okay, C group, D group,
help out the Kazamas in
B group on both sides.
[C GROUP]
C group, roger!
[D GROUP]
D group, ten four!
So what's our plan for now?
Our current tactical
strategy is fairly simple.
As long as we beat
the Captain's machine,
we have a chance to win.
You have an interesting
way of looking at it.
Roger that.
It's coming!
Huh? Knock it off, will ya?!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Don't worry.
We're about to teach your
boyfriend a little lesson.
Huh?
B group, C group,
let's do our special move!
They're coming!
It's the Red Stream attack
of three stars in a row!
The Red, what?
They did a leap frog maneuver!
Uh-oh! Ah!
Assume low stance.
Assuming low stance.
Those guys beat us with
that move every year.
The wait, the timing, the power,
the sheer decisiveness
of it all... Perfect.
That felt really good!
[RYUNOSUKE] If you beat the
enemy, you'll feel even better.
I'd feel better if you
weren't hanging over me.
[SHINJI] Dad, you're slow
turning the right leg.
Yeah, I know, but what
can I do about it?
[SOUSUKE]
Get out of there!
We'll take over from here!
What are you saying?
We can't just leave you
alone to face the enemy!
[gasps]
My staff and I are fighting
alongside you every day.
We're members of the team,
just like you are!
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
Team Narashino is in a pinch.
Will they be wiped out
again this year?
[SUBORDINATE B] Secretary,
we're counting on you!
[SUBORDINATE D] Let's show 'em
the Narashino Airborne spirit!
Oh, Shinji...
I'm hopelessly clumsy.
I can't even repair
a plastic model,
but still, I can't just give up
and throw in the towel.
Then let's give 'em our best!
So, Shinji, will you...
will you fight with me?
Affirmitave, sir!
Right... Let's win this thing.
To all surviving machines
on the field:
who here is feeling hungry
for Nerima Daikon?!
Let's do it!
[SHINTARO]
Everyone forward!
Start the counter-attack!
[MACHINE TROOPS yell]
Shinji, ready for
left counter-punch!
Left counter-punch, roger!
[SHINTARO]
Attack!
Hey, what's going on?
As I said before,
more often than not,
teamwork gets formed
during battle.
Wait a minute. How can
they be beating us?
What? That's impossible!
[KYOKO]
Woohoo!
[ANNOUNCEMENT] Narashino is
beating Nerima's team one-by-one
and evening up the odds!
We'll take out
the Captain first!
All groups, are ya ready?
[NERIMA TROOPS]
Roger!
We're gonna do the
radish jump again, right?
Uh, no, it's called
Red Stream Attack.
They're coming, but now it's
too late to lower our stance.
It's no good! We won't make it!
[gasps]
[SHINTARO] The 96 model has a
weak joint on its right arm.
Shinji, attack the
joint on the right arm!
Right! I'm on it!
Oh my god! They
knocked our arm off!
What the hell?
Do it now!
Roger that!
Here I come!
This year, we're
taking the victory!
See ya, daikon!
[pop]
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
The game is up!
Team Narashino wins
by a narrow margin!
[cheering]
This all feels like a dream.
Thank you, stranger.
No, don't thank me.
You should thank your troops
for making the most
of their abilities.
[SHINJI]
Dad!
We did it! We won the match!
[SHINTARO]
We did.
[KANAME]
Ugh! Leave me alone!
It's all over. The
game's finished. Jerk!
I know you're
nervous about this,
but trust me, I've never
let a lady down.
--[RYUNOSUKE groans]
--That's enough.
This is the first
time I realized
my father's work
is important, too.
I really do owe
you one, Sousuke.
Hm?
Thanks to you and everyone else,
we won the competition.
No, "we" didn't win anything.
The Narashino Airborne Troops
and the secretary won the game.
Mr. BS Pilot...
My summer...
[SOUSUKE, SHINJI]
Huh?
[KANAME] Where have my
summer memories gone?
[KANAME] Sousuke, now
where are you going?
[SOUSUKE] To a country
called Helmajistan.
[KANAME]
For what?
[SOUSUKE]
An assassination.
[KANAME]
Seriously?
[SOUSUKE]
Seriously.
[KANAME]
Okay...
Next Full Metal Panic,
Episode 15:
"The Wind Blows
at Home, Part 1."
You need to make
sure you come back.
[SOUSUKE]
If I'm lucky.