[MARDUKAS] The visible fatigue
on the metal of the
variable torque screw
is more than we expected.
Our hopes tend to err on
the side of disappointment.
However, I think that
Tuahar de Danaan
is doing better than we
expected, all thing considered.
[sighs]
Huh?
[MELISSA]
Yo! Welcome back.
Thought I'd drop in for a visit.
No wonder this place smells
like cigarette smoke.
[MELISSA]
Hm?
I've been using the
ventilator, you know.
[TELETHA]
I wonder what the cleaning lady,
who loves to gossip, will have
to say when she sees this mess.
[MELISSA]
Hm?
If word gets out,
people might start thinking
I drink and smoke
like a cheap bar girl
and I'd rather die than
have that happen to me.
Oh, so you're saying
I'm a cheap bar girl?
Is that it?
Well, who else does
that sort of thing?
Heh. So it's a fair
assumption that
in high-ranking little
Miss Testarossa world,
chicks who like to light up
and lit are all bitches.
Is that right?
Could you please stop
talking like that, Melissa?
You sound like a
B-movie gangster.
[MELISSA]
Well, if that's true,
then I guess that makes
you big bad crime boss.
That's really hurts, you know.
I try hard everyday
to see that people
don't think of this
organization like that,
but the way lower-level
people like behave...
What's that? I'm lower-level?
How can you even
think such a thing,
let alone say it?
I'm talking about your
irresponsible attitude.
I wish you would
remember who you are!
Oh, look at you.
I like to hide underwater
and sit in my chair,
giving orders...
[TELETHA]
You're way out of line!
You'll never know
what my job is like!
It must be hard on you imagining
what kind of
responsibility I have,
but I shouldn't be
surprised, coming from
an ex-marine with
muscles for brains.
[MELISSA] Ugh! Why don't
you put your money
where your mouth is
and stand in front of the
bullet sometime, huh, Captain?
Oh, so relying on a
high-performance M9
makes you a battle
hardened hero?
Yeah! And just what do
you know about the AS?
You, who can't even pilot one?
Oh, I can pilot one.
I simply choose not to.
Aw, is that right, sweetie?
Yes, that's right,
and I can do it better
than you can, too.
A primitive savage who only
has her instincts to go on,
and who can't make the most
out of the specs. Hah!
Why you little...!
[chuckles]
[MELISSA]
How 'bout you show me?
Huh?
Since you say you're
such a skilled pilot,
how 'bout you and me have
a match with the AS's?
If I lose the match,
I'll strip down and run
a lap around the base.
[TELETHA]
Naked?!
[MELISSA]
If I'm feeling nice,
I may allow you your underwear.
[MELISSA chuckles]
Ooh...
[TELETHA]
Fine. You're on.
Let's have ourselves
an AS match, Sgt. Major.
I'll be happy to correct
this concieted attitude
that has a hold of you.
If I lose, I'll do
whatever you say.
Even run a lap naked.
--[WOMAN gasps]
--[MAN] Whoa!
[TELETHA]
Damn, Melissa.
I hate her!
[BOTH] Aditional equipment
includes paint bullets,
training ATD, and also
a training blade.
Permission for use
has been granted.
Teletha Testarossa.
P.S. Don't be a coward.
The loser must run a lap
around the base naked?!
Naked? Tessa, naked?
Uh... I guess it
could be Melissa, too.
[MELISSA]
What? Am I not good enough?
Ah!
Our little Captain
is challenging you?
Do you accept?
Of course I do.
You heard what the little
tart said to me, right?
[chuckles]
Well, you shouldn't.
She's pretty fragile.
Yes, it's a waste of your time.
Oh, no, no, no.
I am gonna tease
her to no end.
She's gonna cry, "I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, Melissa,"
and I'm gonna keep digging
my heel in. [chuckles]
I find her happiness
quite disturbing.
Hey, Marquis de Sade,
stop actin' like a little kid.
You should say the
same thing to her.
She's the real little
kid around here.
I'm sorry, who's a little kid?
Uh... Ah!
[MAN]
Whoa, I'm outta here.
Miss Captain, you've come to
grace us with your presense.
You may be thinking that
you can easily beat me,
but it's not going
to happen that way.
Heh. You really think you
can run a lap naked?
I can hardly wait.
Better ask yourself.
Sergeant Sagara!
Ma'am.
Please follow me.
I need to talk with you.
Yes, ma'am.
[KURZ]
T-Tessa's n-naked body?
Ooh, yeah!
[KANAME]
Sousuke!
Hm? That's okay.
You can't help it
if it's your job.
[chuckles]
[dead line beeping]
Well, shall we begin the
training session now?
[TELETHA]
Yes! I'm ready, coach!
[SOUSUKE] Right... Um, Captain?
Please don't call me coach.
But you are a coach.
I'll call you Mr. Sagara
if you prefer.
[SOUSUKE]
Thank you, ma'am.
I'd appreciate that.
Yes, sir, coach.
I mean, Mr. Sagara.
An expert is often
able to climb up
without the assistance
of a ladder,
but I will ask that you please
not attempt this yourself.
Even in its sitting position,
the height is
approximately four meters.
That's roughly two stories.
So don't attempt it.
Heh.
[SOUSUKE]
Um, please climb up the ladder.
[TELETHA]
Right.
[TELETHA pants]
This is so hard.
Ah... Ah...
--[TELETHA yelps]
--[screams]
[screams]
Ow, that was really... Ah!
A-Are you hurt anywhere,
Madam Captain?
No, I-I think I'm all right.
I'm real sorry and I...
...actually I'm
feeling kinda lucky.
[SOUSUKE]
Hm?
Um, Madam Captain, uh...
Not good... This is
really... not good.
[TELETHA giggles]
[SOUSUKE yelps]
I did it!
I'm in, Mr. Sagara!
[SOUSUKE sighs]
Very good, ma'am.
Now please take one
small step forward.
Yes, right away!
Here I go!
Ah!
Huh?!
Captain, do you copy?
Ah. Ah. [coughs]
Captain, listen,
you have to stop moving
and abort right now! Captain!
S-Someone help me!
[SOUSUKE]
Stay still!
I don't know how
to stop this thing!
How do I stop?!
Wait! Captain!
[KURZ] Heh, heh. Whew!
Someone's been hittin' the tap.
Huh?
Hey, barkeep, gimme the usual!
Me, too! I want another!
Maybe you should have
something else, miss.
[MELISSA] I can take it.
Hit me again, you old meiser.
Heh, heh. Try nursing this one.
Heh, heh!
Now, ya know,
our Tessa's out there
doin' some serious practice.
How stupid.
I feel sorry for poor Sousuke.
I'd say you're the
one bein' stupid.
All her life, whenever
someone told her
she couldn't do somethin',
she made it a point
to prove 'em wrong.
You went and told Tessa
she couldn't operate an AS
and now look what happened.
Get too cocky and you'll lose.
[MELISSA]
I know, dumbass.
Uh...
[MELISSA] I know her favorite
snack. The bugs she hates.
Her bra size.
I just couldn't
stand another minute
of her pretending to be
Miss Strong-and-independent.
Always putting on a brave face,
never knowing when to back down.
Are you serious?
[MELISSA] Oh yeah. It's so
totally pathetic, you know?
She thinks she can
change the world
with her sub and giant robots.
She's like a hyper
active little kid.
[KURZ] What about you
when you were her age?
[chuckles] I think I was
a lot stupider than she is.
[chuckles]
What's so funny?
[KURZ]
So, is that the honest truth?
[MELISSA sighs]
I guess... maybe it's true.
I may very well be the victim
of my own inferiority complex.
I suppose you're also thinking
that I can't win, Mr. Sagara?
No. That's not true... uh...
It's fine. I'll be okay.
Thank you for your kind
words, but I'm not stupid,
and I'm pretty sure
that I know what goes
into fighting
a battle, all right?
So you're planning on
winning this engagement?
[TELETHA]
Mh-mm. The other reason
I asked you to be my coach,
Mr. Sagara, is that I needed
a field expert's opinion.
Y'see, this area doesn't
have good visibilty
because of the think bushes.
The soil is very soft over here.
You see, given the
weight of the M9...
[SOUSUKE]
Huh...
[TELETHA]
So, what do you think?
It sounds like a good plan.
You think so? I'm so glad.
It was worth taking
the extra time.
[SOUSUKE] You may wanna
change the direcion here
to point this way,
taking the time of day
into consideration.
You'd be against the light.
[TELETHA]
I see.
But, no matter which
way you choose,
you're only going to
have one shot at it.
If it doesn't work
after that one try,
I'll give up.
I'll simply have to
surprise Melissa.
Surprise her? You're serious?
Yeah. If I can just do that,
running a lap around the
base naked is nothing.
Don't you think so?
She's late.
[yawns]
Melissa?
Yeah, what?
You have read about
Musashi Miyamoto, right?
[MELISSA]
Huh?
Is it a famous battleship?
[KURZ]
Uh... Yeah, nevermind.
[gasps]
No way!
[MELISSA]
A gas turbine engine?
She's using an M6.
Now I get it.
She'd rather have easy handling
than state-of-the-art
specs, huh?
You know, I've been
waiting for a while now.
[TELETHA]
I'm sorry.
I stopped on the way over
to have a light lunch,
'cause I was really hungry.
[MELISSA growls]
[TELETHA]
Melissa?
Yeah, what?
[TELETHA] You don't need
to pull any punches.
[MELISSA]
Heh. That's fine with me.
[gunshot]
[M9 A.I.]
11 o'clock. Distance six.
Target is one AS.
Setting up Alpha 1.
Well, here goes nothing.
I'm ending this right now.
[SOUSUKE]
That was a miss.
[gasps]
Wait, no way!
It wasn't a direct hit.
You hit the tree
in front of her.
What are you talking about?
A real bullet would've ripped
right through that tree.
Unfortunately, you're not
shooting real bullets this time,
you're shooting paint.
[MELISSA]
Ugh, give me a break.
[SOUSUKE] All misses.
None of them hit directly.
What the hell are
you talking about?
[gasps]
[SOUSUKE]
That was a miss.
You're lucky, Mao.
If it had been a real bullet,
the debry would have
damaged your sensors.
[KURZ] No joke. Looks like
Tessa's holdin' her own.
[KURZ chuckles]
Good luck!
Hey, listen up, you guys!
Gah!
Fine. We'll play by your rules.
So all I have to do
is make a direct hit?
That's affirmative.
Well, just you watch me.
You better be ready, baby.
[TELETHA pants]
[TELETHA] Don't fall down.
I mustn't fall down.
--[beeping]
--[gasps]
[TELETHA]
This is the AS battlefield.
[TELETHA gasps]
[screams]
[TELETHA] Imagine if these
were real bullets.
This is where Melissa
fights all the time.
[TELETHA]
We're both women,
but we fight on
such different levels.
I can't beat her.
There's no way I can beat her.
[SOUSUKE]
Captain!
Calm down, and keep moving.
Don't stay in one spot.
I-I know that, but I...
You'll be fine. I know you
can do it, Madam Captain.
I guarantee it.
[SOUSUKE]
Okay!
The M6 is pretty fast.
Doesn't matter though.
So...
...let's finish this.
[MELISSA gasps]
[MELISSA]
ECS?!
[MELISSA] No reaction.
What does that mean?
Very impressive move,
and yet... y'know...
[MELISSA] ...I sttill feel
sorry for the poor thing.
Sayonara.
[M9 A.I.]
Alpha 1 has been lost.
[MELISSA grunts]
[gasps]
[TELETHA]
Please hit it!
[pants]
[MELISSA] I lost. Oh yeah,
she totally wiped me out,
but I won't complain that
it's not fair to set a trap,
or that the judge
was on her side,
or that everybody
was supporting Tessa.
And I'm not gonna bitch about
how unfortunate and lonely I am.
Oh no, I'm saying
nothing of the sort,
and I won't say how
if it was a real battle,
I would've won.
You won't hear me insisting
like some ungracious loser.
Sounds to me like you got
a whole lotta complaints.
Negligence is the worst enemy.
[MELISSA] Yeah, yeah. There's no
excuse for ignorance, is there?
[MELISSA sighs]
God, what was I doing?
I'm so stupid. Aw, man.
Melissa...
I'm sorry I said all
those terrible things.
[sobs]
I need to thank your people
for their work, Lt. Commander.
[TELETHA sobbing]
[TELETHA] I'm sorry I did
such a stupid thing.
Nah, it's a good thing I lost.
It's natural that the
Captain should win,
but enough talk,
it's over with, okay?
Yeah, I've had more
than enough of that AS.
Excuse me. Uh, girls?
What happened to running a
lap around the base naked?
[BOTH]
Scumbag.
[SOUSUKE] The Self-Defense
Force has set up
an extreme AS challenge:
for pride, for love,
and because I couldn't say no.
Next Full Metal Panic,
Episode 14:
"Is Narashino Burning?"
The keyword for victory
is graded radish.
[TELETHA]
You're kidding, right?