[KALININ]
Once we start the operation,
these two UN transport planes
will land with our support,
accommodate the hostage group
from the jumbo jet,
and take off within 5 minutes.
What? In 5 minutes?!
That's not enough time!
Five minutes is an eternity to
be protecting a target that big.
What should we do if one of the
transport planes gets destroyed
while it's taking off?
Then accommodate as many
hostages as possible
in one of the
transport helicopters.
As a last resort,
you may ditch your AS,
but in that case, make sure
to destroy it completely.
This should take priority
over your lives.
We are the only ones in the
world who can make this mission
a success, so I'm
counting on each of you!
[KANAME pants]
[panting continues]
[KANAME grunts]
Lemme out of here!
[FEMALE DOCTOR]
Hm?
I said out!
Lemme out of this thing!
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Quack doctor! Mad scientist!
Shut your mouth now!
Sit still, and watch the images!
[KANAME] I can't take it! No
more of these stupid 3-D videos!
I'm not your guinea pig,
okay?! Let me go!
[FEMALE DOCTOR sighs]
[KANAME grunting]
Is that it?
[SOUSUKE gasps]
Just focus.
You're acting like
a little brat,
and after I've tried so
hard to be nice to you!
Who're you talk about nice,
you ugly old hag?!
It's been fun,
but I gotta go now.
[FEMALE DOCTOR]
Where're you going?!
[KANAME gasps]
You get back here, now!
No way! You... You can't scare
me just by waving a gun!
[gunshot]
Okay... I'm scared...
[KANAME screams]
What's going on?!
[FEMALE DOCTOR] The subject
was giving me trouble.
I had to reprimand
the little snot.
Just what kinda trouble
was it that you had to go
and pull a gun on her, huh?!
What authority do you
have to question me?!
Just hold her down, okay?!
Hmm?
Hey, what're you doing?!
You know, at first,
I wasn't planning to use
this experimental drug
in the test phase, but...
[FEMALE DOCTOR]
It's your own fault.
I tried to be as
nice as I could.
Heh.
No, lemme go! Please, don't! No!
[HENCHMEN grunt]
[KANAME]
Huh...?
I can take from here,
Miss Chidori.
Oh, God, Sousuke!
And just who are you
supposed to be?
I'm the one who gets to ask
the questions here, lady.
What is all this equipment and
why did you kidnap Miss Chidori?
You think I'm gonna
tell you, just like that?!
[gunshots]
[FEMALE DOCTOR gasps]
Don't shoot me! I'll tell you!
We're using this equipment
as part of an experiment
to find out if she is truly
one of the Whispered.
Th-The Whispered?
I wanna know everything.
[shots firing]
[FEMALE DOCTOR screams]
[KURZ] So, you think our
collision-prone Sgt. Somber
is doin' okay out there?
[MELISSA] If it's Sousuke you're
talking about, I wouldn't worry.
'Cause he could run a marathon
through a mine field
and come out clean.
Even under enemy fire.
[KURZ]
Nah, that's not what I meant.
I mean Kaname. Huh? And certain
feelings Sousuke might discover
in the midst of all this?
What kind of nonsense
are you babbling about?
Rescuing the other
passengers takes precedence
over Chidori, doesn't it?
[KURZ]
I dunno...
If Kaname were in danger,
I'd be happy to forget my duty
and become her hero.
[MELISSA] Let's not confuse
you with Sousuke.
He's not so stupid
as to take that risk
and ignore the
priorities of his duty.
Okay, let's go.
[KANAME]
W-Wait!
I can't go outside with
nothing but this on!
Just forget about it!
We don't have enough time!
[KANAME]
What?! No way!
[KANAME screams]
What d'you think you're doing?!
Get off me, you
molester-pervert!
You don't understand,
Miss Chidori!
That's not what I'm doing!
[TEACHER sobing]
[CLASS murmuring]
[KYOKO]
Teacher, are you alright?
I'm so sorry... I was here
with all of you, but...
They took away Kaname, and...
[SHINJI] Uh, does anybody
know where Sousuke is?
I haven't seen him in a while.
Hey, don't look at me.
Can't you see we're
busy right now?!
All right, I'm sorry already!
Oh, Kaname...
[machine guns firing]
[KANAME screams]
[SOUSUKE]
Get in! Hurry!
[engine starts]
Get down and take cover!
[KANAME] What the heck
is going on, Sousuke?!
Okay, who are you?!
Where are we going,
and what're you gonna do
when we get there?!
Dammit, answer me!
The truth is, I've been
following you since
the first day I reported to
your school, Miss Chidori. Okay?
I already know that!
What I really wanna know is
why you keep on following me!
Right.
All I know is this:
You're a very
special human being,
and some government agency
wants to use you for a
secret medical experiment.
G-Government agencies?
What medical experiments?
[SOUSUKE]
We're not sure yet,
but in order to
prevent such a thing
from happening, Mithril sent
a soldier to guard you 24/7.
And the soldier is me.
[KANAME]
Soldier? Mithril...?
[SOUSUKE] Yes. I'm Sousuke
Sagara, Sergeant of Mithril.
My call sign is Urzu 7,
ID number B-3128.
Uh, look, I understand
you're a big military buff
and everything,
Sousuke, but come on,
I mean, seriously. Hello?
We've got in-coming!
Huh?!
[KANAME screams]
Okay, stay down!
What?! But why?!
Because we're
gonna crash through!
Huh?!
[KANAME squeals]
[tires squealing]
I'm gonna die...
Let's get out!
We've got company!
[KANAME]
Huh?!
Are those...
Are those Arm Slaves?
It's the RK-92,
also known as The Savage.
Don't tell me you're gonna try--
Wait a second,
what're you thinking?!
I don't care if you're
the biggest military maniac
in the whole world.
Stop it, Sousuke!
There's no way an amateur
can pilot a robot like that!
I'm no amateur.
Huh...?
I'm not an amateur,
Miss Chidori.
In fact, I'm a specialist.
[AS COMPUTER]
Closing and locking hatch.
Adjusting master sensors.
[KANAME screams]
[AS COMPUTER]
Main generator switching on.
Main condenser charging.
All joints are locked.
Now in the process
of releasing locks.
Move it, you
Soviet-made scrap heap!
Huh?
[AS COMPUTER]
Ready for combat maneuvers.
Sousuke...
You're kidding me...
[KANAME gasps]
I can't believe it...
He did that? Sousuke Sagara?
[sirens blaring]
[SOLDIER A]
What happened?!
[SOLDIER B] Intruder! There's
reports of an AS being stolen!
[SOUSUKE]
Chidori, get on!
We're making a run for it!
[KANAME] Uh, you want
me to climb on there?
[SOUSUKE]
Hurry!
Listen, Chidori, you're gonna
need to hang on tight!
[KANAME screams]
[KANAME gasps]
[KANAME] Wait! What're you
gonna do about the others?!
I can't leave without them!
[SOUSUKE]
Right now, we're in danger!
My colleagues will make
sure everyone's okay!
[KANAME]
Colleagues?!
They're sending a rescue squad.
[OPERATOR]
Urzu 2, you have 30 seconds
before submarine departure.
Urzu 2 roger.
Urzu 6, do you copy?
[KURZ] Gotcha, babe!
I'll be 10 seconds behind you!
Alrighty, shall we go out there
and pick up Sousuke's body?
[MELISSA] Moron! Don't
say that, it's bad luck!
Go!
Let's get this thing started.
Five minutes... And that's going
to be a long, long 5 minutes...
[KANAME grunts]
[SOUSUKE]
Hang on for a little longer.
Until we build up a good lead.
[SOUSUKE] The sensors
didn't pick up anything...
Where is it?!
He's shooting grenades!
Not another one?!
[KANAME screams]
Chidori!
A blank shell?! It was a decoy?!
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[KANAME gasps]
[KANAME]
Sousuke!
Stay back!
Don't come any closer!
[GAURON] Aren't you that
student who dropped his tray?
I never figured the agent
would be a high school student.
I admit it, you had me fooled.
Hm?!
[GAURON chuckles]
[GAURON laughs]
[GAURON]
This is a nice surprise!
Kashim, is that you?
I hadn't noticed! I never
knew you were in Mithril!
How's Kalinin? What's that
old chicken doin' these days?
Why don't you tell me
how you're still alive?
Heh. See, I already had a piece
of titanium built into my skull
as a result of a
previous injury.
The shallow angle of the
shot didn't hurt either.
But enough about me,
it's fantastic to see you!
It's fabulous! Really great!
There's so much to talk about,
Kashim, but, oh, the time.
I've got this new job where
I have to play around
with a young girl's brain.
It's like a treasure hunt.
Like a treasure hunt?!
[GAURON]
Yes, her brain is full of keys
to the so-called
Black Technology.
Like how to apply the theory of
the Lambda Driver in practice.
Once that's all fleshed out,
nuclear weapons
will be obsolete,
or so they claim.
Is this news to you? I'll let
that be my parting gift.
Tell the Ferryman when
you get to the River Styx
that there's a
big group on the way.
Until then, Kashim.
[KANAME gasps]
No, don't do it!
[GAURON gasps]
[KURZ]
Yee-haw!
Urzu 6 landed successfully!
I've got Urzu 7 and
"Angel" with me!
It's Kurz!
You said Kurz?
Wait, you don't mean...
Yep, it's me, Kurz Weber.
You doin' okay, Miss Kaname?
Who the... What in the
world are you guys?
What are those?
Did we make it in time...?
[KURZ] Sousuke. Take Kaname with
you and go back to the base.
The transport planes will
be forcing a landing soon.
Once they land,
you've got 5 minutes.
I'll take care of
things down here
and catch up with you later.
Understood.
Keep a sharp eye out
for that silver AS.
Both man and machine are
in a class of their own.
What's going on out there?!
All I can hear is gunfire...
This is so awesome!
Just like the
Fuji training field!
Except that it's
actually the real thing!
[SHINJI squeals]
Kick ass!
[MELISSA] Everyone! Keep away
from the windows!
[gasping]
[MELISSA]
I found it!
[gasping]
[UN OFFICER] Please stay calm!
We are the UN's Rescue Unit!
We're here to make sure that
no passengers get left behind.
So just please be patient
and follow the
directions we give you!
[distant gunfire and explosions]
Hang in there.
I'm okay.
[KANAME screams]
Don't be scared, just run!
[KURZ]
You're mine.
Damn, this guy's quick.
Two minutes into this battle,
and the enemy hasn't
shot even once.
[KURZ] Does it mean he only
has hand-to-hand weapons?
Or is he just
that much better...?
You bastard! Don't toy with me!
[CLASS chattering]
Come on, people! Let's go!
Sir, one of my students
has been kidnapped!
Please, let me go find her!
[MELISSA]
Don't worry, Ms. Teacher.
Kaname is going back
on the other flight.
Uh, what other flight?
Wait a minute, how on earth do
you know my student's name?
[MELISSA]
Doesn't matter! Get in!
Wait a sec! Sousuke!
He's missing too! Hey!
[SHINJI yelps]
[MELISSA] Urzu 6, hurry up!
We're running out of time!
I'm sorry, it's just
taking me a little time.
[KURZ] You wanna play games?
Let's play...
[gun clicking]
Here goes!
Burn in Hell!
[gunshot]
Urzu 6, are you ready yet?
Pick up Sousuke and get
back here immediately.
Urzu 6, do you copy?!
Weber! This is no
time for joking!
Don't piss me off!
[KANAME screams, grunts]
[KANAME]
Pull yourself together, Sousuke!
I don't wanna escape by myself!
Why do ya have to send me back?
Why can't we go back together?
Next Full Metal Panic,
Episode 6: "Still Alive."
Is it really time for
us to say goodbye?
[SOUSUKE]
Not if I can help it.