He survived as well.
He's out on a business trip.
Whatever. It's not like
I care about him.
But I... I can't
shake this feeling...
I'm afraid something
terrible may happen.
[gasps]
No! Not good!
Oh, no. It's the Lambda Driver.
Shall we?
Kashim!
So, can you use it?
[SOUSUKE]
Yes.
Damn you, Kashim!
Bastard!
[distant gunfire]
Those boys're havin' a regular
shootin' spree with us.
Well, I guess they have
too many bullets
to keep in storage, huh?
Man, wouldn't it be nice
if Mithril had that same
problem on their hands?
[BATIST panting]
[beeping]
There's more coming.
What the hell gives?
Those guys are from the
country's regular army!
[GRAY] The buyer of
this illegal shipment...
...in all likelihood,
is this country.
Crap. If the sandstorm was over,
we could turn on the damn ACS.
To hell with all these
punk ass savages.
With this thing tyin' us down,
we'll never be able to escape.
I've had enough of this.
Let's just dump it
off the cliff.
[SOUSUKE]
No, we can go down the slope.
Huh?
[SOUSUKE]
Once we get down there,
we'll be in hilly terrain.
It'll give us the
advantage of cover.
And just how do you
know that for sure?
[SOUSUKE]
I used to fight in this land.
Huh?
We've got incoming.
Then lead the way, Sergeant!
[SOUSUKE]
Roger.
[ENEMY 1] They went down
with the treasure, huh?
[ENEMY 2] Even though they
had the latest model AS's,
if they fell from
this height...
Well, Kashim...
[panting]
[GRAY] This is the last
painkiller we have.
We need to remove the bullet
as soon as possible.
[ANDY]
Didn't we have a surgery kit?
Bill was carrying it.
--[BATIST groans]
--Batist!
Hey, man! Hang in
there, all right?
You still gotta pay me $300
from that poke game we played.
[SOUSUKE] We've got a heavy
burden on our hands.
A burden?
What did you say?
Are you tellin' us we should
leave Batist behind?
No, I was talking
about the warhead.
[ANDY]
Jackson!
I'm sorry if I wasn't clear.
If you have time to argue,
why don't you check the
shock absorbers on the M9s?
Did you ring up HQ?
Our long distance communications
are malfunctioning.
Then let's hide the
trailer behind the rocks,
and find the nearest town.
They've gotta have a
telephone there, right?
I have an objection.
Ugh! Not you again!
It takes 3 days to reach
the nearest town.
The enemy is more likely
to find the abandoned
warhead in the meantime.
I propose we launch
a counterattack.
A counterattack?
You must be kidding.
We only have four AS's
left in our squad.
I'm not much for
fightin' losin' battles.
We'll have a better
chance of winning.
This is our unit's mission,
okay, Sergeant?
And you have no right
to give us orders.
Jackson!
--[BATIST] Stop it, Jack!
--[ANDY, GRAY gasp]
Sagara's decision
was the right one.
If only we had listened
to him, then...
...Bill wouldn't have...
That's enough.
We get it, so save
your strength.
Sagara -- he knows this land,
and he knows the target
better than we do.
Listen to his opinion
and... [groans]
[JAKCSON]
Batist!
[ANDY]
Stay with us, man!
[GRAY]
I appreciate your advice,
but I've decided to
reject your plan.
Getting him to a doctor
is our priority.
Understood?
Yes, ma'am.
[GRAY]
When never know where
the enemy will be waiting
for us. Exercise caution.
Roger.
Sergeant, a question.
[SOUSUKE]
What is it?
You said you used to fight
in this region as a guerilla.
Is that true?
[SOUSUKE]
Affirmative.
[GRAY]
But... it was quite a while ago
when this was a hot sopt.
They do say Asians tend to look
young for their age, though.
So you must've been...
Actually I've been fighting
as a guerilla since
I was 8 years old.
--[ANDY] Hm...
--[JACKSON] Huh...?
[GRAY]
Eight?
That's correct.
I guess you could say this
area is like my back yard.
Wasn't it unusual?
Your group having
a child guerilla?
No, ma'am. We had two.
He was three years
older than me.
Name was Zaied.
[footsteps]
[GRAY]
Did he bully you?
[SOUSUKE]
We worked well together.
Almost like brothers.
However...
[SOUSUKE] It's very doubtful
that he's still alive.
I see.
Why haven't we caught them yet?
That goddammed warhead
is our merchandise.
There's no excuse for
it to have been stolen.
No need to worry.
Kashim hasn't noticed
my existance yet.
It'll be easy to outwit him.
I hope you're not
swayed by pity,
knowing him since you
were kids. Eh, Zaied?
Trust me. I've seen many die
because of dreams or
senseless affections,
and I've no intention
of following them.
Your attitude is admirable,
but if you want a spot
on the winning team,
I'll need to see what
you're capable of.
[SOUSUKE]
Captain, I've returned.
[TELETHA gasps]
[helicopter blades whirring]
Damn, we're not even
makin' a mile an hour.
[sighs] When you're at war,
there's always somethin'
to bitch about, isn't there?
But we ain't gonna know
where the hell we are,
unless we get moving.
Then let's go.
[BATIST groans]
--Batist!
--[BATIST] Ow...
[GRAY]
Batist! Can you hear me, Batist?
[ANDY]
What's wrong, Gray?
The painkiller is wearing off.
Sergeant, how long until
we reach the town?
I'm estimating another
ten hours or so.
That's assume that the
enemies don't find us.
[JACKSON]
Can't we do anything?
I don't wanna lose
another squad member.
[BATIST groans]
We may be able to pick up
an emergenc surgical kit.
[gasps]
[ANDY]
What? Is there a village nearby?
[SOUSUKE]
No.
It's a remote camp
we used to stay at.
But we need to take a detuor,
which might put us
out in the open.
[GAURON]
They changed direction?
That's right.
I thought they were going
over the mountain range
and straight to the town.
[ZAIED]
Now they're heading this way.
Taking the scenic route, huh?
Do you think they're
tryin' to confuse us?
[ZAIED] No. It's more likely
that Kashim is headinng...
...here.
[BATIST groans]
Sergeant! Have you found
the surgery kit yet?
[SOUSUKE]
No, not yet.
Holy shit, this
place looks terrible.
Hey, Sagara, you really
expect us to believe
you used to live here?
Affirmative.
Looks like somebody...
lost a battle.
[SOUSUKE]
Affirmative.
[gasps]
Found it.
Oh! All right!
[SOUSUKE]
It's all vaccuum-packed,
but we should still
sterilize everything.
Jackson, give me the flashlight.
Andy, go boil some water.
Okay.
And I'll go keep watch outside.
So is it finished?
Yes, but we shouldn't move
him until his fever's down.
Andy and Jackson are
checking if there
are any tools or bullets left
that we can make use of.
Is it a good idea for us
to stay here hiding?
No, we'd better
assume our enemies
will discover this place
sooner or later.
Unfortunately, Gauron also
knows about this hideout.
[GRAY]
He knows?
The people who attacked
our unit back then--
Gauron was also fighting
on their side.
[SOUSUKE]
It was only by coincidence
that I was away from the
camp on reconnaissance.
I guess I've been pretty lucky.
Just one single mistake,
and I'm sure my destiny would've
been the same as Zaied's.
[GRAY]
I'm from Eastern Europe.
As you may know, that area
is rife with civil war.
I joined the resistance movement
and started to operate an AS.
One day, our enemies
surrounded us.
We were supposed to
have reinforcements,
but they never came
until the end.
And that was it: the whole
unit had been abandoned.
It often happens.
I wandered around for a while,
and now I'm a mercenary
from Mithril.
All the other
soldiers in this unit
must have similar experiences
to mine, I suppose,
but of course, they
never talk about it.
Anyway, I was wondering
if you would stay
with our unit when this is over.
[gasps]
If I have to fill a vacancy,
I'd like a skilled pilot.
You've passed
the test, Sergeant.
Well, I...
[GRAY] You can give me an
answer when we get back.
Well, I hope you'll consider it.
[GRAY] A pretty awful
homecoming, isn't it, Sergeant?
A homecoming?
[GRAY] Oh, right. I guess
Japan is your homeland now.
Homeland?
[GRAY] Do you have someone
waiting for you in Japan?
Uh, no...
Well, maybe yes, maybe no...
[GRAY]
Hm.
There's a six hour
time difference.
It must be nighttime there.
Miss Mao, thank you.
So do you really feel safer
when "he" guards you?
Oh, sorry if I gave
that impression.
Wow! It's pretty good.
[MELISSA] We'll be informed
once the mission is finished.
I'll let you know as soon
as I hear something.
Don't worry. He'll be back soon.
So why don't you think
about getting him
a welcome home present?
He'll probably be
coming back exhausted.
[KANAME]
Mm.
[SOUSUKE]
Gauron will most likely
follow his previous success
and take this path.
With Kashim, one would
expect him to think
we'd attack exactly the
same way we did last time.
If we counterattack directly,
we won't stand a chance.
So we'll set up an ambush.
They'll set up an ambush,
and shoot at us from there.
Kashim really has no
other viable options.
We should dig in
where we can shoot
but somewhere they
won't be able
to shoot back at us.
I propose...
[ZAIED]
Here.
Heh.
[GRAY]
Are you ready?
[SOUSUKE]
Affirmative.
Here we can shoot the
enemies as they come.
We may not be as good
as Kurz though.
[ANDY]
I don't like you, Sagara.
Even though you're a kid
and you're skillful as hell,
you're still a punk.
Real smartass, you know that?
Your kind pisses me off.
[SOUSUKE]
I see.
I'm savin' a punch for
you back at the base
so don't go and
get yourself killed.
I can't promise anything,
but I will try.
Heh. Motivation.
That's what I'm
talkin' about, son.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
[beeping]
[alarm beeping]
[GAUREN] Kashim, there's no
place for you to escape.
There are no reinforcements.
What can I say? Reality is
a harsh mistress.
Next Full Metal Panic,
Episode 17:
"The Wind Blows
at Home, Part 3."
No one's going home
alive, this time.