[GAURON]
Cancelled?
[MAN 2]
We heard about that disgrace
you suffered at Helmajistan.
[GAURON] Are you implying
that I'd fail at this?
What we're saying is
we can't trust a courier
who runs away with his life
but not the merchandise!
You don't trust me, huh?
--[gunshots]
--[MEN groaning]
That boy has certainly made it
difficult to carry a side job.
[GAURON] Time to get back
to my real work.
[KANAME]
What is this?
A gate for the school festival.
It's pretty
impressive, isn't it?
It looks nothing like
a festival gate!
Please explain yourself!
I heard that the theme for last
year's festival was "peace."
So this year's theme
is "security."
The gate will double
as an observation tower
where we can post a guard
for people's safety.
It's designed to stand
for a long time,
even if a heavily armed
terrorist decides to come
and attack the school festival.
[sighs] Look, I didn't
think it was possible,
but your war mania
is getting even worse.
I mean, what's the deal? Is it
eating away at your brain?
And you people!
Don't you have any questions
about this whole thing?
Well, in all honesty,
we agreed with Sousuke's idea
that anybody should be able to
come to the school festival
and feel completely safe.
The only one who would feel safe
around that eyesore is Sousuke!
Oh well... maybe you're right.
Maybe peace has made us
forget about security.
But if you've got it in your
head to build an entrance
that costs 1,471,000 yen,
you're out of your mind!
[SOUSUKE]
Ah, so you noticed.
If we're lucky, we may be able
to obtain some triple-plated
Israeli-made compound armor.
It usually costs somewhere
around 5 million yen for--
Uh, what did you do that for?
Don't you realize that
the entire budget
for the school festival
is only 1,500,000 yen?
If we go with your idea, we
won't have any other attractions
besides your big, ugly,
gloomy doom castle!
Did you think we'd approve
this monstrosity?
Seriously, you need to
dismantle it or something.
Whatever it takes to
get it out of here.
Kaname! That's the--
[STUDENTS gasp]
[coughs]
What is this stuff?
[SOUSUKE] The marking system
is malfunctioning.
You little... Sousuke!
[SOUSUKE]
There's no need to worry.
The paint does no harm
to the human body.
You're wrong!
There's a lot of things
for me to worry about!
Wasting the precious days of
my youth with a military nut
who wouldn't know the meaning
of the word sensitive
if he looked it up in
the dictionary!
The summer of her second
year of high school
is a very special
time for a girl!
Is it really?
Yes really!
But now it doesn't matter.
I'm gonna spend the last week
of summer break at home
and do absolutely nothing
until school starts.
[SOUSUKE] So, you mean you're
going to be free for this week?
I certainly am, sadly enough.
[SOUSUKE]
Hmm. In that case,
would you like to go away to a
southern island with me?
[gasps]
I mean, just the two of us.
A-Are you really
serious about this?
Yes I am. I've been
meaning to ask you to go
for quite some time now.
Uh... lemme think for a second.
Hey, I brought some goodies!
Shh! Come here.
Ya have to watch this.
[SOUSUKE] So what do you wanna
do? Would you rather not go?
You won't do anything weird?
I promise not to. Trust me.
And it's not dangerous?
It's not dangerous either.
[STUDENTS]
Oh...
Well, alright, if you insist,
then I suppose I'll be
able to go with you.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Kaname! Are you all right?
[STUDENTS murmuring]
Huh? Oh, it's okay.
I mean blue is naturally
well suited to summer.
[KANAME humming]
Uh, isn't this a little skimpy?
You should take this with you.
Because I'm willing to bet
the only suit you own is
the school swimsuit, huh?
[coughs] I'll take
this one as my backup.
It seems a bit risky with
just the two of us.
[KANAME]
Uh, nothing risky's gonna happen
if Sousuke's with me.
Wow, Sousuke's a lot
bolder than I thought!
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
It's just a little adventure
at the end of the summer.
Unknown submarine is still
on a collision course.
They-They just keep getting
closer to us, sir!
Why haven't they turned?
They must have noticed by now.
[OPERATOR]
Distance: 100.
Distance: 50.
Distance: 30. 20. 10.
All hands, brace for impact!
[OPERATOR gasps]
[MAN 1]
What the hell was that?
[OPERATOR]
It-It disappeared.
It's gone.
What do ya mean?
That can't be right!
--Check BQQ5 now. Move it!
--Hey, it might be...
it might be that Toy Box
we've heard talk about lately.
What kinda talk?
[YOUNG GUY]
Rumors of a ghost submarine.
It's huge.
It appears and vanishes
without a trace,
and it's supposed to be
terribly fast, too.
If that was the Toy Box
we just ran across,
then the commander must be
a dyed-in-the-wool psycho
with the most warped mind
this side of the Pacific.
I swear we'll have our revenge!
Is there something
the matter, Captain?
No, nothing really.
But I think we may have caused a
little trouble for the Pasadena.
I'm hoping they
weren't too offended.
I think you're asking
for too much.
Had that been my ship,
my pride would have
been severely wounded.
It's not like we can help it.
There's nobody else
to practice against.
[MARDUKAS] Well, we did
receive good results,
but maybe we should consider
adjusting our propulsion.
It may lower our sonic profile.
[TELETHA] I agree. Well,
shall we return to base?
Otherwise we'll be late for
the birthday party.
[MARDUKAS]
Yes, Ma'am.
Also, we'll be having a guest
arrive at the island tomorrow.
[KANAME]
We-We're gonna fly in this?
[SOUSUKE] Yes. I had it
prepared just for you.
Well, let's go.
[KANAME] I'm impressed.
I never thought of you
doing something like this.
So, like, where are we going?
I've planned a visit to
Mithril's West Pacific
Fleet Base.
Captain Testarossa said that
she wanted to see you.
[clatter]
[KANAME]
Hmm. Is that right?
[COMPUTER] Orders from base have
been received on circuit E2.
Mr. Mardukas. Our return
has been postponed,
as well as the party. We've been
given orders to head south.
Going to the Perio Islands.
Is that correct, Madam Captain?
It's a chemical weapons threat.
From what I understand,
an armed group attacked
and occupied the
dismantling facility there.
It doesn't sound very promising.
If they decide to bomb
the warehouses where the
chemicals are being stored...
[TELETHA] We'll have a serious
problem to deal with.
That little nation could
be completely destroyed.
[MARDUKAS] Well, I would imagine
the US military will be sending
in their AS Special Forces.
I hope that'll be
enough to handle it.
[coughs]
Kaname...
[KANAME] What do you want,
Mr. Sergeant Sagara?
Please let me know if you're
feeling at all inconvenienced.
I'll try and meet your
needs as best I can.
[KANAME] I am. But I'm not
gonna bother you with it,
because it's not
a problem you can solve.
Sergeant! We have an incoming
radio call from Melida Island.
[sighs]
Understood.
Go ahead.
[KURZ] You need to meet up
with and board the de Danaan,
which is now cruising. And be
sure to bring Kaname with you.
Are you sure?
But, Kurz, she's a civilian.
Sorry, bro, Tessa's order.
Besides, all things considered,
the de Danaan is probably
the safest place on Earth
for Kaname to be.
Huh. Then I'll be
taking her with me.
[door clicks]
[SOUSUKE]
Do you have a bathing suit?
Uh... I, uh I guess so.
Then please change.
You can use the
far end of the cabin.
Once you finish, put your
belongings in this bag.
All of them.
What's going on? Hey!
[SOUSUKE]
Hurry up, we don't have time!
So what's the deal?
Why are you dressed like that?
You're gonna need to
put this on. Quickly.
Nevermind, I'll do it.
We're short on time.
[KANAME]
Wait! Ah! W-What are...
Sergeant, you got one minute.
Yes, I know.
[PILOT]
There's no time for a re-do.
[SOUSUKE]
I know. It's okay.
Hey, what exactly are you...
30 seconds!
I appreciate it. See you later.
See you later?
[gasping]
[KANAME]
Wh-What are you talking about?
[gasps]
[SOUSUKE]
Okay, let's go!
Let's go?! Don't tell me you're
gonna jump out of this airplane!
[SOUSUKE]
Affirmative!
[KANAME screams]
Blue sky. Blue ocean.
Just the two of us.
[OPERATOR]
Ocean splash down confirmed.
Uh, the two people who
just landed are strugglin'
on the water's surface.
They may be drowning.
I can hear splashing noises
and screamin'. It sounds bad.
Please, patch us in quickly
so I can hear them.
[SOUSUKE]
Chidori! Stop!
[KANAME]
Shut up!
Have you ever given thought
to how I might feel?
I could've killed myself. You
are the worst kind, you loser!
You can just leave
them out there.
[KANAME]
Jerk!
Hi and welcome aboard the Tuatha
de Danaan, Miss Kaname Chidori.
You look a little exhausted.
Of course I am.
After getting dumped from
a plane into the ocean
and then having to dive,
anyone except Sergeant Sabotage
is bound to get
exhausted. Really.
I'm so sorry. Originally,
I was going to
invite you to the base
out on Melida Island,
but the situation here
has changed a bit.
It's all right, I really
wanted to see you too, Tessa.
And you've got a lot of things
you want to talk to
me about, don't you?
Yes, I do. However...
Sergeant Sagara?
[SOUSUKE]
Yes, Captain?
Please head on over
to the main hangar.
And could you tell anyone there
that Miss Kaname and I
will be there momentarily.
As you wish, Captain.
--[TELETHA] Miss Kaname...
--Huh?
If you wouldn't mind,
why don't you go ahead and
change into your plain clothes.
And I'll give you a tour
around the submarine.
[TELETHA] This feels
rather narrow, doesn't it?
But it's actually quite
roomy for a submarine.
I've given every thought to
the staff's safety because
they may need to run through
here in an emergency situation.
Thanks to this,
we've had no reports of
clumsy people running into
things and falling-- [yelps]
...over.
Are you... all right?
Yes. I'm fine. I'm fine.
This is nothing.
You seem a bit unsteady.
Are you really an
honest-to-god Captain, Tessa?
You know it hurts when
people ask me that question.
This ship is my home, and I
assure you that I know all
there is to know about it and
everything that goes on inside.
That is, within the proper
bounds of privacy of course.
Please, come this way.
Though I'm afraid you may not
like what you're about to see.
[MARDUKAS]
Attention!
[gasps]
To Miss Kaname Chidori,
for her great bravery,
resolve, and kindness
when our group and Captain
Testarossa faced so many crises.
Everyone with deepest
appreciation, salute!
The moment they heard you were
coming aboard, they all wanted
to pay their deepest respects
to you, Miss Kaname.
Uh, I... I'm really,
you know, very honored, but,
I, uh, didn't do all these
great things you said.
[MARDUKAS]
Miss Chidori,
what you did would
have been difficult
even for the most respected
and capable soldier.
You should be proud of yourself.
Everything that the commander
said about you is true.
You should be proud.
[applause, cheering]
Well, the welcome
ceremony is over now.
And FYI, we're going to be
throwing a little party
right here on board the ship.
We do hope you'll join
us in celebrating.
Party?
Yes. Well, you see...
Today is this baby's
first birthday.
[KURZ] All right! It's time
for submarine bingo!
Allow me to announce the
fabulous first prize!
It's such a great prize,
I wish I were competing!
What will the winner get?
That's right! A hot steamy kiss
from Captain Testarossa!
[GUYS]
Yeah! Woohoo!
Mr. Weber! I didn't hear
anything about this!
But you told me...
"Please let me know
if there's anything
I can do for the party!"
It's what you said!
[TELETHA]
Ye-Yes I said that, but...
If the smooching idea is
bothering you that much,
how 'bout your favorite
underwear then?
That's even worse!
It's your kiss
then. All right!
We've got the Captain's
okay. Let's begin!
[GUYS cheer]
[KURZ] O-65. How's that?
Now I know someone's gotta be
getting close out there!
Who needs one more?
[gasps]
Huh? Uh, what's the matter?
You lucky dog.
Well it's not over yet,
folks. Let's go!
[TELETHA]
Oh my god. A kiss! What do I do?
N-42.
[MCALLEN]
One more to go!
[LIAN]
Oh yeah? Me, too!
[MCALLEN, LIAN growl]
It's really starting to
heat up in here!
Who's the Goddess of Victory
gonna smile on today?
Will it be Sousuke?
McAllen? Or Lian?!
[TELETHA]
Oh, please let it be Mr. Sagara.
It's B-13.
Sorry, guys, but bingo!
[LIAN]
Oh my god!
[GUYS]
Oh, man.
What an upset! The winner
is Lieutenant McAllen!
[GUYS]
All right! Wow! Yeah!
Captain, give him
a big ole wet one!
Forget her, how 'bout a deep
kiss from me, Lieutenant?
[GUYS laughing]
Well then, are you
ready, Lieutenant?
I sure am, ma'am.
I'm very honored.
[GUYS cheering, laughing]
Oh, my, my! This has gotta
be the best day of my life.
I'm a lucky man. [laughs]
[SOLDIER] This is Echo 84.
I've been bombed!
Mayday! Mayday!
[SOLDIER 2] My legs have
been damaged. Someone help!
[SOLDIER 3] That red devil!
That bastard took out Akshar!
[SOLDIER 4]
Help me! Somebody help me!
No way! He can't have
taken out the entire unit!
Where is he?
Where is that guy?!
[GAURON laughs]
Damn you! Now die!
[GAURON]
Are you running out of bullets?
Oh, that's too bad. You're
the last one left standing.
Some of your friends cried
and begged for their lives,
but you... you did
well, soldier.
Don't patronize me!
Perhaps I should
teach by example.
Ready? Bang!
[KANAME]
♪ Oh take me out... ♪
Beautiful girl, huh?
Good figure like that.
Good fashion sense.
I doubt those guys'd be able to
leave her alone for a second.
Maybe, but I don't really care.
Well if that's the case,
then what's with all
the sighing, bingo boy?
I was worried that they were
going to get too carried away.
This submarine is in the
middle of a mission,
and we're sitting
here playing music.
And where do you get off
thinking that, Sousuke?
If Tessa said it was all right,
then someone like you
has no right to complain
about it, wouldn't ya say?
Yes, that's true, however...
Everyone's uneasy about it.
Even with all the experience
under their belts.
[GAURON]
Stars and stripes forever, huh?
[GAURON'S MAN]
It seems they're coming now.
[GAURON]
Huh?
[GAURON'S MAN]
We received word that
they loaded up an assault
unit out on the ocean.
[chuckles]
What's that old saying? "Like
shooting fish in a barrel"?
[GAURON'S MAN]
Also we think
those two may be
on board together.
Really? My favorite couple, eh?
How nice. How splendid.
[GAURON'S MAN] But if she dies
with the crew of Mithril,
it'll be a problem, right?
Yes, I know. I won't let
the girl die. Although...
[GAURON'S MAN]
What?
As you know,
accidents do happen.
[KANAME] ♪ If you are there then
I don't care where we both go! ♪
[KURZ] Naked Mao makes a naked
confession about her past to
naked Kaname and naked Tessa!
The glowing skin of
their naked bodies
and the stories of
my exploits-- Ah!
[KANAME] Ugh.
Next Full Metal Panic,
Episode 19:
"Engaging Six and Seven."