[INTERCOM STEWARDESS]
Passengers, welcome aboard.
This is flight JNA 903 departing
Tokyo on a flight path to Naha.
[MALE STUDENT A] Hey there,
Miss! Wanna join our party?
Hey, this is the
Marine Corps' M6
I was tellin' you about before!
[MAYUKO]
Awesome! We're really flying!
Oh, yeah! Hey, Kaname,
you have to check this out!
[KANAME groans]
Huh...?
[KANAME]
Hm?
Hey, what's up with you? You've
been weird since yesterday.
Is something bothering you?
Um... No, why?
Does it have to do with Sousuke?
[KANAME gasps]
Well, no! Why do you ask?
I mean, seriously.
[KANAME laughs]
All right, I get it.
I'll change the subject.
[gasping]
[MALE STUDENT B] Oh man,
I think the plane's tilted over!
[PASSENGERS screaming]
Nothing to worry about.
Just turbulence.
Right.
But it's kinda strange, what
with the weather being so clear.
[CO-PILOT whimpering]
W-W-What're you doing?!
[CO-PILOT gasps]
Perhaps you'd like to die, too?
[CO-PILOT]
No, please! If you kill me,
you'll have no one
to fly the plane!
Is that right?
'Cause you know,
I've always wanted a shot
at flying a commercial
aircraft like this one.
Seems like it would be more
fun than a transport plane.
What's your expert opinion?
How's this thing handle?
Please! Don't kill me, Mister!
Hm? I was just asking
if it was fun to fly.
[TERRORIST]
Gauron.
[GAURON]
Hm?
Oh. See what I
have to deal with?
What's the matter with you?
Why did you have to go
and kill the pilot?
He lied and told me the
plane was out of order.
Said he was going back
to Haneda so he could--
[TERRORIST] If you enjoy murder,
that's your own business.
But just in case you've
forgotten, this opportunity
has been given to you by
my country with one caveat.
You will not needless endanger
the success of our mission.
[GAURON chuckles]
Now, don't be like that.
As long as they listen to me,
I'll be a perfect gentleman.
Yes... Don't you agree?
You heard what the man said.
I'll keep up my end and do
my best not to kill you.
But if you don't listen, I'll be
forced to kill someone else.
Passengers, all right?
Now, let's see...
I wanna turn this
plane and head north.
Our destination is
there on the map.
It's a fervently autocratic
enclave. Very rare these days.
Huh?
[SHINJI]
Hey, Sousuke, look over there!
It's an F16 with
UN markings on it.
I wonder why it's flying
around this airspace?
I'm sure it's nothing
to worry about.
[SHINJI]
Mm-hm.
[KYOKO]
Hey, Kaname...?
[KANAME]
Hm?
[KYOKO] Isn't Okinawa supposed
to be surrounded by the ocean?
Last time I checked.
Well, there's been nothing
but mountains for a long time.
[MALE STUDENT C]
This is getting weird.
Isn't there a flight attendant
around here somewhere?
I haven't seen one
in quite a while now...
[SHINJI] Something's not
right... This isn't Okinawa...
You know, I don't even
think we're in Japan.
So it would seem...
Well, gentleman. We're just
in time for the party.
[MALE STUDENT D]
Where are we?
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
This isn't Okinawa, is it?
Look, Sousuke! They've got a
Mig-21 out there on the tarmac!
And that tank over there?
Must be a T-54!
It's all, like,
junk from 50 years ago!
Wait a second;
they've got the latest RK-92!
Everything's Soviet-made,
but there's a huge gap
between the new and the old.
[GAURON]
Your attention please.
I'm speaking to you on
behalf of your captain.
Due to unavoidable
circumstances,
we've made an emergency landing
at this air base in the
autonomous region of Khanka.
What is that supposed to mean?!
[TEACHER] I didn't hear
anything about this!
[TEACHER ASSISTANT]
Hey, calm down!
Huh, I can't believe
she just noticed it now.
[GAURON] Given the complicated
political situation of the area,
I'm gonna need all of you to be
on your best hostage behavior.
Just so you understand
where I'm coming from,
please take a look
outside your window.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[GAURON] Do not be alarmed,
the soldiers and tanks only wish
to extend their welcome.
But if you try to escape or
hesitate to follow orders,
we will not hesitate
to shoot you.
We thank you for flying with us.
[TELETHA]
We were completely taken in!
I thought we destroyed the
enemy's base of operations
to prevent things like this!
[KALININ] It seems there's
another mastermind involved
apart from the KGB.
The Khanka enclave...
But they're too weak for
something like this, no?
Right. It seems they and
the KGB are being used...
...by some unknown person.
What you're saying, then,
is this unknown person
took 400 hostages to cover
the kidnap of one girl,
and on top of that, chose a
politically difficult place
so mounting a rescue would
be next to impossible?
[KALININ]
A well-orchestrated hijack.
Typical terrorist methods.
Atypical execution.
A job well done.
Huh?
Uh...
[TELETHA]
Tell me, Lt. Commander.
What do you think
is the probability
of the hostages being
released safely?
You mean without Chidori, ma'am?
Of course. What I'm think is,
if we do nothing, it might be
easier getting the 400 other
people on board released
without a major incident.
I'm sure the autonomous region
of Khanka doesn't wish
to make the situation any more
complicated than it is.
[KALININ] There will be
no profit in it for them,
should even only a few hundred
Japanese citizens be murdered.
[TELETHA]
I agree.
We'll begin
diplomatic negotiations
and secure their safe return.
We'll find and rescue
Miss Chidori after.
That's a sound argument.
However--
[TELETHA]
We'll wait and see.
[KALININ]
Hm?
For the time being.
Very well. We can take
some time if you want.
But we may be giving
the snake an opportunity
to build up his venom.
I know... But we should wait
until we hear something.
[GAURON]
You, over there.
I'm talking to you, Miss.
Yes, you, the lovely young
lady with the long hair.
What is it?
I would like to send a videotape
off to the mass media,
and you're very photogenic.
You'd be the perfect
face for this tragedy.
Oh no, not me. I'm just
a plain, ordinary girl.
Emphasis on plain.
Nothing special at all.
In fact, your viewers might
get sick to their stomachs
watching me. I'm serious.
[GARUON] What did I say
about hesitating? Don't be shy.
Wait a minute...
Please, sir! Let go of me!
I don't wanna do it!
Why are you taking me?!
[KYOKO]
Kaname!
[TEACHER]
Hold on! My student!
What're you going
to do with her?
Not to worry, ma'am.
We'll return her very soon.
I'm not gonna
let you do that.
If you need someone,
you can take me.
You wouldn't arouse
as much sympathy.
This is for the mass media.
That is the worst
excuse I've ever heard!
You're nothing but a coward!
[GAURON]
Hm?
You're the worst
kind of criminal!
It's bad enough that you had
to hijack a plane at all!
Now you're going to take
a child, and for what?!
To make some point,
whatever that might've been?
It means nothing! It's garbage!
God will never forgive you
for what you've done--
My, my. Aren't we a
little chatterbox?
[gasping]
Oh my God...
No... Please don't...
[crashing]
I'm sorry.
Let go!
[GAURON growls]
[TERRORIST]
Gauron.
[GAURON]
Hm?
We need to move, so hurry up.
[GAURON]
Hm. Let's go.
We don't need all these
other people anymore.
[KANAME] Let me go!
I can walk by myself.
Teacher...
Shut up and keep moving.
[KYOKO]
Kaname!
[TEACHER sighs]
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
Teacher!
[MALE STUDENT E]
Somebody call a doctor!
[SOUSUKE]
I'm so stupid!
[HENCHMAN A] I never expected
it to be this big.
[HENCHMAN B] We had to
consider both scenarios.
Detonation in the air,
and on the ground.
This should be more than enough.
[HENCHMAN B] Okay, see the
red cord down in there?
Remove the insulating tape,
and plug it into
the outlet marked "3."
[HENCHMAN A]
Found it. Plugging cord in.
[beep]
[HENCHMAN B]
Okay. Keep your hands clear,
and don't touch anything.
No one is allowed to
use walkie-talkies
or cell phones for 30 meters.
[GAURON]
When will you know the results?
[FEMALE DOCTOR] Tomorrow
morning at the earliest.
That's a long time. Couldn't
we expedite the process?
[FEMALE DOCTOR] The medications
won't take affect
until at least another
6 hours. If not more.
If I can't get my results,
maybe I should kill you
and take her elsewhere.
Don't be so impatient! You have
no idea what the Whispered are,
nor do you understand the
importance of this research!
[GAURON]
I beg to differ.
[FEMALE DCOTOR] how can you say
that when you have the nerve
to bring Codarl with you?!
[GAURON] It's my backup in case
the people of this country
have a sudden change of heart.
[FEMALE DOCTOR] Hmph.
Then you're a bigger coward
than I thought.
Don't be so cocky. You will do
exactly what I tell you to do.
Now, is that perfectly clear?!
[FEMALE DOCTOR coughs]
[beeping]
[SOUSUKE gasps]
[SOUSUKE] Sgt. Sagara,
B-3128, Urzu 7 reporting.
[TELETHA]
Are you safe, Mr. Sagara?
[SOUSUKE]
That's an affirmative, Captain.
I'm so glad.
Sgt. Sagara, explain the
situation on the ground.
[TELETHA]
How terrible.
[SOUSUKE] It appears
they are going to kill
all the passengers to mask
the kidnapping of Chidori.
The bomb looks extremely
difficult to deactivate.
My equipment isn't good
enough to risk an attempt.
I understand. We will start
preparing a counter-measure.
[SOUSUKE]
Yes ma'am.
Listen, Sgt. At this point,
the safety of the passengers
is a greater priority
than Chidori's rescue.
[SOUSUKE]
Roger.
[SOUSKE]
Sir...
[KALININ]
Hm? What, Sgt.?
[SOUSUKE] The leader of
the hijackers... It's Gauron.
[TERRORIST]
Don't move.
[KALININ] He has assassinated
more than 30 VIPs,
and he's the man responsible
for two aircraft bombings.
At least, that we know of.
In short, a very dangerous man.
The last time we encountered
him, we had the KGB pursuing us.
Gauron was one of
their mercenaries.
One day while Sagara and I were
out on our respective patrols,
he attacked the guerilla
hideout with two Arm Slaves.
[KALININ]
There were no survivors.
And then what?
Together, Sagara and I
vowed to seek revenge.
An opportunity presented itself
to us two weeks later.
We set me up as the decoy,
and Sgt. Sagara as the sniper.
He shot Gauron.
But somehow he's still alive.
Yes, it would seem so.
He sounds like a
viciously cruel man.
I hate to say it, but we
couldn't have counted on him
releasing the hostages
from the start.
Right.
[TELETHA]
It's agreed then.
We need to make this Gauron
pay for his crimes in full.
[KALININ]
Yes, Madam Captain.
[TERRORIST]
Turn this way. Slowly.
Tell me, just who were
you communicating with?
Start talking now!
The person I was
communicating with...
[TERRORIST]
Hm?
[SOUSUKE yells]
[TERRORIST grunts]
Did you really think...
you could beat me...
...if I didn't have a weapon?!
[TERRORIST yelling]
D-Damn you...
Who... the hell are you?
I take out the garbage.
So how are you feeling?
[KANAME grunts]
Not too good.
[FEMALE DOCTOR]
Really? That's too bad.
We have a long way to go.
Please, let me go back home.
I don't think I can take
anymore of this sleep-learning.
[FEMALE DOCTOR]
Learning?
Don't be ridiculous.
This is something you've known
since before you
were born, Miss Chidori.
[KANAME gasps]
We need to move very
quickly on this mission.
[MELISSA]
Sorry we're late, sir.
We told the taxi to hurry!
[KURZ chuckles]
[KALININ]
Please pay attention.
This is the plan which we,
the crew of the Tuatha de Danaan
will carry out.
First, we will send each
respective AS support unit in
led by an AS team
comprised of six Arm Slaves.
Attack helicopters, transport
helicopters, then VTOL fighters.
[KALININ] The greatest
problem we will be facing
is the bomb located here,
which I suspect has a
remote control trigger.
It is utterly imperative
that we disarm the bomb
before the terrorists have
a chance to flip the switch
after they recover from the
shock of our initial attack.
[KALININ]
Once we start the operation,
these two UN transport planes
will land with our support,
accommodate the hostage group
from the jumbo jet,
and take off within 5 minutes.
What? In 5 minutes?!
That's not enough time!
5 minutes is an eternity to be
protecting a target that big.
What should we do if one of the
transport planes gets destroyed
while it's taking off?
Then accommodate as many
hostages as possible
in one of the
transport helicopters.
[KALININ] As a last resort,
you may ditch your AS.
But in that case, make sure
to destroy it completely.
This should take priority
over your lives.
We are the only ones in the
world who can make this mission
a success, so I'm
counting on each of you!
I want you to work to
the best of your ability!
Is that it?
[SOUSUKE growls]
[SOUSUKE gasps]
Just focus...
[TELETHA] Any communication
from Mr. Sagara?
[KALININ]
Not yet.
I hope he's going to be
all right, Lt. Commander.
I mean, considering our enemy...
The one thing I can say is this:
As long as I've known him,
Sgt. Sagara has never let
his personal feelings
get in the way of his judgment.
--[gun shot]
--[SOUSUKE gasps]
[HENCHMAN B] What's going on?!
Where did that shot come from?!
[HENCHMAN A] I don't know!
Was it from inside?!
[HENCHMAN B]
Let's go!
[HENCHMAN A]
Right!
Only the stupidest of amateurs
would go out at a
time like this...
I'm a professional soldier!
Will this be like
those other times...?
I informed him
which of his duties
takes the higher priority.
He's a pro among pros.
[SOUSUKE whimpers]
[GAURON chuckles]
[gunshot]
[KANAME]
What're you thinking, Sousuke?!
Even if you are a military buff,
you can't control
a robot like that!
What?! You can?!
Next Full Metal Panic,
Episode 5: "Whispered."
Who are you anyway, Sousuke?
[SOUSUKE]
I'm the garbage man.
[KANAME]
Right.