[KANAME]
Resonance...
No, don't do it, Dana!
Give her a real apology.
Now!
[SOUSUKE] I mean it. I'm here
because you've been here for me.
Sounds like an attacker sonar!
Huh?
[alarm sounding]
I'm sorry it came to this,
but I need you to stay
on board for a bit.
May I use your telephone?
I hope you're planning
to hire a good lawyer.
We need to avoid a
conflict between Mithril
and the US military.
And we are the only ones
who can make that happen.
[CAPTAIN SAILOR]
Hmph.
It's like a whale that
forgot how to swim.
[SAILOR] Toy Box changed
direction and headed north.
Speeding up to 30 knots.
Distance: two miles.
Launch tube doors
three and four are open
and ready for launch
sequence any time.
Well? You're serious, right?
I dedicate this to
our fallen brothers.
Remember Pearl Harbor!
Launch number three!
Number three, launch now!
[DANA A.I.] A high-velocity
screw has been detected
in the water at bearing 2-9-8.
Unidentified torpedo closing in.
There's no more time...
Please let me have control
of the submarine now.
Unbind the helmsmen
and the sonar crew.
Uh, no.
Listen, this is the difference
between life and death.
I'm not sure if
I can avoid this,
so I'm positive that
you can't do it.
We won't know that until I try.
You'll die like the rest of us.
Wanna kill yourself?!
[gasps]
Let's see, huh...
The most expensive
suicide in the world.
I'm gonna die with a
multi-billion dollar submarine.
I rather like it.
[GAURON chuckles]
[TELETHA]
The reckless terrorism...
A deliberate surrender...
...the missile attack
on the Bunker Hill...
We've been misjudging this
man from the very beginning.
Why...? Why are
you doing this...?
Who's up for a game of chicken?
Dive to a depth of 1500.
[DANA A.I.] Warning: The order
exceeds the maximum depth
of recommended use.
I don't care. Let's go for it.
Aye, sir.
[KURZ] So what now?
If we keep going like this,
there's a very good chance
we'll end up as shark bait.
[GUEN] Don't worry.
I heard people say this ship
could outrun a torpedo
at top speed, easy.
[KURZ] Moron. The latest
torpedoes are so fast it's sick.
And these are US issue.
So what? Who gives a damn?
Stop trying to bluff
your way out, okay?
Although, you know, Kurz-y,
if you come out
with your hands up now,
I may just spare your life.
[KURZ]
Go to hell.
[GUEN] I'm serious. Let's go up
to the command center together.
Why don't you have a talk with
Gauron and kill one of the crew
in front of his eyes.
If you do that, Kurz-y, then
you can join our little team.
I promise he pays well.
[KURZ] Heh, that ain't cool.
It's disgraceful.
Listen, Kurz. Mithril
is a mercenary unit,
not some friends of justice.
I'm pretty sure I told you
before we're just killers
for hire. Isn't it kind
of an unwritten rule
that we work for the
customer who pays the most?
All the coolness and
loyalty in the world
ain't gonna buy you jack.
Come on out!
[KURZ]
Okay, my mind's made up.
I'll kill you and
ask Tessa for a bonus.
I'll take a sexy shot
of her in a swimsuit
and sell it to the other guys on
board for 20 dollars a piece.
If a hundred guys buy a print,
I'll make 2,000 bucks.
And here I was thinking you were
a little more clever than that.
It's not a matter
of how clever I am,
I'm just a practical kinda guy.
[SOUSUKE] It won't be long.
Hang in there.
Kaname, where's the key?
[KANAME]
Here it is.
[gasps]
Fits right in.
[SOUSUKE]
TAROS...
Looks like an older model
than the one in Arbalest.
It's not connected to any Lambda
Driver, but to Dana herself.
What?
I think I'm starting to get it.
Ah. Now I see.
K-Kaname!
[KANAME, TELETHA] Thank you,
Mr. Sagara. Your work here
is done now. Would you
please come and rescue me?
[gunshots]
Ah!
[grunts]
[yells]
--[KURZ] Yah!
--[GUEN groans]
[KURTZ groans]
[gasps]
[GUEN groans]
[yelling]
[groans]
[gunshot]
You're full of shit, Guen!
For someone like me,
that money is the same
as cheap toilet paper.
It's not even good enough
for wiping your ass.
Just hurts your butt
and clogs the drain.
[gasps]
Really, Kurz.
You have absolutely no sense for
hand-to-hand combat, do you?
You jumped over him,
you jumped away from him,
like a street punk.
I couldn't keep watching.
So who is he?
Huh? That's... That's Guen.
What was he trying... to... do?
Hey, where have
you been, Melissa?
Huh? Where was I?
When I woke up,
I was in the clinic
and the alarm for the
evacuation drill was going off.
I didn't wanna go to the
hangar wearing nothing but this,
so I hid. Then I came here.
I saw you guys fighting.
[KURZ]
Ah, gotcha.
[MELISSA] I wonder if Peggy
gave me some strange medicine?
I have no clue what's going on.
What happened to Venom?
What about Sousuke?
And-- Oh, I'm
still feeling dizzy.
[KURZ] Man. Where's a
camera when you need one?
[DANA A.I.] Warning: Deck 3,
corridor B has caught fire.
Warning: C-System, number 16
discharge pipe has burst.
Warning: Abnormal noise from
barrier wall H-7 on deck one.
All right. Excellent.
Buckle up, everybody.
[GODDARD]
He's nuts!
[inaudible]
[beeping]
Dana! Hard rudder to port!
And throw out some decoys!
Aye, sir!
He doesn't know anything!
[GAURON]
So, will we avoid it?
Can we do that?
I don't know.
It doesn't look good.
[chuckles]
[TELETHA] Dana. Launch number
one and number two
countermeasure when I
give you the signal.
Set for deep-sea mode.
[DANA A.I.]
Aye, Ma'am.
[CREW]
Huh?
[TELETHA]
No, not yet...
[gasps]
Do it now!
Follow with an emergency blow!
[growls]
[TELETHA]
Now!
[DANA A.I.]
Aye. Emergency blow.
[CAPTAIN SAILOR]
They avoided it?!
Yes. It seems they
used emergency blow.
They're rising to the surface
at a tremendous velocity.
But how could they
have done that?!
Shit, in that small of space?
Their captain must have balls
made of steel to pull that off.
It's certainly... something.
He's quite a daredevil!
What kind of magic was that?
Don't you understand?
It wasn't magic.
It means Dana doesn't
trust you enough
to let you have
control of this ship.
[GAURON growls]
This ship is mine and
I'm its only captain.
Playtime is officially over.
[GAURON]
She did this?
Heh.
Terrific, isn't she?!
Even if you kill me, she'll be
here to save this ship!
Furthermore--
[GAURON grunts]
So it's you!
There is no escape!
Surrender now!
You really think I would?
You should know better, Honey.
Well, I guess not, then.
Sgt. Sagara, shoot him now!
[TELETHA grunts]
[gasps]
[GODDARD]
Sergeant!
You need to unlock
the handcuffs first!
Another torpedo is on the way!
We're gonna need to be able
to maneuver the submarine!
Yes, sir! Roger!
[GODDARD] One head cap
bearing 2-7-8. Distance 50.
There's no way out...
[ringing]
Sousuke...
[gasps]
[KANAME] Tessa...
She told me... that you...
Kaname?
[KANAME] You needn't
worry about de Danaan...
[gasps]
You take care of the captain!
S-Sgt. Sagara!
[gasping]
That's it... it's
the safety system!
[gasps]
A US Navy surface
ship is nearby.
They've got their submarines
set to disarm torpedoes
above a certain depth to
avoid any friendly fire.
[SAILOR] Captain expected
the second torpedo.
And she knew exactly
what she was doing.
Put her down now!
Wow, what a woman!
I think we can all agree!
[SOUSUKE]
Gauron! Where are you?!
Gauron!
Gauron?!
[gasps]
[SOUSUKE]
Kaname...
[CAPTAIN SAILOR] Son of a bitch!
We missed them again? How?!
It would appear that the
Toy Box captain knew
about our safety systems. Or, it
might just be a coincidence...
Shut up! Unlock the
safeties on the torpedoes
and try it one more time!
Flood the number one and
number two launch tubes!
[KANAME]
He's trapped like a rat.
His back is against the wall,
but he thrives on the pressure.
It thrills him from
deep inside his heart.
It's the bottom of the ninth.
Two outs, the bases are loaded,
and a full count. All he's
thinking about right now
is hitting the ball
out of the park.
[SOUSUKE]
Venom.
That's right. He's heading
out... to the stadium!
[CROWD cheering]
[PERSONNEL A] Go back to your
positions if you're not injured!
Hurry up and check
the anchor wires.
[PERSONNEL B] Man down over
here! Send a stretcher.
Take care of the wound later.
Keep the airways open.
Listen up. Everyone, keep a
clear head. You got that?!
Right!
[grunts]
Hey, Doctor. Doctor
Goldberry, come quick!
[chattering]
[MARDUKAS] It's utterly vital
that we anchor the cargo.
I'll have to enforce these
regulations from now on.
[GODDARD]
Command center.
[MARDUKAS]
It's me. What's happening?
Is there a problem
on the bridge?
[GODDARD] Commander!
Thank god you're alive.
It was that terrorist.
He hijacked the AI and
took control of the ship.
But thanks to the captain,
Dana was able to recover.
[MARDUKAS] I see. What's
happened to the terrorist?
[GODDARD] He escaped.
He's hiding somewhere.
I was going to send the
warning over the loud speaker.
Commander?
[MARDUKAS] Goddard,
is the terrorist injured?
[GODDARD]
Yes, Sgt. Sagara shot him.
[MARDUKAS]
The left shoulder?
[GODDARD]
Yeah.
[MARDUKAS]
Not good!
Anybody, stop him!
[GROUP]
Huh?
[MARDUKAS]
Stop the man by the red AS!
[gasping]
[screaming]
[growls]
[MARDUKAS]
Dammit!
Take all the injured and
evacuate the hangar right now!
It doesn't matter where you go!
Just hurry up and run!
I still got it!
The power! It's mine!
[screaming]
[GAURON laughs]
Huh?
[MARDUKAS]
Huh? Is it Sgt. Sagara?
[thunder rumbles]
[MARDUKAS] He's backed
the Tuatha de Danaan
into a tight corner.
[GREY] Your mission...
Is to make it home, Sousuke.
[MELISSA] If you're thinking
that it's all up to you to
protect us along with
Kaname, you're dreaming.
[gasps]
Did I wake you?
I've... I've had enough!
[GAURON laughs]
I'm so delighted, my Kashim!
Kashim...
Look, Gauron, I'm sending you...
...straight to hell!
[MARDUKAS]
We finally won the battle.
Captain, I'm honored.
Looking back on my 25 years
of service in the Navy,
I've had one
hardship after another.
[KANAME, TELETHA] Next Full
Metal Panic, the last episode:
"Into the Blue."
[SOUSUKE]
It's time. Is everyone ready?
[MARDUKAS]
Huh?