I hope you're
all right, Sousuke.
[SOUSUKE grunts]
Kaname... Madam Captain...
[helicopter blades whirring]
It's too late.
Ten minutes too late.
[beeping]
[VOICE] Gecko 9 to Urzu 7,
the present has been delivered.
Urzu 7, roger.
So, tell me,
where in the world are
my lovely little ladies?
--[MELISSA grunts]
--[KURZ groans]
[SEINA]
How are you feeling?
Why do you ask?
Does it look like
I'm feeling better?
[SEINA]
I guess you're not dying yet.
You look like a
manicured gentleman,
but you're really quite tough.
That's right.
I'm tough enough to not give up
and hang myself like
so-and-so Takechi.
[KALININ grunts]
Are you trying to
tell me he was weak?
How people see him is up to you.
Your master, Seiji Takechi,
exists only in you now.
Your behavior will ultimately
determine his truth.
That's all.
You're a strange bird.
You act more like a
priest than a soldier.
I'm sure it would suit you well
to carry a bible
around with you.
That sounds like a rather
attractive career change.
[SEINA]
It's too bad.
What is?
I wish that I had
met you earlier.
[KALININ]
It's not too late.
Yes, it is.
You've been my enemy since
the beginning of this ordeal.
The reason I didn't kill you
was nothing but a whim.
Once I learn nhow much you know
about the Lambda Driver,
you'll no longer be
of any use to me whatsoever.
I'm not telling you anything.
In that case, it looks like
I'll have to probe Miss Chidori
and Miss Testarossa
on the subject, won't I?
I'll be sure to save you a seat.
Hey. Let's keep the
collatoral damage down.
[MELISSA]
You're one to talk.
Where'd you get
that pickup truck?
Hey, hey. Careful there, babe.
Remember, we're calling
it a borrowed item.
[MELISSA]
Don't break the item.
I have to return it later.
Aw man, how come Tokyo
has so many of these damn
billboards out on the road?
[KURZ]
Hah! Be glad it's not Hong Kong.
Hmph. I'll desert if I get
orders to pack up my bags
and start piloting an
M9 through that place.
[SOUSUKE]
Maybe I was being stupid.
Are you talking about
releasing Tessa first?
Yeah, you are pretty stupid.
That's a rather unpleasant
thing to say to a colleague.
Which one of them would you
have decided to release first?
Let me think.
I guess I'd have to go
with the girl I loved.
Someone really nice who
accepted my warm love
with tenderness and
a caring heart.
It's a pretty important detail.
[SOUSUKE]
Nonsense.
It's not a matter of love.
I was trying to find
the most effecti--
[KURZ]
And that's why you're so stupid.
You gotta follow your instinct
in that kinda situation.
Love isn't just some
thing you can calculate.
I'd rather not talk about it.
[MELISSA]
Hey, listen up, you two.
We don't have time for this.
You can be effective
and calculate
the shortest route
to the Aomi Wharf.
[KURZ] Are you sure we can
trust this information?
De Danaan took a little peek
at the local
Orbis Police Database.
There appears to be a van marked
for a speeding ticket
high-tailing it to Aomi Wharf.
I made Chidori wear a bracelet
with a radio transmitter
hidden inside.
One we arrive at the wharf,
we can pinpoint
her exact location.
All right. Open up
the glove compartment.
There should be a map inside.
[VOICE] Attention! This is
an all-points broadcast
from the Tokyo MPD's Net Crime
Special Investigation Unit.
At 22:52 hours,
investigations confirmed
a hack of the Orbis system.
The hackers sent off flags by
a specific vehicle's records.
The vehicle in question is...
[TAKUMA] Sister! I've had
such a terrible time!
[TAKUMA grunts]
[KANAME, TELETHA gasp[
Sister...
Tell me why you didn't take
the medication in the aircraft.
I'm sorry. The pills
fell into the toilet.
They looked dirty
so I didn't take them
and flushed them instead.
And because of that,
you got caught,
and we had to
spend time, effort,
and lives trying
to get you back.
[TAKUMA]
But... They looked really dirty.
I swear--
[TAKUMA grunts]
Well, you need to be
tougher than that.
I... I'm sorry...
But I'm glad that
you're all right.
I've been really
worried about you.
Sister...
Isn't there any other way
we can go, you guys?
This is the
shortest route there.
If we go through Ariake,
we add 25 minutes to the trip.
And if we go through Ginza,
you'll crush the taxis
waiting for fares by
the kabuki theatre.
[TELETHA]
Miss Chidori?
[KANAME]
Yeah?
I've been acting strange
since we first met at
Sousuke's apartment.
Huh?
I've done a lot of silly things
that I normally
wouldn't consider,
like playing mean tricks
on my subordinate.
You know, just to cause trouble.
Or trying to show off
and assert myself.
Assert yourself?
How exactly?
[TELETHA] I jumped into the
mêlée in the school yard,
ignoring Sergeant Sagara's order
and subverting his
judgment as the expert.
I've never made such a stupid
choice in my entire life.
I acted stupidly to
try and rescue you,
because you were already
doing something stupid.
Oh. I was? Then why...?
Because... By the way,
aren't you scared
at all, Miss Chidori?
I don't know. I mean,
of course I'm scared, but...
...I can't help wanting
to strike back
when I see something scary
standing right there
in front of me, you know.
Strike back?
Yeah, if there's someone
attacking you or something,
what would you call that person?
An enemy, right?
And I don't mean just the people
carrying guns and
stuff like that.
You still have plenty of 'em
in normal everyday life.
If you have an enemy like that,
you have to stand up
and do something.
I guess that's just
the way I choose
to take care of these things.
You know what I'm saying?
So that's how you feel?
Hm! Yeah, pretty much.
[KURZ] Aw, man, don't
put a checkpoint here.
What's the plan?
[MELISSA]
Break through!
I'll step over it.
[KURZ]
No way! You're crazy!
[POLICEMAN]
Hey, stop!
[sirens blare]
Can we shake them?
Well, let's see what
this thing can do.
[POLICEMAN]
This is the Aomi squad car 6.
We're chasing a
small pickup truck
that broke through
the checkpoint.
[DISPATCHER]
This is headquarters. We copy.
[KANAME] It was back when
I was in junior high.
Oh.
I just came back
home from overseas,
and people looked down on me.
Maybe because I'd gotten used
to saying whatever was
on my mind all the time.
I think maybe I was
partially to blame
for the whole mess,
but it was so bad.
They were spiteful
and played real dirty.
It was so awful.
I wanted to kill myself.
Did you ever fight
back against them?
Oh, yeah. Well, as soon
as I started high school,
the problem disappeared.
So as long as that nutcase
Sousuke settles down,
I don't think I'll
have anymore complaints.
[laughs]
Is Mr. Sagara bothering
you that much?
Yeah, he's pretty bad.
He never uses common sense,
so he ends up causing disasters.
I understand he
doesn't mean it, but,
it always seems to
make things worse.
He does try hard,
awkward as he is.
I feel like I have
to look after him.
I admit, he is a
pretty strange guy.
Oh yeah, very strange.
--[BOTH giggle]
--[door clicks]
Get up and come with me.
[TELETHA]
Mr. Kalinin!
Who's he?
You don't wanna let
'em die, now do ya?
What group do you belong to?
Don't tell him, Mr. Kalinin.
I think that'll be something
for me to decide,
Miss Testarossa.
I'd very much like to know
when it was that you
started giving me orders.
[TERRORIST A]
I'll shoot her.
Now tell me how much you know
about the Lambda Driver,
and its countermeasures.
[KALININ]
Fine. I'll tell you.
[TERRORIST A]
Hmph.
[KALININ]
Come over here.
What for?
[KALININ] Any information about
the Lambda Driver is top secret.
I can't disclose it,
even to my subordinate.
[TERRORIST A]
Hm...
I'm not too thrilled
with the idea of a man
whispering in my ear, but...
[gasps]
[whistles]
[TERRORIST A]
Hm?
[yells]
Ah?!
[gasps]
[gunshots]
[police sirens]
There I go, doing
something foolish again.
[KALININ] I know it was
an emergency, but still...
...I hope you'll forgive me
for calling you like a dog.
Yes.
Miss Kaname Chidori.
Uh, yes?
You've been taking good
care of my subordinate.
I wanna thank you
very much for that.
[KANAME] Oh, no... See...
I just met Tessa today.
I didn't mean her.
Miss Kaname. You know
he's not talking about me.
He's talking about Mr. Sagara.
Huh? I thought...
She's not my subordinate,
Miss Chidori,
but my commander.
Shall we go, Captain?
[MELISSA]
Information from De Danaan:
They're hiding out on
the George Clinton...
A tanker.
Sousuke, can you confirm?
The source of the
signal... is there.
Urzu 2, we have a visual
of the George Clinton.
Awaiting orders.
Roger. Urzu 6 and Urzu 7,
prepare to board the target.
Rescue the hostages inside.
I'll be providing ground
support outside the tanker.
[SOUSUKE]
Roger.
[KURZ] Strap in and
hang on tight! Woohoo!
[MELISSA]
Cancel ECS.
[M9 A.I.]
Roger.
[POLICEMAN B]
An AS?
This Aomi Sation squad car 3.
We have an unidentified AS
attacking a tanker at
Pier 3 on the wharf.
Requesting help from the
Maritime Safety Agency.
[POLICEMAN A]
Idiot! It's an AS.
The Maritime Safety Agency
can't handle this.
To HQ: request backup
from the Defense Agency.
Urgent. Request backup.
[DISPATCHER] Roger.
This is HQ to squad car 3.
Secure the tanker's safety
until reinforcements arrives.
[NARASHINO]
This is Narashino.
We accept your request
for reinforcment.
Number two airborne troop,
take off now.
Call sign is WAS-1.
[WAS-1]
Message to Haneda Control Tower,
please detour all aircraft
to the Narita
at Kisarazu Marker.
Repeat: Message to
Haneda Control Tower...
Hey! I don't think
this is the way out!
That's right.
We can't just escape.
There's something
we have to confirm.
[KANAME]
Huh?
[KALININ]
These are cables for operating
a large gas turbine
to generate electricity.
They must be doing something
down at the bottom of this ship.
Like what?
I don't know,
but it's certainly not
some kid's homemade
science project.
Maybe you're right,
but a child who
believes he's a grownup
can often make some
very surprising
and creative things.
[TOKYO CONTROL] Emergency code.
Repeat: emergency code.
This is Tokyo Control
to all airlines.
Haneda is now shut down
by JSDF's order.
We're turning around
all traffic tonight
at the Kisarazu Marker.
Uh, what is that thing?
[TELETHA]
It's nonsense.
If something like
this started moving,
we couldn't do
anything about it.
A lot of people will die.
That still doesn't tell
me what that thing is.
[TAKUMA]
It's my toy.
[KANAME, TELETHA gasp]
Isn't it nice?
I like to call it Behemoth.
This is WAS-1 to Ichigaya.
Is the air open?
[ICHIGAYA]
This is Ichigaya.
All flights were rerouted
from Narita to Kisarazu.
It's all clear now.
[WAS-1] Roger. From WAS-1
to all aircraft.
Starting now, we're going
into assualt formation.
Begin descending clockwise
around the ferris wheel.
You know, when I
heard the gun go off
inside the cabin,
I was positive you'd be
making your way
down here, Kalinin.
I guess I'll take
that as a compliment
coming from you, Seina.
What exactly is
wrong with you people?
You'd have to be crazy
to pilot that thing.
[TAKUMA]
Crazy?
Because we're terrorists,
Miss Testarossas?
[TAKUMA]
You see, I'm not expecting
to get anything out
of this personally.
It's really just a
form of expression.
I'm just expressing my opinion.
Well, something like that.
One year from now,
most people will have already
forgotten all about it.
Just like they
forgot Seiji Takechi.
[TAKUMA]
That's right. However,
I don't really care
what happens after this.
I'm one of the
few chosen soldiers.
Once I take my seat
inside Behemoth,
it will be invincible.
I'll destroy many things
and kill many people.
Then my sister will be happy,
and I'll be satisfied.
Takuma, please stop it!
There's still time for
you to turn back now!
You have no right
to call me Takuma.
My sister's the only
one allowed to do that.
Sorry, but it's too late,
Miss Testarossa.
To tell you the truth,
I kinda liked you,
but it's time to say goodbye.
[ALL gasp, scream]
[POLICE] Quick, somebody
call for backup!
Don't move!
It's about to start.
Takuma, hurry up
and climb into the
Behemoth, right away.
[gunfire]
[groans]
Heh!
Sousuke!
Sergeant Sagara!
[MAN groans]
[KANAME gasps]
Behind you!
[groans]
Takuma!
[KANAME sobs]
[SOUSUKE]
Kaname...
[KANAME]
I was worried about you!
[SOUSUKE]
Sorry.
I was frightened half to death.
I apologize.
Idiot.
[KURZ]
Hey, hey, what about my role?
[KALININ]
Thank you for your hard work.
[SEINA]
Hurry and get in.
But I'm... I'm injured, sister.
There's no need
for you to cry out
over such a tiny wound.
[TAKUMA]
But, I can't do it.
If you can't climb in
and pilot that machine,
then you are worthless.
If you run away,
I won't need you.
Now, or ever.
[gasps]
[POLICE shouting]
This doesn't look good at all.
Uh, guys, I think
we're in trouble here.
Let's go. We'd better
get out of here.
No, Takuma! Wait!
You shouldn't be
piloting that monster!
If you don't get out,
the machine will
take total control!
[TAKUMA]
I understand now, sister.
[BEHEMOTH A.I.] Behemoth is
sinking due to its weight.
Please start the Lambda Driver.
I'm heading out now.
Keep watching me.
I only hope I make you
happy and proud of me.
[BEHEMOTH A.I.]
Lambda Driver first function.
Initialization confirmed.
Goodbye then, sister.
[gasps]
[M9 A.I.] Impossible to maintain
horizontal and vertical balance.
Escape and take the Captain
and Miss Chidori with you.
Hurry up!
Roger.
But what about you?
Don't worry,
I won't die so easily.
Now go.
[TELETHA]
Mr. Kalinin!
[SOUSUKE]
Let's go!
[KALININ]
Let's get out of here.
Huh?
Come on.
[WAS-1]
Is that the target?
Don't know. Where's the AS?
[KANAME] A car chase on
the coastal road at dawn.
Behemoth standing tall.
Arbalest on the counterattack.
I feel that power
awakening inside me again.
Next Full Metal Panic:
Episode 12, "One Night Stand."
I've never driven
before, Sousuke!
[SOUSUKE]
This is the steering wheel.