[KANAME]
His back is against the wall,
but he thrives on the pressure.
It thrills him from
deep inside his heart.
[SOUSUKE]
Uh!
[KANAME] It's the bottom
of the ninth, two outs,
the bases are loaded,
and a full count.
All he's thinking
about right now
is hitting the ball
out of the park.
[SOUSUKE]
Venom.
That's right.
He's heading out...
...to the stadium!
[SOUSUKE]
Uh!
Did I wake you?
[SOUSUKE growling]
I've...
I've had enough!
[GOURON chuckles]
I'm so delighted, my Kashim.
[GOURON growls]
Look, Gouron. I'm sending
ou straight to hell!
Oh, no.
[GOURON grunts]
[SOUSUKE gasps]
[GOURON]
Hm.
[DANA A.I.] C3 system, number 11
power cable, has been cut.
[SAILOR A]
Bypass with the power from C4!
[DANA A.I.]
Twenty-percent power loss.
Fire detected in Hanger C.
Number two airtight
door: damaged.
Temperature inside ship: rising.
Unable to close fireproof
curtain in hanger.
We'll do it by hand.
Is there anybody nearby?
Tanks seven, eight, and nine
have been damaged at the trim.
Flood level 40 from the
tanks numbers 10 and 15.
I'll start an emergency
drain of the jet fuel.
[DANA A.I.] Port side ECS masts
two and three are damaged.
Unable to use.
Shit! Can't anybody
get rid of the psycho?
[GOURON chuckles]
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[GOURON growls]
[panting]
[GOURON grunts]
[GOURON chuckles]
You got me. You won, Kashim.
Then again, maybe not.
Initialize SDM. 120 seconds.
[COMPUTER] Warning. You cannot
cancel after initiation.
Do you approve?
[GOURON]
Idiot. Get on with it.
I'm so delighted
that you'll be here
with me till the end.
[GOURON chuckles]
[SOUSUKE]
Uh? The end?
Let's you and me become
friends, eh, Kashim?
[SOUSUKE groaning]
The hatch.
[GOURON]
Let's see...
Sixty seconds on the clock,
plus one 300 kilogram bomb,
equals lots of little
pieces of submarine.
So now, the question is,
what will you do, Kashim?
Active sonar.
Active sonar, engage.
[ping]
We just got pinged on sonar.
Pasadena approachin' fast,
bearing 298.
Decoy stand by.
Get ready for another dive.
But the compressed
air tanks aren't full yet!
[GODDARD growls]
[SAILOR B]
Closin' in. At 2500.
Confirm signature of
large tube door openin'.
[KALININ]
Is that right?
Mm. I see. Roger.
He says he would like
to have a word with you.
With me, huh?
Hello?
Y-Yes, Sir. Uh!
No... No, it was just th--
Uh. Yes, Sir.
I'll cancel all
orders to attack.
We'll return immediately.
[CAPTAIN SAILOR]
Why the hell not?!
You know, it's kinda like havin'
your first time at
the batter's box,
only the game got suspended
because the sun went down.
[CAPTAIN SAILOR growls]
[GODDARD]
The torpedo isn't coming?
I wonder if that
thing lost our trail.
[SAILOR B] Pasadena stopped
at a distance of 1500.
They're not shootin'.
Oh my god! The flight
hatch is opening!
It's what?!
Commander!
[MARDUKAS]
What are you doing?
Opening the flight hatch
in a storm like this
is tantamount to suicide.
I don't understand.
I can't control anything.
[SAILOR C] There's nothing
showing up on Dana!
[RILEY] The order was
sent from somewhere else.
You're kidding!
[RILEY]
Uh?
[SAILOR D gasps]
[BOTH]
Uh...
[TELETHA] It's all right.
You don't need to worry.
[MARDUKAS]
Huh?
Captain.
[GOURON] How do ya feel?
Are you ashamed it came to this?
That I won't let you
finish me off in one blow,
like some mythical hero.
Why aren't you struggling?
Let's make the most of this.
For old time's sake, before
we're both blown to pieces.
Okay? Kashim?
Thirty seconds left.
What're you gonna do, honey?
[SOUSUKE grunting]
[panting]
Twenty seconds left.
Oopsie. I meant to say 15.
[laughing]
[SOUSUKE]
Uh!
Kaname!
[SOUSUKE grunting]
In another ten seconds...
[GOURON]
Just five seconds.
It's sad, isn't it?
I love you, Kashim.
Kaname!
[GOURON grunting]
[SOUSUKE grunting]
[KURZ groaning]
[TELETHA, MARDUKAS groaning]
--[MARDUKAS] Mm.
--[TELETHA] Uh.
Confirm that we're airtight.
Closing the hatch
is our first priority.
Ms. Kaname,
what happened to Arbalest?
Did Mr. Sagara make it out okay?
[TELETHA gasps]
[panting]
[SOUSUKE grunting]
[ALL]
Uh!
[SOUSUKE]
Kashim? Kashim!
We're not friends!
You shit head!
[TELETHA]
Uh?
Did ya hear that, sister?
He said shit head!
Shit head? [laughs]
[KANAME] I'm sorry for all
the times I was inconsiderate.
I've come to realize I don't
know anything about you.
You're a great guy.
Honestly. I think
you're awesome, Sousuke.
[GOURON]
I love you, Kashim.
Start the dive.
Start the dive!
[SAILOR E]
Dive, dive, dive!
[KANAME]
53... 54... 55 knots.
Lock.
Depth: 500.
Enemies in pursuit:
None.
We made it.
I'll leave it to you, Dana.
[DANA A.I.]
Yes, Ms. Chidori.
[TELETHA]
Commander Richard Mardukas.
[MARDUKAS]
Yes, ma'am.
[TELETHA]
Lieutenant William Goddard.
Yes, ma'am.
Second Lieutenant Bob Riley.
Second Lieutenant Stuart Argyle.
Yes, ma'am.
[TELETHA]
Lieutenant Gale McAllen.
[MCALLEN]
Of course, ma'am. I'm honored.
[TELETHA gasps]
Lieutenant...
Lieutenant Gale McAllen
is out on patrol, ma'am.
Sergeant Major Melissa Mao.
Ma'am.
Sergeant Kurz Weber.
Right here.
Sergeant Sousuke Sagara.
Ma'am.
Leading seaman, Lian Shaopin.
He's out on patrol,
Madam Captain.
She's been there
for ten minutes.
Sousuke, why don't you go over?
Uh?
And try and cheer her up.
[TELETHA sobbing]
[SOUSUKE]
Kaname!
[KANAME]
Yeah?
Sousuke!
I wanted to know if you could
come with me, Kaname.
[KANAME]
Huh?
[KANAME] You're not
gonna do anything weird?
I won't do anything weird.
[KANAME]
It's not dangerous, is it?
[SOUSUKE]
No, it's not dangerous.
Well, here it is.
[KANAME]
Uh... Oh!
[KANAME laughs]
[KANAME]
What is this?
A fishing rod, of course.
Not that, silly. This place.
My secret fishing spot.
I'm the only one who knows it.
Fishing? But if I'm taking
the flight to Tokyo,
I can only spend 40 minutes
here before I have to go.
[SOUSUKE]
I don't mind.
This was the very first
target of this mission.
[KANAME]
Huh?
Originally, I was planning
on taking you here.
But somehow we ended up
taking all those detours.
[KANAME]
Take me here?
Affirmative.
You should fish.
You might even catch one.
Even in the time we have left.
I've never seen anybody
catch something that fast.
You never know.
When I'm with you, I feel I
can do just about anything.
Whether it's catching
a gigantic fish, or...
Or escaping from
some terrible danger.
[SOUSUKE] I know it's only
30 minutes, but will you stay?
[KANAME]
Is that what you really feel?
[SOUSUKE]
Of course.
I'm here now, because you
were always there for me.
All right. Tell you what,
why don't we test
your little theory,
and see if your
lucky streak holds out.
Uh! Help me, Sousuke! Uh!
It's huge!
You think it's a sea bream?!
You just might be right.
What about a whale?!
Well, I can't deny that
there's a possibility of that.
Listen, I wanna catch this thing
and bring it home, Sousuke.
[SOUSUKE]
Roger!