[DANA A.I.]
Welcome Captain Gauron.
Please give me your order.
[GAURON] Thank you, Dana,
don't mind if I do.
How about we start with
an evacuation drill?
Sound the alarm for a fire
at a reactor accident.
Gather everyone in the hangar.
[DANA A.I.]
Aye, sir.
[CAPTAIN SAILOR]
You hear an alarm?
[OFFICER] Yes. Bearing is 1-5-8,
just  under the thermal layer.
Lemme hear.
Huh?
[OFFICER] I can't detect
any propulsion signature,
but it's moving.
And it's going at a
pretty good clip, too.
No sound of the engine screw,
and a very high speed.
[TAKENAKA]
It's that Toy Box.
Huh? Oh, it's "Toy Box", is
it? How can you be so dam--
What?
Nevermind.
Anyway, this means it's finally
showing its true colors.
All right! We're gonna
ambush Toy Box.
Forward one-third power.
Surfacing to depth 180.
Aye, sir.
Forward one-third power.
Surface to depth 180.
[alarm blaring]
What d'ya think?
Not enough information to
make an assessment just yet.
You think it's Gauron?
[alarm continues]
I need to get some weapons.
[PERSONNEL 1] Did you hear
anything about a drill?
[PERSONNEL 2]
No. Any idea what's going on?
Don't you think... this is
just a little strange?
[GAURON] The front half of this
submarine houses the hangar
where they are: the torpedoes,
the missile launching system,
and the weapons
and ammunition room.
On the other hand, the rear
half has the engine room,
the reactor, living
quarters, the cafeteria,
and this central command center.
My little digital sweetheart,
Miss Dana, has locked all
the bulkheads in the
middle at my command.
Opening the bulkheads from
the hangar side is gonna be,
well, impossible.
Which means we won't be getting
any visits from a rescue party.
Good plan, huh?
I have to disagree.
All of the AS's are
stored in the hangar.
I'm sure they could
simply make a hole
with a monomolecular cutter.
Yes, that's why
I'm considering this.
[snaps]
Miss Dana.
[DANA A.I.]
Yes, Captain?
I want you to adjust
the air supply setting
in the front half...
Maximum oxygen concentration.
Wait, if you do that--
It just takes one
spark, and Boom.
Of course, you could imagine,
critical thinking
is not a priority
when you're high on oxygen.
The physics may escape them.
Call it off.
Don't give me orders.
Let's not forget who's
captain on this boat.
[laughs]
It's top brass
from the Pentagon;
some group I've never heard of.
I sure do wonder what they're
gonna be talking about.
[BUNKER HILL CAPTAIN]
Leave them alone.
We're just letting
them use our space.
And I have no desire
to get involved.
Captain, sir. We were able to
capture our nuclear submarine.
We've got it at a bearing
of 2-3-0, distance 500.
It's the Pasadena, sir.
Pasadena? Sailor's boat.
Can't stand that guy.
Leave him alone.
Is that all you're gonna say?
[BUNKER HILL CAPTAIN] That's the
trick to retiring in the Navy
without any trouble.
We'll reach the point
in 20 minutes, sir.
[CAPTAIN SAILOR]
Now we're gettin' somewhere!
Start the masker!
[TAKANAKA]
Aye, sir. Start masker!
[murmuring]
[sighs]
What's the matter?
Nothing. Just getting old.
No, you're not.
[SAILOR 1]
Y-You feel that?
[SAILOR 2] Yeah... my ears...
They're ringing...
[murmuring continues]
[gasps]
Commander!
The room's oxygen
content is shooting up!
I can't open the doors!
What could be wrong?
Contact the command center!
We can't!
All the communications on
the submarine are blacked out.
Oh, no...
[TELETHA] I need to do
something... But what?
[TELETHA]
Miss Kaname.
Please listen carefully to
what I'm going to tell you.
[KANAME]
Resonance...
[TELETHA] Dana recognizes
Gauron as Captain.
We can't cancel the registration
through the usual procedures.
Because of this, we must take
control of Dana directly.
[gasps]
[yawns]
[TELETHA]
It's a key to my safe.
In there, you'll
find another key.
[gasps]
[TELETHA]
The universal key.
[KANAME]
Universal key?
[TELETHA] After that, look in
the central computer room
on the third deck for Lady
Chapel, the heart of Dana.
[TELETHA]
Once you're in,
I want you to resonate
with me one more time.
Wait a minute, Lady Chapel,
what is that?
[TELETHA] I'm a terrible
athlete. You're the only one.
But it'll be...
Impossi-- [gasps]
[GAURON]
Hmm?
It bothers me... when people
shout for no reason.
Hmm?
So... What is it you're hiding
there behind your back?
Show and tell.
[KANAME]
Help me.
Miss Kaname, go!
Huh?
[yells]
[grunts]
[gasps]
Run for it!
[GUEN]
Huh?
Hold it!
Ah!
Stop right there!
[screams]
What the...?
You little shit! I'll kill you!
Did you hear that?
Gunshots, wasn't it?
[SOUSUKE]
It came from the command center.
[clicking]
[gasps]
Very well played, little miss.
[TELETHA]
Ah!
[KALININ] Here are all
the items to confirm.
By the way, what seas is
Toy Box currently patrolling?
I don't understand the
meaning of your question.
Don't insult my intelligence.
We know you have
in your possession
a submarine with
frightening potential.
I'm sorry, but my superiors
do not keep me informed
with details on these matters.
Oh well. But I'd like to
advise you, Lt. Commander...
...to remember who the
police of the world are.
There are some who'd say
the theory of globalism
is nothing more than
words on paper.
If your homeland
collapses, my friend,
that theory suddenly starts
to look much more realistic.
Shall we adjourn to
the bridge now?
These small rooms
make me uncomfortable.
I agree.
[gasps]
[GAURON] Miss Ex-Captain.
You've made me very angry.
But, I won't kill you just yet.
I've come up with an
alternate penalty.
Dana, bring this boat up
to periscope depth.
Speed is five knots. Use ESM and
look for ships on the surface.
[DANA A.I.]
Aye, sir.
W-Wait! What're you doing?
You'll find out soon.
Yes. Very soon.
What's wrong?
[gasps] Sir!
It would appear that
our nuclear submarine
is in hot pursuit of something,
but we can't contact it.
Something?
[OFFICER] Uh... We cannot
confirm the target.
You can't confirm it?
Hmph. Who is that
submarine's captain?
Commander Sailor.
Hmph.
Captain Ahab Sailor, huh?
Him and his interminable
quest for that target.
Show me the CIC data from
now on as is necessary.
Aye, sir.
Our nuclear submarine
seems to be catching
the tail of this Toy Box.
I hope that nothing
happens for your sake.
[KANAME panting]
Did I lose him?
This jacket was expensive, too.
[KANAME grunts]
[door creaks]
[DANA A.I.] Ship found
on surface, bearing 3-2-3.
Confirmed as Echo-1,
American Navy Aegis cruiser.
Estimated distance: Seven miles.
Good. Get ready to
launch harpoon missiles.
Numbers one and two.
The target is Echo-1.
Launch mode is BOL.
[DANA A.I.]
Aye, sir.
Stop it! They have
nothing to do with us!
[DANA A.I.] Echo-1 targeted.
Data input complete.
Opening launch tube doors.
No, don't do it, Dana!
[DANA A.I.]
Opening complete.
[whimpers]
Ah!
Number one and number two.
Please, stop!
Launch them.
Which one?
[gasps]
This is it...
[KANAME]
Huh...?
[gasps]
[KANAME]
What am I doing?
I have to go.
Lady Chapel...
But where...
where is that place.
[DANIGAN]
Looks like I found you.
[gasps]
[alarm sounds]
Captain! Heat sources
are closing in on us!
Two harpoon missiles.
They've locked onto our ship.
Bearing 1-3-2. Distance 8,000!
What the--?!
Evasive maneuvers!
Dispense chaff!
And take the helm to port!
We won't make it!
[MEN yelling]
[gasps]
Captain! We've just
confirmed a harpoon impact!
[gasps] What do ya mean?!
2-5-2, distance 2,000!
It's our cruiser, sir!
Somebody shot it!
Toy Box, you son of a bitch!
Go to a depth of 250!
Prepare the MK-48 torpedoes!
Three and four,
ready for launch!
[GAURON] Are you telling
me it didn't sink?
[DANA A.I.] Target is unable
to sail under its own power,
but appears to
still be floating.
So you kept the
warheads turned off?
Yes. That was my
decision as captain.
Don't you mean former captain?!
[BUNKER HILL CAPTAIN]
It didn't explode?
Report on our condition!
[DEPUTY OFFICER] Portside deck
and hangar have taken damage.
All helicopters on
board were destroyed.
We're currently working
on fire control.
The explosions were probably
ignited by the helicopters.
So what does this mean...?
Huh?
[JENKINS]
I need an explanation. Now.
If this... submarine you call
"Toy Box" really does exist...
[JENKINS groans]
[KALININ]
...it's hard to believe it
would attack the American
Navy for no reason at all.
Maybe. But we were attacked.
And yet, the missile
failed to explode.
I think it would be wise
to take this into account.
[JENKINS]
Why is that?
[KALININ]
If they had been serious,
this ship would have been
blown to pieces by now.
And they would have already
followed up on the last attack.
Isn't it a bit strange to you?
No, not really.
Captain, a severe
storm is brewing!
[BUNKER HILL CAPTAIN]
Ugh... Why now?
[KURZ]
Shit. Who did this?
[clanging]
[BOTH gasp]
In the cafeteria!
[GUEN whistles]
Sagara. You know,
your girlfriend's waiting for
you over in the cafeteria?
Too bad I'm not gonna
let you go see her.
[KANAME panting]
[DANIGAN]
What's wrong?
Aren't you gonna run away?
Dammit! Guen, you
son-of-a-bitch!
I don't think McAllen
would betray us.
But who could it be?
Is that new-comer Danigan
the one in the cafeteria?
[KURZ]
Sousuke!
Let me take care of
this stupid punk.
I'll create a diversion
so you can run through.
But I--
No arguments!
Kaname's in danger,
so you should go!
Give her a real apology.
Now!
[grunts]
What's the matter?!
Keep running!
Stay back!
[SOUSUKE]
Kaname!
[DANIGAN]
Huh?
Dammit!
Ah! Sousuke!
Kaname!
[grunts]
[groans]
Sagara!
[groaning]
Go to hell, Sagara!
[gunshots]
[thud]
[gasps] Kaname!
[SOUSUKE]
Are you okay?
Does it hurt anywhere?
[gasps]
All over...
I'm not... I won't
burden you, anymore.
I'll be all right on my own.
Even just now, I wasn't
scared or frightened at all!
Kaname... I'm sorry.
You're not a burden.
Did you forget? You helped
me countless times.
If I didn't have you,
I would be dead by now.
[SOUSUKE] I mean it. I'm here
because you've been here for me.
So please, don't tell me you'll
be all right on your own.
Okay, we'll stick
together for now.
[sniffs]
[gasps]
Sousuke, you've been injured!
I'm okay, it's not
a problem for me.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
[SOUSUKE]
Can you stand?
[mechanical howling]
[gasps]
Sounds like an attacker's sonar!
Huh?
[KANAME] I won't let him
do whatever he wants.
The nuclear reactor is my heart.
The two pairs of
hydroplanes are my wings.
Next Full Metal Panic,
Episode 23:
"Field of Giants."
Sousuke, the rest is up to you!