[TAKUMA pants erratically]
Takuma Kugayama,
right? Home stay?
No? I was traveling
as a student.
[CUSTOMS OFFICER]
Hm... On your own?
[TAKUMA]
Yes.
[TAKUMA pants erratically]
[TAKUMA]
Your tie is crooked.
[CUSTOMS OFFICER] Weren't your
parents worried about you?
[TAKUMA] Not really.
They trust me enough.
[TAKUMA]
It's none of your business.
Fix your damn tie!
[CUSTOMS OFFICER]
You're free to go.
Excuse me?
I said that you're
free to go now.
[TAKUMA]
Hurry up and fix your tie!
I can't take it anymore.
W-What did you say
about your tie?
Huh? What the heck are
you talkin' about, kid?
[TAKUMA] Y-You think
I'm gonna forgive you?
He's laughing at me.
Sister!
Hey, what's wrong? Are you okay?
[screams]
[COMPUTER]
Target's position confirmed.
Enemy fire power deployed
within 2.4 kilometers squared.
Nine armored motor cars
and three tanks.
Listen up. Urzu 7
and I will tackle
the amored vehicles located
in blocks B and C.
Urzu 6, keep an eye out
for grounds troops.
Don't start trouble.
[KURZ] Ah, come on. This is my
first battle after sick leave.
Don't ya think I
deserve a little treat?
[MELISSA]
Glad you still have an appetite,
but you're on a diet.
[grunts]
[MELISSA]
Everything clear, Urzu 7?
Urzu 7. The coast is clear.
[MELISSA]
Then cancel BCS.
[SOLDIER 1]
Take them down!
[SOLDIER 2]
Okay!
[MELISSA]
You can't escape! Surrender now!
[TELETHA]
It was a miss?
[MELISSA]
Yes, Captain. At this point,
there's no sign of the
terrorist group called A21.
[TELETHA]
I see...
I'm sorry that I made you
waste your time, Sgt. Major.
[MELISSA] Don't worry, ma'am.
It's not your fault.
Yes, well, please return
to base as planned.
I'll be waiting.
[MELISSA]
Roger.
These things happen.
[TELETHA] This is a problem
I can't put off like that.
This terrorist group
we know as A21.
They have a Soviet-made AS in
their possession, don't they?
[COMPUTER]
Line G1, Lt. Commander Kalinin.
Connect him.
[KALININ]
Good morning, Captain.
I received a report
stating that one of
A21's members was arrested
earlier today at Narita Airport.
Are you positive?
[KALININ]
Yes.
What's more, the boy
they arrested
seems to be exhibiting
the same reaction.
Which means...?
[KALININ] Well, Captain, it
means that it's possible the boy
has the capacity to operate
the Lambda Driver.
[KURZ]
Not a single Japanese person.
Another false lead, huh? Dammit.
[MELISSA] Well, it's not like
we can help it, now is it?
Let's just go wait
at the pickup point.
--[SOUSUKE] Uh-oh.
--[MELISSA, KURZ] Huh?
[KURZ]
What's wrong, Sousuke?
[SOUSUKE]
I completely forgot.
[KURZ]
Yeah? Forgot what?
Sousuke, don't tell
me you forgot
something important
like the radio codes?
[SOUSUKE]
No.
I forgot an appointment
to meet someone.
It was at 1900 hours yesterday.
She must be furious.
[MELISSA]
Appointment with whom?
Ha, ha.
I need help with my,
uh, Japanese history.
[UMPIRE] Strike three and
the batter is outta there.
Aw, yeah!
[sighs]
That was awesome.
Three strike outs in a row.
Yeah, it was a total
piece of cake.
But, ya know, flaunting your
softball skills in PE class?
Don't you think
it's a little much?
[laughs]
[KYOKO] Are you having any
trouble with Sousuke?
You said you were
gonna help Sousuke
with some of his
classwork, right?
So what, did he do
something wrong again?
No, no, no. He didn't
do anything.
How could he? I mean,
he didn't show up
for the appointment.
No, nothing. [forced laughter]
[GIRL 1]
Kaname, your turn!
I'm coming!
[KANAME]
Sousuke, you...
...total loser!
--[GIRLS cheers]
--[KYOKO] Home run!
[KANAME]
Hmph!
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[helicopter blades whirring]
--[boom]
--[GIRLS scream]
[KANAME]
What the heck?
S-Sousuke?
Good. I'm only slightly
tardy for second period.
It was worth flying
all the way back
from the South China Sea.
Why, you little--
Kaname.
Huh? Yeah, what?
Um, regarding our
appointment yesterday,
are you angry with me?
[growls] No! I'm not
angry at you.
Not in the least. I mean,
why should I be angry?
Well, that's good to hear.
I had some important
business to attend to,
and I completely
forgot about it.
[KANAME]
You forgot?
[GIRL 2]
Hm? Ah!
Kaname!
You idiot!
[groans]
[pants] Hm?
[GIRL 3]
Tag. You're out.
--[excited chatter]
--[GIRL 3] Wow! That looks good!
[GIRL 4]
Wow!
[GIRL 5]
Oo! Can I haved a rolled omelet?
[GIRL 6]
I get the cream croquette!
[laughs] Go ahead and dig in!
I cooked way too much
food last night.
Hey, Sousuke! Why don't
you come over?
Kaname whipped up an extra
special lunch just for you.
I did not!
Hmph... Ugh.
What do you want?
I don't like people
standing in front of me
while I'm eating.
Hm?
Sousuke?
[SOUSUKE]
Please accept this.
I had it specially made for you.
[GIRLS gasp]
You... You got this for me?
Those earring are pretty.
I bet that bracelet cost a lot.
Let me get a close up!
Oh, my. These are
really lovely and all,
but I'm not sure they suit me.
[SOUSUKE] It doesn't matter
if they suit you or not.
Practicality is
what's important.
--[GIRLS] Huh?
--[KANAME] Uh...
Practicality?
The stars are cleverly
concealed flash bangs
that you can wear on
your ears. And in a pinch,
you can throw them at your
enemies in self-defense.
Very effective,
since most enemies
won't take a second look
at a girl's earrings.
There may be occasions
in the future
where I'm unable to
keep an appointment.
In that case, use those
to protect yourself.
[KANAME]
Oh. How thoughtful of you.
Thank you... so... very... much!
[SOUSUKE]
Also, the bracelet is...
[STUDENTS scream]
I've been waiting
for you, Captain.
[TELETHA] What's the
security situation here?
[KALININ]
Two platoons. That is to say,
60 soldiers on guard 24/7.
This is a facility that
handles top secret research.
The general public isn't
aware of it's existence.
Of course, the boy's
transfer to this place
has been marked as classified.
[TELETHA]
What happened?
[KALININ] He jumped on
an officer in Narita
and nearly choked
a man to death.
He did?
[KALININ]
Yes.
Even after they
had him pinned down,
he was still extremely agitated.
They performed a drug test and
found "TI-971" in his blood.
And that's why they
had me called in, right?
Correct, the Japanese government
took him into custody,
and we had no other
choice but to ask you,
Madam Captain, to come in
and observe him.
You're the only one who
can judge whether he,
Takuma Kugayama,
has been reformed
to use the Lambda Driver.
And whether or not the so-called
treatment was a success.
He's shown symptoms of the
treatments side effects:
manifestations of sudden
violence, defects in memory.
[TELETHA] I went over the
numbers on the way here,
but I didn't see anything
to counter what you've said.
[gasps]
[screams]
[yelps]
[TAKUMA screams]
Are you all right,
Madam Captain?
Yes, I'm all right.
[DOCTOR]
Sedate him!
[sighs]
If we want to perform a
thorough test on the subject,
we would need to measure
his response levels
with a portable NILS.
However, he's probably
gone over the edge.
That's my hunch.
And mine.
If he has been tainted,
somewhere there's a weapon
equipped with a Lambda
Driver waiting just for him.
[KALININ]
Huh?
[gasps]
[screaming]
Oh my god.
Stay away from the
windows, Captain.
[MAN]
Quick! You! Get outta the way!
Their target is Takuma!
We need to get him out of here!
I have to disagree,
Madam Captain.
But why?
The problem is that we only have
enough men here to protect you.
There's an Arm Slave out there!
I don't believe it!
It's a Savage!
[screaming]
[gasps]
Captain, get down, now!
[KALININ groans]
[TERRORIST A]
Seina, where's Takuma?
He's not here.
That can't be right.
Seems he was taken away.
Have you kept up
with the transmitter?
Shit! He's not
anywhere in range.
It's gonna take a
while to find him.
You better find him. Right away.
We need Takuma to
be here with us.
He's the only one who
can pilot that devil.
Seina! We've got an
injured man over here.
If he's a guard, than kill him.
And what if he isn't?
[SEINA, TERRORIST A grunt]
[KALININ groans]
[TERRORIST A]
He doesn't look like
anyone who works here, either.
Well then, who is he?
Tell me, who are you, old man?
I'm your enemy.
How far are you
gonna follow me?
[SOUSUKE]
I'm not.
I assure you, my living
quarters are also
in this direction, Miss Chidori.
[KANAME]
I know that. I'm not stupid.
I apologized for breaking
the appointment.
And you did say that you
weren't angry about it anymore.
We should have a reconciliation
of our relationship,
for the sake of
your future safety.
Reconciliation?
What relationship?
You and I are just classmates
and that's all there is.
I have an obligation
to protect you.
[KANAME]
Obligation?
That's really important
to you, isn't it?
Of course, with a
military freak like you,
duty always comes first.
Hey, I'm not asking
you to change!
If you're gonna
blow yourself up,
just do me a favor and
take it somewhere else
so I don't have to watch you!
Kaname...
You know what else?
You make it really
easy to hate you!
[gasps]
[KANAME] God! Why can't he
apologize like a normal person?
Big idiot.
[KANAME] Though, I wonder
who the real idiot is.
You make it really
easy to hate you!
[gasps]
Sagara...
I'm so glad.
Madam Captain?
[TELETHA] If you were an enemy,
I think I'd be dead by now.
I'm not very good
with things like guns.
What's the situation,
and who's the boy?
We can't let him
out of our site.
He's part of... A21.
[screams]
[TAKUMA groans]
[sighs]
That was far too close.
I guess the tranquilizer
must have worn off.
[SOUSUKE]
Here.
Thank you, Sergeant.
[SOUSUKE] So, you borrowed a car
from the research facility
and made your escape.
That's right. I knew where
to find the spare key,
because Melissa told me.
But still, because I'm
so clusmy, Mr. Kalinin...
I'm not fit to be Captain.
Once I'm on the shore,
I'm practically useless.
No, you did what the
circumstances demanded of you.
And until there's confirmation,
you can't be sure he's dead.
In all probability, he's alive.
Really?
[SOUSUKE] When I met the Lt.
Commander for the first time,
we were enemies.
I've never had to fight
against a tougher man
in all my time as a soldier.
You were enemies?
So I can affirm,
it would be extremely
difficult to kill him.
[giggles]
What an odd way to comfort me.
Do you think so?
[TELETHA] The picture Melissa
painted fits you to a tee.
Huh?
Come to think of it,
we've never talked personally
like this before, have we?
Did you know?
I'm actually the same age
as you are, Sagara.
Yes, I'm well aware of
our common ages, Captain.
If we walked hand in hand,
people might think we're
boyfriend and girlfriend.
Huh?
Yes, ma'am, I'm quite
honored you think so.
Please, you can relax when
we're talking like this.
I don't know what to do
if you're acting all
stiff and military.
Roger. I'll do my best, ma'am.
Sousuke, I'm not
giving you an order.
Please think of it
as a friend's request.
Yes, if that's your order,
then I will.
Hey, would you mind it,
if I used your bathroom?
[gasps] I-I have to do my job.
Urzu 7 here with an
urgent communication.
So, is the prisoner hungry?
[TAKUMA]
No.
I guess you understand
the language then.
Well of course, I do,
Mr. Sousuke Sagara.
[doorbell chimes]
[door clicks]
Ah--!
Kaname, what are you...?
[KANAME] Um... About that
incident earlier today...
I can be a little...
you know, stubborn sometimes.
So, how do I say this...
I'm sorry.
[gasps]
No, I'm the one who's always
been causing trouble for you.
If you're sorry about it,
then where do I stand?
Would you... forgive me?
[SOUSUKE] There's nothing
that needs forgiving.
It was my fault.
Really? Thank you!
Uh, I still have some
leftovers from yesterday.
I-I brought them
with me. Are ya hungry?
If you let me
use your kitchen,
I'll heat them up for you.
Actually...
Oh, did you already eat?
[SOUSUKE]
No, I haven't, but...
Then, why don't we
just eat together.
You don't mind, do you?
No, I appreciate your kindness,
but you see, the thing is...
Huh?
I'm in a rather complicated
situation at the moment.
This is a problem that could
take some time explaining.
How can I put this...
I'm not exactly sure
you'd understand
the full extent of
what's going on.
What are you talking about?
[growls]
[TELETHA]
Mr. Sagara...
Do you have a spare T-shirt
or something I could...?
Oh!
[TELETHA] Being with
Mr. Sagara makes me happy
and kinda of giddy
at the same time.
Oh, my gosh! What am I saying
at a time like this?
Next Full Metal Panic:
Episode 10, "Run, Run, Run."
Am I a burden?
[SOUSUKE]
It's not a problem, Captain.