[RADIO A] Control of Berilabu
Island is almost complete.
We've got some
survivors still resisting,
but that should be
suppressed very soon.
[RADIO B] At last count,
we had 17 POWs.
All the hostages
detained inside the base
have been rescued.
[SOLDIERS chattering]
[RADIO C] Sergeant Major Melissa
Mao is severely wounded.
Repeat: Sergeant Major Mao
is severely wounded.
[KURZ] Well, this kinda
thing happens.
[SOUSUKE]
Kurz. Lian.
I'm sure she'll be okay.
C'mon Sousuke. I'm sure you know
how tough our Melissa is, right?
[gasps]
Don't worry, son.
You gave you best out there.
Lieutenant, but I...
[GAURON]
Yo, Ivan. Long time no see.
What are you planning, Gauron?
'Fraid I don't know what
you're talking about.
Do not expect my forgiveness,
or any kind of deal from me.
I will wipe you from this Earth
once I have your confession.
Remember that.
Oh, How scary.
Take this thing away.
[MCALLEN]
Sir!
[KALININ]
Take off in five minutes.
I need to negotiate
with the US military.
[MCALLEN]
Yes, sir.
[GAURON]
Hmph.
[KALININ] I know he wouldn't
do something like this
for no reason at all.
He seems dissolute
and given up to hedonism,
but he's a professional.
He continually secures his
safety through careful planning.
There's something
suspicious about all this.
[MCALLEN] Don't you think
it smacks of a diversion?
While he has our
attention focused on him,
the main contingent
attacks somewhere else.
[KALININ]
It's possible.
I already said as much
to headquarters though.
[KALININ] Ask Captain Testarossa
for her orders regarding Venom.
I leave his personal
treatment to you.
Keep him isolated until
the medical check is complete.
Once you know
he has no problems,
you may ignore any
new health issues.
[MCALLEN]
Even if he gets seriously ill?
Yes, even if you know without a
doubt that he isn't pretending.
You must think of him as a
highly intelligent savage beast.
I understand, sir.
[HELMSMAN] Transport Helicopter
Number Two, completed landing.
[PILOT]
Hurry and admit the injured.
We're heading back to
Barildabu as soon as we tank up.
[DOCTOR]
Move it! The next one's coming.
Melissa!
Miss Mao...
She'll be fine. Girl's just
got a little concussion
and a ribcage fracture.
You're sure?
Is she gonna make it?
I don't think Death's
gonna be knocking down
any doors to get close
to that spitfire.
[sighs]
Huh?
Hey, Sousuke.
Hey... Why aren't you
back with your people?
[SOUSUKE]
I made a mistake.
I'm too ashamed to see them.
What happened? Did anybody die?
No...
Then it's okay, right?
Miss Mao doesn't look all
that bad and the doctor said--
You have no idea!
What? I-I'm sorry...
I'm not trying to be rude.
One more mistake
and I could have
easily gotten her killed.
Me and that stupid AS.
Huh?
I-I couldn't... I couldn't
start the Lambda Driver.
Now, this enhancing
mentality and images,
I don't get it!
Something that unstable
is not a weapon!
It's a spell!
Whoever came up with it
is the worst engineer!
Why don't you take a rest?
You must be totally exhausted.
First, Helmajistan. Now, this.
Didn't you have a
tough time over there?
Look, Kurz told me about it.
He was worried about you, too.
I'm not tired, so don't worry.
You're not even acting
like yourself though.
What do you know about me?!
[gasps]
How can you sit there and
say I'm not being myself?
I'm a mercenary.
I should've been
doing regular work
and using standard
issue equipment.
But ever since
the airline hijacking,
I've run into
nothing but bad luck.
Gauron, that AS,
Helmajistan, guarding you...
One problem after another.
Now, look here!
I didn't ask to have
someone guarding me 24/7!
So if it's too much trouble,
then you shuld just
quit and forget it!
I can't quit!
I'm the only one
who's fit for this duty!
I'm your "duty?" What the
hell does that mean?
[SOUSUKE] I think you're
the one who's tired.
I'm not tired.
I've been worried to
death about you, Sousuke!
Can't you see?
Fine, I get it, okay?
I get the point.
Why don't you go back
to your room now?
Did you see her?
Yeah, I saw her.
[KURZ]
Sousuke?
[grunts]
Kurz, c'mon. Stop it!
Let go!
What the hell was that for?
I overheard you, so
I thought I'd drop in
and help your head stop
swelling from this idea
you've got about being
a hero. That's what.
I think I'm a hero?
[KURZ] Just because you can't
be perfect 100% of the time,
you get all sulky and
take it out on a woman!
You know, it's people like you
who become violent
husbands and cause trouble
for everyone around!
Do you hear me?!
That's it. Kurz has
gone off the deep end.
I did not take it out on her.
[KURZ]
Then what do you call it?
Why did you make
her cry, asshole?
Think real hard about
what you said to her.
I made her cry?
Hmph! I understand
it bothers you,
but it does happen.
Of course, you know that,
being such a pro.
You think you're fighting
on your own here?!
Don't flatter yourself.
[TELETHA]
It's not broken? Venom?
Right. The armor and the
ECS lens on the shoulder
have received some damage,
but there's nothing else.
There's no danger of it
starting by itself either.
It has a self-destruct system,
but that won't start till
someone physically touches it.
Captain?
Oh!
Yes, thank you very much
for your hard work.
We'll analyze Venom
back at the base.
Understood, Captain.
Mr. Mardukas.
Yes, Madam Captain?
There's something I need
to talk to you about.
That toybox may
be passing within
a 100 kilometers of you and
your crew in the next 12 hours.
Once you find it,
collect as much vital
data on it as you can.
How do they expect us
to find this thing?!
[growls] Dammit!
Considering that
we failed so far, sir,
do you think
maybe headquarters
isn't really expecting
that much from us?
Hmm...
[CAPTAIN SAILOR]
When I was a kid, I was captain
of a boy's baseball team
called the Oklahoma Sailors.
[TAKENAKA]
Huh?
One of our teammates was
this hopeless half-pint
we all called Nobby.
I put him in right
field, eigth at bat,
gave him the cold shoulder,
and when he made an error,
I made him pull his pants
down in front of Kathy.
Who's Kathy?
Ever since I got this
situation dumped on me,
I think I'm starting to see
how Nobby must have felt
sitting in right field.
Well, that was a sure long
and pointless anecdote.
Damn you! Are you making fun
of the fondest memories
of my childhood?!
Are you?!
[KANAME sighs]
[HIROSHI]
Hey, Miss Kaname!
I don't mind if you stay there,
but do you want
something to eat?
We've got plenty.
No, thank you.
If you're tired,
then maybe you should go
back to the captain's room.
I don't wanna go there.
Aw, come on.
Why don't you take a shower
and have a nice long nap?
You'll feel a lot better
when you wake up.
Am I bugging you?
Of course not!
What gave you that idea?
Mmm...
What? Leaving already?
[inaudible]
[KANAME pants]
Ah!
[panting]
[yawns]
Don't let your guard down.
But just look at him,
he's stayin' put.
Not even Houdini could
escape a getup like that.
It's impossible.
Our duty is to be on guard
against all possible dangers.
What kinda danger are we in?
[gasps]
Oh, all kinds,
like this for example.
Uh... Eh...
[muffled gunshot]
[metal clinks]
[thud]
[muffled gunshot]
Aw, man. I almost thought
you were gonna leave
me hanging there.
The thought had crossed my mind,
but the previous mission
made my decision for me.
It's no good here.
The people at
Mithril are useless.
In any case,
thank you, Mr. uh...
It's Danigan. John Danigan.
Nice to meet you, John.
Don't call me John.
I only let a few people
call me by that name.
You got that?
[GAURON]
Uh-huh...
And you're gonna tell me
what I can and cannot do?
I see you're catching on.
Hmm...
[grunts]
[DANIGAN groans]
[gasps]
Oh, my, my, dropped our
guard, didn't we, John?
Damn you.
"Don't use my first name?"
"You'll do as I tell you?"
I'm sorry, but it isn't
gonna work that way, John!
Hmm?
All right, I understand.
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry, dammit!
But are you really sorry?
Yeah, I'm really sorry
and I won't cross you again!
Hmph.
Commnad Center is down there.
Captain should be too.
All right then.
[MCALLEN]
Where are you goin'?
Well this is an
unpleasant surprise.
Kalinin told us
that this scumbag
had probably recruited
a traitor or two.
But I never thought
they'd be SRT personnel.
Lieutenant, what's goin' on?
Get Weber and the others
over here. Come on, move it!
Dammit, what's the matter, Guen?
Hurry the hell up!
[muffled gunshot]
Well, I suppose
that would make you
helper number two, right?
[GUEN]
That's right.
I'm Guen Bien Bo.
Tell me, do I get a
bonus for clean up?
[gasps]
Hmm...
[KANAME]
Ah!
[grunts]
Please let me go!
You can scream for help if
you like, missy, but then we
just might... resort to
torture. After which the boys
may find your body a
little less than appealing.
She looks like trouble.
Let's kill her.
[GAURON]
No, this one's special.
We're not supposed to
kill her... preferrably.
It's been a while, Miss Kaname.
Tell me, how is
everyone at school?
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Don't do it! Stay where you are!
We have no chance fighting
against SRT personnel.
This is an order.
Well done, Miss Captain.
I see you're a person
who can appreciate
the difference in power.
Did ya hear that? Everybody?
Better not try anything funny!
Unless you'd like to see
the adorable Miss Captain
treated in a manner unsuitable
for underage viewers.
Can I get a roger?
Miss Kaname, you're
not hurt, are you?
I'm not, but they...
One soldier...
[GAURON] Well, let's get
right to the point, shall we?
I would like to change
the ships course
to 330 degrees north, Captain.
[TELETHA]
Not a chance in hell.
Hmm?
How 'bout now?
No! Stop it!
Don't listen to him, Captain.
I'm not gonna blame you
and neither will anybody else,
so don't do anything he--
Good. Then you can
shut up and die now.
[TELETHA]
Wait.
Hmm?
Port to helm:
Course 3-3-0.
But, Captain...
Changing our course
is not a problem.
Did you hear what I said?
Course 3-3-0, now!
Port to helm:
Course 3-3-0.
That was for my own
personal amusement.
I had something ready in case
you didn't do what I told you.
Namely this.
[gasp] Where did you get that?!
You see... Those two soldiers
aren't the only ones
who joined my party, miss.
I can find someone who
needs money anywhere,
even in your headquarters'
engineering department.
Headquarters?
Naturally, it was somewhat
difficult to find these people.
Mithril must be an organization
of the highest
moral caliber, huh?
[SOLDIERS whispering]
[DANA]
Welcome, Captain Gauron.
Please give me your order.
Thanks, Dana.
Don't mind if I do.
It can't be. There's no way.
How about we start
with an evacuation drill?
[DANA]
Drill commencing.
[alarms blaring]
[DANA] Number two engine
room is on fire.
All crew, please evacuate
to the main hanger
at the front of the submarine.
This is a drill.
[SOLDIERS]
I was taking a nap.
Where's the fire?
[SOLDIERS]
Oh, no. C'mon! C'mon!
Captain's bustin'
our balls again.
[alarms blaring]
[OFFICER]
No! The door is closing!
Miss Chidori may
still be back there
and she's a civillian.
Now please let me
go and find her.
I can't let you do that.
All the people beyond this
point are supposed to be dead.
[SOUSUKE]
Yes, but--
No, buts! That's an order!
[sighs] I understand, sir.
[OFFICER]
Hey you!
[grunts]
[gasps]
Are ya sure you wanna be here?
cause you just
ignored an order.
Okay, so what are
you doing here then?
The long and short of it is:
I'm not real fond
of group activities.
I thought somebody else
might ditch the drill,
but I never figured it would
be you, Sergeant Somber.
My gut tells me that something
bad is happening here.
Mine, too. Shall we
check it out?
Affirmative.
[DANA]
Main bulkhead closure complete.
The front of the submarine
has now been sealed
off from the rear.
Never give up.
[TELETHA] We're in the
worst possible situation.
Gauron has taken
over the submarine.
The crews' lives are
ready to flicker out
like a candle in the wind.
Next Full Metal Panic,
Episode 22:
"Jack-in-the-Box."
Miss Kaname, you're
our last resort!
Please hurry!