Then imagine this: if you lose,
the bad guys are gonna
rip off all my clothes,
play around with my body,
and kill me when they're done.
Imagine this happening to me!
[gunshot]
[KANAME]
You hate it, right?
[SOUSUKE]
Right.
[KANAME]
Does it make you mad?
[SOUSUKE]
I guess so.
[KANAME] He's trying to
do these things to me.
You can't let him
do that, can you?
[SOUSUKE]
No, I can't.
[GIRLS laughing]
[KYOKO]
Here you go!
[KURZ] S'cuse me, miss.
Are you here alone?
Yes, I am, unfortunately.
Then how 'bout you and me
go watch the sea lice
down by the concrete ba--
Oh, I'm sorry it couldn't
be Sousuke this time,
but he's out on a business trip.
Whatever.
It's not like I care about him.
--Bingo!
--[KURZ groans]
[door clicks]
[SOUSUKE]
Reporting for duty.
Mr. Sagara. Thank you
so much for coming.
This gentleman is
from intelligence.
Sergeant Sagara.
Look behind you.
The Intelligence Department
took these photos
of Helmajistani
weapons merchants
the day before yesterday.
[INTELLIGENCE OFFICER]
What do ya think?
See any familiar faces?
[gasps]
It would seem that you have some
incredibly lucky
friends, Sergeant.
[INTELLIGENCE OFFICER]
I'll make this breif.
Soon, one of our units
in the Indian Ocean
will be carrying out an
assassination mission
on this man.
[gasps]
Futhermore, we have decided that
you will be joining this
unit in the mission.
There are three
reasons for this.
Number one: you have
already engaged
this target on the battlefield.
Number two: we believe it is
necessary to utilize Arbalest
in order to successfully
eliminate the target.
Number three: you know the area
around Helmajistan very well.
Your participation in
this mission is mandatory.
No objections allowed.
So, Captain Testarossa,
we're borrowing your sergeant.
[KALININ]
I see. So he survived as well.
[TELETHA]
I'm truly sorry, Mr. Sagara.
I know that this isn't the
Tuahar de Danaan's mission.
I objected to the idea but...
[SOUSUKE] No, ma'am. I would do
this even if I had to volunteer.
Well then, I guess you'll
be on your way to Helmajistan.
[SOUSUKE]
Yes.
Don't get too hot
under the collar.
Please, Captain, you don't
need to be worried.
Helmajistan is Sergeant
Sagara's home ground.
But I... I can't
shake this feeling.
I'm afraid something
terrible may happen.
[JACKSON] I shit you not.
Last fight I saw,
that damn Herculus was knocked
out cold in 30 seconds.
It was obviously a fixed game.
I was so freakin' pissed,
I punched a bookie.
Strangely enough,
my 100 dollars
turned into 1,000.
Must've been my luck day.
But you know what they say,
Brooklyn's a better
investment than Wall Street.
[BATIST] Maybe, but the
problem with riding bubbles
like that is they tend to burst.
[GRAY] Please, Jackson.
We all know you like to chat,
but try to think
about your duty.
Huh? Exactly what do you
want me to think about?
I say we're lucky to have
such an easy mission.
It don't sit too well with me.
How come so many
of us have to come
all this way to
Helmajistan of all places?
Just so we can say we
knocked off one terrorist?
Because he's an
extremely dangerous enemy.
I've heard he uses some kind of
special experimental weapon.
Isn't that right, Bill?
[BILL]
That's what I heard.
They don't trust us.
[ALL]
Huh?
Hey. Who the hell let a
hitchhiker on board the plane?
Oh, yes. Sgt. Sagara is joining
our mission from de Danaan.
That's you, right?
He's a sergeant?
You're kiddin' me.
Come on now.
If it worked for
the Seattle Mariners,
then who the hell
are we to judge?
Ha! Never thought they'd start
givin' rank to little kids.
[JACKSON]
Hey, kid.
So tell me, you
like chocolate, huh?
You want some candy?
Cut it out!
Give it a rest, Jackson.
I'm just kiddin' man. Chill out.
We got a long flight ahead,
so let's you and
me be pals, okay?
How 'bout it, Tom Sawyer?
I'm sorry that our friend
was acting so rude.
It doesn't matter.
I'm Grace Weisman. Our
group's second in command.
But everyone here calls me Gray.
Sergeant Sousuke Sagara, ma'am.
I heard that you know
Helmajistan inside and out.
We'll be counting
on your expertise.
Now listen up, you little shit.
This is our mission.
We have no intention of
asking you for your advice.
You remember that.
Man, couldn't the transport
have dropped us off
a little closer to the enemy?
Because they often have
sandstorms around here,
we can't make very
good use of the ETS.
It's a very sensitive system.
Ah, it's a useless system,
Camoflauge clothes would
probably be better.
So we get to walk, eh?
You guys sure make it a real
picnic for us old farts.
[TROOPS laugh]
[BILL]
Hold up!
[gasps]
What, Bill?
[BILL] They must've started
moving quicker than we expected.
[GRAY]
Is that it?
Are you able to get a
visual on the target?
I count one, two...
Let's see, six savages total.
And what?
And one AS I've never
seen up at the front.
No, they got one more.
Look at the trailer
towards the rear.
[gasps]
[BILL]
Listen up!
The enemy should be reaching
this valley in four hours.
It should take their
unit a substancial
amount of time to go
accross the whole valley.
The area between points
zero four and zero seven
provide sutible terrain to
launch a surprise attack.
While they're going
through this area,
we'll separate into two groups
and attack from both sides.
The plan seems simple enough.
Heh. Let's not
forget our mission
is to kill that
damn scarface guy.
There ain't no point in
playing cheap tricks here.
That's true.
We don't have any instructions
regarding what to do
with the shipment, now do we?
Well, that just means the
higher ups wouldn't give
a flying rats ass, even if we
took it and sold it on eBay.
Don't overstep your authority.
I was just kiddin' man.
You need to chill out.
[SOUSUKE]
I have an objection.
Are you talking
to us, samurai boy?
In order to kill Gauron,
our only choice is to attack him
when he's a good distance
away from his AS.
Once he gets into that machine,
we'd have no chance,
even with an ambush
from all of your M9s.
Do you wanna die, little boy?
Kid, I told you.
We're not lookin' for
your advice, so shut your yap!
Hold it. He has experience
fighting with the man
we're trying to kill.
Don't you think we should
at least listen to him?
Ha! A toddler who got lucky
and scored a hit on
a sumo wrestler?
Think he'll share some
of his tips on defense?
Stop it! He fought that
man on equal terms.
[BATIST]
And did ya see him do it?
I read it on the report
from the de Danaan.
[JACKSON] You really gonna
count on a report from them?
[ANDY] If ya ask me, they're
just a bunch of spoiled brats.
Always gettin' the newest toys.
[JACKSON] Aw, how sweet.
Gray's fallen for the kid.
[GRAY]
Shut your mouth!
--[blow lands]
--[JACKSON groans]
[BILL]
I've said all I need to say.
[gasps]
[BILL] The target will be
reaching point zero four soon.
Everyone get ready.
[JACKSON]
Ugh. Dammit with my luck,
you'd probably squash them.
Well, when we finish this,
I'll give you the name
and number of a good vet.
[JACKSON] Oh, yeah? If they're
squashed, I'm taking yours.
You break it, you buy.
[GRAY]
Hey, Bill.
Yeah, what?
I'm thinking about Sagara.
Don't you feel like we
should take his opinion
on this matter a bit
more seriously?
Any reason I should?
If it's anything close
to what was written
on the de Danaan's field report,
we may not be equipped
to deal with it.
[BILL]
Why so timid all of a sudden?
Well, I heard a rumor.
They say the last battle he
fought got so destructive,
he nearly wiped out
an entire city.
I wouldn't be surprised
if he succeeded this time.
[ANDY]
Target has passed the A-line.
Point zero four one.
Distance: 2,000.
Okay, the lead man will pass
the B-line in 90 seconds.
Wait till they reach
pont zero four five.
Once they come within range,
we all attack at once.
--[ANDY] Got it.
--Roger.
I'm ready anytime.
Heh, heh! Let's kick this
sucker off with a bang!
[gasps]
[SOUSUKE]
Something's not right.
What is it?
Do you see something?
I still haven't located Gauron.
Does any other position have
a confirmed visual on him?
No, I don't see him at all.
Bill, you?
That's negative.
I don't see anything.
You, Batist?
[BATIST]
Me neither. Negative.
[BILL]
Andy? Jackson?
Negative here. But he's
gotta be there somewhere.
I mean, there's no way
he'd leave the caravan.
No shit, Sherlock.
So if we poke around,
he'll come out with his
hands up and his pants down.
[SOUSUKE]
No, there's no guarantee
that he's not in the AS.
If we can't confirm where he is,
we'd be better off
to cancel the attack.
Now you listen--
[GRAY]
Jackson!
Well, I don't see the AS moving.
Ugh. Who cares if the son
of a bitch is in it or not?
[JACKSON] It doesn't matter,
Bill. Let's do this thing.
You'll do it when I say so.
Once I give you all the sign--
[SOUSUKE]
Don't!
That AS is dangerous.
Listen to me.
[ANDY] Do you ever shut
your freakin' mouth?
[BATIST] Bill, they're in range.
Distance is 750.045.
[JACKSON] Come on. Are you gonna
give us the sign, or what?
[ANDY]
What's goin' on, Bill?
The plans haven't been changed.
Move!
[SOUSUKE] Wait. He nearly
killed me and my comrade.
If you make even the
slightest mistake,
we'll all end up dead.
Hey, Bill. Why don't we
shoot this loser first?
You hear what you're saying?
What are we doing, Chief?
Those bastards are gonna
waltz right through!
[SOUSUKE] First lieutenant,
sir, stop the attack!
Are you trying to
kill all your men?
[yells] Go to hell!
[gasps]
[KANAME]
Bang.
Let's go!
Idiots!
Batist, you stop their
forward movement!
Jackson, make a feint!
Andy, you too!
Gray and I will find the target!
Where is the target?
I can't find him!
I can't either!
--[BILL] Batist?
--[BATIST] Negative.
[JACKSON] Shit! Where's
that bastard hidin'?
[GRAY]
Jackson!
I'm tired of these small fries.
Show me the final boss!
Sorry, pal. The road's closed
to traffic beyond this point.
Huh?!
Hmph!
Whoa!
Heh...!
So where's our man?
[BATIST groans]
Batist! What happened?
[JACKSON, ANDY]
Batist!
Hang in there! I'll be
there in just a minute!
Oh, no!
[grunts]
Hi. Mind if I join
your little party?
[gasps]
No! Not good!
[JACKSON]
Batist?! Damn you!
You... You be careful...
That guy is bad news.
Don't try to speak.
I'm on my way.
[gasps]
Thanks for the exercise.
My shoulders have been
rather stiff lately.
What happened? I know
I hit him dead on.
Oh, no. It's the Lambda Driver.
Shall we?
[BILL]
Let's.
[gasps]
Let's get 'im, Jackson!
Hell yeah! Four-to-one;
it'll be a piece of cake!
[GRAY]
Hold it! Look at this!
[ANDY]
Gray, what is it?
[GRAY]
The shipment on the trailer.
[ANDY gasps] They've got a...
a nuclear warhead!
Smuggling?
Holy shit!
[GAURON] Hey, what's wrong? Out
of ideas yet, Captain Clueless?
[BILL growls]
Go to hell!
[gasps]
You son of a bitch!
[screams]
Andy! Jackson!
Heh.
[SOUSUKE]
Stay back!
So, it's you, Kashim.
[gasps]
[SOUSUKE]
Can I use it?
So, can you use it?
[SOUSUKE]
Yes, I will use it!
[gasps]
Damn you, Kashim!
You bastard!
[GAURON]
They stole the merchandise!
Connect me to
Helmajistani military HQ!
Move it, you worthless
sack of shit!
Ow! Dammit, you idiot!
Kashim...
[GAURON]
Don't let them go!
[groaning]
Hang in there! Come on, Batist!
Double time, people!
We have to take this as far
away as we possibly can!
Dammit... Bill was... He was...
You bastard!
[ambulance siren blaring]
[SOUSUKE]
The weapons of a powerful foe.
The death of our commander.
While the enemies close in
on us, we make a pilgramage
in the hopeless wilderness.
Next Full Metal Panic,
Episode 16:
The Wind Blows at Home, Part 2.
I know, this land is my home.