[TELETHA] He's having a
tough time out there, isn't he?
[KALININ] I believed it would
give him some good experience.
[TELETHA]
Good experience?
Even though he returned to the
safe house chained to a chair
with his firearms confiscated
and after being
physically assaulted
by the mission objective
and several other civilians?
Still within the allowable
range, Madam Captain.
I guess it'll be fine.
Sgt. Major Mao and Sgt.
Weber will be there to help him.
[TELETHA]
But, tell me Lt. Commander...
How long were we planning
to leave them in Tokyo?
[KALININ] As long as it takes
to eliminate the threat.
Now that the weight of the
mission has shifted to us,
would I be correct
in assuming that
if we make our
secondary objective,
we won't need to post a
guard for Miss Chidori?
[KALININ] Yes. Not only Chidori,
but all the other
Whispered candidates
will be safe as well.
They'll all be safe
for a while, anyway...
[KALININ]
Yes. For a while...
[KANAME growls]
So, what got him to
come running this time?
Like I'd ever know.
I was carrying this
plaster sculpture for art,
and he just runs into
me shouting something
I can't make out.
Can you blame me for not
knowing what he's thinking?
There, there.
It was an accident. I slipped.
[KANAME groans]
[KANAME]
Right. You just bumped into me.
The sprinting and shouting
had nothing to do with it.
Look, do me a favor
and shut up, okay?
[KYOKO giggles]
[KURZ] What's the matter?
You do something bad?
I thought I saw a terrorist
attacking Miss Chidori
in the hallway,
but it turned out to be a
plaster sculpture she had made
for art class.
She should be coming outside
the school gate any minute now,
but I have to stay after
and report to the teacher.
Cover for me, will ya?
Hey, I'm on it, but don't waste
your time worrying about it.
[SOUSUKE]
I'll try.
[KURZ chuckles]
[MELISSA] Sounds like you're
having a tough time adjusting.
Trust me, you're not
the only one
still getting used to changes.
Huh...?
980 yen?!
Ugh, these Tokyo prices
are deadly! What is the deal?!
It's just crab! We're on an
island! Canned freakin' crab?!
You hear me, Kurz?!
[SOUSUKE gasps]
[CHIDORI]
Yeah, no kidding.
[SOUSUKE growls]
--[giggling]
--Boo!
[BOTH scream]
Oh my god, Maya! You shouldn't
scare people like that!
[MAYA giggles]
So I scared ya, huh?
Come on, let's try to
keep the halls quiet.
Oh, sorry.
[ALL]
Huh?
[SOUSUKE growls]
[ALL scream]
[TEACHER grunts]
[TEACHER screams]
[KANAME sighs]
I have never ever had
a new transfer student
cause so many problems!
I'm very sorry, ma'am.
[TEACHER]
And another thing!
You cannot bring toys
like these to school!
I told you yesterday!
Perhaps you've forgotten?!
[TEACHER growls]
No, that gun is not a toy.
[TEACHER]
Oh, enough already!
[KANAME] So what's with
this hobby of yours?
Do you just like taking pictures
of weird or funny stuff?
Uhh... I guess so.
[KANAME] Okay... So why take
pictures of that bozo?
[KYOKO]
Hmm... I dunno.
As goofy as he is, watching
him and the way he acts
sorta brightens my day.
It's like a breath of fresh air.
Huh...?
It seems our angel has finally
decided to go to sleep.
Watch what you're doing!
[KURZ] I could say the same
to you! Two days, man.
You'll be dead by the time
you finish the mission.
Lemme see your back, man.
[KURZ] Y'know, you haven't
run into an enemy yet.
And in two days,
you've fallen down
the stairs, broke a window,
knocked over a bookcase
in the library,
and generally taken masochism
to a whole new level.
I'm trying to do my best.
Sousuke's point man because he
can do all those crazy stunts.
Of course, you should
know that by now.
So laugh all you want,
but it won't be too funny
if the terrorists attack
and he's not running
on all cylinders.
[SOUSUKE sighs]
[KURZ]
We're probably wasting our time.
I doubt she's
even a real target.
[SOUSUKE] Blind assumptions
lead to trouble, you know?
And rabid obsession
leads to stitches.
But... you're a tough guy!
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[KURZ] Kaname seems like your
everyday ordinary girl.
I mean, sure, she's
pretty and everything,
but her background's
fairly normal.
At least, if you compare
it with our backgrounds.
[MELISSA] Yeah, teenage
mercenaries aren't exactly
what you'd call normal.
[KURZ] You have to wonder
what good it's doing the KGB
to try and kidnap a regular
high school student.
[MAN]
Ooh, chilly isn't it?
[KGB OFFICER]
What did you say?
[MAN] Ha, thank you, chief.
It's good to know the KGB
employs men of understanding.
[MAN]
That's Mithril's AS.
Though I'm afraid none
of your current models
can match it in battle.
[KGB CHIEF]
Mithril?
[MAN] A secret mercenary
agency that destroys
illegal drug refineries
and terrorist camps.
In their spare time, they defend
nuclear weapons exports.
Their equipment is
roughly ten years ahead
of the Americans
and the Soviets.
Their top brass also
has a penchant
for sorting out
regional conflicts.
You know, like champions of
justice or something like that.
[KGB CHIEF] So, this Mithril
is the one disrupting my plans?
[MAN] My guess is they felt
they couldn't leave you alone.
Once a breakthrough is
made in these studies,
the power balance
of the entire world
will be turned on its head.
Bodies are much more difficult
to come by these days.
[KGB CHIEF]
And you want an increase in pay.
[MAN] I'm not a communist.
I'm just a simple businessman.
[KGB OFFICER]
We've heard enough from you!
There are plenty of
agents in this country
who can take your place!
Maybe you should be thankful
that the chief hired
you at all, Chinaman!
I'm afraid that I'm not
actually of Chinese descent.
[KGB OFFICER]
Who gives a damn?!
We'll send you to
coal mines in the Urals
and turn your face black!
[KGB OFFICER gasps]
[gunshots, grunting]
Now that that's out of the way,
let's get on to business.
I believe we were talking
about securing bodies
for experiments
on the Whispered.
I'm thinking of
kidnapping this girl.
What d'you think?
[MAN]
Mm... Quite pretty, isn't she?
[KANAME] And that is why we
need to decide very soon
who is gonna be in charge of
what during the school trip!
[CLASS murmuring]
[KANAME growls]
[KANAME]
Hey, is anybody listening?!
[MALE STUDENT A]
Well, of course we are.
Let's hurry and get it over
with so we can go home!
I can't believe I
actually wanted to become
a stupid class representative...
You hang in there, Kaname!
Thank you, Kyoko!
And since I figured the class
meeting would dissolve
into this anyway...
A-ha!
I came totally prepared!
[CLASS gasps]
Oh yeah!
I remember seeing you run around
with a memo during recess!
Mm-hm!
Good job, Kaname!
A model student!
Mm-hm!
Everyone, just leave it to me!
[CLASS cheers]
Don't you think she's
overdoing it a bit?
Yeah, if she keeps this up,
she's gonna be sick
when it comes time for the trip.
Hey, I can hear you!
Sorry my best friend
is acting so weird...
If she weren't so fanatical,
she might have a shot
at being Miss Jindai High...
'Kay, please listen
when I call your name.
[GIRLS]
She's on a power trip!
[KANAME] Takada and Tanabe
will be in charge of meals.
Got it.
Right!
[KANAME] Kaneda and Uchida,
you've got luggage.
Me?
[UCHIDA]
I'm on luggage?
[KANAME] In charge of
communication, Moori and Mukai.
[MOORI]
Okay!
Yeah, cool, I hear ya.
[KANAME] Sakamoto and Kudo
are in charge of events.
Aye, Captain.
Okay!
[KANAME] And nobody
wanted garbage duty...
So, the only person left is...
Sousuke Sagara.
[CLASS]
Huh?
Is something
the matter, Sousuke?
How come I get that job?
Well, our
long-standing tradition
at this school has been
that the newcomer
handles all garbage duty.
If that's the case,
then I accept it.
Good...
All right, are there
any objections?
[CLASS]
No, ma'am!
[KANAME]
Dismissed!
[CLASS murmuring]
[KYOKO]
Good job, Kaname!
Yes, I suppose.
[KYOKO]
Mm-hm. Well played.
[CLASS murmuring]
[MAYUKO] That was so funny!
Did you see Sousuke's face?!
[MAYA] He totally believed
that stuff you made up
about the new guy
being trash-bitch.
All the same, I still feel
a little sorry for the guy.
Yeah, it was a bit of a shock
coming from Miss Perfect here.
I dunno what the big problem is!
I mean, Sousuke accepted
the job, didn't he?
Would you mind telling me
what you're doing?
Hang on... There's a grease
stain from your thighs
that looks like Godzilla...
[SOUSUKE]
Okay.
Right now, she's talking with
her friends at a hamburger shop,
but she's not by the window,
so I don't think it's likely
that she'll be
attacked from outside.
[KURZ]
Hey, don't sweat it!
Take it easy,
you gotta blend in!
But I am... taking it easy.
[KURZ]
Are you?
[SOUSUKE gasps]
[KURZ]
What is it?
[SOUSUKE] I've got a suspect.
Suitcase at his feet.
Keeps checking his watch.
It's just like in the
anti-terrorist field manual.
Time-bomb.
A time-bomb?!
Wait, but this is a kidnapping,
not an assassination, Sousuke!
[SOUSUKE]
Uh-oh...
What is it this time?
[SOUSUKE] He stood up. He may
have noticed me, so stand by.
[WOMAN A] We better
be getting back soon...
[SOUSUKE sighs]
[KANAME]
Oh...
No way!
I gotta catch him!
Not good!
[WOMEN scream]
[KYOKO]
Huh...?
[KYOKO gasps]
[KYOKO]
Sousuke!
Agh, dammit, Sousuke!
What's going on?!
Huh?
[KANAME]
Sir! Excuse me!
Hey, you! You left
your briefcase here!
[SOUSUKE gasps]
[horn honking]
[KANAME gasps]
[MAN screams]
[MAN]
Oh no! My treasure!
Oh, what a relief!
[MAN giggles]
[KYOKO]
Kaname! Sousuke!
[KANAME]
Huh?
Sousuke, what're you...?
What're you doing here?
Just a coincidence.
[KYOKO]
Are both of you alright?!
Well, no injuries on my part.
And you, Kaname?
No, I think I'm okay.
I'm so glad!
Wow, you're like
a hero, Sousuke!
I think it's totally cool
that you risked your life
to save hers! Mayuko's right!
I just did what I had to do
under the circumstances, ma'am.
[KANAME moans]
It was merely a
matter of coincidence
that I happened
to be in the area.
[KANAME growls]
[KYOKO]
Oh, yeah, right!
What. In. The. Hell?!
[SOUSUKE]
Huh?
Keep your hands
off me, you pervert!
[KURZ chuckles]
[KANAME sighs]
[KANAME]
What is the matter with you?!
Do you have some kind of
grudge against me or what?!
[SOUSUKE]
Ah, Kaname!
It's just a coincidence.
[KANAME growls]
How can you just sit
there and say that?!
Doha Tragedy?!
This newspaper's from 1994!
My reading selection should
be none of your concern.
Tell me why the hell you keep
following me everywhere I go!
I honestly do not know where
you're getting this idea
that I'm following you,
Miss Chidori.
Are you a very
self-conscious person...?
I would have to be unconscious
not to notice this
level of harassment!
Speak to me directly if you
have something to tell me!
Like I told you,
it's just a coincidence.
You have the nerve to tell
me this is a coincidence?
That's right.
It's all coincidence.
Very well, then.
[SOUSUKE gasps]
Hey, wait!
Bye-bye, Mr. Pervert!
[KANAME gasps]
[SOUSUKE grunts]
Hey, Sousuke. Sousuke!
Sousuke Sagara!
Hey, Sousuke, are you alright?
[SOUSUKE] Yes.
There's nothing wrong with me.
Nothing wrong with you?!
What on earth were you
thinking back there?!
I just wanted to get out at
this station all of a sudden.
It has nothing to
do with you, okay?
So you mean to tell me
after all this time...?
It's still a coincidence.
[KANAME sighs]
Lemme guess. Your choosing to
sit here is also a coincidence?
Uh-huh.
[KANAME]
I can't take this anymore.
Hmph!
[KANAME]
Hey, Sousuke.
Uh, yes?
[KANAME]
I promise I won't get angry;
I just want a straight answer.
[SOUSUKE] I take it you want
to know what coincidence
it was that brought me here.
[KANAME groans]
[KANAME]
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
Then, as someone who also
just happened to be here,
can I ask you something?
What's that?
[KANAME] You've lived overseas
for a long time, right?
Were you like this
at your other schools?
[SOUSUKE] Yes. I enjoyed
peaceful days like this one.
[KANAME]
Okay... But aren't you sad
to be away from
your old friends?
[SOUSUKE] No. We keep in touch
through telephone and post,
so I guess I'm not technically
separated from them.
[KANAME] You have a weird way
of answering questions.
Do you have a girl?
[SOUSUKE]
A girl?
[KANAME] A girlfriend!
A lover, someone like that.
[SOUSUKE] No, I... don't have
any friends of that nature.
[KANAME]
Hmm... Is that so...?
[SOUSUKE] According to my
colleague-- I mean, my friend,
There's no woman in the world
who would be my girlfriend,
even in the remotest
corner of the tundra.
But I've never known
quite what to make
of some of the things he says.
[KANAME laughs]
Your friend's a funny guy,
you know that?
You know what he means?
[KANAME]
Yeah!
I mean, you are a bit
of an odd bird, Sousuke.
Odd bird?
You might even say,
extremely odd.
[KANAME giggles]
[KANAME]
But maybe...
Even with that rare
personality of yours,
you just might find someone
nice who'll understand you.
You think so, huh?
Someone... nice...
From what I can gather,
you seem like a nice person.
Now, wait a second,
I wasn't trying to be all
serious or anything. Ugh...
Very well, I will
disregard what you said.
[KANAME gasps]
You're pretty weird, all right.
[KANAME laughs]
[KANAME]
Make that really weird!
Really, really weird!
[KANAME laughs]
[MAN]
Hm?
[rumbling]
[CAT hisses]
Oops!
[KURZ sighs]
Oh boy.
[DOG barks]
[GIRL]
I'm really sorry, sir!
Fairy! What's the
matter with you?!
[FAIRY growls]
Did they notice me...?
Well, thank god.
[KURZ]
Damn, that was close.
[KURZ] Sousuke's got me doing
too many things at once.
Hm...?
I don't believe it...
There's no reason for
a grown man to litter...
[KYOKO]
So, what happened?
Did anything good happen
to you on the way home? Hmm?
[KANAME]
No, nothing!
[KYOKO]
Nothing between you and Sousuke?
[KANAME]
Ah! Oh, please, Kyoko!
Nothing could ever happen
between me and that maniac!
[KANAME laughs]
[KANAME]
Too funny!
[KYOKO]
Yes, yes, I keep forgetting.
Hey, did you study
for tomorrow's test?
It's gonna be bright and early!
[KANAME]
Test?! What test?!
[KYOKO]
The kanji test!
The teacher said she'd decide
groups for the school trip
based on our scores.
[KANAME] I didn't hear
anything about that! Nothing!
[KYOKO]
Oh, Kaname, you're okay.
[KANAME]
No, I'm not okay...!
I know it's not a good idea
to let my guard down around him,
but I didn't think he'd be
pawing through my underwear!
I was right, wasn't I?
Total pervert.
Next Full Metal Panic,
Episode 3: "Lingerie Panic."
Come here, Sousuke. I've got
something I wanna show you...
[SOUSUKE]
Why're you so angry?