[beeping]
[ARBALEST A.I.]
Warning.
Heat source closing
in from behind.
Execute ABHS.
[CODAR AI]
On which band?
Probably microwave.
[CODAR AI]
Hunting for frequency.
Please wait one minute.
Moron. Do it in 30 seconds.
All units halt.
[CODAR AI]
ABHS hunting mode complete.
Communication now possible.
Hello, Kashim.
It's Gauron.
[GAURON] I don't appreciate you
interrupting my business.
Why not show some
courtesy and die?
Fire!
Zaied, please take
over from here.
[ZAIED]
Leave it to me.
[GAURON] How do you
feel about torturing
your old friend to death?
[ZAIED] I don't feel
anything. It's my duty.
[GAURON] Hmm. You make
it sound so boring.
[SOUSUKE] The angle of
the slope is 20-23 degrees.
Thirteen or 15 seconds
to the valley floor.
If we can force
close-quarters combat
under the cover of the dust...
AI, the enemy found
our frequency.
Scramble and forward
the data to all machines.
[ARBALEST A.I.]
Roger. Forwarding data.
Kashim.
[SOUSUKE] Another attack
from behind in this terrain?
Who's giving orders?
[ARBALEST A.I.] Enabling data
link. Unable to transmit.
Please try it again.
[ARBALEST A.I.] Tuner and fixed
band mode are out of order.
Unable to communicate.
[ZAIED] Kashim, when they
can attack you from behind,
that's when you die.
Remember that.
[GRAY]
Sergeant Sagara's communications
have been cut off.
Are you serious?
What about the
information read-outs?
[GRAY]
I haven't received any.
[ANDY] Then he must have been
outsmarted by the enemy
and got attacked.
I'm dead sure of it.
[gasps]
[BATIST] It's not something
I wanna believe,
but sometimes God
likes to shuffle in
and deal a card
called despair...
Especially on the battlefield.
[GRAY]
Batist...
Listen, Gray. You said you
fought in Eastern Europe.
You must have witnessed this
moment dozens of times.
The moment when God
calls someone's number.
[grunts]
[BATIST] I'm not saying I need
a rosewood coffin,
but do you think you can find
something suitable for me?
[SAVAGE 1] Shit! The sand
filter's reaching its limit.
The leg joints
aren't functioning!
Stop kicking up the dust!
[SAVAGE 2]
Don't panic! Number 3,
use Passive Thermograph
to find the heat source.
[SAVAGE 3]
Got it! Target at 5 o'clock!
Dist--
[SAVAGE 1]
He's aiming for the sand filter!
Defense! Once the filter is
damaged, we can't do anything!
[SAVAGE 1 screams]
[SAVAGE 2]
Where? Where is he?
[SAVAGE 1] Search for the heat
source! Protect the fil--
Just calm down!
I'll handle all the data and
forward it to each machine.
So everyone switch to
CIC synchro-mode.
Surround it. We only
have one machine to fight.
Somebody out there
is firing on us
with a Gatling cannon, AI.
Use enemy search mode
to pinpoint the noise
from the motor.
[ARBALEST A.I.]
One minute, please.
No, do it in 30 seconds!
[ZAIED]
It won't be so easy when
you're in close-quarters
combat with another AS.
The monomolecular cutter or
Gatling cannon is your best bet.
[SOUSUKE] It would have been
impossible to surprise me from
behind if he didn't know
the terrain around here.
And that Gatling cannon...
[gasps]
[ANDY] Five minutes have gone by
since we lost communication.
What should we do,
Gray? Withdraw?
[JACKSON]
Yeah, what if he's...
Well, you know...
like Batist said.
[GRAY] What if he's alive?
What if he's still fighting?
Withdrawing would mean
abandoning him.
I could never do something
like that to him.
And furthermore, we haven't
carried out the mission
that was assigned to us.
[gasps]
Oh god, it's Gauron.
Damn! How come the
surveillance system
didn't pick his ass up?
You fool. Did you think I'd slip
and get caught in your slow net?
[GRAY]
AI, execute trap!
[AI]
Roger. Executing.
[gasps]
[ANDY]
No way! He broke through.
[JACKSON]
Oh, shit.
[GRAY] Andy, stay in
defensive formation.
Get the enemy's data first!
Here, partner. Let me show you.
I'm gonna carry out my mission.
[gasps]
He got Andy!
[GRAY]
Jackson, secure the trailer,
and for god's sakes, cover me!
[JACKSON]
Roger! Go to hell, you bastard!
[ARBALEST A.I.]
Enemy's equipment identified.
Anti-AS Gatling cannon.
AK-87. Fully automatic.
520 rounds per second.
Equipped with large
reserve magazine.
Reserve magazine?
[ZAIED]
Kashim...
it is the cautious soldier
who survives until the end.
Even in a heated battle,
make sure to save some bullets
in a reserve magazine.
You'll stand a better
chance of winning.
It can't be... Zaied.
AI, I wanna talk to that AS.
Search for the frequency.
[ARBALEST A.I.]
Searching.
Error. The frequency
cannot be identified.
Allied communications restored.
Now receiving.
Connect me.
[GRAY]
Sergeant Sagara, do you read me?
Are you okay?
[GRAY]
We're being attacked by Gauron!
You're what?
[GRAY] We still have
the nuclear warhead.
Andy was killed.
[gasps]
What's the status on your end?
Gray, what happened?
[ARBALEST A.I.]
Communication has terminated.
I'll be right there.
Get out of my way!
Someone steals merchandise from
a businessman, he gets angry.
You agree?
It's time to shut you up!
What the...?
[GAURON]
So long, lousy thief.
Dammit, I can still fight!
Close the freaking hatch,
you piece of shit!
Batist, what are you...?
As long as you can curse
up a storm like that,
you can fight... Listen,
I'm gonna give you support.
But you can't let them
get their hands on the warhead.
But how are you gonna...?
I'm real sorry...
I still owe ya $300. Please
leave it that way for now.
[ZAIED laughing]
Take that!
[SOUSUKE laughing]
Oh yeah?
--[ZAIED] Oh, ya got me!
--You missed!
[ZAIED] Well it's a good
thing you're not against me
in a real battle. Otherwise
I'd take you down right now!
[ZAIED]
Forgive me, Kashim.
I wanted to be on
the winning team.
[ZAIED]
You haven't changed.
Your attacks are as
effective as ever.
[ARBALEST A.I.]
Communications system restored.
Then connect me.
[GRAY]
Batist, what are you doing?!
[BATIST]
I'm going to kill that Gauron.
[GRAY] You're injured!
What are you talking about?
[BATIST]
Do you wanna know why
God deals us such
a terrible card?
It's simply because...
...he went to all this trouble
to create these idiots
called humans, and he's
regretted it ever since.
Listen, Gray.
If you survive,
please tell Sagara...
that he'll make a good
soldier when he grows up.
[GRAY]
Batist!
[BATIST]
SDM, stand by!
[AI] Warning, once the
self-destruct mode has been set,
it cannot be cancelled.
Do you accept?
I accept! Start the sequence!
[AI] This is the final
confirmation. Do you accept?
Yes I accept. Hurry it up!
[AI] Roger. Please set a time to
schedule the execution.
In ten seconds.
[AI]
Roger. Ten seconds starting now.
ADM will be executed in ten,
passengers should
evacuate immediately.
Counting down. Six.
Don't do it. Stop it, Batist.
[AI]
Three. Two. One.
[screams]
Batist, damn you!
What, going somewhere?
[gasps]
Well, well, well. Since I
don't see you giving up,
I guess we'll have to fight
to the bitter end.
Won't we?
[GRAY]
Batist! Jackson!
[ARBALEST A.I.] No response
from Jackson's machine.
[gasping]
[GRAY gasps]
It really isn't anybody's fault.
These things often happen
on the battlefield,
but you can understand
that... Right, Kashim?
[GRAY]
Don't worry about me.
There's no need. Your mission
is to make it home, Sousuke.
[SOUSUKE gasps]
Zaied!
K-Kashim...
[panting]
Miss Gray, I'm coming.
All right, Gauron,
where are you?!
[GAURON] If you want it, why
don't you just come and get it?
[SOUSUKE] Because, I'd
rather kill you first!
Huh, wasn't quite as easy as
catching a sparrow, was it?
But please, amuse me.
[ARBALEST A.I.]
Heat source rapidly approaching
at 5 o'clock.
AI, now listen to me!
Start the Lambda Driver!
[ARBALEST A.I.]
Roger.
Show me how it's done!
Goodbye, Gauron!
[growls, yells]
[SOUSUKE panting]
Zaied... but...
[ARBALEST A.I.]
Performing thermal scan.
Reserve magazine contains
unused bullets.
Like I told you... the soldier
who wins is the one who
saves a few rounds and keeps
them in a reserve magazine.
Why don't you...
say something... Sousuke?
[SOUSUKE]
No problem.
[KANAME] Whoa! All of a sudden,
he said we should take
a summer vacation, just the
two of us. Of course I want
some nice memories,
but I need some time
before my heart
is ready for that.
[SOUSUKE] Next Full Metal Panic:
"Deep Sea Party."
Kaname, have you ever
parachuted before?
[KANAME]
Huh?