Here we go!
But, Mr. Kalinin--
Don't worry. That old
man wouldn't die
even if the world
came to an end.
[grunts] What are those things?
The JSDF 96.
[TAKUMA chuckles]
[MELISSA]
What is this?
Sergeant Major!
Melissa!
[gasps] I can't move!
Melssia, aim the thumb with
the monomolecular cutter!
Do it now!
[gasps]
[MELISSA screams]
[TELETHA]
Melissa!
Take aim, now!
And fire!
[BEHEMOTH A.I.]
Lambda Driver, B function.
Yes, let's try it.
[TAKUMA]
A shield... That's right.
A shield.
Lambda Driver...
[TAKUMA grunts]
You're wasting your time.
[pants]
[TAKUMA]
I've found you.
The girl who never
noticed my feelings,
Miss Thick-skinned Testarossa.
[TELETHA]
If I had killed Takuma
when I had the chance,
our enemies would have given
up on operating Behemoth.
And... And...
But that's over.
If I can't have her,
then I'll simply destroy her.
[truck engine whining]
[KURZ]
Shit! Tessa, get in!
Sousuke, help me push!
[SOUSUKE]
Roger!
[KURZ]
Sousuke, you drive!
[laughs]
[gasps]
[silence]
[SOUSUKE]
Captain! Captain!
[background noises fade in]
[KANAME grunting]
Captain, can we get some backup?
Huh?!
We need to do something
to get rid of that giant.
Request backup!
[TAKUMA] Go ahead and run.
You'll never get away from me.
Nobody here has the
power to stop Behemoth.
[laughing]
[eeiry laughter]
[MARDUKAS]
Are you safe, Captain?
[TELETHA] Mr. Mardukas, where
is the submarine right now?
120 km south of the
Kii Peninsula, Captain.
[TELETHA]
It's too far from here.
We're out of range for the
emergency deployment booster.
I've got it!
Why don't we send Arbalest
by ballistic missile?
It's impossible.
It would take an hour
just to get everything
ready for it.
Can you imagine the
scale of the damage
Behemoth would cause
in the one or two hours
before the missile arrived?
Nothing can be done.
There's nothing I can do.
[MARDUKAS]
Captain, are you in a situation
that requires the
use of Arbalest?
Yes, I am.
[MARDUKAS]
Immediately?
That's right.
Then we'll start
the launch sequnce.
What did you say?
[MARDUKAS] I didn't receive
your permission, Captain,
but we have a
ballistic missile loaded
with Arbalest ready
to launch in 3 minutes.
It will arrive six
minutes after launch,
which means I will need you
to allow me a total
of 9 minutes.
Mr. Mardukas...
[MARDUKAS] I apologize. I'm
ready to accept your punishment.
[TELETHA]
No, I'm glad you did.
Please launch it right now.
Yes, Captain.
Where should we drop it?
[TELETHA]
It's no good here.
The giant might attack it
after it descends.
[TELETHA]
Somewhere with rougher terrain.
Somewhere we can
spare enough time
for the pilot to get in and
start it up after it lands.
It shouldn't be out in the open,
but downtown is no good either.
We'd involve civilians.
Low lighting and
limited open space.
It can't be flat.
We need slopes.
Somewhere Arbalest can make
full use of its abilities.
Where would that be?
[gasps] That's it!
[MARDUKAS]
Start launch!
It's still chasing us!
And it's shooting at us!
Change lanes when I say.
[SOUSUKE]
Right!
Coming, coming, coming... Now!
If he shoots at us
one more time,
we're all gonna die
in this little truck.
[KURZ]
Sousuke, drive straight.
[SOUSUKE]
What are you doing?
I'm gonna shoot him
so listen up!
I need you to drive
dead straight,
and don't change speed either.
Roger that.
Wh-What are you...?
[KURZ]
Hang on, Miss Kaname.
You'll find out soon enough.
[KURZ]
That's right. Come on.
Aim at me, you son of a bitch.
[growls]
[BEHEMOTH A.I.] Damage to
Vulcan on right side of head.
My-My Behemoth! You hit it!
But how...?
[KANAME]
Kurz, that was awesome!
[KURZ]
Hah! Leave it to me!
Wow, and all this time I thought
you were just a pretty boy
bluffing your way
through everything.
[sighs]
Hey, we can't let
down our guard yet!
[SEINA groans]
[SEINA]
The Behemoth...
Did it move?
Yes, it seems you've won.
Heh... But it doesn't
matter anymore.
[sighs]
[SEINA]
It's impossible to destroy it,
and it has enough fuel
to last 40 hours.
Until then, no one can stop it.
[KALININ]
So it's up to Takuma.
I truly feel sorry for that boy.
His memory got messed
up and somehow...
...he started believing that
I was his real sister,
whom he had killed.
I used his beliefs and
confusion to my advantage.
I have no family.
I've always been alone...
[SEINA]
Aren't you going to ask me?
Ask what?
[SEINA]
Why I saved you?
I can guess why.
You talk like... you know
everything, don't you?
I hate you...
You make me sick...
Sorry.
I hate you... All that you are.
All that you've done.
Can I at least take
your name with me...?
It's Andrey Sergeivich Kalinin.
What a strange name...
[MELISSA coughing]
Oh, God...
I thought I was dying.
Someone you know?
[KALININ]
Mmm... Something like that.
[KURZ laughing]
Faster! Faster!
[SOUSUKE] Quit laughing and
line up your next shot!
Let's be reasonable here! Ah!
I can't do that if
you keep this up.
Oh, ho! Ride 'em cowboy.
Is that it?
[KANAME]
Hm?
I think I've seen that before.
[SOUSUKE]
It's no good.
It's a sitting duck.
[TAKUMA cackles]
Well, that kills that.
It's not over yet.
That machine isn't going
to break so easily.
Sergeant!
Right, Captain!
Chidori!
[KANAME]
Uh, what?
[SOUSUKE]
Take the wheel!
[yelps] But I'm only
in high school!
[KANAME, TELETHA scream]
[KANAME]
Nevermind, I'll drive.
[KURZ]
Turn here, Kaname!
No, not the break!
Once it stops, that's the end.
Oh, God, what am I doing? Ah!
[KURZ]
Urzu 6 to Urzu 7.
This is Urzu 7. I'm here.
What the hell is
taking you so long?
[SOUSUKE] The hand lever
is buried underneath
and I'm not able to
break the capsule.
You can't open it?
[yells]
You're telling me you
can't crack the shell?!
Yes, that's affirmative.
[KURZ] You moron! If we
end up as scrambled eggs,
I'll curse your
remotest descendents.
[SOUSUKE]
I have one more grenade.
I'll try using that.
[grunts]
--[KURZ yelping]
--You have to speed up!
[KANAME]
Yeah, I know that!
[gasps]
Inside! Go into the garage door!
[grunts]
[KANAME groaning]
Tessa!
[gasps]
[KANAME]
What is this?
I've seen this before.
[smack]
Let's move it, Kaname!
[pants]
[BEHEMOTH A.I.] Lamba Driver,
A function dropping.
Interference waves reported
in skeletal system.
No, I need to keep my focus!
Where is Sousuke Sagara?
I don't know, loser!
Why don't you go
ask your big sister?
[TAKUMA]
Where is he?!
[SOUSUKE]
What do you want?
[growls]
[SOUSUKE] Licking your lips
in front of the target:
something a third class
soldier would do.
[TAKUMA]
What did you say?
[SOUSUKE]
You wanna fight? Attack me?
[TAKUMA]
Fine, you asked for it!
[KANAME]
Ah!
What happened? [gasps]
[KANAME yelps]
Sousuke!
Brr...
Kaname, what's the matter?
[KANAME gasps]
How... How cold... It's so
chilly... C-Cool down?
[TELETHA]
Miss Kaname, listen to me.
Please tell him to attack
one of the giant's
cooling systems,
he has to use the
Lambda Driver. Hurry!
[gasps]
A.I.
[ARBALEST A.I.]
Yes, Sergeant.
So this machine must be
equipped with a Lambda Driver?
Am I right?
[ARBALEST A.I.]
Correct.
If we assume the enmy has
Lambda Driver capabilities,
is there any way we
can counter against it?
[ARBALEST A.I.]
Unknown.
As the site commander,
I demand to know.
[ARBALEST A.I.]
Demand accepted.
Answer still: unknown.
I've got to
concentrate my senses.
[ARBALEST A.I.]
Damage to right knee joint.
[KANAME]
Sousuke, can you hear me?
[SOUSUKE]
Chidori?
[KANAME] Listen up.
I don't know the specifics,
but apparently there's
a cooling system
for the Lambda Driver
located near its groin.
[SOUSUKE]
Roger.
You need to attack it there...
...I think.
[SOUSUKE]
You think?
[KANAME]
That's all I know, okay?
A regular attack won't work.
You have to use
the Lambda Driver.
You've got it, right?
Did the Captain tell you that?
[KANAME]
You mean Tessa?
Um, maybe she did.
I'll just leave it at that.
[SOUSUKE]
Could you be anymore random?
[KANAME, KURZ scream]
No! Kaname!
[SOUSUKE]
Don't panic.
Don't think of it as nonsense.
The bullet I shoot now will
break through his shield.
Believe it.
Yes! Just like last time!
Let's go! C'mon!
You're looking for
a narrow slit.
Left or right.
Doesn't matter. Pick one!
[SOUSUKE]
Concentrate my senses.
I will make it hit the target.
I'll destroy it!
Now die!
[BEHEMOTH A.I.] Lambda Driver
function has haulted.
No chance of recovery.
Behemoth will be purged
due to excessive weight.
[gasping]
I lost... sister... But why?
You didn't lose, Takuma,
but these things
sometimes happen.
It isn't fair. It just isn't.
Yes, you're right.
It really isn't fair.
There... There isn't
anything left for me now.
You're going to be
all right, Takuma.
I'm here for you.
Sister...
And I'll...
continue to be with you.
[TAKUMA]
Really?
That's right. Don't worry,
you can rest easy.
[TAKUMA]
Yes, I'm sorry...
[TELETHA] Thank you for
your hard work, Mr. Weber.
Your skill is as good as always.
[KURZ]
Yeah, I guess so.
[TELETHA] And thank you,
for your hard work, Mr. Sagara.
[SOUSUKE]
Not at all, Captain.
This mech is officially
yours, Sergeant.
I hope you'll take care of it.
[SOUSUKE]
Oh! Yes, ma'am.
[TELETHA]
And Miss Kaname?
I especially need to
thank you for your help.
Okay, if you really feel
the need to thank me,
but could you tell me why?
Yeah, well, maybe later.
Huh?
Because... I'm utterly
exhausted at the moment.
But there is something
that I'd like
to get off my chest right away.
What's that?
[TELETHA]
Sergeant Sagara, please turn off
all hearing sensors.
That's an order.
Uh, roger that.
[KANAME]
Wait, what are--
I think I may have
fallen in love
with our serious sergeant.
[KURZ]
Ooh! Oh, my!
--I... That is...I mean...
--[KURZ giggles]
Well then, now that
everyone's clear,
may the best woman win.
Fair enough?
[KURZ] Oh! Tessa and Sousuke
sittin' in a tree,
K-I-S-S-I-N-G...
[TELETHA]
Shall we withdraw now?
I heard that Mr. Kalinin
made it out safely.
[TELETHA]
Please, you have to listen.
Melissa's making fun of me.
[MELISSA]
You started it.
[TELETHA]
I can't take it anymore!
I challenge you to a duel.
[MELISSA] Fine with me.
I'll mop you up good.
[TELETHA gasps]
[SOUSUKE] Next Full
Metal Panic: Episode 13:
"A Cat and a Kitten's
Rock &amp; Roll."
This is starting to worry me.