Hey, who is this little
girl? Why does she have
the same name and
hairstyle as me?! And
where did she come from
anyway? Wait, you're
after the Silver Crystal?
That means you're an
enemy! Well, you can act
all cute and innocent,
but you can't fool me
because I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of the
Moon.. I'll punish you!
[snickering]
Master Rubeus. Is this
area the Tokyo Juban
District?
Yes. And just as I
thought, the whole place
appears to be
under-developed.
Great! Then let's go
find the Silver Crystal
so we can destroy it.
There's really no need to
rush, Koan.
But, sir...
He's right...
I think our very first
order of business is to
hunt down the Rabbit.
We can worry about
the Silver Crystal
later.
[chuckling]
Good suggestion.
All right. Let's make
finding that Rabbit and
getting rid of her our
primary goal.
"Angel or Devil? The
Mysterious Girl from the
Sky."
Mamo, tell me.. Will we
always be together, from
now on?
Yes, we will, Usako.
This is the happiest
moment of my life!
[chuckling]
You're being a little
dramatic, Usako.
Watch your step...
[struggling]
Sorry.
Hm??
[startled]
[grunting]
[losing balance]
Hey, what just happened
here?
[gasping]
Y-You there! Just what
do you think you're
doing?! Why are you
hugging my Mamo?!
"Mamo"?
Hey! Back off! Get away
from my man!
Who are you? Just where
did you come from,
anyway?
I am Usagi.
Huh?!
"Usagi"?
Who are you supposed
to be?
And why are you wearing
your hair in my bun-head
style?
What do you mean your
bun-head style?!
I'm the one and only
bun-head! Me, Usagi
Tsukino, got that?!
You're Usagi Tsukino?
If you are who you say
you are...
...then you must possess
the Silver Crystal.
So... hand it over
right now.
Hey, come on. That's a
toy gun and this is just
a joke, right?
Stay right where you are,
mister! If you move, this
girl dies!
Now give me.. the Silver
Crystal.
What? What do you mean?
I don't know what you're
talking about.
Don't try to fool with
me! I already know you
have the Silver Crystal,
so stop pretending
that you don't.
Look.. I'm not pretending.
You can continue to threaten
me with that toy,
but I don't know what
I don't know.
So.. You've decided to
tough it out by playing
dumb.
Big mistake...
[gun shots]
Usako!
[gasping]
Huh?
It was a toy! But it
sure sounded real.
Hey! Your joke went too
far!
Where'd she go?
I'm home.
Who in the world was
that girl? She ruined
what was going to be the
most perfect date ever.
[groaning]
Shingo!
[panting]
What's the matter,
Usagi?
Shingo! Fess up!
You trashed my room and
tore everything to
shreds, didn't you?!
What the heck are you
talking about?
Don't you play
dumb with me!
[gasping]
What are you doing in the
middle of my house?
She came down from the
sky?
Yeah. It's the only
explanation.
But there's another
puzzling factor. She knew
about the existence of the
Silver Crystal, as well.
Mamo...
It'll be all right.
You have me.
Your little cousin Usagi
will be staying here with
us for the time being.
This girl is tricking
you! She isn't who you
think she is at all!!
Don't be silly. What are
you talking about?
Usagi's always saying
stupid stuff!
We don't even have
a cousin! Who's saying
stupid stuff now?!
Boy, Usagi. You've really
lost it this time.
Huh?! What's this? No
way!
She came to visit us
during the New Years.
Don't you remember?
[growling and screaming]
This is totally
ridiculous!
Usagi. Calm down.
Yeah Usagi, you should
calm down.
The nerve of that little
pipsqueak!! Huh?
[grunting]
Who is that manipulative
little girl, anyway?!
I don't know. By the time
I came back, everyone one
was acting like they've
known her for years.
Those pictures were
somehow manipulated and
slipped into the album!
You're probably right.
And she had to have used
some kind of strange
energy to alter your
family's memories, to
accept her.
She's also after the
Silver Crystal! Luna,
what do we do?
For now, let's wait and
see until we can learn
more about this girl.
But that's gonna take
like, forever. I say we
need to act before things
get much worse.
Huh?
[sniffing]
Ahhhh!
Give me the Silver
Crystal!
[yelling]
I want it now! Give me
the Silver Crystal! Hand
it over! Don't act dumb
with me! For all I know--
Well... It doesn't look
like her life's in danger
and at least they'll both
be clean...
[groaning]
Don't worry, we'll think
of something.
You're right. Plus, I
have Mamo who said he'd
love me forever!
[groaning]
It'll be all right. I'm
here with you.
Mamo...
[swooning]
Heh?!
Where did you hide the
Silver Crystal?
[screaming]
Hand over the Silver
Crystal!
Ah!
Get out! Go on!
Get out of my room
right--
Usagi!
Why in the world are you
being so mean to her?!
But I'm not the one
being mean! She
started it!
I'm sorry. I
didn't mean to.
Why, I oughta---
Usagi... She came to
Tokyo all by herself
because her parents are
too busy to watch her.
She's just frightened
and lonely.
Don't act so stupid,
Usagi. You should be
nice to her.
[screaming]
Master Rubeus..I've
searched every inch of
the Juban District, but I
haven't located Rabbit yet.
And what about you,
Berthier?
No. I'm very sorry, sir.
Hmph!
Great Wizard Wiseman!
I foresee that the Silver
Crystal will bring us
great misfortune... As
long as that Crystal
exists.. we will be
unable to destroy the
despicable Crystal Tokyo.
Lord Wiseman, tell us.
Is the Silver Crystal
really here in the Juban
District?
Yes. You must trust my
powers to foresee the
future.
Without fail, I'll find
the Silver Crystal and
destroy it, along with
that Rabbit.
[chuckling]
Sailor Moon...
...'R'!
Sailor Moon! R!
Rin Pyo To Sha Kai Jin
Retsu Zai Zen!
This is bad.
Huh?
So Usagi was right?
You picked up on an evil
aura around that photo?
Usagi, the kimono
you're wearing in this
picture, makes your
butt look fat.
[groaning]
C'mon! Be serious, Rei!
But that's all
I got!
I don't sense anything
strange at all from this
photo. Sorry, Usagi!
What? Are you sure?
So... It looks like those
girls are Usagi Tsukino's
best friends.
Maybe she got one of them
to keep the Silver
Crystal for her.
[humming]
Uh-Oh!
What a surprise! Hi
there, little girl. What
brings you here?
Uh!
Luna P! Transform!
Ah! That was a very
impressive trick!
Huh?
Agh, don't do that! It's
not coffee! You can't add
milk, it'll ruin them!
I'm not adding
milk to them!
Huh?
[grunting]
I told you it wasn't
milk. I guess when you
wake up, you'll realize
I wasn't lying.
Ugh. This is so odd that
you didn't sense anything
at all...
Ya sure that spiritual
power of yours is working,
Rei?
It's solid! How dare you!
Usagi, maybe you're
reading too much into
this situation.
Huh?
Yeah. We've taken care of
all the incidents that came
up and things are going well
now with you and Mamoru.
Uh--
There really isn't
anything keeping you
busy,
so maybe you're
overcompensating for
boredom and looking
for some excitement.
No, I'm not!
Are you sure?
Usagi... Maybe it's time
to pursue the one thing
that should really excite
us.
Yeah? What's that?
Well, we middle-schoolers
want to go to high
school, so...
... that means...
we should all study!
[groaning]
Next time, give a warning
before hitting us over
the head with reality.
[chuckling]
Hello! You girls are all
looking as cute as ever!
Which one of you would
like to go out on a date
with me?
Not that again,
grandpa, we're busy
right now!
You don't have to be so
nasty. It can't hurt to
try.
And I brought all of you
your favorite, Juban Hot
Spring Manju.
Okay, okay. Just leave
them there and be on your
way. Thank you!
Throwing me out. How
inhospitable.
I never thought my own
grand-daughter would
treat her poor, elderly
grandpa so callously. It
makes me sad. So, so
sad...
For crying out loud!
If anyone's sad, it
should be me. I'm the one
whose grandpa refuses to
act his own age,
and is always
hitting on young
girls.
Yeah, but he's got
good Manju!
Hm?
What's the matter? Aren't
you all gonna have some?
Is there enough?
Ehh--
[savoring]
Hm?!
What happened to
everyone? Rei? Huh?
[humming]
Ah-ha! I see the sleeping
drug took effect..
[laughing]
Now then... Time to start
looking for the Silver
Crystal.
[gasping]
Too bad for you! I didn't
drink the spiked tea!
[gasping]
How dare you drug all
my friends! It's
unforgivable!
[grunting]
Exactly who are you?
...Where did you come
from? And finally, why
are you looking for the
Silver Crystal?!
[whimpering]
Tell me!
[crying]
You can cry, but I won't
forgive you.
[crying]
Huh?! What's going on?
Hmmm.
Huh?
It's her.
[crying]
What exactly are you?!
[chuckling]
Looks like I've found
you... Little Rabbit.
I've been looking all
over for you.
[gasping]
Now that I've got you,
it's time to get rid of
you.
Wait a minute. Stop right
there! Who are you?!
Who am I?
I'm the youngest of the
four Spectre Sisters...
Koan.
You're like an
oversized crow!
Well, you're
in my way.
You'll die first!
Ahhhh!
Rei's manga collection!
[chuckling]
[gasping]
You're not getting away!
Hey!
I don't know who you are,
but you seem like an evil
person. So...
Moon Crystal
Power! Make Up!
Ahhhh!
You're fast. No wonder
they call you The Rabbit.
Help me... Daddy...
Mommy... [sighing]
Heh. Prayers won't
help you.
Stop right there!
[gasping]
Well, now. Who are you?
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
Can't say I'm impressed.
You're an evil villainess
who has threatened to
take a young girl's life.
So, now, in the name
of the moon, I'll
punish you!
Yeah? Whatever.
Ah!
[gasping]
Dark... Fire!
[panicking]
[gasping]
Get ready to roast,
Rabbit!
[grunting]
Sailor Body Attack!
How dare you rub my fine
face in dirt!
Die!
Who did that?
The bright flames of
passion are noble and
lovely...
But the evil
dark flames of murder are
ugly and despicable.
Tuxedo Mask, thank
goodness!
I'll incinerate both of
you, and the Rabbit!
I'm not going to
allow that!
Huh?
Moon Princess...
...Halation!
Ahhh!
I did it!
Sailor Moon!
How did you?!
Mark my words, I'll get
you for this!
It appears we have
a new enemy.
Thank you, Tuxedo Mask!
My pleasure. But what's
going on? Why would
anyone want to destroy
her?
[sleepily moaning]
Uh?
Tuxedo Mask?!
Huh?
Something wrong?
No. It's nothing.
Did I just have some sort
of vision?
So warm... Like Daddy...
What? Did you say Sailor
Moon?
Yes. And a stupidly dressed
guy she referred to as
Tuxedo Mask.
Huh. This interference
is quite unexpected...
Be that as it may...
We know the Silver
Crystal and the Rabbit are
somewhere in this town.
In time, both will
be in our possession.
And then I will crush
them for you, sir.
Sailor Moon. I'll make you
pay for messing up my face,
if it's the last thing I do.
Hmm... Seems like she's
been through some sad,
tough times.
Hey, little Usagi...
If you tell us
everything, I'm sure we'll
be able to help you out.
[sleeping sounds]
Mamo! Just being with you
makes my life so happy.
Will you please stop
fawning over me like
this.
Aw, you're just so shy.
C'mon, don't be
embarrassed.
No, it's not like that. I
don't have any feelings
for you anymore.
What?
It's over between
you and me.
Next time on Sailor Moon
R: "Usagi Devastated;
Mamoru Declares a
Break-up."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.