Berthier! Using people
and deceiving them is no
way to live your life!
Truly helping, loving,
and caring for other
people without expecting
something in return,
that's the way to fill
one's life with meaning.
Humans are born with the
power to love and care
for each other.
That's what you
need to understand!
"For Friendship: Ami
Vs. Berthier."
[groaning]
Ehhhhh!
And checkmate!
[groaning]
You beat me again!
[giggling]
Wow, great game!
[groaning]
But I even studied
this guide to chess!
Not only are you smart
when it comes to school
stuff, Ami, but you're an
ace chess player, as well.
Chess is the perfect
mental game for developing
a calm demeanor and it
promotes the ability to
make precise decisions.
Hear that? Calmness!
Precision! You couldn't
develop those things in
a hundred years!
Hmph! Hey, no
one asked you!
But you're right,
Ami is awesome!
Well actually Ami was the
junior chess champion of
Japan, isn't that right?
That was just luck.
Well then let's all learn
to play chess from Ami
and that way we can all
be chess champions!
Uh... I'm gonna pass
on that, I'm not really
good at being calm.
Ha! Mm-hm! I know!
When it comes to being
calm, you're even worse
than I am, Mako!
Well... You didn't
have to agree with
me.
Oh Usagi! Talk about
the pot calling the
kettle black...
Hey, do you wanna
play against me?
Why sure, but don't
expect me to go easy
on you. I'm gonna teach
you how to be a
gracious loser.
Check mate!
Whoa! Don't do that
yet we only just
started!
Nope! When in battle
never show mercy.
[groaning]
Chibi-Usa, you're
really good!
Hey sorry, I
gotta get going.
Oh wow, look at the
time. I have something
to do too.
Are you off to
do some studying?
Mm-mm! I'm going
to the Chess Tower.
The Chess Tower?
You look just lovely!
You really think so?
Hmph! Pathetic!
And thank you so much
for your purchase!
She has brought disgrace
to the Four Spectre Sisters.
Hi! Would you like
to try some new
makeup?
I don't understand...
Why would Koan want to
become an ordinary human
being in the first place?
I couldn't care
less what motivates
a traitor.
She's no longer
our younger sister.
Our clan has no use
for traitors like her.
I suppose you're right.
[gasp]
We'll figure out how
to rid ourselves of
that traitor later on.
Right now I want to show
you the location of the new
Crystal Point I found.
The Chess Tower...
Please Master Rubeus,
I'll handle this one!
Berthier seemed quite
anxious to go...
There's nothing wrong
with that. If she does
well, we'll help her
finish the job.
Of course.
Make sure you succeed.
Yessir!
Hnh! Exactly. Succeed and
you will continue to work
for me until I no longer
have a use for you.
After all, you're all
nothing more than expendable
pawns, here to protect the
king, me!
Huh? This building has
a shape I've seen
somewhere before.
It kinda looks
like a cake...
[giggling]
It's not a cake,
it's shaped like
a rook.
A rook?
I know this one!
A rook's that chess
piece that looks like
a castle!
You see, this
building's owner is
a huge chess fan.
Ohh...
As a matter of fact, this
Sunday, as a part of the
grand opening ceremony for
this Chess Tower, the
World Chess Tournament
is going to be held here.
So I guess you must
be signed up for that
tournament, right?
If you entered, you'd
be sure to win it!
I did sign up, because
I enjoy playing chess. But
it isn't that important to
me if I win or lose.
But winning is important...
Competing when you don't
care about winning is a
waste of time.
Winning this tournament
is what it's all about.
Excuse me, but,
who are you?
[giggling]
It's not whether you
win or lose, what really
matters is that you try
to do your best.
That's exactly what
losers always say!
[groaning]
Ahha! Silly girls, go
play your little chess
games, cause you'll
never lear anything
about being a winner
in the game of life.
You're being kinda
rude, you know...
Oh, did I hurt your
feelings? Well we'll
just have to play some
chess to prove my
point. See ya!
Boy is that girl
stuck up!
What a snob!
Ohh, Ami!
Is that you?
Huh?
It's been awhile!
Yes it has!
What a beautiful
piece of work this
building is!
Why thank you! So I
take it you'll be playing
in the chess tournament
Sunday?
Yes.
Well for old time's
sake, what do you say
we play a game?
Sure!
Y'know, I used to
play chess with your
grandfather all the
time.
Oh!
You know, Ami, you
seem a bit different.
Huh?
What I mean is, the
Ami I knew years ago
played chess to keep
herself from feeling
lonely. But now you
seem so much more...
That's because now
I have friends...
How nice. I'm glad to
hear it. Good friends
are more precious than
any other treasure.
Yes, I think
so as well.
Check!
Um, Ami...
Just between you and me,
would you mind holding
off on that kind of move?
[chuckling]
You haven't changed
a bit!
I forgot what a
lovely smile you
have.
Um... Does your
receptionist get
off at six today?
She does. You and I
should be the only
ones left here on
this floor.
Then would you mind
terribly if I took
a look around the
facility?
Be my guest.
[chuckle]
Thank you, sir!
Mmm!
This room is the exact
center of the Crystal
Point!
Dark Water!
Stop that!
Hm?
Wait, that's one of
the silly girls from
earlier, isn't it?
Leave now,
or else...
Hmph!
You're brave, but there's
no way you can stop me by
yourself. I'm way too
powerful.
Besides, I can't stand
goody-goody girls like
you and your stupid
friends. So...
Go to hell!
[screaming]
I wouldn't suggest
you try to stand up.
Because if you do...
[screaming]
Oh sorry, did
that hurt?
Well, don't worry.
Next time I hit you
like that, you probably
won't feel a thing.
Muh...
Mercury...
Mercury Star Power!
Make Up!
Oh my, what a surprise!
You're Sailor Mercury,
one of the Sailor
Guardians!
Master Rubeus will be
so please when he
hears this.
Shine Aqua Illusion!
Well! How dare you
interfere with my
work!
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
Ow!
That hurt!
You know three against
one isn't fair. It's
actually cheating!
And you didn't have
to be so rough!
Why don't you stop
whining and tell us
what you're doing here!
I've had enough for
today, but I swear
you'll pay for this!
Guys, there's
a problem!
Why? What
happened?
Berthier knows who I
am when I'm not a
Guardian.
Huh?!
I had to transform
right in front of her.
I couldn't help it.
Well if her target is
the Chess Tower, she'll
be back and we'll deal
with her then.
Don't you worry about
it! It'll work out!
Thanks, Sailor Moon.
Oww, she scratched
my hand.
The nerve of those creeps.
That blast could have
scarred my alabaster skin!
Oh, did you get hurt?
Aww, looks like
you did!
I-! The three of
them attacked me
at once!
But you fought them
back, right?
Your palm's bleeding.
They still didn't stop
you from succeeding in
your mission, did they?
Of course not!
That's what we thought!
Because if you have
failed after volunteering
to go, then there's no
way you'd have the guts
to come back.
If I failed, I think
I'd probably kill
myself.
Well, even if somehow I
had failed, I wouldn't
dream of asking my older
sisters to help out.
What a relief that
you didn't have to.
One disappointing
embarrassment like
Koan's failure is
quite enough.
[laughing]
Sailor Moon R!
So Ami, or should I say
Sailor Mercury. It's time
to settle this over your
favorite game.
A serious game
of chess...
[chuckling]
I'm here to compete
in the World Chess
Tournament.
Of course! May I
please have your
name?
Let's see, what
should I call
myself?
Huh?
I haven't decided
my name yet.
The competition's
that way...
Thanks!
This is exciting!
Yeah!
Hey! Ami won again!
Wouldn't it be great
if Ami wins it all!
Yeah.
Okay everyone, ready
for a chess cheer?!
Go! Go! Ami girl!
Do your best and
rule the world!
Usagi!
I say there...
Oh, I'm sorry!
Were we getting
too loud?
No, you're fine.
Are you girls all
friends of Ami?
Yes!
I see! So you must be
the good friends she
was telling me about
earlier.
You know her, too?
Who are you?
I'm the rich, eccentric
old man who built this
Chess Tower.
Whoa! So you're
the owner!
Mm-hm!
So do you think Ami has
a chance of winning
this tournament?
I'd say it depends
on her opponents.
So, she won again.
That girl is quite
good.
Ah! Berthier, my big
sister! What is she
doing here, competing
in this tournament?
All right!
Ami's awesome!
I hope she wins
this!
I bet she gets
through this round
no problem!
Wow! That same
girl won again!
Yeah, the old guy
was right! She
really is good!
Hey! It's down to
the final two!
Oh, Ami's playing that
girl for the chess
championship.
Let's have a fun
match, shall we?
[giggling]
[gasp]
Her hand's as
cold as ice!
[giggling]
I'll use this chess
game to crush you and
fill this entire building
with Dark Power. Now
that will be fun...
To the finals!
For this match, I'd
like to use these
playing pieces.
They're lovely...
Oh they're more
than just lovely.
[giggling]
What?!
What is Berthier
up to?
She is good.
Oh! Ami lost
another piece!
C'mon, Ami!
[giggling]
What's the matter?
It's time for your
move.
[gasp]
I got it!
Yeah! Ami turned
the tables on her!
[gasp]
Check mate!
Ami did it!
Oh no. This match
isn't over. We're
not done!
Huh?!
The game has just
begun, Sailor Mercury.
[gasp]
I've had enough
playing around!
There's nothing
to see here!
[gasps]
There must be some
problem with the
camera.
That sounds right!
We'll go check it out!
Koan, stay here!
Moon Crystal Power...
Mars Star Power...
Jupiter Star Power...
Venus Star Power...
Make Up!
I should've known
it was you!
Stop right there!
You're not ready to
challenge Ami in chess
or anything else for
that matter!
Cheating and lying
aren't the way to
succeed in life!
So now, in the name
of the moon, I'll
punish you!
Silly girls...
[screams]
What did you do?
Death is the only
cure for fools like
them!
Now, Sailor Mercury,
let's play another
titillating game of
chess together!
They'll die if
you don't.
This is awful!
It's freezing!
It's no use!
We're trapped in
this deep freeze!
So, have you made
up your mind yet?
Alright then,
let's play!
Good, that's smart and
since you're smart, I'll
need a small advantage.
Wait! That's cheating!
[giggling]
You better think fast
or it'll be a checkmate!
Oh, what a shame!
[gasp]
Oh wait, I forgot! If
you lose a chess piece
while playing with my
specially made pieces,
your body will
slowly freeze up.
Sailor Mercury!
Hang in there!
We have faith in you!
Believe in yourself!
We know you can do it!
Just know that if you
forfeit this match,
I will spare your life.
No! Let's play on!
Oh! You might be a
bigger fool than I
thought.
No! Save yourself!
Get away! Run!
This has gone
to far!
Burning...
Mandala!
[screaming]
Are you trying
to kill us?!
I'm sorry!
Check.
[giggle]
[sigh]
There's no point in
being a martyr. It's
crazy to die trying to
protect those strangers.
[chuckling]
That's where
you're wrong...
Huh?
They're not strangers,
they're my friends!
You're friends?
All my dear friends
are very important
to me.
Even if it costs me
my life, I would
protect them!
Hnnh! Stop trying
to stall for more
time.
Nicely done,
Berthier.
Now we can help
you finish her
off.
I can't believe you're
going to take the credit
for my hard work!
But the three of us work
as a team, the Three
Spectre Sisters!
Right. We should share
the credit for this win.
Check!
[gasp]
Oh! So it's you!
Check!
[gasp]
[screaming]
Oww!
Someone who doesn't
know what it's like
to be a pawn has no
right...
...to try to move
the queen! Farewell!
[gasp]
I need your help!
It looks like you're
plan failed, Berthier!
Right! And you should
make amends for your
failure by giving up
your life!
Do what's right!
[crying]
[laughing]
You see? Even among real
sisters, there's no such
thing as caring for
someone.
That's why it's absolute
nonsense that you would
risk your life to protect
a friend, a stranger,
or anyone!
You're all looking at
me like you feel so
sorry for me. Go on,
laugh.
Even I think it's funny
that I was counting on
my sisters to help me.
The joke's on... Me...
I said laugh!
Dark Water Full Power!
I'm going to take you
all with me!
[panicked breaths]
Every human being is
born alone and they
die alone!
And all this talk
about love! No one
needs love!
Stop it! Don't do
this sister!
Koan, have you come
here to shame me
like the others?
Listen to me- Ah!
You are not alone!
A sister like you who
betrayed us, could nevr
understand the pain
that I'm feeling!
That's not
true, sister!
I do understand you!
I know your heart and
your loneliness!
You can't understand!
[screaming]
Koan!
I beg you! Don't die!
Humans have-
[groaning]
All humans possess a
deep nurturing love!
I've seen it!
You have?
Will I be able to
see that love, as
well?
Bertheir!
Koan, are you
crying? Are
you hurt?
No! I'm just happy!
I'm so sorry, Koan!
I love you,
big sister!
Moon Crystal Power!
Refresh!
[giggling]
Thank goodness!
Yes! Thank you all!
Let's go home, guys.
Oh! Could you not
make that move?
Even though we're
sisters, I'm not
gonna go easy on
you.
Uh...
Hey! No fair! You
were using an extra
Queen!
C'mon, I need all
the help I can get.
Why you-!
[giggling]
I love you, sister!
Sailor Moon!
Why is it that you
sisters must fight
one another?!
Because for a traitor,
there is only death.
They may be my younger
sisters, but I will
show no mercy.
Petz! Calaveras! Open
you eyes! Can't you see
Rubeus is manipulating
you!
If you dare to defy
our clan. You will
die!
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"Rubeus the Heartless: The
Tragic Sisters."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.