So what if I'm a silly, dumb,
flat chested, lazy, and clumsy
goofball!
I'm used to being called those
things. But I'm not used to what
you're calling Ami!
And spreading rumors that Ami
cheated on her tests is totally
unforgivable!
I am Sailor Moon! In the name of
the Moon, I'll punish you!
[Sighs]
My body is just so gorgeous.
And I'm making it even more
gorgeous by immersing it in this
wonderful jasmine bath oil.
My darling Prince Demande just
loves the scent of jasmine.
Esmeraude, time to get out.
Really, Saphir? I think it's
very rude to spy on a woman
while she's bathing.
Get over it. As you well know,
we must complete the Dark Gate
as soon as possible.
I shouldn't need to remind you,
we have to send the power of the
Malefic Black Crystal into the
Juban District and destroy it.
And here you are, taking a bath
instead.
[Laughing]
My plan for all that is moving
forward even as I bathe. So
don't tell me what I have to do.
Really?
The newest Negative Point is the
Juban District's Eisai Cram
school!
Hmph!
[Groaning]
Come forth, Droid. Giwark!
Giwark!
[Evil Laughter]
You see that? The Henge is
already growing with Dark Power.
By tomorrow evening the Dark
Henge will be completed. I want
you to defend this point until
then.
Giwark.
"The Terrifying Illusion: Ami
All Alone."
[Screams]
[All Talking]
I'm so impressed! Wow Ami,
that's great!
You're at the top of our whole
class again!
You got everything right except
one, you're a genius!
Oh, that's not really true. All
the things I studied just
happened to be on the test.
It must be so nice to
always be the best.
All you do is study.
How dull.
It shouldn't come as any great
surprise that the boys call you
a nerd behind your back.
[Sighs]
How rude!
Don't pay any attention to what
those girls say. They're just
jealous because you're smarter
than they are.
Thanks, Usagi. I should be
used to this stuff by now.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
They all laugh cause my grades
are so bad. [Embarrassed
Chuckle]
I found this cheat sheet with
all the test answers in Mizuno's
desk!
Huh?
So Mizuno got a perfect score
because she cheated on the test.
I knew it!
She's probably been cheating
all along on every test and
that's the real reason she
always gets the best grades.
[Angry Grunting]
I've always wondered if she
buries her head in books just to
look intelligent.
I mean how smart can she
possibly be, she hangs out with
Usagi all the time.
That's right! Usagi is a
goofball she couldn't get a
good grade if she tried!
[Gasp]
Hey, Tsukino! You and your
friends hang with Mizuno. What's
your opinion?
Don't you think it's weird she's
at the top of the class while
you're stuck at the bottom
permanently.
It's not weird! Ami's really
smart and she studies harder
than anyone!
That's right. What is wrong
with you, Umino?
Picking on Ami! You're not
acting normal.
Sounds to me like you've decided
to take the side of a dirty
cheater!
We don't like it!
Back off!
Are you defending this cheater,
too? If that's your problem, I'm
ready to fix it!
[Screams]
Ha!
[Grunts]
Nice moves, Mako!
Mako, stop! You're gonna
get in trouble!
Huh?
That one boy did grab her, and
the other two looked pretty
mean.
They were accusing you of
cheating! Did you want me to
just let them get away with
that?
It's okay, because I know I'm
innocent.
Yes you are! We believe you!
Mhmm.
I appreciate it.
But what really bothers me the
most is how did I end up getting
that one question wrong? I was
so close to a perfect score!
Oh boy!
I can't get over the fact that
Umino and those others were
badmouthing Ami.
Yeah, they aren't the usual
students who go around doing
that sort of thing.
But I know they all go to Eisai
Cram School together.
[Heavy Breathing] Hey, is it
true Ami gets good grades
because she's a cheater?
Huh?
That guy who wears round
swirly glasses says so.
[Gasps]
How nasty! That just makes me so
angry!
[Grunts] Next time I see him,
I'm gonna wring his neck!
Usagi. Mako. It's alright.
At the end of the day, I know
you two will never believe that.
And that's good enough for me.
[Sighs]
She won't admit it, but she's
taking it badly.
I wish there was something
we could do.
There goes the cheater.
She really needs to change her
status from best student to best
cheater!
She just faked all that
studying! What a fraud!
[All] Cheater!
[Crying]
I'm...innocent!
Yes you are! We believe you!
[Sighs] It's okay!
Huh?
But I know they all go to
Eisai Cram School together.
Wait, is it more than a
coincidence that Umino and the
others spreading rumors go to
that school?
[Gasps]
There's Dark Power everywhere!
[Grunting]
Mercury Star Power Make Up!
Curses! That girl is Sailor
Mercury, one of the five Sailor
Guardians I have to get rid of!
I know you're here! And I know
you work for Esmeraude, where
are you hiding?
Come to the Eisai Cram School!
I'm here now and it's filled
with Dark Power!
Oh no! Just sit tight Ami, and
we'll be right there!
Come on Usagi,
we'd better hurry!
[Grunts]
I'll kill her!
Hmph!
[Grunting]
[Gasps]
[Screaming]
Bubble Spray!
Freezing!
Now I'm angry!
Hmph!
[Screaming]
How many of you are there?!
Giwark!
Double Bubble Spray Freezing!
She keeps making more clones. I
need to find that main Droid and
defeat her. Then this will
stop, once and for all!
Well, she's more powerful than I
thought. I guess I'm going to
have to try something else.
I'm going to make her kill her
friends when they arrive to
help. Ha!
Where'd they go?
Why'd they all disappear like
that?
[Laughing] Now, Sailor Mercury,
you're about to find out what
your friends truly think of you.
And I can't wait to watch, this
should be fun.
[Laughing]
Sailor Moon R!
[Heavy Breathing]
Dark power is everywhere!
Be careful! A Droid is hiding
here somewhere!
Really? What happened
to this place?
It appears the enemy has been
using the Eisai Cram School to
carry out their latest plan.
I'm sure that Umino and the
others suddenly became so mean
because they were exposed to
their Dark Power.
That would certainly
explain it.
Unforgivable!
Looks like those pesky Sailor
Guardians have arrived.
One is missing, but I'll make
sure Sailor Mercury kills the
others.
Hallucination Giwark!
[Painful Grunting]
Mercury!
Good grief! Would you
look at yourself?!
I've been meaning to tell you
for a long time that wearing two
shades of blue on white washes
out your skin tone.
Uhh, why are you criticizing me
all of a sudden?
You've neglected to improve your
wardrobe because you're wrapped
up in studying all the time.
What? You're picking on me too?
I am so tired of hearing you
talk about your studying and
brag about your good grades. It
makes me want to throw up!
What can I say? I study a lot,
but never thought I was bragging
about my grades.
I apologize to each of you for
my thoughtless behavior.
Oh, please Miss
goodie-two-shoes, I don't
believe you!
[Grunt]
This can't be happening! There's
no way my friends would say
these things to me!
I'm making you hate them. And
when you've had enough you're
gonna crush them!
Sailor Mercury! What's wrong?
Sailor Mercury! We hate you!
[Grunts]
[Gasps] A Dark Henge!
And a Droid too!
Moon Crystal Power Make Up!
Go ahead, Sailor Mercury. Kill
those bad mouthing girls before
they kill you!
Hold it right there!
What? Who the hell are you?!
I am the Pretty Guardian who
fights for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
Hmph! So the last one of you
finally shows up!
You have filled this Cram school
with Dark Power...
...infecting the minds
of students with animosity,
so they say spiteful things!
That is unforgivable!
[Chuckles]
And now in the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
I'm so scared!
Hallucination Giwark!
You've got to get out of
the way, Sailor Moon!
[Screams]
What just happened?
You're so dumb, Sailor Moon.
Flat Chested too!
A clumsy idiot!
You suck at everything!
[Sigh]
[Crying]
[Giggles]
Yeah! So what? I'm a dumb, flat
chested, clumsy idiot who sucks
at everything! Who cares?!
[Gasps]
That won't work on me, I'm used
to people calling me names!
Giwark! That is some twisted
personality!
I'm just gonna take that as a
compliment.
Let's see how you like this!
[Screams]
[Gasps]
[Grunts]
That hurt!
Giwark!
Sailor Moon!
[Gasps]
[Grunts]
[Gasps] Tuxedo Mask!
You have attacked and toyed with
the innocent minds of young
teenagers, by planting a Dark
Henge in a Cram school...
...their trusted place, where
students prepare for the high
school entrance exams.
I won't forgive a Droid as evil
as you are!
[Grunts] Don't interfere!
[Grunts]
[Screams]
[Gasps] Tuxedo Mask! You okay?
[Grunting]
Be sure to watch closely as
Sailor Mercury kills all her
other ex-friends.
Hallucination! Giwark Power Up!
Mercury!
[Grunts]
Are you okay?
Sailor Mercury! Ami Mizuno! You
cheated on all your tests!
[Wincing]
You're nothing more than a
disgusting cheater!
Yeah you are!
[Wincing]
Mercury!
What is it?
What's wrong?
Ami Mizuno, you big cheater!
You're disgusting!
Cheater, you're a fraud!
Ami Mizuno, you cheat!
Cheater! I'm tired of you
cheating!
All you've ever done is cheat.
Cheater!
No! [Crying]
What's going on with her?
Mercury, calm down!
Someone's controlling her!
[All Yelling At Ami]
[Gasp]
You heard them Sailor Mercury,
kill all those bad mouthed
fools!
Get rid of them so they can't
call you names anymore!
Come on now, I'm so looking
forward to watching you wipe
them out! [Laughing]
[Gasp] Oh no, what is she doing?
It looks like she's going to use
her Shine Aqua Illusion!
Mercury! You've gotta
snap out of it!
Please don't buy into
those hallucinations!
Mercury, please stop!
[Screams]
Mercury, don't attack us!
Please don't!
It's okay, Sailor Mercury would
never harm any of us. Never!
I know that, because I trust
her.
[Gasps]
Why are you waiting Sailor
Mercury? It's time to destroy
them.
You must never forgive what they
said about you.
You're the one I'll never
forgive!
What?!
[All] Huh?!
Sine Aqua Illusion!
[Screams]
[Gasps]
[Grunts]
Why weren't you fooled by my
hallucinations? How did you
resist my Dark Power?
Your Dark Power can never
deceive us! Our hearts are
connected by trust in one
another.
[Happy Sighs]
You tell her!
Damn it!
Now finish her, Sailor Moon!
[Gasp]
Hmm.
Moon Princess Halation!
[Gasps]
[Screams]
Good work. You successfully
stopped another enemy plan.
As always, the power of your
friendship is nothing short of
impressive. Farewell.
Giwark failed?!
I told you that lazing around in
a tub wasn't the way to get the
job done.
[Laughing]
Don't worry. I'll find a new
Negative Point soon.
And Saphir, let me make this
perfectly clear. There is only
one person allowed to watch me
bathe.
Now get the hell out!
[Laughing]
Next time I'll destroy anyone
who gets in my way.
Thanks Ami, for not letting
those hallucinations fool you
about us.
No worries.
Besides, I felt that all of you
truly believed that I would
never cheat, am I right?
Hmm.
Okay, even if you had some
momentary doubts...
...we're bound by trust, and
that's all that matters!
That's right.
Hi guys, how's it goin?
Oh no.
Hey, Mizuno! Congratulations
to you, for scoring the best
grade on this semester's final
exam.
Good work! Can you give us
pointers on how to study for it
next time?
Do your best. That's the only
secret I know.
There's no particular method.
Just know all the material.
What's up with them?
Those are the same students who
spread the nasty rumors about
Ami being a cheater.
Now don't be angry, Usagi.
You're forgetting that everyone
at the Cram school was affected
by the Dark Power.
That's right. You should
be angry at the enemy.
Hmm.
Usagi, why don't you come
join our study sessions?
Ew!
Ahh! Studying makes me crazy!
Studying! I'm getting a rash!
I'm itchy all over!
[Sigh] That's our Usagi all
right.
[All Laughing]
Hey Chibi-Usa, who was that girl
that came by to visit you?
Oh, you mean Momo? We go to
the same school! She's my best
friend.
Yeah? Well she was acting
kind of strange.
What?!
I think the enemy is controlling
your friend!
Sailor Moon! You have to get her
away from them!
Next time on Sailor Moon R: "The
Dark Gate is Completed! The
Targeted Elementary School!"
The moonlight is a messenger
of love.