Chibi-Usa stole my Silver
Crystal and tried to return
to the future. That's what
alerted Rubeus as to her
whereabouts. The other
Sailor Guardians raced to
protect her, but were sucked
up into Rubeus' UFO.
Chibi-Usa! Everyone
is gone because of
you!
Listen to me, Sailor
Moon! Even though you
avoided capture with
the others, you might
as well give
yourself up!
Face it, without your
fellow Sailor Guardians,
there isn't much you can
do on your own to save
your precious city. However,
I'll allow you time to
think it over. No rush.
But I will return to this
spot three hours from
now, at three a.m.
And I'll expect you to
have made up your mind
by then.
[evil laughter]
No!
"Defeat Rubeus: The
Battle in Space"
[laughing]
Hmph!
[giggling]
Just idly standing
around waiting, Rubeus?
You wouldn't have to if
you had gotten rid of
Sailor Moon and the Rabbit
when you had a chance.
Hmph! You, being a
woman, wouldn't
understand.
I want to savor every
moment of eliminating
that girl. I want her
to suffer!
Oh... Is that so?
Now that I have these
hostages, Sailor Moon
is demoralized. She'll
come here to get them
back. And when she does, I
will slowly and painfully
kill her, right in front
of their eyes.
Really?
I hope it all goes
according to plan.
I'll pray for your
success.
[laughing]
Ha! Watch me,
woman.
I'll show you just how
powerful I can be.
Chibi-Usa...
Well...
Mamo, I'm pretty sure
you're Tuxedo Mask,
right?
Uh, yeah. I guess
it's time to fess
up.
Knew it. Nothing
surprises me
anymore.
Especially after
finding out that
Usagi is also
Sailor Moon.
By the way, Chibi-Usa,
did you finally return
the Silver Crystal
brooch to Usako?
Mm-hm...
I don't know why this
didn't work the way
its supposed to.
And if it did, you would
have taken the Silver
Crystal with you when you
went back to the
future. Right?
Uh...
Chibi-Usa, I want us to
stop keeping secrets
from each other.
What exactly were you
planning to do with the
Silver Crystal when you
got it back home.
It's for Mommy. I need
the Silver Crystal to
rescue her from those
bad people.
Please! Chibi-Usa!
Straight answers...
What happened? Tell
me everything you
can remember.
I don't know.
Chibi-Usa!
I really don't know much
of anything. Those people
just showed up out of
nowhere...
[sobbing]
The large unidentified
flying object that
appeared in the sky over
the Juban District, seems
to have flown off into
the night. However, there
is a growing anxiety among
residents that the object
may have altered
something in their
neighborhood.
Only thirty
minutes left.
Usagi, what happened
to Mamoru and Chibi-
Usa? Where'd they go?
I think their up on
the roof together.
I guess he's having
a little talk with
her.
She's making it
so difficult!
I really don't care that
she's being targeted. I
know I should protect her
but I don't feel like
doing that anymore!
Not after what she did!
Usagi!
I almost feel like handing
over the Silver Crystal and
Chibi-Usa to the enemy, just
so I can get everyone back!
If she hadn't appeared,
we wouldn't have gotten
into this whole mess,
and this city would
have stayed peaceful.
Usagi! I don't like
to hear you talking
like this! Do you
mean it?
[whimpering cry]
Of course not...
But it's pretty obvious
I'm not mature enough
to remain strong in
times like these.
It'll be alright.
I'm tired. And I'm
sorry for being so
negative.
It's okay. Why don't you
rest for a minute while
Luna and I put our heads
together to come up
with a workable plan.
Thank you. I think
I'll go out on the
balcony for a bit and
try to clear my head.
[worried sigh]
That's it. I'm just
going to have to
confront the enemy
alone.
If I bring the Silver
Crystal along with me,
maybe that'll distract
him just enough.
At the very least it
should draw his attention
away from Chibi-Usa, and
keep her safe...
I can just hear my old
self saying, "I'm scared!",
"I'm sleepy!", "I don't want
to do this thing all
alone!" Noooo!
I guess my crying
days are over.
Hold on, everyone. I'm
coming to rescue you,
now!
As I see it, our best
option is for one of us
to hand Rubeus a fake
Silver Crystal, in
order to buy some
time...
...While the other sneaks
aboard the spacecraft and
rescues everyone before
he can react.
But won't he be
expecting Chibi-
Usa to deliver it?
Uh...
Hmm...
Ah! I've got it! What
if the two of us
disguise ourselves as
Chibi-Usa!
Hmm...
I'm the Rabbit! I'm
the Rabbit! I'm the
Rabbit! I'm the Rabbit!
I'm the- Ahhhh!
I'm afraid we're not
going to be able to
make this work.
Uh-huh...
The front door's wide
open! Where's Usako?!
I can't find her!
What?!
She's not here!
I suspected this...
What? Are you thinking
that she, you know, took
off without a word to go
rescue the Sailor
Guardians herself?
It's entirely
possible.
But that's total
suicide! Rubeus
will kill her for
sure!
[gasp]
Chibi-Usa?
Chibi-Usa!
She must've run
out after Usagi!
You're probably right.
Those two are on the
same wavelength.
Man, if it weren't for
the age difference, those
girls could easily be
identical twins.
Moon Crystal Power!
Make Up!
♪ Sailor Moon!
I'm sorry, Mamo, Luna,
and Artemis, for sneaking
off on you. But I don't
want to put anyone else
in danger. So I'm going
alone.
[gasp]
[evil laughter]
You showed up on time,
Sailor Moon, and the
Rabbit, too!
The Rabbit?!
Chibi-Usa! What
are you doing here?
I'm going, too. It's my
fault the Sailor Guardians
were taken away, when all
they were trying to
do was protect me.
No! Don't you get it?
If you come, you'll
be doing what the
enemy wants.
[screaming]
We're too late!
We can't stop
them! Damn!
Usagi!
Sailor Moon R!
[gasp]
[gasps]
What have you
done to them.
[chuckling]
Nice of you to
come, Sailor Moon.
And I appreciate your
bringing the Rabbit
along, as well.
You bastard!
Agh!
[chuckling]
Go ahead, laugh! The
joke's on you. This
child isn't your
elusive Rabbit!
She's my very
disobedient
cousin!
Huh?
Come on, did you seriously
think I would simply hand
the Rabbit over to you?
Dummy!
You completely
fell for it!
Huh! I'll have plenty
of time to test whether
that's true or not,
later.
But first...
I plan to deal
with you!
Fine!
Now, little cousin. You
need to move away, find
some spot where you'll
be safe.
Oh. Uh. All right.
Okay, bring
it on!
Hmph!
What are we going to
do? If that craft goes
into orbit in outer space,
there's no way
they can escape!
Yeah!
Usako!
[screaming]
That was merely a warm-
up exercise. Now you
will pay for the bitter
experiences you
have given me.
Moon Princess Halation!
Hmph!
Hey, what happened?
Moon Princess Halation
isn't working!
Agh!
My body feels heavy.
[laughing]
Shall I tell you
what's happening?
My ship enables me to
amplify my power to
play with the forces
of nature.
You're experiencing
my super-gravity
right now.
In case you're wondering,
I can do the opposite, too.
Hah!
[screaming]
Where are we?
I thought you'd
never ask.
Outer space. Tens of
thousands of meters
above the earth's
surface.
It's impossible
for you to escape.
[screaming]
Chibi-Usa!
Ha! Just as I thought,
she is the Rabbit.
[groaning]
I suggest you stop
your futile rescue
efforts...
...There's a high voltage
shield surrounding them
that will zap you every
time you try to get near.
[screaming]
[groaning]
Chibi-Usa!
Well, guess it's just
about time to finish
you off.
[screaming]
Crawl like a toad while
my gravity grinds you
into muck!
Hah!
[groaning]
[evil laughter]
Die!
[groaning]
[evil laughter]
[struggling grunts]
[gasp]
[grunting]
I'll never give up.
I will save
my friends!
And I will...
...defeat you!
That's impossible! You
can't stand up in the
super-gravity field!
If Chibi-Usa has the
courage to try to break
through your high-voltage
barrier...
Then I, Sailor Moon, am
determined to find the
strength to do nothing
less!
Hmph! You're not as
helpless as I thought.
I underestimated you
quite a bit.
Agh!
I'm going to come at
you with full power,
that would crush any
person alive.
Moon Princess Halation!
[powerful grunt]
Ah! Sailor Moon!
This must be it! The
source of his super-
powers!
[screaming]
Everybody's here
because of me. So
it's my responsibility
to find a way to
stop this thing and
save them all.
[grunting scream]
Die! Sailor Moon!
[screaming]
Hm!
[groaning]
Annoying Rabbit! She
must've found my power
amplifier!
Hah! You just
sealed your
own fate!
Now, die!
Moon Princess Halation!
Huh?!
Stubborn girl!
Now, Chibi-Usa!
Do it!
Right!
[screaming]
Agh!
Damn you two...
[gasps]
Does anyone know
where we are?
The last thing I can
remember is Rubeus
capturing us.
I'm sorry. This
is my fault.
Chibi-Usa!
I'm so happy.
You're all okay.
Sailor Moon!
[evil laughter]
[gasps]
You think everything's
okay now? You fools!
This ship is out of
control and is going
to blow up at any
given moment.
And when that happens,
you'll all become space
dust.
Why should we
believe you?
That would mean you're
gonna end up the same
way!
[laughing]
Exactly! I won't ever
be able to return to
the future!
However, at least I'll
have the satisfaction of
knowing you're coming
along with me.
[screaming]
Ah! Rubeus!
We'd better figure a way
out of here quick, or
we're all going to go up
in flames with him!
We're up in a
spaceship. Where
are we gonna go?
There is a way, but
it's a long shot.
Huh?!
Wait, Mercury, are
you thinking of using
Sailor Teleport?
Yes.
That's nuts! Sailor
Moon used up all her
energy, and don't forget
we have Chibi-Usa
with us here, as well!
If we put our hearts and
minds together, I believe
it's possible to make it
work! We have to take
that chance and try!
My energy is
just fine!
Chibi-Usa, concentrate
with all your heart and
mind.
Hm! I'll do my best!
That's the spirit.
You'll get a treat
when we get home.
I want hotcakes,
with lots of
syrup.
It's a deal.
All right! Let's
get started.
Moon Crystal Power!
Mercury Star Power!
Mars Star Power!
Jupiter Star Power!
Venus Star Power!
Sailor Teleport!
[grunting]
Damn it!
[laughing]
What a mess, Rubeus.
Ah, Esmeraude. You came
to check up on me and
I'm so glad you did.
Now take me back to
the future with you!
We need to hurry. This
ship is going to explode
in two minutes.
Oh, tough luck.
Esmeraude?!
You allowed Sailor Moon,
the Sailor Guardians and
the Rabbit to escape.
And now you want
me to save you?
You're a truly
pathetic specimen.
Our glorious clan
really has no use
for an incompetent
man who has failed
in his mission. Do us
all a favor and vanish
with this ship.
[laughing]
Esmeraude! No!
Don't leave me!
Esmeraude!
[gasp]
We're back!
[cheering]
Hey, Sailor Moon! Don't
forget, you promised me
hotcakes with syrup!
And I want the best
kind, that are made
from scratch!
What?!
[giggling]
Usagi is a horrible
cook! I think you'd
be better off settling
for take-out.
Nope! I don't
want that!
I'll make 'em, but
I can't promise
they'll be edible!
[laughing]
Prince Demande, it was
just more than Rubeus
was able to handle.
Distressing... I
thought he was more
capable than that.
Well then, Esmeraude.
You'll have to see to
it that you don't
repeat Rubeus' failures.
Yes, my lord. You
can count on me.
[chuckling]
Everything I've ever
wanted will be mine.
Everything.
♪ Sailor Moon!
Mommy! Mommy!
I'm scared!
Snap out of it! Ya
gotta hang in there,
Chibi-Usa!
Please, Sailor Moon!
I need your help!
Save my mommy!
Sailor Moon is
invincible. Trust
me, Chibi-Usa.
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"The Mysterious New Guardian:
Sailor Pluto Appears."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.