(Usagi)
Mako... Minako...
What's wrong?
(Usagi)
This is not a
good time to be
fighting..!
(Usagi)
A powerful enemy has
appeared and things are
starting to get scary!
(Usagi)
We've got to power
up and keep moving!
(Usagi)
Come on, you two!
Let's work together
to pushing them!
[groan] All this sun
and heat is really
annoying me...
Speaking of annoying...
...what is up with
these couples? Couple
flirting needs to be
outlawed...
[yawn] Hope everybody
shows up pretty soon.
(Makoto)
Minako..!
Hm?
(out of breath)
So so sorry!
You're late, Mako.
Oh, you're upset...
I was only a
little late. You
gotta chill out!
It's too hot
to chill out!
I think you're
jealous of all
these cozy couples.
No I'm not!
I'm just teasing you!
C'mon, Minako, lighten
up already!
By the way, Ami said
she can't make it.
She's too busy with
summer courses.
And Rei's busy doing
shrine-maiden work.
Oh, bummer! I thought
it'd be fun if we all
met up and went
shopping together...
Oh! What about Usagi?
Have you ever known
Usagi to show up on time?
[giggles]
Yeah! That'll never
happen! Haha!
(Usagi)
Dispute Over Love:
Minako and Makoto's
Conflict"
Usagi is... later
than late...
She's just totally
hopeless... Hm?
Huh?
Hey Chibi-Usa
Hiii!
Yeah, hi! Where
ya going, bun-head?
You're trying to
hit on me? How
immature..!
This is exactly why
the girls in my class
make fun of boys like
you all the time!
What did you say!?
[gasp]
Take it back!
Or else....
(Thinking)
Maybe I should...
(Makoto)
What's going
on here?
Huh?
Put her down. You
should be ashamed
of yourselves.
[nervous laughter]
We're sorry!
That was pretty awful
of them to pick on
the new kid in town.
Don't worry
about them!
Boys will be boys,
and for whatever reason
they always tease the
girls they like.
Oh please, come on!
There was no 'like'
involved, they were
bullies!
You try to put a
romantic spin on
everything...
I think you go too far
the other way and get
over anxious about guys
all the time.
Really, is that so?
How do you figure?
You immediately judge
every man who comes along!
You think they're
just like the guy
who rejected you.
(Minako)
You'll never find
true love that way.
At least I'm trying!
Why aren't you?
I've never seen you
looking for anybody!
You just sit here, sulking
watching all the couples.
I'm doing fine
all by myself!
Oh yeah?
(Chibi-Usa)
Hey! Calm down!
I've already got my
guy picked out! And
I plan on marrying him!
I'm gonna be
Mamo's bride!
What did you
just say!?
Try saying that
again!!
I said, I'm gonna
be Mamo's bride.
GRRRR!!
I'm the one who
calls him "Mamo,"
not you!
But he dumped you.
(Usagi)
Ugh! Keep your
mouth shut!
Why do they
always fight?
Take back what you
said. I don't appreciate
you judging me!
Why are you so attached
to your old crush, anyway?
It's not healthy!
You're the one who's
stuck and can't let go!
No, it's you!
It's you, Minako!
It's you, Mako!
[girls arguing]
[giggle] You 3 girls are just
going to become old maids if
you don't hurry up and get over
the guys that dumped you.
-What an awful brat!
Ugh, these people are
sweltering in the heat.
They can't even control
their own weather...
...How much longer
must we stay in this
primitive world..?
There's no need to
get so worked up,
my dear old sister.
Besides, why are you
so eager to return? It's
not like you have someone
waiting for you...
Watch your mouth!
There they go
again... Always
squabbling with
each other...
Did I hit a nerve?
I never bring up how
unlucky you are with
men...
I know how being
dumped has made you
rather... touchy.
I'm doing just
fine on my own!
Sounds like you
two are bored here.
Master Rubeus...
The length of time that
we spend in this world
depends on how well you
handle your assignments.
I've found another Crystal
Point that could use your
handiwork...
(Petz)
What is this place?
(Berthier)
Oh! Are those
gemstones?
(Calaveras)
Hmph! They look cheap.
I wouldn't call them
real gemstones...
(Rubeus)
Whether they are or not, human
girls believe if you make a wish
on one, your wish will come true
Ha! What a stupid
primitive superstition!
Calaveras, I'm assigning
you to handle this one...
Your mission is to
replace the Crystal Power
in that shop with Dark
Power...
But Master Rubeus...
I'm overqualified! My
field of expertise is
high-grade gemstones.
Calaveras..!
So please, consider
reassigning this
particular job.
Come back here!
[sigh] This assignment may
be beneath me, but now that
I think about it, it's not a
good idea to anger Master Rubeus
Jamanen...
How may I serve
you, ma'am..?
Jamanen, tell Master Rubeus
that I have had a change of
heart and I will accept the job
that he just offered me...
(Berthier)
You're a little
late, sister.
Berthier..?
Sorry, but Petz
volunteered to
take on the job.
She's already left.
What!? I'm not letting
her take this one from
me!
Come with me, Jamanen!
Well, see ya later!
Come on, guys! Stop being
upset with each other!
We're going shopping
together, isn't this
fun!?
I am not the
least bit upset.
Neither am I!
[nervous laugh]
No doubt about it,
they're upset.
Agh! -Ooof!
Heey! Who bumped
into me!? Huh?
'Your wish will be granted
for sure. Omazinai House'??
Yeah, I've heard of
this place. They sell
gemstones that are supposed
to grant wishes.
Oh yeah?
Whattaya say!?
Let's go inside!
So should we follow
her? Whattaya think?
[gasp] Hmph!
Gemstones that grant
wishes... could it be?
(Calaveras)
Amethysts will keep your
boyfriend faithful to you.
(Calaveras)
If you lack the courage
to tell him how much you
love him, then try diamonds.
We're having a
sale. They're all
very affordable...
Wow!
Lovely!
I wish he'd fall in
love with me and our
love would last
forever!
[gasps]
[evil chuckle]
I really really
despise him so
much!
I don't believe
in love at all...
Foolish girls!
Wishing upon our special
energy stones makes the very
opposite of that you're
wishing for happen...
...Now you're
filled with hate.
Soon this entire area will be
filled with Dark Power, and
won't be able to function as
a barrier for Crystal Tokyo.
(Usagi)
Wow! Mako, Minako!
Take a look!
Huh?
Are these all
lucky charms!?
Oh boy! There's even one
to improve your grades!
And a charm to make you
prettier!
Huh?
[gasp] What's this!?
This is stupid. You
can't tell me that
the kids these days
would fall for this thing.
Oh boy!
You're really into
this kind of stuff,
aren't you, Usagi?
Huh? Guh!
Usagi...?
You're gonna
choke yourself!
[big gulp]
That's tasty!
[groan]
Good chugging... So
What's that juice
gonna do for you?
Don't tell me it's
supposed to make your
love come back to you
or something...
Uh huh...
Welcome, young ladies.
If you're looking for
love charms, we have
quite a few of them
in the back.
We have a very nice
selection, I think
you'll find what you
want.
Please, follow me.
Wow, awesome!
When you make a
wish upon them,
that wish is going
to come true.
What about a heart that's
grown cold? Is there a
gemstone that you can
wish on to heat it up?
Of course! This gemstone
can bring back your love...
And I think you'll
find that it's not
too pricey...
Oooo... Whatever's in
there revives love?
[gasp]
Mako... Minako.
Hm? Oh!
Oh no! I am so not
hung up on a past
love and want to bring
him back to me!
Right. No, me
neither...
[nervous laughter]
[evil chuckle]
Sailor Moon!
R!
Sailor Moon R!
[running]
I can't see! What
are they doing in
there..!?
Don't move!
[frightened gasp]
Hands in the air!
(Chibi-Usa)
Mamo..!
So what are you doing
here, Chibi-Usa?
[crazed laugh]
I want this one! Oh!
That one too! But I
don't have enough money!
Which one would
yoube interested
in, miss?
Mako, I think the guy
who dumped you, did so
because he has very
poor taste in girls.
Huh?
You were dumped!?
I'm not gonna
listen to you
bad-mouth him!
It came out wrong!
I just meant that
you deserve true love.
After all, you're
my good friend.
Thanks, Minako.
You know what? He's
ancient history!
That's right!
Huh?
[clearing throat]
But never the less,
he was quite a
wonderful boyfriend...
He set the bar high.
Now I have to find
someone even better
than him!
Well then, I'll
do the same!
I'm going to make an
all-out effort to find
somebody I like, even
better than Alan!
Good. And I bet you're
still gonna keep hitting
on Mamoru, right?
That's right!
Well you'd better give
up, cause Mamo's mine!
[gasp]
[gasp] Mamo..!
I don't believe it! The
charm juice did work!
Usako...
Let's go, Mamo! You
can buy me a popsicle!
Sorry, I have things
to do. Why don't you
hang out with these
girls today?
But... Mamo!
[sigh] It happened
again. Fate just seems
to keep bringing us
together.
I'm pretty sure they
should be shopping
in this area...
I left work early
to do this. I hope
we find them. It'll
suck if we don't.
This is all your fault!
Mamo went away because
of YOU!
Why are you
so stupid!?
Oh pipe down,
will ya!? You're
making me crazy!
So I was a little
sappy when I saw
him, is that so wrong!?
I think it's your
fault for acting
so spoiled!
It's your fault for
talking about the
charm juice, dummy!
Grrr....
(Usagi)
It's your fault!
(Chibi-Usa)
Nuh uh! It's YOURS!
Ughhh... Cut
it out!!
Hm?
Huh?
Petz, you've got
to focus so that
we can proceed with
our plans here.
What are you
two talking about?
All your chatter about
love and romance is
just... rubbish!
You think love
is rubbish?
Absolutely...
Go ahead. Make a wish
on this gemstone.
You'll forget love, but
remember to despise all men.
These woman don't seem
like ordinary sales
clerks! Usagi, be careful!
Mhm!
Jamanen!
Yes ma'am.
[frightened gasps]
So a droid was behind
this all along!
[evil chuckles]
Usagi... Get Chibi-Usa
out of here..!
I'm not going
anywhere with you!
No time for that
now! Come on!
[grunts]
[[gasps]
There's no way out...
[gasp]
I'm going to kill you
so you'll shut up about
stupid things like
being in love--
--and wishing for
love to come back!
[gasp]
[grunts]
[evil chuckle]
Usagi!
I feel bad about
doing this, but
you have to die.
(Minako)
Stop right there!
[attack grunt]
[gasps]
[coughing]
How impudent!
Luna!
Usagi! Over there!
Got it!
If we don't want
to turn into man-
haters like these
two women...
...we'll need to
take care of em.
Exactly.
Jupiter Star Power...
Make... Up!
Venus Star Power...
♪Sailor Moon...
Sailor Moon...
Sailor Moon...♪
Your days of toying
with the hearts of
young girls are over!
What!?
We won't forgive you for
ruining their special
moment of feeling love!
That's right! In the
name of venus, the
guardian planet of love,
we'll punish you!
And who are you!?
Sailor Jupiter!
And Sailor Venus!
But it's impolite to
ask others who they are
unless you intend to
introduce yourselves...
You insolent brat!
I am Petz, the oldest, and
if I do say so myself, the
prettiest of the four
Spectre Sisters...
[evil laugh]
I'm much more popular than
my sister, Petz...
Men are totally
captivated
by my looks...
I'm Calaveras...
Uhhh...
Please..!
Hmph!
What the heck...?
This is pretty
awkward....
All this talk about
men and love... Who
needs it!?
[angry shout]
Hiya!
Hiiiyah!
[grunt]
[frightened shout]
[choking]
Ha! How pathetic!
[whimper]
Hiyah!
[grunt]
[shouts]
[struggling grunts]
Always obsessing about
love and believing in
your man makes a woman
grow weak!
You're wrong! Love gives you
the strength and courage to
take on almost anything!
QUIET!
[painful screams]
Die!!!
[screaming]
[growl]
[screams]
Burning.... Mandala!!!
[relief gasps]
[gasp]
Sailor Mars! Sailor
Mercury!
Huh?
Sailor Venus! Let's
teach them a lesson!
This is the power
of those who believe
in love..!
[power yell]
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
Venus Love Me Chain!
Useless!
[grunts]
[attack yells]
[gasps]
Calaveras, we'd
better retreat...
Jamanen! Finish
this up for us!
You can count on
me, ma'am.
we're done here,
and so are you,
Sailor Guardians.
You can't leave!
I'm taking over
now. Let's fight!
[fear gasps]
(Chibi-Usa)
I don't wanna
stay in here..!
You'l be safe in
there! I have to
go check on some
things!
I'll be back!
Usagi, time to
transform.
I'm on it.
Moon Crystal Power...
Make... Up..!
♪Sailor Moon...
Sailor Moon...
Sailor Moon...♪
♪Sailor Moon...
Sailor Moon...
Sailor Moon...♪
[grunts]
[evil chuckle]
(Sailor Moon)
Hold it, you!
Mercury? Mars? Where
did you come from?
Not now, Sailor Moon!
Hurry up and
finish her!
Huh?
[attack yell]
Jeez! There's barely
enough time for my
catch phrase montage!
Moon Princess Halation!
[death scream]
[relieved sigh]
[surprised gasp]
(Makoto)
Stop doing that, Usagi.
It can't be good for you.
[gulp] I'm gonna drink
this whole thing so I
can see Mamo again..!
You're gonna drown
yourself, Usagi.
Well, it's the best way
to sure her stupidity.
Hey! Why are you
being so mean to
me, Rei!?
I'm only speaking
the truth...
(Rei)
USAGI!!!
(Usagi)
Whoops! Sorry!
(Rei)
Not good enough! I need
some payback! Quit hiding
your face!
(Usagi)
What are you doing!? I
already said I was sorry!
(Waitress)
If you two are going to be
squirting juice at each other
you'll have to go outside.
(Usagi & Rei)
Make her go! She
started it!
(Mamoru)
When it's hot outside
there's nothing like
spicy foods!
(Mamoru)
Especially curry that
burns your tongue like
a flame of passion!
(Usagi)
Mamo, I'm going to capture your
heart with my very own super
special spicy curry! It's HOT!
(Mamoru)
Just don't put any green peas on
top of it, it'll just wipe out
my passion...
(Mamoru)
That is, I mean,
for curry....
(Usagi)
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"Usagi's Parental Love: The
Curry Romance Triangle"
(USagi)
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.