Demande, hear me
out! Saphir hasn't
betrayed you.
Please listen to what
he has to say about
the things he saw
in the future!
And what
he found out
about Wiseman!
That man is just
using you to
accomplish his own
evil objectives.
That's right, Demande...
your real enemy
is Wiseman!
Saphir Dies. Wiseman's Trap.
The mysterious object that
suddenly appeared in the
middle of Tokyo...
...has brought
traffic to a standstill,
and completely shut down
the Metropolitan Area.
Those of you
living in the
surrounding vicinities
should stay away.
We are on high
alert until
authorities are able
to assess the danger.
This has become
a major disaster!
Do we have a
plan in mind?
First we have to find
out how powerful that
giant malefic black
crystal is...
...before we're
able to come
up with any sort
of counter measure.
So that means we'll
just have to wait and
see what Mamoru and Artemis
are able to discover.
Until then, there's
not much to do
except stand by.
[upset quivering]
Chibi-Usa...
These TV reports
are getting me worried.
Perhaps we should be
thinking of evacuating
like everyone else.
Mom! What's that?
Huh...what?
This...Oh.
One, two, three, four,
five...Oh dear. I brought
out an extra cup.
Huh...A pink cup.
I wonder why I
felt I needed to
bring out this particular
cup with all of yours.
Thanks for
the cake!
How strange!
With Luna P gone,
memories of Chibi-Usa
should have been erased
from everyone's minds.
Do you suppose that
deep down they still
remember her?
Luna...Do you
think it's wrong
that I actually
miss her?
Huh?
Now that Chibi-Usa's
gone, everything's
back to the way it
should be.
There's no one
jumping on my
bed and bugging me.
But this house
feels so empty
without her.
[quiet sobs]
I know.
It's gonna be
alright, Usagi.
But how?
We'll work together.
We'll find a way by
combining our powers.
I'm sure we can remove
her evil and bring
back the girl
we love.
You're right...
Thank you.
O'emptiness..O'silence..
Obey me!
Swear your allegiance
to the almighty
Death Phantom!
The one who shall
rule the universe
is not someone
like Prince Demande...
...With his fleeting
dreams of power.
But someone like the
Death Phantom, who
wields absolute
power!
Ohh...foolish
Prince Demande.
You shall do my bidding
and bring on silence
and chaotic barrenness.
And then bestow this
devastation upon the true
conquerer of this world...
the Death Phantom!
Purge the universe
of all impurities,
like the living.
So that only
emptiness prevails
everywhere!
[unpleasant grunt]
Who's there?
Hmph!
[small chuckle]
Just as I thought!
He's only been
using my brother
all along.
Curse you, Wiseman!
[disturbed grunt]
There's been an
unnatural surge
of energy in the crystal.
Wiseman again
I bet.
I must stop this.
That's better. I can't let
the reactor get out
of control. It needs
to cool down.
Saphir.
[surprised gasp]
Wiseman!
I order you
to put that
back right now.
You cannot order
me to do
anything.
I will talk to
my brother first
and then decide
what's best.
Death Phantom, ruler
of the entire universe,
is giving you this order.
Defying Death Phantom,
will result in your
total destruction.
You've referred to
him before. Who
exactly is this
Death Phantom?
He is a supreme God who
intends to restore glorious
silence and crystal-clear
emptiness to the universe.
In time, he will
eliminate every
one of you filthy
creatures.
Who...Who
are you really?
It is not yet time
for me to reveal
that information.
[painful reaction]
Wiseman!
You bastard!
You shall perish
without finding
what you seek!
[painful scream]
He managed
to get away...
But it doesn't
matter. I know
exactly where
he's going.
[sinister giggle]
The Dark Gate
is coming along
quite nicely.
Very soon, the reactor
will have reached it's
peak energy output.
Then if we're
able to send
it through...
This world
will disappear.
A new history
will be written.
[chuckling in unison]
[Citizens panicking]
Please remain calm
and evacuate in an
orderly manner.
Should we leave?
Well it looks
like everyone
else is.
We'd better pack
up our shop and get
out of here too.
Right. Huh?
Is that...
What's wrong, Petz?
[stumbling painfully]
Brother!
Don't do it! This
is exactly what
Wiseman...
The smell..
of grass..
brings back memories.
Look at that!
A flower, brother!
Yup. It's pretty.
And unusual!
You're right. With
the harsh environment on
Nemesis to find a flower
is almost a miracle.
However, one day
I will invade planet
earth and reclaim it
for us.
Then you'll have
a whole garden
filled with
flowers.
[pleased gasp]
Yeah, you'll get
our earth back. I
know you can!
I'm sure of it!
[pleased sigh]
Come...Let's go
my prince.
[shocked gasp]
Wiseman! Stop,
now!
[gasp]
Brother, no!
Stay away from
him! He's using you!
Don't you see that?
Brother...Brother!!
[painful gasp]
Where am I?
[soft sigh]
[relieved sigh]
I'm glad
you're awake,
Master Saphir.
Petz, is
it really you?
Yes.
Where am I?
In my home,
on earth.
That's right. I was told
that you and your sisters
decided to live in this
world after you betrayed us.
I will accept
my punishment.
But..Please Master,
you must forgive
my three sisters.
I take full
responsibility.
[rueful chuckle]
You have nothing
to worry about.
I didn't come
to this world
to punish you
or your sisters.
[surprised breath]
Why is she tending
to him? The last I
heard she hated all men.
We should get
out, before he
gets better!
What if..he changes
his mind and wants
to punish us!
I think we're
going to be
alright.
Huh?
Right now..let's
leave them alone
for a little while.
Do you know
something we
don't?
The truth is..not
so long ago Petz
loved him.
What's that?!
Saphir has gone mad.
He removed the control
module from the
reactor to stop it
from functioning.
We must get it
back, and he must
be eliminated
immediately!
He has fled from
this world, betraying us,
and all of our people.
Ridiculous! Saphir would
never do that. There must
be a reason!
So, does that mean
you would like to cancel
our long awaited plans?
Well, I-
Nonsense. I will
take it upon myself
to retrieve the
module for the reactor.
I just can't believe
it. Why Saphir?
Sailor Moon, R!
Would you
like some?
Thank you.
Something's different..
about you.
I'm not quite sure what
it is. But I feel very
relaxed and comfortable
being with you now.
Oh...
I guess that's
because I'm very
content with
myself now.
I've come to learn
true kindness and trust
from Sailor Moon and
her circle of friends.
Sailor Moon, huh?
While it's true there are
some some difficulties
living in this world as
compared to Nemesis..
It's filled with warmth
and joy. We're grateful
for being given the chance
to experience this.
I like how the
people living here
truly seem to
care about one another.
I'm finding it to
be quite a wonderful
way to live.
Is destroying this
world really the
right thing to do?
What kind of
future are we
trying to create?
I never questioned
our reasons for
revenge.
But maybe that was because
Wiseman was manipulating us
into believing that it was our
only way for survival.
[upset reaction]
Master Saphir?
I need to leave..now.
[painful grunt]
Master Saphir!
I must see my brother
as soon as I can.
How typical of you.
Always putting Prince
Demande before
yourself.
I'm sorry. I
need to go!
You can't leave
in this condition!
He needs to know about
Wiseman's true
intentions right away!
[gasp]
No!
But Petz...
I get it now,
I know who
hurt you.
If you go to Prince
Demande in this condition
you won't have the energy
to stand up to him...
And you could...
[quiet sobs]
Petz...
[small sob]
If something..should
happen to you..
[quiet sob]
I have go
and make him
do the right
thing.
[scared reaction]
Put yourself
in my place.
If one of your sisters
was going down the wrong
path, would you be able to
just turn away and ignore her?
[quivering sob]
He's all I have.
Prince Demande and I
are all that's left
of our family.
But-
Don't worry. I'm just
going to talk to him.
That's all that's going
to happen.
[quivering sob]
When things are
settled, I'll
come back here.
I'll wait for you.
It will be okay
Petz, you'll see.
[upset whimper]
Why did Petz just
let him walk
out of here
all alone?
He was so injured.
Shouldn't we follow him
and be his backup?
How? We can't.
Not anymore.
You're forgetting that
we no longer have
any powers.
I'm afraid we'd
just get in the
way.
All we can
do is wait..
and hope he
returns safely.
[worried breath]
This is Usagi.
Oh, Koan!
Usagi, please..
help us!
[stumbling in pain]
[sinister laughing]
Huh?
How nice of you to
show up. It saves me the
trouble of having to
go look for you.
Don't interfere,
Black Lady!
I have
business to discuss
with my brother.
That's too bad.
Sorry to say you'll
be dead before
you see him.
[grunt]
[shocked reaction]
Hold it
right there!
Sailor Moon?!
Ugh!
You're here
too?
Stop, Chibi-Usa!
Don't make another
move to try and
harm him!
[surprised gasp]
Please snap out of
it, Chibi-Usa! Wiseman
has brainwashed you!
I don't know what you're
talking about. This is the
real me. I'm not brainwashed.
You are! Why
can't you see it?!
Enough!
Luna P...Transform!
Chibi-Usa!
[startled reaction]
Crescent..Beam!
Oh no
you don't!
[painful scream]
Bubble..Spray!
[painful groan]
Why are you
protecting me?
Saphir, now's your
chance. Talk to your
brother while
she's distracted.
Wait, how did
you know about
that?
Actually, we really
don't know the exact details.
But Koan and her sisters
asked us to help you.
That's insane!
You could have been
walking into a trap!
Perhaps. It's just a habit
we picked up from being
around our clumsy but
caring team leader for so long.
We tend to trust people
sometimes, even if they're
our enemies.
And the most
trusting of us
is Sailor Moon.
[puzzled reaction]
You thought you could
stop me? This isn't over.
[battle cry]
[coughing in unison]
Chibi-Usa! Become
your true self!
Moon Crystal Power!
Not falling for
that trick again!
[fearful gasp]
And now I'll
serve up..my power!
Venus Love me...
Huh?!
[painful screaming]
[fearful gasp]
Don't worry about
me anymore. You'd
better hurry and
help your friends.
[gasp]
But-
[painful screaming]
You were asked to get
me safely to my brother.
And you've accomplished
that.
Now...
Go save them.
[agreeing reaction]
Saphir...
Saphir! Why
did you
betray me?
I've done no
such thing!
Brother! Wiseman
has been deceiving
us all along!
[loud grunt]
[painful reaction]
Stop talking
nonsense.
You're wrong.
But if anyone,
including you, dares
to interfere with-
Brother! Wiseman is
the one who came up with
this plan, not you!
He's just using you!
Try to remember!
Was this really what
you and I were wanting
to achieve?
What we were
fighting for?!
[chuckle]
Brother!
I'm tired of all
this dramatic nonsense.
Just die.
[startled reaction]
Not him again!
[gasp]
Stop this,
Chibi-Usa!
Demande! You need
to listen to Saphir.
He knows something
about the future
that you're unaware of.
Please, listen
to what he has
to say.
Fine then. Saphir,
I will hear you out.
Brother...
[shocked gasp]
[painful screaming]
[collapsed reaction]
Oh, no!
S-Saphir!
[shocked gasp]
Wiseman!
Saphir is a traitor. I
am just sparing you the
unpleasant task of having to
execute your own brother.
Brother...
[speechless reaction]
[heavy breathing]
Wiseman, he..he wants
to erase the future.
His goal is...
Die!
No, wait!
Wiseman!
[painful screaming]
Saphir!
[defeated gasp]
Foolish young man.
He allowed himself
to be tricked into
spouting nonsense by
those Sailor Guardians.
Come, Black Lady
and Prince Demande.
We will settle our
score with those
young ladies
on another day.
Hmph! Fine
by me.
Saphir...
I'm..I'm sorry
I couldn't
protect him.
[small groan]
Petz..I'm sorry.
[shocked gasp]
Saphir! No!
You can't die!
You just can't!
What about Petz?
You can't leave
her alone!
Saphir wake up!
[soft sobs]
Demande!
Saphir...
Wiseman!
[gasp]
[soft breathing]
[startled]
I'm sorry Petz..."
It's alright.
Somehow, I knew
this would happen.
I felt it the
moment I let
him leave.
I will never
forget you,
Master Saphir.
Your smile will
live on in my
heart..forever.
Sailor Moon, your
beauty and strength
have always brought misfortune
to my people.
But today, that will
change as I command you
to pledge your love and
loyaly to me and only me.
Demande, please stop!
This is not what
Saphir wanted!
You need to understand
the true meaning of love.
Only then can two people
connect with each other.
Next time on Sailor Moon R,
"Believing in Love and the
Future: Usagi's Decision."
The moonlight is
a messenger of love.