Chibi-Usa where are you?
Why did you leave the Crystal
Palace? Running away from your
problems won't solve anything!
Come back here immediately! If
Wiseman ever finds out about
your secret he'll...No, I won't
let that happen!
I am Sailor Moon! In the name of
the Moon, I'll find you!
Saphir, set the Malefic Black
Crystal Reactor to full power.
Direct all its energy towards
the barrier at the Crystal
Palace.
Once the barrier has been
eliminated, I will go get the
Queen myself.
No you mustn't!
Brother, get over it.
She rejected you in the past as
Sailor Moon, and now as Neo
Queen Serenity.
Enough!
I fear you have lost sight of
the ultimate objective of our
Black Moon Clan, all because of
your obsession with her.
Our ancestors resented having to
leave the fine planet of Earth,
and being forced to live here
on Nemesis.
And I for one have not forgotten
our plan to rewrite Earth's
history so that we may reap
our revenge!
Hmph!
[Screams]
Sir, what are you doing?!
Instead of wasting so much time
lecturing me...
...why don't you make yourself
useful and start working on
powering up the reactor.
[Grunting] As you command, sir.
Neo Queen Serenity...
One day, you'll be mine.
[Grunting]
"Wiseman's Evil Hand: Chibi-Usa
Disappears."
So this is the Crystal Palace.
It's so quite it feels
like a ghost palace.
It's hard to believe that people
actually lived here once, and
that the Black Moon Clan killed
all of them.
If this place had been protected
by the Legendary Silver
Crystal...
...there wouldn't have been such
extensive loss of life and this
much destruction.
So what happened to that Silver
Crystal? Why wasn't it secured
safely in the palace?
Are you okay, Chibi-Usa?
[Gasp]
[Sigh]
It's been a while since Tuxedo
Mask went to find Sailor Moon.
Hope they're okay.
I'm gonna go look for them!
Wait.
Huh?
King Endymion!
That will not be necessary.
Observe.
[All] Sailor Moon!
Sailor Moon! You're okay!
[All Giggling]
Hey, girls!
Glad to see you! Jupiter! Venus!
Mercury! Mars! [Crying]
Now stop crying. Pull it
together, we're not out of the
woods yet, you know.
Why are you so angry at me?
[Giggling] Here we go again!
I'm not mad at you, Usagi, I'm
just trying to cheer you up.
That's not how it sounded!
[Gasp] Is that?
She is the monarch of Crystal
Tokyo, Neo Queen Serenity. And
she is also my wife.
Mommy!
I brought Sailor Moon and the
other Sailor Guardians from the
past to help.
Mommy, please open your eyes.
King Endymion, what's causing
her to remain in this state?
I hate to ask, but will she ever
wake up?
I don't know.
But if the Legendary Silver
Crystal hadn't been lost, we
would still have hope that
perhaps she could be revived.
[Gasps]
But how could something as
powerful as that be lost?
I wish I knew. The only possible
explanation I can think of is
somehow it was removed from the
palace...
...just before the Black Moon
Clan's all out attack began.
Sailor Moon, why don't we see if
your Silver Crystal will work.
But she's been like this for
such a long time. Does my
Crystal really have enough
power to wake her up?
You have to try!
Yeah, give it a shot!
Have faith in yourself,
Sailor Moon.
All right.
Moon Crystal Power!
[Sighing]
[Grunting]
[Sighs]
It looks like nothing's
happening.
It's no use. Even Sailor Moon
isn't strong enough to save
Mommy.
[Crying]
[Gasps]
Chibi-Usa!
Let's leave her alone for now.
She'll be safe as long as she
remains inside the palace.
[Crying]
Mommy.
Mommy, what should I do now?
[Laughing]
[Gasp] Who is that?
I foresee our stars are aligned
with one another at this very
moment.
Thus fate has brought me the
Rabbit's capture.
[Gasps] I can't move!
[Laughing] It's useless. You are
now inside my domain.
I see fear preying on you.
Memories of the Legendary Silver
Crystal remain hidden in the far
corners of your mind, under a
clouded veil of sadness.
No! No!
Mommy is so elegant. A wonderful
queen loved by all!
Small Lady, you've been very
naughty again!
You won't become an elegant
lady acting like that!
I will too! Just watch me!
Small Lady!
I want to become a lady soon. A
real lady, and elegant, just
like Mommy!
I'm only going to borrow it.
For a little while. That's all.
If I hold the Legendary Silver
Crystal for a moment, I can
become as wonderful as her!
[Sighs]
[Screams]
What's happening?
Where did it go?
Small Lady!
Mommy!
Daddy!
[Grunts]
No!
Mommy! Daddy!
So, the Legendary Silver Crystal
vanished.
And because you were traumatized
by what you had done, you hid
that memory deep in your mind.
You're wrong! I didn't do
anything! It's not my fault!
I wonder what your Sailor
Guardian friends would say?
Huh?
It's all your fault, Small Lady.
This happened because you lost
the Silver Crystal.
Neo Queen Serenity left the
safety of the Crystal Palace to
search for you!
And now she's in a
coma because of you.
You're the one to blame!
No! No!
[All] You're the one to blame!
It's all your fault!
I didn't do anything wrong! I
didn't make it disappear!
All I did was touch the Silver
Crystal! It's not my fault!
[All] It is your fault!
Small Lady.
Stop it! Stop it! I
didn't do anything!
That's true, Rabbit. Don't let
those so-called friends blame
you.
It's not your fault. Use your
power to prove to them that you
are right.
You really think I can do that?
But what if no one believes me?
You will make them understand.
Now, come and take my hand.
My, I have never seen the
Malefic Black Crystal Reactor
brimming with so much energy.
It's like a ticking time bomb,
waiting to explode.
Huh?
My brother doesn't realize how
dangerous the full power of the
Malefic Black Crystal can be.
He blindly does whatever that
dubious sorcerer, Wiseman,
wants.
I fear we may be taking the
wrong path by using this
reactor.
[Laughing] Oh please! What makes
you think any of us trust
Wiseman?
I'm sure Prince Demande is fully
aware of the man's tricky
nature.
Saphir. Is the reactor ready?
[Inhales] Prince Demande,
there's no need to waste the
Malefic Black Crystal on this
mission.
Allow me to handle it
for you instead.
[Gasp] Prince Demande!
My brother has clearly
become too emotional.
If he hadn't fallen in love with
Neo Queen Serenity, this new
mission wouldn't be necessary...
...and we would already have
killed Sailor Moon by now.
Enough of this!
That damn queen is always in
my way! I'll do Wiseman's
bidding as long as I get rid
of her!
I'm not sure what Wiseman's
after, but when all is said and
done...
...I'll be the one using him to
grant Prince Demande's wish for
a new future.
However, Neo Queen Serenity
won't be the one who builds the
future with Prince Demande! It
will be me! [Laughing]
Sailor Moon R!
Wiseman! Where are you? Show
yourself!
[Giggling]
Who is that? There shouldn't be
any droids left at this base.
Show yourself!
Wiseman.
In the words of the ancients,
anger emerges from within to
give power.
But it is a double-edged sword,
it confuses the mind and the
ears at the same time.
Are you trying to tell me that
I'm hearing things? Whatever.
Wiseman I want to make
a deal with you.
I will attack the Crystal Palace
myself and destroy it, once and
for all.
But to do that I will need
strength unlike any seen before.
I'm sure you are capable of
giving me plenty of power.
You're doing this on the
Prince's orders?
Mm, no. But if the outcome of
this battle is to your liking,
then it's a pretty good deal for
you, wouldn't you say?
I foresee another queen reigning
over the future with Prince
Demande.
And that queen is, Queen
Esmeraude.
Queen?!
Right now, Neo Queen Serenity
possesses more power than you
because of her position.
But if you take in the
full energy of the Malefic Black
Crystal, you can become a queen
with even greater power.
Me, become a queen?
Don't assume I'm buying into
this idea of yours, but I'll do
whatever it takes to win Prince
Demand's heart.
Even if I have to make a deal
with the Devil.
[Gasps]
[Screaming]
[Laughing]
My body's overflowing with
power!
I am the true future Queen.
Prince Demande will be mine, and
we shall rule the world
together!
[Laughing]
I wouldn't be so sure.
What?
What is this?
Did you really think a woman
like you could control the
Malefic Black Crystal's true
power?
Now, surrender your body and
soul to do my bidding!
Damn you, Wiseman. [Grunting]
[Grunts]
Prince Demande, I wish you were
here right now so I could die in
your arms.
Such a pathetic fool.
[Screech]
[Heavy Breathing]
What's going on?!
[Screech]
[Gasps] You've got to be kidding
me.
How are we supposed to
fight that huge thing?
Hold on. Something's
not right.
What's this?
Wow! This future technology
is just amazing!
Observe.
If these energy readings are
correct, to fight this creature,
you must see its actual form.
That giant dragon we're seeing
was created by enormously
amplified life energy.
Energy initiated by
a human mind.
Are you serious?
What kind of sick mind would
even think of making a huge ugly
monster like that?
[Gasp]
It's trying to destroy
the barrier!
We'll have to go outside and
distract it, before it's able to
break through.
Oh, darn it.
We have to do
whatever we can.
The main reason we came to the
future was to help, and that's
what we need to do right now.
Mhmm.
Please look after Chibi-Usa,
I mean, Small Lady.
Good luck, Sailor Guardians.
[Screech]
[Nervous Breathing] It's really
humungous up close!
You can do this, Sailor Moon!
[Screech]
[Gasps]
[Screams]
[Grunts]
Any bright ideas on
how to fight that thing?
[Screech]
I say we just go for it!
Venus Love Me Chain!
[Screeches]
[Screams]
[Grunts]
Venus!
Did it work?
Damn, guess not.
Wait! The scan shows that it
clearly did some damage!
[Both] Everyone, hang in there!
Serenity.
If you can hear me, please give
those Sailor Guardians strength.
[Gasps]
Small Lady.
[Screech]
[Groaning]
It's coming!
[Screams]
[Grunts]
Are you okay, Sailor Moon?
Mhmm.
My turn.
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
[Screech]
I think I got it.
Yay! I knew you could do it!
[Gasps]
Take that you ugly monster!
Wait! Don't go near it! It's
still dangerous!
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
[Roars]
[Gasps]
[Screams]
[Screeches]
[Gasps]
Hmph!
Sorry, I guess you were right.
Let's double up!
All right.
[Screech]
Burning!
Mandala!
Shine Aqua Illusion!
[Roars]
[Gasps]
This'll take forever,
it's useless!
I'm afraid we're incapable
of stopping it!
Don't give up now!
Believe that the power of
justice will always prevail.
Remember King Endymion's words,
see its true form!
That's right I almost forgot.
That thing is made
up of energy.
From a human.
[Screech]
[Gasps] Look out!
Follow me, Sailor Moon!
Okay.
[Roaring]
[Grunting]
[Screeching]
Okay, do it now Sailor Moon!
Yeah, all right.
I'm counting on you, Moon Rod.
Moon Princess Halation!
[Gasps] Esmeraude?
[Screams]
Prince Demande.
Esmeraude.
They did it! They won, Luna!
Your Majesty?
It seems Small Lady has
disappeared. She's nowhere to be
found within the Crystal Palace.
What?!
So, Esmeraude has fallen to her
demise into a dark void. Well,
it was inevitable.
After all, my true objective is
not to help the Black Moon Clan
get their revenge.
And eventually, Prince Demande
and Saphir will be persuaded to
give up their lives for my great
cause, as well.
The true power that I seek is
already in my possession.
[Evil Giggles]
Small Lady, you poor thing, no
one will ever love you for who
you are. But don't concern
yourself with that.
Embrace this Dark Power, and I
assure you that everything
you've ever wished for will be
yours!
Don't listen to him,
Chibi-Usa! We do love you!
Try to remember!
Next time on Sailor Moon R: "The
Dark Queen: Birth of Black
Lady."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.