Love is sweet. Love is
sad. Love is painful.
Oh, love, love, love!
Mako! You've gotta go
for love with courage!
As for me. In the name
of the Moon, I'll
punish you!
The Moonlight Knight.
He's a mystery all right.
Whenever we're in
danger, he appears out of
nowhere and saves us. I
wonder who he is?
The way he leaves by
saying adieu... He's
just like the guy, who
broke my heart.
Your old boyfriend used
to say adieu??? Wait
a minute, so he was
French?
Er, I just mean that he
was like that.
There you are! Naru my
dear! [giggling]
Hi, Umino.
Ta da! Guess what I did?
Lookit! I made a special
lunch just for you!
Oh, is it fried
shrimp again?
No, love. It's got bell
peppers, okura, plus
fried shrimp today!
I'm trying to
add some variety for you.
Fried Shrimp! Fried
Shrimp! Yay! Yay! Yay!
Mako, have you
noticed that making a
lunch for a girlfriend or
boyfriend is really
popular these days?
Yeah, I guess I just
haven't made a special
lunch... for anyone...
in a long time.
Are you okay? Oh no.
Usagi didn't show up.
I'm positive I told her
that we were going to
meet. We've really got
to talk about who the
Moonlight Knight is.
[chuckling] Did you
really think Usagi would
wake up early for a
meeting?
[giggling]
"Is Seijuro the Moonlight
Knight? Mako on Fire"
I'm late!
Usagi! Hold on, slow
down. You forgot your
lunch!
[gasping]
[panting]
[groaning]
Miss Tsukino! You came in
late and forgot your
homework.
And now you're caught
sleeping in my class?!
I'm very sorry.
I doubt that. But
whatever. Now just go and
eat your lunch.
I wish I could eat lunch,
but I forgot mine.
[giggling]
I'm so jealous.
If I already knew I was
going to be late today,
why didn't I just stop
to get some breakfast?
[giggling]
Oh stop it, Kazu!
I am so very jealous.
Eat it while
it's hot.
[drooling]
Here it comes.
Please stop that.
No, no. Open up.
Come on. Ahhhhh---
I'll pass.
Aw, you're so shy.
You're embarrassing
me.
Ugh. I can't jump in
there. I'll look like a
total loser. Oh, I know!
I'll ask Mako to share
some of her awesome lunch
with me! Yeah!
Ahhhhh---just
say ahhhhhh!
You never give up,
do you, Umino?
I guess Usagi's not
here, either.
I want to talk to her
about the Moonlight
Knight.
What's that?
[sighing/swooning]
[flute playing]
She's not here, either.
That's surprising.
That's a beautiful piece.
I just love it.
[chuckling] At it again.
Does Seijuro also remind
you of the guy who broke
your heart?
[giggling] No, but
Seijuro does love music,
just like... my ex.
Oh, wait a sec. I just
realized that Seijuro
transferred to our
school around the
same time that Moonlight
Knight started showing
up.
Huh? Wait, you
think he's--
No, it couldn't
be!
[gasping]
[screaming]
Seijuro!
I made lunch for you!
Take mine!
Alright, hold on. Thank
you for the offers, but I
usually skip lunch.
No way! Just a bite.
[gasping and grunting]
Oh, Seijuro!
Come back here!
I stayed up all night
to make this lunch for you!
Is it possible? What
if... What if he really
is the Moonlight
Knight?
Mako? Hey, Mako?!
[laughing
It's been a while
since I fell in love!
[groaning]
Ami! Let me handle this
one. I'll find if there's
a connection between Seijuro
and the Moonlight Knight!
Let's do this!
But--but Mako!
What's gotten into her?
Hm-hm-hm!
[screaming]
Hmph!
Huh? How did he
get up there?
No way... Could he really
be the Moonlight Knight?
W-What should I do?
[chuckling]
Here goes nothing!
[cackling]
[flute playing]
Huh... I just don't get
it. Why do they all want
me to eat those homemade
lunches so badly?
It's because they like
you!
Who are you?
[chuckling]
According to the data,
the probability of
Seijuro Ginga being the
Moonlight Knight is only
zero-point-two percent.
I guess they aren't the
same person after all--
Hi, Ami.
Usagi?!
I've finally found you...
Are you okay?
[gasping and screaming]
Uh, what's wrong?
Your lunch.
Oh
[crying]
Ugh--Usagi! Come on,
snap out of it!
W-What's that?!
Here, try it.
It looks like one of this
planet's sea animals, but
its composition is
different.
Is there a reason for
making it look like that?
The way it's staring at
me and those legs.
Umm, Seijuro, do you
happen to like white
roses?
Do you sometimes feel
like... I dunno, maybe
wearing an Arabian outfit
with a head cloth and a
cape? You know?
Uh--
[grunting]
Is it good?
Er, uh, you like it?
[chewing and swallowing]
Can I have another
one, please?
Here! Take whatever you
want! I have some
desserts, too! Do you
have a sweet tooth?
Ail---
Hmm. Not bad.
Thanks! I once had a
special guy I would make
lunch for on beautiful
days like today.
I remember how he used to
tell me they were pretty
good, too.
Then he dumped me.
Sorry-how silly of me to
bring that up.
I just don't get it.
Huh?
Why do you want to make
lunch for someone you
like?
Huh--
[giggling]
Huh?
Oh, I don't know.
Sometimes girls express
their feelings by doing
something extra special
for the person
that they care about.
Sometimes they don't
think things through and
try to do things they
shouldn't.
There are even times when
girls would give up their
lives for love.
No way.
Big brother!
Huh?
Natsumi?
She's your sister?
Y-Yeah.
Dear brother. Remember
you shouldn't consume
any objects you're not
familiar with!
You might get sick!
Excuse me? You may not
think so, but I'm an
expert chef!
I've been making lunches
my whole life and I've
never made anyone sick! K?!
I'd appreciate it if
you didn't hit on my
brother any more. He's
off limits. Got it?
It's really creepy
you're getting jealous
over your brother...
What did you say?!
[choking]
[gasping]
What's wrong?!
Are- Are you okay?!
Don't touch him!
Go away!
[growling]
[struggling]
Sailor Moon...
...'R'!
Sailor Moon! R!
Miss Tsukino... You were
tardy, you forgot your
homework, you slept in
class all morning, and
then you slept in class
all through the
afternoon!
I'm so sorry, ma'am.
Forget it. Just go home.
Yes, ma'am.
[weakly grunting]
Oh, Usagi! You okay?
Nope. I'm so hungry I
can't feel anything at
all.
Usagi.
Oh, Luna. Hey! Is
that--?
[sheepishly laughing]
It-It's my lunch! I
don't believe it!
I guess she wasn't able
to give it to you this
morning.
I love you, I love
you, I love you, I
love you, I love you.
I'm telling you it's all
a misunderstanding!
Liar!
An.
How could you be so cruel
and eat human food?!
After all the years
we've spent together,
sharing the Makai
Tree's energy?! What
you did is totally
disrespectful.
Wait. No, listen.
Hi, Seijuro!
Do you want to walk home
with me?
Uh--uh--
What are you waiting for?
Go ahead! Enjoy your new
friend!
A-An-- I mean, Natsumi!
Don't worry about
little old me. Take your
sweet time!
Oh my goodness.
What's her problem?
So, uh, I was wondering
if we could, like, talk
about stuff, you know?
Uh, sure.
I could tell back there
that your sister likes
you a lot. You two seem
like you're really close.
You think so?
She must be furious
with me.
Huh? Wha-What's wrong?
Oh, nothing. It's just
that Natsumi seems to
really hate me for some
reason.
[chuckling]
Hey, since we're here
to get to know each other,
there's something I'd like
to ask you about.
Sure! Ask me! Anything!
Well, um, I don't
understand the logic
between liking someone and
making lunch for them.
You don't get it at all?
I don't.
You're so funny.
[laughing]
Uh, why are you laughing?
B-because--
Damn you, Ail!
What?! Mako is on a date
with Seijuro right now?!
Usagi!
It's not really a date. She
just wanted to see if he has
anything to do with the
Moonlight Knight.
There's no way that
Seijuro is the Moonlight
Knight! Are you kidding
me?
Thank you for the food!
Okay then!
Hey, where are you
going?!
I'm on a mission to
see whether or not it's
really a date!
Seijuro said he likes me!
He better not be lying.
Gotta goooo!
What was that about? I
thought she complained
that boy gave her nothing
but trouble.
[chuckling]
So then, you're saying
love and lunches are just
things that you give to
someone?
That all sounds
backwards to me.
Not at all.
Love should be something
you simply reach out and
take for yourself!
Why would you give
things to people for
love?
Humph! I don't
get it at all.
Really? You think love is
to be taken? But that's--
kinda sad.
I mean, love comes in
many different ways but I
don't think it's something
you can--
Silence!
Huh?
You meddlesome earth
female!
[gasping]
An?!
I'll teach you a lesson!
[grunting and screaming]
[grunting]
Who do you think you are?
A primitive human like
you has no right to
lecture anyone about
love!
Why you---
[growling]
W-Wait!
Ha!
[grunting]
Mako!
It's that alien!
What's going on?!
W-W-What should we do?!
Ami, look after Mako!
Mm!
And me?!
You transform and fight!
Do I have to?
Mmm!
Moon Crystal Power Make
Up!
My precious lunch box!
Ruined! You witch!
What are you blabbering
about, human? Time to
finish you off now!
Stop right there!
Uh?!
Sailor Moon!
How dare you ruin a young
girl's date with a cute
boy! That sort of crime
is truly unforgivable!
Only a big, huge,
oversized, ginormous,
humongous pest!
Says the person who was
just about to do the same
thing.
Humph! A lower life form
like you calling me a
pest? You need to learn
your place, girl!
Oh yeah?!
I am Sailor Moon! In the
name of the--
W-What's going on?!
I-I can't move!
Ail! You
stay out of this!
I can't stand you.
Don't say anything.
[blushing]
An, please trust me.
Ail...
Now pick a Cardian that's
worthy of this occasion.
[sighing]
Okay.
Come forth, Cardian! Our
servant, Utonberino!
Utonberino!
[struggling]
What?
[grunting]
Mako!
Utonberino!
[grunting and yelling]
[grunting]
[laughing] You've met
your match, Sailor Moon!
Utonberino!
Mako, are you okay?!
Yeah. Those guys are
gonna pay for ruining
my special lunch filled
with love.
I think it's time to
teach them a lesson.
Right!
Jupiter Power Make Up!
Sailor Jupiter!
I'm here. Leave the
rest to me!
Utonberino, get rid of
those Sailor Guardians!
[grunting and screaming]
Rino! Rino rino
rinoooooo!!!
[gasping]
Supreme...
what is this?!
Jupiter!
[laughing] Excellent
work, Utonberino.
Now bundle Sailor Moon
and her friends into a
sushi roll!
Rino!
[gasping]
Rino Rino Rino!
[panicking]
Sailor Moon! Sailor
Mercury!
[struggling]
Rino rinooooo!
[screaming]
[gasping]
I can't breathe!
[laughing]
Now that's
entertainment!
[laughing]
If only I could move
my arms!
That rose!
[gasping]
It's the Moonlight
Knight!
The power of the
moonlight shines down on
all. Even to those who
have lost sight of love.
Love that makes one risk
their own life for
another, is true love.
Beautiful and courageous,
it shines brightly.
True love and courage...
I get it now!
I'm willing to put my
life on the line... for
my cherished friends!
Jupiter, my guardian
planet! Bring forth a
storm! Summon the clouds!
And bring down your thunder!
Supreme Thunder Dragon!
Rino rino rino!
Rino Rino Rino Rino
Rinooooo!
R-Rino!
How impudent!
Crescent Beam Shower!
Look out!
Fire Soul!
Hot hot hot!
[groaning]
Next time, Mars...
Less heat.
I saved you didn't I?
Stop whining!
You've gotta call when
you need help, okay?
R-rinoooo!
Sailor Moon! Finish her
off!
You've got it!
Moon Princess Halation!
Cleansing!
Dammit!
[sighing]
Excellent work, Sailor
Guardians.
[gasping]
Moonlight Knight! Please
tell us. Who are you
really?!
One day you will all find
out the truth. Until
then... Adieu!
Uh--wait!
Jupiter...
He knows about the true
meaning of love. And that
tells me everything. He's
certainly not Seijuro.
That's for sure.
Of course Seijuro wasn't
the Moonlight Knight!
Yeah, Moonlight Knight
looks much more like the
guy who broke my heart!
[exaggerated groaning]
The next time I see him,
I'm gonna make him a
special lunch filled with
delicious food and love.
[giggling]
All done!
Ail? What is this?
It's umm... This is how
an Earthling expresses
their love for another.
Oh, Ail! You mean you did
this all for me?
Mmm-hmm.
I'm so happy! But what
exactly should I do with
this thing?
Yeah... That's the part I
don't get.
Hmm.
"Who was it that said a
first kiss tastes like
honey?"
"Because it doesn't. A
real kiss tastes much
sweeter, and--"
Hey, wait! Luna!
That's my diary!
While you're scribbling
away, someone's gonna
steal Mamoru from you!
They're just rehearsing a
play, but I can't stand
him kissing Natsumi!
Next time, on Sailor Moon
R: Steal a Kiss from Mamoru.
An's Project Snow
White.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.