[Laughing] Wowie! We're all
vacationing on a tropical
island!
What could be more fun!? That's
what I thought at first, but
wait...!
Is that a dinosaur? !
And nobody said anything about
an active volcano!
But since that dinosaur is just
so cute, he better...
Come and play with Sailor Moon!
So did you two finish your
summer break homework yet?
Not yet...
Hey, we should plan a summer get
away and go somewhere fun!
Yeah we should. A summer
vacation somewhere else would be
great...
Somewhere where we could
cool off and relax.
With no homework
and no stairs.
[Sigh] I love how cool it is
under this tree.
Do you think Rei's around ?
Oh look! It's Chibi-Usa!
So did you come up here to cool
off as well?
Yeah, but if you're looking
for Rei, she left town.
[All] Huh!
Well then where did she go?
I came all the way up here to
play with her because I was
bored.
But she's doing spiritual
training on a remote island.
Wait! She's gone away to a
remote island?!
So then, she's there, all alone
on a private beach, enjoying a
vacation?!
How could Rei do that to us!?
Chibi-Usa! Did Rei happen to
tell you where that remote
island is?
Uh-huh.
Well in that case I say we all
join her there right away!
It would be wrong to let Rei
keep all the summer fun to
herself, right girls?
Right!
"The Beach, the Island and a
Vacation: The Guardians' Break."
[Inhales]
Great, finally some time to
myself, I'm gonna do some
serious spiritual training.
Pyo, To, Sha, Kai, Jin, Retsu,
Zai, Zen!
Huh!
Huuuh!
Rei!
[Gasp]
[All] Rei!
[Laughing] Woohoo!
Wait, but how, how did you
guys...?
[Screams]
How could you keep a place like
this all to yourself Rei? Why
didn't you tell us?
Yeah! Oh, the water here's so
clean and clear. Wow! I can even
see the fish swimming in it!
This is the perfect vacation
spot. I've never breathed air
that's this fresh!
And it's great for studying!
Look guys, I came here because I
really want to get some serious
training done.
Oh, we know that, and actually
we didn't come here to relax.
We came because Chibi-Usa said
she was missing you.
Isn't that right?
[Muffled] No I didn't!
Oh Chibi-Usa is that true?
She told all of us she wants
you to play with her, huh!
[Muffled Talking]
But Chibi-Usa before that, I
think you need to complete your
summer homework assignment for
today, right?
[Muffled Talking]
Alright, when you're done with
your homework I'll play with
you.
[Muffled] Okay!
I can understand Chibi-Usa
missing me, but why did all of
you have to come with her?
You didn't come to keep me from
doing my spiritual training, did
you?
[Both] Ohh, right. You're
spiritual training.
I read somewhere that ocean
swimming is one of the best ways
to build one's spiritual
strength.
Hmm? Huh?!
[Screams] I-I brought my suit
just in case I needed a little
break!
Well maybe it's time for a
break! Why don't we all go
for a swim right now!
[Both] Let's go!
[Laughing] Race ya!
Last one in cooks dinner!
[Giggling]
Make sure to be careful, guys!
I've seen sharks cruising around
in the deep water!
[All] We'll be careful!
[Panting Breathing]
[Panting]
Chibi-Usa don't you know how
to swim? Well let's fix that!
Hey, stop that!
There you go free lesson!
Hey! Don't you see
you're scaring her?
Yeah, ya big bully!
You need our "love-and-
justice Niagara Falls Attack!"
[Laughing] Yeah! Take that!
Taste the payback!
[All Laughing] Over here!
Wow! What an awesome sand
castle!
Do you want to try making
something together, Chibi-Usa?
Come on, let's do it,
it'll be fun!
Okay!
Boy, Chibi-Usa really
loves being with Rei.
And Rei's really
fond of her as well!
Hmph! I think the reason those
two get along so well is because
both of them can be so mean!
[Both Giggling]
[Gasp]
[Sigh]
What's the matter?
[Giggling] Oh, nothing.
Okay everyone, lunch is ready!
Go on, dig in!
[Chewing Sounds]
What's the matter, Chibi-Usa?
I know you've gotta be hungry.
I just don't really like eating
fish...
It's not good to be a picky
eater.
What I don't like I don't do!
[Gasp] Chibi-Usa!
Huh! I hate you Rei!
Maybe I was a little too
hard on her...
Ahh, all this sun! It's so hot!
How can all of them eat in this
heat anyway?
Uh, where's Chibi-Usa?
In the water.
No she's not.
[Both] Huh?
She was there a minute ago!
Oh no!
The tide must have pulled her
all the way out there!
Huh, what? Where am I?
What! Was that a shark! Ahh!
[Gurgling] Help! Help!
[Gurgling]
[Coughing] Huh!
Huh?!
Where'd you learn to
drive a boat, Mako?
Eh, I can do anything.
Are you sure you know how?
That's strange, I don't
see her anywhere.
Rei, do you sense Chibi-Usa's
presence at all?
No. Not yet.
You don't think sharks
ate her, do you?
Don't say that!
This whole thing is my fault.
This only happened because I
scolded her.
Don't blame yourself. I should
have had something else she
could eat besides just fish.
This isn't the time to be
squabbling over details, you
two.
We need to expand the search
area so we can find her!
Yeah, you're right.
[Cry Of Pain]
That's it, you sharks!
Luna P Transform!
See ya later, sharks!
[Grunting]
Ahh!
[Sighs]
Thank you for saving me.
Grrr.
So is this where you live?
[Licking wound]
You're hurt!
You got hurt because of me!
I'm sorry, I'll fix you up!
Luna P Transform!
[Confused Noise]
[Wincing Sound]
It should only sting for a
little bit longer, but it
should help.
[Sigh]
What made you decide to
risk your life to save me?
Oh! Now I get it, look! You're
just a newly hatched baby,
aren't you?
[Giggling] You probably think
that I'm your mommy, is that
it, little guy?
[Confused Noise]
Well I wish I could be...
But I'm not your mommy...
But I can still be your
best friend! Sound good?
[Happy Noise]
Okay! That should
help you heal.
You see, a friend is someone who
cares about you, and treats you
nice.
Where could your mommy be? Well
there's no need for you to
worry, I'll stay here with you.
My name's Usagi. But
everyone calls me Chibi-Usa.
[Giggles] And you are?
Oh, right! You were just born,
so you don't have a name yet, do
you?
Okay, with that long neck of
yours, I'll call you "Giraffe!"
[Giggling] That'll be your name!
Hello Giraffe! Let's
be friends forever! [Happy
Noise]
[Sigh] Could it be sharks
really did eat her after all?
You need to quit that negative
thinking! Chibi-Usa's still very
alive.
I sense her energy.
We're gonna find her. Look at
Luna and Artemis, they haven't
given up.
Look at how intensely they're
searching for her.
[Groaning] I feel seasick.
I wanna go home. [Queasy
Reaction]
Sailor Moon! R!
A little while ago I had a fight
with a girl who's a friend of
mine. [Whimper]
But now that you and I have
become friends, Giraffe, I feel
much better about everything
that happened!
[Stomach Rumbles]
Oh my! You sound pretty hungry
Giraffe. I'm hungry too.
Grr.
Huh? Fish!
[Happy Noise]
I guess that's all we've got.
[Gasp] What's that smoke?
Could it be Chibi-Usa built a
fire to try to signal us?
No, that's volcanic smoke.
Chibi-Usa...
Are you sure this
will taste good?
[Chewing Sound]
[Happy Noise] Okay Giraffe, I
trust you, I'll give it a try.
Oh wow! Fish is delicious! Mmm!
[Giggling]
[Happy Noise]
Huh? What was that
squealing sound?
Being seasick has you
hearing things, Luna.
Artemis, you saw that?
Yep. Seasick or not
I saw that.
[Confused Noise]
[Sigh]
[Sigh] I gotta go potty.
Huh? Ahh!
[Confused Noise]
Whoa, hang on, could you
be Giraffe's mommy?
Huh?
[Struggling Noise]
Wait, please! Don't take my
friend Giraffe away!
[Happy Noise]
Your baby and I are friends.
I know that Giraffe is better
off with his mommy, but I
was hoping that...
Mommy...[Sigh]
No wait! Don't take Giraffe
away!
[Struggling Noise]
Giraffe!
[Sad Noise]
Giraffe...[Sigh]
[Happy Noise] Huh?
[Happy Noise]
[Giggling]
Huh? What's that?
Ahh! An Earthquake!
[Screams]
Everyone, look!
It's erupting!
Ahh!
[Gasp]
She's alive! I felt her
presence, she's on that island!
Then Chibi-Usa's in big trouble!
That volcano's going to explode!
There's no time to lose!
Everyone, transform!
Hmm. Let's do it.
Moon Crystal Power!
Make Up!
Mercury Star Power!
Mars Star Power!
Make Up!
Jupiter Star Power!
Venus Star Power!
Make Up!
Sailor Mercury!
Sailor Mars!
Sailor Jupiter!
Sailor Venus!
Sailor Moon!
[Grunting]
Giraffe's mommy!
[Scared Noise]
[Sigh] Mommy.
Oh no!
I will find a way to save you!
I'm the reason you guys got
stuck here in the first place.
I'm the one who kept you here.
No!
I can't let this happen to you!
We're friends and I care about
you!
And you just found your dear
mommy!
No!
[Whimpering]
Huh!
The Sailor Guardians are here!
Hey wait a minute girls, you
forgot all about me!
Burning!
Mandala!
Thank goodness. [Sigh]
You girls handle the rest. Huh!
We've got this!
Huh!
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
Venus Love Me Chain!
Shine Aqua Illusion!
Sailor Mars, please save Giraffe
and his mommy. They're in
trouble!
Who's Giraffe?
My dinosaur friend!
They're trapped
underneath those rocks!
Sailor Moon! Can you do it?
You bet! I've got this!
Hmph.
Huh.
There they are!
Hurry Sailor Moon, quickly!
Yeah, we'll all be covered in
lava in just a few seconds!
Even with our powers, we can't
hold that lava back any longer!
I can do this!
Moon Princess!
Halation!
[Relieved Noise]
Oh good, they're okay!
[Gasp] Is Giraffe okay?!
Is his mommy okay?!
They're both fine. The Sailor
Guardians were able to rescue
both of them, see?
Hey you two!
Oh wow, where are they going?
I think they're leaving to find
themselves a more peaceful
island to call home.
Hey, don't you wanna
say goodbye?
Oh, yeah.
Giraffe, don't you ever
leave your mommy.
[Happy Noise]
Bye-bye! I'll miss you!
Guess what Rei? I really like
eating fish now!
What? Really?
Yeah, thanks to my friend
Giraffe.
I want to go back to
where mommy is.
Chibi-Usa...
Sailor Moon! I'm scared!
Those people are back and
they're trying to kill me!
I'm tired of always
being scared!
You'll be all right Chibi-Usa.
I'll protect you.
I promise, you have my word!
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"Protect Chibi-Usa: Clash of the
Ten Warriors."
The moonlight is a messenger
of love.