It's time to begin our
journey into the unknown.
We're ready to leave for
the future!
We don't know what danger
lies ahead or how we'll
be able to deal with it.
But no matter what happens,
we won't give up until
we save Chibi-Usa's
mother!
O Door of Space
and Time...
Show us the way
to the future!
Please! Please,
everyone!
Rescue my mommy!
[gasps]
[screaming]
Everyone!
Sailor Mars!
Sailor Mercury!
Sailor Jupiter!
Sailor Venus!
Sailor Moon!
No! No!
No!
"Journey to the Future:
Battle in the Space-
Time Corridor."
Until my dream last night,
all I could ever think about
was returning to the future...
...to rescue Mommy with
the help of the Sailor
Guardians. But now I'm
thinking...
...the Black Moon Clan
may be way too powerful.
What if Sailor Moon and
the others get defeated?
Mommy! What should
I do? I'm scared!
Chibi-Usa...
Mamo...
What are you doing
here? Is something
wrong?
Let's go. Everyone's
waiting for you.
Uh... Yes, but...
Chibi-Usa...
You're going to rescue
your mommy. That's all
you ever talk about. So
don't get cold feet now.
Believe in your strength.
And in the strength of your
friends. You must have faith
that all of you can do this.
C'mon. Let's go
together to the
future.
I'll be with you,
to keep you safe.
Thank you, Mamo.
We're good?
Yeah.
I wonder what's
keeping Chibi-Usa?
Sailor Moon, how come
she didn't come here
with you?
She told me to go on
ahead because she had
something she needed
to do.
I sure hope nothing
happened to her.
I'll go look for her.
I'm gonna go
with you.
That won't be
necessary.
I've got her right
here. Sorry we're
late.
Chibi-Usa! What
took you so long?
You know how it is when
you're going away. I
had things to do.
Okay. Is everyone
ready to go now?
Chibi-Usa, we're all
counting on you.
All right.
O Guardian of time!
Tear apart the heavens
and open wide for me the
Door of Space and Time!
I summon thee by
your true name.
Omnipotent God
of Time...
Father of the
Guardian. O
Chronos!
Guide us on our
journey!
Protect these
travelers!
Grant us the
path of light!
I-Is this the future?
Where did
everyone go?
What's that?
Stop right there!
Those who violate the
taboo and approach the
Door of Space and Time...
...must be eliminated!
Huh?
Wait! Just a minute!
Let me explain why I'm
here!
Prepare to die!
[gasp]
Puu, no!
Stop!
Small Lady?
Sailor Moon?
And, ah... You're
Sailor Pluto?
Everyone!
Is this your doing?
I'm sorry I broke my
promise and brought all
these people with me to
the Door!
But they're my friends
and they're here to help.
We're all going
to rescue Mommy!
Don't say anymore...
[gasp]
Puu, does this mean
you're not angry?
No, I'm very proud of
you. You've finally
mastered the space-
time key.
You've become an
exceptionally fine
young lady.
Puu...
Forgive my behavior. You
were kind enough to
accompany Small Lady
here. I should not have
threatened you. Please
accept my apology.
Huh?
But I must tell you my
life never seems to be
easy when I'm dealing
with you, Sailor Moon.
Uh... Hm?
I will open this Door
to allow you all to go
beyond the boundaries
of time.
The Door of Space and
time is now open. You
may set forth on your
journey to the future.
Thank you, Puu.
All right. Hold
each others' hands.
Sailor Moon, you must
never let go of Small
Lady's hand. If you
are separated at any
point, you may become
trapped between the
gaps of time, forever.
Sailor Pluto, please
come with us!
I cannot leave. This is
my permanent station. And
since I cannot go with
you, please protect
Small Lady for me.
We'll do our best.
Puu, see you soon!
Now I remember, Queen
Serenity once told me
about a Sailor Guardian
who'd been assigned to
protect the Door of Space
and Time for all eternity.
A solitary Guardian whose
name and very existence
shall never be known to
anyone but the Queen.
She was talking about
Sailor Pluto...
A solitary Guardian...
That no one would
ever know about...
No wonder there's
such a sad look
in her eyes.
We've come to the
space-time corridor.
Everyone be careful!
[gasps]
So this is the space-
time corridor?!
It must be, but this
blast of pressure is
really intense!
Let's try to
move forward.
I'm seeing movement in
the ancient space-time
corridor, and it appears
to be traveling by time-
warp to Crystal Tokyo.
That must be
the Rabbit.
There's more than just
one. This energy reading
suggests several.
Hm?
Hmph! It's unusual for
that planet to have
any visitors.
The time has come...
We must now seize the
Legendary Silver Crystal
and the Rabbit, and then
topple that impenetrable
castle.
Seize the Rabbit?
Why do we need her
now?
Bringing the Malefic
Black Crystal and the
Rabbit together will
result in an
extraordinary power.
Those eyes...
Ah... She must be
Sailor Moon. So
beautiful.
Brother, what's wrong?
You must get hold
of the Rabbit!
Esmeraude, capture
the Rabbit.
Bring her and Sailor
Moon here alive.
Understand?
You want Sailor
Moon, too?
I want to gaze into
those beautiful eyes
of hers.
But brother...
Do not fail me!
Wiseman! That feeble old
prophet always shows up
here, trying to get my
brother to do his bidding.
Toying with his mind,
making demands, but never
revealing what his true
intentions are.
Come to think of it, he
was the one who put those
strange ideas about the
Legendary Silver Crystal
into Prince
Demande's head.
One day, I'll
expose that fraud.
Personally, I think it's
more important to make
Prince Demande forget
about that dewy-eyed
temptress, Sailor Moon.
[evil chuckling]
Sailor Moon R!
This force feels like
it's gonna crush us!
Not sure I'll
make it!
You will! Just
hang in there!
I'm trying!
Wow. If she's having
trouble bearing this I
wonder if she's going to
be strong enough
to rescue Mommy.
I know I mustn't be so
negative, but can she
really save her?
Chibi-Usa!
Hold on!
We'll make it!
Trust me!
Yeah, I've got to
trust her. Sailor
Moon has never let
me down.
[crazy laughter]
How nice of you to
step into our domain!
Esmeraude!
Allow me to give you
a proper welcome!
[screaming]
[laughing]
Ugh! I've lost them
in the space-time
labyrinth!
Luax!
At your service...
Your power let's you
move easily about the
space-time labyrinth.
So go find the
intruders and
get rid of them.
Yes.
Except one!
It's the small one.
You mustn't harm
the Rabbit.
Don't kill the Rabbit.
Understood!
Oh dear, I must have
forgotten to mention
not to kill Sailor Moon.
Or perhaps Luax left
before hearing all my
instructions. Oh,
that's too bad.
[laughing]
Agh! Is everyone okay?
Chibi-Usa and Tuxedo
Mask aren't here with
us!
Apparently...
We've been sucked into a
dark gap in the movement
of space-time.
How are we ever gonna
reunite with Chibi-Usa?
If we're lost in time, we
could be wandering around
here for an eternity, and
we wouldn't even know it!
I'm sorry. If only I
hadn't let go of Chibi-
Usa's hand!
It's not going to accomplish
anything to blame yourself
like this. We need to focus
on finding Chibi-Usa.
How do we do that?
By brainstorming to
come up with a way.
What's going on? The
Silver Crystal's
glowing...
Look! Up there...
How strange! It's
glowing, too!
It's as though it's
signaling the Silver
Crystal.
Yes, perhaps the Silver
Crystal of the future is
resonating with Sailor
Moon's Silver Crystal
of the present.
I think we should
go check it out.
I agree. There's no
use staying here.
Let's go!
Right!
Where are we?
This place is
kinda creepy!
Worse than that, we
got separated from
everyone else.
Yeah, I know. So now
what's gonna happen
to us?
We have to find the
others. C'mon. Let's
go.
Wait!
Who's there?
You must not go that
way. Turn around. Go
the way you're facing
now. Quickly.
What do you think?
Could be a trap.
We'll do as he says. I
can't explain it but I
have a feeling we should
trust that man.
[nervous gasps]
Where is everyone?
Nobody's here.
I've ended up all
by myself again.
Mommy...
The door to the
future...
Beyond that is
the future...
I've come home...
But I'll never be able
to rescue Mommy all by
myself.
Mommy...
Poor little thing...
Oh, you poor little
thing. My little
darling...
It's all right now.
Ah! Mommy!
Let's go home together.
Mommy!
Wait, you're
not my mommy!
Who are you?!
You don't recognize
me? I'm your mommy,
Rabbit.
No, you're not! You're
just pretending. My
mommy never called me
Rabbit!
Ohh...
[evil laughter]
Guess no one can
fool you, little
Rabbit.
[gasp]
However, this would have
been a lot easier on you
if you had believed me.
Are you Mommy's
little crybaby?
[gasp]
It's all over. I'm
sorry, Mommy! I can't
save you!
Chibi-Usa! You're going
to rescue your mommy.
That's all you ever talk
about. So don't get
cold feet now.
He's right!
I'm not going to
give up yet!
Luna P!
Agh!
Luna P! Transform!
[grunting]
Take that!
[laughing]
Mmm, that's not very nice
of you, trying to hurt me
with a slingshot full of
energy balls.
You're a naughty child.
You should be punished.
Severely!
[roaring]
[screaming]
Back off!
We're warning you! Don't
even think about laying a
finger on that child!
Well! How were you
able to get through
that labyrinth?
Not that it's any of
your business, lady, but
we have a strong guide
called "luck"!
I am the Pretty
Guardian...
...who fights for
love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name
of the Moon, I'll
punish you!
Doubt it. I'll give you
a taste of my punishment
now and deal with the
Rabbit later.
Ready or not...
Take this!
[screaming]
Wait! What just
happened here?
[laughing]
I radically changed
the polarity of time!
Is that even
possible?
That's not gonna
stop me! Burning...
No, don't!
...Mandala!
[gasp]
Huh? What's happening?
The reversed polarity
made it go backwards!
[chuckling]
You ready, Venus?
Yeah!
Try dodging this!
Sparkling Wide
Pressure!
Venus Love
Me Chain!
Sorry...
[screaming]
According to my
calculations, the
time distortion
vanishes for a
moment when she initiates
her power. That's our
chance!
We're only gonna
have a moment?
It's all or nothing.
Our only hope is the
Sailor Planet Attack.
Right! Let's do it!
Hold on. How are we
going to get her to
activate her power?
Leave that to
me! I'll do it!
Chibi-Usa!
No, it's too
dangerous!
[sigh]
Ahh!
[giggling]
What are you up to
now, little girl?
Mamo, I'm going to
believe in me. And I
promise to believe more
in everyone else, too!
You little fool! You
think because you're
cute, I'll go easy
on you?
I'll give you all
I've got, cutie-pie.
[yelling]
Now's your chance,
everyone!
Mars Star Power!
Mercury Star Power!
Jupiter Star Power!
Venus Star Power!
Moon Crystal Power!
[growling]
[grunting]
Agh!
Curse you!
Luax Power!
[gasp]
You're here for
me just as you
promised!
Attack now!
Sailor Planet Attack!
What?!
[screaming]
Alright!
I'm proud of you,
Chibi-Usa!
Thanks!
Same goes for you
all. Good work.
[complementing]
Now that we're all
together again, let's
continue on to Crystal
Tokyo.
[gasps]
No way!
This is...
...the future?
The time has come to tell
you everything about us
and about your future.
I know that voice...
That's the voice from
our dreams! Who are you!
At this moment in time,
your feelings for one
another are being tested.
Show me the strength
of your love.
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"The Shocking Future:
Demande's Dark Ambition."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.