Mamo, look at me. I
braided hope into every
strand of this promise
bracelet. The hope that
we could be together
again. But then you,
droid, came along to
crush that hope and the
hopes of all young girls.
I can't forgive you for
that!
I am Sailor Moon! And
in the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!
[panting]
I'm late for class again!
Look out!
Hm?
Ahhhh!
My goodness! Are
you all right?
[groaning]
I think you
broke my head.
Oh. Sorry.
So, did they
take roll?
Oh, Miss Haruda isn't
here today. So first
period has been turned
into a study hall.
Oh, I wish I'd had
known that! I could've
slept in and had
second breakfast.
Umino. Give it back.
Huh? Do I
have to?
It's not done. You'll get
it when I'm finished, okay?
Whatever you say, but I
hope you finish soon.
What is that thing?
A promise bracelet.
Huh?
It's bracelet for two
people who just can't
wait to get it on!
To get it on?
[grunting]
Sounds painful.
Just forget it.
"Shared Feelings: Usagi
and Mamoru in Love Once
Again."
These are what Umino and
I were talking about,and
everyone's making them
now.
Oh! They're really
lovely, but what do you
do with them?
You put your hopes and
wishes into every braid
and fasten it to your
wrist or ankle.
It's meant to
symbolize friendship
or everlasting love.
It's becoming quite
popular all over Japan.
Yeah!
[chatting]
You're not kidding! It
looks like everyone's
making them and
wearing them!
I wonder if I can learn
to make one, too?
Different kinds of
materials and colors
stand for different
wishes!
Why don't we go to
this new specialty store
that just opened up in the
Juban District?
Cool!
Yeah, I'm pretty sure they
carry everything you're
gonna need to make a
bracelet! Embroidery floss,
leather laces, beads,
patterns, special tape,
instruction books. And
they even have classes
for anyone who buys their
materials there.
And it's said that if you
braid one of these for
your boyfriend and give
it to him, that the two
of you will be together
forever.
That's why Naru's making
one.
Hey! I should
make Mamo one! Uh!
Stop being so damn
affectionate all the
time!
I just don't feel that
way about you anymore. So
please cut it out!
It's over between you and
me!
Go home, now! Go on!
Uh...
But you said... we loved
each other... and we were
going to be together
forever and ever.
Mamo...
[sighing]
Usagi? Usagi!
Huh?
What's the matter? You
look a little sad.
Did something happen at
school today?
Oh, no. That's not it.
I'm fine.
You sure don't look your
happy self.
If you have a problem,
you know you can always
count on us to help out.
Thanks a lot, guys. But
it's really nothing that
you should be worrying
about.
I heard that a promise
bracelet shop opened up
in the Juban District!
Mamo!
He's looking at me! My
wish is answered! I may
not need that bracelet.
Hey, wait!
Uh!
[whimpering]
M-Mamo...
I've been thinking about
us for quite some time,
now.
I don't understand.
Please tell me...
What did I do that was so
awful, to cause you not
to like me anymore?
If I knew what it was, it
would help me get over
the feelings I have for
you.
[sobbing]
Please! Could you just
tell me what it was I
did?
You didn't do anything,
Usako. It's my fault.
Mamo!
No. Don't go.
[crying]
[chuckling]
Prince Demande...
...cleansed the beautiful
Crystal Tokyo. The
streets were awash in red
as millions fell...
I shall do my own
cleansing of this filthy
Tokyo... with a wash of
Dark Power everywhere!
Now our new negative
point is...
...right there.
[grunting]
Come out, Droid Udering!
Udering!
This Tokyo is cramped and
stifling. You must grow a
Dark Henge, so the Clan
has a gate to pass
through to take
it over.
Understood!
I miss him already. I
want to go back to him as
soon as possible.
I long to bury my head in
Prince Demande's arms.
This is that shop where
you get the materials for
braiding.
These bracelets are great
at promoting happiness
because they make your
wishes come true!
Oh, nice.
And do you know the
best way to make sure these
bracelets are working to
make you happy?
Uh?
From what I understand,
the trick is to absolutely
believe that they're working
and that in itself
will bring you lots
of happiness.
I'm repeating what I read
somewhere.
But don't you think that
being a believer really does
give you the power to make
yourself feel better?
Yeah. Thanks for
cheering me up, Mako.
Okay, here are the items
you need to make a promise
bracelet for mending
broken relationships.
Thanks, Ami!
The braiding class is
right down there.
Oh, yeah?
Looks busy.
We're going out front to
see if there's anything
else we need.
Have fun,
Usagi.
Okay.
Someone new is joining
us?
Usagi...
You're taking
the class, too?
Hi, Umino. Yeah,
I am!
Since you're friends..
why not sit right here at
their table?
I'm glad you decided to
come. You looked so down
today, I was getting
worried.
First cut the embroidery.
You'll need to measure
out and cut ten
ninety-centimeter lengths
of floss...
Okay.
Once the floss is secured
with the tape, you begin
braiding by using the
middle pieces and forming
a figure four. Repeat
this twice.
If I do that,I'll
lose my place.
[groaning]
Then how about we try
starting with a simpler
pattern instead?
Mmm.
Take six strands and
start braiding them in the
same figure-four shape,
starting from the left.
It's actually quite
simple, once you get
the hang of it.
[groaning]
Oopsie.
Uh...
Every beginner
struggles... just
not as much as you.
Ah, closing time. That's
it for today! Now, I want
all of you to read your
instruction book and
finish your
bracelets at
home.
Awww, I don't wanna
have to read a book.
That means everybody!
Got it!
Bye!
Thanks for the lesson.
Everyone be careful. Get
home safe.
Ole, ole, ole! Udering!
Udering, update me on
your progress.
Those who wear the
bracelets home tonight,
will be contaminated.
The Dark Power that I put
in all of the braiding
materials will quickly
intensify and the Dark
Henges will grow.
Excellent. Good
work, Udering.
[chuckling]
I wonder if she finished
her promise bracelet?
Oh, she dozed off. Darn,
I was going to ask her
to make me one!
Trying something
new must have tired her
out. Why don't we let her
rest for awhile?
Yeah. Good idea.
Uh... why, Mamo?
I don't get it.
Mamo... We're finally
able to marry, at long
last.
Usako, I'll never let
you go again.
Mamo...
Usako...
I'm so happy...
[screaming]
Mamoru Chiba, you must
stay away from Usagi
Tsukino.
Who said that?
The moment that the two
of you are wed, the world
will come to an end and
tragedy will befall Usagi
Tsukino, Princess
Serenity...!
No! That's a lie!
A lie!
[gasping]
A lie?
Why did I dream that?
M- Mamo...
[gasping]
Sailor Moon...
...'R'!
Sailor Moon! R!
Mamo! It's me!
Open the door!
Be quiet! Do you realize
what time it is?
I'm sorry!
But I need you to listen
to me. There's something
that I have to ask you!
I'm not listening, and
I'm not answering any
questions! Now go!
Wait, Mamo! Did you
have a strange dream
about us getting married?
How did you know that?
I wonder why Usagi
suddenly went out to
see Mamoru at this time
of night.
She shouldn't see him
'til she's done with
his bracelet.
From what you're
saying, it sounds like we
had the same dream.
That's just what I
thought...
But maybe the dream has
no meaning, other than
just being a dream.
But what if you're wrong?
You could die, Usako!
Wait a sec. You broke
up with me for what
you think is my own good.
I'm not believing that
dream, and you shouldn't,
either.
Well, at first I didn't
believe it, but then, I
kept having the same
vision every night.
Which makes me think this
isn't any ordinary dream
and that its purpose is
to show us the future.
But even if the dream's
true... as long as we're
together...
I would be okay
dying, Mamo.
Uh!
Usako... I
think...
No, wait!
...we shouldn't be
together at all! Just go!
Mamo, don't push me
away! No matter what
happens, I wanna be
with you!
Even if the world is
destroyed, I want to be
with you, Mamo!
Even if I die, I want to
be with you!
Don't you get it! I want
us to be together forever!
I know, but we can't.
Mamo, please!
[sobbing]
Mamo!
Usagi's sure taking a
long time.
Uh-huh.
Ah! Here she comes now.
Usagi!
[gasping]
Chibi-Usa!
It won't let go! I can't
get it off of me!
[screaming]
[gasping]
What is it?!
[screaming]
Just hold still!
Chibi-Usa, are
you all right?
I think so.
Luna, what just happened
here?
Your promise bracelet
attacked her!
But... why
would it?
Wait a minute...
That store...
What's the matter?
We gotta get to
the store. Let's go!
We're coming!!
[panicking]
I can't get it off!
[gasping]
[screaming]
Umino!
Everyone! We have a
situation!
What's going on?
It involves the new
promise bracelet shop
that just opened up.
We'll head there right
now! Let's go, Artemis.
C'mon!
All right!
Look, Usagi!
Just as I thought. This
place is the source!
Moon Crystal
Power! Make up!
Ahhh! Dark Power Intensify!
Hey, you! Stop what
you're doing!!
Oh yeah, who are you?!
Girls put their wishes
into those braids and
were waiting for them
to come true!
You put evil power in
them...
...so their wishes
were denied. That's
unforgivable!
I'm the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for justice.
I am Sailor Moon!
And now, in the name
of the moon, I'll
punish you!
You mouthy little twit!
Here's what we do to
those who get in the way
of our plans!
I'm going to ring you!
One ring!
A diagonal pattern to
make my wish come true!
[chuckling]
Refusing to give up after
one try is my secret to
my success. I just have
to change my pattern.
Two rings!
Normally I'd use a heart
pattern, but since you
have no boyfriend,
why bother?!
How dare you! I may look
single, but I have a
boyfriend!
Look out, Sailor Moon!
Get back!
Ahhhh!
[groaning]
That was only the
warm-up. More to come!
[growling]
Ringa, ringa, ringa,
ringa, ringa, ringa,
ring! [gasping]
Who's the wise guy?
Promise bracelets are
strands of hope. Young
girls put their faith in
them, but you, with your
ugly heart, shatter their
faith.
I, Tuxedo Mask...
won't forgive you!
[chuckling]
Don't make me laugh.
Faith is meaningless...
So... wake up.
Three Ring Thunder!
[grunting]
You're pretty agile for a
guy in a tux! Let's see
how you do with my zigzag
design!
Uh!
Shine Aqua Illusion!
Sailor Mercury!
I got here just in time!
Just for you!
Four Ring Drive!
This design gets a lot of
traction! And pretty
soon, without it, you're
gonna spin out!
Burning....
...Mandala!
Sorry I'm late.
Boy, we're glad
to see you!
I've got one
design left!
Five Ring... Spin out!
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
Venus Love Me Chain!
Better late than never!
I'm all out of rings!
[panicking]
You know what to do,
Sailor Moon!
You bet!
Moon Princess Halation!
Ri-i-i-i-i-i-ng!
[groaning]
Huh?
Umino!
Naru!
[laughing]
We know that laugh.
It's Esmeraude.
I guess you Guardians are
feeling pretty cocky! But
listen...
It'll be only a matter of
time before a Dark Gate
opens in Tokyo. And then,
the power of the Malefic
Black Crystal will come
gushing in, changing your
Silver Crystal into a
Malefic Black...
...that will envelop and
destroy the entire world
with Dark Power.
[laughing]
Sailor Moon...
Uh! What is it?
As you know, we have been
entrusted with the
mission of protecting our
beloved city and the
future city of Crystal
Tokyo.
No matter what hardships
we may encounter, we must
endure them and move
forward.
I understand what
you're saying.
Sailor Guardians... Let's
continue to fight
together!
Farewell!
So we can only be
together when we fight.
Sailor Moon, you can't
just let him walk away.
Huh?
Put on your running shoes
and go after him!
I don't know what
happened previously, but
there is no misunderstanding
between you two, now.
How can you be so
certain?
We can see the love
shining in your eyes.
It's really a
no-brainer.
Live the moment. Put away
all your worries for the
future.
Go get him!
Okay. Thank you,
everybody.
You can do this,
Usagi! Just go for it!
I hope your wish
comes true!
Good luck, Usagi.
Mamo!
Usako?
Perhaps in the future, we
won't be together. But
for now, it suddenly feels
all right. And I know in
my heart that Mamo, at
this very moment, feels
the same way.
Mamo!
Usako.
Ah!
Mamo...
Usako...
A wave of influenza is
sweeping through the
Juban District. One after
another, the Sailor
Guardians are falling
victim. Achoo!
Just leave the
healing to me!
I, Sailor Venus,
goddess of love, will
lovingly nurse everyone
back to health!
Thanks, Minako.
Hey, flu bug that's
making everybody sick...
In the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
Next time on
Sailor Moon R:
"Venus: Minako's
Nurse Mayhem".
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.