C'mon! It's just not fair
that I'm the only one who
has to be a Sailor Guardian
again! Hurry up and bring...
...back the others! And exactly
who are Ail and An? Are they
connected to these evil
monsters? Oh, I feel like...
...my brain's gonna
explode!
I am Sailor Moon!
In the name of the
moon, I'll punish you!
"For Love and For Justice:
Sailor Guardians Once
Again."
Hey there, Mamoru?
Whoa! Let go!
What's going on?!
You know perfectly well
what's going on. Don't
act so surprised.
But-But I am surprised.
How is it you even know
my name, Bun-head?
C'mon! There's nothing
endearing about the
name Bun-head.
When we're out in public
together, why don't you
just call me Usagi?
[Chuckle]
Your name is Usagi?
Good to know!
What?! I can't believe
it! How could you ever
forget my name, Mamoru?
I get it now. Mamoru
doesn't remember our
former life together,
like I do...
Which means...he's
forgotten how much we
loved each other back
then, too!
[Whimpering]
Hey, do you have a
fever or something?
What's the matter
with you?
[Gasp]
Oh! There's that cool
guy. I wonder if he
remembers me?
Hey, Tsukino! Hold onto
that guy! Don't let him
get away, okay?!
Natsumi?
What? Not another
weirdo! Oh, man!
Let go of me! I'm
gonna be late for
work!
You got a job?! What
kind of work do you do?
Where do you have to go?
That's really none
of your business!
Hey, I was just askin'!
You're such a klutz!
How could you not hold
on to him? How difficult
could that really be?
Let go of me!
Mamoru's getting
away!
Oh really, his name is
Mamoru? I didn't know
that.
Mamoru! I'm
Natsumi Ginga!
Back off! What do you
think you're doing?!
Mamoru's mine!
I don't think he feels
the same way about you.
Well maybe not at
the moment...
Then that means Mamoru
if fair game for both
of us!
Mamoru...I, Natsumi Ginga,
will pierce your heart and
all your passion receptor
points with arrows of...
...adoring love!
[Giggle]
Crazy stalker!
We have no idea if we're
up against a new enemy at
this point, but we do know
something bad is happening.
But Minako and the other
Guardians are finally
leading peaceful lives.
I don't want to spoil all
of that for them by
bringing them back!
Mm. Yeah, I know
what you mean...
But then how should we deal
with this? I'm very worried
about Usagi handling it all
on her own.
It's just awful! Mamoru
doesn't even know who
I am, and without his
memories...
...He refuses to pay
any attention to me!
Usagi! There's no time
to be concerned about
that now!
[Whining]
[Groaning]
We really should consider
bringing back the memories
of all the others.
What?! You mean you can
restore Mamoru's memories
of me?!
We're only thinking about
restoring the other girls'
memories right now...
...so you'll be able to
fight together as Guardians
again.
Huh?! What are you
talking about?
I'm quite able to protect
the Earth by myself! See?
It'll be fine!
There's really no need
to get any of the others
involved.
Yeah?
Is sounds like you've
matured quite a bit from
your battles with the
Dark Kingdom.
You seem serious about
your responsibilities.
That's right. A couple of
bad guys are no problem.
I can stand on my own
two feet!
Uh...Looks to me
like she's gonna
need everybody.
I agree.
[Sighs]
The Makai Tree, the
very source of our
life...
...is getting very weak.
Its accumulated energy
is running out.
So! That effort was a
waste, and depleted
my resources.
Ail, I'm gonna
need more energy.
An, there isn't
much left. The Makai
Tree is depleted.
What?! Are you
absolutely sure?
Yes. To replenish it,
we'll need to steal
some life energy from
the humans on this planet.
I'd say we'll need
to steal a lot...
[Chuckling]
Go ahead, An...
It's up to you to pick
the right Cardian who is
best suited for this
energy-gathering task.
Okay...
Cardian Minotauron...
We've narrowed the search
for the role of Mikan
Shiratori's younger sister
to these final candidates.
Forget her. The others
are good choices,
especially this one.
I like her, too. Very
natural looking.
Any of those five would
be perfect for this series.
It wasn't easy
to find them.
Well, now that you have,
we need to bring them in
to audition and go from
there.
Let's get started.
Set up the appointments
as soon as possible.
Yes, sir.
What do you think
of these girls?
I think they'll
do nicely.
They'll give us
both a lot of
energy.
Hey! How did you two
get in here?! This
screening room is for
executives only.
Extras casting is down
the hall.
My mistake. I didn't
know that. I apologize.
[Screaming]
[Chuckling]
It would be so easy to
steal energy from these
humans.
But let's wait. There's
no need to stuff ourselves
with a lesser grade.
We'll get a much higher
quality of energy from
those young girls.
I agree, but for now,
these guys can help by
turning over their staff
to us.
[Chuckling]
What?! Are you really
gonna be on TV?!
Shh...Keep your
voice down, Usagi!
Oh...
It might happen.
I don't know.
The talent scout who
spotted me, now wants me
to go to some big audition
down at the TV station.
Mmm... That's cool!
So, Usagi...
What is it?
You know how I seem to
have a knack for getting
involved in strange
situations?
I'm worried this might
be another one of those.
Stop worrying! And
besides, they don't
happen to you all that
often.
I'm sure you're
gonna be just fine!
You really think so?
Of course! I could go
with you if that would
make you feel better.
[Gasp]
You would do that?
You really are my
very best friend!
[Chuckling]
Once I'm there, I bet
I'll be able to wrangle
my way in to get an
audition, too!
That's all it'll take.
I'm a shoo-in for the
role! Next thing you know,
I'm on my way to stardom!
[Laughing]
Oh! Miss Kino!
Well, it looks like the
rumors are true. Class
Five's girl genius is
going to audition for...
...this TV show, as well.
Yes, some person from
the TV station called
and insisted that I
come and try my luck.
But I don't know if I
can take the time away
from my studies.
Well, I'm sure
you'll find a way
to do both.
Excuse me. Are you two,
by any chance, here for
the TV show audition?
Yeah.
We sure are.
Well, then, why don't
we all go in together?
I heard that these TV
stations are pretty big...
...and it's easy to get
lost in them. But first,
we should introduce
ourselves. I'm Rei Hino.
Oh, and I'm
Makoto Kino.
I'm Ami Mizuno.
Nice to meet you! My
name is Minako Aino.
Hi there.
Good to meet you!
[Gasp]
Is it possible that the
four of us have met
somewhere before?
No. This is a
first. I think.
But it is sort of
odd. I feel like
we're not strangers.
That's weird. I'm
picking up the exact
same vibe.
Huh?! What do you mean
I can't go in! That's
so not fair!
That's the rule...
You can't go inside
unless you're on the
list to audition.
Ah, c'mon! Can't you
just make an exception
just this one time for
me?
Sorry! No can do. Now,
why don't you just go
home.
Sorry I made you come.
[Gasps]
Welcome...
If you ladies are here
for the audition, please
sign in and wait inside
this room.
Looks like everyone's
doing okay.
Thank you all
for waiting...
We are now ready. The
audition process will
begin in a moment.
Sir, I'm going to have to
turn down this audition.
I really don't have the
time to be here right now.
[Gasps]
This set is amazing!
By all means take a good
look at everything. Because
it's going to be your last.
[Gasps]
[Chuckling]
Sailor Moon!
R!
Sailor Moon! R!
Hello? Excuse me!
I'm afraid...
...with my heavy study
schedule I just won't
have the time to appear
in a TV drama.
Thank you for calling
me in, but I need to
go home to study right
now.
You're not going
anywhere!
[Flute Music]
[Gasp]
Come forth,
Minotauron!
Mi-no!
Is that some
special effect?
I thought we were
auditioning for a
family drama, not a
monster show.
It's not a special
effect. It's real!
[Whimpering]
Go, Minotauron! Absorb
every drop of energy
from these girls!
Mi-no!
Run!
[Screaming]
[Chuckling]
I love the screams of
young women! They're more
beautiful than any sound...
...a musical instrument
could ever make!
Ail! Stop reveling in it.
Let's hurry up and steal
their energy before it
runs out!
You've got to be kidding
me, An! Why should I miss
the opportunity to enjoy
such exquisite art?
Well! I don't have
any patience for
this!
I'm gonna go somewhere
else and gather energy
in my human form!
Hmph!
Let's see...
Oh dear!
What are you doing?
We're right back where
we started! [Sigh]
I can't help it!
This place is so
big and confusing...
...it's hard to tell where
I've been not to mention
where I'm going !
Great! We're
completely lost!
[Gasp] Tsukino! What are you
doing here wandering around
this building with that cat?
I was just about to
ask you the same thing!
Well guess what,
smarty-pants? I don't
even have a cat!
Well big deal!
Excuse me everybody.
Watch out!
Coming through!
Huh?
Was that?
...Mamoru?
Oh yeah!
I remember him saying
he had a job!
Wow! I guess he works
at this TV station!
Well then in that case!
Let the competition
begin!
Mamoru!
Mamoru wait up!
[Gasp]
What is this eerie
power that I'm sensing?
[Screaming]
Ahh!
[Panicked Breathing]
[Chuckles]
It's no use!
She's gonna get us forsure!
Where's the exit?
I can't run anymore!
I'm too tired! [Hmph]
[Laughing]
I'm not sure if we stand a
chance but it's far better
than just running around!
Couldn't of said it
better myself.
Huh!
[Screams]
[Chanting] Rin-Pyo-To-Sha-
Kai-Jin-Retsu-Zai-Zen! Evil
Spirit, be exorcized!
[Screams]
[Yelling]
Ahh!
Amazing! They're able to hold
their own against evil even
without their Guardian Powers!
I screwed up!
[Heavy Breathing]
I've lost sight of Mamoru.
Must be because I'm running
so short on energy.
Now anybody will have
to do.
[Scream]
Don't worry,
you won't die.
After you take a long
rest you'll get right back
to normal.
[Giggling]
[Gasp]
That thing's no
ordinary monster!
Mi-no!!
Naru!
[Screams]
Go away!
[Growl]
[Screams]
[Painful Breathing]
A cat?!
[Sigh]
I'm back here again?
Oh I wonder if they already
finished doing the auditions?
Come on everybody stay
focused!
Well lift her up.
We've got to hurry
up and get out of here as
soon as we can!
Damnit! Where's An? She
should be here at a time like
this!
Minotauron! Do your job.
Finish them off now!
Mi-no!!
What should I do I better
think of something fast or
they'll die!
[Heavy Breathing]
I'm gonna have to reawaken
them as Sailor Guardians
before it's too late!
Huh?
This sure is strange.
Usagi?
Oh! Luna!
Perfect timing!
Hurry up and transform, now!
Why?
I don't understand.
What's going on?
Don't ask!
Just do it already!
Fine.
Moon Prism Power!
Make up!
[Heavy Breathing]
[Screaming]
It's a dead end!
Hmph!
[Laughing]
Stop right there!
Huh?
I don't know what's really
going on here. As a matter of
fact, I am totally clueless!
[Sigh]
You're not supposed
to tell them that!
But I can't forgive you for
whatever you're doing, even
though I don't know what it is!
[Growls]
So in the name of the Moon...
I'll punish you!
Mi-no!!!
Who is that?
I'm so close to remembering
something, but I don't
know what!
Stay there. I'm gonna turn you
back into a good girl!
Uh oh! Where's my Moon stick?
[Gasps] Right.
Ahh!
[Growls]
[Screams]
What's wrong with her?
She's so useless.
I guess it's up
to me to handle this!
Hold on, why did
I just say that?
Rei!
She's starting to remember.
And so are the others!
Watching Sailor Moon is
causing them to regain their
memories!
[Screams]
No!
I'm loosing...
my strength...
Mi-no!!
So much for handling
things by herself!
That cat's talking!
What's going on here?
Well, the cat's out
of the bag, so to speak.
Sailor Moon's not able to
handle this, please
help her.
Help her with what?
[Inhales]
[Heavy Breathing]
[Sigh]
Usagi...
No...Sailor Moon!
I remember everything now!
We're guardians...The four
Guardians that protect the
Princess!
That's right! How could we have
just forgotten all this?
Mercury Power!
Mars Power!
Jupiter Power!
Venus Power!
Make...up!
[Laughing]
Bubble...!
Spray!
[Grunt]
Supreme...!
Thunder!
[Screaming]
Fire...!
Crescent...!
Soul...!
Beam!
[Screaming]
Cleansing!
[Giggling]
Curses! We didn't know there
were five Sailor Guardians!
We'll get you for this!
You're back!
Oh, boy. You really do need
our help. You never could
defeat bad guys by yourself.
That's why we're here!
Guess what?
I heard that Mikan Shiratori
collapsed from total exhaustion,
so the TV drama was cancelled.
Oh no. That's really
too bad.
But it's a relief to only
have to focus on my studies
again.
Yeah, but it sucks that we've
gotta put up with fighting
alongside Usagi again.
I'd much rather do
that TV drama.
Sorry everyone. If Usagi
had been more competent
on her own...
...you could have
continued living peaceful
lives.
Yeah but, it couldn't be
helped.
A new enemy has appeared on the
scene, and we have a mission.
It's our duty to defend
the earth from them, right?
Mhm.
[Laughing]
That's right! But
I'd rather play!
Well, she didn't forget
how to be a dork.
Now, all we have to do
is bring back Mamoru's
memories!
[Giggling]
You saved me,
but who are you?
Those gentle eyes...that
heroic face...
She's falling into the
same bad habits again.
Yes, it's all because
I'm so beautiful!
Oh I'm such a
bad girl!
[Sigh]
You're such a silly
girl Usagi.
Next time on 'Sailor Moon R:'
"For Whom Is The White Rose? The
Moonlight Knight Appears."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.