Chibi-Usa, can you
hear us?
Trust me when I tell
you this, you're not
alone.
We're all right
here with you.
Death Phantom! I
will not allow you
to turn our world
into darkness!
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of
the moon, I'll purge
your evil energy!
The time has come
to destroy the Earth!
[evil snickering]
I am Death Phantom, and
it would be my pleasure
to turn this world
into darkness!
[maniacal laughter]
The power of the
Malefic Black Crystal
is becoming much
stronger!
We're running out of
time! Do we know if
Chibi-Usa's been rescued?
There's no word yet.
But if the Dark
Gate opens..
..and allows the energy
of the Malefic Black Crystal
to be fired at us from
from Planet Nemesis...
The Earth will
be destroyed.
In that case...
We have to win!
"The Final Battle
Between Light and Dark:
Pledge of Love for
the Future!"
Release the power of
the Malefic Black
Crystal!
Chibi-Usa!
[gasp]
[terrified gasps]
It is time.
The Dark Gate
will open soon.
Proceed, Wiseman.
Send in the power
of the Malefic
Black Crystal.
Once you have done so,
I will channel that power
and turn this world
into dust!
She can't be serious!
I know! Even
she can't handle
that much power!
Chibi-Usa! If you
do this, you'll
die as well!
Then so be it!
I don't fear
death.
Darkness is all that
exists in this world.
I would rather destroy
everything than live in
a world that refuses
to love me.
You've been tricked
into thinking that!
Chibi-Usa!
What are you
talking about?
I know that none of you
have ever cared about
what happens to me!
That's not true,
Chibi-Usa!
All of us care!
Shut up!
Be Quiet!
[painful screaming]
[groaning and gasping]
I can't stand listening
to you anymore so
you'll be the
first to go.
Chibi-Usa!
Don't do it!
[evil chuckling]
Chibi-Usa!
Please, stop!
Die!
[stunned gasp]
[yelling in pain]
[defeated groan]
Are you alright?
Mamo, talk to me!
I don't believe it...
He was willing
to sacrifice
himself just
to save her?!
Of course he was!
What?
Our friendship
is that strong.
Yes, we would
do anything
for each other.
What sentimental
rubbish!
It's all true!
And you are one
of us! We are all
friends!
And what that means is
we would risk our lives
to protect you too,
Chibi-Usa.
I am one of
your friends?
That's right.
You've always been a
good friend to us
and we couldn't stand
to lose you.
The truth is,
we love you..more
than you know.
[shocked gasp]
Chibi-Usa.
We are your friends.
[sounds of struggle]
Black Lady.
[gasp]
Do not listen
to their nonsense.
The truth lies
in total
darkness.
Receive its power,
Black Lady.
I will send you the
energy of the Malefic
Black Crystal
once again.
Wiseman's right.
I won't allow you
to fool me.
Chibi-Usa! You
mustn't let this
evil energy
possess you!
This world will turn into
darkness and I won't let
any of you interfere!
[quick grunt]
[sounds of distress]
To win this battle,
to stand strong against
this enemy...
You can't have a
frivolous half-hearted
love between you.
[grunt]
Unless the two of you
share an unbreakable
bond of love...
You will not be
able to overcome the
danger that you
will face.
I've just begun!
I'll fill this world
with darkness!
[evil laughter]
I'll find a way to
save you, no matter
what it takes!
Sailor Moon,
I'll help you.
We'll overcome this
challenge with our
love and together we
will save our daughter.
Alright!
Chibi-Usa,
we're going
to save you!
The evil energy that
possesses you...
We're going to
remove it!
I will not let
you defeat me!
Bring it on!
Moon Crystal Power!
What?!
[stunned gasp]
Ah!
She's...
...no longer Sailor Moon!
She's become
Neo Queen
Serenity!
No way!
Listen to me, Small Lady.
Try to remember...
...back to when you
were just a child...
[startled breath]
[sounds of discomfort]
[loud crying]
Crying won't
help you.
[small sniffle]
Oh Mommy
I hate you!
Daddy...Help
me up!
Get up by
yourself.
Chibi-Usa, do you
understand why
we didn't help you
up back then?
It's because you
needed to know
you had the strength
to stand on your own.
We held back because
we wanted to raise you to
be the kind of girl
who can meet any challenge.
No matter how
difficult it
might be.
It was out
of love?
What a poor
love-starved bunny
you are!
Don't be fooled
by their sweet words!
Usagi!
Mamoru!
You mustn't
trust anyone.
Humans are born alone,
and in the end, they die
alone.
The only thing
you can trust
is the darkness.
I was born alone,
and i'll die alone.
I can only trust
the darkness.
Daddy! Mommy!
Come back!
Don't leave me!
You see the truth!
You were always
alone!
Yes. I have
always been alone.
That's only
an illusion!
She's right!
Don't be tricked!
The memories are clear,
I was always alone.
And nothing you
can say can change that!
[screams of terror]
I can see the truth!
[groans of pain]
Small Lady! Listen to
me, please! You must
leave this place
immediately!
It's dangerous, not
just for your mind,
but for your body
as well!
The same goes for you.
If you stay here much
longer you are sure
to die.
So go ahead
and leave while
you can!
It's not my
life that's
important!
The only thing that
matters is that you
survive.
Remember, Small Lady...
Everybody experiences
pain and sadness within
their lives.
There are times when
you feel like
burying yourself
within your sadness.
But you have to find the
strength to bear
it and move forward!
Despite everything that
happens to us, we must
always hold tight to our
memories of love!
Please, try to
remember!
[sweet giggling]
Those happy
memories you
shared with
everyone...
I know those times
were not illusions.
They were real
experiences, fueled
by real feelings!
[disgusted reaction]
Chibi-Usa!
Trust me when I
tell you you're
not alone.
So warm...
What you're feeling right
now, is the deep emotional
connection that human
beings share.
Tell me something.
Why do you care so
much about me?
Because I have always
loved you and I
always will, Chibi-Usa.
I believe you
now, and it
warms my
heart.
Chibi-Usa!
She's back to
her former self!
They did it!
Thank goodness.
Sailor Moon, R!
Chibi-Usa...
Chibi-Usa!
[concerned gasps]
Can you hear me?
Please wake up!
[gasp]
Sailor Moon,
is that you?
Welcome back.
Thank you.
For saving me.
I understand now,
I'm not alone!
You've all been
with me the whole
time.
And knowing that,
made me feel all
warm inside.
And I hope you
realize that you'll always
be first in Neo Queen
Serenity's heart.
Yes.
I'm so glad
that you're alright.
[small breath]
[startled gasp]
Sailor Moon!
Are you okay,
Usako?
I think so.
But, Sailor Moon...
Don't forget you used
the Silver Crystal!
It's alright,
I'm fine.
[panicked reactions]
What's happening?
You may have stopped
Black Lady, but the
Dark Gate has
already opened!
[grunt]
[evil snickering]
Soon, the immense
energy of the Malefic
Black Crystal will
reach Earth!
And once it does, there
will be no stopping it!
The destruction
of this world
is at hand!
[sinister chuckling]
Not if we can
help it!
[satisfied chuckle]
Fools! You people
will be destroyed,
along with this cursed
planet!
[painful screaming]
What's that?!
The Dark Gate is
about to open!
It looks like
we were too late!
[evil laughter]
[screaming]
We have to do
something quickly or
Earth will become a
wasteland!
I won't let
that happen!
I will use all
my power to prevent it!
What?!
I love this planet...
...and everyone
on it.
The Earth is filled
with so many memories.
I can't let it
just disappear.
The people who live
here must be protected
at any cost.
This threat ends now!
You're in no condition
to use the Silver
Crystal!
She's right!
Sailor Moon!
You'll die!
Don't do it!
Your Silver Crystal is
no match for my
awesome power!
[various gasps]
[struggling breath]
[grunt]
[battle cry]
You're wasting
your time.
Now that the Dark Gate
is open, the Silver
Crystal is powerless!
[groan]
She's too weak!
Sailor Moon!
We have to help!
But how?!
Usako!
[whimper]
I'm sorry!
It's my fault!
I'm the one who
caused all of this!
Chibi-Usa...
If it wasn't for
me you'd be safe!
What have I done?
What is this?
I see now...
The Silver Crystal!
It didn't disappear!
It became
a part of me!
What are you doing?
Listen, Mamo. I'm going
to use the Silver Crystal
to protect everyone.
Chibi-Usa, if you use
that Silver Crystal
you might die.
It doesn't matter. You
all risked your
lives to protect me.
Chibi-Usa...
Alright.
Then we're going
to help you
fight this thing!
Yes! It's all up
to us, we can't
afford to lose!
We made a vow to
protect this
beautiful planet!
We're doing this
for all the people
who live here.
And to guarantee
their future!
Forget it!
You're wasting
your time!
[groaning in pain]
[heavy effort]
[yelp of pain]
Please Silver Crystal,
I need the power to
protect everyone
that I love.
What?! A second
Silver Crystal?!
[gasp]
Chibi-Usa!
Give me your strength,
right now!
Mercury Star Power!
Mars Star Power!
Jupiter Star Power!
Venus Star Power!
Moon Crystal Power!
I won't succumb to
the power of the
Silver Crystal!
Evil power...
...Begone from this world!
[battle cry]
This can't be
happening!
I am Death Phantom!
The Ruler of Darkness!
What happened to us?
Did we die and
go to heaven?
Oh well. At least
we were able to
protect everyone,
right Chibi-Usa?
Uh-huh!
Listen to me, neither
of you are dead.
Huh?
The two Silver Crystals
answered your strong desires
of wanting to protect each
other...
...and brought
about a miracle.
Mommy?
Everyone is waiting for
you, it's time to go
back home.
Usako, can you hear me?!
Talk to me!
Usako!
[soft sigh]
Mamo...
I'm right here.
Hey there.
[sounds of relief]
[gasp]
Chibi-Usa!
[soft breath]
Usagi?
I'm so relieved!
Chibi-Usa!
The dark power of
the Malefic Black
Crystal has vanished!
They did it!
The Sailor Guardians
saved both Earth and
Planet Nemesis!
Thank goodness!
[sighs of relief]
Thank you for everything!
Thank you, Chibi-Usa.
I guess it's time
for goodbye.
I'm gonna miss
you telling my
fortune.
Take good care
of yourself.
Thank you for helping
me with my homework.
Be sure and give our
best to the Sailor
Guardians in the future.
I won't forget about
all the good lunches
you made!
Will you remember
not to wet your bed?
Oh, those days are
so over!
But I'm gonna
miss playing
with you.
[nervous breath]
Go on, Usako.
[emotional breath]
[hesitant breath]
Usagi, it's
your turn
to say goodbye.
Usako...
[breathless gasps]
I love you, mommy.
Chibi-Usa...
Goodbye everyone!
Goodbye for now, Chibi-Usa.
Usako...
[content reaction]
[heavy panting]
[excited panting]
Mommy!
Welcome home.
Mommy...
Yahoo! Sailor Moon
is about to start
its third reason!
But before we do,
we have something
special for you.
A bonus episode with brand
new scenes and images
from the upcoming season!
We hope you'll
keep watching!
Usagi, since it's our third
season, isn't it about
time someone else
played the lead?
What?! No way!
Next time on Sailor
Moon...
"Usagi and the
Girls Resolve:
Prelude to a New Battle"
Be sure and tune in!