Look Natsumi, I know life can be
tough sometimes, but that's no
reason to stop coming to class.
You're my friend, so if there's
anyway I can help you, just let
me know!
Huh? There's a Makai
Tree in your house?
Well if that's
the case...
I am Sailor Moon.
And in the name of
the Moon...
I'll punish you.
"Disconnecting Love:
The Raging Makai Tree."
[sigh] Here I am looking
perfect on my day off and
yet the boys don't seem
to notice.
Seriously, what is
wrong with them?!
Today for sure,
I'm going to steal
Usagi's heart!
Today's the day.
I'm determined to find
a way to steal Mamoru's
heart.
What a surprise
to see you,
Mamoru!
Hey there,
Natsumi.
Isn't it a wonderful
coincidence, running
into you here?
[giggle]
[startled]
Yeah. Sure is.
What a surprise, Usagi.
I never expected to bump
into you here.
Me, neither.
Just being able to spot you
here among all these people
is almost a true miracle.
It sure is.
(Mamoru)
C'mon, now.
Let go already!
Huh?
[giggles]
You're so cute when
you get upset with me!
Mamoru...
And Natsumi!
Why look who's here.
If it isn't little
Bun-Head.
Hello, Brother.
Here on a date
with Tsukino?
You told me you
were going off
to the library!
And you said you were
going to a friend's
place to study!
[groan]
(Ail)
Natsumi, Wait!
What is it about him
that's so special?
What about
her, Ail?
[gasp]
Why is this
happening
so suddenly?
It really
is bizarre.
It must be reacting
to you chasing after
Tsukino.
Oh, look who's talking
you've done quite a bit
of chasing, too!
You know what happens
if it wilts and dies.
We won't have an energy source.
How will we be able to go on?
I'm well aware.
But we have no
choice, we must
feed it.
Even if it now
needs a larger
amount of energy.
How exciting! They're
doing a Sailor Moon Show!
[giggles]
I'm a superstar!
Hope they were able
to find a good lazy
goof ball to play
the part.
Luna!
I am the Pretty Guardian who
fights for love and for justice.
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name
of the moon...
I will punish you!
Sailor Moon has
sure become famous,
hasn't she?
She sure has. I never
imagined she'd become
this popular.
We should feel proud
to have met her.
I know!
[startled]
Yamandakka!
Whatever it is,
it's sure weird
looking.
Ya..Man..
Dak..Ka!
W-What is that?
Yamandakka!
[confused screams]
[fearful screams]
[pained moan]
Yamandakka, Yamandakka,
Yamandakka, Yamandakka.
[gasp]
What is this?
What happened?
All of them have had
their energy stolen!
And this time every bit
of it's been drained from
their bodies!
That's never
happened before.
[gasp]
Not these two
again!
Yamandakka, Yamandakka,
Yamandakka.
That's strange.
There's no reaction.
Something's definitely
different this time.
That can only mean.
What?
It means the Makai Tree
is unable to adapt to
this planet's environment.
That can't be!
What if it is?
What are we going
to do about it?
Yaman..
..dakka.
(Haruna)
So it looks like Umino
and Miss Osaka are out
sick.
And Miss Ginga
is also absent.
Most likely her brother,
Seijuro Ginga, won't be
here, either!
And how did you know
that, Miss Tsukino?
[chuckles]
I can't reveal my sources
but it's a pretty safe bet!
I don't understand why
we have to go along with
you to check up on them.
C'mon. I asked you
because I wanted to
walk with my friends.
Do you know if Umino
and Naru are going to
be okay?
Yeah, but they're completely
drained of energy, so I figure
they're gonna need a lot of
time to recuperate.
It looks like the enemy
has started attacking
in a different way now.
Oh I guess so.
Is anybody home?
Mm?
[small gasp]
Usagi! What a
pleasant surprise!
[fake cough]
You have matching outfits?!
Sort of weird for a brother
and sister.
Yeah, that's more of a
boyfriend, girlfriend
kind of thing to do.
You think so? Well, we lost
both of our parents when we
were very young children,
so I guess you could say we're
probably a whole lot closer
than most of the siblings
you've come across before now.
That makes sense.
Why are you
here, anyway?
It's rude to just drop
by without letting us
know you're coming.
Lighten up on the
attitude missy.
Usagi wanted to come by
because she was worried
about both of you.
Hey, Mako!
It's just annoying!
Usagi's only trying
to do a good deed.
Mm-hm.
Since you've come all
this way, why don't you
come in and have some
tea with us?
Hold on, Brother.
Please,
I insist.
Hmph!
[humming]
What is this
sensation that
I'm feeling?
Natsumi, why did
you stay home
from school?
My personal life is
really none of your
business.
I get that but we're
asking because we
were worried about you.
Worried about me?
Why would you be?
Why was I worried?
Well because I started
thinking,
maybe she's had an accident,
or hurt herself? Or maybe she's
sick?
Those are the kind of
things I worry about.
That's what
friends do.
And we're also worried,
if you miss school, you'll
fall way behind in your studies.
Oh yeah,
so what
if I do?
What happens to me is not
really any of your concern.
It's my business.
I've had enough of this!
Let's get out of here!
(Sailor Moon)
Hey, what's behind
this door- your study?
Cool!
It's automatic!
[gasp]
Don't touch that!
[startled]
You can't go in there.
I don't want you to see
how messy we are.
Then you should
ask Mako to help
you clean it.
She's an absolute
whiz at cleaning
up messes!
Isn't that
right, Mako?
[scoffs]
I can't take anymore of you
trying to butt into our lives,
so would you please leave!
[sigh]
Now.
Out you go.
Usagi, it's pretty clear
we're not wanted here...
Come on.
Okay, see you later.
Ah.. What about
your tea, Usagi?
Uh, maybe next time.
[small giggle]
How kind of you to keep
an eye out to make sure
they get home safely.
An..Do you feel what I can
only describe as a warm,
glowing sensation inside,
around your heart?
What are you
talking about?
I'm not
really sure.
I've never experienced
this before now.
Time to
wake up,
Usagi!
C'mon,
get up!
Well that's
strange...
Where'd
she go?
C'mon!
Let's go!
What are you doing
at my house this
early?!
Look I'm totally against
getting up early and I'd
love to skip school...
But we can't,
we have to go!
Oh! I didn't expect
you to be back here
so soon to see me!
Oh, uh actually,
I came over here
to get Natsumi.
Brother, tell her
that she needs to
leave right now!
Well, she did come all this way,
so why don't we invite her in
for some cake and meat buns?
Thanks!
I love those!
[giggles]
Yeah, thanks a lot.
(An)
Why did you
do that?
I'm not really
sure why I did
it.
It just seemed
right at the time.
You've been acting
strange lately.
Yesterday, he said not
to go inside, but now
I'm even more curious.
Sometimes I'm
just a bad girl.
It's pitch black.
So bright!
[struggling]
[fearful scream]
[small yell]
Usagi, are
you all right?
You weren't hurt
or anything, were
you?
W-What's with that room?!
Ah, nothing really.
I was conducting an
experiment.
What kind of
experiment?
Well, all I can tell you is
astro-botany is involved.
Wow...
Space plants.
(An)
What were you
thinking?!
Huh?
You had no right to
go into our room!
You're so rude!
I'm sorry.
Anyway, I'm not going
to school. You can go
on without me.
Oh. All right.
[happy giggles]
[small chuckle]
Be sure you both
come to school
tomorrow, okay?
[startled gasp]
There it is again..
This warm sensation
around my heart..
What could it be?
Sailor Moon...
R!
Sailor Moon! R!
What do you make
of this, Ail?
Maybe the energy
is finally having
an effect.
But it hadn't been
growing at all until
now.
What do you
mean, An?
Until it
grabbed
Tsukino.
[struggling yell]
Taking Tsukino's
energy caused it
to grow!
It can't be!
If we squeeze every drop of
energy from her, that actually
might be enough to rejuvenate
the entire Makai Tree.
Wait!
You're against it?
No, of course not,
not at all if it works.
But there's something
I'd like to try, first.
Huh?
Yamandakka!
Dakka.
Give all your energy
to that sapling!
Yamandakka!
Why are you telling
it to do that?
If we can get this sapling
to grow, then we'll have a
brand new Makai Tree with
lush green leaves.
I don't think this
is the best idea...
[gasp]
Yamandakka.
There goes our
one good sapling.
[Pain wailing]
[gasps]
Did the Makai Tree
just make that sound?
You must have been
hearing things.
Ail, what exactly
is the Makai Tree?
You should
know that!
The tree is our
precious life source.
Something passed
down from our
ancestors.
Yes, but is
that all?
It also has the ability to
extract and filter the prime
energy best suited for our
bodies.
So that's it?
Yes, I believe
that's everything.
Wow! You went back
there again alone?
That took a lot
of courage, Usagi.
[giggles]
[gasp]
Usagi, there's
something on
your head!
Huh?
[pained yelp]
Hmm...
Huh?
[scream]
What is
that thing?
It's really creepy.
Luna, did you find
out anything?
Yes, this plant has
a terrible secret.
It's quite dangerous.
Show them, Artemis.
Huh?
I don't
want to!
Artemis!
All right I'll do it.
[small whimper]
[scream]
[scared yells]
[pained yell]
Do you understand?
Not at all!
[groan]
Looks like it
steals energy,
doesn't it?
Exactly!
How did you ever manage to get
that thing stuck on you anyway,
Usagi?
Uh...
What Luna and I discovered
is almost unbelievable.
Huh?
Wait for it?
Stop with the suspense
and just tell us.
This is a small branch
from the Makai Tree.
Makai Tree?!
Oh...
I get it.
So what's a
Makai Tree?
[groan]
A mysterious energy-sucking
tree that grows in outer
space.
That's all we really know.
And it's anyone's guess as
to what its true purpose is.
But why was such a dangerous
branch in Natsumi's apartment
in the first place?
Seijuro said he was doing
some kind of special
experimental botany project.
Which means...
Which means
what Usagi?
This thing must be
some kind of plant.
You still don't get it?
How can you be so dense?
It means that this branch
came from a Makai Tree that
might be in their apartment.
A normal person wouldn't
keep a tree like that
in their collection.
What're you
trying to say?
We're saying,
that those two
are suspicious.
Huh?
If this is true, then they may
be the ones behind the series
of recent unexplained incidents.
In other words, Seijuro
and Natsumi are actually...
Ail and An!
C'mon.
No way!
Usagi, it's too
risky to go there
by yourself.
But, thing is I gotta tell
you, I'm still having a hard
time believing that Seijuro and
Natsumi are actually Ail and An.
I understand how you
feel Usagi, but...
No, no you don't.
I'm going there
again to look around.
It's dangerous!
Well, maybe I'll
go there some
other time.
[sign]
She just makes
me crazy!
Hey! What's up,
Bun-Head!
Hi! Mamoru!
Where are you
going?
Right there.
Huh?
I heard Natsumi isn't
feeling well and has been
staying home from school.
That's not true!
I don't know where you
heard that, but she's
faking it!
Mm?
[small cry]
Why would you even be
thinking about her in
the first place?
Well, she did help us in
putting together that Snow White
play, so I thought this would be
a chance to thank her.
Ah-h! Wait! She has a
Makai Tree inside her
apartment!
It'll take away your
energy if you're not
careful!
Wow, an evil tree?
Now I've heard everything.
[chuckles]
I'm serious!
Mamaru!
Wait, Usagi!
Oh you came all this
way to check up on me?
Why would you do that?
Friends worry when friends
get sick, and just wanted to
see if you were all right.
I don't know what it is, but I
have this warm feeling around
my heart.
You should go back
home now, while you
still can.
Oh, how nice to see
you back again so soon.
And since you're here,
won't you please come
in and stay awhile?
Huh!?
(Ail)
Oh, Usagi,
you're here
again!
Please stay for tea.
I saved the meat buns
and cake for you from
last time.
Great!
All right! I hope
I get to eat
them this time!
[chewing]
I need to find a way to
get her alone with the
Makai Tree. But how?
[chewing]
Wow! What a
great view.
You can get an even better
view standing on the balcony.
Why don't you show him
the view from outside,
brother?
Hm?
Right.
Hmm, That'll do.
Ah-h!
Tsukino.
Huh?
There's something
interesting that
I want you to see.
Oh?
It's there, just inside
that room you were curious
about before.
What should I do?
I want to go inside,
but it's probably
dangerous.
The truth is.. We're being
threatened by something
behind that door that's
very frightening.
Something
frightening?
Yes, it's been
living in that
room.
[scared groan]
But it's asleep now,
so it's safe to go in.
C'mon.
Uhh..
Maybe we should do
this another time.
[scared chuckle]
Now is the
best time.
[yells]
Yamandakka,
make sure this girl
doesn't get away!
What?!
Dakka!
[scream]
(Makai Tree)
I can't take it anymore!
Enough! Enough! Enough!
Dak.. Ka?
(Makai Tree)
Enough of this!
[screams]
[gasp]
What's
wrong?!
Hey! What's going
on in there?!
[yells]
This wasn't
supposed to
happen!
[screams]
Help me!
[yells]
[groan]
Bun-Head?!
Usagi!
[struggling yell]
Yamandakka!
[screams]
Dak.. ka.
What's going on?
It's huge!
We can't get inside
with this thing
blocking us!
Everyone
transform!
Got it!
Mars Power!
Mercury Power!
Venus Power!
Jupiter Power!
Make up!
Sailor Mars!
Sailor Mercury!
Sailor Venus!
Sailor Jupiter!
Let me handle this one.
Supreme...
...Thunder!
It didn't work!
(Usagi)
[screaming]
[gasp]
(Usagi)
[continued screaming]
Seijuro is Ail...
...And Natsumi is An.
You two, please stop the
Makai Tree! Don't hurt
anyone anymore!
Usagi...
I don't care what happens
to me. Just spare everyone
else! Please!
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"True Love Awakens: The Makai
Tree's Secret."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.