Yikes! I can't believe there are
people in this world so
heartless that they would
abandon their pets like this!
At least these pets found
someone nice to adopt them.
What's this?! The Black Moon
Clan is using these dogs and
cats for their evil schemes?!
That's just not right!
Listen up you creeps, I am
Sailor Moon!
And in the name of animal
lovers, I'll punish you!
You thieving cat!
Take that!
Hey! Dammit! Ya big
mooch, come back here!
If I get a hold of you,
the fur's gonna fly!
[Heavy Breathing] Damn! Where'd
he go? That darn fur-ball!
[Heavy Breathing] I thought he
was gonna kill me!
You push things
too far, Artemis.
C'mon Luna, cut me some slack! I
was trying to find the enemy's
hideout!
Then why is it that you're only
searching at restaurants?
You sure you're not just trying
to find a way to get some free
food?
[Guilty Exhale]
You're gonna have to do better
than that, or people will say
you're nothing but a furry
freeloader.
Well!
[Grunts] Not only does Usagi not
do her laundry, she won't even
put her clothes away!
Open up!
Hmph!
[Grunts]
"Artemis' Adventure: The Monster
Animal Kingdom"
I'm really sorry, Artemis!
Does that bump hurt
when I touch it?
[Screams]
That thing looks as
round as the moon!
[All Laughing]
That's a good one,
Chibi-Usa!
[Grunts]
Hey, don't get mad, we were
only having some fun!
It's okay.
He's just mad cause he hasn't
gotten much done lately.
Huh?
Hey Luna, I heard that!
Uhh, maybe you should have gone
a little easier on him, Luna.
You think so?
Don't you worry. I'll be your
mediator and patch things up
between you two.
You can consider it
already done!
Oh I'll consider it done
alright. [Groans]
[Humming]
Artemis, what's wrong?
I'm a proud cat, and I refuse to
be insulted!
I see! So then you had a fight
with Luna?
[Gasp]
You know, there's this old
saying that goes "Fortune favors
the old."
Actually the saying is "Fortune
favors the bold" it's not the
old.
Uhh, well some say it that way!
Anyway, it means you can't
expect to accomplish anything
unless you're willing to get out
there...
...put yourself on the line, and
take a real risk!
Take a risk?
Okay! I'm gonna take some
real action. That'll show Luna
and the rest of them!
Hmph!
Hey what's up? Where're
you running off to?
So Luna, you think Artemis is
back at Minako's place?
[Heavy Breathing]
[Screams]
[Moans]
[Giggling] You're so clumsy!
Don't call me clumsy again!
Let's all just calm down.
Consider me your mediator. I'll
handle this!
How about mediating
your foot off my head?
Oh, sorry!
[Grunting]
[Gasping]
[Laughing]
[Grunting]
Huh?
He left because of
you, Luna!
What're you talking about Usagi,
you were laughing too.
[Meowing]
Huh?
Wha...huh?
[Meowing]
Where's he taking those cats?
This is my chance to finally
take some real action!
[Whining]
Hey, here you go!
That's a good
boy, enjoy it.
I see, he's kidnapping animals!
Go on boy, hop in!
Hmm?
[Laughing]
It looks like our Negative Point
is located somewhere inside
those gates.
[Giggling]
Being as beautiful as I am is
such a curse.
Hmm?
You stupid mutt! I am not a fire
hydrant!
Hey! Come back here! When I get
a hold of you, you'll be sorry!
Ami? Wasn't that Artemis
going by in that car?
I wasn't looking, I was
memorizing my one-hundredth
English vocabulary word.
Do you think learning a hundred
a day is too few of them?
For you that sounds
about right.
[Birds Chirping]
Just what is this place?
[Animal Noises]
So I think all these animals
could use a checkup.
Why sure, all of you are so
lucky you were picked up by
this nice gentleman.
Hmm.
[Screaming]
[Laughing]
The Negative Point is
right here!
Dark Henge!
Come forth, Droid Dogbar!
Dogbar!
Hmm.
Oh my!
Bravo Dogbar! [Laughing]
[Laughing]
Master Esmeraude, please try to
keep your voice down, Dogbar!
My bad.
What?! Artemis went to
the Great Animal Kingdom?
Why in the world would
he go there?
So, what kind of place
is that exactly?
It turns out it's a shelter that
houses and takes care of animals
that have been abandoned.
And when people are looking to
get a new pet, they can go visit
there and adopt one.
Well now I'm sure!
He ran away!
[All] Ran away?!
Artemis is always getting teased
by Luna, so he must have finally
had it!
Decided to give up on living
with us and he's run away to the
Great Animal Kingdom!
That's totally absurd.
And there's only one of us who
can get Artemis to come back.
Luna! It's up to you!
It's not my job to fetch him.
You're completely overreacting.
I cannot even believe you would
say that. You've gotta help him,
he's your friend!
You were being pretty
rough on him, Luna.
Artemis probably left because
you hurt his feelings.
You know, the Great Animal
Kingdom doesn't just have cats
and dogs, it has alligators!
[Screams]
And giant hungry snakes!
It's even got tigers!
[Roars]
[Screams]
By now, Artemis might already
be...
Turning into a ghost!
Okay, I get it! I'll go convince
Artemis to come back.
Wait! Did I hear that you're
going to the zoo? I wanna go
too!
Look Chibi-Usa, we're not going
to visit the Animal Kingdom for
fun.
Hey! No fair! If you don't let
me go I'm gonna tell Mamo!
Well in that case, come along!
[Groans]
I think that Luna
should handle this.
I agree.
Luna, bring Artemis back before
he ends up looking like this!
[Sighs]
Sailor Moon R!
[Birds Chirping]
Guess I was worried over
nothing. I'll head home.
Huh?
[People Cheering]
Huh?!
What? That's unbelievable!
Now! I will show you some more
amazing animal tricks! Dogbar!
[Cheering and Clapping]
Dad I want that white kitty,
that's up on top!
[Growls]
[Screaming and Crying]
[Screaming]
[Laughing]
[Growls]
Something's definitely wrong
here! [Heavy Breathing]
[Heavy Breathing]
Artemis!
Luna, why're you here?!
I'll explain later,
get in here!
[Growls]
[Exhales] That was
a close one.
Well, explain yourself.
I came here to take...
Huh?
Oh, I was just passing by, saw
you and thought I'de say hi, but
enough about me...
Artemis, what are you doing
running around this place?
Whaddya mean?
Did you mess something up again?
[Grunting] No, but I'm very
busy, I'll see ya.
Those cats and dogs might've
been influenced by the Black
Moon Clan. This is my chance to
really prove myself.
Hmm?
Quit following me!
What's with the attitude? I came
here cause I'm trying to look
out for a good friend.
[Gasps]
I'm going home. Hmph!
Wait, Luna came here for me?
Why'd I act like that! What's
the matter with me?
I'll be seeing you, Luna. If I
live through this.
[Grunts]
Artemis?
[Screams]
Oh boy!
[Screaming]
Help!
We're surrounded by them!
[Frightened Murmurs]
Dogbar!
[All] What's going on?
[Screams]
Look out! [Screams]
[Laughing]
Dark Henge! You're growing
beautifully!
[Laughing]
[People Screaming]
I wonder why Luna's taking so
long to find Artemis.
I don't know. Maybe she got lost
in there or something.
Why are they running?
[Screaming]
Hmph.
Something bad's happened in
there!
Minako, time to transform!
Mhmm.
Moon Crystal Power Make Up!
Venus Star Power Make Up!
[Laughing]
[Attacking Grunt]
[Grunts] Damn! I'm not gonna
just sit here and let them do
this!
What a stroke of luck to have
such a great opportunity against
one of our enemies!
I'll stop her for sure! [Grunts]
[Heavy Breathing]
[Screaming]
[Grunting]
Don't do this, come to your
senses. [Grunting]
Hmm!
[Grunts]
[Heavy Breathing]
[Grunting] Huh?
Damn it!
[Wincing]
Huh? [Grunts]
[Laughing]
Dogbar!
[Grunting]
Ya!
[Grunts]
Luna!
She's too strong! You can't
handle this Droid on your own
Artemis, we need to get help!
You're wrong! I'm going to prove
to everyone that I'm not clumsy
and I can beat our enemy alone!
Please stop, you'll get hurt.
Luna...
Dogbar!
Ya!
[Screams]
Luna!
Hmph!
Stop, Artemis!
Don't do it!
Dogbar!
[Attacking Grunt]
Venus Love Me Chain!
Huh?
Hmm? Huh!
You have done the unthinkable!
You changed the pure hearts of
kind animals into evil!
Perhaps God and Buddha
might forgive you...
But as for us, we can't!
I am the Pretty Guardian!
Who fights for love and for
justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I'm...
Sailor Venus!
And now in the name of the moon,
we'll punish you!
[Grunts] Dogbar!
Huh? What the?!
[Barking and Hissing]
Uhh, nice puppy!
[Screams]
Uh, we're in trouble.
I'll handle this!
No don't!
But we have to help out!
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
Burning...!
Mandala!
[Whining]
Sine Aqua Illusion!
All right, now try behaving
yourselves.
Hmph!
Oh, thank you! Thank you! Thank
you! Thank you! Thank you! Thank
you!
[Grunting]
Way to go, really! You saved us!
Uh, you know Sailor Moon, we've
still got some unfinished work
to do.
Ah, piece of cake!
[Grunting] Dogbar! Hah!
What's that?!
[Gasping]
Dogbar!
[Screams]
[Grunts]
We let our guard down.
We gotta free ourselves,
or we're done for.
[Grunting] Hmph!
Artemis!
[Hissing] Meow!
[Grunting]
[Hissing]
[Gasps]
Enough! Just hang on, everyone!
Moon Princess Halation!
Uhh! Dogbar!
[Grunts]
[Laughing] You're all quite
mistaken if you think you've
won!
Huh?
You peed on me again?!
I've had it!
[Barking]
They're so cute!
And so sweet! It's hard to
believe these little guys were
attacking us.
[Giggling] You look like my cram
school teacher.
His eyes look a little
like my Grandpa's.
This dog looks just like the
grandpa of the guy who
broke my heart...
Uhh.
Sorry Artemis, but I have to
say, I still think you're
clumsy.
But I guess you really do
deserve the credit for saving
everyone today.
Because of my keen
investigation, the enemy's
plan never even had a chance.
It seemed more like you
found them by accident.
Hmm.
Hey! Why did all of you
leave me behind?!
I wanted to see the
animals too! Oh!
[Screams]
[All] Silly Artemis!
Aw come on guys!
Wait what?! You're saying
Ami cheated?!
I've never done such a thing!
Yeah! Ami's not that kind of
person! Why won't you believe
her?!
Everyone thinks I cheated, even
my friends. I don't know who
to trust anymore!
Ami, what's wrong?
No! Get away from me! No!
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"The Terrifying Illusion: Ami
All Alone"
The moonlight is a messenger
of love.