In today's episode of
Sailor Moon, We'll be
showing lots of clips
from past adventures...
...and a special sneak
peak at what's to come
for our third season.
And there's a rumor
the Sailor Guardians
might be getting a
new leader.
What?!
"Pretty Guardian Sailor
Moon. Usagi and the Girls'
Resolve: Prelude to a
New Battle."
Moon Crystal Power...
Make Up!
Hey! I'm Usagi
Tsukino and as you
know I'm also Sailor
Moon!
The Pretty Guardian
who fights for love
and for justice.
Today you're going to
get a taste of our
upcoming season.
And of course, just in case
anyone was wondering. I'm
going to continue to do
my best as the leader.
So don't pay any
attention to that
silly rumor.
Now let's get this
show started!
Woah! Where did
they come from?
Who are they?
Potential friends
or brand new enemies?
Or maybe you're getting
dumped as the series lead
and one of these girls
is your replacement.
My replacement?!
What's up? I thought
I was popular!
So Ami, is
this guy supposed
to be our new enemy?
It appears to be. But
we still don't know
what his objectives are.
Or even who he is.
And we don't know who
those two girls
are either.
It looks like the next
season is going to be
pretty intense from
the start.
Hey, go back a second.
Do those two girls look
like Sailor Guardians?
As far as we know,
the only Sailor Guardian
who exists besides
us is...
Sailor Pluto!
Those who violate the
taboo and approach
the door of space and
time...
...must be eliminated!
But since she's on permanent
guard duty at the Door of
Space and Time, she's not
going anywhere.
I wonder if Sailor
Pluto is somehow
connected to those
two girls.
Ah! I've got it!
I know what' going on.
Those two are being
recruited by Luna the
same way she recruited us!
[in unison]
What?!
[scared squealing]
First thing's first,
I wanted to say thank you for
saving me from those kids
earlier today.
[curious reaction]
A little gift
from me, just for you.
Wow! For me?
It's so beautiful.
Usagi, I need
you to listen to me.
Awesome! Thank
you so much.
[squeal]
No way! What's
going on?!
I don't believe it
I transformed!
Usagi, we weren't
actually recruited.
If you remember, long ago
we were chosen to be
Guardians by the
Moon Kingdom.
O-Oh yeah,
that's right!
Hmm...
Well then maybe the
girls came here from
the future, like
Chibi-Usa!
Hm?
[startled gasps]
[grunt]
[muffled sounds]
[confused reaction]
Who are you?
Just where did you
come from anyway?!
I am Usagi.
Huh?
But if they're from the
future...Why didn't King
Endmyion tell us that
they'd be coming our way?
Maybe he forgot?
Well...I guess we
should think positive, and
assume that they're on our
side. Right?
Then why haven't they
shown us their faces?
Oh brother!
Maybe they're just being
sneaky 'cause they don't
want us to know that they're
really our new enemies!
Well we can't say
for sure.
But there will be
others who are
clearly not friendly.
[gasp]
Hey! Who was
that monster?!
Maybe she's a Dark
Kingdom monster!
She kinda looks like
Ail and An's Cardians.
[yelp]
[shocked gasp]
[snickering]
Or she could be a
droid from the
Black Moon Clan.
No. She doesn't seem like
any of the enemies we've
come across before.
I'm still wondering about
those two new girls and
how they'll fit into
our story.
Time to finish you!
[nervous gasp]
[terrified wailing]
Who are you?!
Oh, I got it!
I bet those two girls are
here to watch over us, and
will show up in the knick
of time to save us.
Just like Tuxedo Mask!
That would be nice.
[gasp]
Morga...You
failed me.
You fool.
It would be a refreshing
change if our leader
didn't need to be saved
all the time.
Yeah I think another
one of us should take
over as the leader
in the new season.
Huh? What are
you talking about?!
I love being saved
by Tuxedo Mask!
Sailor Mars!
Sailor Mercury!
Sailor Jupiter!
Sailor Venus!
Play time is over.
Who are you?!
Who am I,
you ask?
I am Crimson Rubeus
of the Black Moon Clan.
Why are you after her?
We are on a mission to
change the future
of this metropolis.
And the only way for
that to happen is...
...For her to die!
[gasp]
[battle cry]
[grunt]
[gasp]
So, as I was saying...
Since we'll be going
up against new enemies,
it might be time for
a new leader.
Why do you
keep saying that?!
[giggle]
Don't worry Usagi, it's
gonna be alright.
You'll see.
Just leave everything
to me!
Hey-hey-hey-
hey-hey-hey!
Well, I'd like a
chance to try out for
the leading role.
Now just hold
on here!
I guess I'm not
the only one
interested in taking
over from Usagi.
What?!
I've got my computer
handy.
I think we should check
into our data bank to
see who has the best skills
to handle our new enemies
Oh, come on!
There's no point in
doing all that long
research.
I think we should just
make it easy, and decide
with a simple game of
rock, paper, scissors.
Seriously? No way!
I really suck at that game!
Then why don't we
arm wrestle
for the job?
Oh, get real!
Yeah, forget it!
Let's decide it with
fortune telling based
on who's had the best
luck this year.
Let me see...Oh!
Look at that,
it's me!
That's not fair!
I think there's
a bett way.
Why don't we decide it
fair and square with
a game of chess.
No, not chess! I
suck at that too!
You couldn't
even beat Chibi-Usa.
Thanks for reminding
me, Mako.
Let's have a staring
contest instead!
What?!
A staring contest!
Let's do it.
If you laugh,
you lose!
On the count of three
stare at me one,
two, three!
[laughing]
What a bunch of goofy
faces! You all look
so weird!
[laughing]
Laugh's on you,
you lose!
[disappointed whine]
If we keep doing silly
stuff like this,
we're going to lose
our viewers, too.
What?!
We definitely don't
wanna do that!
No way!
Then let's take a look back
at all we've accomplished and
choose who should take the
new leading role...
...based on who has
the best overall appeal
to our viewers.
Sounds fine by me!
Alright everybody, let's
learn how popular we
really are with the fans.
I can't wait
to find out!
Jeez!
I have so many wonderfil
qualities that I should
be a shoe-in! So bring
it on!
After the commercial break,
we're going all out to show
you more exciting clips
from our past seasons.
And a glimpse of the new!
So don't go away, we'll
be right back!
Sailor Moon!
Wait a minute,
what's going on?
I'm showing clips
from the next season...
...which have been
carefully kept under
lock and key, until now.
Why have they been
given to you?!
Rei's just trying
out having the
leading role.
No way!
[evil laughter]
Just leave everything
to me! I'm going
to be the new leader!
I'm the natural choice!
If you remember, I was the
big star at the T.A.
Girl's Academy School
Festival!
[cheering]
And just watch
how I handle these
action scenes.
[grunt]
[battle cry]
As you can see I am more
than qualified and I have
no worries about my
popularity.
But if you take
the lead...
The show will be overloaded
with craziness from all your
goofy faces and epic fails.
Oh yeah?
Yeah it could get too
silly and turn off
viewers who're looking
for a story.
[chattering]
Fire...!
[surprised reactions]
Soul...
[hearty laughing]
Hey! I am not
the comic relief!
[small whines of pain]
What about me? I've
got plenty of star
qualities.
She barely bumped you.
That's pretty low,
trying to con an
innocent girl.
Why you!
[grunt of pain and shock]
I'm not only strong...
...but I'm agile, as
you may remember
from my ice-skating
episode.
[battle cry]
Let's do this!
My domestic skills
are outstanding too.
I'm a super-duper
cleaning whiz, and a
terrific cook.
My appealing abilities
make me the best-
suited candidate.
You won't admit your
weaknesses!
I, on the other hand,
don't have any!
But since you offered...
[chewing effort]
Yeah Mako, your big
weakness, is you can't
get over the guy who
broke your heart.
Well you should talk,
you're in the same
boat Minako.
No way! I am not hung up
on any past boyfriend, and
I'd be perfect for the new
lead!
After all, I was the
original Sailor Guardian,
formly known as Sailor V.
[painful yelp]
Back in those days,
they made all kinds
of Sailor V merchandise!
Anime! Video games!
Even pencil cases!
I was super popular,
and kids just love me!
[cheering]
You're right. We won
because they believed
in us.
[yelling]
Why is this happening?!
I can't stop this thing!
Sorry about that!
[screaming]
You may have been a
superhero to those
kids...
But when you tried
to be our nurse, you
were clumsier at it
than I was!
What do you mean clumsier?
You girls are so
alike, you even look
alike!
I don't see
that at all!
Groups of five, really?
But why?
Well-
It sounds suspicious!
Don't you wanna
check it out and
see what's going on?
Rei has a point. You
guys act like twins
when you're together.
But, I'm not
a ditz like Usagi.
And I'm not nearly
as clumsy as you!
Need I remind you
what happenedn when
you tried to
ice-skate.
You really don't
need to bring that up.
At this point, I
guess I'm about the
only candidate left.
But taking on the
leading role really
isn't for me.
Don't let that stop
you from showing
off all your best
moments!
Oh, it's not like
that at all.
I'm just trying to
share some useful
advice for the kids
watching our show.
Uh-huh...
Wait, I know what must
have happened. You
stopped using the crystal
disk, didn't you?
I did! Studying should
be done on your own.
Using the disc was like
cheating, you jerk!
When I do turn into
an evil monster...
Don't hesitate to kill
me immediately!
You're wrong. The
future is something
you create yourself.
if you give in to
negative thoughts,
nothing will change.
You can create any fate you
want, if you just believe
in yourself enough to
know you can do it!
Mm-hm...
That's what a friend
of mine told me...
She said I was in
denial and that I
should just be more
honest with myself.
But Ami...
Sacrificing yourself
is certainly noble...
But be honest, wouldn't
you really rather keep on
living as a human
being instead?
Seems like you've
forgotten about the
people who will be
very sad if you die.
Mercury!
You saved us!
You came back!
How come?
Friendship is just
way more important!
[soft giggles]
You're the one
I'll never forgive!
What?!
[shocked gasps]
[frustrated grunt]
Why weren't you
fooled by my
hallucinations?
How did you resist
my dark power!
Your dark power
could never deceive us!
Our hearts are connected
by trust in one another.
[pleased reactions]
You tell her!
We don't have anymore
time to spend in
the past.
It appears our new
enemy is getting ready
to make a move.
Oh sure, you say that
after you show us all
your clips.
Make way, 'cause now
it's my turn!
[painful reactions]
Stop it!
[defeated whimpers]
Even if you went out right now
and bought us the finest haute
couture trend-setting designs
as replacements...
I can't forgive you
for trying to shred
our Sailor Guardian
outfits!
[shocked gasp]
I am Kunzite! A
proud member of
the Dark Kingdom's
Four Kings of Heaven!
You can't make me
yell out refresh ever!
[battle cry]
What?!
[shocked gasp]
Impossible!
Crawl like a toad
while my gravity
grinds you into
a muck. Ha!
[struggling]
[nasty chuckle]
Now die.
[small groans]
[laughing]
[struggling]
[surprised gasp]
[painful struggling]
I'll never give up!
[painful groan]
I will save
my friends!
[triumphant laugh]
That's what I'm
talking about!
The undisputed, very
appealing lead heroine
is me, Sailor Moon!
Well I don't know
if I'd go that far...
But i'll admit, it
does look like you've
been doing your job
as a superhero.
Right?! Right?!
But we can't say
the same about your
personal life.
That's the truth.
You're a very
sloppy eater.
And you act around
Chibi-Usa's age most
of the time.
There's no sign
you're improving
your study habits either.
Why are you all
picking on me?!
[wailing]
We're not picking on
you. We're just trying
to be honest.
Yeah, we're just trying
to get you to see what
you need to work on...
...so you can be more
serious about being a
guardian and a princess.
That's all.
Yeah, we just want
you to be the best
that you can be.
Huh? Oh wait, so does
that mean you're not
really upset with me?
Of course not. We all have
weaknesses we could work on.
But we wouldn't be Sailor
Guardians without you.
We love you!
You guys!
[struggling]
I won't be sealed away
by the Silver Crystal now
that all the Dark Energy
is mine!
[struggling grunt]
Everyone...Give
me all your strength!
Please...Right now!
Yes, we are Sailor
Guardians, putting our
hearts and minds together,
working as one.
It doesn't matter who
is the star of this show,
we're all equals.
No matter how powerful
our enemies were, we were
always able to
overcome them...
...with the power of our
friendship!
[painful screaming]
What is this?
Please Silver Crystal,
I need the power to protect
everyone that I love.
[gasp]
Chibi-Usa!
Give me your
strength, right now!
Mercury Star Power!
Mars Star Power!
Jupiter Star Power!
Venus Star Power!
Moon Crystal Power!
Evil power...
...Begone from
this world!
[battle cry]
This can't be
happening...
I am Death Phantom,
the Ruler of Darkness!
Usako...Can you
hear me? Talk to me!
Usako!
[exhausted sigh]
Mamo...
I'm right here.
Hey there.
[sighs of relief]
[gasp]
Chibi-Usa!
I feel so lucky that
I've met all of you, and
that we've become such
wonderful friends.
Let's keep this happy
energy flowing,
as we begin the new
season!
Well, I'd feel a lot
better if I knew
who those girls were.
Friends or foes? We don't
have a clue as to what
the new enemy is gonna be
like.
It'll be alright, Ami. We
won't know the answers
until we see the new
episodes!
That's true. So rather than
worrying about things we can't
do anything about...
Let's just move forward!
After all, as long as we
always continue to work
together, we can overcome any
challenges that come our way.
You're right.
That's all for now, thanks
for watching! And be sure to
check out our new season!
See ya later!
With the Death Phantom
finally defeated, it
was time to have
some fun!
Or so I thought!
[yelp]
Now we have to study
for entrance exams!
Can you believe it?
We're already in
our final year of
middle school!
Rei, what's wrong?
It's coming...
The silence is coming!
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: "Premonition of the
Apocalypse: The Mysterious
New Guardians Appear."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.