Saphir lost his life
trying to tell his brother
Demande the truth behind
Wiseman's betrayal.
And now, Demande
is about to share
the same fate!
Wiseman, you are
nothing but pure
evil!
To protect love and
justice, in the name of
the moon, i'll punish you!
Believing in Love
and the Future: Usagi's
Decision.
[heavy panting]
Sailor Moon, you and
the Sailor Guardians
must fallback to prepare
for the battle to come.
I'll stay here and
try to learn more
about our enemy's plans.
[heavy panting]
Okay, but please
be careful.
Alright everyone,
let's regroup
tomorrow at Hikawa
Shrine.
The Malefic Black
Crystal's growing so
fast. I have to hurry!
Usagi?
[soft gasp]
Oh, hi Naru.
What is it?
Is something
wrong?
[puzzled gasp]
Lately you've been
acting strange.
Could it have something
to do with that bizarre
phenomenon going
on over there?
[surprised gasp]
I knew it! You
totally know what
that's all about,
don't you?
Usagi, if there's
anything I can do to
help out, just ask.
Naru, I...
[small chuckle]
Oh come on, Naru!
What makes you think
that I'd know anything?
Of course you wouldn't!
And you wouldn't be
able to talk about
it even if you did.
Huh?
What was that?
Usagi...
[confused reaction]
Please just try to
be careful. I'll see
you at school tomorrow,
okay?
Thanks, Naru.
See you then.
Don't be late
again, ya hear?!
[concerned sigh]
Please God, I really
need you to hear
my prayer right now.
Help Usagi,
and please protect
our world.
I'm sorry Naru,
for not being able
to tell you the truth.
But i'll do
everything I can
to protect the Earth,
I promise.
The time has come.
Wiseman, you
have a lot of nerve
coming here after
ignoring my orders.
Not to mention
killing Saphir for
no reason at all!
We have toiled for
years to be able to
rewrite Earth's history.
Those not true to our
vision...Those who betray
our ideals, must
be cast off!
What made you
think you had the
right to kill him?
Gaze upon the beauty
of this magnificent
Malefic Black Crystal.
Now that the crystal
has been nurtured and
further strengthened by
Black Lady's dark power.
We have the opportunity
to fulfill our long held
dream of taking revenge
upon the Earth and its people.
For their
transgressions
against us.
Our long
held dream...
Wiseman!
Your words will
not distract me.
Why did you
defy my orders
and kill Saphir?
I need an answer now!
Saphir's passing was
a minor occurence
compared to the great
things about to come.
So are those
your true
feelings?
Prince Demande...
..Have you forgotten why
our Black Moon Clan was
forced to come to planet
Nemesis in the first place?
For ages we have hoped
for this unique set of
circumstances to present
themselves.
You're not seriously
thinking of allowing this
this chance at revenge to
slip away..
..because of
an inconsequential
casualty?
You're right. Occupying
Earth and finally getting
our vengeance has been our
clan's dream for a long time.
So go ahead
and proceed
with our plans.
But do not think
I have forgotten, or that
I have forgiven you for
what you have done.
Once we have crushed
the Earth completely
I intend to re-examine
your actions.
Consider yourself
warned.
Of course,
as you wish.
You are free to carry
out any investigation...
If you are still alive,
my prince.
[evil chuckling]
The Malefic Black
Crystal's evil energy
continues to
get stronger!
Yeah, if this
keeps up...
It'll destroy
us all.
We need to
do something,
quick.
I'm also worried about
Tuxedo Mask. After all,
he's still inside of
that thing!
The only way to
help out is for
us to go in there.
[agreeeing reaction]
[painful screaming]
Luna! Oh no...
Artemis...
We just have
to get past
that barrier!
I bet if we
transform
we can do it!
Kay, let's
do it!
Moon Crystal Power!
Wait!
[surprised reactions]
What?
I just wanna say
thanks, and that I was
really looking forward to
going out for cakes again.
I'm sorry girls...I don't
mean to be pessimistic
but I had to tell you,
just in case.
[soft nervous giggle]
Ami...
Oh, come on now!
We'll be scarfing down
cakes again before
you know it!
How about we get
the all-you-can-eat
deal the next time?
[excited giggle]
Last time,
you did eat
it all.
Hey, I didn't
eat that much!
[soft giggle]
Okay! First we
protect the Earth,
then we celebrate.
Let's go
do this!
For our
future!
We'll do our best to
save Chibi-Usa and
the people of the future
city of Crystal Tokyo!
Let's all
put our hearts
together...
...To protect
our beloved
Earth!
[soft giggle]
Right!
Please, be
careful everyone!
We're counting
on you.
Okay! Time
to transform!
Moon Crystal Power!
Mercury Star Power!
Mars Star Power!
Jupiter Star Power!
Venus Star Power!
Make Up!
Let's go!
[heavy panting]
[surprised reaction]
[painful screaming]
Sailor Moon!
Oh no!
Are you alright?
[painful gasp]
Don't worry,
I'm fine.
Come on!
One more
time!
Let's do it!
[painful reaction]
Sailor Moon,
stay strong!
We've gotta
get inside there
and find Chibi-Usa!
We can't let
this barrier
stop us!
You're the only
one who can save
Chibi-Usa, Sailor
Moon. Don't give in!
We're coming
for you, Chibi-Usa!
[wince of pain]
I'll turn you
back into the
cute girl you
once were!
And put an end
to this evil energy
forever!
Please everyone!
Give me your
strength!
Mercury Star Power!
Mars Star Power!
Jupiter Star Power!
Venus Star Power!
Moon Crystal Power!
Think they'll
be okay?
I'm sure they're gonna
come back to us in one
piece, Luna. They'll
be alright.
It looks like
we've made
it inside.
This place is
like a maze of
mirrors.
Well let's
get moving.
Wait, Sailor Moon!
We really should
be cautious!
[startled scream]
Sailor Moon!
[panting]
She disappeared.
Where do
you think
she'll end up?
We'd better
go find her!
[startled gasp]
Where am I?
Sailor Moon.
[nervous breath]
Let me welcome
you inside our
Malefic Black Crystal.
[startled gasp]
Demande!
It's a pleasure
to see you again.
[surprised gasp]
[soft quivering]
How lovely...Today
both you and the
Silver Crystal
will be mine.
[small whimpering]
Now, Sailor Moon.
You will show your
total allegiance to
me with a kiss.
I must give a
kiss of allegiance
to Prince Demande.
Sailor Moon, R!
Now, Sailor Moon...
You will show your
allegiance to me, Prince
Demande, with a kiss.
Oh, Mamo...
You will obey me
now Sailor Moon!
Obey me and be mine!
[soft gasp]
Demande...You may have
found a way to me capture
me but there is no way
you'll capture my love.
Hmph! Your love?
As long as I have
you I can take
your love!
I know what you're
doing now so it
won't work anymore!
Sailor Moon...
Look into my eye!
Demande, what you're
doing is absolutely
wrong!
Don't you know
you can't use
tricks to win
someone's heart?
You'll never find
true love that way!
There is no such thing
as true or false love.
It's all about power.
Sailor Moon, pledge
your love and
allegiance to me!
Pledge to me.
I pledge to you.
Sailor Moon!
I'll see you
at school
tomorrow, okay?
Be strong,
Sailor Moon.
Right!
[shocked reaction]
Impossible! How come
my spell isn't
working on you?!
Stop this foolishness!
Power alone never
solves anything!
Can't you see that?
Our power will
destroy all
humanity on
Earth.
Otherwise we
will have
no future!
Why would you use
your power only
for destruction?
Wouldn't it be
better if we could
all live together
in peace?
But you are the
ones who shunned
us first.
Your people could
never coexist with
the Black Moon Clan!
That isn't true!
The Four Spectre Sisters
were able to find a way,
and are now living happily
right here on Earth!
But Wiseman said...
[gasp of realization]
I wonder...
Could it be Wiseman
was lying to us?
[agreeing reaction]
That was probably
the real reason
Wiseman killed your
brother.
Saphir was trying
to warn you about
Wiseman's betrayal.
[groan]
Listen to me...
Wiseman is...
[gasp]
I just can't
believe this, but...
Those eyes of yours,
they can only belong
to someone who tells
the truth.
Sailor Moon...
Prince Demande.
Wiseman!
Sailor Moon is
in our way. She's
keeping us from
achieving our goals.
She must be
disposed of!
I don't take
orders from you!
Stay out of
this!
I have no use for
a fool who believes
the words of
some silly girl.
What's that?!
I have Black
Lady to do my
bidding now.
And the dark
power is growing
with every moment!
You're no
longer needed.
Be gone!
Finally I see
your true colors!
If you think you can
kill the leader of the
Black Moon Clan so easily..
Give it your best shot!
[grunt]
Destroying the Earth
and turning it into a
dark world...
That is what the
Ruler of Darkness,
Death Phantom, desires!
Death Phantom?
Turning the Earth
into a dark world?
Is that what you
intend?
[evil laughter]
I won't let
you do it!
Sailor Moon...
[fearful gasp]
You must die
as well!
[cry of fear]
[evil laughter]
Demande!
[grunts of pain]
So you still have
enough strength
to stand?
Then you will die
with Sailor Moon!
Don't underestimate
me!
[outburst]
[painful screaming]
[painful groans]
Demande!
Hold on!
Sailor Moon...
It appears..I was
wrong about some things.
I truly believed
moving our clan to Earth
was the only way
forward.
And I was willing
to give me life, to
make that happen.
I became so totally
obsessed with my
mission, I couldn't see
through Wiseman's deception.
So I allowed
countless lives
to be sacrificed.
I guess I've simply
forgotten what it
means to be human.
You haven't forgotten.
After all you just
saved my life.
Now that you know what
the truth is, you won't
make those mistakes again.
You're right.
But it's too
late for me.
Don't say that!
I'm glad to hear the
Spectre Sisters are
living so happily
on Earth.
And the fact that
you and your friends
tried to save Saphir...
Makes me think we
might actually
have been able
to all live in peace.
[small breath]
We can do it!
With your help we
can make anything
happen!
[touched exhale]
These tears of
sadness, are
for me?
You are the ones
who will create
the future.
Please promise
to look after
my people..
The Black Moon Clan
back on planet Nemesis.
[quiet sob]
I thank you...
Sailor Moon,
I love...
Demande!
Prince Demande!
Huh?
[painful yelp]
The Legendary Silver
Crystal that possesses
the power to change
the world!
Give it to me!
But I saw you die!
I am an
immortal being.
I would rather die,
than give you the
Crystal!
You will hand
it over to me!
Tuxedo Mask, help!
[evil snickering]
Help? Would you
care to see where your
Tuxedo Mask is now?
Your precious Tuxedo Mask,
also known as Mamoru Chiba,
and Chibi-Usa, or should I say
Black Lady...
Have fallen in love.
You've been abandoned.
They have forgotten
you.
[soft crying]
[sinister laughter]
You're lying.
Wiseman, I know all about
your illusions and
I won't fall for your
tricks!
This isn't a lie.
[evil chuckling]
In this world,
there is nothing that
you can truly trust.
You must loathe
everyone and everything,
Sailor Moon!
Go on, instill
the Legendary Silver
Crystal with the
power of hatred!
Destroy this world!
Turn it into
eternal darkness!
It's not true...
Mamo and Chibi-Usa
would never betray me.
[evil laughter]
How could they?!
Answer me,
Chibi-Usa!
Please help me
Sailor Moon!
You must believe
in me!
Chibi-Usa...
Wait, why aren't
you under my spell?!
Chibi-Usa and Mamo
are very dear people
to me.
I know that they
would never betray me!
Well, in that
case...die!
[fearful gasp]
Using evil lies to
toy with the heart of a
pure, young innocent girl
is the work of a true coward.
I Tuxedo Mask,
will never...
forgive you!
Tuxedo Mask,
you're here!
Don't forget about us!
Sailor Mars!
Sailor Jupiter!
Sailor Mercury!
Sailor Venus!
The Guardians
have arrived!
[sinister chuckling]
You are too late,
the time has come!
Black Lady's
dark power has
reached its full
force!
The Malefic Black
Crystal's Power,
has now opened
the Dark Gate!
That will turn
your world to dust!
We won't let
that happen!
Watch as the entire
Earth plunges into
darkness forever!
[evil laughter]
Guardians, I have
discovered the
Dark Gate's very center.
We must hurry!
Right!
This is it, the Dark
Gate's center.
Ah, the
Sailor Guardians.
Look up there!
It's Chibi-Usa!
I am known as Black Lady,
messenger of the Ruler of
Darkness, Death Phantom!
This world of yours
will soon be destroyed.
Watch as it becomes
filled with hate!
[maniacal laughter]
Your world will
soon become nothing
but darkness.
Please Silver Crystal,
change Chibi-Usa back
into herself!
The Silver Crystal is
powerless against the
Malefic Black Crystal!
Die!
No, I won't
give up!
I will find a way to
save you Chibi-Usa,
and all my friends!
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"The Final Battle Bettween
Light and Dark: Pledge
of Love for the Future."
The moonlight is
a messenger of love.