Poor Koan... She's been
betrayed by the very
person she loved. Now she
no longer knows what to
believe in anymore.
And it's all because
of you, Rubeus!
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of
the moon, I'll punish
you!
Rubeus...
Your repeated failures
have greatly upset
Prince Demande.
What? Are you sure?
His patience is wearing
thin. Unless you fulfill
your mission as soon as
possible,
you may very well
lose your position.
I don't need you to
tell me that! I'm well
aware of the consequences.
I foresee that, in the
afternoon, the Rabbit will
appear, releasing a burst
of Crescent Energy.
Huh? Where?
The Hikawa Shrine,
which was once a
Crystal Point.
Yes, not too long ago we
contaminated that Shrine
with Dark Power.
Koan. I'll send her
there immediately.
A word of caution. I'm
sensing an ominous aura.
Tragedy will likely befall
Koan if she goes there.
Well, that doesn't matter.
She's merely a simple pawn.
What does matter is that
we catch the Rabbit.
Battle of the Flames
of Love! Mars VS. Koan!
Hey, Rei!
Please slow down!
I'm not walking that
fast. You need to
keep up!
But these boxes aren't
that easy to manage.
They're heavy, you know.
You're a man, aren't you?
You'd better be able to
handle them! And watch
that you don't bump
into anybody!
Hey, cut me
some slack!
Thank you!
Come again!
[screaming]
Ugh! What a klutz!
[groaning]
Huh? I'm sorry!
Are you all right!
What's the matter with
you! Watch where you're
going!
Sorry! I'm so
sorry! Sorry!
C'mon, Yuichiro!
Hurry up and pick up
all the stuff!
Ah! Right right right
right right right right!
Wait a minute. He's the
guy from that Protection
Aesthetics class.
Your bag. Here you go!
Ugh!
Man. What a loser.
Huh?
Guys like him will
never find love or
happiness.
Hey! Stop staring
at her!
U-Uh, sorry. But I think
I've seen her somewhere
before!
Huh?
Looks like you're
angry about something.
[gasp]
Master Rubeus!
Been waiting
for you, Koan.
Oh! For me?!
Of course, for you.
Who else would I want
to be by my side?
Master Rubeus...
But at the moment,
something has come up,
and I need your help
with it.
I want you to go to
the Hikawa Shrine.
Hikawa Shrine? I've
already been to that
place once before.
This time the Rabbit
will appear there.
The Rabbit?!
That's right.
This afternoon.
If I know for certain
that she'll be there,
she's as good as mine
right now!
And for you, I will
slaughter her, even
if doing so costs me
my life.
Good girl...
Do not fail
me this time.
Leave it to me.
Oh, by the way,
Master Rubeus...
When I was out shopping,
I got you a little gift. It
has a wonderful fragrance.
I hope you will
wear it, my love.
How nice...
I gratefully
accept your gift.
[gasp]
Oh my. Apparently I'm
not aware of my own
strength.
I should be
more careful.
Master Rubeus said she
would be here for sure
this afternoon.
But I don't
see her yet.
What was going on with
Master Rubeus earlier?
First he acted like he
cared about me, and
then a minute later,
he didn't.
How odd.
Welcome to the
Hikawa Shrine!
I'm at your service! What
can I help you with today?
A fortune slip?
An amulet? A prayer?
I know! How 'bout a
real exorcism! Tell
me what's bothering
you.
At the moment,
it's you, loser.
Huh?
I hope that fortune
you purchased is good
for you!
It says 'great blessings'.
My long-held wish will
come true!
Oh! This means I have
nothing to worry about.
What a big relief!
He must have been overly
hard-hearted and cold just
to motivate me, so I
wouldn't fail him in
this afternoon's mission.
Well, Master Rubeus,
I'll make myself even
more beautiful for you!
[screaming]
Koan, has the Rabbit
shown up yet?
N-No, there's been no
sign of her, Master.
Even so, you shouldn't be
standing around, wasting
time preening yourself!
I'm very sorry, Master!
How did he know?
Waiting around for the
Rabbit to appear is not
the way to get your job
done.
Get rid of every young
girl who could potentially
be the Rabbit!
I will!
See that you do, and
don't disappoint me
again, my love.
Oh! I won't! You
can count on me!
He called me "my love"!
He does love me! I should
have never have doubted it.
Yuichiro! What were
you thinking?! I told
you the chickens need to
be fed in the morning!
You idiot! How many times
do I have to repeat myself?
Heh! Those two are
certainly world's apart
from the love that Master
Rubeus and I share.
[sigh]
The sight of two teen
girls having parfait
snacks with cats...
...is pretty
pathetic.
Come to think of it,
what's Usagi up to
today, Luna?
She went over to Rei's
place to return one of
her mangas, and hasn't
come back yet.
And as usual, Ami's
busy attending cram
school.
We're the only ones with
nothing to do. You're
stuck with cats!
[laughing]
Quit laughing or we'll
get out the flea comb!
[sighs]
[hysterical laughter]
That Yuichiro
is so useless!
Rei, this manga is
extremely hilarious!
Quit making so
much noise!
And how long do you
plan on being here
reading that manga,
anyway?!
Oh, just a little bit
longer. If I take it
home, I'll never get
to it, with Chiba-Usa
and Luna interrupting
me all the time.
Yeah, so what?
Excuse me,
anyone home?
Huh?
Hi, can I help you?
I came here to show you
some new cosmetic products
that I'm repping.
My! You two young ladies
are lovely looking! Are
you models, by any chance?
Oh! Do you really
think we look like
models, Ma'am?
Uh... Ma'am?
This one is very
gentle on super-
sensitive skin.
Mmm...
If you use this product,
I guarantee that you'll
find boyfriends in no
time at all.
Or do you already have
that special someone?
Well, I wouldn't quite
call him a special
someone, but...
Hey! I do! Sort of... but
he more than qualifies
in the 'special someone'
sense.
Oh really? He's not
even a 'sort of'
boyfriend. Mamoru
dumped you.
Shush! That's enough!
I admit I'm having a
little trouble trusting
him, and he has been
rather cold to me lately.
I don't think you understand,
Usagi. To love someone you
have to be able to trust him.
If you don't trust
Mamoru anymore, you
can no longer be
in any kind of
relationship with him.
Just believe in him. No
matter how coldly he
treats you. Eventually,
he's bound to come
around and things will
go back to normal again.
You really think so?
It'll be fine!
Hope you're right!
I have to disagree.
Huh?
It's not about believing
in him, it's about him
believing in you. You're
loved because he sees how
beautiful you are and
that he can't live
without you. But
to continue to love
him when he treats
you coldly is frankly
just pathetic.
So, you're saying-
I'm saying forget
about him.
Never ever ever!
You must.
And then...
Pamper yourself with
beauty treatments to
make you so desirable
that no guy would
dare treat you
coldly again!
Wear fabulous makeup that
highlights your best
features and dazzles any
guy who comes near!
That is what love
is all about!
Uhhh...
I got so carried away
with my own speech, I
nearly forgot about
my mission here!
You know, I think
I'll pass on the
makeup.
Oh...
Well...
By the way, are there
any little girls who
might hang out in
this area?
Why are you
asking that?
Oh, I have cosmetics
for little girls, as
well. You can never
start too early.
Sorry, no little
girls here.
Well, thank you
for your time!
She was weird.
This is a bad luck day,
starting with you, and
then that lady.
[growling]
I guess they're not
expecting the Rabbit to
come by this afternoon.
In that case, I'm just
going to have to be
patient, and see if
she shows up.
Sailor Moon R!
Gotta go!
See ya later!
Oh, you leaving
so soon, Usagi?
Yeah, I'll be back
again! Bye-Bye!
See ya!
Oh...
Hop-hop-hop!
Slow down, Chibi-Usa.
Don't tell me you're
heading to Rei's place
just to read her
manga again!
What about you?!
I see what you got
there! 'Bghhh!
Ugh! She's so annoying!
Ah-h! Hey,
wait for me!
There you are.
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Ahhhh!
[screaming]
[chuckling]
I was getting tired
of waiting, Rabbit!
Who did that?
Hey, leave Chibi-Usa
alone or I'll whack
you again!
How dare you! Don't
tell me you had the
nerve to hit me over
the head with that
filthy broom of yours,
mister? What were you
thinking?
Huh?
You know how long it
takes to look this
good? Listen! No one
messes with my hair!
Got it?!
Dark Fire!
[scared breathing]
[screaming]
What's going on?!
It's Koan!
Die!
[grunting]
Get up, Yuichiro!
Run!
Right!
Quit interfering!
I've got work to do!
[screaming]
[laughing]
Die!
Oh no!
Rei!
[grunting]
Yuichiro!
But why?!
Why did you protect her,
when all she ever does
it treat you badly?
Please, Yuichiro!
All that matters to
me is that I love her!
That's the stupidest thing
I've ever heard! Why would
you love someone who doesn't
seem to care about
you at all?!
I can't stop the way
I feel. And I don't
want to!
[painful breath]
No, Yuichiro!
Please don't die!
You've gotta hold
on, Yuichiro!
You monster! I'll
make you pay for
this!
Mars Star Power!
Make Up!
[gasp]
You- You were a Sailor
Guardian all along?!
Burning...
...Mandala!
This is a surprise.
Although it sort of
works in my favor. If
I kill you along with
the Rabbit, Master
Rubeus will be so
pleased!
[grunting]
Heh!
Hah!
[gasp]
[screaming]
Agh!
Fool! If you had
abandoned him, you
could have escaped!
I would never do
that to Yuichiro!
Never! It's because
of me that he was hurt!
He was protecting me,
and I can always trust
him to be there for me!
Hmph!
I remember you said that
trust was important in
any kind of relationship.
[gasp]
You're that saleswoman!
Aren't you?!
What do you see in this
guy that you have to
protect him? I think he's
a loser without any good
qualities, he follows
you around like a lost
puppy!
The good qualities you
missed is that he's
sincere and caring!
[chuckle]
If that's it, then you
two can't win against
the love that Master
Rubeus and I share.
Ridiculous! Yours
is all about loving
yourself!
You don't even think
about how the other
person feels. Or care...
What you have is
not true love!
[gasp]
Of course it's true
love! We're very,
very close! He calls
me his love!
[gasping]
Yeah? But what do
his actions tell
you?
[gasping]
No! That's not how it
is! I'm not going to
listen! Just shut up!
[gasping]
I've heard enough of
your silly nonsense.
I'll be back to take
care of you as soon
as I eliminate
the Rabbit.
No!
Huh? What is this?
The image of love shimmering
in the sun. Come, you sad,
lost soul. Listen to the
sound of a loving heart.
Huh?
Farewell...
Hey!, you! Wait!
Come back!
[gasp]
Damn you!
I'm right here in
front of you! Take
me on!
[growling]
Koan!
[gasp]
Master Rubeus!
So? Have you taken
care of the Rabbit
yet?
Um, I'm very sorry,
Master. I did have her
for a minute, but she
got away.
Once again,
you've failed.
You've worked for me for
a long time, but you've
never had much success.
That being said, let me
add that we won't be
seeing each other anymore.
Give me one more
chance, Master.
I'm in the middle of a
battle with that Sailor
Guardian over there.
I'll kill her...
...to make up for
my failures!
You no longer have the
power necessary to
fight her.
Then you could help
me. As a couple, we
could fight her
together.
Hmph! Where'd you get
the idea we're a couple?
You're just a lowly
incompetent subordinate?
How can you say that?
I've loved you for
so long. And you
love me!
Love, you say? Ha!
What foolishness!
I've never loved you!
In truth, there is no
such thing as love in
the Black Moon Clan!
[horrified gasp]
This will be my
first and last
gift to you.
Just take it.
But...
This is...
Something to erase
that Sailor Guardian
from this world.
I think you'll find it
to be quite a useful
gift. Unlike that stupid
cosmetic fragrance
you gave me.
A Space-Time
Bomb. Oh...
He wants me
gone for good.
What? Don't
activate it!
Koan! Get rid
of it... now!
No. Too late.
[gasp]
You win.
Sailor Mars...
You were right.
My love wasn't
real.
Venus...
Love me...
Chain!
[gasp]
Sparkling Wide
Pressure!
[grunting]
Uh...
Surrender yourself
right now, Koan!
Don't try to run
away this time.
I have nowhere
to run to.
Huh?
[crying]
I've always been able
to run away and go where
I felt I was beautiful.
But now I have been
banished forever. I've
lost everything. And
it's because of you!
It's all your fault!
[gasp]
[screaming]
Agh!
My life is over! I've
lost everything! My
home! My family! My
love! There is no
future! I'm not
welcome anywhere!
It's all your fault!
Stop! Let her go!
[sobbing]
[roaring]
[gasp]
[gasps]
Sailor Mars!
You protected her?
You're life isn't
over, Koan.
You see? Now you have
a chance to start anew.
To begin with, you're
still here. And all that
was wrong before, you can
make right, a
little bit at
a time.
Your future begins
right now.
Trust me...
Sailor Moon. Please
turn her into a normal
human woman.
I wish I could, but
I don't know if it'll
work.
Use the Silver Crystal.
Let's see if that will
work on her.
Perhaps it doesn't have
the full power it once
had, but it may be able
to turn her into a normal
woman, since she's
in a very fragile
state.
Give it a try.
Hm!
Alright, then!
Please...
Silver Crystal.
Moon Crystal Power!
Refresh!
Yuichiro, I still see
streaks. In order to
get them out you'll
really need to put
your back into it!
Yes, ma'am!
My back's in it!
[sigh]
Guess I'm gonna
have to live with
it.
Yoo-hoo! Is
anyone home?
I'm here to show you
some brand new cosmetic
products that I'm repping.
Hm?
Hey! Don't I
know you?
[laugh]
You two look like the
perfect couple. I'm
a little envious.
[giggle]
Looks like you're
finally happy. Good
for you, Koan.
♪ Sailor Moon! ♪
Check!
Hold on a minute!
Usagi, this is your
one-hundred-and-first
try.
Uh! Ami, you're not only
academically smart, but
you're also a wiz at
playing chess!
Chess strengthens your
calmness and precise
decision-making skills.
Guess I don't have to
worry about that ever
happening!
You shouldn't keep
avoiding important
things, Usagi.
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"For Friendship: Ami vs.
Berthier"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.