What a relief --
Chibi-usa's all better.
But now she's back to
hitting on Mamo! The cure
for my jealousy? Cake, of
course! But who's this
mysterious woman in the
bakery? Ack! The
Guardians have all turned
into fattening treats! No
more sweets for me.
In the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
Magic of Darkness:
Esmeraude's Invasion.
See you later!
I'm so glad you
recovered and you're
feeling better now,
Chibi-usa.
Yeah! Thank you, Luna!
To celebrate, would you like
it if I took you out? My
treat. Anything you want.
Really?!
Well, that's what I'd
like to do, but I've
already spent my allowance.
So, why don't we play
hide and seek in the park?
Hey! No way! You just
said you'd treat me!
[awkward chuckling]
Sorry about that!
[grunting]
Yay! It's Mamo! I
missed you!
Hey! It's good to
see you, too, little one.
You mean it?
[seething]
Chibi-Usa!
I have a great idea!
Let's go somewhere
special together, Mamo!
I want a new notebook
and a pencil case, and an
eraser... uh, and some
donuts, too!
Okay, hold on there. I
definitely want to celebrate
your recovery, but I have
to check my wallet.
Uh?
Uh--[awkward laughing]
Yeah, that sounds like
a fantastic idea!
Chibi-usa, why don't
you spend the whole day
with Mamo?
I mean, after all,
I've got a ton of other
very important things
I need to do! Bye-bye!
Hey! Wait
for me!
What was up with her? I
thought she was going
to come with us.
Right, Mamo?
Yeah, that's weird.
[grunting]
Usagi...
It's just for today.
Chibi-Usa can't go home
to her mom, so I'll let
Mamo cheer her up on a
date. It's fine! It's
fine! It's totally
fine!
Why don't you
just go with them?
Then, while you're out
together, you can try to
make up with Mamoru?
Because it kills me to
see him spoil her and
carry her around!
They're so cute,
I hate it!
This is so frustrating!
[groaning]
[yelping in pain]
Usagi!
Prince Demande...
Hm?
Preparations are nearly
complete. I shall be departing
for the 20th century shortly,
your highness.
Esmeraude... I suggest
you to remember how your
predecessor, Rubeus, died.
You must be
extremely careful.
[laughing]
I could never humiliate
myself like that!
I have a strong sense
of grace and dignity!
I doubt that.
Saphir.
Don't underestimate the
20th Century Sailor
Guardians.
Hmm...
Why don't you take a
good look at this one
more time?
As you can see, my brother,
the prince, is struggling
with these 30th century
Sailor Guardians.
If Rubeus had completed
our plan and filled the
20th Century Crystal
Points with Dark Energy,
they never would have
been able to wield this
much power and use it
against us.
Thank you for the
reminder, Saphir.
Sorry!
This display of yours is
merely proof of Rubeus's
complete incompetence!
My plan is different.
Since I am going to be
working in the 20th
century, I intend to
permanently infuse it
with the Dark Power of
the Malefic Black
Crystal. I will plant the
seeds for our victory far
into the future.
Considering the failures
of the last strategy,
I'm confident that this
will not only be easier,
but deadly and effective!
It's an interesting
strategy, but our current
transfer methods
cannot transmit that
much Dark Power to 20th
Century Earth.
Furthermore, we would
need to open a remarkably
powerful Dark Gate.
You underestimate me.
I haven't overlooked
that...
We have a unique
opportunity... in the
primitive 20th Century
world, there are sites
known as Negative Points.
Fortunately for us, these
specific locations are
already teeming with
Negative Energy, just
waiting to be tapped. If
we drive wedges filled
with the power of the
Malefic Black Crystal
into those Points, we can
transmit Dark Power from
the future...
Once those wedges have
absorbed enough Dark
Power and fully matured,
the Dark Gate will open.
That is our chance to
strike, and we'll send a
burst of Dark Power from
the Malefic Black Crystal.
Then, we'll transform the
world into a beautiful
ebony planet! Victory
will be ours!
I've already asked Saphir
to create the Dark
Henges.
Those are the critical
wedges infused with the
power of the Malefic
Black Crystal.
Mm.
Mm!
I think it's in poor taste,
but I've followed your
instructions to shape the
henges just like you.
I'm happy to create as
many as we need, but don't
make me do unnecessary work
like Rubeus did with his
string of failures.
Understood?
I would never
dream of it!
I plan to keep this
simple. I don't want to
be apart from my beloved
for that long. [giggling]
Esmeraude, I hereby grant
you permission to carry
out your plan. Do not
fail me.
Thank you, my dear lord.
I swear I will do my very
best to please you and make
sure this plan is a success.
[laughing]
[chatting]
Check it out. The pastry
shop is having a grand
opening sale!
All-you-can-eat cakes!
Sounds too good
to be true!
My heart's racing, I
can't stand it!
It's so tempting,
it's evil!
Did you know that cakes
are remarkably high in
calories? Not only do
they exceed the
recommended dietary
guidelines, but they also
lack healthy vitamins or
nutrients.
Thanks, right,
okay, we got it.
Ami...
Don't you understand?
Cakes are nourishment for
the soul. I mean, we've
been working so hard,
I think we deserve
a treat like this to
recharge.
You'll get fat!
Shush you!
Fine. But don't
complain to me when you
get on that scale
tonight.
You know, Usagi and
Chibi-usa would love
this. Let's call them!
I already did, but they
didn't answer the phone.
Knowing those two, they'll
probably catch a whiff of
these cakes and follow the
smell here, anyway.
So! Come on, let's go
in! Who's ready for
cake?!
Me!
You'll regret it.
Oh, so this is an Earth
city in the 20th Century.
How primitive.
But I have to admit,
these people's savage
energy is kind of
charming.
[laughing]
Looks like I found a
Negative Point.
[chuckling]
Excuse me! Excuse
me! Sorry!
[gasping]
So many cakes!
I'm just gonna stuff
my face! I'm going to eat
so much, this place won't
have any left over!
[chatting]
This is my fifth one.
Yeah? I'm on my sixth!
Ah! Bliss!
When I think about all
the battles we fought,
it was worth it just to
get to this day!
I'm in heaven!
How dare those girls keep
me locked up in here while
they stuff their fat faces
with cake!
I'm goin' back
for more!
Amazing! It's so good!
So very, very good!
[gobbling]
Oh, this one's
good, too!
[gobbling]
[giggling]
How can this be so
good?! I've never tasted
anything like this! Oh!
[laughing]
I feel like I could eat
every cake on earth!
Usagi?!
[gobbling]
Stop eating and open
this basket!! Luna,
where is everyone?
See for yourself.
For crying out loud,
have some self control!
Cake fills the void
in my heart! Let go!
Cut it out, right now!
Shut up!
Usagi!
Must eat cake!
Oh, sorry, ma'am.
Oh! The nerve!
[judgmental chatting]
[gasping]
Uh, excuse me.
[awkward laughing]
[sighing]
How could I lose my cool
and get so carried away
back there?
But those cake things
were just so cute! I
couldn't help myself. Oh,
and I can't believe those
20th Century humans were
staring at me like that!
So humiliating!
Fine! Those girls will
pay a heavy price for
judging me! I'll make
all of them the first
sacrifices to the Dark
Henge! [laughing]
[laughing]
Sailor Moon...
... R!
Sailor Moon! R!
[chatting]
Wow, cake really is
nourishment for the soul.
Yeah, I have a feeling
that's especially true
for Usagi. I mean, her
soul must be famished
because she's eating
everything in sight.
... and then Mamo picked
up Chibi-Usa and they got
all cuddly! That little
girl is using her
adorable size as an
excuse to snuggle up
to my Mamo!
I'm so angry! Make it
better, Minako!
Mamo!
There, there, Usagi.
Ugh, all those tears and
snot. I've really lost
my appetite.
[sobbing]
Oh, Rei!
Ugh, Usagi...
[chuckling]
This will do.
The Negative Point is
right down here.
Come, Dark Henge!
[laughing]
Ah, the sweet sensation
of Dark Power flowing in
from the future. Come
forward, Droid!
Maxipan!
[laughing]
It'll take a while for
the Dark Henge to put a
barrier on this spot,
but in the
meantime...
Maxipan, I command you to
dispose of the girls
outside. Be sure to do it
discreetly.
Maxipan!
Now then, I have
another job to do.
[chuckling]
I've finally calmed down.
Thanks, guys. Hey, aren't
any of you gonna eat
more?
[laughing]
Wow! Look at all those
cakes!
Huh?? Chibi-Usa!?
Hey! You're
all here!
Whoa, is this how
much you ate?! My
gosh!
Why should you care?! And
whose fault is it that
I'm stuffing my face,
anyway?!
What do you mean?!
Don't pretend you
don't know!
[sticking tongue out]
This was a mistake.
[gasping]
W-What going on?
What's wrong?!
[gasping]
We've got a problem!
Uh!
Wait!
[grunting]
Who are you and what are
you trying to do?!
[laughing]
[grunting]
Give me that!
No way! This one's all
mine! I found it first!
There's something weird
about this food! Don't
eat it, Usako!
Usako?! You hear that?!
That must mean he still
cares!
That's not
important right now!
We've got a serious
situation, Usagi!
Sorry about that.
[growling]
Maxipan!
[grunting]
Ahhhh!
Get Chibi-usa out of
here! I'll handle this
monster!
Got it! Hurry, Usagi!
But shouldn't--
Quickly!
Okay!
Maxipan!
Look out!
Looks like it's time
for some exercise to
work off all those cakes.
Artemis, Luna. Make sure
you take care of
Chibi-Usa.
Got it!
Good luck, everyone.
Moon Crystal Power Make
Up!
Mars Star Power Make Up!
Mercury Star Power Make
Up!
Jupiter Star Power Make
Venus Star Power Make Up!
Sailor Mars!
Sailor Mercury!
Sailor Jupiter!
Sailor Venus!
Sailor Moon!
[grunting]
Maxipan!
[laughing]
Stop right there!
Huh?
We're the Guardians
of Justice!
And our job is to
bring down evil!
You ruined the dreams of
innocent girls...
... and trampled on their
simple pleasures!
And now, in the name
of the moon, I'll
punish you!
[grunting]
Maxipan!
[dodging]
Burning Mandala!
Maxipan!
[grunting]
Mars! Ah!
Mars! Sailor Moon!
I can't move!
I'm stuck!
We've been frosted
like a cake!
[grunting]
Maxipan!
[gasping]
Jupiter!
Watch out! She's too fast
with her sugary blast!
Venus, be careful! Her
body's been transformed!
She's as delicate as sugar!
If you bump into
her, she'll crumble
to pieces!
Are you serious?!
The same goes for all the
other girls that are
trapped here!
[gasping]
Maxipan!
Venus Love Me Chain!
[grunting]
[gasping]
Maxipan!
Ahhh!
Oh, great.
I feel like a
marshmallow.
[grunting]
Enough already!
Yeah, cut it out!
[laughing]
Maxipan!
Huh?!
[chuckling]
Tuxedo Mask!
Sugary delicacies are an
art that nourish a
girl's dreams.
These young girls admire
beauty and sometimes,
their passion can melt
their delicate hearts.
Uh, what?
While it's true that sweet
treats can melt away
one's worries,
there are other times
where it is the sugar
that melts instead.
Okay, you've lost me
this time around.
I know! I've got it! The
hint is the sugar composition
of her body! Leave it to me!
Maxipan!
Shine Aqua Illusion!
[struggling]
You did it!
It's melting!
Yes! Way to go, Mercury!
[struggling]
Max...i...pan.
Sailor Moon!
Now's your chance!
Okay!
Moon Princess Halation!
[grunting and groaning]
Wait, what the hell
is going on here?!
[groaning]
Time to go!
Huh?!
[gasping]
That's impossible!
Didn't you ever learn
it's not polite to spy?
[gasping]
Who dares to--
Oh... you're a
hottie.
Uh--farewell!
Cut it out! Don't you
dare look at him like
that!
I'll bet you're the one
who was controlling that
desert droid out front.
Ah, so you're the
Sailor Guardians
I've heard about.
Well, you're just skinny,
pimply school girls with
flat chests and flat butts.
Who are you
calling flat?
We prefer to think of
ourselves as small, but
toned, old lady!
What?! Old Lady? Is that
what you said?
How dare you! You brat!
[growling]
Right! Listen up,
pipsqueaks! You're
looking at a proud
member of the Black
Moon Clan. I am formidable
and I will do whatever it
takes to make sure we
conquer the 20th century.
Every man in this world
will kneel before me.
For I am the greatest
beauty that ever was!
Remember my name:
Esmeraude! [laughing]
[struggling]
Her awful laugh is as bad
as her attitude.
I will be the one to
defeat you once and
for all.
Your doom awaits at
the hands of Esmeraude!
[laughing]
Esmeraude.
Team, I think we just met
our new mortal enemy.
Better buckle up.
My dear Mamo, I finally
know the reason why
you've been avoiding
me lately.
You do?
But don't worry. I know
that love is forever and
our feelings for each
other will never change.
Here's the proof.
Pro wrestling.
You mean a "promise
ring"?
Next time on Sailor
Moon R: "Shared Feelings:
Usagi and Mamoru in Love
Once Again".
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.