Every one of us has a
beautiful everlasting song
inside our hearts that keeps
our spirits up through the
hardest and saddest of times.
How dare you trample on the
heart of someone with such a
lovely song!
I am Sailor Moon!
In the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
Everyone gather around!
I have something to
show you!
The amulets from the Hikawa
Shrine work wonders on
lovesickness!
And I'm telling you this,
based on my own personal
experience.
No matter how many times
I've had my heart broken,
I've always found a new
love with this.
Our amulets are the best
cure for problems of the
heart.
I could sure use one!
Me too!
[girls chattering]
Here you go! Come back if
things don't work out
for you.
Weren't you listening?
These amulets fix
everything.
Oh! That's right.
Ah! Being a Shrine
Maiden sure is tiring.
Thank you for all your
hard work, girls!
Hi, Gramps!
Ah! It's Usagi!
How come the two
of you are here?
Hey, where's Rei?
Rei is chairman of the
school festival, so she'll
be coming home late for a
few days. But would you like
to be Shrine Maidens
too, and help out?
[chuckle]
Well, that would be
pretty cool, except for
I don't want to memorize
sutras.
This is a Shinto Shrine.
Only Buddhists do sutras.
The School Festival is
for Me?! Queen Rei's Song.
A little up and to the
left. A bit more. Right
there. Okay!
Miss Rei...
What is it?
Um, I have a question
about our class exhibition.
I told you everything you
need to know about it
yesterday! How many times
must I go over it?!
I don't have time right
now. I'm busy trying to
get the stage ready!
But we've got a problem
and we're afraid to proceed
until we get your permission.
Oh, all right.
I'll come by later.
Who left this equipment
here? Somebody could bump
into it, so put it away!
Miss Rei is so
efficient.
She is!
We wouldn't be able to
have a successful festival
this year without her
putting everything together.
You two, stop standing
around gabbing, and get
working!
Okay!
Miss Rei actually spoke
to us for the first time!
Lucky us!
Ugh! Jeez! I have so much
to do that I would even
ask a cat for help.
Hey, Rei!
Huh? Oh, Usagi!
Here they are!
Luna and Artemis!
Huh?
You said you were so
busy you'd ask a cat
for help.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Did you all come here
just to make me go
totally crazy?!
Ha! Ha! We came
here to support you!
Here. Mako made some
lunch for you.
Thank you!
You don't mind if we
stay and watch rehearsal
do you?
Of course! We're just
getting everything ready
to run it.
♪ I'm not about to ignore
you. I will save you...
After all... ♪
You on the spotlight!
This isn't a cabaret!
Don't use those colors!
Cabaret?
We don't know what that
is, so we don't know what
colors not to use!
Forget it!
Take five!
Ughh...
Nobody really seems
to care but me.
Nice song! It sounded
really good, and I was
wondering who wrote the
lyrics?
Well, you have good taste
in music. As it just so
happens, I wrote every
single musical number for
the School Festival.
Huh?!
What is it? You have a
problem with the fact
that I wrote all the
songs?
[laughing]
No problem at all!
Although, it does sound
like you're using the
School Festival to show
off your personal talent.
I sure am! Why do you think
I became Festival chairman
and on-site manager? I have
a lot invested in this!
[giggle]
And here we thought
you had changed!
Thank goodness,
you're the same
Rei!
A school festival...
That means tomorrow, this
place will be brimming
with youthful energy.
I can almost taste
it already.
Yes, then the Makai Tree
will be able to thrive
once again.
Yes...
Hey, Rei! Tomorrow's
the big day!
We're gonna take the day
off from our Shrine Maiden
jobs to come and watch the
show!
Oh? Did Grandpa say
he's coming too?
Yeah. Yuichiro's said
he's going to cover
for us.
It's pretty amazing that
you wrote all the songs
by yourself.
I'll say. That must've
been a lot of work.
No, not really.
The lyrics came to
me rather easily.
And the melodies just
seemed to flow right
off of my finger tips.
I never even
broke a sweat.
It was easy. A piece
of cake. It's what
they call talent.
Rei! You're so
awesome!
Uhh...isn't it inappropriate
for the Guardians to get so
excited about these things?
I think it's all
right once in a
while.
Wow, Rei wasn't kidding
when she said it was an
all girl school.
Hey, there...
Young ladies! Oh, you're
both so cute! Would you be
interested in a part-time
job at my shrine?
I'm so sorry, sir, but
this school doesn't allow
us to take part-time jobs.
Thanks anyway!
Have a nice day!
You have a nice
one, too!
I better brush up on
talking to young girls
so I don't scare them
off.
Where's the takoyaki?
The yakisoba? The curried
rice?
Chill...
Where's Ami?
Umm, I think she went
to watch the research
presentations.
Say cheese!
Oh yeah!
C'mon, let's go over
there! That looks like
fun!
[giggling]
Ehh... I can't do it!
Oops, I missed!
[laughing]
Energy's overflowing
around here.
Yes. Let's make it
overflow inside us.
Yes...
Huh?
[gasps]
We've found him!
I just know it!
He's the guy we've
been looking for!
Junko, take his
measurements!
Right!
What's going on?
Come this way!
First, I need you to
stretch out your arms.
Huh?
Like this. See? Spread
your arms out wide.
Is this right?
That's very good. Now,
I'll need you to squat
down.
B-But why?
Just hurry up!
What is this
all about?
Shush! You need to
stay still! You're
absolutely perfect!
We're good here,
too! Just right!
I'm glad we kept looking,
but we're almost out of
time. C'mon. Hurry!
J-Just a minute!
Who are you girls,
anyway?
Oh, I forgot to
introduce myself!
I'm Sakurako Ougi. We're
all members of the Fashion
Design Club and we've been
searching everywhere to
find you, because you're
absolutely perfect to model
the outfits we designed
for today's show.
Model?
Yes! And the theme, as
you may know, is aliens
from outer space!
[gasps]
Wait! How'd they know?
[gasp]
I never expected that
we'd be found out this
quickly!
These three aren't
normal girls.
What is it? What's the
matter? You looked scared
like we'll hurt you.
Don't tell me you believe
in aliens and are afraid
if you're dressed like one,
we're likely to grab you
and run experiments
on you!
No! Of course not!
[laughing]
Come along with
us now!
Let's go!
In a few moments, this
year's Queen of the T.A.
Girl's Academy, Rei Hino,
will begin her musical
performance in the
auditorium. We invite
you to please bring your
guest and come to the show.
Wow! So Rei's queen
of this event, as well.
That's right. Everyone's
counting on her for this
year's festival to be a
huge success.
She does have very good
leadership qualities.
Mm! Someone we know
should follow her
example.
You deserved that!
I'd appreciate it if
you'd warn me first.
We'd better hurry up or
we won't be able to get
good seats.
Yeah! Let's go!
[giggling]
Are you guys
ready to go on?
Wha- What is
all this?!
A fashion show,
of course.
You're the opening
act for Miss Rei.
What is it we're
supposed to do?
I don't...
Okay! All set?
Now get out there!
[crowd laughter]
Uh...Hello!
[laughing]
Wow! They seem
to like us!
It's not so bad
after all.
Hey, who are they?
I think that's
Natsumi and Seijuro.
You're right!
What happened to his
'mister cool' image?
I can feel that
energy rising.
And there's plenty of
it, which makes this
a good place to steal
some.
Yes it does. This
auditorium is just
brimming with it.
Then I think the time
to gather it up would
be right now, my sweet.
[laughing]
Keep watching, Earthlings.
You're in for an exciting
show!
Sailor Moon!
R!
Sailor Moon R!
Thank you for your
generous applause,
ladies and gentlemen.
Next we present a
musical performance
by Rei Hino!
Finally! It's
Rei's turn to
perform!
I am so nervous!
Why's that? You're not
the one who's going to
be on that stage.
I know that...
Shh, it's about
to start.
[crowd cheering]
Good afternoon, everyone.
I'm Rei Hino, but I'd
prefer it if you'd just
call me Rei.
[cheering]
Thank you all for coming
out to see me today. I'm
so happy to have such a
large, enthusiastic turn out.
Good grief!
She thinks she's
a rock star!
Looking good, Rei!
This song is from
my heart for every
one of you!
Rei, you are
so awesome!
♪I'm not about to ignore
you, I will save you.
After all, no one's
closer than we are.♪
It's time for us to
choose a cardian.
Come forth!
Cardian Siren!
[flute music]
Siren!
[gasp]
An evil aura!
Siren!
What's that?!
It's a Cardian!
Keep away from
that shiny dust!
[groaning]
Young lady, wanna work
part-time as a Shrine
Maiden? It's a lot of
fun...
Well, looks like
it's going nicely.
All we do now is
wait by the Makai
Tree.
Siren!
[gasp]
[screaming]
Look! Rei's in trouble!
We've gotta help her.
Moon Crystal Power!
Mercury Power!
Jupiter Power!
Venus Power!
Make Up!
♪ Sailor Moon! ♪
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for justice. I am Sailor
Moon!
Sailor Mercury!
Sailor Jupiter!
Sailor Venus!
We're the Sailor Guardians!
[grunting]
I'm a star! Let me
go you monster!
Supreme!
Bubble!
Thunder!
Spray!
[gasp]
Hm?
Siren!
[grunting]
Rei, are you okay?
Look out!
Huh?
[screaming]
Siren!
[groaning]
Her hair's stealing
all our energy...
Can't free myself...
Me neither...
[grunting]
Hang on, everyone!
I'm coming!
Don't do it, Rei!
You're too weak
to fight!
M-Mars Power!
Make up!
You ruined my concert
and stole energy from
my dear fans...
Those are terrible crimes!
So now...
In the name of Mars,
I'll chastise you!
[grunting]
Fire!
Soul!
[screaming]
[gasps]
Agh! Siren!
Siren! Siren!
No way! That thing put
out my Fire Soul attack!
It's hopeless! Just
save yourself, Sailor
Mars!
Sailor Moon!
Siren!
[growling]
[gasps]
In a corner of the silent
expanse of the universe
there is a planet that plays
a lovely melody. That planet
is our Earth. But the song
created there belongs to
everyone. And if you trample
on this everlasting melody,
no matter who you are...
I, the Moonlight Knight,
will make you pay!
Moonlight Knight!
Thank goodness!
Sailor Mars, will you
please sing your beautiful
song once more?
I'll be more
than happy to!
[grunt]
[gasp]
Unforgivable...
Unforgivable!
Namah Samanta Vajraanaam,
Candamahaarosana Sphotaya
huum Trat Haam Maam!
Hnnh!
Fire!
Soul Bird!
Siren!
Ah! Siren! Siren! Ah!
Sailor Mars' true
power has awakened!
[groaning]
Your energy has returned!
Sailor Moon! Now!
You got it!
Moon Princess
Halation!
Cleansing!
Good work, Sailor
Guardians!
Don't ever forget the
light that shines in
your hearts! Adieu!
Thank you,
Moonlight Knight!
[cheering]
In a corner of the silent
expanse of the universe,
there is a planet that
plays a lovely melody...
...And that planet is
our Earth. My final song
is "Everlasting Melody".
I hope you enjoy it.
♪I feel the warmth
within my heart... ♪
♪...'Cause I know
that's where you are. ♪
♪If I never say I
love you so...♪
♪You will always be a
part of me. And now,
I thank you for giving
me the strength... ♪
♪I found this amazing
power. It shines and
embraces all that I
see... ♪
♪I love you more than I
can fathom. And your smile
it glows, surrounding me
with laughter, and growing♪
♪like a seed, and it's
flowing in the wind.
And I know there are no
more limits to my dream...♪
You know what?
Huh?
I thought that was
a lovely song.
Thank you.
I never realized, but
you're a really super
hard worker.
[giggling]
Usagi, why don't I teach
you a thing or two about
hard work?
What?! No thanks, I don't
need to be like you!
Well fine then! You're
the one whose gonna
regret it later!
Uh-uh! I'm perfectly
happy the way I am!
Are you sure about that?
Of course I'm sure!
I wouldn't say it if
I wasn't sure!
And move over!
You're hogging
the bench!
Hey Usagi! Mako seems to
be really interested in
Seijuro.
What?!
Yeah, and she said she
was even gonna make lunch
for him!
Unacceptable! A girl
shouldn't be that
obsessed with some boy!
Uhh...
I mean that's like, well
I don't know what it's
like. But, hey, I should
do that for Mamoru too!
Good grief...
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
Is Seijuro the Moonlight
Knight? Mako on Fire.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.