Under the spotlight, I
finally get to dance with
my Prince Charming! I am
the heroine of this story!
What?! Natsumi's the
heroine?! Agh! And now
there's a Cardian running
amuck?! That's it! If anyone
interrupts our play...
In the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!
Well what do we have
here? You're studying
on your own?!
Hello? Usagi?
[snoring]
Same as always...
Huh?
I wonder if this story
is making her have
romantic dreams...
You know, some day, I hope
and I dream that I will
share a passionate kiss
with a wonderful male cat!
[kissing noises]
[falling grunts]
Aw! I was having this
great dream about eating
a huge meat bun! Luna!
Huh?! A meat bun?!
Where did the girl with
romantic dreams go?!
"Steal a Kiss from Mamoru:
An's Project Snow White"
Is this necessary? Do
we really need to study
English?
If we have time for that,
shouldn't we be thinking
up ways to gather energy
instead?
Ugh!
[gasp]
[giggling]
Love is something that
you have to reach out
and take! Like kissing a
girl in a deep sleep to
capture her love.
That's it!
I will win Mamoru's heart
by stealing a kiss from
him.
[sigh]
Sorry I'm late!
That's okay. We're
used to it by now!
Eh... But, Rei, why did
you call this meeting
on such short notice?
There another Cardian
running loose?
No, that's not the
reason. Actually,
Mamoru is the one
who's in trouble.
No way! Mamoru?! Oh,
no! Is he seriously
injured?
Poor Mamoru!
That's so awful!
[crying]
Agh! That's not it!
Relax, Usagi. Mamoru is
merely supposed to appear
in a play at Juban Hall,
that's all.
What? A play?
Yeah, that's right. I
guess some of Mamoru's
friends were supposed to
be in the play along with
him, but they dropped
out.
They got into an argument
about casting, and their
troupe disbanded.
He's having a hard time
finding new people to take
on the roles in the play.
He's really worried.
You know how responsible
a person Mamoru is. He
doesn't want to cancel
the play.
Earlier he left this
prayer at the shrine.
Ahhh!
In that case, we
better go give him
a hand!
Meow!
You're telling me that
you all want to have
parts in the play?
Yeah, that's right! Rei
came up with the idea. We
thought that all of us
could put up a performance
of Snow White!
Snow white, huh?
And, and, and! I think
I should get the role
of Snow White because
it was my idea in
the first place
What?! Get real!
That's not fair!
I should be Snow White
because I'm just so
cute and adorable!
Uh...
Hold on, you don't get
to make the decision!
I should be the one who
gets to play Snow White.
After all, I do have
the biggest boobs out
of all of you.
Are you out of
your mind!
Hmph! Wanna take
measurements?
Wait a second!
I think that I would be
the better choice for
Snow White since I'm
the most like her...
...elegant and
graceful!
Ugh!
I'm busy with cram
school and homework,
but maybe I can help
out. Snow White only
has a few lines because
she's fast asleep almost
the entire time! So I
could play her!
[annoyed grunts]
Hmph!
Uh, you know there are
still a lot of other
characters to play,
too. There's the prince
and the evil queen...
At least choosing the
prince should be pretty
easy! All of us think that
you should play him, Mamoru!
So the only real problem
is, who's gonna play
Snow White?!
Yeah! Me!
I came up with the
idea, so it should
be me!
Yes, but I have
the best figure.
I'll do it!
I have elegance!
I'll study the part
really well! Pretty
please?
It's mine!
No, mine!
I'll do it!
[arguing]
You're all acting
so conceited!
Yes, stop being
so selfish!
Shut up! No one
asked you anything!
The whole reason I'm in
this spot in the first
place is that my friends
had a fight just like this.
[arguing]
Guys! I know how we can
decide who gets to play
Snow White!
We'll draw straws!
Oh hey, Natusmi...
Just what are you
talking about?
We can decide by randomly
drawing straws, or pieces
of paper in this case.
Also, to tell you
the truth...
I'd like to be a part
of your play, too!
If the end of your paper
is white, then you're Snow
White. If it's red, you're
the queen. If it's blue,
you're one of the
dwarves.
I'll let you all go
first, and I'll just
take whatever one's
left at the end!
Here...
[groaning]
Okay! I'll be the
first one to draw!
[nervous groans]
Ooohh!
Aw, come on! I'm
the evil queen!
Sorry, Tsukino. That's
just the luck of the
draw.
Oh, no! No!
No! No!
[grunts]
[whining]
All of us got
a blue one.
Mmm...
Wow. You all seem to
have terrible luck
drawing straws.
[gasping screams]
Well, look at that! It
appears that I get to be
Snow White. I'm sorry,
girls!
[whining]
None of those fools
realize that I rigged
it so I'd win and get
to be Snow White!
Your play's cast is
short by one dwarf?
No way! I won't do it!
I want to play the prince!
Sorry, but that part is
already taken. By Mamoru.
Just forget it, then!
Hmph! Fine! I guess that
we'll just have to do
it with six dwarves!
The play's going to
be at Juban Hall, huh?
Now come forth,
Cardian Bipierrot!
[flute music]
Bipierrot!
Ha ha ha!
Next week, a large number
of people will gather at
Juban Hall. I want you to
steal their energy!
Bipierrot!
What?! We're going
to do it again?!
Yes! Now, Snow White is
still asleep and the
prince gives her a
passionate kiss.
This is the climactic
moment of the story!
It's the biggest scene
in the whole play!
We'll practice it as
many times as it takes!
Now, Mamoru. Could you
go over it with me one
more time, please?
Sure. Let's do
it once more.
And... Action!
[whining]
Oh, princess!
My true love, accept
this kiss with your sweet
lips and awaken at last
from you eternal slumber!
No, don't kiss her
for real! No!
This is my chance!
Agh!
That's not going to work!
Snow White is supposed to
be asleep, you have to
stay still!
Darn!
Oh, I'm sorry! Could
we do it just one
more time?
We've done this
scene enough!
Yeah, I think it's
about time that we
practiced something
else.
What are you two talking
about? This is a very
important scene. We cannot
cut any corners, you know!
Now, stop your
selfish whining!
Give me a break!
You're the most
selfish of us all!
This is getting
ridiculous!
See you later!
Goodnight!
I'm taking off!
Good work!
Okay! Thank
you so much!
Oh, Mamoru! You mind
if I walk with you?
Since we're playing
characters who love
each other, we should
probably spend some
time together so we can
get to know each other
better!
[angry growling]
What is her problem?
If she keeps this up,
the play is going to be
a huge flop!
I really think she should
give up the role of Snow
White if she keeps on
acting as selfishly as
she has been!
Yes, I agree! I mean
after all, she only got
the part in the first
place because she
cheated to get it.
Ahem! What's all
this about cheating,
exactly?
Heh...
Hey! Start talking!
What do you mean by
cheating?!
Hmm! I can't believe
you guys knew about
it all this time and
didn't tell me!
[crying]
All right!
We'll explain...
Yeah, it's simple.
Natsumi rigged the
drawing so she'd be
Snow White.
Every single one of
these had a colored
part at the end. When
she drew hers, she
pulled the color
off.
So it looked like
hers was white.
THat's not fair! If you
knew this, then why
didn't you say anything
to her, huh?!
Because, we knew we'd
all continue fighting
no matter which one
of us got the role.
That's right. And besides,
Natsumi doesn't really have
any close friends because
she's still new here.
She's always by
herself and seems
so lonely...
She also wanted to be
Snow White so badly.
And to tell you the
truth, I was impressed
by her moxie!
Wow, guys. That
was really kind.
But still, is it true
friendship to ignore
what she did?
Cheating is cheating!
I say we call her on
it?! You with me?!
Anyway!
If we ignore this-
We should talk
to her.
Mm-hmm!
Ugh!
Usagi! Are you sure you
should be the one to
handle this?
Leave it to me! I'll
talk to her at school
tomorrow and-
[gasp]
Hey, there
she is!
But why is she going
to the Hikawa Shrine?
Sailor Moon!
R!
Sailor Moon R!
Oh, please...Please,
I really want this
play to be successful!
Please allow me to
steal Mamoru's kiss.
Natsumi looks
so serious...
She must be very
passionate about
this play.
She's still selfish, but
everybody knows that most
actresses are pretty
selfish.
I've even heard the
more selfish the actress,
the better her acting is!
You know what? I'm
totally fine with Natsumi
getting to be Snow White!
So let's all do our
best to make this
play a success for
Natsumi's sake. 'Kay?
Mm! Hm! I don't like
that she gets to kiss
Mamoru, but I'll let
it go.
What? You say
something?
Uh...not really!
Ha ha ha ha!
Poor Snow White...
La la la...
She took one bite...
That poisoned apple
knocked her out like
turning out the lights.
And now she'll sleep
for all eternity.
La la la!
It really is about
enough to make you
weep!
[evil laughter]
You have got to be
kidding me! This show
is not some kind of
costume contest! Why
in the world do I
have to wear this
ridiculous thing!
Yeah, and how come I
have to wear the gorilla
one?!
Oh, well it's because...
They say entertainment
has to be original.
So I got us some
adorable animal
costumes!
This is what you think
of when you think
adorable?
But you all do look
very cute in them!
Hmph!
And Tsukino, you look
great as the witch,
as well!
[growling]
Well, then? Shall we
continue rehearsing?
I wanted to wear a
pretty dress like hers
and have a romantic
scene with the prince!
Oh, princess! My
true love!
Accept this kiss with
your sweet lips...
And awaken at last...
...from your
eternal slumber.
Just what are you
doing?! Huh?!
Oh! Uh... I'm
rehearsing for
the play!
Hm?
Ail? Ail!
Tomorrow's the
big day. Break
a leg.
Why couldn't I
be the prince...
Mirror, mirror, on
the wall...
Tell me true: who
is the fairest of
them all?
What?! I'm the
second fairest?!
Snow White is the
most beautiful in
all the land?
How vexing!
[chuckling]
You are such a
ham, Usagi!
How dare you?!
I'm coming to see your play
tomorrow, so try to make
your performance at least
somewhat decent, all right?
[groaning]
You can just stay
home for all I care!
[chattering]
Whoa, it's packed
out there!
You know? I'm getting
kinda nervous!
[ringing bell]
[gasps]
That's the first bell.
Everyone get to your
places now.
Right!
Once the second bell
rings, it's show time!
And Mamoru will kiss me!
[ringing bell]
[crowd applause]
Bipierrot!
[gasps]
What's going on?
A clown?!
There's a clown
in this play?
Has the script changed?
Bipierrot!
Oh no!
Bipierrot! Bipierrot!
Whoa! They're destroying
the entire set right off
the bat!
Stop it!!
Don't ruin our play!
We worked so hard on
it!
Bipierrot!
[gasp]
[screaming]
Natsumi!
[painful yell]
Mamoru! Oh,
you saved me!
[grunt]
Natsumi! Mamoru!
Bipi...
That thing is a
real monster!
Run, Naru!
Aghah!
[screaming]
You're so heavy, Mako!
Get off of me!
You've gotta get
off me first!
Calm down! Climb out
one at a time!
Stop moving away!
Enough!
Okay!
Bipierrot!
[audience groaning]
Oh no!
We've gotta do
something fast!
Get off of me!
How dare that monster
try to ruin our play!
I have had enough!
Moon Crystal Power!
Make Up!
♪ Sailor Moon! ♪
After long hours of
tough rehearsals...
Bipi?
...all of these hard-
working actors...
...finally get to
perform!
This is the result of
all their sweat and
friendship!
How dare you mess
that up!
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name of
the moon, I'll punish
you!
Bipierrot!
[screaming]
Bibibibibibibi!
[grunt]
Agh! Bipi?
No one knows my true
identity, but all young
girls know who I am. The
Moonlight Knight is here!
Wow, it's the
Moonlight Knight!
What is going on? This
play was supposed to be
Snow White, but now it's
Sailor Moon?
Huh?
Who's that?
Fueled by the flames of
passion and the nine
mantras!
Destroying all evil
with spiritual power!
All while wearing
red heels! I am
Sailor Mars!
Born with raw strength
and lightning!
I am the Guardian
Sailor Jupiter!
I can handle cram
school and studying.
I always read reference
books, and in the National
Practice exam...
I hold the rank
of number one!
Sailor Mercury!
I was known as the
Masked Legend. My face
is quite stunning, too!
And I am also the latest
Pretty Guardian to appear!
Sailor Venus!
We're on the scene!
Bipierrot!
My red heels are as
furious as an inferno!
Rin Pyo To Sha Kai
Jin Retsu Zai Zen!
Evil Spirit, Be
Exorcized!
Bipi?!
I took all of that time
away from my studying
so I could memorize
my lines!
I could have read three
books instead, and I want
those hours back!
Bubble Spray Freezing!
Bibibibibi...
I won't forgive you
for ruining our play!
♪ Sailor Moon! ♪
Moon Princess
Halation!
Cleansing!
[screaming]
[audience cheering]
Wow! This is the best
play I've ever seen!
All of you have
saved the day!
Tonight the spotlight
falls on the beauty of
these girls!
Adieu!
[audience cheering]
Moonlight Knight,
don't go!
[audience cheering]
Encore! Encore! Encore!
We did it!
Ail, how could you!
That was just horrible!
I can't believe I worked
so hard and you sent in
a Cardian to ruin it all!
Shut up! Did you forget
we're here to gather as
much energy as we can?!
[sobbing]
I was so close...
...to stealing
Mamoru's kiss!
[crying]
They really should've
let me play the prince...
What? I have detention
after school?!
Being tardy, falling
asleep, eating lunch
in class. You deserve
it!
Oh, my precious
girly time!
Take this as a life
lesson and study by
yourself.
Ha! Wrong! Natsumi's
in detention, too!
That's not something
to be proud of!
Next time on Sailor Moon R,
"After-School Trouble:
Usagi Is a Target."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.