(Usagi)
Mamo! Who's that girl?
And why do you keep
avoiding me!?
(Usagi)
[sob] This can't be
happening. It's got to
be a dream, it has to be!
(Usagi)
Droid Akumooda! How dare you
turn a young girl's romantic
dreams into a nightmare!
(Usagi)
I am Sailor Moon!
In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
(Usagi)
[reading]
"Then the handsome prince
arrived at the thorn castle.
...where he found the
beautiful princess asleep
from a witch's evil spell."
So he gave the princess
a loving kiss, and she
awoke"
How boring.
What are you talking
about? That's the best
part of the story!
I heard this
fairytale
before...
Aw, I thought if I
read it, you'd like
to hear it again.
"The princess had been
awakened by her true love,
and so together, lived
happily ever after."
The end!
Aw! How romantic!
...Right, Chibi-Usa?
Wha-!? C'mon, it's
not that boring..!
Usagi..! Just let
her sleep, okay?
Look at her... she's
probably thinking about her
poor mother who's being held
captive in the future.
Yeah. I wish there was
some way we could help
her...
"Awaken the Sleeping Beauty:
Mamoru's Distress"
[grunts]
[grunt]
Isn't it just wonderful
Mamo- at last we're
finally married!
Wait... Usako...
Usako! Nooooo!
[gasp]
[sobs]
(Voice)
Mamoru Chiba, you must stay
away from Usagi Tsukino.
So it's you again...
Tell me, who are you!?
(Voice)
The moment that the two
of you are wed, the world
will come to an end...
(Voice)
...and tragedy will befall
Usagi Tsukino, Princess
Serenity!
[gasp]
Grr... You expect me
to really believe that!?
Is torturing me all
you want to do!? Stop
with these nightmares!
(Voice)
This is a truth
you cannot escape.
That's all a lie!
It can't be!
No!
[thinking]
So, if I go near her,
Usa will encounter
tragedy...
But is that really
true!?
Usako...
[gasp]
How did that
happen..?
(Voice)
Tragedy will befall her.
(Thinking)
So then, is it true..?
Must I stay away from
Usako, after all..?
(Thinking)
Why...? Why should things
end up disastrous if Usako
and I love each other?
Hi Mamo...
[gasp]
I'm surprised seeing you
here this early in the
morning. Guess it must
be fate...
Hey, by the way, has
Chibi-Usa said anything
to you about Crystal
Tokyo?
No, she hasn't
told me anything.
Hey, wait- Mamo!
Where are you going?
I'm going for a morning
run to stay in shape.
But, Mamo--
(Thinking)
Forgive me, Usako...
Mamo, I haven't given
up on you yet...
Watch me! I'll do
whatever it takes to
win back your love!
I swear...
...One day.
[thinking]
What should I do..?
(Motoki)
Hey Mamoru,
what's up?
Oh, Motoki...
You've seemed kinda
down lately. So is
there something that's
been bothering you?
No...
Come on, we're best
friends! Tell me what's
going on with you-
-I bet you'll feel
better if you talk
to me about it.
Thank, I really
appreciate it.
sluuuuuurp.
Motoki, what do you
think is the best way
to get a girl not to
like you anymore?
[slap]
Huh? Why would you
want to do that?
I need help finding a
way to become the sort
of guy that girls end
up really hating...
Here's your strawberry
sundae... Hey Mamoru!
So Usagi, have you
had a chance to ask
Chibi-Usa anything?
Nahh...
Well, here's what we
know. Chibi-Usa is
from the future--
--And her home, Crystal
Tokyo, is under attack
by this Black Moon Clan.
And on top of that,
isn't Chibi-Usa's
mother being held
captive by that clan?
Yeah...
And now Crimson Rubeus
and the 4 Spectre Sisters
are here trying to
destroy our world...
Usagi! Stop acting
like this doesn't
matter!
Besides, your ice
cream's melting...
So hey, I need your
advice. Why do you
think Mamo's avoiding
me?
-What. -What.
Will you snap out of it!
Right now our top priority
is to find out exactly
where our enemy is hiding!
We all need to get out
there and gather as
much info as we can.
-Right! -Right!
[sigh]
[vroom vroom]
Stop revving that
motorcycle... Hey!
You! Knock it off!
Mamo?
Wait! Hold on!
Mamo! Who's that girl
you're giving a ride?
Is she a relative?
..Your cousin?
Or is she...
It's none of your
business who she is,
and stop being so nosey
about my personal life!
[gasp]
Okay. You better
hold on tight.
But Mamoru, who
is this girl?
(Mamoru)
Eh, she's just
a friend...
So I'm... "just
a friend..?"
[crying]
[Thinking]
Usako... We must be
apart until I figure
out my nightmares...
What's that noise?
Maybe it's a burglar.
[small sob]
Hey, Usagi,
what's wrong?
[nom]
You know, eating after
midnight gives you
indigestion and might
make you fat...
[sob] Well I don't
care one bit! So
what if I get fat!?
[cries]
My Mamo has got himself
a new girlfriend..!
[gasp]
Why should I even care
about what I eat, after
all, the man that I
love, now hates me...
[crying]
[small cry]
[Thinking]
Mamo... it can't be
true that you have
a girlfriend, can it?
[loud truck honks]
[frightened cry]
[screaming]
[sluuurp] Huh?
What's that
bright light?
Usagi! We have a big
problem. I can't find
Chibi-Usa anywhere in
the house!
I just saw a flash
of light! Could it
be Chibi-Usa?
You say you've
detected traces
of Rabbit's energy?
Yes, sir. We think
she's somewhere
near Juban Park.
Go! Find and
attack her at
once!
[running breaths]
There you are...
Now we've got you,
Rabbit.
[gasp]
Someone help me!
Stop running!
We're coming,
Chibi-Usa!
Hurry! Help!
You creeps are gonna
get it b ig time because
I'm in a really bad
mood tonight..!
Moon Crystal Power..!
Make Up!
♪Sailor Moon...
Sailor Moon...
Sailor Moon...♪
♪Sailor Moon...
Sailor Moon...
Sailor Moon...♪
[cries]
Heh, tonight's your
last night alive.
(Sailor Moon)
Not if I can
help it!
[gasps]
-Sailor Moon.
Ah!
[hisses]
[screaming]
Two full grown women...
Ganging up to hurt a
little girl...!
I can't forgive you
for picking on her!
I am Sailor Moon! And
now, in the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you.
[chuckle]
Sailor Moon, we have
been waiting for you
to show up here...
You've been
"waiting for me?"
Akumooda! Come
down here!
[melodic voice]
Dream dream dream...
[gasp]
Dream dream...!
Sailor Moon!
R!
Sailor Moon R!
[melodic voice]
Dream dream dream...
Hey! Stop that!
Sailor Moon! Be
careful..!
Sleep, sleep, sleep,
sleep, sleep...
[weak moan]
Sailor Moon, you mustn't
fall asleep now..!
I'm feeling really
stuffed from all those
late-night snacks I ate
earlier. Nighty-night!
[frightened whimper]
[giggle]
That was easy.
Now for you...
Die, Rabbit.
[whimper]
[surprised gasps]
I'm glad we decided
to stop by to check
that energy spike!
Not you people
again!
There's only two
of us, and there's
four of them!
We're at a big
disadvantage here,
let's go!
Uh, hey wait!
Hey! Are you afraid
to fight us!?
Akumooda is more than
enough to handle you
little girls! [laugh]
Akumooda, I want you
to do the same thing
you did to Sailor Moon.
Lead them to nightmare
land and then you can
finish them off!
[melodic voice]
Dream, dream, dream,
dream, dream...
She's trying to
use hypnosis to
beat you!
Whatever you do,
you can't let her
put you to sleep!
Now go to sleep....
Sleep... Time to sleep.
[grunts]
We're not gonna
let you put us
to sleep..!
Rin, Pyo, To, Sha,
Kai-Jin, Retsu-Zai-Zen!
Evil Spirit be
exorcised!
[death scream]
Thanks, Mars. We were
almost overwhelmed by
that thing...
Mhm!
Sailor Moon!
Wake up!
Sailor Moon will
continue to dream...
...and as she dreams,
her energy will be
drained out of her
until she finally dies...
[gasps]
[groan]
What just
happened!?
[gasp] Sailor Moon!
Sailor Moon!
Please, wake up!
C'mon, Sailor Moon!
Say something!
[running gasps]
Mamo! It's me!
I'm-- whoa!
...Mamo!
Sailor Moon!
Please wake up!
You have to
snap out of it!
You can see the
energy's draining
from her body!
If we can't wake her
up, then Sailor Moon
will end up dead..!
What can we do!?
You have to wake
up! Come on! [sobs]
Mamo..!
Please don't
leave me!!
Wake up!
Ma...mo... Don't
go....
[gasp]
We're running out
of time!
She'll die if we
can't help her!
Huh?
Why should I even care
about what I eat? After
all, the man that I
love, now hates me...
Luna, wait! Where
are you going!?
Ah! What the--?
Mamoru! Sailor Moon's
in really big trouble!
Please! You just have
to come with me to
help save her life!
We've got to hurry!
You see, she's in
this deep, deadly sleep
and you're the only one
who can wake her up..!
Only you can
save her..!
I'm not sure that
I can help...
But weren't you and Sailor
Moon in love with one
another in a world in
the distant past?!
Why are you suddenly
acting so cold to her?
I have to...
If you don't help,
Sailor Moon will die!
Sailor Moon...
Usako... Just hang
on 'til I get there.
I won't let you
die, Usako!
[out of breath]
Mamo... wait!
Sailor Moon! You've
got to wake up..!
Can you even
hear us!?
Oh, Sailor Moon!
Please wake up!
We've got to think
of something to do
here...
Come out of
your sleep...
Hey body temperature
is getting lower...!
What?!
Look over there-
It's Tuxedo Mask.
She's right, it is
Tuxedo Mask... Is
he here to help?
[gasp]
Oh no!
Sailor Moon! Wake up!
Sailor Moon..!
(Sailor Moon)
Mamo...
[gasp]
Usako... Please
forgive me...
Stop that...!
The power of love
woke Sailor Moon and
restored her energy!
Mamo... You're
so warm...
Sailor Moon...
Thank goodness.
I don't believe it.
It's just like that
fairy tale...
How dare you
interfere Tuxedo
Mask..!
Grrrrr!
Look out!
[screaming]
[grunt]
A girl is always supposed
to dream of doing whatever it
takes to help her win the
heart of the boy she loves!
Sailor Moon...
Nightmares for you!
I can't forgive you
for what you've done.
♪Sailor Moon...
Sailor Moon...
Sailor Moon...♪
Moon Princess...
Halation...!
[death scream]
Sailor Moon, as always,
your finishing technique
is breathtaking...
Tuxedo Mask, do you
have feelings for
me after all?
Sailor Moon...
[grunt] No, I don't! I
really don't love you!
[gasp] But how can
that be? You literally
just saved my life...
Those are different
things... Very different!
[gasp]
The red strong of fate
that tied the two of us
together has now been
cut to pieces...
Noooooo!!!
[gasp]
Tuxedo Mask!
Whyyyy!?
Sailor Moon...
Please forgive
me, Usako...
What!? Wait. You're
Unazuki!? So...
Then that means,
you're Motoki's
younger sister?
That's right. Mamoru
did me a huge favor
yesterday by giving me
a ride on his bike...
So that was you
on his bike with
him..?
Yeah! I got so busy
here at work that I was
going to be late for my
date with my boyfriend!
So he helped me out.
So Mamoru isn't in
any way your boyfriend?
Don't be silly! I've got
my own great boyfriend
that I love very, very
much! See ya!
Yes! That's great
news! She's already
got a boyfriend!
Okay...but then, why's
Mamo avoiding me and why
does he keep lying to me?
I don't get it!
Well, there's one
thing I know for sure.
I'll figure everything out and
then I'll win back his love and
we'll live happily ever after
exactly like I want us to!
Oh yeah!!
(Usagi)
Hey, Rei, who's that lady?
Isn't she a salesperson
for cosmetics..?
(Rei)
No, she's Koan, one
of the four Spectre
Sisters!
(Usagi)
Oh no! Not her again!
SHe sure is persistent!
(Rei)
Wake up Koan! What you see as
love is wrong! You're confused,
that's not what true love is!
(Usagi)
Rei! Look out!
(Rei)
Koan!
(Usagi)
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"Battle of the Flames of Love!
Mars vs. Koan"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.