Cherry blossom season's
such a happy time of year
for everyone! So how dare
you show up and try to
wreck it! What?! My tiara's
still not working? Aghh!
Now I can't even transform
and fight! Well, I guess
that's it. Bye guys! Right,
like it's gonna be that
easy! Anyway...
In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
Blossoms?
Viewing cherry blossoms is
an annual seasonal event
for people from this planet.
It seems to go on all day
and night for them. And I
understand humans use a
lot of energy doing it.
I have heard stories that
when our tribe was prosperous,
the Makai Tree had beautiful
flower blossoms on it as well.
Blossoms?
[chuckle]
I think we can gather a lot
of human energy while they're
viewing these cherry blossoms.
A New Transformation:
Usagi's Power Up!
[chattering]
Make way! Make way!
Usagi's coming through!
Hey, you know I really
appreciate you being our
chaperone for today,
even though we're not
your students.
You're always so busy, I
almost feel bad for taking
you away from school to be
here with us..
I was happy to do it!
I think we should all
just forget about school
for today!
For sure!
Right now we're just a
happy bunch of people
enjoying the cherry
blossoms!
Naru? Naru? Naru!
Naru? Naru?
Ah! Hey, everyone!
Over here!
Huh? Wow! Look,
it's Umino!
Thanks for saving
us this spot, Umino!
I'm surprised you
were able to find
one.
Have you been
here long?
Since 8 o'clock
last night.
What?!
But isn't it still cold
outside at night this
time of year?
I was just fine!
I brought my own
secret weapon with me!
My trusty sleeping bag
kept me toasty all night!
That was smart, but you
really didn't have to
go that far you know.
Well, I'm happy to help
all of you, but I really
consider it my special
duty to do this for Naru!
You did this for me?
Yes! For you, my
dear, Naru!
Umino...
Come on everyone!
It's time for our
picnic!
Yeah, let's eat!
Uh...Naru? Zipping me
up in here was really
uncalled for! I did
this for you!
Naru!!
I know right...
How could you! I was
just trying to make
you happy, Naru.
Sorry! But Umino, you
know I was just kidding
around!
[girls chattering]
Oh wow! All your
lunches look so
delicious!
Your lunch looks like
you must've dropped it
on the floor.
Knock it off! I made
my rice balls with real
tender loving care.
Oh really?
Unlike you, I took
my time and made
some food!
[growling]
Hmm...
As usual, your lunch
is looking really
tasty, Mako!
Hah! You think so?
Go on, take whatever
you like.
Really?!
Here's your
lunch, Umino.
All this for me?!
So I guess that
means you like it?
I'm sure it's the
best lunch in the
universe!
Stop exaggerating!
Hmm...
Boy Ami, your lunch
and Minako's sandwiches
look really tasty as well.
Oh, well have some!
Eat as much
as you like!
Mmm!
Hey, Natsumi!
Where's your
lunch?
I feel on energy,
not food.
Huh?
Oh! Nothing!
I gotcha! You were just
planning on eating off
what everyone else
brought, is that it?!
That was your plan!
Oh yeah? Well from what
I can see your eating
some of Mako's lunch too.
Just shut it. Why don't
you stuff your face with
those ugly rice balls
already?
This tastes great! I
want you to have the
other half.
Oh! How generous
and so unlike you!
[girls chattering]
Fire!!
Soul.
[laughing]
Why you! You're
just so unbelievable!
That's what you get
for being so mean!
"Mean"?!
Yeah!
What if my appendix
bursts from eating
that?!
[girls arguing]
[sighing]
Don't get mad, don't
get mad. I mean after
all we're not in school.
So, you all get a
free period hour
starting now!
Uhh, wait a second.
Ms. Haruna, we're not
in school right now.
Oh! Right!
[giggling]
Hey, they're selling lots
of delicious buns at that
stand over there!
Isn't it kinda weird for
a bun-head to be eating
other buns?!
You're being mean again!
C'mon! Cut it
out you two!
She started it!
Don't make fun of me!
I have feelings too you
know! How would you like
it if I did that to you!
How beautiful...
So, you really think
she's beautiful?
No, you're misunderstanding
me. I wasn't referring to
Usagi at all, An.
I don't believe you.
I was simply commenting
on the beauty of these
cherry blossoms!
[chuckle]
Well, that
doesn't matter.
That all can wait.
Right now, let's focus
on extracting some fresh
energy from these young
humans.
Yes, I was actually
thinking the exact
same thing.
Pick one, An...
[flute music]
This is so nice.
Cherry blossoms are
pretty, but to me, you
look even more beautiful
than they ever could.
Doesn't it ever embarrass
you to say that kind of
stuff to me?
No, I am only saying
what's really in my
heart.
Yeah, sure. You
know, honestly...
Huh?!
What?
[nervous groans]
What's that?!
[screaming]
Okay, who wants drinks?
[gasp]
Umino! Miss Osaka!
What happened?
Wake up you two!
Huh?!
Please, I beg you! Can
you go get someone!
We need help here!
[screaming]
Hmm...
I think once they get
some rest, they should
be fine.
It's strange. I can't
figure out what's
going on here.
You're like the tenth
group today that said
their friends had
suddenly passed out.
That many?!
Yeah, and it's way too
early in the year for
a heat stroke.
I wonder what it
could be...
So, you think they're
energy's being stolen!
Mm-hmm! Based on how
weak they are, I'm sure
that's what this is.
The others are checking
out where it happened.
We'd better go meet up
with them!
Right!
So, this is where Ms.
Haruna and the others
collapsed, right?
There doesn't seem to
be anything unusual
here...
Still, we should
stay on guard!
I sense it. I sense
an evil aura...
Hey! What's that?!
[gasps]
[screaming]
[gasp]
They're in trouble!
Transform!
Moon Prism Power
Make Up!
Sailor Moon!
R!
Sailor Moon R!
[gasp]
[painful grunting]
That tree is stealing
their energy!
[laughing]
[scared gasps]
Ah!
Ahh!
[coughing]
Sailor Moon!
Ahh!
[chuckling]
[whimpering]
Sailor Moon! You
have to stop her!
I know that!
Moon Tiara Action!
Huh?! Oh no! It's
not working again!
Sailor Moon,
be careful!
Make sure...not to
look in her eyes!
Her eyes?!
Look out!
Huh?!
Ahh!
[grunting]
[screaming]
Sailor Moon!
[groaning]
Oh no!
[screaming]
Sailor Moon!
[groaning]
Ahh! My brooch!
Leshy!
Ahh! This can't be
happening!
[groaning]
I have to save
everyone!
[screaming]
No! Usagi!
Usagi!
[grunting]
Luna!
I thought I...
Could save all
of you!
I'm sorry!
Usagi!
Luna!
[grunting]
Let go! Get out!
[screaming]
Usagi! Luna!
[gasp]
Usagi!
It appears that the Makai
Tree is gathering a lot
of energy.
Now it's only a matter of
time before our precious
tree will be completely
rejuvenated!
Hear me now, Leshy!
Continue! Keep gathering
even more energy!
What'll we do, Luna?
I can't transform...
Usagi, even though you've
become a Sailor Guardian
again, deep down, you still
desire a normal life.
Yeah, I just want to
be a regular school
girl.
As long as you feel that
way, you won't be able to
use your Moon Tiara Action, or
transform into Sailor Moon.
Oh no! Then how can
I save everyone? How?!
Hm...?
Where am I? Luna?
You're so loyal but
I make so much trouble
for you...
I'm so sorry for
dragging you into
all of this.
I wonder...maybe
we're both dead?
Princess...
Huh?!
Queen Serenity...
Right now, we are
inside your mind.
Thank you, for seeking
out my advice. Can I
help you?
[gasp]
Queen Serenity! I must
find a way to save my
friends!
Hold your brooch...
The Silver Crystal!
Your heartfelt desire
of wanting to save your
friends has formed the
Silver Crystal.
It's a new brooch!
Luna...
Please continue to
help our Princess.
Right.
With the Silver Crystal's
power, now I can save
everyone.
Listen, Princess, the
Silver Crystal no longer
possess the power it once
had...
...but because you cherish
your friends, and desire
to protect those around
you, I know it will allow
you to use its energy to
do good, and reactivate
its wondrous powers again.
Oh, thank you,
Queen Serenity.
Thank you...
Now say, "Moon Crystal
Power Make Up."
Right!
Moon Crystal Power...
...Make Up!
♪ Sailor Moon! ♪
Leshy!
It's no good! There's
no way! I can't stop
this thing alone!
Leshy!
The moon!
Listen! Spring's the
season for living, not
hurting!
And Cherry blossom viewing
is one of the happiest times
of year for people, you
monster!
How dare you interfere
with it like an old
drunk!
I am the Pretty Guardian...
...who fights for love
and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now, in the name
of the moon, I'll
punish you!
I don't believe it,
you're both okay!
Artemis! You were
able to hold her
back!
Leshy!
[screaming]
Leeeshy!
[gasp]
Hang in there!
Sailor Moon...
...You're the only
one who can fight
right now!
Yeah, I know that.
Leeeshhyyy!
[gasp]
Leshy!
[screaming]
[gasp]
It's a wonderful night
for admiring the beauty of
flowers. Cherry blossoms
are so short-lived. I won't
let you and your filthy
hands misuse them!
Moonlight Knight!
It's you!
Sailor Moon, you're the
only one who can save
all of your friends.
[gasp]
Princess...
What's this?
The Cutie Moon Rod.
Use it to light the
flame of hope for
the future.
Queen Serenity...
Right!
Leeeessshy!
♪ Sailor Moon! ♪
Moon Princess...
Halation!
[screaming]
Cleansing!
Damn you, Leshy!
It looks like
she's failed us!
[sighs]
I'm so glad
you're all okay.
Sailor Moon...
Huh?
You did quite well
on your own this time.
Even cherry blossoms are
no match for a courageous
young girl like you.
Adieu...
Thank you so much,
Moonlight Knight!
Thank you, Sailor
Moon...You-
Sailor Moon...?
Huh?
Thank you.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
[giggle]
Looks like Sailor Moon
has made another step
forward.
Mm-hm! Now she needs to
continue to work hard!
But I'd say, it would've
been better for everyone
if she'd gotten around
to saving us a bit sooner!
There you go, Rei,
being mean again!
[screaming]
[grunting]
On second thought,
maybe she hasn't made
any progress at all.
I mean really...
Queen Serenity...
Thank you...
In the next episode,
Minako fights to protect
the children!
Hey, wait a minute!
What about me!
Guess you're
not in it.
Hold it, wait, whoa-oh!
I'm the star of this
show!
Huh? You're the what?
The star! Because I'm
so cute and funny!
Ha ha ha! That's
a good one!
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
The Targeted Kindergarteners:
Venus to the Rescue.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.