I finally got a chance to be
alone with Mamoru at the virtual
reality theatre.
So why did all of you have to
show up and spoil it?
It was just the two of us until
Dad, Shingo, Natsumi, and even a
Cardian butted in. I can't take
it anymore!
So in the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
Usagi!!
You have been snoozing
long enough! It's time to
get up!
Whoa!
[Cat Hiss]
Aw but there's no
school today!
What kind of excuse is that?
It's a lovely day and you should
be up enjoying it.
Your father and Shingo
are already out. C'mon!
But I'm still sleepy! You
are so mean! Give
me back my blanket!
[Sigh]
"Usagi's Crisis: The Tiara
Stops Working."
We haven't collected as much
energy for the Makai Tree as I
had hoped because of those
Sailor Guardians interfering.
We both well know the Makai Tree
is the source of our life energy
and if it withers...
...then we too will
slowly wither and die.
What are you doing?
Huh?
"Virtual Reality Theatre Now
Open In Juban District."
Doesn't that sound like a
perfectly charming spot for a
Cardian to bare its
energy-zapping fangs?
Hm! Well why don't we take a
little trip into town Ail...
...and seek out some
new energy from this place?
Oh, so this is that new thingy
where the games are supposed to
be like real...
...but they aren't really
real or something?
It's called a 'Virtual
Reality Theater.'
Yeah I know that!
It's basically an
oversized arcade!
Well, it's time I showed you
the gaming skills that earned
me the title, "Demon of the
Arcade!"
I invited Rei and
the others but I guess
they're not here yet.
[Sigh]
All I see are couples.
Let's skip it Luna. It's
just pretend war anyway.
But that's the whole point of
being here, you still haven't
regained your sense of duty as a
Guardian.
And maybe this will help you
build up your fighting skills.
But I don't want to
work on my fighting skills!
Although I might consider it
if I were here on a date
with Mamoru.
Come on!
You actually know how to restore
every single one of Mamoru's
memories, don't you Luna?
Tell me the truth!
Out with it!
C'mon, c'mon! Fess up!
Don't take out your
frustrations on that poor
little cat.
[Gasp]
It's not the cat's fault
that you can't get a date.
Don't you have anything better
to do with your free time like
go to the library and study,
Bun-head?
It's none of your
business!
I could get a date
if I wanted to!
Sure!
Of course you could.
Huh?
Wait a minute!
From the looks of it he plans
to go in alone, too!
I wonder if I
should take a chance?
Oh, why not?!
I won't stop trying
until I succeed!
Here I go!
Why can't she show that
kind of initiative during
battle? [Sigh]
Hold on, Sir. You have
to wait in line like
everyone else.
Woah!
What do you think you're doing?
I have no intention of going in
there with you. You are not my
date!
Yeah?
You should be so lucky!
Quit trying to pick
up girls who don't want
to go out with you.
It's really pitiful.
What did you
say to me?
[Grunts]
Ahh!
You have stupid-pants!
Mamoru!
I owe you such a big debt of
gratitude! You really came to my
rescue!
And as my way of saying thank
you, I'll be your date today!
Huh?
Hold on a minute!
He's with me!
Natsumi? What is
going on here?
[Giggling]
Meet my brother, guys.
I've met Usagi.
I don't believe you know
Mamoru Chiba, though.
He really would like to come
join us for this event.
I'm actually busy, so...
I'm gonna join you two...
...then we can have a triple
date together!
[Laughing]
Tsukino!
Natsumi!
This isn't a game.
Yeah but this way
we'll attract less attention!
I'm not too sure
about that.
Let's go!
Come on! [Giggling]
Well, maybe this arrangement
isn't so bad after all.
Hey, where are you guys
going!?
Back of the line like the rest
of us!
Special VIP guests follow
me. Right this way.
We're sure lucky!
Let's go Mamoru. Thanks!
Hey, what about me?
Luna!
Huh?
Oh good!
They're all here!
[Screams]
Fire!
Get 'em, Dad!
It's so bright!
What's happening now?
[Scream]
Mamoru, I'm scared!
Hey get your hands
off of him!
Huh?
He was just comforting me,
calm down!
Usagi?!
Dad?!
Is that you?
Shingo? Did you talk Dad into
bringing you here? This place
isn't for little kids Shingo!
Cut it out, I'm doing fine.
But aren't these high-tech games
over your head?
Don't be such a
wise guy!
[Screaming]
[Screams]
[Gasp]
What are you doing,
brother?
It, it was an
accident.
[Giggling]
It just sort of
happened, sorry.
Usagi! I don't know what
you're doing with those boys...
...but Dad trusts you,
you hear me?
It's not like that.
How long are we gonna
have to wait to get in?
They say "Good things come
to those who stay!"
I think you mean good
things come to those who wait.
[Sigh]
I'm the cool Grade School Boy,
Sneaker Shingo, who fights for
justice...
...In the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
Nice shot Dad.
You got 'em!
Yeah! Cool!
Where'd Usagi go?
[Excited Giggles]
I got the monster!
[Singing] Na-na-na-na-na
[Grunts]
Dad!!
[Giggling] So, so shall we move
on?
He made a big deal of saying he
would trust me but he really
doesn't.
Don't worry Ail! It's an act so
we look like we're only here to
have fun like everybody else.
Awesome!
They are both so way cool!
Just as I expected, my guy's a
natural.
Well!
I'm a natural too!
[Screams]
Nice try, Tsukino.
Too bad you missed!
I just need a little practice, I
don't go shooting for fun it's
so barbaric.
Ah, what a shame! Of course in
all things, what really counts
is winning.
So you might as well admit
defeat right now because you're
clearly not a winner.
What?!
[Grunting]
[Screaming]
Ow!
Oh, this is so nice.
I'd love to stay like this a
little bit longer.
Not gonna happen.
Now go on.
[Sigh]
You can't make people like you
by forcing yourself upon them
every chance you get.
Well said. Good
for you Mamoru.
[Screams]
Come back Bun-head!
You're gonna get lost in
that maze!
[Exhales] Love is just a game.
I play to win. Right?
[Grunt]
My body seeks energy. I'm
getting pretty close to
being totally depleted.
You think everything has to
be a game, but this isn't!
Oh, don't say that Ail...
It's time for action!
[Both Giggling]
Hmmm, just ten in
front of us.
Choose the most appropriate
Cardian for this place.
Cardian Hellant, I call upon
you to appear!
[Flute Music]
Ant...Ant...Ant...
Hellant!
Sailor Moon!
R!
It feels like we've been
walking around in circles.
I've lost track of Usagi. I
don't know where she went.
[Groaning]
What's that noise?
Ant! Ant! Ant!
[Screaming]
Ant! Ant!!!
[Screams]
[Giggling]
Wonderful.
Wow that looks so real!
Yeah, maybe a little
too real...
Ant!
[Gasp]
Ant! Ant!
[Screams]
I hate this!
Why can't I hit them?
You could try opening
your eyes when you shoot.
Thanks you're so cool!
C'mon! Let's go
Bun-head!
Let's you and me go
get the top score in
here!
This finally feels
like a real date!
All right!
Moving forward!
[Chuckling]
Wow! I think I'm
in Heaven.
Sis! Sis!
I'm talking to you!
Shingo! What are you doing
bothering me! Go bother someone
else!
Listen, Sis.
Dad's in big trouble!
What happened?
One of the virtual monsters
is real and everyone's dropping
like flies in here!
What?
I'll check it out.
You two stay here!
Mamoru!
Wait for me!
I'll show you the way.
We've got to hurry and save
my dad!
Alright.
I'm going too!
You stay here, Sis. Leave
this to us men!
You're kidding. Just how
helpless does he think his
big sister really is?
He made me blow my big chance
with Mamoru!But there's no time
to think about that right now!
All right, two more.
That's all for now,
Three to go, then
we're in!
[Growls]
[Yelling]
We won't take your life.
We'll just put you in a nice
long sleep.
[Heavy Breathing]
[Laughing]
[Screams]
Dad!
[Grunt]
Ahh!
S-Shingo!
[Growls]
Stop you monster!
Ant!
[Grunts]
Shingo!...Run!
Ant! Ant!
Go! Shingo!
[Grunts]
A parent's duty is always to
protect the children he loves!
Come and get me
instead Monster!
[Screams]
[Grunts]
Ant!
[Gasp]
[Screams]
Dad no!
[Gasp]
[All scream]
[Grunting]
Moon Prism Power!
Make Up!
[Screams]
[Heavy Breathing]
Hellant, go easy
on that one.
Ant?
Stay still or you'll
get hurt.
[Sigh]
[Grunt]
Stop it!
Huh?
Hello Sailor Moon.
How dare you bully those who are
dearest to me. I will not
accept any of your apologies!
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and for
justice.
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
Silence you nuisance!
Hellant, will you please just
pound her into the ground!
Ant!
Moon Tiara!
Action!
No way!
My Tiara!
I don't know who you are, but
if you're gonna fight, you gotta
do better than that!
[Whimpering]
Ant!
[Screams]
[Grunts]
Even in a world of wicked
shadows, a beautiful flower of
love will blossom.
Who are you?!
I am the white wind that brings
color to the darkness. I am the
Moonlight Knight!
Oh my God! The
Huh?
How?
Oh great, now another
weirdo's appeared.
Huh? They're here together?!
So Mamoru isn't the Moonlight
Knight?
Let me just say, I admire your
courage. But no mortal human is
a match for them.
Stand aside.
Ant!
A true knight knows when
there is a valid reason to
fight.
I must punish those who
harm the innocent!
Hmph!
[Screaming]
[Grunting]
[Laughing]
Let him go!
[Struggling]
Bubble...!
Spray!
Fire!
Soul!
[Screams]
Hmph
Looks like we got here
in the nick of time!
Listen everyone...It's
awful...My Tiara...isn't working
anymore!
[Crying]
Don't cry Sailor Moon.
The Tiara!
How could that be!
Sailor Moon, pull yourself
together!
Thank you Sailor Venus.
We're taking over for Sailor
Moon so you'll be fighting
us instead!
Crescent...!
Supreme...!
Beam!
Thunder!
[Screaming]
Cleansing!
You're going to
pay for this!
Good work.
Huh?
Sailor Guardians...Even in
battle, your friendship glowed
beautifully.
Adieu.
[Whimpering]
So that guy was the
Moonlight Knight?
What's going on here?
Who are you girls anyway?
[Distant Talking]
Huh?
[Muffled Talking]
Ahh!
Ow that hurts a lot!
This is what you get for
not playing outdoors and
enjoying the sunshine.
Well how were we to know
that their equipment would
malfunction?
My Tiara has stopped working,
and it appears that Mamoru's
not the Moonlight Knight...
[Crying] I just don't know what
to do anymore!
Ah, Usagi...
It's cherry blossom season!
You know what that means!
Eating outdoors with friends
and having a good time?
Yup! And couples sharing a
romantic moment together!
Let's just hope a Cardian
doesn't show up...
Even if they do, I can
handle them!
Oh no, my transformation
brooch!
It broke?!
Next time on Sailor Moon R:"A
New Transformation: Usagi's
Power Up."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.