Is love something
that's fragile?
Is love something that
withers?
can die?
Can you not hear it?
The sad voice crying
for help.
Please give me the
courage I need to protect
the one I love!
If that Makai Tree keeps
growing this way,
it's only a matter of
time before it'll suck
up all the energy that
exists on Earth!
We have to stop it!
Crescent...!
Oh Hold on!
What is it?!
Just now, I sensed
something.
Huh?
Tell us!
The Makai Tree might be
an intelligent being.
What?!
That can't be!
[gasping]
Look out!
[grunting]
What's that?!
Looks like it'll
let us in.
Okay!
Then let's go!
Right!
"True Love Awakens: The
Makai Tree's Secret"
[grunting and panting]
[gasping]
It's acid!
Now what?!
It's a trap!
Damn it! It got us
in here to trap us!
This tree really
is intelligent!
[gasping]
Ahhhh!
Uh-Luna!
Bubble Spray---
Freezing!
[sighing]
Luna!
Say something!
Are you all right, Luna?!
Yeah, I'm all right, It
barely got me.
You sure?
Don't worry. Let's
just go. We have to
keep on moving.
Right!
[gasping]
Fireeee Soul!
[panting]
[panicking]
What's the matter?!
Get us out of here!
It's not working!
What?!
It's coming!
Keep trying!
Oh no! Just work please!
We're not gonna make
it!
The escape hatch!
Huh?!
Right!
[grunting]
Hurry it up!
Grab my hand!
[groaning]
A-Are you all right...
... Bun-head?
[struggling]
Mamoru...
Mamoru!
[straining]
Uhh!
Why'd you do that?!
I won't allow you to lay
a finger on my Usagi!
Ail!
Don't you dare talk
to my Mamoru like that!
What?! What did you just
say?!
[gasping]
You just called her
'your Usagi'! I know
what that means!
It means that you must
love her more than you
do me! That makes me
so mad!
It's--it's not like
that. My love for you
is different.
Shut up with your
dumb excuses.
Makai Tree! Take only
the girl's energy-Now!
No, Makai Tree! Take only
the guy's energy!
Ail!
Don't tell me that you've
forgotten how I've always
taken care of you?!
Hear me, Makai Tree!-I
will not stand for you
disobeying me!
[struggling]
Mamoru!
Usagi!
I'll get you out..!
Let her go, Makai Tree!
Makai Tree! I said stop
it. Don't drain Mamoru's
energy out of him!
You ungrateful creature,
let go of her, now!
What?!
[grunting]
Usagi!
Mamoru!
[grunting lightly]
Usagi-Speak to me!
Mamoru, please wake up.
Usagi!
[grunting]
Mamoru, too?!
What have you done to
them?!
Usagi, are you
okay?!
No, not really.
So! You've come
to fight us!
Bad idea!
[grunting]
Ahhhh!
Take this!
Fire Soul Bird!
[gasping]
Bubble...
Supreme...
Crescent...
Your attacks are
useless against us!
[screaming]
[gasping]
[laughing]
Now, it's time
to end this!
[groaning]
[laughing]
That's enough!
Moon Crystal Power Make
Up!
What's this?! Usagi
is also Sailor Moon?!
I thought their clumsy
antics seemed oddly
similar!
You two must be
stopped!
Plants are vital to
Mother Nature! They are
friends to every living
thing!
As the saying goes,
"Heaven does not
create..."
"... one plant above another
plant or another plant below
that plant!
Huh?
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now, in the name
of the moon, I'll
punish you!
Ugh, that catchphrase
is so annoying. Ail, get
rid of her right away.
But... shouldn't
we---
I mean, Sailor Moon
is Usagi...
You still don't get
it, do you?!
Tell me, Ail, if your
Miss Tsukino were really
so greatly in love with
you,
then why would she be
standing here trying to
stop us by turning into
Sailor Moon?!
[gasping]
While you may have
thought otherwise, that
girl's never been in
love with you at all.
No! That's not
true.
Wake up, Mamoru! Please,
wake up!
[grunting]
It's me, Usagi!
[struggling]
Please be
all right.
[gasping]
Well, it certainly would
appear that young man
never had feelings for
you either.
You're...
you're wrong.
That can't be!
Well then prove me wrong
and answer this!
Has he ever shown you
his love by holding your
hand or kissing you?
[gasping]
Face the truth, An!
[grunting]
I-I hate this!
[yelling]
The greatest hate
springs from the greatest
love!
[gasping]
Sailor Moon!
[groaning]
Mamoru!
You annoying pests!
You're finished!
Farewell, my
most beautiful
Andromeda-Usagi.
Or rather our enemy,
Sailor Moon.
[struggling]
Makai Tree! We no
longer have any
attachments that bind
us to this planet!
We have tasted the
misery of cruel
rejection!
Wipe this all away
forever!
What?!
Forever?!
Oh no!
Makai Tree! Release your
awesome power!
We won't let you!
HA!
[screaming]
Moon...
Princess!
[grunting]
[struggling]
Ahhhh!
[laughing]
[growling]
[struggling]
Oh! Mamoru!
You're awake!
Sai--
Are you all right?!
Hang in there!
Sailor Moon?!
Mamoru... it's me, Usagi.
The girl you make fun of.
You know... Bun-Head.
What?! Usagi?!
Please try to
remember.
Remember the Moon
Kingdom? And how we fought
against the Dark Kingdom?
How you would always
show up just in time to
rescue me?
Think back and
remember the girl
who loves you.
Memory?! The Moon
Kingdom?
You can do it-try to
remember!
[whimpering]
That's enough!
[screaming]
No! Sailor Moon!
[laughing]
[screaming]
Sailor Moon...
...'R'!
Sailor Moon! R!
[laughing]
[screaming]
Damn!
[grunting]
[struggling]
[gasping]
But why?
Sailor Moon!
[whimpering]
Why did you risk your
life like that?!
I'm willing to risk my
life in order to protect
anyone that I truly love.
[gasping]
Uh!
My, how noble of you!
[grunting]
Come on-Time to beg for
help, you weak little
human!
I--I don't care what
happens to me!
But... just please
spare Mamoru's life!
Sailor Moon!
[laughing]
What a stupid request to
make! But if you think your
own life's not precious,
oh well, then!
[grunting]
No!
He just--?!
[grunting]
Ha!
[struggling]
Mamoru-No!
[gasping in disbelief]
[struggling]
Ah!
Haaaa!
[screaming]
[gasping]
Mamoru-No! Are you
all right? Mamoru!
How beautiful. So
very beautiful.
Is this what it
means to love?
Ail?!
An! I see now. Love
cannot be forced.
Huh?!
Don't you get it? Love
is something that is
built together.
By caring for
each other.
You don't know
what you're saying!
He's right!
Hm?!
When you truly love
someone, the strength of
that love gives you the
courage to overcome anything!
[grunting]
[gasping]
Moonlight Knight!
All the creatures of the
universe are friends!
Instead of fighting
against them, open up
your hearts to them!
That's easy to say,
but you could never
understand all the pain
that we've been through!
Our pain comes from us
wandering the entire
universe all alone
for so long,
with no one ever
caring about us!
An!
We had to take whatever
we could! And if we
hadn't done that, we never
would've survived!
Nothing good comes out
of stealing. It only
brings shame, heartache
and hate.
You shut up!!!
[straining]
[gasping]
The Moonlight Knight's
in trouble!
What's going on?!
[yelling]
[gasping]
Look out!
[grunting]
Oh no!!
Don't hurt him!
[gasping]
An!!!
An!
A-Ail--?
An. Why did you--?
I--because--I did
it because I love you.
You do?
Now I get it. Love's
something we can't steal.
Huh--
I never wanted to
live without you.
An! I don't wanna
lose you!
Something warm is flowing
through me. I've never felt
this way before.
My only regret is that
I'm leaving you.
[gasping]
An!!!!
An, soon I'll be
joining you.
An!
Please just stop!!!
You finally figured
it out.
What? Did the tree
just talk?! [gasping]
[gasping]
Where am I?
Are we inside the Makai
Tree's consciousness?
Eons ago, on a certain
planet, there was only
the ocean and me.
I was alone for a quite
long time. But then, I
wanted someone to talk to.
The Makai Tree gave
birth to my people?
I loved and cared for
every one of them, and in
return, they treated me
with the utmost respect.
We lived in a world of
harmony. Those were such
happy times...
But it did not last.
Eventually, they started
growing selfish and began
fighting over who would
have my energy.
They started losing their
respect for me. They were
filled with anger and
hatred.
They turned into
malicious creatures
motivated only by greed.
I still had faith in them,
though. I was hoping that
once again, all of us,
could live happily,
in harmony, once more.
But they continued
escalating their violence
and ended up destroying
their entire planet.
I wandered with the only
survivors to many planets
and different worlds,
but we could never
find a place we could
call home.
As the years passed, the
survivors began to
perish, until there were
only two of them left...
Ail and An.
You poor, sad souls. You
never knew true love, so
you were forced to rely
on your
strength and wits to keep
on surviving.
Makai Tree... You poor
thing.
You kept thinking energy
was what I needed. But
what I need is love.
Love.
I made myself wither and
grow weak.
I was trying to send you
a signal, but you didn't
understand my plea for
love.
Forgive us.
All is well. In the
end, you have finally
learned what true love is.
Love is about caring for
one another...
An.
[crying]
Sailor Moon... please.
Huh?
Would you please purify
my body and spirit with
your power of love?
Yes.
Moon Princess...
Halation!
Cleansing!
The Makai Tree
disappeared.
It's going to be
reborn.
Huh?
Moonlight Knight, you're
all right!
Sailor Moon... I mean,
Usagi Tsukino.
How do you know my
name?!
Now is the time I will
reveal my true identity
to you.
[gasping]
Mamoru?!
But Mamoru, there are
two of you?!
That's right. You see,
I am another Mamoru.
I don't understand!
After your final battle
against Queen Beryl,
Mamoru's memories were
taken from him.
But there was something
that couldn't be wiped
away.
His resolve to protect
the girl he cared for,
Sailor Moon or rather
Usagi Tsukino, still
remained quite strong.
And that desire was so
deep that it took on a
life of its own, and
created the Moonlight Knight.
His only mission was to
protect you.
Oh, Mamoru!
But my mission has come
to an end. Now that Mamoru
has fallen in love with you
once more,
he and I will become
one again, protecting you
always, as we stay by
your side.
Huh?
Adieu.
[grunting]
[gasping]
Sailor Moon
Moon. Sailor Moon--
Huh?!
Ma-Mamoru, it's you!
Sailor Moon.
Usagi. The little
Miss Bun-Head.
It's really back! Your
memory! It's come back!
You're back! I'm so
happy Mamoru! Mamoru!
[gasping]
Uh--
An!
Ail!
You came back to
life!
An!!!
Ail!
Look!
What is that?!
It's a Makai Tree
sapling.
An, why don't we take
care of her on a new
planet?
Yes, with our love
energy, she'll grow.
Thank goodness.
Yeah.
I know this. Those two
will be happy together.
Yeah, they will.
And we will, too.
You go, girl!
[gasping]
[chatting]
I wanna meet someone
just like Mamoru!
Hands off!
He's mine!
Just kidding!
[giggling]
Wow! A girl just fell
from the sky!
Hmm-I feel a strange
energy from that girl.
Hey, little girl!
Stop flirting with my
Mamoru or else!
Be careful, Usagi. She's
after your Silver Crystal.
Who are you anyway?
Are you an enemy?
Next time on Sailor Moon
R: "Angel or Devil? The
Mysterious Girl from the
Sky."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.