Why do two pretty and sweet
young girls have to stay after
school to study in a gloomy
classroom?
That time's supposed to be for
shopping and dates! Not for
staying behind to study!
Wait, hold on, was
that a Cardian?!
This looks like a job
for Sailor Moon!
In the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
Do it! Now Sailor Moon!
Moon Princess!
Halation!
Cleansing!
Curse you, Sailor Guardians!
You will pay for this!
"After-School Trouble: Usagi
Is a Target"
Oh, no! We're gonna be late!
I messed up!
In fourteen years
I've never been late, and I
don't want to start now!
We gotta hurry, or we're
gonna be in big trouble!
Hey! Wait for me!
Miss Tsukino?
Has anyone seen Miss Tsukino
this morning?
Here!
[Usagi Struggling]
[Gasps]
Usagi Tsukino, present.
Hmph! Who am I kidding, she's
still probably gonna mark me as
late...
Glad you could join us. Now go
and take your seat, Miss
Tsukino.
But please try to enter the
classroom a bit more quietly
next time, all right?
Uh okay.
Well, let's continue taking
attendance.
That was weird...Ms. Haruna's in
a really good mood today!
Ms. Sakurada? Phone
call for you.
Oh, thank you.
Um, hello?
This is she.
Oh hi Koichi!
Why, yes, of course I can still
make our date later today!
I'll come as soon
as school is out.
[Gasp] So you have
to cancel? Oh...
No, it's totally okay.
Really.
All right. Bye.
[Grunting]
[Students Chatting]
[Sigh] I need food...
[Sigh] I need energy...
That's it! Enough horsing
around! Get to your seats now!
[Gasps]
"Once upon a time, there was a
pretty girl who lived on the
moon..."
Now then, who can
translate this passage?
Tsukino!
Huh!
You certainly have a lot of
gall trying to eat your lunch
early, while in my classroom!
Oh no, I was uh...
Staying after school,
is what you're doing.
[Sigh] I was so close.
All right! Natsumi
Ginga?
Huh?
Uh, [Speaking Gibberish]
What kind of bizarre
gibberish is that?!
You asked me to translate the
passage, so I simply said it in
the language of my home planet.
Stop joking and being
disrespectful! Now you're
staying after school as well!
All right...
[Students Talking]
You didn't blow your cover with
that stunt of yours in class,
did you?
No...I really don't think they
suspect anything.
For the sake of our future, you
have to be much more careful!
Yes, all right.
We don't have a choice.
Leave it to me. I'll
find a way to steal
energy for us this time.
Those Sailor Guardians are to
blame for this! And for every
one of the other problems we've
faced!
You're right about that.
That's why we have to choose a
powerful Cardian that won't lose
against the Sailor Guardians.
Yes!
Natsumi! Natsumi! Oh,
there you are!
[Giggling] Ms. Haruna's about to
start after-school detention!
But-Ahh!
Come on! If we don't get there
fast she'll give us more
work to do!
I understand! Stop
pulling so hard!
[Sigh] Oh, my fairest
lady...Usagi...
Mark my words, I will steal
your heart someday soon.
Did you hear? Usagi had to stay
after school to study. So...
That's what she gets
for being so lazy.
I guess, but we all got off
to a late start today.
I actually kind of feel sorry
for her this time.
And Ami's at cram school. I
guess that we'll have to cancel
today's meeting.
In that case, why don't the
three of us go see a movie?
I'm in!
A good one's showing now!
You shouldn't go to movies on
your way home from school.
Woah!
Oh, it's fine!
Come on! Let's go!
I'm not letting you go home
today until you've finished
that entire set of problems.
I'll be with you the whole time!
After all I seem to have all the
time in the world today...
...thanks to that stupid Koichi.
You have a phone call,
Ms. Sakurada.
Really! All right...You just
keep working on those problems!
Hello? Thank you for waiting.
Oh Koichi! No of course not! I'm
not angry with you at all!
Huh?! Right now?
Of course I can! Okay, see you
real soon!
[Giggling] That Koichi! Always
keeping me on pins and needles
like that!
Hmm what's taking Ms. Haruna so
long? I can't waste my whole day
here!
[Giggling] I have to hurry home
so I can catch Mamoru on
the way back from school!
Wait a minute...
Hmm? What?
Are you telling me that you
still haven't given up on
chasing after Mamoru?!
What?! Why would I ever
want to do that?!
Mamoru and I are destined to be
with each other!
We're tied together by the red
string of fate!
Hmm.
So I would never, ever
give up on him!
You can be so difficult,
you know that?!
You leave me no choice. We'll
just have to battle it out!
What?! Battle?
That's right. You and I will
race against each other to see
who can complete this set of
problems first.
And whoever loses will have to
give up on Mamoru. Agreed?
Uh...Okay...
Hmph!
Come forth, Cardian Amanju!
[Flute Music]
Aman!
Now! Amanju! Steal energy from
these people-huh?
Mamoru Chiba...!
If he were gone...
Usagi would be all mine!
Amanju! I want you to go after
the energy of that man first!
And don't hold back! Drain away
every last bit of his energy
until he's dead!
Aman!
Huh?
[Grunts]
Wait! You can't ignore my
orders!
Where is she going?
A, E, I, O, U. Is it
sometimes Y? Or always Y?
[Sigh] I'm so low on energy
right now that my head is
spinning.
If only I had some more energy,
I could solve these simple
problems in no time and make
Tsukino give up on Mamoru.
[Gasp] What am I thinking?
There's energy right there in
front of me!
[Distressed] I have no idea!
[Sinister Chuckle]
And if I drain away all her
energy, I could get rid of her
and make Mamoru mine...
I can kill two birds with one
stone.
Sailor Moon!
R!
Sailor Moon R!
[Screams]
What is that?!
[Gasp] A Cardian!
Aman!
[Scared Breathing]
[Grunts]
Aman!
What was that
just now?
This is Ami! A Cardian
has just appeared!
What?! Are you sure, Ami?
Where is it now?
Near the cram school I go to,
but it ran off toward the
northwest and disappeared.
Understood. All of us will meet
you near there!
C'mon, we gotta go Rei.
But the movie's just
getting good!
Come on! Hurry it up
and get moving!
Okay, okay I get it!
He looks just like Alan...
Minako, let's go!
No! I can't figure it out!
[Sigh]
Hmph!
Oh...
[Heavy Breathing]
[Screams]
What are you doing, Natsumi?
Oh, I...[Laughing]
I'm just getting some exercise
to keep up my mood!
Aman!
Stop Amanju! I told you,
your target is...
Aman!
What is the matter with you
Amanju?!
It isn't possible for a Cardian
to disobey my orders! What is
happening here?!
I'm not going to give up.
[Yawns]
Ow!
Huh?
Oh, sorry!
But that was kinda your own
fault.
You shouldn't sneak up
behind me like that!
[Sigh] Why does everything seem
to be going wrong for me today?
[Sigh] I wonder what could be
keeping Ms. Haruna. We've been
here forever!
[Sigh] I feel like I've
forgotten something, but I
don't know what it could be...
Oh well! I guess it couldn't
be all that important!
Aman!
Huh?
[Screams]
[Gasp]
All right! Just steal human
energy from someone, anyone.
Understand, Amanju?
Aman!
[Struggling]
What are you doing?! I don't
want energy from those birds!
Humans! Humans!
That's enough!
Huh?
Ah ha! Sneaking up on victims
again?!
You've got guts to try that
trick a second time, that's
for sure!
It's a serious crime to
disturb the peaceful lives of
those birds!
We won't let you
get away with this!
Now, in the name of Sailor Moon,
we'll punish you!
[Laughing] So you've come,
Sailor Guardians!
But this time, things will be
quite different, I assure you!
Get them, Amanju!
Aman!
Huh?
[Grunts]
[Grunts] Again?
It ran away...
Does that mean we won?
I can't believe it! Just one
more problem to go and I'm
finished!
Natsumi! How are you doing? You
almost done?
Uh...yeah I'll manage somehow...
Okay! But I'm not gonna lose!
You are a worthy opponent,
Usagi Tsukino...
You've left me no
openings. Well done.
Natsumi, are you okay? You
don't look good.
And you haven't done a single
problem either!
It's nothing. I'm just a bit
tired, and I can't get my
thoughts together, that's all.
[Chuckles] Is there anything I
can do to help you?
What's that?
You can just call it the
compassion of the victor!
But if there's anything I can
do, you just name it, okay?
I once heard an Earth legend
about a race between a rabbit
and a tortoise...
...that story went very much
like this one.
Something wrong?
All right, then. I do have a
favor to ask of you.
Okay. But wait, you can't ask me
for the answers or tell me to
give up on Mamoru, you got it?
Don't worry, it's
nothing like that.
All I want you to do is
close your eyes and remain
completely still for just ten
seconds.
What? Really, that's it?
Just ten seconds?
All right, here it goes!
Thank you.
Now sleep for all
eternity, Usagi Tsukino!
Oh, woah, I feel weird...
[Chuckles]
Aman!
Huh?
Huh! What?
Aman!
Was that a Cardian?
Ail!
Something is very odd. The
Cardian won't listen to my
orders.
What?! But that's impossible!
Just come with me...
[Gasp]
We got you now, Cardian!
Fire...!
Soul!
Supreme...!
Thunder!
Crescent...!
Beam!
Shower!
Bubble Spray...!
Freezing!
[Heavy Breathing]
Aman!
[Screams]
The Cardian is strong! They
won't last long without help!
Oh, there's Usagi!
Hey! I'll go get her
to come down here!
You see? That Cardian isn't
listening to me.
But how can this be? It
shouldn't be possible for a
Cardian to ignore your orders!
Still, that's what
happened...
[Screams]
Hang in there, guys!
Usagi! Stop being so
laid back and transform!
Luna? Hey wait, where's
Natsumi?
I don't know! Just hurry!
K! Leave it to me!
Moon Crystal Power!
Make up!
Yeah!
Sorry I'm late!
No kidding.
Now, now. Give me a break. I
always manage to finish these
things off!
Aman!
Woah, that's weird I have no
energy left...
What's wrong with
you Sailor Moon?
Maybe I studied too hard or
something...
Aman!
[Struggled Screams]
[Screams]
A wicked world is where the
wicked like you belong.
Now, begone at once from the
light of this lovely moon!
Moonlight Knight! What great
timing!
Now, Sailor Moon...Finish her!
Right!
Moon Princess Halation!
Cleansing!
We did it!
The crescent moon itself is no
match for a Pretty Guardian!
Adieu...!
Well all right then! With that
done I better get back to the
classroom!
Natsumi will be wondering what
happened to me! [Giggling]
All of the sudden,
she's full of energy!
There's nobody who can
bounce back like she can...
Yep, that's Sailor Moon
for you!
Okay, we ought to get out of
here as well!
Mhmm.
We failed yet another time...
[Grunts] Curse those Sailor
Guardians!
Well, I better get back to the
classroom now.
If I don't, Tsukino will start
to get suspicious of me.
[Grunts] Something's up.
It feels like something big's
going to happen. Or that
something already has...
All right I'm finished!
Oh, yeah?
Huh?
Natsumi, when did you...?
I only finished a moment ago
myself. Once I put my mind
to it, these took me no time at
all.
Hey! Let's go home Usagi.
It looks like you
worked hard!
I did!
Well, Natsumi, I think that
today's match was a draw!
Yeah, guess so. Looks like we'll
just have to settle this by
letting Mamoru decide.
Okay! But there's no way I'm
gonna lose! See ya!
Oh we'll see about that...
Hey, Luna! Have you noticed that
Seijuro and Natsumi haven't come
to school in a while?
Maybe we should go
check on them!
They probably caught
laziness from you!
Luna!
Wow, Seijuro's apartment sure is
nice! Hey, what's with this
room?!
[Screams]
That's the Makai Tree!
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"Disconnecting Love: The Raging
Makai Tree"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.