Oh no! This just can't be!
Chibi-Usa, is that really you?
What are you doing?! Don't you
recognize us?
Please stop it! I don't want to
fight you!
We love you Chibi-Usa!
In the name of the Moon, I don't
want to punish you!
Chibi-Usa!
Chibi-Usa, where'd you go?
Where are you?
Any luck?
No. We can't find
her anywhere!
Think the enemy's
got her?
[Gasps]
It's best if we don't jump
to conclusions just yet.
We've got to keep looking!
All right then,
let's split up.
Mhmm.
"The Dark Queen: Birth of
Black Lady"
The horrible memories you have
from your past, have left you
with deep, painful scars.
Small Lady, you remember
how your mean mother and your
cruel father always mistreated
you, don't you?
[Giggling]
[Croaking]
Oh wow! Look at that cute green
froggie! [Giggling]
Don't run, or you
might trip and fall!
[Giggling]
[Screams]
[Gasps]
Hmm?
[Sigh]
[Whimpering]
[Crying]
See? That is what can happen
when you don't listen to Mommy.
[Crying]
Crying won't help you.
[Gasps]
Oh Mommy I hate you!
Daddy, help me up?
Get up by yourself.
[Gasps]
Your parents never gave you a
helping hand. That act alone
proves that they never loved
you.
It's your fault
for tripping.
Now, get up!
[Sigh]
Think back and remember all the
many examples of those who have
hated you.
What's wrong, Small Lady?
Why do you look so sad?
Well, you see, today is my
birthday.
Your birthday?
Oh yeah, that's right.
But Mommy and Daddy are doing
something very far away.
These things happen. Both of
them must have just had
important official business
matters to attend to.
Otherwise, they would be
here to celebrate with you.
[Crying]
[Sighs]
Hey wait! Why don't we help her
celebrate.
No!
Huh?
We just can't.
Oh that's right. Sorry,
Chibi-Usa.
Yeah, we have to go.
Bye, Small Lady.
Everyone, they all, they all
just left me alone.
Nobody celebrated with me. My
birthday was ignored.
Yes, your memories are coming
back to you. You're right. No
one loves you.
That's right.
No one cares about me.
No one loves me.
I'm all alone.
So, you hate them, don't you?
[Grunts]
Then set free that hatred on the
world that has rejected you.
Shroud them in the gloom of
darkness forever!
Now, fill your heart with
darkness, and accept the power
of the Malefic Black Crystal.
And use that awesome power to
destroy this world that refused
to love you!
The time has come.
Wiseman!
Our Malefic Black Crystal now
has a faithful and formidable
servant in the Rabbit.
As the recipient of unrivaled
power, the Rabbit has
transformed, and become
the queen of darkness.
What? It can't be, you're the
Rabbit?
Huh?
[Gasp] She's wearing our clan
symbol!
[Laughing]
I am Black Lady!
Demande! You must leave
immediately for 20th century
Earth.
Once you are there, Black Lady
will manifest her Dark Power.
With her darkness, you will be
able to conquer the world!
[Laughing]
Hmph!
Finally, Earth will feel the
full force of my anger. I will
have my revenge!
Brother.
You would do well to be
very cautious of Wiseman.
Hmm.
I believe that he was
responsible for Esmeraude's
death.
Wiseman used her.
Used her? Absurd.
We were exiled, forced to live
on this distant planet because
of the people of Earth!
I would trade the lives of
thousands to have my revenge on
those damn humans!
But don't you see it? Wiseman's
actions have shown that he just
can't be trusted!
You're wrong!
Wiseman has supported us by
sharing important information...
...and providing us with the
energy of the Malefic Black
Crystal.
With everything that's at stake
in this, who else would you have
me trust?
We are so close now.
Those four Sailor Guardians are
the problem.
They are the only ones keeping
us from winning this war!
We must defeat them to succeed.
I believe the best way to
conquer Crystal Tokyo is by
destroying their world in the
past.
Now that the Rabbit has become
Black Lady and truly serves the
Malefic Black Crystal, we must
seize this chance!
So I will now leave for the past
to join her in building a Dark
Gate on their precious Earth.
As for you my dear brother,
you will assist our efforts by
protecting the reactor...
...and amplifying the Malefic
Black Crystal's energy until the
Dark Gate opens.
I will.
Then onward.
Yes!
What?! Chibi-Usa went back into
the past?!
Yes she did. And it also appears
that Demande followed her there,
as well.
Demande?!
That can't be good.
Small Lady was not acting like
herself.
What do you mean?!
Something must have happened to
her, something that changed her!
You must return to the past
immediately!
[All] Huh?
[Quite Gasps]
Sailor Pluto, what was the
cataclysmic event that
occurred on Earth?
What happened during the time
before we became kings and
queens and built Crystal
Tokyo?
Is there any way for us to
prevent this disaster from
happening?
All of you have seen a glimpse
of the future. But it is best
that you not know exactly what
the future holds.
What is important is that you
continue to believe that good
things will come your way...
...and live your lives to the
fullest in your own time,
unburdened by what the future
may bring.
Sailor Moon R!
Where are we?
We're back in the
Juban District.
Oh.
You're right! Look how
lovely the moon is!
[Sigh] Thank goodness, how nice
to be in a peaceful place.
Let's keep it a
peaceful place.
Hmm.
First things first. We've gotta
figure out what Demande's
planning to do here in the
present.
And we have to find
Chibi-Usa as well!
Chibi-Usa, wherever you are, I
hope you're okay.
Now to fulfill my dream and
wreak my vengeance on Earth.
[Chuckling]
Look at all that evil energy!
It appears as if Demande is
trying to create a new Dark
Gate.
We gotta stop him!
[Heavy Breathing]
[Grunts]
[Gasp] What's that?
Sailor Guardians, stop
where you are!
What?! Wait, who are you?
Who am I? I am the Queen of
Darkness, created by the great
Wiseman. I am known as Black
Lady.
Black Lady?
Huh?
Using the Malefic Black Crystal,
I will turn the Earth into a
world of permanent darkness.
[Gasps]
Ahh, Luna P! So at least you
still recognize me!
You were the only one I could
ever call a true friend.
[Gasp]
Is it possible? Are you?
Are you Chibi-Usa?
[Laughing] I guess I may have
been called by that name at an
earlier time.
This can't be!
There's no way! Our Chibi-Usa
would never grow up to be like
you!
Since you don't believe me, I'll
use Luna P to prove just who I
am!
Huh?
[All Scream]
[Moaning]
She's powerful.
Chibi-Usa, what has
happened to you?
I can't forgive you people!
Something's wrong. Her eyes,
somehow someone has brainwashed
her!
Brainwashed?
Her mind is being controlled by
an evil force!
So what should we do?
[Grunts]
[Screams]
Chibi-Usa! Why are
you hurting us?!
I despise all of the people who
ignored me.
In fact, I despise everyone in
this world!
What do you mean people ignored
you? Like who?!
Everyone that I knew!
How can you even say that?!
Chibi-Usa, your dad, your mom,
everyone around you, all of us
loved and cared for you!
Your stupid love was fake!
[Gasp]
[Screaming]
[Grunt]
Sailor Moon! You can't keep
running away!
But I can't bring myself to
fight against her!
She's still Chibi-Usa!
[Grunting]
[Screams]
Go to hell!
[Screaming]
[Gasp]
[Gasps]
Even the prettiest of flowers
will wither away when infected
with poisonous energy.
Chibi-Usa, an evil energy is in
possession of you right now!
Don't be a fool, shake it off!
So you think all of you can gang
up on me and beat me down?
[Screams]
[Gasps]
Quick! Sailor Moon! You must use
the power of the Silver Crystal
to erase the evil energy that's
possessing Chibi-Usa!
Understood.
Chibi-Usa, your mind is infected
with evil energy! So it's time
for you to refresh!
Moon Crystal Power!
[Grunting]
Chibi-Usa! You are not thinking
clearly!
You need to remember your
childhood again! Your mother and
father were always kind to you!
Mommy, Daddy, where are you?
How can both of you be so mean?
I don't want to be left here all
alone by you!
[Heavy Breathing]
[Gasp]
[Sigh]
Small Lady.
Happy birthday
sweetheart!
Mommy! Daddy!
[All] Small Lady! Happy
Birthday to you!
You're all here!
We're really sorry that you
had to wait an extra day to
celebrate your birthday with us.
They rushed right back here as
soon as they could, so they
could have this party for you.
Yeah and they decided they
wanted to make it a big
surprise for your special day!
So we kept it a secret.
Sorry that we
couldn't tell you.
[Sigh] Thank you! Mommy, Daddy,
all of you!
[Sigh]
You all were, happy for me.
[Gasp] Chibi-Usa!
It's working, she's
changing back!
She's finally
seeing the truth!
She's breaking free from
being brainwashed!
Thank goodness!
Chibi-Usa!
Black Lady, don't allow them to
deceive you!
Huh.
Remember how mean your mother
was, and your cruel heartless
father!
[Gasp]
You were a pitiful rabbit who
was starved for love.
Nothing but a lonely soul who
wanted to be remembered on her
birthday, but who never was.
No Chibi-Usa! Don't listen to
that evil man!
You wanted so badly to believe
you were loved, that you
concocted this foolish illusion.
An illusion?
You mean all of my wonderful
memories weren't even real?
Chibi-Usa, you mustn't
let him trick you!
What you saw wasn't something
you dreamed up! It really did
happen to you!
I don't know, I don't know
anymore.
They are lying. No one loves
you! You must harden your heart,
it's time you became more
hateful.
[Screaming]
[Sigh]
No one loves you. It's all lies!
No one will ever love you! No
one!
The truth is, none of you
celebrated my birthday with me!
No one loved me after all!
He's right! You all hate me and
I hate all of you as well!
No! Chibi-Usa!
Come back to us!
Wiseman has given me a new name
and a better life as Black Lady.
I'm not Chibi-Usa!
You're wrong, you
are Chibi-Usa!
That's who you are!
You're not from
the Black Moon Clan!
Remember your true self!
Don't allow that evil
energy to posses you!
[Laughing]
Soon the power of the Malefic
Black Crystal will be unleashed
from Planet Nemesis, and fired
toward Earth.
Then this entire world will be
destroyed.
And every one of you heartless
people will be disintegrated.
Along with your soon to be dark
world!
[Laughing]
[Gasps]
Chibi-Usa!
[Whimpering]
Chibi-Usa.
What do we have to do to turn
you back into yourself again?
Sailor Moon, I must go warn my
brother, Demande! He must know
the truth!
No, don't Saphir!
You're too injured!
He needs to know what Wiseman's
really up to, before it's too
late!
Saphir, look out!
[Screams]
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"Saphir Dies: Wiseman's Trap."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.