Petz! Calaveras! Come to
your senses! Sisters
shouldn't fight with one
another! And you, Rubeus,
are unforgivable! How dare
you play with people's
feelings and trample on
those who trust you!
I am Sailor Moon!
In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
Rubeus...
There are two paths in
front of you. One leads
you to glory. That is
the path of victory.
The other leads you
to death. That is the
dark path of defeat.
Either glory...
or death?
Rubeus, you only have one
option for staying alive.
Eliminate the Rabbit and
the Sailor Guardians.
I am aware of that! And
I'm more than willing to
sacrifice every one of
my pawns to be able
to grab the glory of
victory!
"Rubeus the Heartless:
The Tragic Sisters."
Yay!
Chibi-Usa! Stop scattering
the leaves again! We just
got them all raked up!
You need to pitch in
and help us with the
work!
Says the person who
shamelessly decided to
help only because Rei
mentioned a baked-
potato party.
[annoyed growling]
You can't talk to me
like that! I am older
than you!
[Usagi ranting]
There's a leaf in
your hair, Chibi-
Usa.
Thank you so
much, Koan.
It's important that women
have beautiful hair. You
have to take special
care of it.
You're so nice! I wish
I had a sister just
like you!
[giggling]
Ah!     I never realized
before, how lovely
this world is.
I was so busy fighting,
I never paid attention
to what you have here.
We were wrong. I'm
sorry for what we
tried to do.
We would love to help you
combat the dark force that
we were once a part of, but
we just don't know how.
We were only puppets,
blindly following our
Master's instructions.
Don't worry,
it's okay.
Huh?
We're all just really
happy that you and your
sister are here and have
become our friends.
Thank you, Ami...
Okay! They're done!
Yay! I want the
first one!
Sorry Usagi, this
one's for Chibi-Usa.
What?! But I deserve
it! I worked so hard!
Chibi-Usa, give me
the other half of
that!
Usagi...
You should be ashamed of
yourself, trying to grab
a little girl's food right
out of her mouth.
But it's too
big for her!
Agh!
[burping]
[digusted whining]
Chibi-Usa, why
you little...
Come back here!
[giggling]
Come catch m!
That was supposed
to be mine!
As the Black Moon Clan's
elite Spectre Sister it's
appalling to see how far
the two youngest of
us have fallen!
I hope you're not
thinking of just
ignoring those two
who have disgraced
us. We could very
well end up losing
our credibility if
we do that.
Exactly...
Hm?
I'm extremely disappointed
that two of your siblings
have chosen to betray
our clan.
It's unacceptable.
Why did you allow
that to happen?
It's not our fault.
We had nothing to
do with it!
So you say...
Master Rubeus, let me
assure you we're not
foolish like our
younger sisters.
We will eliminate them,
along with the Rabbit
and the Sailor Guardians!
Really? Are you
sure you'll be
able to do it?
Yes, I am.
Hey, wait a minute...
Very well.
[gasp]
What's this?
A special stick that'll
prove quite useful, as
it will greatly magnify
your dark powers.
Oh!
Just so we're clear.
This is your last
chance.
Eliminate the Rabbit,
the Sailor Guardians,
and your two traitor
sisters.
If you fail, don't
bother coming back.
Understood?
Yes.
Mmm...
Very well. I
wish you luck.
You could have at least
consulted with me before
agreeing to everything.
It's embarrassing that
you speak for both of
us as if I'm not here.
Well, get over it. And
while you're at it, just
make sure you don't get
in my way. I don't
have time for that.
What do you mean?! I'm
not in your way! You're
always in mine with your
lousy attempts to
do better than me!
I'm forced to take the
lead because you, Koan,
and Berthier are so inept.
And don't forget the
power-enhancing stick
is mine!
I want it!
[grunting]
Hmph!
Usagi!
You've had enough.
You're gonna gain
weight.
So what?
I don't care!
Maybe that 'I don't care'
attitude is what made
somebody dump you!
Rei!
[crying]
More to the point, Usagi.
Overeating is proven to
slow the mind, and makes
you very sleepy.
You really owe it to
yourself as a student to
be aware of your diet, so
you can stay awake and study.
What's more, eating too
many sweet potatoes has
another unpleasant
effect...
That's right. You may
end up passing smelly
gas.
Oh, be quiet. I just
want to eat my potatoes
in peace.
Oh!
Ew! That was
really gross.
Oh, c'mon! It wasn't
all that bad.
[embarrassed giggling]
[gasp]
What is that?
Huh?!
Look out!
Chibi-Usa!
Give them back!
[screaming]
Oh my goodness!
What was that thing?!
Chibi-Usa, no matter
what happens, don't
come out!
Let's go!
Mm!
They were both taken
because they were
protecting me!
Everyone, transform!
[affirmative grunting]
I have to find the Sailor
Guardians to help save
my friends!
Mars Star Power!
Venus Star Power!
Jupiter Star Power!
Mercury Star Power!
Make Up!
♪ Sailor Moon!
Sailor Mercury!
Sailor Mars!
Sailor Jupiter!
Sailor Venus!
Moon Crystal Power!
Make Up!
♪ Sailor Moon!
Sailor Moon!
[affirmative grunts]
What does the
enemy want?
To kill their traitors?
Don't say that!
Stay positive! Let's
not give up hope.
I'm picking up an unusual
energy reading. It seems
to be coming from the west.
Everyone! Let's hurry!
You know, sister. I'm
having a lot of trouble
believing that the Sailor
Guardians will come
to rescue these two
traitorous scum.
Isn't it better to
kill them now and
be done with it?
Hmph! Have a
little patience.
Fine. That stick really
does have some awesome
magnifying force.
It's infinite power is
surging through my body.
At the moment, I'm
invincible!
Oh, and you know what
else? Your complexion
looks better than ever.
Let me try it now.
[forceful grunt]
Why do you have
to be so stingy?
Koan and Berthier already
betrayed the Spectre name.
And I don't feel I can
trust you, either.
But, Petz...
[groaning]
Hmph! Looks like our
scum have finally
awakened.
Petz, Calaveras! What
do you want with the
two of us?
I want you to tell me
where the Sailor Guardians
and the Rabbit are!
We're only willing to
do that if you promise
to stop your mission to
eliminate them!
No way!
Why are you even
suggesting such
a thing?!
We have come to realize
the true nature of that
man, Rubeus, and the
Black Moon Clan!
It's frightening!
The clan is willing
to destroy everything!
As long as it can
achieve its own
ends!
That, my dear sister,
is merely the nature
of battle, where the
victor is always right...
...And love and
friendship mean
nothing!
Now die!
Not so fast!
Hate to tell you,
but you've got it
all wrong!
Sailor Moon!
We fight for the sake
of protecting this
lovely planet!
For all kind-
hearted people!
For trees, flowers,
and all of nature's
creations!
For love, happiness,
and a beautiful future.
You wanna trample
all that?
Not while I'm around!
Now, in the name
of the Moon...
...We'll punish you!
Hmph! You're so
predictable! We
prepared for you
to come looking
for these two.
Didn't you know
this was a trap?
We knew, but we
followed you here
anyway!
We want our friends
back! Please return
them to us!
Sailor Mercury...
Your so-called friends
are our traitor sisters!
I'm tired of all
this nonsense!
Dark Thunder!
Hnnh!
Oh! Wow!
Let me try! I wanna
know what it feels
like!
It's mine!
Back off!
Dark Thunder!
[screaming]
Hah!
[chuckling]
Petz and Calaveras...
When you aren't able
to finish the job,
I will.
[chuckling]
Sailor Moon R!
Dark Thunder!
[screaming]
[groaning]
Is everyone
all right?
What incredible power!
Let's fight thunder
with thunder!
Sparkling Wide
Pressure!
Dark Thunder!
[screaming]
Are you all right?
Been better. She's
several degrees more
powerful than last time.
Wait a minute...
I've found the source
of that power. Her stick
is radiating an immense
energy!
So if we're able to
get it away from her...
...Her power should
return to normal.
Leave it to me!
Venus Love Me Chain!
I missed her!
She's moving too fast!
Burning...
...Mandala!
[grunting]
Whoa!
[gasps]
Dark Thunder!
[screaming]
[chuckling]
I'll put you out of
your misery now.
Stop, Sister!
Enough already!
Forget what Rubeus
told you! Don't do
this anymore!
Once you've done what
he asks, he won't give
you a second thought!
He'll try to get rid
of both of you, like
he did with us!
You can't trust him!
Please believe us!
We are telling you
the truth!
Just listen!
You two always think
you know more than us.
Are you trying to mess
with our heads so we
fail in our mission?
That's not it!
We're only telling you
all this for your own
good!
Now I'm telling you.
You've outlived your
usefulness.
And I really don't care
to listen to your stupid
nonsense anymore.
Sister, these two are
really annoying. Don't
you think it's time you
got rid of these irritants?
Hmph! Why not?!
Dark Thunder!
[gasp]
[screaming]
Sister, stop!
What are you
doing?!
You have ridiculed and
laughed at me for as
long as I can remember,
but it doesn't look
like you're laughing
now.
Ah! Forgive me!
With this stick, my
powers are strong
beyond compare!
Soon, I will surpass
Master Rubeus. I may
even become clan
leader!
You've always tried to
put me down. This time
I'm putting you down
permanently!
[laughing]
What's gotten
into you?
Go to hell with
the others! Traitor!
[screaming]
Koan!
Berthier!
Are you all right?
Koan!
Yes...
Thank you,
Sailor Mars.
I can't believe my
sister tried to kill me.
Are you all right?
Just moments ago we
were trying to kill
you. Why do you care?
Being concerned when
someone's hurt feels
like the right thing
to do.
It is common that
people do this sort of
thing in this world?
That's right, you're
receiving the kind of
love that is part of
the human experience.
It's what we had
forgotten in the
Black Moon Clan.
But the Sailor
Guardians are here
to remind us of it.
I've been so wrong
in how I've treated
my sisters.
What a mess! Earth
trash and Clan trash
all blending together.
What?!
That's enough! You're
out of control and
we're gonna stop you!
Trying to kill your
very own sisters? How
could you be so utterly
heartless?
Hmph! They're useless
garbage! Never been
able to complete a
mission.
Just waste I need
to get rid of!
[growling]
No use trying to
talk sense into
her.
Wait! Don't give
up on her just yet!
[gasp]
She's been completely
taken over by the
immense evil power
of that stick!
I knew it!
What can we do
to change that?
I might know a way.
What we'll do is...
Go to hell!
...combine powers!
Bubble Spray!
Now!
Okay! Venus Love
Me Chain!
Agh!
Jupiter!
Right!
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
[painful grunts]
[laughing]
[groaning]
Are you all
right, sister?
Keep your hands
off me!
I don't want your pity
now that my life has
been ruined!
Don't say that!
Well done, Petz!
Master Rubeus!
I can explain...
You gathered the Sailor
Guardians and the traitors
together. Just as I hoped
you would.
In case you're wondering,
I always intended to take
the glory myself.
Huh?!
Once the Sailor Guardians
are finally out of the
picture, I can do all the
rest.
What about me?
Where do I fit in?
You don't. People
like you are
expendable.
And replacements
are easy to get.
[gasp]
Go to hell with the
Sailor Guardians!
They're about to
experience the true
power of the stick.
Sucked into the tear
between dimensions.
[screaming]
Ahh!
If this force keeps
up, we'll be sucked
in!
What's causing this?!
When Petz was using
that stick, it was
giving off forward
motion power.
He must have now
switch it into
reverse!
It's generating
a black hole?!
Is there any way
to stop it?
Luna?!
He's created a
dimensional tear!
There's no way to
fix that!
Hold on, maybe
there is a way!
If I direct every ounce
of my remaining power
toward that stick, I
might be able to destroy
it. T hen it's possible
that the black hole will
disappear!
But that's extremely
risky! You could be
killed in the process!
Better to try, than
to lose your world
without a fight!
Dark Power!
[gasp]
[screaming]
Calaveras!
You know me, I just
can't bear to see you
get all the glory.
Don't let go!
But why are you-?
I know in the past all
we did was fight with
one another, but we
were always together.
We wouldn't be the
Four Spectre Sisters
if one of us was
missing.
[gasp]
[grunting]
[screaming]
We're done for!
Don't give up,
Sailor Moon!
Tuxedo Mask!
If you put all your
powers together, I'm
sure you'll be able
to seal the tear
between the
dimensions.
But how?!
He's right! I get
what he's saying!
Huh?
We know that stick is
creating a funnel similar
to a black hole, and is
trying to pull us
into another dimension.
...But if you surround it
and project your combined
energies to break it up,
that funnel should disappear!
To do that we'll
have to jump in
there!
I'm afraid that's the
only way to get the
job done! Let's go!
Everyone jump together
on the count of three!
One, two...
Three!
Where's the stick?!
If we don't find it
quickly, we'll be
thrown into another
dimension.
There!
Hurry! Grab each
others hands!
Now focus on that
stick and power up
everyone!
Moon Crystal Power!
Mars Star Power!
Mercury Star Power!
Jupiter Star Power!
Venus Star Power!
Sailor Planet Power!
[screaming]
Did it work?
Yes! The tear between
dimensions is gone!
[sighs of relief]
Huh?
Thank you,
Tuxedo Mask.
Sailor Moon!
I want all of us to
be together. Can
you help?
Mm-hm...
Moon Crystal Power!
Refresh!
Usagi has the Silver
Crystal and is Sailor
Moon.
All this time... Sailor
Moon's had the Silver
Crystal!
Agh! Curses!
Oh? The sisters
started their
own business?
Yeah, they sell products
that are supposed to make
everyone beautiful.
Hi! Would you like to
try a product that will
make you beautiful with
a money-back guarantee?
Berthier, if you don't
stop, you'll use up
all the products!
It's maintenance. I have
to use everything, so
my complexion is
flawless, otherwise
our customers won't
believe us.
Well, believe this!
[arguing]
This is why I prefer
door-to-door sales!
They say the more you
quarrel, the closer
you are.
They're kinda
like us!
Except they don't have
to put up with a certain
someone who's in her own
little world, and is
always competing with
me.
Oh really? Who
would that be?
Gee. I haven't got
a clue. Does it ring
a bell with anyone?
Why you!
[grunting]
Hmph!
[sighs]
Why are you
being so mean?
I'm not! I'm
being honest!
Could you two just
cut it out!
She started it!
♪ Sailor Moon!
What am I going to do?
Chibi-Usa took my
transformation brooch!
Get it back! It'll
put her life in danger!
Why? How come?
The brooch contains the
Silver Crystal! What
if the enemy finds out?!
Chibi-Usa! Give me back
my brooch now! I need
the Silver Crystal to
save everyone!
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"A UFO Appears: The Sailor
Guardians Abducted!"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.