So get this: Rei's grandpa
started this weird business
called Protection Aesthetics.
He says it's supposed to
make you become pretty
and fit, but I don't know.
I just hope it doesn't
get him into trouble.
Uh-oh, looks like
he is in trouble!
Come on, we
gotta save
him!
Rei you must punish them
with your new technique!
(Grandpa Hino)
[sigh]
I wonder why there
aren't any gals coming
to the shrine anymore?
Who knows?
[Rei]
Well, here's
your answer.
What's this?
Huh?
This month's Nanako magazine
has an article talking about
how you harass all the young
girls who visit Hikawa Shrine.
What?!
Oh no!!
You weren't
kidding! Ooh..
So you see Grandpa,
you need to change
your ways.
Nope. I'm putting
you in charge
instead.
Huh?!
I'm done being a priest
and running this place,
I'm going to retire and
do something else!
Having a shrine without
any girls, is like having
miso soup without any miso.
Huh?
"Women Must Be Strong
and Beautiful: Rei's
New Special Technique."
[Luna]
Wow, is she
actually studying?
I should've
known.
[tickled]
[startled]
Wh-aaa! Hand over the
Silver Crystal! Whaa!
You wake me up,
you pay the price!
[laughing]
I wish I were
stronger than
Usagi!
Wh-aaa!
Oh no! I just remembered,
Rei asked me to go help
her out!
[yells]
Must...get...stronger.
Oh wow-wee!
This outfit looks
great on me. It's
so cool!
Uh-hm!
You look weird!
Shut it!
I wonder why we're
getting so many
visitors today.
I think I know the reason
they all showed up. It's cuz
we're here dressed as beautiful
shrine shrine maidens!
I get to be a maiden and
use my business math skills
at the same time. It's great.
With this much work,
we better be getting
paid a lot!
Sure. You'll
all get paid!
By the way Rei,
what sort of
business did your
grandpa start?
Oh boy...
It's a really
weird one.
[practice excercises]
(Usagi)
Uh, what the heck
are they doing?
He says it's a new sport
combining self-defense
with beauty workouts.
I just wish the classes
weren't happening here
at the shrine. They're
a big pain.
What do you
mean by that?!
[startled]
It's inappropriate
and embarrassing!
Plus you both look
ridiculous in those
outfits!
Oh, well,
I kinda
like them.
[snarl groan]
Do you wanna take
an old man's reason
for living away?!
I know why you're doing this!
You just wanna get young girls
to take your class with you!
And what's
wrong with
that?!
It's just
wrong!
[snarl groans]
Well I will not
be responsible
for what happens.
Hmph!
So who'd like to
take our Protection
Aesthetics class?
I-I-I need to
wash my hair!
So can
I try?
[running]
(Chibi-Usa)
What are
you doing?!
(Chibi-Usa)
Put me down, Usagi!
(Calaveras)
Master Rubeus,
where is Koan?
I sent her to take
out our next target.
Huh?!
We have discovered
a new Crystal Point
in a different area.
[chuckles]
Koan's very excited. She plans
to swap the Crystal Power in
this building with Dark Power.
Why would you go
and give Koan such
an important mission?
You didn't trust me
to go and do it!?
I never
said that!
(Grandpa Hino)
Come try our class!
Check us out!
Our Protection Aesthetics
class will make you young
ladies beautiful and uh, uh
strong!
Hm! Not one
sign-up yet.
[sigh] Where's Yuichiro,
he's supposed to be here
signing up girls for class!
I can't count on
that young boy
for anything!
Huhh?
[laughing]
I'm ready
to sign up!
Hmmm, I really only
wanted teenaged girls
and older. But she's
better than nobody.
Will I
become
strong?
Ehh, so you want
to be strong?
Hm!
Once I become strong, I'll
take the Silver Crystal away
from Usagi and spank her good!
Owie owie owie!
Master!
Ohh! Who are
all these ladies?
Master! They all
want to sign up!
[chuckles]
Well done, Yuichiro!
I knew you'd come through!
[laughing]
Dark Power!
[sinister laughing]
I can't wait for tomorrow.
Good morning Rei!
Sleep well?
It's already
afternoon.
[gasp]
Sounds like you're
in a bad mood!
Yeah Rei, is
something wrong?
Yuichiro collected a big group
of girls and he's brought them
back to the shrine!
[groans]
How cute!
You're jealous,
aren't you?
I am not
jealous.
No way!
I don't
believe
you!
Are those gals
ready for class?
Yes, they're waiting
for you Master.
Good, good!
Ugh! I wish they
hadn't done that!
[wincing]
C'mon!
Let's go
take a look!
But I
don't
wanna.
Ah don't be
like that!
[class chatter]
Tat-ta-da-dah!
[cheering]
Good morning, Master!
[con't cheering]
I'm in heaven!
[cheers]
At last! What I've been
hoping for all these years,
wall to wall women!
[giggles]
With this many students,
you'll probably need female
instructors, don't you think?
Uh, could be!
Well my friend and I
know some good martial
art moves. Can we teach
the class?
Sure cutey!
Let's start class!
Dumbull!
Wait I don't
wanna fight!
Dumbull.
Hey! Why'd
you do that?
Dumbull.
Oh calm down. We're
simply teaching
Protection Aesthetics.
Dumbull!
[yelling]
Ouch, what
the heck?
Huh?
Something
doesn't
feel right!
(Chibi-Usa)
Ta-da!
Huh?
[giggles]
Uhh...
(Chibi-Usa)
Okay! Time to
get stronger!
No don't do it!
Dumbull!
[yelling]
It looks painful!
You might be
right, Usagi.
I quit. See ya!
I'd say that's
a good call.
Dumbull!
[grunt]
That is it!
Finally,
she's mad.
[charged running]
[kicking grunt]
Ahhh!
[gasp]
Are you alright?
She sure is rough.
How was that? Did we
highlight protecting
oneself enough, Master?
Well, I uh...
(Yuichiro)
Hold on, Master!
Huh?
I am the instructor here!
Yu-Yuichiro...
But I'm your
instructor.
Let's let
him decide!
Yeah Grandpa.
Hunh...
Who should
I choose?
If I pick Yuichiro,
I'll upset her. So
maybe I'll pick her.
Master you
wouldn't!
Make a
good choice.
Grandpa!
Uhh...
There's nothing to think
about! Yuichiro's been
here with you a long time,
Grandpa!
After all he's done,
you can't just toss
him aside?
This isn't your decision
to make! So then what
do you say, big boy?
It's me,
or her!
[giggles]
I pick her.
You pick her?!
How could you!
C'mon, you can't
seriously mean
that!
No, it's all right.
[panicing]
Hm! How dare you do
this to Yuichiro!
It makes no sense!
That's where
you are wrong!
[groans]
Sailor Moon
R!
Sailor Moon R!
(Minako)
Ohh... So your grandpa
really did that to Yuichiro?
You must feel like he let you
down. I know you care about
Yuichiro; what your Grandpa
did was mean.
That's not really
what I'm angry about!
The most challenging
problems are always
the most satisfying
to resolve!
Take this problem here.
It took me three hours
to find an answer.
Excuse me?
So by the way Rei,
didn't you think
that new instructor
was weird?
Mhm...
Do you think
she could hurt
your grandpa?
At the moment
I don't care what
happens to him!
'Kay, you're taking
this well Rei!
Ahh! Hot!
Oh! You okay?
Yeah.
What's wrong? It's like your
mind's somewhere else today.
Dumbull!
[yelling]
[impact grunt]
[murmuring]
[attacking yell]
[pained grunt]
[kicking grunt]
[pained yell]
My plan's working! If I can
keep spreading the Dark Power,
then Future Crystal Tokyo will
be destroyed.
Girls oh no?! What's
going on here?! This
class was supposed
to be fun!
Stop! Wait! Don't!
[leaping grunt]
(Grandpa Hino)
That's enough rough stuff!
Stop it, before somebody
really gets hurt!
Dumbull!
[kicking grunt]
The motto of Protection
Aesthetics is to become
"Strong and beautiful,"
..with a little pleasure
thrown in for me!
Now you-!
[growling]
What's gotten
into you?
Die!
[propelling grunt]
[punching grunts]
Um-hm!
[fainting]
[laughing]
You are indeed a master.
Dumbull, take Grandpa down.
Hnh! Dum-bull!
Dum-bull!
[grunt]
Ahh!
Dumbull! Time to use your
special Dumbull Elbow Drop
Attack!
Dumbull!
[pained groans]
[attacking yell]
[gasp]
[scared whinning]
[pained yelp]
[wincing]
Rei!
I warned you didn't I?
Now do you believe me?
What are you talking about?
You act like I'm an old man who
can't handle his own business!
Huh?
Let's do this!
[attacking yell]
[confident grunt]
Dumbull!
Uh-oh!
[pained groan]
[pained grunt]
Rei, are you
all right?
[gasp]
Dumbull!
[stomping grunt]
[grunt]
Rei! Save yourself!
You've done enough here!
No, I won't!
I mean, after all,
you're the only
Grandpa that I have.
Rei...
Dumbull! Do the
Dumbull Lariat!
[strengthening groans]
Huh?!
[groan]
Dumbull!
[pained yell]
[gasp]
They're in
trouble!
Moon Crystal
Power Make Up!
[chuckles]
We're not
done yet,
Dumbull.
[throwing grunt]
Koan! Dark
Power Press!
Ahhh!
[gasp]
[landing grunt]
Damn it! Who
just did that?!
You have crushed a slightly
lecherous old man's whole
reason for living!
I'd say you've
gone way too
far!
I am the
Pretty Guardian
Who fights for
love and for
justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the
name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
Hmmm...
Did you say
something?
Da-ahh...
[chuckles]
Dumbull, get her!
[summoning strength yell]
Dumbull!
[gasp]
Huh?!
Tuxedo Mask,
It's really you!
It's fine to train oneself to
become strong, but I would've
hoped you'd still strive to
be graceful and kind.
Dumbull!
[grunt]
[pained grunt]
[landing grunt]
Take her down,
Sailor Moon!
Right!
Moon Princess Halation!
[gasp]
What!?
Oh dear a
dark spot!
Feel the rage of my
ruined complexion!
Dark Fire!
Wa-aa!
[running]
[grunt]
Those monsters,
how dare they do
this to my grandpa!
Grandpa...
I'll make them pay
for hurting you!
Mars Star Power Make Up!
Dark Fire!
Ahh!
Look out!
Now it's my turn
to attack you!
Fire Soul!
[laughing]
[straining]
[gasp]
Hang on
Mars!!
Wait.
I think Mars can
handle this attack.
She's very strong.
But I can't lose to her. Not
after the things she's done!
This one's for
my Grandpa!
Burning...
Mandala!
[scared gasp]
[gasp]
My precious dress!
You ruined it!
[chuckles]
Looks like I
defeated her!
Maybe I should go join the
Protection Aesthetics class
so I can become a strong and
pretty girl.
[gasp]
Suit yourself.
It's really not my
business what you do.
Huh?
Forgive me,
Usako.
Ahh...
The fact that he came to help
you proves that he does care
about you.
Um-hm.
(Usagi)
Aww so your grandpa is all done
with his Protection Aesthetics
class?
(Rei)
Yeah, but now he's started
something called Protection
Jazz Dance!
Protection Jazz?!
Ha! This is so much
fun and it doesn't
hurt a bit! Ha-ha!
And because I've got such
great moves, Master needs
me to help out after all!
Ha-ha-ha!
I'm just gonna keep dancing
'til all those pretty girls
come back!
Ughhh...
And one, two, three, four!
Let's dance some more.
Ha-ha yeah!
Daddy... Mommy!
What's wrong, Chibi-Usa?
You don't look happy.
An airhead like you wouldn't
understand my problems!
How rude!
I may not show it,
but I have my share
of worries too!
There's Mamo,
there's my family,
and... huh?
By the way,
where are your
parents, Chibi-Usa?
Next time on Sailor Moon R:
"In Search of the Silver
Crystal: Chibi-Usa's Secret"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.