KAZUMA: Eyes as blue
as the azure sky.
That is the symbol
of the Contractor.
Entrusted by the spirit
king of the wind,
with the powers of his domain.
I bear this mark, the
stigma of the wind.
You have no idea who
you're messing with, Kazuma!
Actually, I do.
You inherited the Enraiha,
so you're the next head
of the Kannagi family.
[YELLING]
I won't forgive him.
Not now, not ever.
Kazuma!
Ugh, it's so unfair!
It really makes me mad!
I was just trying
to help the family,
but did I get any thanks?
No, I got yelled at!
So I snuck out and
tried to beat up the guy
without father's permission.
Big deal!
He still grounded
me for a month.
A month!
[GULPING]
Yeah, I really
don't understand
what she's talking about.
The only thing
I could figure out
is her father grounded
her again for some reason?
That's the fourth time she's
been grounded this month,
I think.
AYANO: I'm gonna see that guy
again and settle the score!
Hey, wait!
She's talking about a guy!
Oh, yeah, so what?
Do you think maybe
she has a boyfriend?
Uh.
[SLURPING]
No, not a chance.
Ah, yes!
This place doesn't close
for another five minutes!
If we hurry, we can still
get a few more pieces
of cake before time's up.
Come on!
Yeah, there's
definitely no boyfriend.
Nope.
MAN 1: Shingo Yuki
and Takeya Ogami?
MAN 2: It's awful to be
cut down so young in life.
Do you think it was Kazuma?
MAN 1: Of course,
who else could it be?
The murders started
happening after he came back.
MAN 2: You're right.
He's a wind magic
user now, and has
a grudge against the family.
So you feel the
same way I do, Genma?
If it was Kazuma, why would he
trap Ayano with a wind barrier,
then murder Shingo and
Takeya in front of her?
It just doesn't make any sense.
That's like announcing
he's the killer.
I doubt the boy
would be that stupid.
Too bad the rest of the family
doesn't share our feeling.
It is easier to believe that
Kazuma is behind the attacks
than some unknown enemy.
I can't blame them.
He's acted suspiciously and has
plenty of reasons to hate us.
JUGO: Genma, why did
you abandon Kazuma?
I'm a member of
the Kannagi family.
You know our traditions
and principles, Jugo,
they call for our children
to learn our way of life.
And he had difficulty
mastering it.
Is that why you
decided to shun him,
so that he could find
his own path to follow?
GENMA: I will bring Kazuma
back here myself, Jugo.
You think he'll come?
Yes, I will convince him
either by words or by force.
JUGO: Very well, good luck.
[PHONE RINGING]
Yeah?
Put him through.
GENMA: Kazuma, I'm
surprised you picked up.
Been a while, old man.
Sorry, but calling
you father doesn't
seem appropriate anymore.
GENMA: You can call
me whatever you like.
I take it you're not
calling just 'cause you
wanted to hear your
son's voice for the first
time in four years.
GENMA: Of course not.
You know damn well
what I'm calling about.
The old park, tonight.
Be there.
I knew the Kannagis
would send somebody,
but I never would have
imagined it'd be him.
Father, I'm so sorry!
Forgive me!
You lost to a girl four
years younger than you are.
This is pathetic.
You're supposed to be the heir
to the head of the family.
Stop crying.
I was wrong for trying to
make you learn fire magic.
Now there's no longer any
need for you to practice it.
And there's no longer any
place for you in this family.
The Kannagis are fire
magic users and you're not.
Pack your things and go.
Now get out of my sight.
Do you understand me?
Wait, father!
Please, no!
I'm not your father anymore.
I have only one son
now, and that's Ren.
I'm sorry!
Father, forgive me.
I'll try to do better.
Please!
You've shamed me
for the last time.
Now, leave!
Back then, my father
pushed me around
and rolled over every aspect
of my life with an iron fist.
But I'm not the same
scared kid I used to be.
Time to find out if I'm finally
strong enough to push back.
HYOE: The identity of
the wind magic user
who killed the young men
from the branch families
is still unknown.
However, the entire
Fuga Clan has
been mobilized for the search.
We will find this
killer for you.
Please grant us just a
little more time, sir.
Of course.
Carry on, then.
Hyoe, how has your
son been recently?
His name's Ryuya, right?
Yes sir.
His condition requires
much bed rest.
Though he will
survive, I fear he
may never recover enough to
serve your family, master.
That should be the
least of your concerns.
Just let him recuperate and
tell him that I wish him well.
Yes.
Many thanks, Master Jugo.
AYANO: Ugh!
The more I think about
it, the angrier I get!
My family's in crisis,
but I can't do anything
about it because I'm grounded.
I'm the next head of the
Kannagis and now all I can do
is sit back and watch
what happens next?
This is crazy!
I hope you're happy
wherever you are, Kazuma.
This is all your fault!
Make this quick.
Turn yourself in.
Guilty or innocent, you've
got a lot to answer for.
Those are the first words
you have to say to a son
you haven't seen in four years?
What if I say no?
Are you gonna use your powers
to take me in by force?
If it's a fight you
want, I'm ready.
Don't make me laugh.
You don't have a chance
of beating me, boy,
and you know it.
I'm not a kid anymore.
I'm strong now, old man.
By studying the lesser art
of wind magic for four years?
I doubt it.
You're a weakling.
KAZUMA: You don't know
a damn thing about me,
but I'll let you in
on a little fact.
I refuse to take orders from you
or anyone else in the family,
ever again.
I'm not surprised.
I had a feeling it
would come to this.
Yeah?
How's this for a surprise?
Don't tell me
that's all you've got.
No way, not even close.
Damn.
It has no effect.
Look, I don't care what you
think about the family or me,
but I don't have time for you
and your little parlor tricks,
so let's end this right now.
GENMA: So, you're using a
wind barrier to repel things.
He burns only his
target and nothing else.
No wonder he's the family's
strongest fire magic user.
I'm actually impressed.
I see now that I
shouldn't have held back.
That's a mistake I plan
to rectify, this time.
[YELLING]
I'm scared now.
But I have to let you live.
I'm gonna need some
answers before killing you.
I don't think so.
Impressed?
GENMA: It'll take a
lot more than that.
You controlled the
oxygen within the wind,
creating excessive combustion‐‐
a trick you used on
Shingo and Takeya.
You're pretty smart, old man.
And you're pretty dumb if
you thought the same thing
would work on me.
Is this one of the
skills I supposedly
don't know about you?
Is that all you've accomplished
in the last four years?
You disappoint me.
Oh, really?
Hey, why don't you try
telling me something
I don't know, old man?
Disowning me made
it pretty clear.
GENMA: I'm going to
say this one last time.
Surrender now.
I'd rather die
than give in to you!
I'm not going anywhere.
Very well.
If you won't come
along willingly,
I have no other choice but
to use an alternate form
of persuasion.
Oh, yeah?
That's the God's Fire.
KAZUMA: The azure flames.
God's Fire.
The ultimate power.
So strong that only the
greatest masters of fire magic
can summon it.
Over the 1,000 years of
the Kannagi family history,
only 11 members have had
the skill to master it.
I guess that's the
legendary God's Fire, huh?
Bravo.
I've never seen it.
You never bothered
to show it to me.
Well take a good look.
This is true power, and
those little tricks of yours
are totally useless against it.
You're right.
Those tricks won't work
against the God's Fire.
So I guess I'm gonna have to
use something a little stronger.
You showed me your
true power, old man.
And now I'm going
to show you mine.
Wait, are those
spirits of the wind?
And there are so many of them.
My God, but how?
It's not possible!
Nice try, but wind magic
can summon spirits faster.
I see.
He did it.
He found his own way.
[LAUGHING]
I did it!
I beat him!
How about that, old man?
This so‐called weakling
just kicked your ass!
[LAUGHING]
What should I do, Tsui‐Ling?
Please, tell me.
What am I supposed to do?
A fire magic user's here.
Another Kannagi?
Come on out!
REN: I never thought
anyone could do it,
but if you're here that
can only mean one thing.
You defeated him.
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
Come on!
Don't tell me you've
forgotten what
your own brother looks like.
My brother?
Oh, man.
Then I guess that means
you're Ren, aren't you?
That's me.
You sure have gotten big.
What's it been, like
a million years now?
It's only been four, Kazuma.
Sure feels a heck of a
lot longer than that to me.
Do you remember when
I left home back then?
Yes, how could I forget it?
You didn't even bother
to say goodbye to me.
I'm sorry about that.
Hey, how did you know you
could find me at this hotel?
Hyoe Kazamaki told me this
is where you were staying.
He did, huh?
So, what are you up to?
Why'd you come here?
To talk to the brother
I haven't seen in years.
Hmm.
Right.
Where are you going?
Upstairs to my room.
It's been a crazy
day and I'm beat.
Well, you coming?
Of course!
Cool.
Oh, by the way, don't
worry about your old man.
I made sure he
got to a hospital.
You took him yourself?
No, that would've been too
much of a pain in the ass.
I just called 911 and told
them where to find him.
REN: What?
How could you?
He's your father!
Weird.
Who's texting me this late?
It's from Ren.
"I'm going to the Royal Bay
Hotel to see my brother.
Please don't worry."
I've got you now, Kazuma.
It's true.
You're him, aren't you?
The contractor.
You can tell me.
The Contractor?
What makes you say that?
Well, it's the
only explanation
for what happened tonight.
A Contractor makes a pact with
one of the great spirit kings,
and they're given powers.
All the powers of
that king's domain.
You know this, right?
Yeah, of course I do.
And that's why the Kannagis
can use fire magic today.
The first head of the
family was made a Contractor
by the spirit king of fire.
It's ancient family history now.
Maybe it's not so ancient.
There have been rumors floating
around the internet recently.
Some occult websites
are claiming
that there's a new Contractor
in the world today.
Supposedly, a wind magic user.
KAZUMA: And you believe
this stupid rumor?
Why?
Because there's no other way
you could have defeated Dad!
He's too strong!
You have to be the
Contractor, otherwise
you'd be too weak to beat him.
Gee thanks, you're really
breaking my heart tonight, kid.
I'm sorry.
[LAUGHING]
I'm just kidding.
Look, I know you didn't
just come here to talk
about goofy internet rumors.
What's really on your mind?
Well, I need to
ask you something.
Are you the wind
magic user who's been
killing members of our family?
No.
I've told that to every
Kannagi I've run across.
But none of them seem to believe
me, even though I'm innocent.
Then why don't you do
something to clear your name?
Come to the compound.
Someone in the family's
just gotta believe you.
KAZUMA: I don't know.
Jugo might.
If I met with him,
he could probably
get this mess straightened out.
Then let's go!
And give in?
I'm done doing what the
Kannagi family wants me to do.
Why?
It's not like I hate
the family or anything.
But still, I can't forget
what they did to me.
And I don't think
that I ever will.
That's why I cast off the
family name and took a new one,
to liberate myself.
The old Kazuma Kannagi might've
yielded to their demands.
But Kazuma Yagami never will.
Not an inch!
I could swallow my pride
and try to patch things
up with the family,
but it really
wouldn't matter in the long
run because the Kannagis
won't be around much longer.
Ayano's not strong
enough to handle
the one behind the
killings, and dear
old dad is down for the count.
How can you be so cold?
This is your family
you're talking about.
It's in danger!
How can you not help your own‐‐
It's not my family anymore.
Yes it is!
Now let's get something
straight here, Ren.
I didn't abandon
the Kannagi family.
The Kannagi family abandoned me!
REN: But can't you‐‐
What, help them out after
the way they treated me?
Oh, yeah right.
I don't think so.
Hey, wait, Ren, I didn't
mean to make you cry.
I thought I could convince you
to straighten things out with
the family, but I couldn't.
You won't do it.
I failed!
First time I see my brother
in years, and I do this to him.
[CRYING]
Here, wipe your face.
And just stay here tonight.
I'll take you home
tomorrow sometime, OK?
You're the best!
[SIGH]
You never could stand to
see the kid sad, could you?
What are we going to do next?
Get some sleep.
No, it's too early!
Not yet!
I'm tired.
But we've got so
much catching up to do,
can't we talk just a
little bit more, please?
All right, but not
for too much longer, OK?
[PANTING]
You're so gonna pay for
what you've done, Kazuma!
Hmm.
Great.
Ren!
I'm awake.
What was that noise?
What happened?
Some idiot sliced this hotel
in half using wind magic.
[CRASH]
Damn.
Let's go!
Wh‐‐ what are you doing?
That's not the exit!
That's it.
You're in trouble now, Kazuma!
Enraiha, come forth!
[YELLING]
Why is she here?
Kazuma?
[EXPLOSION]
Hey, wait a minute.
This is so not good!
You're not gonna fight
me yourself, is that it?
You're just gonna drop
part of a building on me?
Fine, bring it on, you coward!
I'm the inheritor of Enraiha.
How dare you underestimate me!
[SCREAMING]
[CRASH]
Did the other wind
magic user do that?
Yeah, I barely saw it coming.
You're a wind magic user too,
couldn't you have done anything
to stop him back there?
Nope.
It's not like that.
Even if I wanted to, I can't
interfere with the guy's wind.
REN: What?
Hey, don't worry,
because now that I've
seen how this guy operates, I
know how to expect his attacks.
Move!
Get out of here, now!
[CRASH]
Well, well.
Thanks for your help
the other night.
We didn't get a chance
to meet face to face.
Your fight against
the Kannagi family
isn't any of my business,
and I had no intention
of getting in your way.
But you tried to hurt Ren, so
I'm making it my business now!
REN: Kazuma, help!
Ren!
There must be another one.
That wind kept me
from sensing him.
I know you.
Bastards.
They really pulled
one over on me.
Well, it won't happen again.
Just hang in there, Ren.
I promise I will get you back.
OK, that was rough.
Come out, Kazuma!
Jerk.
I can't believe he'd go this far
just to carry out his revenge.
I won't forgive you
for this, Kazuma.
Do you hear me?
Never!
AYANO: What?
Revenge for
something the Kannagi
family did over 300 years ago?
Yeah, right.
Ren wasn't born to
be eaten by a youma.
What do you mean I have
to work with Kazuma?
You can't be serious.
He makes me sick!
His little brother's
life is on the line
and all he's worried
about is getting paid.
Fine.
I guess I don't have much of
a choice in the matter, do I?
Let's go.
Next time, on Kaze no Stigma,
the head of the Kannagi family.
Wow, I've never seen Kazuma
look like that before.