MAN (VOICEOVER): Gonzo.
VOICES (VOICEOVER): Funimation.
You should be watching.
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): Eyes
as blue as the azure sky.
That is the symbol
of the Contractor,
entrusted by the
Spirit King of the Wind
with the powers of his domain.
I bear this mark.
The stigma of the wind.
[THEME MUSIC]
Now, take this!
It's‐‐ it's her.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on!
Ah!
This ends now!
Kazuma.
What's the matter with you?
Kazuma?
TSUI‐LING (VOICEOVER): Promise
you'll protect me forever.
I promise, Tsui‐Ling.
Tsui‐Ling?
No.
No more.
Come on, old friend.
What are you so upset about?
I don't see the problem.
You just got to reunite with
your dead lover, did you not?
Lover?
KAZUMA: Tsui‐Ling is
never coming back.
You and your people
took everything.
Her spirit and her body.
You made that demon eat away
every part of her being.
Tsui‐Ling doesn't exist anymore.
Of course, friend.
You should know that
I was there four years
ago when everything happened.
You what?
Lapis.
Come over here.
Of course, my master.
VESALIUS: When she died,
Tsui‐Ling left behind elements
of her thoughts and her spirit.
We simply picked up the pieces
and used what she left behind
in order to create Lapis.
No.
That's just an imitation.
Just an imitation?
I am surprised at you.
Are you really that cold
hearted, my old friend,
you would reject your
lover's exact replica?
The lover that you
couldn't even protect?
AYANO (VOICEOVER):
What does this mean?
That girl and Kazuma used to‐‐
No more games.
I've had enough.
Now it's time for you to die.
What the?
[LAUGHING] Looks
like I can call
it a day for now, doesn't it?
This isn't over, you hear me?
We're not gonna
let you get away.
And how do you
plan to stop me?
My work is already done here.
I've granted power
to countless people.
The same power I've
given to Lapis.
And she is an
unparalleled swordmaster.
Why don't you show our guests
exactly what you're capable of?
Of course, master.
AYANO: What is that?
Destroy it all.
Leave nothing.
Ayano.
I'm OK, Ren.
Kazuma!
Bernhardt!
We will meet again.
I assure you.
No!
Come back here!
Bernhardt!
UTSUMI: I don't understand.
Why did it turn out this way?
I didn't ask for this.
They picked me.
I guess it's because I'm
smarter than everyone else.
So Why?
Why?
It was all Nanase's fault.
I wish she never existed.
I wonder if everyone's gonna
rise up and retaliate now.
I don't want that to happen.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I'm completely innocent.
This whole thing
is Vesalius' fault.
He gave me the power without
me knowing the consequences.
So if I'm innocent,
why am I in jail?
He's the one they
should arrest, not me.
Ah!
KIRIKA: We're releasing
a doctored version
of this footage to the public to
try and keep things contained.
The official stance
of the department
is that this incident
was an explosion.
At any rate, what you
did was quite reckless.
Frankly, I'm surprised all
three of you managed to escape.
Kazuma got us out
of there just in time.
Yeah.
If it wasn't for him, we would
have really been in trouble.
So, I assume no one's
heard from my idiot son yet.
We can't find him.
He disappeared right
after he rescued us,
and we haven't heard
from him since then.
What a worthless punk.
To disappear right in
the middle of a crisis.
That's not true.
Easy now, Ren.
Ayano.
You must prepare
for the possibility
of facing this enemy again.
Understand?
Of course I do.
I'll be ready.
Sure, but Pandemonium
has already been destroyed,
hasn't it?
Maybe the enemy won't
make a move any time soon.
KIRIKA: They already have.
Huh?
Take a look at this film.
It was taken last night after
Pandemonium was destroyed.
AYANO: Is that blood?
REN: Congratulations.
You have just advanced
to the next level.
Now you will acquire even more
power by changing your class.
Wait, isn't this?
That's right.
See?
Look at the bottom.
We welcome you to Pandemonium.
Do you wish to‐‐
Don't tell me this means‐‐
Yes.
They've already surfaced.
There's a brand new Pandemonium.
So So that means
this bloody message
was sent from the new location.
But I don't get it.
What's with the hand print?
They got to pick Yes or No.
That hand print is
the choice he made.
Who is he?
I'm sorry, but it's Utsumi.
I don't understand.
I thought Utsumi was locked up.
Our people found the bloody
message in his isolation cell.
We think he escaped sometime
in the middle of the night.
We're not exactly sure
how he managed to do it,
but when they checked his cell
this morning, he was gone.
Do you realize how bad
you guys have screwed up?
And if he's out
there on the loose,
he'll go after Nanase first.
You have to send
someone to help her.
Don't worry about her.
It's under control.
Our people are on it.
AYANO: You'd better hope your
people know what they're doing.
If something happens
to her, I swear!
Now, calm down, Ayano.
How many messages
have been delivered?
Can we be sure?
Could it be only
Utsumi's received it?
No way.
It's reached others.
This information hasn't
been confirmed yet,
but it looks like at
least four or five
people changed their
classes between yesterday
and this morning.
It's safe to say
the enemy's activity
has entered a new phase.
It seems they've intensified,
wouldn't you agree?
Unfortunately, yes.
Do we have any idea
who's responsible?
The leader goes by
the name Vesalius.
However, based on what we
know, it's not his real name.
We saw him when we
were inside Pandemonium.
From what I can remember, Kazuma
called him something else.
That's right.
Kazuma was talking
to the guy like they
knew each other pretty well.
And like they had some
sort of history together.
I remember his
name was Bernhardt.
What did you say?
Is that true?
You're sure.
REN: I'm positive.
Then it's gotta
be Bernhardt Rhodes.
He's currently the council
chairman of Almagest.
Almagest?
You mean the order
of magical arts?
There's far more to
it than that, Ayano.
They've mainly been
active in Europe,
but worldwide, they're regarded
as the ultimate authority
on modern magic arts.
Their techniques
are unparalleled.
Do you think someone in
the position of authority
he's in would risk being
involved in this kind of thing?
I don't know.
I suppose someone could
be posing as Bernhardt.
I doubt it.
I'm certain it was him.
Really?
And what makes you so sure?
Almagest has held a grudge
against Kazuma for a long time
now.
And there's the girl, Tsui‐Ling,
who's the basis of Lapis.
She's definitely a major
factor in this whole thing.
Tsui‐Ling?
Wait just a minute.
You knew about that girl
and you didn't tell us?
That's right.
Did you ever think I
might like to know that?
Ayano, please.
What?
Look.
Everybody has certain
things they don't want
other people finding out about.
If it had been about you,
what would you want me to do?
Would you want me to
tell them to everybody?
Detective Tachibana.
I agree that it's
important to keep secrets,
but in this particular instance,
if this girl affects this case
in any way at all,
then we need to know
everything, immediately.
Detective, you
must level with us.
Course.
I understand.
Just know this information
is unconfirmed.
I can't guarantee
its credibility.
I can only tell you
what I heard, all right?
Mm.
They said it was
four years ago.
It happened before
he received his power
and became the Contractor.
BERNHARDT (VOICEOVER):
Just an imitation?
I'm surprised.
Are you really that cold
hearted, old friend,
you'd really reject
your lover's replica?
The lover that you
couldn't even protect?
Kazuma.
Kazuma, come on.
Wake up, sleepyhead.
Rise and shine.
Ugh.
Five more minutes.
Five more minutes, my foot.
If you don't get out of bed,
I'm not making you breakfast.
[GROAN] All right.
What a beautiful
morning, don't you think?
Yeah, it is.
But if you don't get a move
on, you'll miss it completely.
Hurry up and get dressed.
Well, yes, ma'am.
Oh, I forgot to
tell you something.
Good morning, Kazuma.
Yes, it is, here with you.
From the looks of
things, I think it's
gonna be another amazing day.
What do you think, mom?
[CAWING]
Come on, Junior.
Hurry up.
I'm not paying you a
thing until my little baby
is safe and sound.
Hey.
Here, kitty.
Come on.
Just give me a break.
[BORED MEOW]
[SCREECHING]
[HISSING]
You had to do it the hard way.
Ah!
My precious baby!
There, there.
You we're scared, weren't
you, my little angel?
Will that be cash or check?
What?
You're nuts I'm not paying you.
Uh.
You just broke my
sign, didn't you?
You're lucky I don't
make you pay me,
you reckless little punk.
But I saved him.
Hey.
You're back.
How was your day?
Long and uneventful.
No offense, buddy,
but you look like hell.
So what did you
do today, Kazuma.
I rescued a cat and it sucked.
Way to go.
You must be raking
in the big bucks now.
Yeah, well, when you're a
jack of all trades like me,
you take what you can get and
do it with a smile on your face.
TSUI‐LING: Kazuma.
Huh?
Stop fooling around
and get to work.
We've just got five more
tables, and we're out of ice.
I know.
That guy is so
whipped, it's pathetic.
Guess we know who's
wearing the pants, don't we?
Well, if I was getting
a piece of that action,
I do what I was told too.
Yeah.
Like when she tells
you to get out.
[LAUGHING]
Bottoms up, fellas.
You sure have
changed, haven't you?
Huh?
The Kazuma I used to
know was a hell raiser.
Drinking booze, fighting,
and picking up women.
But now, ever since
you met Tsui‐Ling
it's like you're a
completely different person.
Kazuma.
Stop slacking and get to work.
Oh, yes, dear.
[LAUGHING]
Take care of that girl.
You hear me?
Yeah.
Hey.
Look at that.
It's just like the
night we first met.
With that big full
moon, remember?
Of course I remember.
Kazuma.
What were you and your
friends talking about tonight
at the restaurant?
Uh, just about the old days.
What do you mean?
Have I ever told you
about my family back home?
Mm‐mm.
It's our tradition to make
one of the youngest members
with power the successor
of the family line,
but for whatever reason I
wasn't blessed with any power.
I was kicked out, so I came
here to get away from all that.
I tried to forget about
them and everything
that went down, but I couldn't.
No matter how much I tried, I
couldn't get it out of my head.
More than anything else in
the world, I wanted power.
Power I don't have and
probably never will.
Back in the old days, I was a
completely different person.
TSUI‐LING: Kazuma.
Hm?
TSUI‐LING: Tell me the truth.
Do you still want it?
You do, don't you?
Because if you have power,
you'll get to go home.
You could have a better life
than living in a filthy place
like this with me.
You don't get it.
What?
Why would you say that?
I just don't understand
you sometimes.
Ever since the moment
that I arrived here,
I swear, every day's
been like a dream to me,
because it doesn't
matter if I have power.
No matter what, you
see me for who I am.
I can't thank you
enough for that.
I treasure the life
we have together.
I don't care if it's
ordinary or small.
You're the greatest thing
that's ever happened to me,
and I've never been happier.
I wouldn't trade this for
all the power in the world.
[SOBBING] Kazuma.
Hm.
Please protect me.
Promise you'll
protect me forever.
Swear you'll always watch over
me, no matter what happens.
Yes.
I will.
I swear on my life,
I'll protect you.
No matter what, you'll never
have to be afraid again.
Forever and always, Tsui‐Ling.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING]
[LAUGHING]
AYANO (VOICEOVER): I heard
Kazuma say to Bernhardt, you
and your people took
everything from me.
So this girl named Tsui‐Ling.
I guess she must have
meant the world to him.
No way.
The reason he disappeared
all alone is because he‐‐
[SIRENS WAILING]
OFFICER (OVER RADIO):
Calling all available units.
A violent brawl has been
reported inside District Four.
I repeat, a violent
brawl has been
reported inside District Four.
Proceed with caution.
Over.
What in the hell
happened out here?
Looks like a tornado just
blew through this place.
It doesn't make sense.
[GROANING]
That's awful.
Go call an ambulance.
Right.
Just hang in there.
You're gonna be OK.
[WHIMPERING]
Are you all right, son?
Can you tell me
what happened here?
Ah!
I was just watching
during the class change.
The seat.
What are you talking about?
What changed?
And then he‐‐
then he‐‐ he‐‐
[HEAVY BREATHING]
Who?
Ah!
The wind.
BERNHARDT (VOICEOVER): Lapis.
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
Nothing at all, my master.
KAZUMA: You're a
dead man, Bernhardt.
I'm gonna kill you.
And while I'm at it, I'm gonna
kill that little imitation
doll of yours as well.
Now, spirits of the
wind, show me the way.
[THEME MUSIC]
AYANO (VOICEOVER): No.
He wouldn't do
something like that.
I know it.
Kazuma's a lot of things‐‐
selfish, violent,
arrogant‐‐ but he would
never do anything like that.
It's just not in his nature.
I swear to you, it wasn't him.
That's impossible.
If he's who I think he
is, there's just no way.
Next time on "Kaze no
Stigma," the raging wind mage.
I have to stop Kazuma.
I'm the only one.