ANNOUNCER: Gonzo.
Funimation.
You should be watching.
KAZUMA: Eyes as blue
as the azure sky.
That is the symbol
of the Contractor,
entrusted by the
Spirit King of the Wind
with the powers of his domain.
I bear this mark, the
stigma of the wind.
[MUSIC ‐ SAORI KIUJI, "BLAST OF
WIND"]
What the hell is that?
CATHERINE: You have nothing
to fear, common citizens.
I've exterminated the
ghastly beast for you.
It won't threaten
your city anymore.
There's no need to thank
me, but you may if you wish.
This heroic deed was just
another part of my training.
Now I'm even more
ready to defeat
the heir of the Kannagis.
[LAUGHING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
So they're just
taking out random youma?
It's obviously
a fire magic user.
We just have no idea who it is.
I don't exactly
understand the problem here.
The problem is that too
many people are seeing it.
Wait a minute.
They're doing it
right out in public?
We've been trying
our best to keep
the incidents suppressed, but‐‐
It's a mess.
I got it.
So?
Well, I bet you
could find them for us.
I had a funny feeling
you were going to say that.
Do you have any leads to go on?
We've got a few
eyewitness reports.
We know it's a blonde woman.
And she dresses like
she's got money.
Anything else?
She apparently lets a spirit
beast do all the dirty work.
Really?
Yeah, it looks like a
Greek statue with wings.
Kind of like that?
This is outrageous!
I clearly ordered a
sweet ginger peach tea
and you bring me a chamomile?
Sorry!
‐ Hey.
‐ Hm?
Oh, it's you.
Guess you haven't left yet.
What?
Don't tell me you
know her, Kazuma.
You're a member of
the McDonald family?
You're legendary
fire magic users.
I don't want to boast, but
we are the most prestigious
family in the United States.
What's with the
rogue exterminations?
I'm training to defeat
that unworthy maiden
and claim my rightful title.
Unworthy maiden?
She means Ayano.
She keeps on trying to
pick a fight with her.
Some junk about being the
most powerful magic user
and claiming
Enraiha for herself.
Are you serious?
[GIGGLING]
And what is so
funny about that?
Well, all of
it's pretty funny,
but mostly the stuff about
you trying to defeat her.
Urg.
That vulgar present doesn't
stand a chance against me.
I could destroy her in my sleep!
Yeah, in your dreams, maybe.
I'll admit you've
got some skill,
but you'd rather stroke your
own ego than actually train.
You should be strengthening your
spirit beast instead of wasting
time on some measly youma.
What!
How dare you!
I can't believe a
pathetic wind user
would speak to me that way.
I demand an apology!
Catherine, you can
demand all you want,
but it's a pretty well‐known
fact that this pathetic wind
user over here
doesn't even know how
to pronounce the word sorry.
Huh?
Well, if that's the
case, then I suppose
I'll just have to teach the
insolent fool how to apologize.
[SCREAMING]
MAN: That girl's on fire!
MAN: Let's get out of here!
Did you really have to
provoke her like that?
I guess not, but
she's your problem now.
Thanks for the help.
Let me know how it turns out.
Great.
You'll be sorry.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASP]
Hm?
Who are you?
That was impossible.
I'm just a pathetic wind
user that can't apologize.
Answer me seriously, damn it.
No ordinary wind user could've
defeated Metatron like that.
Are you saying
I'm extraordinary?
Nah.
Truth is, I'm just
better than you.
And save yourself
the embarrassment
of challenging Ayano.
You're not ready for her.
Are you saying that I'm
inferior to that little girl?
Not what I mean.
You're not, but your
fighting style is inferior.
CATHERINE: What?
You're putting too
much stock in Metatron
and trying to win the battle
with your first attack.
That, of course, leaves you
dumbfounded and helpless
once he's been defeated.
Just think about it.
We both know Ayano can stop
Metatron with a single flame.
And what have you got then?
It's just stupid to
rely on that thing.
You need another strategy.
CATHERINE (VOICEOVER):
He's got some nerve.
Who is he to point out
what I'm doing wrong,
even if he's right?
CATHERINE: I'm a
little surprised
you're telling me this.
I mean, I have declared
Ayano as my mortal enemy.
Oh, that's right.
We should talk about how
much this little lesson
is going to cost.
What do you mean?
Aren't you supposed
to be on Ayano's side?
KAZUMA: No.
She's just a business associate.
There's only one side
I really care about‐‐
whichever side is willing
to pay me the most money.
Seriously?
Is something wrong?
Well, if that's the case,
I'll double whatever she's
paying you to work for me.
Huh?
You saw him
walking with a girl?
YUKARI: Yeah, and she
was really pretty, too.
Oh, yeah?
What did she look like?
Like she was
perfect for Kazuma.
I can't even begin to describe
how good they looked together.
NANASE: Oh, that's
really awesome for him.
Right, Ayano?
YUKARI: Yeah, it's nice
he's met someone since you
don't like him or anything.
AYANO: Uh.
Yeah, sure.
Good for him.
I mean, it's not like I
really care, but yeah, great.
So I don't know about you,
but this is getting really sad.
I know.
This too good to stop.
KAZUMA: Yo.
Perfect timing.
Kazuma!
Come on.
Here it comes.
You got something
to say to me?
Here.
Huh?
I've been challenged to a duel?
This is from Catherine McDonald.
I thought she went
back to the States?
The duel's happening
a week from today.
What?
She'll leave, and you'll never
see her again if she loses.
Wait.
I bet that was the blonde woman
I saw Kazuma with earlier.
Don't tell me you've been
spending time with her!
Well, yeah.
I'm coaching her.
I've been training
her for the past week.
I thought you
were my bodyguard!
I never signed an
exclusive contract.
‐ Yeah, but‐‐
‐ Later.
Hey!
I'm still talking to you!
Well, I don't think
you have to worry.
It doesn't sound like
they started dating yet.
How many times do
I have to tell you?
I don't care.
I'd say you're
definitely improving.
Are you really surprised?
I guess it is tough
to improve perfection.
But do you really think
all of this training
will help me defeat Ayano?
You've got a better chance
than relying on Metatron.
The only strategy Ayano
has is to take out
her opponent in a single blow.
Sorry to compare you two, but
you're pretty damn similar.
If you have the same
technique, it all comes
down to the weapons you use.
A spirit beat can't
compete with Enraiha,
so you've got to switch
up your game plan if you
want to catch her off guard.
Well, I guess
that makes sense.
It totally goes
against my style,
but I'll do it if you
think it will help me win.
All right.
You can take it on
your own from here.
What?
I gave you your
homework, so get to it.
I'm going to go get
something to eat.
You can't just leave me
here while you go home.
Don't walk away from me!
[HEART BEATING]
You OK there?
Sorry.
I just wasn't looking.
CATHERINE (VOICEOVER): Why
was my heart beating so fast?
I can't be starting to‐‐
no, no, that's impossible.
He's just my coach
and that's all.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I understand that
someone else has
stepped up to challenge Ayano.
Yeah, I heard
something about that.
And she's from a
well‐known American
family of fire magic users.
So she's Ayano's direct enemy?
More or less.
But I think Ayano could
benefit from a different type
of competition.
What?
Perhaps, if this girl were
to challenge her true feelings,
Ayano would be a little nicer
to Kazuma before it's too late.
Right.
Stupid Kazuma!
I hate you!
Do you hear me?
You make me sick!
[WHINING]
AYANO (VOICEOVER): Idiot.
AYANO: [SHOVELING FOOD]
I don't know why, but
I am in the worst mood.
Ayano, um, don't you have that
duel with Catherine tomorrow?
Yeah.
Should you be
pigging out on cake?
Whatever.
That's the last thing
I'm worried about.
I could wipe out
her stupid spirit
beast with my eyes closed.
KAZUMA: I don't really
see why you need me here.
CATHERINE: Because it's
embarrassing to eat alone.
Oh, hi.
Well, well, well.
If it is my mortal enemy.
Isn't it a pleasant
surprise to see you here?
I hope you're prepared
for our duel tomorrow.
I wouldn't want it
to end too quickly.
Our last battle might
have been a draw,
but with the wonderful
training Kazuma has‐‐
Give me a break.
Is this part of
your coaching now,
taking her out to a
restaurant to eat pastries?
Of course not.
She just dragged me here
because she wanted to celebrate
the end of her training.
Kazuma's such a
fantastic coach.
I might hire him for
a full‐time position.
I wasn't talking
to you, so butt out!
Oh, please.
You're acting obnoxious.
What!
Are you kidding?
You're the obnoxious one.
CATHERINE: You're so childish.
AYANO: You want
to say that again?
Is it me or is Catherine
acting really territorial?
Do you think she likes Kazuma?
[BOOM]
AYANO: That's it!
I'm ready to settle
this thing now!
Fine, let's see
what you've got.
Yeah!
Fight!
Do it!
Hey, whoa.
Save it.
The duel's tomorrow.
Haven't you two destroyed
enough buildings?
Hm.
I hope you enjoy today, because
it's going to be your last.
Well, aren't you confident.
I know.
Let's make this interesting.
If I win the duel
tomorrow, then Kazuma
returns to America with me.
Huh?
AYANO: W‐‐ wait.
That wasn't part of the deal.
Wow.
I just came to the realization
that I can't stand the idea
of leaving Kazuma with you.
But what if he
doesn't want to go away?
Don't stand there
and take this, Ayano.
Just tell her Kazuma is yours.
Shut up!
You do know what I cost?
I would appreciate
it if you didn't
underestimate the immense
wealth of my family.
Well, if you're
willing to shell out
the cash then why the hell not?
I'll go to America.
AYANO: I understand!
Fine!
Do whatever you want.
No.
Wait, Ayano.
Hold on!
Well, you've
really done it now.
Tomorrow won't be easy.
She gets pretty extreme
when she snapped.
I couldn't care less.
Besides, I wasn't just trying to
make her angry by saying that.
Huh?
Uh, nothing.
Never mind.
My point is, no
matter what happens,
I promise nothing will stop me
from defeating her tomorrow.
Hm.
AYANO: I've made a decision.
Huh?
I won't let her
take him to America.
You what?
I'll make Kazuma
stay here with me.
Ayano‐‐
AYANO: There's no
way I'm going to let
that jerk get out of paying
for my meals so easily.
Uh.
Huh?
From now on, it's
breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
Italian, Chinese, or French.
Anything that I want to eat.
He's going to spend every
last penny he makes on me.
[SIGH] Is she ever going to
find out what she really wants?
At least she realized
she wants something.
I promise you I will win.
I'll win just so I can
ruin Kazuma's life.
You're going to pay,
Kazuma, for all my meals!
Take her down, Ayano!
You can do it!
OK.
Are you two ready?
CATHERINE: Of course I'm ready.
AYANO: Not as ready as I am.
Begin.
Enraiha, come forth!
I summon you, my spirit
guardian, Metatron!
You're really going to use
that thing again after what
happened the last time?
And why not?
Then let's go.
Kannagi flame!
She did it!
You're awesome, Ayano!
The flame of purification.
No real surprise there.
That all you got?
I hope you didn't spend too
much money on Kazuma's training.
You lose!
Ayano!
AYANO: What are those things?
They're called wisps.
What?
So are they supposed to be your
new spirit beasts or something?
They don't look quite as
impressive as your other one.
I'm not the person you
should be telling that to.
They might look measly, but
the wisps are part of Kazuma's
strategy to defeat you.
Let's start the real
battle now, shall we?
No, she's losing.
Hey, Ayano, you have
to counterattack!
Don't think so.
The only way she
knows how to fight
is to take out her
opponent with one blow.
She's completely clueless
dealing with multiple targets.
You might even say
it's her Achilles heel.
Did you tell Catherine that?
Did you set up Ayano?
Of course I did.
So?
I'm her coach.
That's terrible.
You jerk.
Well, Ayano might end
up getting her ass kicked,
but at least she'll
learn something from it.
She might even realize
what her weakness is.
NANASE: Ayano!
YUKARI: Is she all right?
This looks to be
the end of our battle,
so feel free to admit
your defeat at any time.
Who said it's over?
You are stubborn, aren't you?
Well, that makes my victory
that much more enjoyable.
Oh, I can't wait to start
my new life with Kazuma.
I have a feeling he's just
going to love America.
The first thing
I'll do, of course,
is bring him to our estate
and introduce him to Daddy.
And afterwards, I'll throw
an extravagant welcome party
for him.
I'm certain we'll be as
happy as humanly possible
with each other.
We'll have such a
wonderful life together.
[LAUGHING]
Take it easy, Catherine.
I wouldn't push her too far.
It's not going to happen.
He's staying here.
I'm not going to let
you take him anywhere.
Are you too stupid to
realize when to quit?
I'm obviously the winner.
She's OK!
About time she started
acting like herself.
That's the real Ayano.
Try all you want, but I
won't let you take Kazuma.
AYANO (VOICEOVER): Don't
focus on just one thing.
She figured it out.
Catherine's in for it now.
[YELLING]
My wisps!
Wait!
How did you do that?
Before I pay you back
for all you've done,
remember this was your idea.
No.
No, you can't!
Yeah?
Watch me!
[SCREAMING]
She won!
I knew she could do it!
[GROANING]
I did it.
It's finally over.
CATHERINE: [LAUGHING]
Oh, come on.
You've got to be kidding.
I gladly admit defeat.
What?
To be honest, I
never thought you
would have come back like that.
But you proved me wrong.
That was an incredible fight.
Yeah, thanks.
And you're not half bad, either.
I got to admit, it was
a pretty decent fight.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hm.
[GIGGLING]
Catherine could have won if
she hadn't let her guard down.
She just got a little too
cocky there at the end.
That's all.
So Kazuma, you just
wanted to teach Ayano?
Is that what this
was really about?
Hey, the only thing I
did was coach Catherine.
I can't help it if
Ayano learned something.
So in a backwards
way, I guess you
can say I was Ayano's coach.
Yeah, you're not very honest
with yourself, either, are you?
Kazuma!
Listen up.
You better have cash because
you're buying me dinner.
I'm doing what?
I won the duel, so you owe me.
French, Italian, Chinese food.
I want it all, and
you're buying it for me.
All right.
That's enough.
Enough what?
Your behavior is
absolutely atrocious.
You shouldn't speak that way.
Now, tell him that you're sorry.
Hey!
Who said it was any
of your business?
He's not going back
to America with you.
I remember the
terms of the duel,
and I promise that I won't take
him back to America with me.
But I never once said I was
going to leave him alone.
Ah‐‐
Nobody can make me leave.
I have every right to
remain in this country.
You are such a liar!
You said you would
leave if I won.
Well, it's your
word against mine.
So when do we start
training, Kazuma?
I can't believe this.
You just admitted your defeat!
Well, yes, but that was
an entirely different thing.
Was not!
[UNCOMFORTABLE LAUGHING]
Fight's over.
OK?
Here they go.
Because it ended!
You can't do that!
Oh?
You heard me.
Then we'll have another
match right now!
CATHERINE: Fine.
Bring it on!
I'd be glad to teach
you some manners.
You can't just order a man
to buy you food like that.
AYANO: Oh, yeah?
Says who?
CATHERINE: Says me!
Let's go, Kazuma.
[MUSIC ‐ AYUMI FUJIMURA,
"MATATAKI NO KIWOKU"]
AYANO: All right!
This is amazing!
I can't believe you won a
free trip to the hot springs
from a quiz show.
You're so lucky, Yukari.
What?
Kazuma and Catherine were
taking a bath together?
And what's Kazuma's
father doing here?
I thought they didn't get along.
They got into a fistfight
with each other?
Oh, great.
What should I do?
Next time on "Kaze No
Stigma," "Father and Son".
I don't care if you did
take a bath with him.
Don't talk to me like that.