MAN: Gonzo.
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): Eyes
as blue as the azure sky.
That is the symbol
of the Contractor.
Entrusted by the
Spirit King of the Wind
with the powers of his
domain, I bear this mark,
the stigma of the wind.
[THEME ‐ SAORI KIUJI, "BLAST OF
WIND"]
[DOG BARKING]
[PANTING]
I can't believe how late it is.
Our new class president sure
likes to hear herself talk.
There it is, the demon tree.
Nah, come on.
It's just an old
dead cherry tree.
[GASP]
Yeah, OK.
Now I'm just imagining things.
Right?
[SPOOKY MOANING]
GHOSTLY VOICE: Go away.
Go away.
GIRL: [SCREAM]
AYANO: They're seeing ghosts?
Yes, almost every
evening at Seiryo Academy.
Apparently, several
of your classmates
have had quite a scare.
Are you sure?
If there were ghosts, it
seems like I'd have sensed
some kind of evil presence.
No, not necessarily.
You would only sense
something if the apparition
intended harm, you see?
Yeah, I guess, even if
it's a friendly spirit,
most people still would probably
freak out if they saw it.
True.
The academy director personally
asked the Kannagi family
to find out what's happening.
Given that it's your school
and you know it best,
I thought you might like to
handle this case yourself.
Sure, no problem.
I'm heading back
up there right now.
They should be ghost‐free
by tomorrow morning.
JUGO: Wait just a moment.
You can never be
too careful, even
on such a seemingly easy case.
Therefore, as of today,
I've taken the liberty
of assigning you a bodyguard.
Bodyguard?
But why?
I never needed any
protection before.
As the future
head of the family,
your safety is important.
We can't afford to
take any chances.
Yeah, OK, I understand.
But with all due
respect, someone
from one of the
branch families would
probably just get in my way.
I assure you that
won't be a problem.
Huh?
K‐‐ Kazuma?
Ayano.
What are you doing?
We're kind of in the middle
of an important meeting here,
you know?
Well, someone's
a little edgy, huh?
Look, don't worry.
If we get out there and it's
too much for you to handle,
I'll step in and save you.
You'll what?
You're joking, right?
He is my bodyguard?
Yep.
Come on.
Now, let's get moving, partner.
‐ [GROWL]
Forget it!
There's no way!
Very well, Ayano.
You may stay here,
and I will send
Kazuma out with someone from
the special investigations unit.
Can you believe it?
The future head of
the Kannagi family
turning her back
on her own school.
Someone having a little
performance anxiety?
Well, I suppose it's up to
us to show her how it's done.
I agree.
[CHUCKLE]
Just kidding!
I'd be happy to do it!
This is my school
we're talking about.
I wouldn't dare trust a
job like this to outsiders.
Good.
Let's go then.
You know?
Uh‐‐ uh‐‐
I'm counting on you.
AYANO: Hey!
Who's in charge here?
Let me go!
[SLAM]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
So how did this happen anyway?
Beats me.
I mean, why would you even
consider a job like this?
It's not your style at all.
Yeah, but the
money is incredible.
Huh?
Let's just say your father
is extremely generous.
I'd be a fool to turn it down.
I still don't sense
anything out of the ordinary.
Are you sensing anything
strange right now?
Let's get this straight.
I'm just here as your bodyguard.
I've got my own job to do.
This whole paranormal
investigation thing
is your deal.
Yeah, I know that.
But I‐‐
[RUSTLING]
[GASP]
Hey, over there!
Um, what do you
think you're doing?
Take a look.
Oh, uh, hi there, Ayano.
Hi, Kazuma.
Yeah, what's up, guys?
Yukari?
Nanase?
So what are you guys
doing up here this late?
YUKARI: Uh, waiting.
It's not every day a girl
gets a chance to see a ghost.
And besides, as a member
of the student council,
I feel a personal
obligation to investigate
these kinds of situations.
Never mind that.
I want to know how you knew
about the ghost sighting
and where your
information came from.
It was supposed to be
strictly confidential.
Yukari's pretty good
at staying informed.
Juicy school gossip, secrets
scandals‐‐ you name it.
She's got all the dirt.
Oh, stop it.
Even I wouldn't
know little details,
like most of the sightings
occurred after 7:00 PM
or that the only related injury
was when Mr. Ohara got scared
and fell and then
tried to run away.
I also wouldn't know
anything about all
the gossip magazines
the principal hides
in his desk drawer.
That kind of information's
impossible to get.
You have got to be kidding me.
What do you do?
Set up a bug in his office?
A reporter never
reveals her sources.
[SIGH]
Anyway, you guys
should go home now.
What?
I can't just walk
away from a shot
at actually seeing a ghost.
Me either.
Yeah, but listen.
There's no way to
know how dangerous
it could get in there.
We're not scared.
No matter what it is, I'm
sure you can handle it.
I mean, we both have the
utmost confidence in you.
And if it turns
out you can't do it,
I know we can always count
on Kazuma to save the day.
[GASP]
Hmm.
I was only hired to
protect you, Ayano.
So I won't be
babysitting anyone else.
If they're coming with us,
their safety is your problem.
Got it?
You're the most
self‐centered‐‐
Heh‐heh, come on, Ayano.
I think it's sweet.
He's saying he's totally
devoted to protecting you.
Yukari.
NANASE: It's all right.
If our being here is messing up
your romantic date or whatever,
just tell us, and
we'll be on our way.
Nanase, I so thought
you were better than that.
Hey, are they coming or not?
You girls would argue
all night if I let you.
[GROWL]
Fine.
But you better do
exactly as I tell you to.
And don't go wandering
off on your own.
TOGETHER: Promise!
[BUGLE PLAYING]
Attention, please.
Announcing the first
meeting of Seiryo
Academy's Paranormal
Investigation
and Eradication Club.
[GROAN]
[DRIPPING]
AYANO: I still haven't sensed
anything out of the ordinary.
This was probably
just a stupid mistake.
YUKARI: What?
No way.
This school's gotta be haunted.
How else do you explain
all the weird things
that happened here, like the
seven wonders of Seiryo High.
AYANO: Seriously.
Come on, you are kidding, right?
NANASE: [CHUCKLE]
OK then.
Let's hear them.
Well, let me see.
I guess the classics are
the faucets in the bathroom,
the music room's piano playing
itself when no one's around,
the staircase that lengthens
under a full moon‐‐
NANASE: I'm not sure
I'd call those classics.
‐‐the scary mannequin
that moves at midnight,
the ghost of the dropout student
in the library, and the legend
of the demon tree.
What are you talking about?
YUKARI: You know, the
ugly, old cherry tree
in the back of the schoolyard.
It hasn't bloomed in years,
but it still keeps growing.
I know a lot of students
who swear they've heard
whispers coming from that tree.
I'd be willing to bet all
they really heard was the wind
blowing through the branches.
All right, so let's
hear number seven then.
Well, actually,
there are only six.
"Seven wonders" just
had a nicer ring to it.
That lame ending is
the most classic of all.
Not even one of those
sounded believable to me.
Not that it really matters,
because if there was any kind
of ghostly presence
around here, Mr. Stoic
would have reacted by now.
[WHOOSHING]
[GIRLS SCREAM]
Kazuma!
That wasn't me.
Did you see it?
Not a thing.
That's enough.
Start talking!
[GASP]
Ha.
What was that?
Did you see where it went?
I don't know.
Wow, thanks again
for all your help.
I knew it.
There really is a ghost.
I only wish I had my camera
ready when it flew by us.
At that speed, you'd be
lucky if you got anything more
than a blurred flash of light.
[SIGH]
[BUGLE PLAYING]
Come back, Mr. Ghost.
Nothing to be afraid of.
If you come out, I promise that
I'll only shoot your good side.
Sensing anything from
what happened earlier?
Nope, nothing.
But how is that possible?
I mean, this cannot
be the one thing that
your senses don't pick up on.
You have a point.
I knew it.
You are hiding
something from me.
Maybe I am, and maybe I'm not.
Why?
Because you can't
figure me out and you're
just dying to know more?
Don't dodge the question!
I'm not kidding around!
Now, tell me what
you know, mister.
YUKARI: [GASP]
Oh, my.
There it is.
Aah!
Hey!
What'd you do that for?
No reason.
It just seemed like the quickest
way to get you to let go of me.
You‐‐ you idiot!
Oh, and by the way‐‐
Now what?
Turn around.
Unh!
Agh!
[MOAN]
I got to be honest with you.
I think that's the least
graceful thing I've ever seen.
Well, that's just Ayano.
She's always been that way.
You know, that's more
believable than all
of your other stories combined.
Yeah, right.
GHOSTLY VOICE: Go away.
Go away.
You've been warned.
Don't come closer.
Or next time, you will suffer.
All right, I've heard just
about enough out of you!
Ugh!
GHOSTLY VOICE: Ow!
You'll pay for that.
Follow me.
Easy.
[GASP]
Fire!
Aah!
[WHOOSH]
[GROWL]
Kazuma, why didn't
you let me go?
OK, let's think about this.
The first thing it said to
us was, "Go away," right?
My guess is it's up to something
it doesn't want us to see.
So instead of cornering
and killing it,
why not be patient and have it
lead us to what it's hiding?
Hmm?
You just made all that up.
I know you did.
And why would I do that?
Do I really look like
I'm lying right now?
It's true.
I don't want to hear it.
You know where that thing
is headed, don't you?
Sort of, yeah.
Shall we go?
[BOTH GIGGLE]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
So Ayano and Kazuma are
officially on a mission
together?
That's right.
They're investigating a
situation at her school
and probably right in
the thick of it now.
Sounds pretty exciting.
I would have been more than
happy to go along with them
and help out any way I could
if you had wanted me to.
But doing that would
defeat the purpose.
Tell me, Ren.
You've been around the
two of them enough.
What do you think of them?
What do I think?
Well, honestly, I think if
they could just figure out
a way to get along
a little better,
they'd make a much better team.
As it stands now,
it seems they're
attacking each other
more than anyone else.
Yes, I see.
GHOSTLY VOICE: Go away.
Go away.
[WIND BLASTING]
[GIRLS SCREAMING]
Wha‐‐ what's going on?
[GRUNTING]
Stop right there!
Yeah, I wouldn't do
that if I were you.
[PANTING]
[GASP]
[MUFFLED YELLING]
TOGETHER: No!
AYANO: [MUFFLED SCREAM]
[TUMBLING]
[CRASH]
Ayano?
Are you alive down there?
I'm fine, but
that thing must die.
Wow, nothing but a couple
of bruises here and there.
I know.
She's even tougher
than she looks.
But I don't feel any better.
You've got to swear
to me you aren't
the one responsible for this.
You can believe
whatever you like.
If you want to dismiss
all the evidence
staring you in the face and
blame me, go right ahead.
[GRUMBLE]
TOGETHER: [EXCLAIMING]
[CRASH]
[PAINED GROANS]
GHOSTLY VOICE: Get out now.
[SIGH]
[DOOR SLIDING]
GHOSTLY VOICE: Leave this place.
TOGETHER: [SCREAMING]
[SIGH]
That thing sure is having
a field day with us.
I can't wait to see
what it tries to do next.
I don't understand
what's happening at all.
And there's really
no point in trying.
It's impossible to know
what they're thinking.
So don't worry about it.
And that's all the information
you're willing to give us?
It's not like I'm trying
to hide something from you.
I'm just not certain
of anything either.
And sharing my opinion
isn't going to help us.
You're lying.
I'm telling the truth.
Just trust me.
Remember, it is my sworn
duty to protect you.
Uh.
Stop dodging the question.
I know exactly
what you're doing.
Why can't you just believe me?
Oh, look at that.
I think they just
shared a moment.
I'm glad you got your chance
to play boyfriend‐girlfriend,
but we are sort of being
stalked by an angry ghost here.
What?
No, it's not like that.
Aw, it's OK.
We totally understand.
Yeah, who wouldn't
fall for him?
He's cool.
Are you two even
listening to me?
Kazuma, don't just stand there.
Say something.
The schoolyard.
The winds are
beginning to shift‐‐
all the winds on the property
and the terrestrial auras.
They're gathering
in the backyard.
AYANO: Why couldn't
you sense that earlier?
KAZUMA: Because those forces
are completely natural,
native to the space they occupy.
They're not like a youma
or an angry ghost that
disrupts the natural order.
Their presence is
constant, so it's
easy to ignore, sort of like
tuning out background noise.
AYANO: I guess that explains
why I didn't notice it.
[CLICK]
Now, there's one
for the yearbook.
I know.
I can honestly say I had no idea
this would be so entertaining.
GHOSTLY VOICE: Ha
ha ha ha ha ha ha!
When will you foolish
mortals ever learn?
[CACKLING]
[GROWL]
Agh!
Argh.
[SHOUT]
[GRUNTING]
GHOSTLY VOICE: No!
GHOSTLY VOICE: Whoa‐oh!
AYANO: Die!
[GRUNT]
Die!
You think we should
probably do something?
If we don't, I'm
sure the cops will.
Come back here!
What's wrong with
this stupid sword?
Get a hold of yourself.
It's not fair!
Stop crying.
Don't let a little teasing
get to you like that.
Sure, that's easy
for you to say.
You don't know how
humiliating it is to have
a bucket dropped on your head!
[WAILING]
True, I never want
to let that happen.
All right, you've manage
to upset the princess.
Game's over.
Come down and
introduce yourself.
GHOSTLY VOICE: [LAUGHING]
Never!
Ha ha ha!
[BLAST]
[WHOOSH]
[WARBLING]
[SOFT MOAN]
TOGETHER: Wow, it's a fairy.
She's a special type
of fairy called a pixie.
They're related to
wind spirits in a way.
But mostly, they're a bunch
of annoying little bugs.
Huh?
[GIGGLE]
Hello, I'm Tiana.
Quiet.
Why have you been
torturing people?
I was trying to get all
of you ridiculous humans
to stay far away from it.
You do realize
that this building
was built for humans to use?
Yeah, that's not really
my problem, you know?
It is now!
Calm down.
But why?
Maybe it's because you're
acting like a spoiled brat.
I could be wrong here,
but I think you're letting
this thing bother you too much.
[SIGH]
I can't believe it.
They have so much in common.
Yeah, take their
emotional maturity.
I mean, it's like they're
exactly the same age.
That's right.
They're five.
TOGETHER: Humph!
I am not as immature as she is!
Shut your mouth and
stop interrupting!
[LAUGHTER]
TOGETHER: Quit laughing!
Grr.
Hmph.
Humph.
Hey, don't get upset.
I'll make it up to you
over dinner sometime, OK?
Ooh, did you hear that?
Your next date with
Kazuma's in public.
It's not like that.
It sure is.
I just said it's not!
Look, don't think for a
second that you could take me
to some cheesy fast food joint.
It'd better cost at
least half as much money
as you made on this job.
Are we crystal clear?
No problem.
Whatever makes you feel better.
Now, why don't you
go ahead and tell
us what all the fuss was about?
It's an old man's
dying request.
We're gonna make his last
wish come true tonight.
TOGETHER: An old man?
The demon tree.
OK.
So I guess people really
were hearing whispers
and they were made by
the pixies all along.
All right, everyone.
It's time!
[WARBLING]
[WIND WHISTLING]
See ya!
AYANO: Wow, that was
pretty unbelievable.
I'll never be able to look
at the old tree the same way
again.
And even though it has
been a disaster, to find out
they were protecting
something so beautiful sort of
makes it all OK.
Hmm.
What now?
Nothing.
Hey, don't you "nothing" me.
Say it.
The best way to
protect something
is to keep it totally hidden.
And no one's going to search
for it if they don't know
it exists in the first place.
The pixies were causing trouble.
That was the only reason we
came here to investigate,
meaning what they were
really doing was anything
but protecting that
old cherry tree.
Hold on.
Are you trying to tell us
that the pixies aren't smart?
KAZUMA: Actually, it's
just the opposite.
They're pretty clever
when they want to be.
Why did they do it?
Pixies are
relatively innocent,
but they do enjoy
getting into trouble.
The truth is they were
just having a little fun
by doing what they do best‐‐
messing with you.
[GROWL]
Those annoying, little bugs!
I know you're still around here!
You can't hide from me forever!
So Kazuma, you really knew
what the pixies were up to all
along, right?
But you just
kept it to yourself
because you were
having way too much
fun watching Ayano go crazy.
TOGETHER: Naughty, naughty.
AYANO: Grr!
Show yourselves, you
miserable, little menaces!
I'm gonna show you what happens
when you play with fire!
AYANO (VOICEOVER): [SIGH]
I never knew until
this exact moment
how absolutely incredible a
meal can taste when someone
else is playing the bill.
Ren, a thief?
Possible.
Someone's obviously
making up lies.
There's no way.
Tsuwabuki?
As in the Tsuwabuki clan?
As in the most powerful
family of earth
magic users in the world?
Next time on "Kaze no Stigma,"
"Meeting Under the Moon."
And you, could you try dressing
like a decent human for once?