MAN: Gonzo.
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): Eyes
as blue as the azure sky.
That is the symbol
of the Contractor.
Entrusted by the
Spirit King of the Wind
with the powers of his
domain, I bear this mark,
the stigma of the wind.
[THEME ‐ SAORI KIUJI, "BLAST OF
WIND"]
[CHATTER]
AYANO (VOICEOVER): He's late.
How could he do this?
That idiot probably
doesn't even own a watch.
Is something wrong, Ayano?
You look kind of mad.
What?
No, no, nothing's wrong.
Are you kidding me?
MISAO: We have a visitor.
Well, it's about time.
There you are, Kazuma.
Come in.
Please sit down.
Guess I'm kind of late, huh?
No.
We're very happy that
you've decided to join us.
As you know, this young man is
Kazuma Yagami, who we must all
thank for his
invaluable assistance
in dealing with the Fuga clan.
Invaluable nothing.
We had to play him.
Uh‐‐
Hey, Kazuma!
[CHUCKLE]
I'm so happy you're
finally here.
[GRUMBLE]
Do you want anything to drink?
I didn't come here
because I'm thirsty.
You're going to eat
with us, though, right?
I didn't come here
for food either.
Huh?
You're acting
like a real jerk.
Is that what you came here for?
You're blocking my view.
Aren't you‐‐
I know you.
Masayuki's daughter, right?
Yes, that's right,
and Takeya's sister.
To show my appreciation, I
will attend to your every need.
So feel free to ask
me for anything.
Ask you for anything, huh?
I'll do anything you want.
Back off, you pervert!
Ugh!
No way!
I won't let you touch her.
So you're just gonna have
to find someone else.
What's wrong with you, Misao?
Have a little self‐respect.
Don't degrade yourself for a
worthless scumbag like him.
Nice to hear you have such a
high opinion of me, princess.
Thank you, but you
really don't have to be
so protective of me, Ayano.
I'm offering myself to Kazuma
to thank him for putting an end
to the Fuga clan's uprising.
We wouldn't be alive today
if it weren't for him.
And he took revenge for
the death of my brother.
I'm willing to do anything
to repay him for that.
He's already been
paid with money.
So believe me, he's just fine.
A simple thank‐you
would be good enough.
You shouldn't thank me.
Doesn't really make much sense.
I mean, what do you
have to be grateful for?
After all, I'm responsible
for your brother's death.
What did you say?
Ryuya killed him,
but I definitely
made it easier to do.
If I hadn't knocked
Takeya unconscious,
then Ryuya might not
have been able to pick
him off so quickly.
Of course, even when
he was conscious,
he was no match for Ryuya.
Anyway, I understand if
you want to blame me.
So you can go ahead
and use the blade
you got hidden in your sleeve.
[GASP]
[SHOUTING]
No.
Kazuma.
Are you all right?
Say something.
You feel better now?
Father, this would probably
be a good time for you
to step in and do something.
Kazuma.
If you're unwilling
to punish Misao,
then it becomes necessary for us
to take the appropriate action.
Masayuki, I ask you as her
father, do you approve?
Yes.
As a member of the
Kannagi family,
Misao will accept full
responsibility for this,
as I'm sure she's prepared to.
KAZUMA: Don't you think you're
all kind of overreacting?
It's not like she killed me.
She couldn't hurt
me if she tried.
Then if you do not
wish to punish her,
we will respect your decision.
However, we cannot permit
such inexcusable behavior.
And therefore, I'm
afraid we will have
to suspend Misao for a time.
It's not fair!
It should have been you.
Why did this have to happen?
Why did my brother have to die?
KAZUMA: Because he was weak.
Kazuma.
If that was supposed
to be some kind of joke,
then you've got a really
sick sense of humor.
How could you say
something so disrespectful?
Have you already forgotten
how weak you were
and what it felt like
before you discovered
how to use wind magic?
Are you done?
Because I am.
[QUIET WHIMPER]
[CAR HONKS]
YUKARI: Wow, look at her face.
And she's not even
joking around with us.
She's definitely in a rare
mood today, isn't she?
I know, and she didn't
waste any time on that guy who
tried to talk to us earlier.
‐ [GRUNT]
[GROAN]
Hey, are you talking about me?
Fess up, Ayano.
There's something going
on between you and a guy,
am I right?
Whoa.
What?
Where did that come from?
That doesn't make
any sense, you guys.
Oh, wow, so it's true?
No, that's not it at all.
It's no big deal.
You can tell us the truth.
So what's he like?
Is he cute?
Dude, enough!
Oh, come on.
Just give up.
There's no way Yukari's
going to let you off the hook
until you come clean with us.
She's right.
I already told
you, there's no guy!
Well, what a surprise.
Ayano making a scene again.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Wait, you know him?
You think he's the one?
You know, this might not
be the best place to be
drawing attention to yourself.
[GASP]
Oh, I guess I didn't
realize this place is‐‐
So Kazuma, is she one
of your little girlfriends
or something?
[GROAN]
No, Kirika, she's more
like the exact opposite.
She's just a distant
relative of mine.
Oh, is that so?
Then why is she so angry?
Don't know.
Think she was just
born that way.
What did you just say?
Ayano, you kids really
shouldn't be hanging
out in this neighborhood.
[CHUCKLE]
[GROWL]
Guess if I fell in love with a
guy like that, I'd be confused.
Yeah, right.
I totally don't get it.
He seems like the kind of
guy she normally hates.
Ugh!
That's it!
Tell me what you two are
whispering about now.
We're talking about
your new boyfriend, duh.
Though it looks
like you two haven't
started dating exclusively.
Will you please shut up?
How could I possibly
date that jerk?
I hate him more than anybody
I've ever met in my life!
Argh!
‐ Really?
Then what's with
the jealous fit?
What?
Well, uh, that's because I‐‐
I don't like him.
Now get off my back already!
[CHUCKLE]
Oh, yeah.
You know what?
I just realized
I've got this thing
I've got to do somewhere else.
I should really get going.
OK, bye!
[SIGH]
Talk about dodging
the question.
Yup, fleeing the scene.
But yeah, I think
you're exactly right.
She was totally acting
jealous, wasn't she?
Crazy thing is I don't think
she even realizes it herself.
How is that possible?
She'd have to be pretty
out of touch with reality
not to notice a thing like that.
We are talking about Ayano.
Then I've got a sneaking
suspicion that this is only
going to get more interesting.
You might just be right.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
AYANO (VOICEOVER): I
can't believe them.
Where would they get the
idea that I liked him anyway?
I don't even understand how
someone could like that guy.
I was just angry because
he was being a jerk.
What was he doing in
that kind of neighborhood
in the first place?
And who the heck was
that girl he was with?
Why were they walking
so close together?
[GASP]
And what were they
doing in that hotel?
Were they‐‐
[WHIMPER]
about to‐‐
That scumbag!
Where the heck did he go?
Oh, hey.
How's it going, Ayano?
What are you up to?
I need you to meet me now.
Why?
Just get over
here and help me!
(PANTING) Can't we
please take a break?
There's no way we're going to
find him in a busy neighborhood
like this.
We don't have tracking skills
on wind magic users too.
Sounds like the only skill
you have is whining, Ren.
Now that I think about
it, instead of dragging me
all over town to find
Kazuma, why didn't you just
call him on his cell phone?
Why would I even have
that guy's cell number?
And besides, I don't
want to talk to him.
Ayano, can we please rest
for just a little while?
I'm begging you, please.
I'm so thirs‐‐
AYANO: Oh, walk it off.
We don't have time to rest.
REN: Um‐‐
Huh?
I think I just found him.
Aah!
So, um, why are we
hiding behind a tree?
We just spent an
hour looking for him.
Don't worry about it.
Doesn't look like
he's with anyone.
Why?
Was he with somebody
else earlier?
Uh, no, I was just making
an observation, that's all.
REN: Although it
does kind of look
like he's waiting for somebody.
AYANO (VOICEOVER): Who
could he be waiting for?
REN: Here she comes.
[GASP]
[SAD SIGH]
Wow, she's kinda pretty.
Is that‐‐
Wait, that's Misao.
Yep, that's definitely her.
Do you think they're on a date?
[GROWLING]
Ayano, are you OK?
Let's go!
[GROAN]
Don't you think we're a
little close right now?
They're going to see us.
AYANO: Will you stop grumbling?
REN: They're
obviously on a date.
Now, can we please
stop stalking them?
This is getting creepy.
We're not stalking them.
We're just secretly
following them.
[SIGH]
Something wrong, Kazuma?
You seem kinda distant.
Oh, no.
Everything's just fine.
We're almost there.
Why did he bring
her back here?
OK, I think
we've followed them
enough to know what's going on.
We've already come this far.
it's too late to turn back now.
Huh?
Come on, keeping moving.
[GASP]
Is that a hotel?
Seriously, Ayano, I don't
think I want to see any more.
[FLAMES IGNITE]
Perv, how could you?
Can we go home now?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROWLING]
Ayano, you should
try to breathe.
I can't believe he brought
her here to a place like this!
This is unforgivable!
Ayano, please calm down.
You got to control yourself!
Grr.
Hotel Campanera, huh?
What?
Something wrong?
It's OK.
This place is kind of a dump,
but I guess it's all right.
[GIGGLE]
Well, it's too late now.
You're here for good.
[GUNSHOT]
[GASP]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GRUNT]
[COCKING]
[GUNFIRE]
[BOOM]
Guess I was more of a threat
than you thought, wasn't I?
AYANO: You want to tell
me what's going on here?
Ayano.
Ren.
I'd hoped to avoid
any witnesses,
but maybe it's good
that you're here.
It seems appropriate that
a member of the family
should be here to
gather his remains.
His what?
Seriously?
Don't tell me you really
thought a lame attack
like that could kill Kazuma.
I doubt you even put a
single scratch on him.
[GASP]
Oh no, that's impossible.
[MEN SCREAMING]
Yeah, it's much
nicer here now.
[THUMPING]
Hey, don't even bother.
I already had a little talk
with your rooftop sniper.
MISAO: What?
How could you‐‐
Don't feel too bad.
It was a good idea in theory.
I was almost surprised.
And weapons are more
effective than your magic.
Only thing is you'll
need more guns.
You've changed, huh?
Did I make you this way?
Are you serious?
You haven't seen me in 10 years.
You really think you know me
well enough to even ask that?
OK, good point.
All right, you too.
That's enough with the chatter.
Misao, you're
coming home with me.
You're going to
explain everything
you've done to my father.
Hey!
Get back here!
Wait!
She's right.
10 years.
[HURRIED FOOTSTEPS]
You've cornered
yourself, Misao.
Just give up.
You're not going to
get away from me.
You're chasing after me like
I'm some kind of criminal,
and I haven't done
anything wrong.
Now, leave me alone.
Don't try to
play dumb with me.
I was standing right there.
Do you even realize
what you've done?
What?
You hired mercenaries
to gun down an ally
of the Kannagi family,
and that's unforgivable.
As the next head of
the family, I can't
let you get away with this.
Misao, please.
Just come home.
I won't be punished for
doing something the rest
of the family was scared to do.
Then you've left
me with no choice.
Enraiha, come forth!
That's enough.
You girls are going to get
heard playing that way.
It's Kazuma.
Oh, great.
I've got this under
control, all right?
Look, I'm just
returning her purse.
That's got to be the worst
excuse I've ever heard.
Ayano, you're taking
this a little too far.
Misao didn't do anything
to the Kannagi family.
She tried to kill me.
So I don't see how it's
any of your business.
You're missing the point.
Misao is a member of
the Kannagi family,
and her actions
reflect on all of us.
Don't you get that?
No, I guess I don't.
I mean it.
What happened here is
between Misao and me.
So just leave it alone.
What?
You can't be serious, Kazuma.
You're talking about a girl
that just tried to kill you.
And if you do anything to stop
her, she's going to try again!
And I don't care.
What?
Why not?
Because it doesn't matter.
She can't even put
a scratch on me.
Hah!
It's pointless, Misao.
Can't you see that?
Just let it go.
He's too strong for you.
You have nowhere near the
same level of magic he does.
How could you?
It's not fair.
Argh!
Why did you kill my brother?
You killed him!
This is all your fault!
You took him from me.
You killed my precious Takeya!
He was the only person in my
family that cared about me,
and you killed him.
He was the only
one that I loved!
Why did you kill him?
Why'd you have to
take him away from me?
You have to learn to
be strong for me, Misao.
I need to know that you
can take care of yourself.
But why, Takeya?
I'm not on my own.
You're here.
I know I'll always
have you to protect me.
I hope you're right.
[GRUNTING]
[WHIMPERING]
[SOBBING]
I'll never forgive you
for what you've done.
Never.
And I will do anything it takes
to make you suffer like he did.
Do what you have to do.
Are you OK?
Hey, wait.
Kazuma.
What is it you wish for?
Is it the death of another?
Do you seek vengeance?
Or do you simply hunger for
an unstoppable strength?
All of them.
[CHUCKLE]
You're a greedy little girl.
Ambitious.
But if that is what you desire,
I will grant your wishes.
Now, look at me.
[GASP]
What's happening?
[PANTING]
[GRUNT]
No!
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
All right.
Let's begin.
Yes, please.
Help me, angel.
[THEME ‐ SAORI KIUJI, "HITORI
KIRI NO SORA"]
AYANO (VOICEOVER): Did you
just call me a burden, Kazuma?
I'll show you a
burden, you idiot.
Just wait until
you need my help.
You could be dying
for all I care.
I'll never help you again!
Wait a minute.
You want me to do what?
You want to use me as bait?
Are you out of your mind?
How dare you ask me to do that!
Next time on "Kaze no
Stigma," "The Price of Power."
Misao, can't you even see what
you're doing to your aura?