MAN (VOICEOVER): Gonzo.
VOICES (VOICEOVER): Funimation.
You should be watching.
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): Eyes
as blue as the azure sky.
That is the symbol
of the Contractor.
Entrusted by the
Spirit King of the Wind
with the powers of his domain.
I bear this mark.
The stigma of the wind.
[THEME MUSIC]
All right.
I'll do it.
Kazuma has to be stopped.
Ayano.
Now, look.
I may not completely understand
what I mean to Kazuma,
but I do know this much.
If there's even the
slightest chance that I'm
the key to bringing
him back, I have
to do everything I
can, no matter what,
and we can't afford to
wait around anymore.
So I swear on the
Kannagi sacred flame,
I'll turn Kazuma around
and bring him back.
Not to the past or
thoughts of Tsui‐Ling,
but right here with us.
Thank you, Ayano.
Oh, joy.
Miss Kannagi's here
to save the day.
Just don't screw it up or
I'll never forgive you.
It's almost time, Bernhardt.
You are a dead man.
This is my cross to bear.
I'll bury both Kazuma and
Pandemonium in the same grave.
You don't mean that.
Genma.
This cannot be.
No matter what he and
I think of each other,
he's still my son.
I brought him into this world.
I should be the one
to take him from it.
But that isn't
the only option.
Try giving us a chance.
Just let Ayano and
me go after him.
And why should I do that?
REN: Because we can stop
him without killing him.
GENMA: That defeats the purpose.
REN: But we can‐‐
GENMA: This is
the only way, Ren.
Each member of
the Kannagi family
is born with great
responsibility.
Even if Kazuma is
my son, I can't
make the same mistake he has.
He must be punished.
REN: There's a difference
between punishment and death.
Please don't kill him, father.
He doesn't have to die to
pay for what he's done.
GENMA: There are times when
death is the only atonement.
OK.
I've had as much as
I can take of this.
With all due respect, sir,
you're behaving like a child.
Isn't the life of your
own son more important
than the code of the Kannagis?
My loyalty belongs
to the Kannagi family,
and I hope you can understand
that as our next leader.
There won't be a
Kannagi family if we all
kill each other, and I'd like
to have a few members left
when I take over, so listen up.
As the next head of the
family, I'll handle this.
GENMA: Excuse me?
Ren and I will take
care of Kazuma ourselves.
You're officially off the case.
You're joking.
You really think you
can stop a Contractor?
I'm willing to
bet Enraiha on it.
If that's what
you want, so be it.
[SIGH]
Um, Ayano.
[GIGGLE] OK.
That was intense.
Your dad's kinda
scary, isn't he?
But no one's gonna
try to stop us now.
It's time to shake
some sense into Kazuma.
Yeah.
Ayano.
How exactly do you
plan on stopping him?
Well, you know.
You don't have a plan, do you?
Hm.
We still have a
little bit of time left.
JUGO (VOICEOVER): Please, Ayano.
Don't let me down.
[EXPLOSION]
Mystic Battleaxe!
Dark Explosion!
Falling Star Light!
REN: They've already
started fighting,
and Pandemonium hasn't
even descended yet.
It's a strategy.
They're trying to
level the playing field
and decrease their competition
before the descent begins.
Really?
Then all the seeds must be here.
Probably won't be long
before Kazuma shows up.
AYANO (VOICEOVER): Any time now.
Shouldn't we try to stop
them or something, Kirika?
If‐‐
I don't really see
the point in trying
to stop a group of criminals
from fighting each other.
They're pretty much
doing my job for me.
I see.
[EXPLOSION]
I'll take care of this one.
You sure?
Ah!
A flame of purification?
REN: They may not act like it,
but these guys are still human,
and we can save them
if we erase the yoma.
And if we can, we should.
I don't really see the
point in having powers
if we don't use them to try
and protect everyone we can.
AYANO (VOICEOVER): He
sounds more and more
like his brother every day.
Just hang back.
I'll deal with the seeds.
Try to lay low and
save your energy.
You've already got enough to
worry about if you're gonna
try to take care of Kazuma.
[BELL CHIMING]
It's already 12 o'clock.
It's supposed to descend
at exactly midnight.
[RUMBLING]
It's starting.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Is that the same Pandemonium?
REN: It has to be,
but it's bigger.
KIRIKA: Look.
AYANO: What's happening?
REN: I've got a bad
feeling about this.
[GROANING]
A yoma.
That light must've
somehow triggered them.
It was like an alarm clock
and they're all waking up.
KIRIKA: There's nothing
we can do to save them
once they've fully transformed.
REN: What are they doing?
They're all heading
straight for Pandemonium.
KIRIKA: Looks like
Kazuma's here.
AYANO (VOICEOVER): But there's
an evil feeling in the air.
It can't be him.
I'm sorry to leave you like
this, guys, but that's my cue.
I'm only gonna get in your
way if I stick around.
All right.
Ayano.
No matter what, don't give up.
I know you can help him.
Just have faith in yourself.
Thank you, Kirika.
[EXPLOSION]
AYANO: Kazuma.
REN: Please stop.
Just think about
what you're doing.
Do you really think
Tsui‐Ling would
want you to act like this?
I know you're angry,
but you have to stop.
I'm sorry, but revenge
won't bring her back.
You know this isn't what
she'd want you to do.
She would hate to
see you this way.
Please.
You don't know what the hell
you're talking about, Ren.
It doesn't matter what Tsui‐Ling
would want, because she's dead.
REN: But Kazuma‐‐
KAZUMA: You've got it backwards.
I'm not gonna waste my time
trying to please somebody
who doesn't exist anymore.
And I know there's nothing
I can do about the fact
that she's gone.
It's far too late
to save her life.
However, it's not too
late to end Bernhardt's.
I'm not gonna kill
him because I think
Tsui‐Ling would want me to.
I'm gonna kill him
because I want him dead,
and I won't let
anyone get in my way.
REN: You don't mean that.
KAZUMA: Shut up, Ren.
There's nothing you can
say that's gonna stop me.
REN: Kazuma.
Please.
KAZUMA: I'm warning you.
Don't get in my way.
So you're not gonna
bother listening to reason.
Is that it?
Well, can't say I'm shocked.
Time for plan B.
Oh yeah?
What's that?
Enraiha!
[INAUDIBLE]
You're not going any
further with this.
I've had it.
This is your last chance.
You can't stop
me, and you know it.
AYANO: Yeah, I can,
and I'm going to.
KAZUMA: And just
what the hell makes
you think you can do that?
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
AYANO (VOICEOVER): So this
is Kazuma's true power.
I had no idea he
was this strong.
And he hasn't even started using
his Contractor abilities yet.
My hands are shaking.
Am I actually scared of him?
Of course.
I'm terrified of him.
How can I possibly win
against a Contractor?
But there's something
different now.
My hands didn't shake like this
the last time I fought him.
And not only that, but something
just feels more ominous.
The wind almost seems toxic.
OK.
I think I understand.
KAZUMA: You're in my way.
Now, move.
AYANO: I just
realized something.
I figured out why I'm
so angry with you.
Not that you care.
But do you have any idea
how much of a disappointment
you are right now?
I said move.
AYANO: I can't believe
I'm telling you this,
but the truth is, I've always
kinda looked up to you.
You probably think
this sounds stupid,
but all I ever really wanted
was to be as strong as you are,
and to have your approval.
KAZUMA: Last chance.
I'm not gonna say it again.
AYANO: And that's why I
can't let you go any further.
I've had too much
respect for you
to let you do this to yourself.
This isn't who you are.
So I'm gonna force you to
open your eyes if I have to.
But don't worry.
I'm gonna try to
take it easy on you.
This is too much.
Please be careful.
Ah!
Take this!
He's behind you!
AYANO (VOICEOVER):
It makes sense now.
I'm scared because I've never
seen this side of him before.
This isn't the Kazuma I know.
Something's different.
If he was acting like himself,
I wouldn't be afraid of him
at all.
He's usually so
strong and noble,
even when he is being a jerk.
He's acting like this
because he's given up.
He's only letting
his anger guide him.
But that means he doesn't have
full control of his powers.
He just can't be this weak.
I refuse to accept that.
I refuse to accept
that this is who he is.
I'm not gonna let him destroy
himself and become a monster.
I'll use everything
he's ever taught me,
and I'll remind him
of who he really is.
[SCREAMING]
Now, try not to look
so scared, Kazuma.
This is nothing.
If you're afraid of
this, blame yourself!
You taught me this, Kazuma.
You taught me everything I know.
The meaning of power.
How to use it.
You even taught me the
meaning of our existence.
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): Why
hasn't she given up?
How can she still care about
me after what I've become?
Why is she standing in my way?
AYANO (VOICEOVER):
He's different.
This isn't Kazuma.
It can't be.
And I won't stop
until I get him back!
Is that‐‐
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER):
The Crimson Flame.
AYANO: Our powers should
be used to protect
life, not destroy it.
It's our responsibility
to protect others.
Have you forgotten you were
the one who taught me that?
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): Was I?
AYANO: You told me you didn't
acquire your powers just
to let people die.
You said when you
realized you had
the power to protect everyone,
you swore that's what you'd do.
Isn't that the real reason
you signed the contract?
I know you remember!
Please protect me.
Promise you'll
protect me forever.
Swear you'll always watch over
me, no matter what happens.
Yes, I will.
I swear on my life,
I'll protect you.
No matter what, you'll never
have to be afraid again.
Forever and always, Tsui‐Ling.
So what are you doing
with your powers now?
I wouldn't call this
protection, would you?
And you're not defending anyone
by trying to avenge the past.
Tell me!
Who are you protecting
now, Kazuma?
[WIND HOWLING]
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): What
the hell have I been doing?
The whole point of this
power is to save lives,
and I've been using it
to try and take them.
I've failed.
I've done exactly what I
swore to myself I'd never do.
What a joke.
My powers are
pathetic right now.
No wonder she was winning.
But then again, look at her.
She summoned the Divine Flame.
I wasn't sure if I'd
ever see it again.
I'll never forget
the first time.
It was at that moment that I saw
how truly remarkable she was.
It's amazing, really.
I can't believe how much
her magic has developed.
[SCREAM]
Why won't you snap out of it?
Wait!
Hold on!
[HEAVY BREATHING]
REN: Ayano.
Did you kill him?
No, he's fine.
If I'd hit him straight on,
it would have obliterated him.
No matter what, I beat him.
I actually beat Kazuma.
Yeah.
It was pretty awesome.
Why didn't you ever
tell me that you knew
how to use the Divine Flame?
What?
Divine Flame?
What are you talking about?
You're kidding, right?
The Divine Flame.
The Crimson Flame.
You just used it.
I did?
No way!
I don't even know how to use it.
Aw, man.
[GROANING]
Kazuma.
So I guess that makes
you and me officially even.
I figured it'd be best to go
ahead and settle the score now.
How can you even
walk after that attack?
Well, I managed to deflect it.
I figured I would have at
least burned you a little bit.
Whatever.
I still won.
Are you at least back to
your old jerk self again?
When did I actually stop
being my old jerk self?
What?
You've gotta be kidding.
Are you really gonna stand
there and act like you
didn't do anything wrong?
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER):
No matter what
happens, I promise that
you'll always be in my heart.
But I think it's
about time I made room
for some other people, too.
You understand that,
don't you, Tsui‐Ling?
What are you doing?
Hey, uh‐‐ hey!
What are you thinking?
You pervert!
Don't act so surprised.
You should know by now how
selfish and greedy I am.
REN: Kazuma, look.
Pandemonium.
AYANO: This doesn't look good.
REN: It's gathering
up all the yoma.
AYANO: It's about to
start something, isn't it?
Not if I shut it down.
I have to destroy
Pandemonium now.
This has gone on
for far too long.
You can't just
destroy it, you idiot.
For all we know, Nanase and
Yukari are still in there.
And it's all your fault
they were kidnapped.
So the very first thing you're
gonna do is rescue them.
Fine.
Let's quit standing
around and do it.
REN: Yeah.
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): I won't
betray my power again.
I swear it.
I'll protect everyone I can.
[THEME MUSIC]
AYANO (VOICEOVER):
I'm not asking
you to protect me, all right?
And whatever happened in your
past, it's none of my business.
But it's pretty obvious
that you're in pain,
and I want you to know
that I'm here for you.
You don't have to deal with
everything on your own.
Kazuma, be honest with
yourself, and give me a break.
Next time on "Kaze no Stigma,"
protectors of the wind.
So I guess this might be the
last time I see your face, huh.