ANNOUNCER: Gonzo.
Funimation.
KAZUMA: Eyes as blue
as the azure sky.
That is the symbol
of the Contractor,
entrusted by the
Spirit King of the Wind
with the powers of his domain.
I bear this mark, the
stigma of the wind.
[MUSIC ‐ SAORI KIUJI, "BLAST OF
WIND"]
There's really no
need for you to worry.
Ren is a little
depressed at the moment
but is otherwise unharmed.
We do appreciate your concern.
Thank you.
JUGO (VOICEOVER):
Damn Tsuwabukis.
Only yesterday they were
threatening to kill him.
Father?
You're back.
How's Ren doing?
Much better.
This morning before lunch
he finally spoke to me.
That's great news.
Wait, did he say whether or
not they did something to him?
First there is something
I need to tell you.
No member of the Kannagi
family can interfere with
the Tsuwabukis' grand ceremony.
It's important that we
stay out of the way.
So don't go
looking for payback.
Is that what you're
trying to say?
Listen to me, Ayano.
I know you might find
it disturbing, but you‐‐
No, I get it.
Trust me.
I do know what duty means.
And I understand the importance
of what they're trying to do.
That's good.
Now, we should talk about Ren.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
KUREHA: There were
three obstacles
standing in the way of my plan.
One was the little Kannagi boy,
but that's been taken care of.
Then there's the wind magic
user and his pixie counterpart,
but Yuuji will
take care of that.
And finally, we have you.
But somehow, in your
current condition,
I doubt you'll be interfering.
Will you, Father?
I never had any intention of
stopping the grand ceremony,
Kureha, only your ambition.
There are civil ways
to go about curbing
someone's ambition.
And I think you and I
can both agree attempted
murder isn't one of them.
But you tried anyway, didn't
you, while failing miserably,
as usual.
I'll tell you something else.
If this little
girl doesn't work,
we're fully prepared
to use Mayumi.
You can't!
It seems to me I can do
whatever the hell I want,
Father, and there's not a damn
thing you can do about it,
is there?
Wait!
Please don't do this!
But I already have.
Now there's nothing left
for you to do but sit back
and watch your family fail.
[MANIACAL LAUGHTER]
Damn you, Kureha!
Kureha!
KUREHA (VOICEOVER):
The time has come.
Tonight, with the
arrival of the full moon,
everything I've wanted‐‐
all my wishes come true.
Ren, don't sit out here
feeling sorry for yourself.
That won't solve anything.
It's pointless.
[GASP]
Hey, what was that for?
Look, I heard the whole story.
I know, when push came to
shove, you abandoned that girl.
Abandoned her?
You let them take Ayumi
right out of your hands
and you didn't do
anything about it.
In my book, that's called
abandoning someone.
No, that's not
what I meant to do.
Then what did you mean to do?
I didn't have a choice.
I had to let them take her.
She's the master
of the ceremony.
That's the only reason
she was created.
She has to sacrifice her
life to keep us safe.
If she doesn't go
through with it,
then everyone will be in danger.
There's nothing I
can do to save her.
I can't even believe
what I'm hearing right now.
You and Ayumi became
close friends, am I right?
They took your friend
away from you, Ren.
Are you sure that's
something you can live with?
Now, come on.
You've got to do something.
REN (VOICEOVER):
She means more to me
than anything else in the world.
But still, there's
nothing I can do.
Or is there?
I could rescue her, but then
the grand ceremony will fail
and the beast will be set free.
I can't let that happen.
That's not what Ayumi wants.
But she made a decision.
I have to respect it.
She's going to
sacrifice her life.
Think, Ren.
What do you want?
Well, I‐‐
I think what I want
more than anything is‐‐
I want‐‐ I really want to
see Ayumi one last time.
I want to apologize to her
for the way things went.
I want her to know how
much she means to me.
I just need to tell
her how I feel.
That's more like it.
Lets go.
We'd better hurry if
we're going to make it.
I'll be beside you
every step of the way.
I want you to know I'm
really proud of you.
Thanks, Ayano.
But I need to be perfectly
clear about one thing.
We're only there to apologize
to Ayumi, not to interfere.
Right!
KUREHA: That dress looks
lovely on you, Ayumi.
It's a shame your
little friend turned
his back on such a pretty girl.
If I were you, I'd
forget about him.
Those foolish thoughts
will only distract you.
You need to focus on being
the master of the ceremony.
But I know how you must
be feeling right now.
When you're different
from everyone else,
it's hard to find someone
who truly understands you,
isn't it?
But unfortunately, that's
the way things are.
Human beings can be vicious,
vindictive creatures.
Trust me.
I know from experience.
Kureha, intruders!
Who is it this time?
Is it the wind magic user?
No.
Two fire magic users‐‐
one of them a woman,
the other a young boy.
He's coming.
Hey, what the heck was that?
What happened to not
getting in the way?
That was not my fault.
They attacked me, OK?
That doesn't mean you
have to hit them back.
Listen to me.
We didn't come here
to cause problems.
I just want to see Ayumi
and I'll be on my way.
Let me through.
I'm not here to interfere
with the ceremony.
It's not gonna happen.
[YELLING]
Come on.
Right.
REN (VOICEOVER): I've got to get
to Ayumi before it's too late.
Watch out!
What the heck is that thing?
[YELLING]
That ought to slow him down.
[LAUGHING]
I certainly hope that's
not the best you can do.
REN (VOICEOVER): Wait.
I know that voice.
Hm?
So that must be the
legendary Enraiha.
You go ahead.
I've got it under control.
I'm going to teach
this guy a lesson.
I'll catch up with you
when I'm done here.
No, you can't.
Just go!
You're not getting
away from me.
Ren, no!
Let him go!
Unh.
Ayano, are you OK?
Why isn't Enraiha
working on this guy?
It doesn't make any sense.
It's pointless
for you to resist.
Surrender right now or I
promise I will crush the boy.
Hang on.
I do know that voice.
I remember it now.
I know who you are.
You're Yuuji, aren't you?
Congratulations.
You figured it out.
What happened?
Why do you look like that?
It's simple.
I chose this path.
I look like this because
I finally have power‐‐
the power to defend
what I love most.
Don't you see?
I can finally
protect Lady Mayumi.
What?
You did all this for Mayumi?
If the grand
ceremony's interrupted,
her life will be
in grave danger.
And I won't let that happen.
That's why Kureha gave me this
power in the first place‐‐
to make sure that
nothing stands in our way
and that the ceremony is
successful and Mayumi is safe.
A child like you could
never understand this,
but I will happily sacrifice my
own life to see it fulfilled.
REN (VOICEOVER):
It's unbelievable.
He means every
single word of it.
But somehow, the things he's
saying just don't seem‐‐
You sacrifice
yourself for love,
and I can understand that.
But don't you see that
there's another side to it?
What?
If you sacrifice yourself,
you're only causing pain.
Pain to yourself and then
pain to your loved ones.
And once you're
gone, you'll never
be able to see them again.
Enough of this.
You know that I'm right.
Sacrifice isn't the answer.
But you keep on believing
if that makes you happy.
Be sure to say
goodbye to Mayumi!
[YELLING]
No!
Stop!
Ren, are you OK?
REN: Kazuma!
‐ Sup?
‐ What?
Kazuma, what are you doing here?
How did you know where we were?
Kazuma's here to recover
the pixie's secret treasure
that was stolen from‐‐
OK, what is up with the pixie?
Well, it's kind
of a long story.
If I were you, I'd
watch your back, though.
That thing's not dead yet.
Impressive regenerating ability.
What the hell is that thing?
His name's Yuuji.
He used to be human.
What happened?
He sacrificed his
body to save a family
member named Mayumi Tsuwabuki.
KAZUMA: Yeah, that
sounds about right.
REN: What do you mean by that?
That's how the
Tsuwabukis think.
It's always about
sacrifice for them.
It's the Tsuwabuki way.
They've been killing their own
people for hundreds of years
now.
It's sickening.
[STAGGERED BREATHING]
Lady Mayumi, that is
completely inappropriate.
That was my first kiss.
It's the only one I've ever had.
Now own up to it.
Own up to it?
Please stay with me forever.
Promise me you'll stay by
my side till the day I die.
What are you talking about?
They finally
told me the truth.
They told me that eventually
I'll have to give up
my life in order to silence Mt.
Fuji.
I guess I don't
have a choice, huh?
It's a destiny that
I can't escape from.
I have to carry the burden
of the Tsuwabuki family.
But Lady Mayumi‐‐
Please, Yuuji, listen.
From now on, you have to
do everything I tell you.
And if I escape, stop me.
No matter what happens,
you must bring me back.
Never let me get away,
no matter what the cost.
YUUJI: On that day,
I swore my loyalty.
I swore to give up everything
for her, even my own life,
if necessary.
[YELLING]
You can't defeat me,
so turn around and go.
I won't let you pass.
Do you understand?
Anybody got any bright ideas?
If he's an earth magic
user, it should be easy.
We just have to keep him off
the ground where he has power.
If it's earth magic, that is.
AYANO: And what if it's not?
REN: Kazuma?
Hm?
Would you do it?
Would you be willing to die
if it meant protecting me?
Ren, stop!
What kind of a horrible
question is that?
I got an answer for you.
First I'd save
you, then I'd kill
the bastard that put my
little brother in harm's way.
There's no reason everyone
can't be happy, right?
I know what to do now.
Just stay back, you guys.
I'm going to take care
of this one myself.
Ren, wait!
Don't!
What's up with him?
Did something happen?
You're a little too
late for an explanation.
Are you going to beg
for your life, boy?
I'm sick and tired of
hearing about this ceremony.
If you want my
opinion, you people
are obsessed with sacrifice.
What?
It's not just you, either.
Ayumi's the same way.
But you Tsuwabukis
have it all wrong.
It's just like my
brother said before.
There's no reason
everyone can't be happy.
Happiness is not the
path of our family.
Why not?
Because we Tsuwabukis have
a fate we cannot escape from.
It is our destiny.
It's your destiny?
I see now.
The beast is the real enemy
that must be defeated.
Argh!
Enough of this!
I don't get it!
Why couldn't Ren's fire
stop that stupid thing?
That wasn't a defensive move.
He's doing something else.
Ah!
What is this?
Agh!
What's happening?
It burns!
[SCREAMING]
How'd he do that?
I hit him with Enraiha
and he didn't even budge.
Guess Ren wasn't stupid
enough to try to cut up a rock.
He used fire to
purify Yuuji's aura
and turn him back into
his original form.
And he did it without
sacrificing his life.
AYANO: OK, how does
Ren know how to do
something that complicated?
KAZUMA: Yeah, good question.
Where did that come from?
Kazuma, it's all
so clear to me now.
I know what I have to do.
And I know who the real enemy
is I must defeat to save Ayumi.
Ren, no!
You can be serious.
I have to say I'm impressed.
That's as crazy as any
idea I've ever had.
I like the way you
think, little brother.
Hey, stop encouraging
him, Kazuma.
There's nothing
impressive about it.
Understand?
[YELLING]
Now that is just pathetic.
He still lost despite
the power I gave him?
Guess it wasn't his
fault, then, was it?
If it isn't the wind
magic user, Kazuma Yagami.
I figured you were
behind this, Kureha.
But I sure as hell didn't expect
to see you defying gravity.
That's an impressive trick
for an earth magic user.
Where'd you learn that one?
Wait, let me guess.
You got your power
from the beast.
Very perceptive.
And you're absolutely
right, Kazuma.
My ability comes from
the beast that's sealed
away inside the mountain.
So Yuuji was able to transform
his body because of the beast?
KUREHA: That's correct.
He joined with part of its body.
REN (VOICEOVER): I knew it.
I have to put a stop to this.
Feel free to attack
me, but I must warn you,
I won't go down as
easily as Yuuji did.
Guess we'll see, won't we?
That's right.
This is Enraiha.
You two haven't
officially met, have you?
Let's give her
an introduction.
Hey, Ren.
‐ What's up?
You go on ahead.
We've got this under control.
[YELLING]
Kazuma, where'd you send him?
I figured he'd want
to see his girlfriend.
You mean he's going
to go see Ayumi?
He'll be fine.
I used my wind to
find her location.
[YELLING]
[FAR‐AWAY YELLING]
Ow!
Ow, ow!
What the heck did you
do that for, Kazuma?
Ren?
Ren, it's you!
I'm here, Ayumi.
I found you.
Who in the hell are you?
Tell me what you're doing here.
What am I doing here?
Well, at first I thought I
just wanted to see you and tell
you how sorry I am, Ayumi.
Yesterday was one of the most
amazing days I've ever had,
and I wanted to tell you that.
Thank you, Ren.
REN: But now that
I'm here, I realized
that it's just not good enough.
I'm sorry, but I'm going
to rescue you, Ayumi.
And that's not all.
I'm going to save Mayumi.
I'm not going to let
anyone be sacrificed.
There's no reason
everyone can't be happy.
Are you crazy?
What are you saying?
Stop the ceremony and the
beast will destroy us all!
I guess I'll have to defeat
the beast, then, won't I?
That's right.
The real enemy is the beast, and
it must be destroyed tonight.
There's no way in hell that
you can stop that monster.
We won't let you put
our people at risk.
REN: I defeated Yuuji
before I came in here.
You defeated Yuuji?
You two can't beat me,
but feel free to try.
I only want you to hear me out.
If we can kill that beast, then
no one has to be sacrificed.
Everyone can be happy,
Ayumi, including you.
It's not right.
You don't understand
how dangerous this is.
If you can't defeat the beast,
that mountain will erupt
and you could die.
But I can protect you
and everyone else.
I was created to protect
the world from this evil.
Sacrificing yourself so
you can protect others.
That's what Yuuji
believed in, as well.
But you know what
I think, Ayumi?
I truly believe you don't
have to give your life away.
And I know you think that
sounds like wishful thinking,
but in my opinion, it's the
only path worth believing in.
I don't understand.
Why would you go this far
for some thing like me?
Even if the ceremony
doesn't happen, I'm still‐‐
I'm still going
to die very soon.
Then you should treasure
every single minute
that you have left.
Anything you need, Ayumi,
I'll give it to you.
I swear I'll take you
anywhere you want.
Come on now.
We can do this.
Let's go.
Let's be happy.
I just want‐‐
I want‐‐ you're right.
I do want this.
I want to be happy.
I want to live a long,
happy life with you.
Good.
KAZUMA: Sorry to interrupt,
but we're kind of in a hurry.
REN: Kazuma!
Hi there.
I heard an awful lot about you.
I'm Kazuma, Ren's brother.
It's really nice to meet you.
Oh, wait.
If you're here,
then where's Ayano?
She's keeping Kureha's
attention away from you.
Great.
You didn't use her as bait
again, again, did you?
KAZUMA: Of course.
Who'd save you if I didn't?
REN: I was doing fine by myself.
I know.
I saw you.
Anyway, we're running
out of time here.
You're still planning on
killing the beast, right?
Right.
[MUSIC ‐ SAORI KIUJI, "HITORI
KIRI NO SORA"]
AYANO: Kureha
wasn't ever planning
on sealing the beast away.
Kazuma, don't you realize
what you've done, you idiot?
What?
You know the Kannagis can't
go up against the beast of Mt.
Fuji.
Don't tell me Ayumi's
about to start
the grand ceremony right here.
No!
If you do that, then you'll‐‐
next time on "Kaze No Stigma,"
"Confession Under the Moon".
Can that thing get any bigger?