MAN: Gonzo.
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): Eyes
as blue as the azure sky.
That is the symbol
of the Contractor.
Entrusted by the
Spirit King of the Wind
with the powers of his
domain, I bear this mark,
the stigma of the wind.
[THEME ‐ SAORI KIUJI, "BLAST OF
WIND"]
[BOOM]
What's going on?
Look, there he is.
Good to see you again, Ryuya.
Now, where'd you
take my brother?
I hear you want
to sacrifice him.
It's him‐‐
Ryuya.
Why didn't I sense his presence?
He's a wind magic user.
If he doesn't want to be
found, a fire user like
you doesn't stand a chance.
Get right in his face
and fight him close.
Attacks from a
distance won't work.
Why don't you worry
about yourself, 'K?
Enraiha, come forth!
[GROWL]
Hah!
There's never been a youma
that Enraiha can't destroy!
‐ [GROWL]
‐ [GRUNT]
[BOOM]
[CHUCKLE]
[GRUNTING]
I could use a little
help right now.
[GRUNT]
Kazuma!
Kazuma?
Since you've got
everything under control,
I'm going on ahead.
Take care of him, all right?
Ugh.
Don't you leave me
like this, you traitor!
Go on.
Now is the time.
Release the seal of our god.
Summon the great youma.
Using the seed of the
Kannagi to free him.
[FAINT CHANTING]
Here is Lord Gehou.
We offer the child of the
Kannagi as a sacrifice.
Devour his soul and
give us the power to put
an end to the Kannagi forever!
[BOOM]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[SCREAMING]
[SIGH]
That was close.
[WHOOSHING]
I'll deal with you in a minute.
[WIND WHISTLES]
Kazuma.
Well, what do you know?
Look who decided to wake up.
You saved me.
What the hell is
wrong with you letting
them kidnap you like that?
I thought you were supposed to
be some kind of big‐time fire
magic user now.
Would do you have to
save for yourself?
I'm really sorry.
I swear it won't happen again.
Please let me go.
Tell me, why are you
getting in our way,
helping those you hate?
The abused feel a grudge
that cannot be shaken,
humiliation that never dies.
You of all people should
know what I'm talking about.
I know you feel it, Kazuma.
I know you hate the Kannagi
family just as much as we do.
Yeah, well, I'm not
going to lie to you.
They're not exactly my favorite
people in the world right now.
Kazuma.
If you share our hatred
for the Kannagi family,
then why help them?
It simply doesn't make sense.
For money.
The head of the family hired me.
Man's got to eat.
Wait a second.
You're saying you're
not here to rescue me?
The only reason you saved me
is because you're being paid?
I play to the
highest bidder, kid.
I'm not a hero.
But if I happen to do some
good in the process, so be it.
You fool, it's our mission.
There's no way in
hell we'll let someone
like you stand in our way.
[MEN GRUNT]
[MEN SHOUT]
Ryuya‐‐ he's finally here.
KAZUMA: Guess Ayano wasn't
able to hold him off.
REN: No way.
Ayano never loses‐‐
not with Enraiha.
[ROARING]
I hear spirits
calling each other.
[GRUNT]
[BOOM]
It's time for you to
become one with Lord Gehou.
Join with him now, Ryuya,
and fulfill our destiny!
[ROARING]
Behold his majesty, the great
youma, lord of the Fuga clan.
Destroy these Kannagi intruders.
Crush them beneath
your feet and wipe
away their seed from the earth!
[SHOUTING]
No, Lord Gehou!
Please!
[MEN SCREAMING]
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): He must be
heading towards the Kannagis'
main house.
I don't get it.
Why did that youma attack them?
Aren't they supposed
to be on the same side?
I guess being in
prison for so long
made him snap and turn
on his own people.
His hatred for the Kannagi
who locked him away
must have consumed him
entirely, leaving nothing else.
REN: That's awful.
I suppose so.
But you can't say these bastards
didn't have it coming to them.
So naive.
Kazuma.
I've got to stop him.
Not that I give a damn
what happens to the family.
It's just business.
If they all get killed,
I don't get paid.
But before we go‐‐
What do you think?
Should we leave
her or pick her up?
Now, that is a sorry sight.
He beat her up pretty good.
Ayano, please wake up.
Ayano.
What happened to her?
Is she OK?
I'd say no.
REN: What?
KAZUMA: The wound
isn't that bad,
but she's been
infected by his aura.
His spirit is eating
her from the inside out.
It's just a matter
of time before it
takes over her entire body.
This is bad.
There has to be some way
we can help her, right?
Hmm.
Yeah, I got something
here that might work.
I just hate to waste it on her.
What are you saying?
Hey, listen, kid, I'm not
trying to be insensitive.
But this stuff's valuable
and hard to come by.
That's it?
You'll just let her die?
Is that little
bottle of medicine
more important to you
than Ayano's life?
KAZUMA: So what if
she kicks the bucket?
What's the big deal?
It's not all bad for you.
You get to inherit
Enraiha, and I know
the old man will love that.
Shut up.
Give me that medicine.
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): The
flames of honest anger.
Well done.
That's the key to synchronizing
with the spirits of fire.
Whatever you say.
You can turn down the heat now.
This isn't going to work.
[GULPING]
[GASP]
Ew!
Wha‐‐ what was that?
Tell me you weren't.
You were, weren't you?
You‐‐ you were really just‐‐
Aah!
If you touch me again,
I swear I'll kill you!
You're a pervert!
That's not a very nice
way to talk to the person
who just saved your life.
Ayano!
I'm so glad you're all right.
Ren?
The evil spirit was
going to eat your soul,
and then Kazuma gave you
some medicine and saved you.
What kind of medicine
did you give me?
Elixir.
What?
Wait a second.
You mean like alchemist elixir?
But that's supposed to
be the rarest medicine
in the whole world, right?
Tell me about it.
I'll probably never be able
to get my hands on it again.
Now, don't you have
something to say?
Oh.
Thank you for helping me.
KAZUMA: Ah, it's no problem.
I'll just tack the cost of
the elixir onto the bill.
Double ought to cover it.
[GROAN]
Now, you listen to me!
And how come you
lost that fight?
What was it you said
to me earlier today?
If I remember correctly, you
said there wasn't a youma
that Enraiha can't take down.
What, you couldn't burn him
even after you stab him with
your precious little fireblade?
Well, it's not that simple.
Oh, I get it now.
You weren't able to
burn him because you
couldn't even touch him, huh?
[HEAVY SIGH]
First of all, you're the one
who dumped that maniac on me
and then took off without
even giving me any warning.
Yeah, that was a mistake.
I thought you were strong
enough to take care of yourself.
When you attacked
me the other day,
I thought you were
kidding around
or maybe taking it easy on me.
I mean, we are close
to being family.
Kazuma!
See, that's what
I'm talking about.
Let's go, Ren.
Right.
I don't know about you, but
I'm ready to get out of here.
[WHOOSH]
AYANO: [YELLING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[WIND WHISTLING]
Look.
AYANO: That's Ryuya?
But his aura's‐‐
KAZUMA: It's spreading.
And if we don't
stop him in time,
he'll wake the evil
spirits in the ground too.
Do we really stand a chance
against something like this?
Don't tell me you're
scared just because you
got roughed up a little bit.
You're the next head of the
Kannagi family, aren't you?
Wait, who said I was scared?
It's a Kannagi's sworn duty
to rid the world of youma.
I'll stop this thing no matter
what, or I'll die trying.
[WHAP]
What, are you trying to
sound noble or something?
Because if you die,
then it's over.
Your past and future disappear
in the blink of an eye.
There's no coming back.
No matter how
hopeless things seem,
as long as you live
to fight another day,
there's always a chance.
The last man standing wins.
So you fight to survive.
And you never give up.
Now, let's go.
REN: Look!
Ren!
REN: Yah!
You guys go on ahead.
I can take care of them.
Don't forget what I said, Ren.
We're counting on you.
REN: Right.
[WIND WHISTLING]
The Kannagi fire is a
fire of purification.
It's a power given
to us to put an end
to the evil in the world.
By the power of
our sacred flame,
in the name of the Kannagi,
go back to the darkness!
[GRUNT]
[ROARING]
[SHOUTING]
Aah.
[BLASTING]
What are you doing?
Leave me alone!
KAZUMA: Look out!
[ROAR]
[GRUNT]
Aah!
Kazuma.
I really don't like him.
[RUMBLING]
What can we do to stop
something that powerful?
Just keep doing
what you're doing.
Go after him with Enraiha.
Wait for an opening, and
I'll try to slow him down.
[ROARING]
AYANO: What?
But how can you‐‐
KAZUMA: Let me worry about that.
Take him out.
All you need's one clear strike.
You got it?
[ROARING]
Go, now!
[SHOUTING]
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): All right.
Time to stop this guy.
I could create another
tornado that cancels his out.
No, I've got a better idea.
[LOUD WHOOSH]
Now.
[THUNDERCLAPS]
[ROARING]
[LOUD RUMBLING]
REN: [GRUNT]
REN (VOICEOVER): He crushed him.
AYANO: Incredible.
Now I've got to end this!
[ROARING]
[GASP]
[ROAR]
[LOUD BLAST]
Go back where you
came from, youma!
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): That
barely even fazed him.
I guess I'll have to step
it up a notch, won't I?
Let's just hope Ayano
can hang in there.
[GRUNTING]
KAZUMA: Ayano!
Just hold him off
as long as you can.
Try to buy me some time.
Are you kidding me?
Time for what?
[GRUNT]
‐ [ROAR]
[RUMBLE]
I could use some backup.
Hurry!
Hey, Kazuma!
Kazuma!
[SWORD STRIKES]
[GRUNTING]
[ROAR]
AYANO: Kazuma!
You idiot!
What's the matter with you?
Are you even listening to me?
Hello?
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): Hear
me, spirits of the wind.
In the name of the contract,
entrust me with your power.
[ROARING]
[BOOM]
[GRUNT]
So anytime this century!
Aah!
AYANO (VOICEOVER): I can't win.
He's too powerful for me.
All you need is
one clear strike.
You got it?
AYANO (VOICEOVER): What
am I supposed to do?
I'm just not strong enough.
My power's useless.
Just hold him off
as long as you can.
Try to buy me some time.
AYANO (VOICEOVER):
He thinks I'm weak,
a frightened little child.
He doesn't have any
faith in me at all.
Don't tell me you're
scared just because you've
got roughed up a little bit.
You're the next head
of the Kannagi family.
[ROARING]
Back off!
I'm tired of buying you time.
And I don't need
your stupid backup.
I can handle this one on my own!
[GROWLING]
AYANO: Just stand there
and watch how it's done.
[GRUNT]
[SHOUT]
[LOUD ROAR]
[GRUNT]
GEHOU: [GROAN]
[FIRE CRACKLING]
[LOUD ROARING]
[PANTING]
[STOMP]
GEHOU: [SNARLING]
AYANO: You've got
to be kidding me.
KAZUMA: Well done.
Kazuma.
Wha‐‐ what happened
to your eyes?
The Spirit King of the Wind
marked me as the Contractor.
Marked you as the‐‐
you mean, the Spirit King
is giving you his blessing?
[GASP]
[ROARING]
Now, time for you to go back
to hell, where you belong.
[SHOUT]
[ROARING]
You're purifying him.
It's really working.
[GASP]
Ayano.
Right.
[ROARING]
[SHOUTING]
Now, die, youma!
[LOUD ROAR]
REN (VOICEOVER): Kazuma.
Ayano.
[WIND WHISTLING]
KAZUMA: [MOAN]
[THUD]
[FOOTSTEPS]
You didn't need me to
win that fight, did you?
No, I did.
Just because I have a
contract with the Spirit King,
that doesn't make me invincible.
AYANO: I guess not.
At least not if it
takes you that long
to get your attack ready.
Well‐‐
AYANO: Hold on a second.
You waited on purpose?
When were you really ready?
It was about the time you
got blown away, I guess.
Then why didn't
you do something?
Why didn't you try to help me?
Oh, come on.
If I'd have stepped in
while you were down,
you'd feel like a loser
for the rest of your life,
and you know it.
[GROWL]
As it is, you got
a chance to show off
your stuff with Enraiha,
had the whole little speech
and everything.
That's supposed to
make me feel better?
Yeah, 'cause you really
impressed me out there, Ayano.
Wh‐‐ why are you
being nice to me now?
KAZUMA: No reason.
So how long are you
going to sit like that?
[GASP]
[WHIMPER]
I mean, I'm flattered and all.
But‐‐
REN: Ayano!
Kazuma!
[CHUCKLE]
Aah!
[MUFFLED GASP]
[GROWLING]
[FLAMES WHOOSH]
You jerk!
KIRIKA: [CHUCKLE]
It looks like they've
gone crazy again.
IZUMI: I wonder if
the same wind magic
user is responsible for this.
So he really has
come back then.
KIRIKA (VOICEOVER): Kazuma.
I gotta get going.
I've got places to be.
So‐‐
What are you going
to do now, Kazuma?
Who knows?
Try to take it easy, old man.
You're no spring
chicken anymore.
[WIND WHISTLES]
That punk.
[THEME ‐ SAORI KIUJI, "HITORI
KIRI NO SORA"]
AYANO (VOICEOVER):
I'll never forgive him.
Where does that stupid Kazuma
think he's going walking
arm in arm with that woman?
I mean, what the heck was he
doing with her in a hotel?
That pervert.
Misao, you must be
completely out of your mind.
Please tell me you
didn't really believe
an attack of that level would
be enough to take out Kazuma.
Next time on "Kaze
no Stigma," "The One
Who Casts Aside His Doubt."
Father, are you just going to
sit there and let this happen?
Do something!