KAZUMA: Eyes as blue
as the azure sky.
That is the symbol
of the contractor,
entrusted by the spirit
King of the Wind,
with the powers of his domain.
I bear this mark, the
Stigma of the Wind.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SINGING JAPANESE]
[CRYING]
Please, please, stop.
Let‐‐ just let her go.
Tsui‐Ling.
Kazuma?
You are self‐destructive,
aren't you?
You would have to be
suicidal to think you stand
a chance against Almagest.
Kazuma.
Hang on, Tsui‐Ling.
I do love the looks on your
faces, fear and desperation.
Beautiful.
So perfect.
[SCREAMING]
TSUI‐LING: Kazuma.
You sure you can go
through this, Kazuma?
You ever see me
hesitate before?
Well, no.
But I mean, you do realize
that you're going to have to go
up against Lapis, don't you?
And your point?
I know that you
loved each other.
And I just need you to tell me.
Can you do this?
I don't know who the
hell told you that.
But my girlfriend was murdered.
They killed her
right in front of me.
I'm so sorry.
And that thing is nothing but
a cheap knockoff of Tsui‐Ling.
I don't give a damn if they used
her last thoughts to make it.
Lapis will never be
the girl I loved.
Any other questions?
No.
They know we're here.
Nanase.
Yukari.
Thank goodness
you guys are OK.
And there she is.
Welcome to Pandemonium.
I'm glad you could join us.
I apologize on behalf of
my master for his absence.
But an unexpected
matter required him
to suddenly leave the country.
So he ran, like a
scared little boy.
Listen up, Lapis.
I'm taking those
two home with me.
Go right ahead.
We have no further
use for them now.
Utsumi.
I suppose you
want this one too.
Well, they've all
served their purpose.
Each person was used as
bait to lure Kazuma here.
Why?
Why me?
I'm special.
I thought I was the chosen one.
So why are you torturing me?
KAZUMA: You enjoying this?
I suppose so.
It just hadn't occurred to me.
Of course, pain and suffering.
That's all you people
know how to enjoy.
Pandemonium is the
architectural fusion
between humanity and pure evil.
It was originally designed
as part of an experiment
to create the ultimate species.
What do you mean by
architectural fusion?
The evil was dispersed
over the internet.
Yoma downloaded
directly into humans.
Then, their souls were tested
in battle to find the strongest.
And those souls were then
harvested as the building
blocks for Pandemonium.
Pandemonium was created to
serve as a sacrificial altar.
That is the most sickening
thing I've ever heard.
Now, I think we should
talk about you for a minute.
Bernhardt knew I'd try
to stop him, didn't he?
So he used you to
mess with my head.
Well, more or less.
But you mustn't forget the
simple entertainment of causing
you great agony and despair.
What are you talking about?
That's entertaining to you?
The only pleasure they allow
themselves is to torture others
and bring pain to the world.
And they're going
to keep doing it,
until somebody makes them pay.
What did you do?
What's happening?
Lord Belial has
now been summoned.
Who?
She's trying to summon of
the most powerful demon lord.
LAPIS: Belial can
only be awakened
through the ceremonial
offering of poisoned
souls, ones that have been
completely possessed by Yoma.
Utsumi was the final
sacrifice for the ritual.
You look so somber.
Aren't you impressed with my
master's plan for such colossal
devastation?
How can you let
yourself do this?
There has to be some part
of Tsui‐Ling left inside you
that knows this is wrong.
It's the only way
I can develop a soul.
I'm nothing but
a doll, a replica
of Tsui‐Ling who was
made from the residue
of her last emotion.
Master Bernhardt
taught me that despair
is the most complex and
beautiful human experience.
He said that if I
can find pleasure
in the intricacies
of another's pain,
I would then be able
to cultivate my own.
So if I can develop
my own emotions,
different from the ones
I was created with,
then those feelings will become
the foundation of a soul.
And all you have to do is
torture other people to get it?
That's just pathetic.
Even my feelings for
you aren't really mine.
They were chosen for
me by someone else.
They're lies.
And I just want to feel a
true emotion, something real,
from within me.
I just want to be human.
What are you doing?
I've heard about
all I can stand.
If I could just become
human, then I could become her.
Don't you want me to
finally become Tsui‐Ling?
Enough.
Stop using her voice.
You may look like Tsui‐Ling,
but you'll never be her.
Do you want me to die?
Kazuma.
That's not her.
REN: Kazuma.
You've got to snap out of it.
If I can stop the conjuring,
I can stop the summoning.
Ayano.
Keep an eye on them, Ren.
Sure thing.
Be careful.
[SCREAMING]
Where'd she go?
I got you.
I'm through messing
around with you, imposter.
I‐'ve‐‐ I've never
felt so much evil before.
I guess we were too late.
So get ready.
It's coming.
The ceremony
has been answered.
Belail will soon carve
a scar of despair
across the face
of this dimension.
Are you trying to
destroy the world?
Of course not.
It's not even
possible to entirely
summon Belial with such a
small number of sacrifices.
It will only materialize
for a few seconds, at most.
But a few seconds is more than
it will need to reduce the city
to lifeless ash and rubble.
And you Kazuma, I look
forward to watching you die.
I'm sure I'll enjoy the
look of agony on your face.
What now?
We fly.
It's a summoning circle.
And it's huge.
This is hopeless.
My contractor powers are nothing
against a demon this strong.
And your divine flame won't
even put a scratch on it.
Then, what do we do?
The only chance we've got
is to attack it together.
We might as well
die trying, right?
Put all your power
into a single shot.
Then, let it all
out in one blast.
You with me, Ren?
‐ Yeah.
Ayano?
Yeah.
So I guess this could
be the last time
I ever see your face, huh?
Hm?
You got anything you want to
tell me, before we, you know,
die?
How about you cook
me a meal after this?
And I'll tell you then?
I'd rather die.
Suit yourself.
Get ready.
Hear me, spirits of the wind.
In the name of the contract,
entrust me with you power.
Tsui‐Ling.
Kazuma.
In the name of stars and
wisdom, let my words be heard.
I pursue only the truth.
Erwin, just let her go.
Please, let Tsui‐Ling go.
Was I really put on this Earth
just to be eaten by a demon?
Is this really how my
life is supposed to end?
Kazuma.
No, Tsui‐Ling.
Don't leave me.
I could have saved her.
I could have stopped them
if I'd had my powers then.
But I didn't.
And there's nothing I
can do about that now.
I can't change the past.
But I know I can
protect the future.
We can do this.
Enraiha, come forth.
Here it comes.
Just a few more seconds.
Now, fight with
everything you've got.
It is extraordinary
how genuinely fearsome
the Kannagi bloodline is.
You were able to prevent
for summoning of Belial.
That should be
humanly impossible.
I figured a coward like
you would've hauled ass
out of the country by now.
Did you really
think I would pass
up the opportunity to
witness Belial lay waste
to an entire city?
Yeah, well, sorry
to disappoint you.
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): This is bad.
None of us has the
energy to take him on.
You have nothing
to worry about.
I have no desire to try
and fight you right now.
And I've never been one
to bet against the odds.
I'd prefer a fight
that I know I'll win.
And this doesn't look
to be in my favor.
KAZUMA: What's the
old man doing here?
I can feel that he's just
as powerful as you are,
contractor.
It is remarkable.
The Kannagi family
truly is a great force
to be reckoned with.
Well, sorry to cut this short.
But I really must
be leaving now.
Although, you shouldn't worry.
I do have the feeling we'll see
each other again sometime soon,
Kazuma Yugami.
Wait.
Just tell me what the last
emotion was that Tsui‐Ling
felt before she died.
Please, I need to know.
What did she want to tell me?
It's all right.
Go ahead.
Very well, master.
Her last thought was that
she wished you were dead.
I think we should
go now, Lapis.
Well, then, have a nice day.
Kazuma.
I'm sorry.
You know she was lying, right?
She only said that to try
and mess with your head.
There's no way Tsui‐Ling
wanted to kill you.
I just can't believe that
was her last thought.
Well, it could have been.
I lied to her, you know?
I told her that I'd
always protect her.
Then, I couldn't
even save her life.
She probably
resented me for that.
But it's not your
fault. You hadn't even
awakened to your powers yet.
So you couldn't do
anything to stop them.
I guess you're right.
Strange thing is, I
awakened to my power right
after she died, when
they tried to kill me.
It's common for that to
happen when you're in danger.
That's not strange.
But nothing happened
when she was in danger.
Why didn't I wake up then?
Maybe I should let her do it.
Maybe that's what I deserve.
I don't know what
you're saying, Kazuma.
And I hope I'm wrong.
But it sounds like you almost
want Lapis to kill you.
And what would that solve?
What is wrong with you, Kazuma?
What's it going to take to
make you realize that it's over
and you're here now?
Come on.
Will you calm down?
I've already realized that.
I have to live with my past.
But it won't control me.
Now, is the only
thing that matters.
And that's what I'm
going to protect.
And I swear, I'll
protect all of you.
What'd you do that for?
Jerk.
Did I ever ask
you to protect me?
Whatever happened to you in the
past is none of my business.
And I realize that, OK?
But I can tell that
you're in pain.
So you don't have to
try and hide it from me.
I mean, I'm strong enough
to be here for you.
You don't always have
to deal with everything
all by yourself.
Am I so unreliable that
you can't even trust me?
What do you think of me anyway?
Am I just a burden to you?
A helpless little girl?
Do you just want me to hide
somewhere while you swoop in
and save the day
then, gratefully
kiss you on the cheek
once the danger's clear.
Listen.
Quit treating me like
I can't do anything,
when I know that I really can.
[CRYING]
Well, I'm glad you've
got my back, partner.
Kazuma.
Whoa.
Ayano, that was
totally an accident.
Can't we just talk
about this peacefully?
Oh, boy.
[SCREAMING]
KAZUMA: Hey, calm down.
She'll burn down the
house one of these days.
Sorry about the noise.
She tends to get a
little carried away.
It's OK.
We're kind of used to it by now.
That's what makes her Ayano.
I kind of feel sorry
for Kazuma though.
Yeah.
I know what you mean.
I guess it's good
they get along so well.
Just look at him go.
Yeah.
So shouldn't we try to
stop him or something?
Oh, whatever, Tatsuya.
They'll totally be all right.
Do they always act like this?
Well, not always.
Just most of the time.
AYANO: I'm never
going to forgive you.
Come back here, Kazuma.
You're going to
get it this time.
[SINGING JAPANESE]