NARRATOR: Eyes as
blue as the azure sky.
That is the symbol
of the contractor.
Entrusted by the spirit
king of the wind,
with the powers of his domain.
I bear this mark.
The stigma of the wind.
[THEME MUSIC]
Enraiha!
Come forth!
Spirits of fire, please grant me
your power and guide my sword.
[YELLING]
Hmm.
I guess he couldn't
stand the heat.
Hey guys, I didn't mean
to keep you waiting.
That didn't take long, Ayano.
Did everything go OK?
Yep.
There's just a little less
evil now, thanks to me.
Great, why don't we go
celebrate with some karaoke?
Again, Yukari?
You're obsessed.
Look who's talking, Nanase.
Well, it is fun and all.
But we're so close to the beach.
Let's enjoy the ocean wind.
YUKARI: Yeah, that sounds
like an awesome idea
NANASE: Then we'll go do
karaoke after that, OK?
The ocean wind, huh?
Oh, yeah.
Give me a break.
I hate the wind!
We've been expecting
you, Mr. Yagami.
This way, please.
What the‐‐
Kazuma?
It is you.
Why are you here?
Wait a minute, don't tell me.
You're the other
person Mr. Sakamoto
hired to exorcise his house?
You've got to be kidding.
So who gave you permission
to come back to Japan?
No one.
I was never kicked out
of the country, genius.
Not that it's your business.
Shinji, you know
Mr. Yagami, then?
Yeah, but Yagami
is not his real name.
This is Kazuma Kannagi, the
black sheep and disgrace
of the Kannagi family.
I missed you too.
Thanks, cousin.
Why are you here?
Trying to worm your way back in?
I'd rather burn in hell.
I can arrange that, loser.
Gentlemen, please.
Stop this bickering at once.
I don't care who you
are as long as you can
rid of my house of this ghost.
But please, keep in
mind my antiques here
are very valuable‐‐ worth far
more than what I'm paying you.
I'd ask that you use your
powers with discretion.
Don't worry, sir.
Now pay attention, you idiot.
You're about to see a master
of fire magic at work.
Yeah, where is he?
A branch family
punk's all I see.
Wha‐‐ you bastard,
what'd you say?
Heads up.
It's time to go to work.
[GROWLING]
You picked the wrong house.
Now eat this!
Oh, no.
[LAUGHING]
[EXPLOSION]
That's not a ghost, you idiot.
It's a youma.
Please, save me!
I'll pay double what I
promise you, I swear!
If that's all, you don't
put much value on your life.
I'll make it ten times, then.
No, 50!
Have a nice day.
100 times!
So you do want to live, huh?
[GROWLING]
Well, I'm done.
You've got three days
to get me the money.
OK.
Don't you have any respect?
I don't know what
happened between you two,
but to kick a dead
man just isn't right.
He's not dead.
Hey, how long are you going
to pretend to be unconscious?
But how?
The Kannagis are a
family of fire magic users.
They can summon and
control fire at will.
Every Kannagi is protected
by the spirits of fire,
so even a member of a branch
family like this moron
here can't be hurt by flame.
No way.
You used wind magic?
Sure did.
I am the black sheep, remember?
Look I'm sorry,
but I can't stay.
I really have to go, all right?
See you later!
Now I feel kind of bad.
Maybe we shouldn't have
kept her out this late.
What, are you crazy?
It's not even eight o'clock yet.
But you know how strict
Ayano's family can be.
Yeah, she's kind of
unlucky in that department.
I guess with all their
history and traditions,
it can't be easy
being the eldest
daughter of the Kannagi family.
This is bad.
Really bad!
I'm two hours past curfew!
If father finds out,
I don't even want
to think about what he'll do.
Ayano!
Aah!
I'm sorry father!
I wasn't just hanging out!
I was at the library
and lost track of time.
Please forgive me!
Why'd you call me father?
Ren.
You really scared me.
What's going on?
He's come back.
After all this
time, he's returned.
Who do you mean?
Who else?
My big brother?
Huh, yeah, I don't remember
you ever having a big brother.
That's mean.
You've really forgotten him?
Hey, wait, I bet this
will jog your memory.
He fought you for Enraiha, at
the ceremony of inheritance.
Enraiha.
Oh, now I remember.
He was the guy I knocked
out with a single blast
of my magic.
But it was so fast it wasn't
much of a fight, you know?
Do you have to be so
mean my brother, Ayano?
[CRYING]
So, then.
He defeated the youma
with wind magic.
Shinji Yuuki, you have
brought shame upon our family.
You will double your
training and I expect
you to act more professionally.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
Forgive me, Master Jugo.
Cousin Genma.
Now, raise your head.
There's no need to
be so formal here.
Father, did you‐‐
Hey, father.
Cousin Genma, I didn't
know you were here.
You would have if you
hadn't missed your curfew.
Unbelievable.
He's using wind magic?
We've heard the rumors
but had written them
off as just that until now.
So what you're telling
me is that my second cousin
Kazuma Kannagi, who left
home four years ago, is back?
Mm.
Are you serious?
A member of the Kannagi
family has actually trained
himself to use wind magic?
I can't believe that.
It's just so‐‐
It's embarrassing
and shameful.
I pity him, despite myself.
He's not had an
easy path in life.
If only he hadn't been born
into the Kannagi family,
he wouldn't have anything
to be ashamed of.
But he was, and he didn't have
the ability to control fire.
The Kannagi family
has been practicing
the sacred art of fire magic
for countless generations.
It has no place for those
who can't master it.
Genma.
Therefore, Kazuma no longer
has any connection to us
at all.
And as far as I'm concerned,
I have but one son, Ren.
Father.
Perhaps it's for the best.
Wind magic may allow Kazuma
to achieve true happiness.
Do you think that he could
ever be a member of our family
again?
[WIND HOWLING]
Guess there's a storm coming.
Forgive me, Please!
That is you, isn't it Kazuma?
I'm sorry that I didn't
help you out back then.
I'm so sorry!
Please, forgive me!
[SCREAMING]
You're supposed to
be the heir to the head
of the Kannagi family!
This is pathetic.
You've shamed me
for the last time.
Now, leave!
Well, so much for thinking
I've gotten over that.
What was it, Hyoue?
Due to the severity of
the cuts on their bodies,
I've concluded that they
were killed by wind magic.
Not only that, but a type
far more powerful than we
in the Fuga Clan use.
It would seem so.
Shinji Yuuki, Masato
Agami, Takeshi Agami.
They might have
been branch family
members, but to think someone
could kill them so easily is‐‐
Unbelievable?
I'm afraid it's much
worse than that.
It's humiliating for them to
be defeated by a magic user.
Sorry, Hyoue.
I hope you'll forgive me.
Yes.
We of the Fuga Clan have lived
only to serve the Kannagi
family for generations, sir.
Who would attacks
us like this?
It's Kazuma.
How much more
evidence do we need.
Well, it does look
like a grudge slaying,
and the killer used wind magic.
So, I'm going to have
to agree with you
that he would fit the bill.
If you asked me, he
murdered them out of revenge
for getting kicked out.
It wasn't their
fault he got disowned.
It was his for being weak.
Power is everything
in this family.
He should know that.
Oh, gee, you really think so?
Damn that guy.
He'll pay for what he did.
My brother Shinji's death
will be avenged, I swear it.
Father, everyone's
saying that Kazuma
is responsible for the murders.
Now that he's
acquired wind magic,
they think he's using his powers
to take revenge on the family.
If it's true and he is the
one who murdered those boys,
you may be certain
that he will pay.
Please let me.
I'll destroy him.
Ayano.
When will you learn that
every problem in life cannot
be solved by using force?
You will lead this family one
day, so you mustn't act rashly.
I can't sit back
and do nothing!
But that is exactly
what you're going to do.
We don't yet have any
proof of his guilt.
You'll take no action until
further orders, is that clear?
I understand.
Why must she be so impetuous?
So, I'm being followed.
But not by the same person
I sensed at the hotel
this morning.
The aura is different.
But there's something
familiar about it.
Your people have
located Kazuma?
Yes.
The Fuga Clan's
expertise at tracking never
ceases to amaze me.
Send word that we must
meet with him at once.
He might even agree to
come here willingly.
I hope.
And what if he refuses to?
Do we have your permission
to bring him back by force?
Certainly.
Decide who you want to send.
Very well.
I know two people who will
be perfect for the job.
[LAUGHING]
Shingo, Takia?
Don't tell my father
about this, OK?
He doesn't need to know.
What, are you kidding me?
If Master Jugo ever
finds out, we're the ones
who will be in trouble.
Oh, I wouldn't even
worry about that.
You two are the most powerful
members of the branch families.
My father trusts you way
more than he trusts me.
Seriously, he'll
never suspect a thing.
I hope.
You know, there is
a reason we agreed
to bring you along with us.
Purely selfish, of course,
but we've always wanted to see
the famous Ayano in action.
Oh, yeah?
Wow.
I'm totally serious.
Right, Shingo?
Sorry Ayano,
but tonight I have
to ask you not to do anything.
Huh?
If anyone kills that bastard
Kazuma tonight, it'll be me.
No, you can't.
Father said he has to hear
his side of the story first.
Fine.
I'll just burn his
arms and legs off then.
'Sides, he'll be a
lot easier to carry
back to the compound that way.
Oh, yeah.
Um, whatever you say.
According to our spies, he's
only one block ahead of us.
Right.
What's going on?
Hey, where'd Ayano go?
There he is.
Kazuma!
You murdering son of a bitch!
You killed him!
It's been quite a while.
Remember us?
Yeah, the heirs to
the branch families.
You know why
we're here, right?
Nope, don't have a clue.
Last night, three
Kannagi branch
family members were killed.
Yeah, and?
The cause of their death‐‐
it was wind magic.
All right, I know
what'll get rid of this.
Enraiha, come forth!
It wasn't me.
We're done here.
No, we're not.
Master Jugo has requested
to speak with you in person.
If he wanted to talk, he
should've come here himself.
I'm not at his beck
and call anymore.
Tell him I said that.
[EXPLOSION]
So, it's the Fuga Clan
that's been trailing me.
This is your last chance.
Come with us quietly
or else, Kazuma.
Would it kill
you to say please?
Bastard!
Die!
What in the‐‐ what
in the hell did you do?
Just a little trick I learned.
You Kannagis think
you're invincible.
You're immune to the
heat from an explosion,
but its impact is another story.
How did someone sneak up on me?
That was wind magic.
[LAUGHING]
What is going on here?
Spirits of the wind!
What the hell is wrong with you?
That's a breach of our contract.
Great, now what?
Enraiha.
Ayano?
Is that you?
Kazuma.
Kazuma!
Hold on, it's not
what it looks like.
I didn't kill them, I swear.
You'll pay for this!
Hear me out, would you?
Wow, look at you.
You really have grown up.
Flattery will get you
nowhere, you murderer!
You have no idea who you're
messing with, Kazuma.
Actually, I do.
You inherited the Enraiha,
so you're the next head
of the Kannagi family.
I said I didn't do it.
Do you really think I'm gonna
believe a word you're saying?
That's up to you.
I don't care if you
believe me or not.
Somebody killed them.
So if you didn't, then who did?
Some other wind magic user.
You'll have to find out
the rest on your own.
But I'll be honest with you.
Based on what you've
shown me tonight,
I don't have much hope of that.
Some future head of
the family you are.
You've got to be kidding.
You're the last person that
should be talking about family.
Come on.
A Kannagi that
practices wind magic?
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Not really.
I'd love to stay and
chat, but I've got to go.
We'll have to continue
this another time.
Hey, wait a minute!
I won't forgive him.
Not now, not ever.
Kazuma!
Guess I'm in an all out war
with the Kannagi family now.
Could be fun.
But I don't want
to be manipulated
by whoever is behind the
curtain pulling the strings.
One thing's for sure, it's
going to be interesting.
AYANO: What?
You can't be serious.
This is all Kazuma's
fault, so why am
I the one who's being grounded?
It's not fair!
Cousin Genma, I hope you show
that ungrateful excuse of a son
of yours why it's
unwise for him to mess
with the Kannagi family.
No way, he wouldn't be
willing to go that far
to get his revenge, would he?
That's crazy.
Next time on Kaze no Stigma,
confrontation with the past.
Don't ever underestimate
my powers, Kazuma.