MAN (VOICEOVER): Gonzo.
VOICES (VOICEOVER): Funimation.
You should be watching.
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): Eyes
as blue as the Azure sky.
That is the symbol
of the Contractor.
Entrusted by the
Spirit King of the Wind
with the powers of his domain.
I bear this mark.
The stigma of the wind.
[THEME MUSIC]
It can't be her.
TSUI‐LING: Was I really
put on this Earth just
to be eaten by a demon?
Kazuma?
Wait!
Kazuma!
Where are you going?
Come back here.
Tsui‐Ling.
This is so wonderful.
What's next on the
agenda now, Ren?
Shopping, maybe?
Karaoke?
Or should we just skip all that
and go straight to my room?
Just kidding!
Sorry.
I got a little carried away.
You know what, Kanon?
It's kinda hard for
me to walk like this.
Yeah, you heard him.
He doesn't want you
around, all right?
What?
He never said that.
Come on, Ren.
Why don't we ditch this leech?
Let's hit the arcade.
You've got a lot of nerve
calling me that, you gorilla!
You're just a partially
evolved neanderthal.
Hey.
Shut up.
I am not.
All right.
No more fighting, you two.
Come on, now.
I've been looking
everywhere for you, Kanon.
You didn't forget about our
date to the karaoke bar, right?
You did promise.
Are you delusional, Tekashi?
How do you misunderstand
the word no?
TEKASHI: Come on.
Quit joking around.
We really should get going
before it gets too late.
Well, what do you knew, Ren?
Looks to me like she's already
made a date with this guy.
She works pretty fast, huh?
Let's get out of here.
[SCREAMING]
Tatsuya!
You OK?
Now, listen closely.
I will never go out with you.
Have I made myself
perfectly clear?
[CHUCKLE] You're
playing hard to get.
‐ What?
‐ It's OK.
I get it.
You're just too proud to
admit you like someone
without making them sweat it.
But you don't even
have to admit it to me
if you don't feel like
it, because I already
know you like me, Kanon.
Hands off, you jerk.
All right, Tekashi.
Just leave her alone, OK?
I think she's had enough,
so stop bothering my friend.
Oh, Ren.
You're so sweet.
What the hell
is with this guy?
Stay out of this, pretty boy,
unless you want me to ruin
those good looks for you.
KANON: Don't you
ever threaten him!
Ren is twice the man that you
could ever dream of being.
TATSUYA: Ren's my best friend
and I would kill for him!
So go ahead and insult him
again, and see what I do.
Wow, you guys.
Thank you.
What do you know?
Guess there is something we
can agree on, you gorilla.
Yeah.
And maybe you're not
so bad after all.
You know, for a
blood sucking leech.
You're gonna pay for that.
You hear me?
Ren?
That was freaking awesome, man.
You stepped in to protect me.
Oh, Ren.
You're so amazing.
REN: Sorry, but you can't go
around hitting girls like that.
You.
You're not gonna
get away with this.
You're gonna regret it.
I'm gonna tell my
big brother on you.
He could kill you
in a split second.
All of you.
He's got super powers, and
he'll make you pay for this.
Hm?
Did you just say super powers?
[LAUGHING]
KANON: You're an even bigger
nerd than I thought you were.
Go on and make fun of me.
You're only gonna make it worse.
We'll see who the nerd is after
I tell them what you've done.
KANON: Come on, Ren.
Let's go.
Yeah, sure.
TEKASHI: I swear
you're gonna pay.
You'll be sorry when
he's done with you!
YUKARI: The girls at school
are a lot more comfortable now
that we've got Utsumi
locked behind bars,
and it's all thanks
to you, Nanase.
NANASE: It was nothing.
So now the only thing
left is for the police
to figure out how
he got his powers,
and we can finally
close this case.
Yukari.
You're not seriously gonna help
Detective Tachibana, are you?
YUKARI: Yeah.
What's wrong, Ayano?
You look a little upset.
I'm just kinda worried.
I mean, aren't
you scared at all?
And those people
you'll be dealing with.
Every one of them has
magical powers and abilities.
You know?
You don't really have too much
room to talk on that subject,
do you, Ayano?
AYANO: I guess I am like them.
Hey, wait a minute.
After all, I was
born with the power
to take a person's
life in a split second.
I can't really hold it against
people for being afraid of me.
I understand it.
Really.
So you guys don't have to
force yourselves to hang out
with me or anything, you know.
Honestly, it won't
hurt my feelings if you
don't wanna be around me.
NANASE: We're your friends.
Of course we wanna
be around you.
I like you more
than anybody I know.
Because you're a good person
and you actually help people.
Yeah, you have magical
powers, but you
don't use them to hurt anybody.
You use them for good.
Don't compare yourself
to people like Utsumi,
because you're
nothing like them.
Both of us will always
trust you with our lives,
and you know that.
Mhm.
It's insulting to even put you
in the same category with them.
Thanks, guys.
I wanna help
you with this case
because we're best friends,
and I'm happy to do
anything I can for you.
Yeah.
And that makes two of us.
So don't ever hesitate to
call on me for help anytime.
All right?
AYANO (VOICEOVER):
I'm really lucky.
They're so special to me.
I couldn't have better friends.
CATHERINE: Quit running from me!
If you don't wanna chase
me, then you better be
ready to fight me in a battle!
I deplore violence, but
you are certainly testing
the limits of my restraint!
Miracle Smiling Star Fly!
Smiling stars?
Really?
I've never seen that type
of magic used before.
All right.
Do you wanna tell
me who you are?
I guess I can give you the
pleasure of an introduction.
Before I defeat you, that is.
I'm the next It Girl everybody's
gonna be talking about!
Miracle C!
No matter how
hard I try, there
are just some things about this
country I'll never understand.
AYANO: Catherine!
Just what do you
think you're doing?
Were you following me, Ayano?
For your sake, you better
not be the one that's
causing all these incidents!
How dare you?
I ought to arrest you
for speaking to a police
officer so disrespectfully.
Police officer?
You heard me.
Detective Tachibana recruited
me for my expertise.
I could never refuse
a desperate request
when my services are
needed, so I'm officially
a member of Tokyo's finest.
Ah!
There's no way.
The shadowy evil
of this city will
soon cower before the name of
the virtuous McDonald family.
And this works out
for me as well,
since it legally qualifies
me to obtain my work visa
so I don't ever have to leave.
[CACKLING]
This can't be happening.
I know that the special
unit is really understaffed
right now, but seriously.
This is ridiculous.
MIRACLE C: Hello!
Did you forget that you're
in the middle of a battle
right now?
Do not ignore me!
Fine.
Oh, great.
I guess she's a player too.
I hope she's not trying
to steal my thunder.
Well, I can only assume that
you're the girl who's been
terrorizing this neighborhood.
Now, I want you to explain to
me how you acquired your powers.
How I acquired them?
You mean to tell me
you two didn't get
your powers from Pandemonium?
AYANO (VOICEOVER): Pandemonium?
Well, doesn't matter to me.
I'm just happy to
have the chance
to duke it out with a couple
of female players for a change.
It's a rare thing.
Unfortunately for
the two of you,
there can only be one
heroine in this game!
And that would be me!
Miracle C!
Eternal Shooting Star, attack!
Uh oh.
Ah!
So, game over, then?
That was my silly
encounter of the week.
You can't hide that
much inexperience
beneath a skimpy costume.
She said she got her
powers from something
called Pandemonium.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello.
Indeed.
I've just apprehended the area's
most notorious troublemaker.
Please.
I didn't even come close
to breaking a sweat.
[LAUGHING]
Kazuma did what?
I see.
Sure.
I'll be there right away
with the perpetrator.
What happened to Kazuma?
It's official police business.
I really shouldn't tell you.
Don't blow me off!
Sorry, but I have
too much work to chat.
Do have a lovely evening.
Wait!
Come on!
Catherine!
[PHONE RINGING]
What's up, Kirika?
KIRIKA (ON PHONE):
What's up with me?
What's up with you?
I've been trying to
reach you for hours.
Is everything OK?
Where are you?
I'm not sure where I am.
KIRIKA (ON PHONE):
Kazuma, come on.
You gotta pull
yourself together.
You realize you let that
Hellhound guy escape, right?
I know.
All right.
Let's just regroup.
We'll meet at the Kannagi
mansion in 30 minutes.
Ayano's agreed to
help us, so we'll
fill her in on all the details.
OK?
See you soon.
What the hell is going on?
I gotta say, you were
pretty awesome earlier, Ren.
Have you been taking martial
arts lessons or something?
Uh.
Uh, no.
I don't even know
what came over me.
I do.
It was love.
The power of lo‐‐
Follow us, kids.
We got something for you.
[WICKED LAUGHTER]
Well, it doesn't look
like you're gonna
walk away from me this time.
My brother's gonna make you
pay for what you did to me.
Yeah.
You're dead meat.
All of you.
Hold on.
It's just you?
I was actually worried
for a minute there.
KANON: Oh man.
What a waste of time.
We could've been eating already.
What?
Hey, I'm serious, dammit.
Chill out, Tekashi.
I'll take it from here.
TEKASHI: You guys
are in trouble now.
Don't hold back on
your super powers.
Destroy them!
Show no mercy.
KIYOSHI: Yeah, I got it.
You can apologize to my
brother in your next life.
What?
Is he really doing that?
TEKASHI: Awesome.
Kiyoshi calls that
one the Firebird.
Yeah, Kiyoshi.
Do a big one, man.
Come on.
Incinerate them.
Enough, already.
Shut up and watch how it's done.
Firebird!
How did you do that?
REN: Are you crazy or something?
What do you think you're doing,
using your magic in public?
And you're trying to use
it against innocent people?
How can you even call
yourself a magic user?
KIYOSHI: What?
Whoever said I did?
And I would've hit
you harder if I'd
known you were a player too.
But now that I do know,
I'll pad my experience
points by kicking your ass.
Phoenix Wing!
Heh.
You gotta be kidding.
You really think
that could stop me?
Hate to burst your
bubble, but you're dealing
with a fire master here, kid.
REN (VOICEOVER): A yoma's
gotten a hold of him.
The guy doesn't even
realize he's been possessed.
He's just thinks he's
some kind of super hero.
Kiyoshi.
I didn't think anyone could
deflect your Phoenix Wing.
You're right.
He'd have to be ranked as high
as I am to block that move.
I guess that means
Vesalius was lying
to me when he said
I was the highest
ranking flame enabled player.
I'll just have to
defend my title.
REN (VOICEOVER): Vesalius?
He must be the one who
cursed him with the yoma.
There's only room in this
city for one fire master,
and that's me!
Flame Vortex!
Try my purifying flame.
Heh.
Almost had me there.
But now, you're dead meat!
Flame Vortex!
Am I out of points?
All right.
Fire Bird!
Uh.
Come on.
Please work.
REN: It won't.
Your magic's gone.
I erased it when I destroyed
the evil spirit possessing you.
Just accept it, all right?
The game is over.
Welcome back to reality.
Hey, wait.
Come back.
Please don't leave me here.
[WHIMPERING]
Please don't kill me.
TATSUYA: Uh, Ren.
Ren.
You‐‐
How did you‐‐
what was that?
Oh yeah.
That was‐‐
So awesome!
Oh, Ren!
That was so cool.
You're amazing, man.
I've always had a
feeling there was
something special about you.
That has to be the coolest
thing I've ever seen.
You sure know how to
make a girl fall for you.
Heh.
All right.
All right, you guys.
Try not to get too excited, OK?
Let's have a talk.
And why don't you
start by telling
me where you got your powers?
So what's Pandemonium?
All I know is
that it's a website.
I found it one night when
I was up surfing the net.
There was hardly
anything on the page.
Just a question.
As soon as I clicked it,
the screen turned white,
and I guess I blacked out.
And when I woke
up, somehow I just
knew I'd been given powers.
The only logical
explanation is
that the website must emulate
the yoma summoning ritual.
By clicking Yes,
you're signing over
the contract for your soul,
and without even realizing it.
REN: So after you've
signed the contract,
the yoma must somehow download
directly into your body
from the internet.
KANON: So how'd you
even find the website?
Off a search engine
or something?
You can't, all right?
I got disconnected while I was
passed out, and when I woke up,
I couldn't remember
how to find it.
No matter how much
I've searched,
never come across it again.
As far as I know, nobody
can get to Pandemonium twice.
At least that's what
everyone's saying.
CATHERINE: Everyone?
There's an online
message board
where players post their
stats or challenge each other.
It's mostly just people
bragging about their powers,
but it's where you make
your battle appointments.
Appointments?
Explain.
You gain experience points
from battling other players,
and if you get
enough, you can move
up to a higher skill level.
Once you move up,
Pandemonium sends
you an email to let you know.
But from the rumors
I've heard, things
get really interesting when
you reach the highest level.
When that happens, you
get a personal invitation
to physically go to Pandemonium.
And you're saying that
you've actually been there?
Not to the website, but
to Pandemonium itself?
KIYOSHI: Yeah.
The email didn't even
give specific directions.
Just said to go for a walk.
And the next thing I knew, I was
standing in front of a mansion
with a sign that said
Pandemonium on it.
TATSUYA: What the hell?
KANON: Are you sure you
didn't just dream this?
It happened, all right?
That's how I got the power
to become a fire master
from this guy named Vesalius.
He actually gave
it to me in person.
VESALIUS: Welcome
to Pandemonium.
You've been chosen
for your strength.
Your power has
developed impressively,
and I believe you're ready
to advance to the next level.
Do you wish to become a master?
I remember looking out
on the entire city, almost
like we were
hovering in the air.
TATSUYA: Like you
were on a helicopter
or a plane or something?
Uh‐uh.
Because we weren't
moving at all.
And there were‐‐
I‐‐ I think I remember
that there were
two towers next to the mansion.
What kind of towers?
I don't know.
I can't really remember
what they looked like.
I just know the mansion
was in between them.
Were they attached
to the mansion?
Like it was all part
of the same building?
AYANO: Detective Tachibana.
KIRIKA: Oh, Ayano.
Were you waiting
out here for me?
I wanna know what's
going on with Kazuma.
We'll talk about it inside.
Hm?
There's nothing there.
KANON: Don't be stupid.
They're obviously gonna hide
it with some kind of magic.
If they didn't, then
all of the players
would storm the mansion
demanding more power.
It'd be like a
magical nerd riot.
TATSUYA: Oh, yeah.
I guess you're right.
So what do we do, Ren?
I really wish
Kazuma were here.
He can find anything,
no matter how much
magic they use to cloak it.
KANON: So your brother
has powers too?
I guess that makes sense.
TATSUYA: Well, maybe we
should come back with him.
Good idea.
I'm starving anyway.
Let's get something to eat
and worry about this later.
OK, Ren?
I'm not sure if
this will work,
but if they're hiding the
mansion behind a veil of magic,
then I should be
able to burn it away.
KANON: Whoa!
Did you see that?
All right.
Something tells me we need
to get out of here now.
VESALIUS (VOICEOVER): Not
the most polite way to knock,
but you did get my attention.
Ren?
TATSUYA: What the?
We only turned our
backs for a second.
Where did he go?
KANON: He was right there!
Ren!
How could he
disappear like that?
TATSUYA: What?
I‐‐ I have no idea.
Ren.
Where are you?
Ren!
[THEME MUSIC]
AYANO (VOICEOVER):
I can't believe
someone would infect the
public by distributing
yoma on the internet.
Who would do
something like that?
Don't worry.
I swear on my life,
I'll rescue Ren.
And Kazuma won't let anything
happen to him either.
So this is the Pandemonium that
everyone won't shut up about.
And you must be Vesalius.
Next time on "Kaze no
Stigma," Pandemonium.
Stop messing around
and get to it.