ANNOUNCER: Gonzo.
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
VOICES: Funimation (WHISPERING)
You should be watching.
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): Eyes as
blue as the azure sky, that
is the symbol of the
Contractor, entrusted
by the Spirit King of the Wind
with the powers of his domain.
I bear this mark, the
Stigma of the Wind.
[THEME MUSIC]
THEME SONG: A blast
of wind in my heart‐‐
ah‐‐ ah‐‐ ah‐ ah‐‐
ah‐‐ ah.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
Did I say that
you could leave?
In the name of the MacDonald
family, I command you to stop.
Surrender now and I
will let you live.
You'll let me live?
Megatron, attack.
Nooo!
Tsui‐Ling, she meant
everything to Kazuma.
And she‐‐ she still has
a hold of his heart.
If you do face
that girl again,
you have to defeat
her this time.
Huh?
Please, there's
no one else, Ayano.
It's up to you.
You have to stop
him or no one will.
There's no way.
I just‐‐ I can't beat her.
It's impossible.
It doesn't make sense.
I can't believe
Kazuma helped Utsumi.
I don't get it.
Why would he kidnap Nanase?
If he follows Utsumi,
then he might find
a way to the New Pandemonium.
We feel confident
that is his motive.
Then I guess all the work
I've done is pointless.
I was hoping to pinpoint
Kazuma's location
by identifying potential
areas where the seeds
might show up to battle.
Right.
No, wait.
That might prove useful.
You think?
There's no evidence
Kazuma's found the location
of Pandemonium yet.
If he hasn't found it, he would
continue hunting the seeds.
And we need to know
where we can find him.
I can't keep
letting this happen.
This rampage has
to come to an end.
Kazuma‐‐
Kazuma.
Who's there?
[LAUGHTER]
Hey, Tatsuya and
Kanon, what are you‐‐
Well, well, what a
coincidence that you're here.
Wow.
Ren, what are
you doing out here?
What about you?
What are you two doing here?
Don't you know that the park is
off limits after it gets dark?
We were just worried.
Sorry.
At school you look
so sad, like you
were depressed about something.
And you had the most
pathetic look on your face.
Mm hm.
We're friends, aren't we?
If you need anything,
you just let me know.
Yeah, right.
Tell me, not this ape.
We're friends.
You're not.
Am too.
‐ Are not.
‐ Am too.
Are not.
I am too.
I'm his best friend.
No, I'm his best friend.
He likes me way better
than you, you big fat idiot.
Thanks a lot, guys.
You jerk.
And I'm really sorry
that I worried you.
But look, it's really dangerous
here this time of night.
Thank you for your
concern, but‐‐
Are you ready to be
destroyed, wind magic user?
[LAUGHS] And after
I've defeated you,
I'll be loaded with
experience points.
Then I'll finally
become the master.
[LAUGHS] Aaaaaa!
No, please.
Brother, what
are you doing here?
I tried to call.
I looked for you.
Damn it.
Is that really all you've got?
You will never defeat me.
[PAINFUL SCREAM]
Kazuma, let him go.
There's no point
in torturing him.
He can't defend himself anymore.
Stop it.
Stay out of my way.
[PAINFUL SCREAM]
Kazuma, no.
Hey, what are you doing?
Let me go.
I have to stop him.
I don't think that talking
is going to work on him, Ren.
If worse comes to worse,
he'll turn on you too.
I don't understand.
It's like he wasn't
even himself.
It's scary.
How does something
like that happen?
How does a person change
like that all of a sudden?
Kazuma, no.
[CHATTER IN JAPANESE]
We've looked everywhere for
Kazuma, but we can't find him.
I see.
Well, I guess Kazuma
hasn't found Pandemonium.
He's hunting the seeds.
He must still be trying to get
information about its location.
Don't you think that's
a little bit unusual?
Huh?
Remember, this isn't
how he hunts them.
He usually attacks the
seeds during a big battle.
But Ren said this
fight was different.
He says all he saw
was Kazuma battling
against one other seed.
What are you saying?
It just doesn't
make any sense to me.
Why was that man even here?
Why?
Why was he here alone?
It looks like interrogating
him is out of the question.
Isn't it?
Your big brother, he was like
a completely different person.
Those eyes‐‐
I swear, they
scared me to death.
Ren couldn't reach him.
Kazuma threatened
his own brother.
If Ren can't stop
him, then no one can.
It's over.
It's hopeless.
We've got to end this.
We don't have a choice.
We have to do this.
You can't be serious.
No, it's not safe.
It's too dangerous.
So what.
Look, if not us, then who?
I know how he feels.
I know what it's like.
It's horrible to lose someone
you love more than anything
else in the world.
And if somebody used that
person for their own advantage,
I wouldn't want to
forgive them either.
This must be about Ayumi.
But being hurt doesn't make
you right, because you can't
let the past hold you down.
Look, I just want my brother.
I want him back
to his normal self
again, no matter how
much he Tsui‐Ling.
I swear I'll bring him back.
I will do whatever I have to do.
Ren.
I swear.
No matter what happens,
I'll never stop fighting.
[SIGHS] Oh yeah.
Bingo.
I found a clue.
Yes!
Guess what, Ayano.
It looks like you're
not the only one
who gets to help rescue Nanase.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Ren, just promise me you
won't do anything too crazy.
Call us any time, especially
if something happens.
Thanks so much, guys.
Catherine, what's up?
That Ren, he's
really something.
He reminds me of his brother‐‐
the old version anyway.
I know.
I was moved by
his determination.
I wish I wasn't stuck in here.
I would go with him and
help bring Kazuma back.
This is so‐‐ it's so annoying.
Release Kazuma from the spell,
help him to forget the past?
I just can't.
How do I do it?
Are you all right?
I don't know what to do.
Kazuma only sees the past.
He has no interest
in the present.
How can I possibly save
him and bring him back?
Kirika said that he needed to
be reminded of why he changed
his ways in the first
place, that there
are things in the
present worth living for.
And she says I'm the only
one who can make him see it.
But I don't understand why I'm
the only person who can do it.
What does that mean?
Hey, wait a minute.
You're sure Kirika
said that to you?
You're positive?
Yeah, why?
Well, I just can't believe it.
Stupid woman.
So what does she think I am,
chopped liver or something?
What about me is so
inferior to her anyway?
Hey, Catherine, what
are you talking about?
Like you don't know
she picked you over me.
Don't play dumb.
Picked me?
What?
Give me a break.
Are you actually saying you
don't understand the meaning
of what she told you?
Are you joking right now?
No, I'm serious.
Right.
You, you, you,
thick‐headed idiot!
Just think about it.
Don't you understand?
No, I don't.
Well, why don't I spell
it out for you then?
When she said he needed to
remember what was worthwhile,
she meant you.
You're the reason he changed.
No, idiot, why in the world are
you telling her all this stuff?
You are supposed
to be her rival.
No, wait.
No, that's not‐‐
that‐‐ that can't‐‐
he doesn't think
of me like that.
And besides, he already
rejected his brother, so I‐‐
I‐‐ I couldn't.
I'd be out of the question.
Ayano, she's absolutely right.
Kirika.
You know, I thought
I made my point clear.
But I guess not.
You really are clueless,
aren't you, young lady?
Hey, I am not clueless.
[CHUCKLES] Listen,
I believe in you.
You can turn Kazuma
around and bring him back.
I've been watching it
grow for a long time.
Try to remember the bond that
the two of you built together.
It's the only hope we have.
The what?
Our bond, that's it.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Know what?
I think you might actually
turn out to be a damn fine
woman one of these days, kid.
Kazuma.
You should learn to
have more confidence.
I mean it.
You're more than
just a little girl.
You're an amazing woman.
And I know you're just
as good as Tsui‐Ling.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
This disguise is perfect.
I'm totally going to get
some awesome information.
[CHATTER]
MAN: Is that Vesalius?
It's Nanase.
But who's that guy?
Utsumi?
MAN: That's not Vesalius.
Who the hell are you?
You may call me
the grand mage.
Just like you, I have
special abilities.
You see, I have moved
to the fourth class.
MAN: What did he say?
That impossible.
How did you get
to be so powerful?
Now listen to me,
you chosen ones.
I'm impressed at how quickly
you responded to my call.
And now, I will read a
message from Vesalius himself.
I feel confident
you will be pleased.
(READING) "Tomorrow
at midnight, you
will witness the source of the
greatest power, Pandemonium,
as it descends to
the material world."
[CHEERS]
"And to celebrate, each of
you will have the opportunity
to obtain a gift.
I, Lord Vesalius,
do hereby announce
the beginning of the race of the
seeds, the race to Pandemonium.
The person who gets there
first wins the race.
And the winner will be
given the ultimate power,
and unmatched
invincible power that
can't be undone by anyone."
Ultimate power?
To be invincible.
I will win.
I know I can do it.
Hey, what's the deal here?
Where's Pandemonium going to be?
The place for the
descent is Central Park.
[CHEERS]
This is too good to be true.
I think I just hit the jackpot.
[GASP] It's her, Yukari.
Huh?
Oh, no.
[LAUGHS]
No, I don't understand.
What exactly do you mean?
All right, fine.
Just send it my way immediately.
Hey, Kirika, Yukari texted me.
Here, look.
What is this?
Pandemonium will descend.
The secret location
is Central Park.
Descent will take place
at midnight tomorrow.
And what does the beginning
of the race of the seeds mean?
Yukari sent this to you?
What's wrong with her?
What's she thinking?
She went by herself?
What a stupid thing to do.
Way to go, Yukari.
Hey, this is still
good information though.
It tells us everything
we wanted to know, right?
Like where Pandemonium
will descend.
Well, no.
Actually it isn't descending at
all because it's already there.
And it's been there the entire
time, right under our noses
in Central Park.
And that means Kazuma
probably knows about it too.
What makes you say that?
This is an email found on
the cell phone of the young man
of Kazuma assaulted earlier.
I just received it.
Kazuma?
You'll earn massive
experience points.
You just have to defeat
this wind magic user.
He's at Central Park.
What exactly does this mean?
Kazuma has been there
ever since the beginning,
when we lost her.
When Utsumi took Nanase.
He must have been
trailing Utsumi.
And that's when he
discovered the location
of the New Pandemonium.
Then Bernhardt probably
found out about it.
That's why he sent that young
man to fight him, just for fun.
Of course, he didn't
think the young man
stood a chance at all.
He was just provoking Kazuma
and laughing at his expense.
But I still don't get it.
Kazuma found
Pandemonium, didn't he?
So why hasn't he attacked yet?
I don't understand.
You see, Kazuma is waiting.
He's waiting for Bernhardt
to finish up the job.
Then Kazuma will
destroy everything
moments before he finishes it.
He'll take pleasure
in watching him fail.
He'll sit back and relish
in Bernhardt's despair
before he finally
finishes him off.
For Kazuma, that would
be the perfect revenge.
Kazuma.
Of course, he's not the
only one enjoying this.
Bernhardt loves watching
the drama unfold.
They're eating this up.
It's just a game.
They deal each other cards
of hatred and revenge.
They gamble on each other's
lives and their own.
It's a dark and twisted game.
And now, a new card
has been dealt,
and both players must
make their final move.
The descent of Pandamonium.
We don't have much time left.
All right.
I'll do it.
Kazuma has to be stopped.
Ayano.
Now look, I may not
completely understand
what I mean to Kazuma.
But I do know this much.
If there's even the
slightest chance that I'm
the key to bringing him
back, I have to do everything
I can no matter what.
And we can't afford to
wait around anymore.
So I swear on the
Kannagi's sacred flame,
I'll turn Kazuma around
and bring him back,
not to the past or
thoughts of Tsui‐Ling,
but right here with us.
Thank you, Ayano.
Oh, joy, Miss Kannagi
is here to save the day.
Just don't screw it up,
or I'll never forgive you.
So what are you
going to do now?
What?
Your strategy.
How exactly are you going to
rescue him from his own past?
Strategy?
Oh, great, please tell me
you at least have some idea
of what you're going to do.
Hey, it's under control.
Yeah, don't you worry about it.
I'm coming for you Kazuma.
Now, old friend, we end this.
I delivered the message
just as I was told.
The seeds will be gathering
down here soon enough.
That's good news, yes.
I want to let you know, I
have no intention of doing
any more errands for you.
Oh really?
But I still have
something I want
you to do for me, my friend.
No thanks.
You see, I don't need
to any more Vesalius.
I have the ultimate power.
And now I'm going to
take over this place.
Do you really think you
can actually defeat me?
Your power was a gift.
I gave it to you, and
I can take it away.
Feel free to try.
You're no longer my master.
Nanase.
Well, well, where do
you think you're going?
We're just getting started.
You don't want to
miss all the fun.
[CHUCKLES]
[THEME MUSIC]
THEME SONG:
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
AYANO: Can I be
completely honest?
I've always looked up to
you, from the very beginning.
It'd be great if I could
catch up with you one day
and earn your respect.
That's why I can't agree with
what you're doing right now.
I can't believe
I actually wanted
to be something so disgusting.
You know what?
I don't want your
approval anymore.
Next time on "Kaze no
Stigma," "The Crimson Flame."
Come on, now.
Wake up already.