ANNOUNCER: Gonzo.
Funimation.
You should be watching.
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): Eyes
as blue as the azure sky.
That is the symbol
of the contractor,
entrusted by the
spirit king of the wind
with the powers of his domain.
I bear this mark, the
stigma of the wind.
[THEME MUSIC]
Stressful job
straining your nerves?
Throw it.
Family friction rubs you wrong?
Broken heart broke your spirits?
Throw it.
Relax and throw
your worries away.
Come to Marunaga Hot Springs
and leave your troubles behind.
Just throw!
Here we are.
Throw it.
Relax.
‐ Wow.
It's even more incredible
than I thought it would be.
Oh yeah.
It's super popular right now.
That commercial correctly
brainwashes you to come here.
It's so great that you
invited us to come, Yukari.
I still can't believe
you won a deluxe vacation
package from a TV game show.
Yeah, I know.
I'm pretty awesome.
Now, which show was it again?
Huh?
Which show was it?
You never told me
what it was called.
Uh, well, it was‐‐
It was called
"Fabulous Hotsprings
from Around the World."
Isn't that what you said
it was called, Yukari?
Oh yeah, how could I forget?
Huh.
Never heard of it.
Doesn't really sound
like a game show.
[YAWNING]
I appreciate you both
coming to speak with me.
Well, sure, no problem.
So what did you wanna
talk to us about?
Because your Ayano's
closest friends I,
was hoping I might be able
to ask something of you.
Not just a favor, but
a truly urgent request.
There's nothing more important
to me, and I need help.
Don't you think it's weird
that her father made up
this whole story
about you winning
this trip just as an excuse for
us to invite Ayano and Kazuma?
Hey, don't question it.
Who cares what he's up to?
I just know we're getting a
free vacation out of the deal.
Good point.
Besides, I've
got a funny feeling
that something interesting
is bound to happen
between Ayano and Kazuma.
Nanase, Yukari!
Hey, come on.
We gotta get checked in.
Hurry up, or we'll
leave without you.
This whole vacation was
her father's idea, wasn't it?
Well, yeah.
You could tell?
It's pretty obvious.
Throw your worries away.
They should be arriving at
the resort just about now.
A man and a woman, a
romantic location‐‐
all of the pieces have lined
up exactly as I arranged them.
In a place like that, nothing
can prevent the inevitable.
So here we are.
What should we do?
Simply perfect.
It would probably be wise
to tell Genma about my plan.
We must begin preparing
for the future.
He did what?
Genma's at the Marunaga
hotsprings this weekend?
So here we are.
What should we do?
No, no, no.
This could seriously
put a damper on my plans
for Ayano and Kazuma.
It'll be a catastrophe if he and
his father run into each other.
The two of them might just
destroy the entire resort.
Thank you for coming.
I'm sorry to drag you all
the way out here with me.
You don't need to
apologize for anything.
I'm the one who recommended
spa therapy, remember?
If anybody could use some
serious R&R, it's you.
And besides, this isn't exactly
torture for me, you know.
True.
Throw your worries away!
Wow.
This looks more like a
royal palace than a hotel.
I knew it'd be nice since
it was prize from a game show,
but this is amazing.
[YAWNING]
So what's with the yawning?
Not impressive enough for you?
Hey, sorry I'm not
doing cartwheels.
I just can't seem to
shake this fatigue.
I think I'm exhausted
from dealing with
your irritable moods every day.
Look, it's your fault
that I'm irritable.
Do you know how
exhausting it is‐‐
Whatever.
You, me, I'd just like to
try and relax for a change,
all right?
So what are we waiting for?
I can't believe this.
Like I am irritable.
What idiot thought it
would be fun to invite him?
Should we tell her it
was her father's idea?
OK, Kazuma, Ren, looks
like that's your room.
And we're right across the hall.
So now what?
What should we do first?
I say we hit the hotsprings.
Oh wait.
Check this out.
It says they have a spa.
Why don't we do that?
Yeah, that's even better.
REN: What do you think?
Do you wanna head
down there too?
KAZUMA: Nah, you go ahead.
I just wanna relax in the
outdoor hot tub for a while.
REN: Oh, OK.
I guess you are
pretty tired, huh?
Well, get some good rest.
Whoa.
Look at the size of this place.
Yeah, there's a lot to do,
but if we get started now,
I think we could see it all.
Mhm.
Wow.
There can't be anything
better than a cypress bath.
That's the truth.
Yeah, I couldn't agree more.
Oh wow.
There can't be anything
better than a jacuzzi.
You said it.
This is the best.
Wow.
I can't think of anything
better than a hot waterfall.
Oh yeah.
Right again, Ayano.
Wow.
I can't think of anything that
could top a hot stone spa.
For sure.
I'm just gonna go ahead and
say everything here is awesome.
Throw your worries away!
Finally, some peace
and quiet all to myself.
I brought you some sake.
I thought it might help
with your relaxation.
Thanks.
Yeah, that should do the trick.
Hey, Catherine.
You're the last person I
was expecting to bump into.
What do you
think you're doing?
Get out of here right now.
You must have missed the sign.
It says "unisex bath."
So it's for girls and guys?
[SCREAMING]
That was an overreaction.
OK, I just need to calm down.
It was a little
surprising to see him.
And it was even more surprising
to see so much of him.
But it hardly seems proper that
they would have unisex baths.
No matter how much
time I spend here,
I learn something new about
this country every day.
Is anybody else starving yet?
Yeah, I think
it's time to eat.
And we probably
shouldn't wait for Kazuma.
Who knows what he's up to?
I think I've been
in here long enough.
Hey, old man.
Kazuma.
Huh.
So how long have you
been back from the dead?
That's just wishful thinking.
I was never dead.
Oh yeah, that's right.
I forgot that
useless son of yours
decided to let you
live after all.
I just figured you were so
embarrassed that you would
have killed yourself by now.
You shouldn't flatter
yourself over a single victory.
Your arrogance is
only gonna make
it that much more
humiliating when
I defeat you the next time.
Oh, next, time?
Well, if, you insist,
I'd be more than
happy to kick your ass again.
You're a fool.
If you really
wanna test how much
luck you've got
left in you, then
what are we waiting for, boy?
Come on, is that all you've got?
You're pathetic!
Well, you've got
some pretty impressive
moves for a senior citizen!
It's too bad you
haven't made any progress
since you were a child!
Father?
What is he doing here?
I had a weird feeling
something bad was gonna happen,
but I never thought
it was gonna be this.
Didn't they already
settle this fight?
They fought, but
they never settled it.
I guess this is my father's
return match or something.
Do you think maybe we
should try to stop this?
Yeah, but I have no idea how.
It'd be suicide to get in
between the two of them.
But you're the only
one that can, Ren.
Kazuma and Cousin
Genma care about you
more than anything in the
world, and neither of them
would hurt you.
So they have to stop
fighting if you jump in there
and tell them to knock it off.
But what if they
don't see me somehow?
Well, it'll probably be
a quick and painless death.
Yeah, that's not
exactly reassuring.
Excuse me, Genma,
but your dinner's
gonna get cold if
you keep this up.
I don't wanna wait
all night to eat,
so why don't you come up now?
AYANO: Detective Tachibana?
What are you doing here?
I'm here with Genma
for a romantic getaway.
Just so we're clear on
this, I could easily kill
you any time I feel like it.
But‐‐
But if there's anything
you hate more than me,
it's a cold meal.
That meal just
saved your life.
You mean yours.
You won't be so lucky
the next time we meet.
[CHUCKLING]
I'm starving.
How about we get some grub?
How could I eat anything
after hearing that?
Does this mean now we're
gonna have to start calling
Detective Tachibana "Mom?"
That's so gross.
Why couldn't she
have just lied to us?
Yeah, yeah.
You're both scarred for life.
Now, can we eat?
Aw man, I'm stuffed.
I still can't believe it.
Father mentioned spa
therapy once before,
but I had no idea
he'd be coming here.
I guess it really is a
small world, isn't it?
Yeah, too small.
And when did that geezer get
discharged from the hospital?
You know, Kazuma, do you think
that maybe you and dad could‐‐
Don't even finish
that sentence.
All right.
I'm heading out.
You are?
Where to?
We're at a spa.
Where do you think I'm going?
Oh, hey.
Hey, perfect timing.
We were about to head
down to the rec room.
Would you like to come with us?
The brochure says that
they've got a full arcade
and a ping pong table.
Yeah, sounds good.
Why isn't Kazuma with you?
He went down to take a bath.
Another one?
Yeah, he said he needed
to cool down after the fight
he had with Father.
Oh no, Ren.
We need to get down there.
Cousin Genma might
wanna cool down too!
You'll have to do a lot
better than that, boy!
Looks like we're too late.
As much as they
both hate to admit it,
they're undeniably
father and son.
Better enjoy this, 'cause
it's the last fight you're ever
gonna have, old man.
Twice in one night, huh?
I think your luck's
starting to run out.
I'm done playing
around with you.
This ends right now!
Not the way you want it to.
Hope you have better
luck in the next life.
Excuse me, Genma.
The outdoor bath is
only open until 11:00.
If you keep this up, you're
not gonna have time for a soak,
you know.
Just to remind you, I could
kill you any time I want.
But‐‐
The only thing
you enjoy more than
killing me is a nice warm bath?
Don't worry, kid.
You're next on my list.
You might wanna go ahead
and scratch me off that list
now, while you can still
use your hand to write.
This fighting is exhausting.
I'm gonna have to take a hot
bath just to calm myself down.
Enjoy.
Relaxing, isn't it?
It's incredible how the hot
springs wash your worries away.
What do you have
to be worried about?
Nothing, really.
My useless son's been giving me
problems, but what else is new?
I know how you feel.
Except I've been having
problems with my dad.
Well, my son is a
arrogant, pig‐headed fool.
And my father is
a heartless jerk.
GENMA: He doesn't have respect
for anybody except himself.
He demands respect, like
some kind of dictator.
GENMA: He's a natural born
loser who whines like a child.
He's a feeble old man who's
too proud to admit his age.
GENMA: He's a failure
wasting everyone else's time.
The only thing your
son's gonna waste is you.
Well, you know how
to use your mouth.
Back it up with your fists.
[SHOUTING]
I can't believe it.
They're going at it again?
So I think I'm gonna have
to add the outdoor bath
as my new favorite.
Yep.
No kidding.
Hey, Catherine, what
are you doing out here?
Well, surprise, surprise.
I should have guessed
you were here.
Are you OK? 'Cause
you look kind of‐‐
I'm fine.
I'm‐‐ I'm just flustered.
Your culture is
shocking, really.
I saw Kazuma naked.
What?
Um, did you just say what
I think you just said?
Explain yourself!
CATHERINE (VOICEOVER):
Wow, she looks mad.
Does she think
that Kazuma and I?
Oh, this is perfect.
I think I'll have a little fun.
Well, there's not much
to explain, really.
We took a bath together
earlier, and Kazuma just felt
more comfortable in the nude.
I must admit, it was
a little shocking
to my American sensibilities,
but he just couldn't
relax with his towel on.
[LAUGHTER]
Well, I'm sure you
know how he is.
I assume you've taken a
bath with him before, right?
It's only natural for
two people so close.
But now that I think about it,
I doubt you're that close to him
at all.
CATHERINE (VOICEOVER): This is
really getting under her skin.
My accidental viewing has become
a fortuitous tool of warfare!
Um, Ayano?
You OK?
That's it.
Taking a bath with
Kazuma doesn't mean
you're closer to him than I am.
It just means that
you're a slut.
And I'm not gonna sit here
and let you rub it in my face.
You want a fight?
You got it.
Who the hell do you think
you are, calling me a slut?
If you think you're going
to walk away from this fight
after calling me that,
then you're dead wrong!
Kazuma!
You OK?
Sorry.
Great.
Are you trying to take a
bath with Catherine again?
Son of bitch.
You're gonna pay for that!
[SHOUTING]
They're fighting again?
Yeah.
You know, maybe‐‐
What Ren?
I know this sounds
kind of weird,
but do you think
that fighting is
the only way those
two know how to truly
communicate with each other?
You mean it's kind of like
you're talking to each other
with their fists?
You know what?
That's a pretty
good observation.
Neither of them are very good
at expressing their emotions.
Guess this is the
only way they can
tell each other how they feel.
Is that his father
he's fighting with?
I'll have to introduce myself
to him when they're finished.
REN: Should we do something?
I don't think so.
Not if this is their
way of talking.
And they've obviously got
plenty of things to say.
Are you sure?
What's the matter with you?
Already out of breath?
It's gotta suck to
be as old as you are.
[PANTING]
That's enough.
I'm gonna teach you to
respect your elders.
Now it's time to finish this!
What the?
Go to hell old man!
He just knocked him down.
He defeated Father.
Is he OK?
He's helping him up.
They were able to communicate
how they felt by fighting
and can really understand
each other now.
Now you die!
What is with you?
What's with you?
I can't believe
you just did that.
How could you offer
him your hand just
so you could sucker punch him?
That was really low,
Kazuma, my even for you.
Yeah, it was a good
trick, wasn't it?
It was awful.
Why do you have to
act like such a jerk?
KAZUMA: Oh, come on.
Don't start crying.
How could you ruin
such a moving moment?
I didn't realize there
was a moving moment.
AYANO: That's because
there wasn't one.
I was just stupid enough
to think that maybe you
and your father finally
came to an understanding,
that you were only using your
fists to share your feelings.
Yeah, that does sound
kind of stupid, actually.
Seriously, you have
got to be the biggest
jerk I have ever met.
Don't you feel ashamed for
tricking him like that?
Not at all.
Yeah, well, you should!
See what happens when
you don't finish the job?
You either make sure that
your opponent is dead,
or you get yourself killed.
That's good advice.
I'm not dead yet.
Just try it again,
you son of a bitch.
And just so you don't
forget, I could easily kill
you any time I feel like it.
But I think that we've both done
enough damage to this hotel,
so I'm letting you live tonight.
I really hope the hotel
doesn't bill us for this.
[GROANING]
Will you just hold still?
I can't make it better if
you keep moving around.
I didn't ask you
to do this, you know.
AYANO: You're not gonna
do it, and I don't wanna
look at your infected wounds.
KAZUMA: Can you
believe the old man
still can't get over the
fact that I beat him once?
It's friggin' annoying.
Does it really
upset you that much?
Yeah.
Why'd I even bother wasting my
time fighting someone if I'm
not getting paid for it anyway?
I ought to write up an
invoice and charge that idiot.
I don't know.
Kind of looked like
you were enjoying it.
KAZUMA: No, not at all.
I hate violence.
Yeah, well, OK, but you
sure could have fooled me.
I guess, in a strange way,
I do feel a little better.
Really?
I'm glad to hear it.
KAZUMA: You know I would have
won if he hadn't walked away,
right?
‐ Come on, Kazuma.
How can you even think that
after the total thrashing
he gave you back there?
KAZUMA: Whatever.
Look, there's always gonna
be someone better than you.
Yeah, that may be true,
but it's definitely not him.
You know, I was terrified of
my father when I was younger.
I never thought that I was
gonna be able to defeat him.
I guess everything changes, huh?
I'm sorry you've
had to deal with this.
You don't need to apologize.
Although I must admit I'm
a little surprised at how
much he was able to injure you.
Maybe I'm wrong, but I get
the feeling that you're
actually proud of him.
He's got a long way to go
before he earns my respect.
KAZUMA: It's pathetic that
he's still fighting at his age.
He really should just
go ahead and retire.
TACHIBANA: Hey, wait.
Genma, where are you going?
AYANO: Get back here, Kazuma.
Where are you going?
KAZUMA AND GENMA: To the bath!
[THEME MUSIC]
AYANO (VOICEOVER): What?
Someone put a curse on the
girls in the tennis club?
Wait.
It's that low‐life camera geek
from Nanase's class, isn't it?
There's something weird
about all these people
developing special abilities.
This kind of thing
doesn't just happen.
Oh no!
Nanase's in trouble?
Next time on Kaze no Stigma,
"How to Defeat a Magic User."
What?
Kazuma's involved with this?