MAN: Gonzo.
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): Eyes
as blue as the azure sky.
That is the symbol
of the Contractor.
Entrusted by the
Spirit King of the Wind
with the powers of his
domain, I bear this mark,
the stigma of the wind.
[THEME ‐ SAORI KIUJI, "BLAST OF
WIND"]
[SHOUTING]
Hah!
Aah!
[GRUNTING]
You're wasting your time.
Your paltry fire magic
is useless on me.
The power of Mount Fuji
flows through my veins.
KUREHA (VOICEOVER): I've
lived with the shame
of being born without my
family's earth magic abilities.
I was an impotent freak
in the Tsuwabuki clan.
So I had to take matters
into my own hands.
I sought power from
a greater source
than my family's meager
talents, and I surpassed them.
Once the ceremony's
complete, the absolute power
of Mount Fuji will be mine.
KAZUMA: Come on,
let's get out of here.
Whoa, hold on
a minute, Kazuma.
We can't leave now.
We got your girlfriend.
Let's go.
But what about Mayumi?
KAZUMA: What?
That doesn't make any sense.
What's the point of
having a clone if you're
still going to get sacrificed?
AYUMI: That's because she‐‐
Tell me later.
[GRUNT]
Mayumi!
[RUMBLING, CRACKING]
Aah!
Kazuma, you may have acted a
little quickly on that one.
I think that crystal
was holding up the cave.
The exit's blocked off!
KAZUMA: Guess we'll
have to make our own.
Straight to the top, Ren.
The top?
You heard me.
Right through it.
[LOUD RUMBLING]
I hate to admit it, but that
was cutting it pretty close.
Is everybody all right?
I'm OK.
Yeah, I'm good.
Hmm.
Now to find Ayano, we‐‐
That was easy.
She always did know how
to keep a low profile.
[DISTANT MOAN]
Wait.
I think I just heard something.
Hey, what is that thing?
It's Master Iwao.
Head of the Tsuwabukis?
Master, what happened to you?
You must stop her, please.
It's Kureha.
She doesn't know
what she's doing.
Please, you must.
[CRACK]
[SHOUT]
[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
[BOOM]
[PANTING]
I don't think it's
possible to have
wasted more energy deflecting
such a simple attack.
What a disappointing fire user.
Don't start
judging my abilities.
You got yours from the beast.
AYANO (VOICEOVER): That
idiot actually dumped
her on me to handle by myself.
I can't even get close to her,
much less dodge her attacks.
That's it.
He is so dead.
KAZUMA: Hey.
Been having fun?
[GROWL]
Yeah, see, you
might want to think
twice about going for the high
kick while wearing a skirt.
I'm just worried it
might give your opponents
the wrong impression.
Do me a favor and shut up!
You saved her.
Good job, Ren.
Thanks, Ayano.
Hah!
I'm afraid this
battle isn't over yet.
Yeah, and you
might as well quit.
We've rescued Ayumi
and Mayumi, so you're
not going to have
too much luck pulling
off your little ceremony.
Well then.
I'll just have to take
them back from you,
because nothing will stop me
from completing the ceremony.
It is my sworn
duty as a Tsuwabuki
to keep the beast
concealed, and I
won't let you stand in my way.
Aren't you noble?
Drop the act and admit
what's really going on.
KUREHA: What are you talking‐‐
You don't give a
damn about keeping
the beast in prison, do you?
The only thing you care
about's trying to absorb
its power for yourself.
What are you talking about?
That's impossible.
So my father managed to
squeeze out a few last words.
That's right.
He told us everything
about your plan.
With his last dying breath.
But the beast
represents all of Mount
Fuji's energy and power.
There's just no possible
way a human body could
contain a force like that.
That's why she's so
hellbent on performing
the grand ceremony.
The beast is too
strong to fight,
so the only thing they
can do is trap it.
And the ceremony confines
the beast by compressing
all of its power.
When it's in this
compressed state,
she can transfer all of
the energy to her body.
AYANO: OK, but why does she
even want the beast's power?
She hasn't exactly
led the easiest life.
It's tough being
born without them.
How would you even know
the first thing about it?
You have no idea
what kind of misery
my family forced me to endure.
They treated me like
some kind of freak
because I wasn't
like them, because I
couldn't harness any magic.
The only way I could
end their cruelty
was to become
stronger than them.
Absorbing the beast's
power was my only choice.
She's doing all this
because she couldn't develop
her family's magic abilities?
But that means
she's just like you.
I know.
Everyone's got their
own cross to bear.
But you were so busy whining
about your powers you haven't
even realized the truth.
Oh, and what truth is that?
KAZUMA: Just take
a look at Yuji.
When he absorbed
the beast power,
it transformed him
into a monster.
But for some reason, you've
still kept your human form.
And why is that?
Well, that's because‐‐
Don't even bother
saying it's because you're
stronger than he was.
We both know that's not true.
So why hasn't she changed?
When it comes down to it,
there's only one possibility.
Without knowing it, you'd
already been absorbing
that power since birth.
It wasn't your idea
to use the beast.
The beast thought
that one up for you.
What are you talking about?
That doesn't make any sense.
All this time,
you thought you were
using the beast for its power.
But it's been using
you and leading
you right up to this
point to be the medium
for its resurrection.
But that's impossible.
I would know if the
beast was controlling me.
KAZUMA: You do know.
You're just afraid to
admit it to yourself.
The beast has
controlled everything.
It made you want its power and
try to execute the ceremony
so it could escape.
That can't be right.
That's a lie.
You're lying!
If what you're saying is true,
then that means my whole life
has been an illusion.
I've been the beast's
puppet, and it
used my pain to control me.
It took my magic
so that it could
separate me from my family
and make me hate my father.
And all of the anger
and horrible isolation
I've suffered was just
a tool for the beast's
resurrection, just
a way to help it
escape from beneath the earth.
It can't be true.
Nothing in my life was real.
He took everything.
Wait.
She said, "escape from beneath
the earth," didn't she?
Hey, Kureha.
Not to ruin the moment, but I've
got a quick question for you.
You didn't have the beast sealed
inside the cave with the giant
crystal by any chance, did you?
Yes, that was its tomb.
Oh, boy.
That's not good.
All right, Kazuma.
I've seen that look before.
Did you screw something up?
Now, spit it out!
Tell me what you did, or
I'll beat it out of you!
Well, yeah.
You see, the thing is, when
we saved Ayumi earlier,
we were in a pretty
tight spot and had
to get out of there fast.
And funny story‐‐
I had no idea we were
in the beast's tomb.
So I, uh, kind of blew a massive
hole in the roof of the cave.
But you know, it's probably
nothing to worry about.
Really, I'm sure it's fine.
Nothing's fine, you idiot.
Any kind of disturbance to the
cave breaks the seal's spell.
Great!
Way to go, you moron!
This has got to be the dumbest
thing you've ever done!
Hey, what's happening?
[RUMBLING]
It has awakened.
It's Zenon.
Zenon.
[PAINED GRUNTING]
Kureha!
Get ready, guys.
So that's the beast.
This should be easy.
[SCREECH]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROAR]
You have got to be kidding me.
Is there any way this
could possibly get worse?
[SCREAMING]
AYUMI: Kureha!
[ROAR]
I think it just got worse.
That's an understatement.
It looks like the
beast just regained
the power it gave to Kureha.
We need to act fast and
destroy it before it
comes down from the mountain.
Right.
What are we waiting for?
REN: It's OK, Ayumi.
Don't worry.
I won't let anything
happen to me.
There's no way I'm
going to let that thing
stop me from being with you.
Ren.
Now, just wait here.
I'll be right back.
Come on, Ren.
Coming.
[ROAR]
[SHOUT]
All right, you freak!
Crawl back in your hole!
It's not working.
Hey, your turn.
Got it!
[SHOUT]
It bounced right off that thing.
Aah!
I don't understand.
Enraiha didn't even
put a scratch on it.
Are you really that surprised?
You haven't exactly
mastered your powers.
Hey, watch it.
Kazuma, look out!
[WARBLING]
[BLAST]
That thing is huge.
And it's got an incredible
amount of power.
[ECHOING ROAR]
Careful, Ren.
How dare you.
You stole my entire
life from me.
I'll make you pay
for what you've done!
Hah!
[SHOUT]
It isn't that the
attacks aren't working.
It's that they
aren't even reaching
that thing in the first place.
What are you talking about?
KAZUMA: It's using all of Mount
Fuji's energy as a barrier,
like it's got a force
field around it.
AYANO: Wouldn't this
be a good time for you
to use your full‐blown powers?
But I can only use them
for a short amount of time‐‐
five minutes tops.
If you really want me
to risk it and then
collapse from
exhaustion afterwards,
I'll do it right now.
So you have like 1,000
ways of being useless.
And you've been
such a great help.
If I could only weaken its
energy barrier for a second.
[SNARL]
KAZUMA: Kureha.
She's attacking the
beast with earth magic.
You're finished!
I won't let you get away
with what you've done, Zenon!
I want my life back!
Give it to me and
everything else
that you've stolen from me!
You destroyed my life.
And if you don't return it,
then I'm destroying you.
Get out of there.
You can't fight it.
If my life was "never
mind," then why was I born?
Answer me!
Please stop, Kureha!
[THUNDERCLAP]
What a pointless
way for her to die.
Oh no.
[BEAST ROARS]
What's he doing?
Ren, hold on!
[WEEPING]
REN (VOICEOVER):
Ayumi, we can do this.
Let's go.
Let's be happy.
Ren.
[WARBLING]
[BLAST]
I have to do everything I
can to live my life with you.
It's getting out
of the mountain!
Then there's nothing
we can do about it.
What the hell's that?
[GASP]
[HIGH‐PITCHED WARBLING]
It's Ayumi!
[BOOM]
She's weakening
the beast's energy.
But the only way
she could do that is
to perform the grand ceremony.
Ayumi, you can't survive.
You'll have to
sacrifice yourself.
She knows what
she's doing, Ren.
But she's taking a chance
and choosing to fight.
She's willing to risk
her life, because she
has something to live for.
She's doing this because
she wants to be with you.
She's fighting to live.
[QUIET WHIMPERING]
She's in pain!
She's putting her life
on the line to be with you.
So what are you going
to do to be with her?
That's an easy question
with an obvious answer.
I'm going to
annihilate that beast.
But I can't do it alone.
I need you.
I need both of
you to back me up.
Hell yeah.
That's what I wanted to hear.
KAZUMA (VOICEOVER): Hear
me, spirits of the wind.
In the name of the contract,
entrust me with your power.
This thing is nothing
but a big pile of rocks.
So let's do some demolition!
Ren, let's defeat the
beast no matter what.
We'll destroy it so we can
live our lives together.
[ROARING]
OK, Ren.
We've only got one shot at this.
Right.
We've got to put
everything into this attack.
Focus your power,
and make it count!
[SHOUTING]
You're going down!
It's over, Zenon.
We're sending you back to hell!
[RUMBLE]
[GASPING]
We did it.
We did it, Ayumi.
[GASP]
I'm coming, Ayumi.
Ayumi!
Let go.
Might as well stay here.
What are you talking about?
She's hurt.
We have to go and help her.
I don't think there's
anything we or anyone else
can do for her now.
Think about it.
It's only been a month
since she was cloned, right?
A clone typically grows
just like anything
else, a year at a time.
It's impossible for her
to have aged that quickly
in four weeks.
Then how did they do it?
Because Iwao Tsuwabuki cheated
by stealing the pixie's secret
treasure from their homeland.
It's way more important
than just some treasure.
It's actually the egg that
contains the next pixie chief.
AYANO: I'm sorry, what?
Iwao infused Ayumi's DNA with
the egg's reproductive powers
to rapidly accelerate
her growth.
But they didn't
build her to last,
so you can imagine what'll
happen after she's exhausted
all of her body's energy.
Then you mean
Ayumi's not going to‐‐
so why didn't you
try to stop her?
Why didn't you do something?
I knew there was no reason.
If I stopped her, she
still would have died.
But so would everyone else.
But Kazuma, this
just isn't right.
I don't even understand what
we were fighting for then.
We were supposed
to save her life,
and all we did was give
her a reason to end it.
And what's the point of being
a Contractor anyway if you
can't even save a little girl?
I'm sorry I wasn't strong
enough to do anything.
No, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
I was just taking
everything out on you.
But you're absolutely
right, Ayano.
As much as I wanted to, I didn't
have the power to protect her.
Neither of us could.
I couldn't do anything for her.
We need to stay strong
now for Ren's sake.
[WEEPING]
REN: Ayumi, can you hear me?
Wake up, Ayumi.
Oh, Ren.
Ayumi.
I'm afraid I might
have used too much power.
I don't know if my body
can last without it.
No, please.
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
If only I was stronger.
I need you to
do me a favor, OK?
Anything.
Don't be sad, Ren.
You don't have to
feel sorry for me.
[GASP]
I don't regret what I've done,
because I did get to live what
little life I have with you.
I chose to do this,
because the time we've had
has been wonderful.
I was never meant
to live for long.
But at least I got
to be with you.
I don't want you to
feel sorry for me,
because I'm happy with my life.
I'm proud of what I've done.
I wouldn't take back any
of it, no matter what.
You're right, Ayumi.
You're an amazing person.
And I'm very proud of you.
You are so much stronger
than I could ever be.
Oh, Ren.
Thank you.
Mayumi.
I'm sorry for what I've done.
I shouldn't have treated
you the way I did,
and I'm so sorry that
your life was created
for such a horrible reason.
REN: [CHOKING UP]
Ayumi.
Please, Ayumi.
Please don't die.
Don't cry, Ren.
Smile for me.
This is the last time that
I'll ever see your face,
and I can't bear
to see you crying.
So just smile for
me one last time.
Please do that for me.
Let me see you happy.
OK.
[SNIFFLE]
I'm so happy I met you, Ayumi.
I love you so much.
You're the best person
I've ever known.
I'll never forget you.
[INAUDIBLE WHISPER]
[GASP]
KAZUMA: Ren.
I tried, Kazuma.
I tried, but I
couldn't protect her.
Why couldn't I save her?
It's OK.
You can let it out now.
There wasn't anything else
you could have done for her.
[SOBBING]
Ayumi.
Ayumi!
[SOBBING]
[SEAGULL CALLING]
There's so much.
There's so much more that I wish
I could have shown you, Ayumi.
This world is just so
large and beautiful,
and you barely got to see it.
You know what?
I think you made her
happy for the first time.
They treated her
like she was nothing,
but you showed her that she
was special, that she mattered.
I think she'd thank you.
REN (VOICEOVER): I didn't
have to prove anything to her.
She was more special
than anyone I know.
And her words will
never leave my heart.
[SEAGULL CALLING]
Hey, Ren!
AYUMI (VOICEOVER): And
I love you, too, Ren.
AYANO (VOICEOVER): What
are you talking about?
You want me to
spend an entire day
at an amusement
park with Kazuma,
and it's supposed to be fun?
Why is my heart
pounding like this?
Quiet down.
I hope Kazuma doesn't hear it.
You have to admit, there's
something weird going on here.
We haven't found any
spiritual disturbances.
We can't get in
touch with my father.
And to top it off,
someone's been following us.
Next time on "Kaze
no Stigma," "Let's Go
to the Amusement Park!"
And here's the death sentence
for all Peeping Toms!