[TOI] My brother
sacrificed everything.
All to protect me.
He never even gave it
a second thought.
Now I'm going to give up
what I love.
Just like I did before.
[bubbling]
-[water babbling]
-[splashing]
[YOUNG KAZUKI]
Why'd you throw it away?
You hate soccer?
[YOUNG TOI] No,
but if I don't leave it behind,
I can never move on.
[YOUNG KAZUKI]
That's like me, I guess.
I'm not really connected
to anyone, after all.
[YOUNG TOI] People don't realize
who they're connected to
until they lose them.
I have to protect
the connections I have left,
and that means giving up soccer.
[grunts]
[YOUNG KAZUKI inhales sharply]
-[YOUNG TOI] Take it.
-[gasps softly]
Not all dreams need connections
to come true.
[TOI]
Of course he wouldn't remember.
Last time we'll see
this place, huh?
Chikai! What happened?
Are you okay?
For right now. But I think
someone sniffed out
our little incident
from four years back.
-[TOI gasps]
-Oh.
Don't tell me you're still
blaming yourself for that mess.
I'm not.
[CHIKAI]
Well, either way,
there's one thing
you gotta remember.
Just like you need me,
I need you, too.
[TOI inhales sharply]
Come with me this time, Toi.
You mean that?
-[grunts]
-[CHIKAI] What's wrong?
Do you think you could give me
a little more time?
[CHIKAI]
Mm.
No! Wait! I'm not backing out!
I've made up my mind.
I just gotta make sure
my friends are okay.
[laughs]
I haven't seen it in years,
but I remember that face!
Yeah, fine, sorry. I can wait.
But only for a day. Got it?
[ENTA]
Damn it, Kazuki! You traitor!
I make one mistake
and suddenly everyone hates me!
Who do you care about more?
Him or me?
-[balls clattering]
-[ENTA grunts]
Huh? Out of balls already?
[yells]
Man, why does everything suck?
[CHIKAI]
Well, when everything sucks,
then you throw it all away.
You only get one shot at life,
after all.
That means no do-overs
and no take backs.
[ball clattering]
[beeps]
-No way!
-Easy.
[gasps]
What?
You're staring.
Do I have something on my face?
No, no. Uh, here, as thanks.
It's not much.
Oh. I should help people
out more often!
[CHIKAI scoffs]
[REO]
Hold up.
I thought you said
this fraudster guy
was working out of Tama.
Why is it our case?
He operates elsewhere,
but lives here.
Fine. So?
[MABU] Apparently,
he's also wanted in connection
to a fatal shooting
four years ago.
If we capture him, we can easily
make him into a kappa zombie.
Ha! Would you look at
the half-baked little doll!
Always so eager to please
your masters, aren't you?
You think if you bake up my old
favorite that'll win me back?
[growls softly]
It's... half-baked.
[door squeaks open]
'Kay.
I think you're in the clear.
[ENTA, CHIKAI]
Shh, shh, shh, shh!
[CHIKAI]
Man, I owe you one.
This place your stomping ground?
[ENTA] I've hung out here
with Kazu-- uh, I mean,
with my friends
since I was little.
So, I guess.
[CHIKAI]
Well, enjoy it while you can,
'cause the places and the people
change before you know it.
[ENTA] Are you, uh,
running from the law?
Question, Specs.
How old are you?
[ENTA]
Huh? Um, fourteen.
Pretty shrimpy for fourteen,
aren't you?
-You got a problem with that?
-[laughs] Sorry, kid!
I was just thinking I have
a little brother
-about your age, that's all.
-I know.
I didn't come to see him enough
and he grew up too fast.
He used to be cute,
but now he's a punk like me.
Anyway, we're leaving town
together.
[chuckles softly]
That is why I can't afford
to get caught.
[gasps softly]
[ENTA]
Hey.
Will you let me help you?
I know how!
[TOI] Jeez,
would you just grow up?
[KAZUKI grunts]
Come on!
Aren't you pissed off, too?
Your wish should've
been granted already,
but I don't know
what's gonna happen now!
[grunts angrily]
What the hell
is wrong with him?
He lied to us.
I thought we were friends!
I'm sure he's got his reasons.
Give him a break.
What reason could that be?
[TOI]
Well, that's not for me to say.
Huh? What the hell!
Why would you side with him?
Are you two keeping
some kind of secret from me?
[TOI]
No. I'm on your side here, okay?
Just forget it!
I'll find those dishes, myself!
Hey!
Damn it.
Why am I so bad at this stuff?
[SARA]
Now for our next dish.
We have received reports
that Chikai Kuji,
wanted leader of the
fraud ring, Shikotama,
has been sighted in the area.
The police believe that he fled
to Asakusa to escape arrest.
A special team has been
deployed to capture him.
Stop right there, evildoer!
[scoffs]
I'm running out of time.
[screeches]
[CHIKAI] Damn, I haven't seen
this old place in ages.
It's so strange.
Back then, he was
this innocent little thing,
hanging on my every word.
It's crazy. These days,
I hardly even recognize him.
Right now, I think he's torn
between helping me
and helping some buddies of his.
Buddies, huh?
Can't hardly blame him, though.
I made my brother
throw away something
that meant the world to him.
[bubbling]
[splashing]
[CHIKAI]
That should settle things.
Forget we ever had that gun.
Okay?
'Kay. And I'll catch up
with you later.
[CHIKAI]
Uh-huh.
[humming softly]
-[splashing]
-Huh?
You gave it all up for me.
Everything you ever had.
So I'm gonna give up
what I love the most!
[CHIKAI]
He quit soccer because of me.
He was serious, too.
Really wanted to shoot
for the big leagues someday.
[ENTA]
Huh?
What?
Wait.
I know that micanga.
[chuckles]
Well, he really liked
that thing,
but I think he said
he gave it away.
To who?
Who did he give it to?
The hell if I know! Chill out.
He just wanted someone
to remember him, that's all.
To understand how much
playing soccer meant to him.
I'm telling you,
that's kid's too serious.
He'd do anything
if he thought it might help me.
He'd get his hands dirty,
put his life at risk...
Not that I'd ever
ask him to do that.
[ENTA]
I'm the same way.
There's nothing
I wouldn't do for Kazuki.
[CHIKAI]
Hmm.
Not that any of that matters.
It's all for nothing
if he doesn't even care.
Don't worry about
how they feel. Think about you.
If it makes you happy,
if it makes your life easier,
do it.
Huh?
Police.
-[grunts softly]
-[ENTA yells]
[CHIKAI] Looks like
I'm fresh out of time, huh?
That's right, you are.
Now, hurry up, take your brother
and get out of here.
[shrieks]
[BOTH gasp]
Chikai.
[ENTA]
Whoa. Who is that guy?
[CHIKAI]
Aw, shit.
You murdered my bro.
Now it's time to die!
[ENTA gasps]
-[shrieking]
-[ENTA yells]
-[CHIKAI grunts]
-[ENTA groans]
-[grunts]
-[ENTA screams]
-[YASU] Huh?
-No, I...
-[running footsteps]
-[CHIKAI] Shh, shh, shh, shh.
[ENTA]
Hey!
Yo, kid!
You Chikai's friend or what?
[ENTA]
Um, uh, no, sir!
-Don't play dumb!
-[ENTA whimpers]
[REO]
Oh, no! Someone call the police!
But we are the police.
Always gotta play
the straight man.
[MABU] What are you doing
to that child?
[REO] We'll have to confiscate
that, uh, sword.
-[YASU shrieks]
-[ENTA yells]
I'm gonna kill Chikai!
I haven't waited
all these years for nothing!
-[ENTA whimpers]
-[MABU] Chikai.
Are you referring
to the fugitive, Chikai Kuji?
[YASU] I'm not letting you
po-pos have him!
I'll avenge my bro's death,
on my own terms!
-He's so lame.
-Kuji's long gone, now.
Don't ignore me!
[shrieking]
[YASU]
Oh! Oh!
-[thuds]
-[grunts]
[YASU]
Damn it.
You really shouldn't get
in our way.
Not the best place.
But why not?
You think that thing
intimidates me?
We shall open a brand
new door for you.
-[shrieking]
-Is it desire? Or love?
-[gunshot]
-[YASU grunts]
[whimpering]
[body thuds]
[shudders, yells]
Well, now what?
He'll make a fine kappa zombie
once we move him.
[OFFICER 1]
Sounded like a gunshot!
Look! There's a man down!
Uh-oh, guess we're in trouble.
He's dead.
Did you shoot this man?
Don't know if this passes
for self-defense!
[OFFICER 1] Hey, say something
already! What did you--
[OFFICER 2]
It was the fugitive. Kuji.
How do you know that?
It was the murder
from four years ago.
This man came for revenge.
Exactly!
And then Kuji shot him dead.
[OFFICER 1] Where are you
getting this from?
[gasps]
Why don't you calm down
and tell us who killed this man?
[OFFICER 1]
Chikai Kuji. The fugitive.
[REO chuckles softly]
[SARA] I've been watching them
for the past few days.
And I'm convinced
that they're the ones
who captured Dark Keppi.
There's no doubt.
[KEPPI]
Reo and Mabu.
Shocking.
I was certain they had died.
This time, we have a secret
anti-otter weapon
to take them out.
[KEPPI]
A machine?
Pop the lid, flick the switch,
and the target's frozen solid!
This way, we can
capture them both alive!
[KEPPI]
Intriguing. Hmm.
We'll need to determine
their location, first.
[beeping]
[SARA] Can't fight on an empty
stomach, as they say!
A little spice.
[gasps, whimpers]
-[screams]
-[KEPPI grunts]
[thuds]
-[machine whirring]
-[beeping]
-[shrieks] My prince!
-[KEPPI yelling]
[beeping]
[hissing]
-[SARA whimpers]
-[KEPPI] Cold...
-This is a dish-aster!
-[KEPPI] Cold, cold, cold...
I've gotta go dish
out the news, soon!
-I can't be late for work!
-[KEPPI] Cold, cold...
[ENTA] You're the worst!
I thought I was dead back there!
Bad guys are the ones
who survive in this world.
Be careful. Softies like you
have got targets on their backs.
Only thanks to you!
Well, now that you're
all nice and alive,
you should go make up
with that buddy of yours.
[ENTA]
It's not that easy.
[phone ringing]
[CHIKAI]
Gotta dash.
Share those with your pals.
Hey, Masa. Yeah, I'm taking
the boat there tonight.
Yep, and Toi's
coming along, too.
[phone ringing]
[gasps softly]
[TOI]
Jinnai? About Yasaka.
[ENTA]
Why didn't you say anything?
-[TOI] Huh?
-I didn't know that Kazuki
got that micanga from you!
[TOI gasps]
-[TOI] He remembered?
-Uh, nuh-uh.
Least not as far as I know.
[TOI]
I see. Of course not.
[ENTA] I don't get why
you didn't tell him!
[TOI] If he doesn't remember,
there's no point
in dragging it up.
Especially not now.
You're the Golden Duo, right?
You don't need my baggage
getting in the way.
[ENTA]
You can't be happy with this!
[TOI] My brother is
all that matters now.
Goodbye.
[ENTA]
You're such a bad liar.
[grunts]
[KAZUKI]
Not here, either.
Hmm. That's funny.
This is where
we first met, isn't it?
[bubbling]
[KAZUKI]
I thought Toi was bad news.
He was pretty scary, after all.
Not to mention violent.
[bubbling]
[phone ringing]
[KAZUKI]
Hello? Toi?
[TOI] I don't need
the dishes anymore.
I'm already leaving town.
[inhales sharply]
Wha-- What are you
talking about?
You're not even mad about this?
Come on! Say something!
[boat horn honks]
[gasps]
Wait, Toi!
Don't you dare leave!
I'll fix this somehow!
People don't realize
who they're connected to
until they lose them.
[KAZUKI]
Huh? What are you saying?
Sorry, but I have to protect
the connections
that I have left.
[KAZUKI]
Toi! Hey!
Toi!
[line disconnects]
Toi.
[CHIKAI]
Mm.
Did I make you throw away
something you love again?
I'm fine. We aren't like that.
[stomping]
-[stomps]
-[KAZUKI gasps]
[whimpers]
Good. It's me!
Kazuki, we gotta help Toi!
He's really leaving!
-[grunts]
-[angry whimper]
-[punches]
-[ENTA groans]
-[crashes]
-[clatters]
[ENTA shudders]
It's all your fault!
If it weren't for you,
then he would be here.
And we would've
made our wish already!
You did this to him!
What the hell!
[growls]
It's "Toi" this and "Toi" that,
but you weren't even able
to remember him!
You're just as bad as me!
You should've known
what he was trying to do!
I'm not listening to
another word that you say.
You betrayed us, understand?
[ENTA gasps]
I'm done with you.
It's over.
[gasps]
[ENTA whimpers]
[sobs]
I don't care!
I don't...
[sobs]
There you are!
-The police? Huh?
-Huh?
[laughs sinisterly]
[gasps softly]
You see that?
The Dishes of Hope.
You know?
Oh, yes, we know
all sorts of things.
-[BOTH gasp]
-But we're not here
to answer your little questions.
Sorry.
We're here to open
a brand-new door.
So is it desire? Or love?
[gasps]
Kazuki!
[gunshot]
♪
[thudding]
[exhales]
[gasps]
Enta!
[REO] Do you want to save
your friend's life?
Sorry!
The Dishes belong to us now!
Our wishes are
going to come true!
You've said enough. Let's go.
[REO] Ugh, I was just
getting to the good part!
I'd call for help.
Your friend might still survive.
[ENTA]
Kazuki?
Hey! Come on!
Hang in there!
Why did you do that?
[ENTA whimpering]
[coughs]
It's no use.
Even when I'm mad, I...
can't say I hate you.
Oh, no. Wake up.
Enta!
[boat horn honks]
[wind blowing]
[phone buzzing]
[buzzing continues]
-[siren blaring]
-[OFFICER 3] Urgent. Urgent.
Emergency orders
from headquarters.
Shots fired in the jurisdiction
of Asazara Police Station.
Repeat: shots fired.
All units in the area
to the site, immediately.
Asazara Three to headquarters.