[KAZUKI]
When I was five years old,
Haruka was born.
--[yawns]
--[KAZUKI] Even now,
I remember the day
they brought him home.
Looks like you're
a big brother now!
[KAZUKI] Don't worry, Haruka.
Everything's gonna be great.
Your big brother will
protect you, no matter what!
But everything came
crashing down
the summer when I was ten.
All it took were a few words
from my grandfather
on his death bed.
[KAZUKI'S GRANDPA]
Kazuki, your mother was a whore.
[KAZUKI]
Why would my grandfather
say something like that?
Even now, I don't know.
But there were two things that
became perfectly clear to me.
First, I had a mother,
different from the one I knew.
And second, I was taken
away from that mother,
and she was kept
secret from me.
My family was
nothing more than a lie.
Or rather,
they were a real family,
but I wasn't connected to them.
[HARUKA]
Hey, Kazu!
Good morning!
[KAZUKI]
Yeah.
I thought I knew what
home smelled like,
but not anymore.
[KAZUKI]
Okay. She's in that car!
Hey. Are you sure about this?
Of course I am. I can't stop.
There's an important
mission on my plate.
You're so weird.
But you look so normal.
Huh?
Oh. I'll change in the bathroom.
[TOI]
I don't mean how you're dressed!
I mean, why don't you care
about getting involved
with a criminal?
I'm not sure.
I cared at first.
I was scared, even.
But not now.
Now I envy you. A lot.
[TOI] I'm starting to think
you might be crazy.
[KAZUKI] Maybe. Or maybe I
just want too much.
Sorry. Ignore me. Let's go.
The manager's our first target.
[whistling]
--[door creaks open]
--[soft gasp]
--[thudding]
--[grunting]
[sighs]
[muffled screaming]
--[flapping]
--[muffled yelling]
[soft humming]
[knock on door]
Hmm?
[door opens]
Pardon me.
[gasps]
Is that for me?
[TOI] We'd like to take some
promotional pictures
before the fan meet.
Can you come with me
for a moment?
Whatever you say.
[door closes]
[TOI] What the
hell am I doing?
Okay. Good job!
--Halfway there!
--[phone dings]
[HARUKA] You know how
we were talking about
a secret passcode yesterday?
I thought of a good one
we could use!
[KAZUKI]
What is it?
[phone dings]
[HARUKA]
When I meet you, I'll say,
"From the beginning
to the end,"
and then you'll say, "We're
all connected in a big circle."
[gasps]
[KAZUKI]
That's splen-dish-erous.
[HARUKA] It's a sign, to show
our special connection!
[KAZUKI] Even if it's
nothing more than a lie,
Haruka and I are connected.
[MAN]
You'll be entering in order,
based on your ticket number.
What are you looking at?
I need to find out
Sara's Lucky Selfie!
Good morning to you!
You'll see her in person
in just a second!
You really love
Sara a lot, don't you?
[laughs]
She's the best!
Now it's time to take a look
at our lucky item for today!
[SARA]
Sachets!
Um, hey, Mom?
What is a "sachet?"
[KAZUKI'S MOM]
It's a little pouch
you fill with things
that smell nice.
A little pouch.
So, no Kazuki today?
He's too busy, huh?
Yeah. He left early this morning
to do something or other.
I see.
[ENTA] You're about to
get exposed here, Kazuki!
I hope you have a plan!
That's all we have on the plate!
Get Sara-cky, you guys!
[MALE OFFICER]
We've determined the identity
of the corpse that was
discovered this morning.
[MALE OFFICER 2]
Fukuro Nioino.
Thirty-five years old.
He was arrested
and detained six months ago
for his suspected involvement
in the Asakusa Natural
Treasure Sachet Incident.
He was eventually released
from custody
for lack of evidence.
At any rate, we will be treating
his death as a murder.
We're the ones who
sniffed him out, of course.
A stench in yesterday's sachet.
[NIOINO]
This reeks of injustice!
[MABU] For those lost souls
with no beginning,
no end, and no connections...
...we shall open a
brand new door for you.
[REO]
Is it desire?
[MABU]
Or love?
[BOTH]
Desire extraction!
♪ Otterly...Sexy! ♪
Soiya! Soiya! Soiya! Soiya!
[REO] ♪ Pathetic livestock,
beaten and defeated ♪
♪ Are you man or swine? ♪
[MABU] ♪ Pathetic insects,
living hand to mouth ♪
♪ Do you have a spine? ♪
[REO] ♪ Let desire flow
Never let it go (Ha!) ♪
[MABU] ♪ Let desire flow
[BOTH]
♪ We possess a single body ♪
♪ We've attained a second fate ♪
♪ You're the same as anybody ♪
♪ You can strive for
something great ♪
♪ Let desire flow
Never let it go (Ha!) ♪
♪ Let desire flow ♪
♪ Never let it go (Ha!) ♪
[BOTH]
Otterly sexy! (Soiya!)
Otterly...Sexy!
Let desire flow.
Every last drop.
[TOI]
Inside here, please.
Oh, my!
Why, it's like I've stepped
onto the set
of a murder mystery!
[door creaks shut]
--[chain rattling]
--[heavy breathing]
[squealing]
[TOI] I'll let you out
once we've settled this.
Not my plan. Don't blame me.
Nailed my escape!
Huh? But how?
It's locked tight!
[SARA squealing]
[grunting]
[humming happily]
--I nailed it again!
--[grunts]
Oh!
[SARA humming]
Bam! Nailed it!
[SARA]
Oh!
[knife clinks]
[TOI grunts]
[SARA]
I'm pretty good at this, huh?
[TOI groans]
[panting]
What is going on?
[WOMAN]
Ladies and gentlemen,
we now begin the very first fan
meet for Asakusa local idol,
--Sara Azuma!
--[applause]
I can see her right there!
[yells]
Good evening to you!
Are you ready to get the dish?
Kazuki, why?
Crap! Haruka's gonna find out!
It's Sara!
And she's cute in person, too!
[gasps]
[OLD MAN] That Sara's like
a granddaughter to me!
[ENTA] They can't tell
the difference?
Thank you all
for coming out today!
I'm sorry it took me so long!
I've had a lot
on my plate lately,
but I've been dying to see you!
Enta!
Haruka hasn't found out!
[KAZUKI]
Mm.
[HARUKA]
Sara!
[gasps]
[KAZUKI]
Were Mom and Dad angry with me?
[HARUKA] No, but I think
they were worried.
It's kinda weird that you went
and got clothes of your own.
Is it 'cause you don't want
to look like us?
Not exactly.
I'm gonna be
in middle school soon.
Coordinating clothes with
my parents? It's embarrassing.
I think it's fun!
But I'm not all grown
up like you are.
Listen, though.
No matter what clothes you wear,
even if you grow up
and move far away from me,
we're connected, right?
From the beginning to the end.
In a great big circle.
From the beginning,
to the end.
We're connected
in a big circle.
[laughs]
You're the greatest!
Impostor!
You aren't the real Sara!
[gasps]
What do you mean?
What have you done with her,
you wicked beast?
[yells]
Stop this pervert!
--[BOTH grunting]
--Look out, Sara!
She's the real thing!
Nothing's fake about her!
She even knew
my secret passcode!
Uh-oh! Is that
another me up there?
Why are there... two of her?
Sara! Are you okay?
I was taking a little stroll,
that's all.
From the beginning, to the end.
Uh?
The secret passcode!
That we talked about before!
I don't know you.
[grunts] I knew it!
This one's a phony, after all!
Right, Sara?
[SARA'S MANAGER grunts]
Impostor!
--[ENTA yelling]
--[thudding]
Kazu? But I...
--Come back!
--[whooshing]
--Whoa. Stop!
--Hey, Kazu! Wait!
Hey, Kazuki.
[KAZUKI]
It's over.
[ENTA]
Huh?
[KAZUKI]
Everything I've worked for.
[ENTA]
Kazuki.
[TOI] It was bound to happen.
Today was the day. That's all.
Huh? What are you--
[TOI] Listen. Nobody can
keep a secret forever.
We had to deal with it.
Now it's his turn again.
This whole thing
was stupid from the start.
Did you really think you could
hide the truth forever?
[ENTA]
You've said enough!
You don't have any
right to cry over this.
You hurt your brother,
not the other way around.
You're an abuser. You get that?
And you're a murderer,
so shut your damn mouth!
All right, then!
Why don't you tell him?
You're supposed to be
the Golden Duo!
Then wake him up!
Give him a kick in
the ass, damn it!
[KAZUKI]
He's right. I hurt Haruka...
...after I swore
I would never do that again.
I can't fix this.
I can only do harm.
Desire extraction!
[yelling]
[ENTA]
You could have warned us first!
[KEPPI] You know this happens
when kappa zombies appear.
You've been transformed
several times already.
I can't imagine any complaints.
[TOI] And none of that sounds
like a problem to you?
[ENTA] So, this zombie likes
that thing Haruka had?
The bag dealie?
[KEPPI] The "dealie" you are
referring to is a sachet.
A scent pouch.
[ENTA]
If it's important to Haruka,
then we have to
get it back, right?
♪ Time to take back
what I need ♪
♪ I can't leave
'til I retrieve it ♪
[BOTH]
♪ Sachet Sachet! ♪
[NIOINO]
Sachet! Sachet!
[KAZUKI] ♪ Time to
take back what I need ♪
[NIOINO]
Sweet! And spicy!
♪ Deadly secrets
hiding in my history ♪
[BOTH]
♪ Mystery! ♪
♪ Carry on through! ♪
[ALL 3]
♪ How can I connect to you? ♪
[NIOINO]
Smells are feelings!
Memories.
Get a whiff!
[ALL 3]
♪ Deep inside, ♪
♪ your desire's calling me ♪
[NIOINO groaning]
I'm gonna etch her scent
straight into
my olfactory cortex!
[gleeful yelling]
[ALL 3]
♪ Seize the truth, buried away ♪
♪ Is it love? I can't say ♪
[NIOINO]
You're washing away the smell!
♪ Souls combine,
stack up the plates ♪
♪ Mystic ball
deciding our fates ♪
[ALL 3]
Nailed it.
Hold on to what you love.
Or it will just slip
through your fingers!
And I would know!
[yells]
[NIOINO]
Ooh! Whiffed it!
[ALL]
We got it!
[NIOINO sighs]
Spicy.
I see. He was
looking for her smell.
He loved her and he lost it.
[NIOINO]
I'm letting it rip!
Sara!
[BOTH]
[ALL 3]
Sara!
Sarazanmai!
[MALE VOICE]
Leaking.
[KAZUKI]
That day, what Haruka said.
It brought me back
to my real family.
But then...
[KAZUKI'S BIOLOGICAL MOM]
Kazuki.
[KAZUKI] Even meeting her
for the first time,
there was something nostalgic
about her smell.
But why?
Why did Haruka have that?
It was my mom's.
It had to be!
[KAZUKI groaning]
--[popping]
--[yelling]
[NIOINO]
And right back in you go!
[gleeful yelling]
[KEPPI] If you think you're
going to get a Dish of Hope
after that absolutely
foul display, you're wrong.
I'm so angry,
I'm boiling tea on my belly!
That also means I'm not
turning you back, naturally.
What?
[KAZUKI]
I'm better off this way.
What are you saying?
That's crazy!
[KAZUKI]
If he had that sachet,
then Haruka must
have known all along...
[KEPPI grunting]
[KAZUKI] ...that we
weren't real brothers.
[KAZUKI]
I was a little uneasy at first,
but the more I talked to her,
the more I felt like she really
was my mom, after all.
[KAZUKI'S BIOLOGICAL MOM]
The truth is,
I have another family
I love just as much as you.
It's selfish, but...
but I couldn't help it.
I had to see you.
You know,
I really love my family, too.
I have this little brother,
and he's great.
Kazuki.
[KAZUKI] If you don't mind,
can we keep this our secret?
I'll see you off
at the station tomorrow.
[KAZUKI'S BIOLOGICAL MOM]
Sure.
[KAZUKI]
I did the right thing.
Haruka, Mom and Dad.
They are my real family.
[HARUKA]
Kazu!
[panting]
[HARUKA]
Wait for me! Kazu!
Haruka? Why are you here?
Don't go away!
At least take me with you!
I can't.
[ringing]
Is it my fault? Is it
'cause I did something bad?
What? No, this has
nothing to do with you!
I'm sorry, Kazu! I'm sorry!
I swear, I'll be good
from now on!
Don't go! Don't leave me!
[KAZUKI]
Shut up!
[walk sign beeping]
[HARUKA]
Wait.
Kazu! Wait--
--[tires screech]
--[crashing]
[gasps]
[KAZUKI]
Haruka!
I have so much regret.
Like Kuji said.
I just keep hurting him.
Like that accident
wasn't enough.
An accident. Not your fault.
It's not like you
did it on purpose.
That's what everybody says.
My mom, dad, and Haruka, too.
I'm the one
who screwed all this up!
But nobody will blame me!
It's all a lie.
My whole family, it's all fake.
Then they act like
everything's fine,
like they're just waiting
for me to get over it.
But as soon as I see
Haruka's wheelchair,
I can't even breathe.
I thought if I quit soccer,
something might change, but no.
I stole Nyantaro.
I pretended to be Sara,
all for Haruka.
Just so I could...
No, that's not true.
I was just protecting myself.
That's why I lied to him.
That's why.
[REO] So we finally had a
zombie with some backbone.
That's a relief.
[MABU] Indeed.
I was eager to leave our post.
Huh? Having maintenance again?
It's my lifeline,
after all, isn't it?
Huh. Yeah, I wonder about that.
If you ask me, you're just
looking for something
that'll make you feel good.
Nonsense.
Personal feelings such as
those are hardly a priority.
[REO grunts]
Screw this crap.
What the hell do you know?