[MABU]
I'm so hot. Isn't this enough?
[IMPERIAL BOSS]
"Otter" nonsense.
It's far too early to pull out.
[MABU]
But I... I can't take any more.
[IMPERIAL BOSS]
"Otterly" pathetic.
Your endurance really
could use some work.
[MABU]
Please, stop teasing me.
[IMPERIAL BOSS] If you insist,
then pull it out yourself.
-[clattering]
-[gasps]
[IMPERIAL BOSS]
You "otter" know better.
Look at how doughy they are.
Too soon. Too soon.
-May we please try it again?
-[IMPERIAL BOSS] Later.
But first,
some fine-tuning is in "otter."
Why don't you go lay down
and show me what's inside you?
As you wish.
I only want to be desired again.
Whatever it takes,
I'll do it.
[gasps]
[IMPERIAL BOSS]
Mabu, my beautiful doll.
I pity you, like no "otter."
[SARA]
Good morning to you!
Sara Azuma here.
And with my lucky selfies,
you'll be happy every day!
We have a summer break special
on the plate for today!
I'm going to rank all our
previous lucky selfie items
in an extremely biased,
no-holds-barred
elimination match,
where I alone am judge and jury!
[REO] Now that's a balanced
breakfast if I've ever seen one.
Let's dig in!
That I shall.
[REO]
I didn't mean you!
What's the point
in playing this game?
You'll just get sick.
I can actually eat food now.
Thanks to my last maintenance.
Is that so?
You think if you eat
your old favorites,
everything'll be back to normal?
That I'll accept you?
All you're doing here
is playing pretend.
Well, don't bother,
because it's a waste of time.
I know that everything about you
is a lie.
It's not me
that I'm trying to make happy.
[scoffs] Yeah, yeah, you think
I wanna hear this crap?
Reo.
Listen to me.
I don't care.
By the way,
that thing we saw is our secret.
So don't spill it
to your little boyfriend
you're so eager to please.
-All right.
-[SARA] That's all!
[BOTH]
The food was great, thank you!
[HARUKA] Kazu,
I'm sorry it took so long,
but there's something important
I need to give you.
She wanted me to bring it
to you that day.
Actually, could you
keep it for a while?
Huh? I'm confused.
[KAZUKI] For now,
I think it's more important
to build connections
with the people
who are already close to me.
You mean,
people close to you like me?
And like Mom and Dad, too,
maybe?
[laughs]
Yeah, definitely!
That's great!
[munching]
[OTONE]
This is it! Summer's here!
Whether you laugh
or whether you cry,
you're only gonna get one try!
So no matter what you do,
you've gotta give it
a hundred percent!
Whoo!
Been a while. I might be rusty.
-Is that okay?
-[ENTA] You're fine.
Did you let my sister know
that you're planning on
coming back to the soccer club?
Yep!
I'll be in at the start
of next semester.
All right!
We've got all summer to train!
Let's get you back
in fighting shape, okay?
Oh, uh, sorry!
[KAZUKI]
Hey!
Toi!
Get down here!
Why is he so happy?
[KAZUKI]
Come play soccer with us!
I see.
I guess he picked it
back up again.
[grunts]
Whoa.
-Did you used to play, too?
-Uh-huh.
Well, I mean, kinda.
You're way better
than just "kinda!" Aw, man!
You gotta play on the team
with us!
I mean, how fun would that be?
And we already know
our teamwork's solid, right?
Well?
Tell him!
This is great!
Kuji, if you're on the team
with us,
we might even make nationals!
Oh, uh, I don't know.
Huh? You don't want to?
It's not that.
I mean, I wouldn't mind, but--
Oh!
Would you give it up already?
I can tell you're excited!
[yells]
-Your aim sucks!
-[TOI] Nope. Nailed it.
[KAZUKI laughs]
[REO] If I get those dishes,
I can fix all this.
[bubbling]
[gasps]
Mabu!
[IMPERIAL BOSS]
So you're finally awake.
Who are you?
An otter, obviously.
Specifically, I'm the Otter
Empire's Chief "Otticer"
of Science and Technology.
You were caught up
in an accident
during the destruction
of the Kappa Kingdom.
Accident.
Where's Mabu? Is he--
I'm afraid he was
gravely injured.
We were able to retrieve him
from the rubble,
but it was too late.
-[REO] No.
-[clattering]
You can't die!
Do you hear me?
Damn it, Mabu, I'm not letting
you leave this world without me!
I'm right here!
This can't be true!
[IMPERIAL BOSS] "Dis-otter-sty"
is not my policy.
All is just as it appears.
But what if there was some way
that you could
save your partner?
[REO] I would do anything
just to hear his voice again.
He's all I have.
[beeping]
-[TOI] What happened?
-[KAZUKI] Who would do this?
Some sicko, I bet.
What are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
Cleaning up.
This is our spot.
You mean that?
[KAZUKI]
Come on!
Let's do this together!
♪
[KAZUKI]
Okay, see you tomorrow!
[ENTA, TOI]
Yeah.
[MABU] I regret to inform you
that systems are operating
at only thirty-nine percent.
[IMPERIAL BOSS]
Surely not.
[MABU] I would not jest about
such a serious matter.
The kappa zombie reserves
are dwindling.
[IMPERIAL BOSS]
I "otter" remind you,
unless this is remedied,
it puts the survival of you
and your partner in jeopardy.
I'll do everything
I can to fix this.
[IMPERIAL BOSS] Then let's hope
you can prove your loyalty
to the empire without any hint
of "dis-otter-sty."
Now, do you have anything else
to report?
[MABU]
No, sir.
[KAZUKI] My life used to be
weighed down by secrets.
Three rules that decided
everything for me.
[SARA] With my lucky selfies,
you'll be happy
every single day!
[KAZUKI] I had to carry a box,
watch Sara,
and take lucky selfies.
[SARA] Balls!
Like soccer balls!
The more you get,
the happier you'll be!
That's all we have
on the plate for now!
Get Sara-cky!
[KAZUKI] I'm free of that now,
but I still have a few secrets.
Like turning into a kappa,
for example.
[laughs]
And sure, that's stressful.
But I have friends
I've connected with.
We can make it through
anything together.
-[TOI] Seriously?
-[ENTA] They did it again?
We just cleaned this!
[TOI] Well, I guess
we pissed somebody off.
[ENTA]
Huh? Who? Why?
-[KAZUKI] It's fine.
-Kazuki?
Who says we can't
clean it again?
Let's show these bullies
that we're not giving up.
A little trash isn't
going to stop us!
You're right.
Let's do this!
We'll go even faster this time!
[phone ringing]
[ENTA] Damn it!
It's not coming off!
[KAZUKI]
Is something up?
You better hurry!
You owe us croquettes
when we're done here!
Sorry, guys.
[KAZUKI]
Huh? What is it?
[TOI]
Something came up.
Turns out I can't play soccer
with you after all.
[TOI] That call I just got
was from my brother.
One of his jobs fell through.
A major one.
It wasn't exactly legal.
So there's always a big risk.
This time, one of his partners
sold him out.
He's gonna be
a wanted man, soon.
He can't stay in one place.
When he skips town,
I'll be going with him.
And that's that.
Forget what I said
about the soccer club.
-[KAZUKI] Just one more.
-Huh?
One more Dish of Hope!
Then we'll have five
and make a wish!
And then we can use it
to help out your brother!
But Kazuki...
[KAZUKI] If we do that, then you
won't have to leave anymore!
Uh, yeah. I guess.
Then that settles it!
Right? Easy!
You bet!
One more silver plate!
We got your back on this, Kuji!
You heard him!
Don't go anywhere!
We're a team!
[ENTA]
Got that right!
I guess you wouldn't know.
But this is the real Kazuki
you're seeing now.
This is what he was like
before Haruka's accident.
He finally got
his old smile back.
I'd been waiting so long.
I was losing hope.
[TOI]
Are you cool with this?
You said before.
You wanted to spend
the wish on him,
so I'm kinda imposing
on all of that, aren't I?
What's that?
Kuji is worried about me?
Why, up is down and down is up!
I'm serious!
It's just a joke!
I'm sorry.
But yeah, of course I still want
Kazuki's wishes to come true.
That's what I mean!
But right now,
helping you is his wish.
So it all works out fine!
So just smile and say thank you.
-[TOI] Thank you.
-Nah.
That's actually kinda gross.
No deal.
[TOI]
I'll gut your ass!
-[laughs]
-I'm all done!
Let's go see Keppi, okay?
Kero Force, march!
Once again, we shall valiantly
right the wrongs of this city!
Take heed!
This is a kappa.
You positively nailed it!
[KEPPI]
But this... is a mere frog!
You're dishing out truth bombs!
Here's another truth bomb.
You're the only kappa
for me, baby.
[SARA]
Next on the plate: smooches.
You and I are the ultimate
kappa power couple.
[REO, MABU]
♪ Soccer Soccer ♪
♪ Soccer
Soccer ♪
♪ Soccer Soccer ♪
♪ Otter Otter,
Liar liar ♪
♪ My desire,
Soccer Soccer ♪
♪ Getter hotter,
Liar liar ♪
♪ Light the fire,
Soccer Soccer ♪
♪ Otterly sexy! ♪
♪ Soiya! Soiya! ♪
[MABU]
♪ A stolen heart beating ♪
♪ True feelings
never fleeting ♪
♪ Will you tear them free? ♪
[REO] ♪ Synthetic passions
feel as cold as ice to me ♪
♪ What a travesty! ♪
[MABU] ♪ Let desire flow,
Never let it go, ha ♪
[REO] ♪ Let desire flow,
[BOTH] ♪ Wandering an
endless twilight ♪
♪ Morning isn't meant to be ♪
♪ Meet again at
breaking sunlight ♪
♪ Under skies we'll never see ♪
♪ Let desire flow,
Never let it go, ha ♪
♪ Let desire grow,
♪ Otterly sexy! ♪
♪ Soiya! ♪
[bubbling]
[energy whirling, shimmering]
[SARA]
Now for our next dish.
There are soccer balls flying
through the skies of Asakusa
for some unknown reason.
Balls are our friends!
Now be good!
[TOI]
Did something happen?
They're just leftovers,
I think.
Why would Keppi leave his
favorite snack behind, though?
Oh, no.
Do you think he was kidnapped?
[KEPPI]
I've got everything you need.
You can't leave...
Well, there's your answer,
I guess.
[grunts]
[KEPPI]
I sense a disturbance.
Someone has trespassed
in my absence.
It's a home invasion!
[ALL gasping]
[ENTA]
The Dishes of Hope are gone!
Be wary, for this might be
the work of the Otter Empire!
[ENTA]
You mean they found your base?
[yells]
My soccer ball!
[KEPPI] Seems another
kappa zombie has come to play.
[TOI] Damn it, we don't
have time for this right now!
We can worry about the dishes
another day!
Let's get that ball back
and hop to it!
[KEPPI] Was that supposed
to be a frog pun,
you little piece of crap?
[ENTA]
What did I say?
♪
[KEPPI] Seems we have some
manner of ball-zombie this time.
[ENTA]
Seriously, what did I even say?
Would you guys back me up?
[KAZUKI] We'll get those dishes
back somehow.
Just focus on the fight!
[ENTA]
R-Right.
♪
♪ Time to take back
what I need ♪
♪ I can't leave
'til I retrieve it ♪
[BOTH]
♪ Soccer Soccer! ♪
[BALL ZOMBIE]
Balls. Soccer balls.
-[singing continues]
-Kick 'em.
[ENTA] ♪ I can't leave
'til I retrieve it ♪
[KAZUKI, TOI]
♪ Soccer Soccer! ♪
♪ Deadly secrets hiding
in my history ♪
[BOTH]
♪ Mystery ♪
♪ Carry on through! ♪
[ALL]
♪ How can I connect to you? ♪
♪ Share your love,
even if it isn't true ♪
This feeling's
"un-ball-ievable!"
Kick 'em harder! Harder!
Harder!
You kick 'em and they bounce
right back!
It's not fair!
I'm so jealous of balls
I could die!
[ALL]
♪ Give it to me! ♪
♪ Ride the waves into the fray ♪
♪ Seize the truth buried away ♪
[BALL ZOMBIE] You're going
balls-to-the-wall, huh?
Pretty ballsy!
[yelling]
No spitballs. That's not fair!
[thudding]
-[ALL] ♪ Our dishes ♪
-[ALL] Nailed it!
Sarazanmai!
[BALL ZOMBIE]
Good follow-through!
[energy surging]
[ALL]
We got it!
-[energy shimmering]
-[raining]
[BALL ZOMBIE]
Sock it to me!
Oh, weird.
He wanted to be a soccer ball
so his girlfriend
could kick him.
I didn't want to "socc-her,"
I wanted her
to sock me in the balls!
[exploding]
[BALL ZOMBIE]
There goes my secret!
Sara!
[BOTH]
[ALL]
Sara!
Sarazanmai!
[energy bursting]
[energy whirling]
[ENTA yelling]
[MALE VOICE]
Leaking.
[ENTA]
Wait.
No! No!
[chuckles]
Aah!
Make it stop!
[groaning]
No!
[TOI]
No.
[ENTA]
Mess it all up!
[TOI] Why? I thought that place
meant something special to you.
Take this!
[evil chuckling]
[evil chuckling continues]
[ENTA]
You're all mine!
[KAZUKI] Enta, why would you
do something like that?
Damn it!
Why do you care so much
about Kuji?
[dings]
[gasps]
-Reo.
-How?
I'm sorry that I worried you.
Everything's back to normal now.
Who are you?
Mabu's dead.
[MABU] I'm your partner.
What do you mean?
Liar!
The Mabu I know would never look
at me like that!
Do you really think you can
trick me that easily?
The operation was
a complete success.
Even my personality
has been replicated in full.
Shut up!
It's nothing but lies!
[IMPERIAL BOSS] "Dis-otter-sty"
is not my policy.
Mabu has been fitted
with a mechanical heart.
It is functional now,
but he needs your assistance
to keep it that way.
If you're not happy,
merely stop his heart
with your own hands.
I just watched him die.
How could you suggest
I end his life again?
[IMPERIAL BOSS] I expect you
to be "otterly" loyal
to our cause, nothing less.
Which is why I'm sure
you'll accept your transfer
without complaint.
Today, you will be departing
for the human world,
along with the hope we seized
from the Kappa Kingdom.
[DARK KEPPI]
Darkness.
[energy bursting]