-[KAZUKI sighs]
-[ENTA gasps]
[NYANTARO shrieks]
[KAZUKI]
When did I fall asleep?
Hey, Enta.
You... You're gonna catch
a cold sleeping out here.
We should both go home now.
-[KAZUKI] Okay.
-[ENTA] The truth is...
I have a huge crush on him.
Enta! Food is ready!
Okay.
Come on. I know it's Sunday,
but that's no excuse
to be so lazy.
Fish again, huh?
-Pucker up.
-Aah!
This kisu is so fresh,
you'll want to kiss it!
Huh? Kiss the kisu.
Oh, I get it. Very funny.
So, uh, did you get this kisu
from your boyfriend?
I sure did!
He's cute and he's cool
and he always gives me
the seafood hookup!
We're having
a fishing date today!
Well, if things don't
work out with him,
see if you can date
a butcher next time, huh?
[singing on TV]
[singing continues]
[SARA]
Smoochy, smooch!
-[spitting]
-Here, let me get that for you.
Get those kisses!
The more you have,
the happier you'll be!
Ooh, gimme, gimme!
Maybe I'll get a kiss
on our date!
[GRANDMA]
You can have this back.
That's all we have
on the plate for now!
Get Sara-cky!
[ENTA panting]
[sighs]
Thinking back, I don't remember
the exact moment
when I fell in love with Kazuki.
But I know I've had
these feelings
in my heart for a long time.
That's why I won't let him
give up on soccer.
[bubbling]
[ENTA] Because ever since
we were little,
we've been the Golden Duo.
We understand each other
better than anyone else.
My passes are only for him!
His goals are only for me!
I'll make sure his wish
is granted by a Dish of Hope.
Then I'll give him this
and we'll be together again.
There's nothing more I want.
Damn it!
Why did I have to risk
everything with that kiss?
-[city chatter]
-[KAZUKI] What? It's closed?
I can't get a real kiss,
so I thought
I'd kiss some kisu to be funny.
My selfie! I'm done for!
Mm, um, let's see.
-Here. Yeah!
-[ENTA yells]
-You always win!
-Too bad! Guess I'm just lucky!
[ENTA]
Yeah, you're crazy lucky.
I'm starting to think you have
the Goddess of Fortune
on your side.
[laughs]
I've got Sara.
Guess that's close enough!
-[phone dings]
-Oh, a text.
Is that Kazuki?
-Not telling!
-[ENTA chuckles]
[KAZUKI]
I hate to dish-appoint you,
but it looks like my selfie's
gonna be
a bit late today. Sorry!
[HARUKA] No worries.
I know you'll send it soon.
Good luck at work!
[HARUKA]
Kazu doesn't message me.
[ENTA] Well, you see each other
at home all the time,
so I guess that makes sense.
Better than my sister,
who keeps spamming me
with dumb stuff every day.
Kazu seems so upset.
He doesn't smile
like he used to.
I know he loves soccer,
so why'd he quit?
Why'd he throw away his miçanga?
It's not fair.
Watching him
play made me so happy.
You guys were a great team!
[ENTA] Thank you.
Watching him play soccer
made me happy too.
I want him to play again,
but I don't think
there's anything I can do.
Even if I told him,
it's not like
he'd care. You know?
Haruka.
Hey, don't you worry!
I'll get him smiling again
and I'll get him
playing soccer again, too.
Promise!
Leave everything to me!
[laughs]
You're part of the
Golden Duo, after all.
If anyone can
pull it off, it's you!
Uh-huh!
Keiss is awfully late today.
Usually he sends me
a text message, at least.
I wonder what's up?
[phone ringing]
[phone continues ringing]
[electronic whirring]
[ENTA]
Kazuki. Even Haruka noticed
how miserable you've been.
[chuckles]
Well, I guess it's really
none of my business
anymore, is it?
-[KAZUKI] Of course it is!
-[ENTA gasps]
♪
[gasping]
Kazuki? Why are you here?
[KAZUKI panting]
Enta, there's something
I need to tell you.
[inhales sharply]
I...
I've been so lonely without you.
[ENTA whimpers]
[KAZUKI] I want to play soccer
with you, more than anything.
If you'd take me back,
do you think we could be
the Golden Duo again?
[ENTA laughing, gasping]
[ENTA]
Don't ever take it off, okay?
Do you promise?
Of course. I swear to you.
We're the Golden Duo
'til death do us part.
[BOTH laughing]
[BOTH]
Nailed it!
Thank you!
-This miçanga is so cute!
-Huh?
[ENTA]
Why are you here?
I'm on the way to meet
my boyfriend at his fish shop.
See ya!
Hey, wait! That's for Kazuki!
[panting]
-[footsteps]
-[ENTA grunts]
Go away! Why are you here?
-Hey, I know you.
-'Sup? You look pissed.
[grunts]
This spot belongs to me
and Kazuki.
You can't use it.
[BOY 1] Huh? What the hell are
you talking about?
Kazuki's the other
forward from your school, right?
I heard he quit the club,
so what's the big deal?
Yeah. You can't call dibs
if you don't even
have a partner.
Kazuki's coming back soon!
[BOY 1 groans]
Face it, man, he ditched you.
I can tell you're
taking it hard,
but this is getting
pretty pathetic.
[ENTA groaning]
-Shut up, you bastard!
-[BOY 2] Whoa! Stop!
-[ENTA grunts]
-[thudding]
Hey! What the hell
is your deal, you little weirdo?
-[thudding]
-[grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[ENTA yelling]
[MALE OFFICER] We've determined
the identity of the corpse
that was discovered
this morning.
Keiss Memore.
Twenty-seven years old.
Owner of the kisu
specialty shop, Uogashi Keiss.
[MABU singing]
Kissy, kissy.
[MALE OFFICER]
He was arrested six months ago
on suspicion of marriage fraud
after a woman
he was apparently pursuing
committed suicide.
He was eventually released
for lack of evidence.
At any rate, we'll be treating
his death as a murder.
We're the ones who baited him,
of course.
Why, he's merely
yesterday's catch.
[KEISS]
You're floundering, here.
I have a hot date
tomorrow morning,
so let me off the hook,
will you?
[MABU] For those lost souls
with no beginning,
no end, and no connections...
We shall open a brand
new door for you.
-[REO] Is it desire?
-[MABU] Or love?
-[BOTH] Desire extraction!
-[energy surging, exploding]
-[phone clatters]
-[electronic whirring]
[BOTH singing]
Otterly Sexy!
Soiya! Soiya! Soiya! Soiya!
[REO] ♪ Pathetic
livestock, beaten and defeated ♪
♪ Are you man or swine? ♪
[MABU] ♪ Pathetic insects,
living hand to mouth ♪
♪ Do you have a spine? ♪
[REO] ♪ Let desire flow.
Never let it go. ♪
[MABU] ♪ Let desire flow.
Never let it go ♪
[BOTH singing]
♪ We possess a single body ♪
♪ We've attained a second fate ♪
♪ You're the same as anybody ♪
♪ You can strive for
something great ♪
♪ Let desire flow.
Never let it go. ♪
♪ Let desire flow ♪
♪ Never let it go ♪
[BOTH]
Otterly sexy! Soiya!
Otterly sexy!
[bubbling]
-Let desire flow.
-Every last drop.
-[punching]
-[grunting]
[BOY 2]
What's your deal? Stay back!
-[punching]
-[grunting]
-[punching, grunting]
-[BOY 1] You punk!
Damn it, this is
none of your business!
Of course it's my business!
Don't you dare lay a finger
on my Golden Partner!
[BOY 1 grunts]
Enta! Are you okay?
Kazuki. You saved me.
But please don't
put yourself in danger.
If anything happened to you,
then I...
I'd rather die than go on!
We're the Golden Duo.
I'd never leave you alone.
We're gonna be together
to the end!
[BOTH laughing]
[BOTH]
Nailed it!
♪
Stop playing dead.
Huh? Huh?
It's Kuji?
What happened?
-You suck ass at fighting.
-I'm confused.
You mean,
you just rescued me?
[TOI]
Not really.
As soon as they saw me,
they ran away.
This sucks! Ugh!
[TOI]
So who are they?
They're from a soccer team
our school beat last year.
-[TOI] I see.
-Not to brag,
but we took out
a whole bunch of strong teams.
That's because we had Kazuki.
Then he said
he needed a break.
And one day,
he quit
without any explanation.
That was when
you transferred here.
[TOI] If he already quit,
why'd you fight those guys?
'Cause this place...
It's been ours
since we were little kids.
Even if he's not here,
I still can't let it go.
[TOI]
You're like brothers, huh?
[ENTA]
I don't know. Maybe.
We understand
each other at least.
That's why I'm afraid.
I'm worried I
might have lost him.
[TOI]
So what now?
I don't wanna play without him.
So I refuse to accept that
he's decided to quit soccer.
I'll protect this place,
and bring him back here.
Once I have a Dish of Hope,
then that'll be my wish!
What makes you
so sure you'll get one?
[ENTA gasps]
I'm taking them myself.
[energy surging]
♪
[SARA]
Now for our next dish,
there are brides flying
through the skies
of Asakusa
for some reason.
It's carrying you!
[KAZUKI]
What should I do?
There's no kisu anywhere.
All the shops around town
are sold out.
[KEPPI] You can blame
a kappa zombie for that.
[KAZUKI]
Huh?
-[kissing]
-[popping]
[KAZUKI]
Kisu kisses?
-[ENTA] Sis!
-[KAZUKI] Enta! Kuji!
[gasping]
Keppi! Make me a kappa!
[KEPPI]
Desire extraction!
-[ENTA yelling]
-[gobbling]
-[gulping]
-[ENTA yelling]
-[energy shimmering]
-[KEPPI grunting]
[KEPPI]
Kero!
-[popping]
-[ENTA yelling]
[KEPPI]
This kappa zombie
desires kisses
in great quantity.
[TOI]
My brother said that kisses
are the tools of the devil.
[KAZUKI]
They can keep the kisses,
but I need the kisu
for Haruka's sake.
[TOI] I don't care, as long
as I can get my plate.
[ENTA] And I'm here to take
that miçanga back!
♪
♪ Time to take back
I what I need ♪
♪ I can't leave
'til I retrieve it ♪
-[BOTH] ♪ Kissy kisu ♪
-[ENTA] ♪ It hides a secret ♪
♪ That I won't let
anybody see ♪
♪ Time to take back
I what I need ♪
♪ I can't leave
'til I retrieve it ♪
[KAZUKI, TOI]
♪ Kissy kisu ♪
♪ Deadly secrets hiding
in my history ♪
[BOTH]
♪ Mystery ♪
♪ Carry on through ♪
[ALL]
♪ How can I connect to you? ♪
[KEISS ZOMBIE] Kisu!
They're all
for me and none for you!
[ALL]
♪ Deep inside, your desire's ♪
♪ Calling me... ♪
-[singing continues]
-[punching]
-[punching continues]
-[GIRLS screaming]
[KEISS ZOMBIE]
There's lots of fish in the sea
and I want them all!
All their kisses!
I'll take any woman out there!
Gimme, gimme, gimme!
[ENTA]
Quantity over quality sucks
for fishes and kisses!
[song continues]
[spraying]
[KEISS ZOMBIE]
Holy mackerel!
[singing continues]
[ALL]
Sarazanmai!
Nailed it!
[grunts]
If my secret gets out,
no one will wanna kiss me!
You shouldn't plant a kiss
on just anybody!
It's an expression of love that
you share with one person alone!
That's the whole point!
[yelling]
-[KEISS ZOMBIE] Oh, my cod!
-[energy surging]
[ALL]
We got it!
[energy shimmering]
-[exploding]
-[rain falling]
[KEISS]
I'm hungry for more than kisu.
[ENTA] Oh, weird.
Looking at those
puckered fish lips all day,
made him want to do
some puckering of his own.
-[energy shimmering]
-[exploding]
-Sara!
[ALL]
Sara!
Sarazanmai!
[energy bursting]
[energy whooshing]
♪
[ENTA yelling]
[MALE VOICE]
Leaking.
[panting]
[ENTA]
Wait. I remember this.
Don't look!
[yelling] No!
[whirring]
-[gasping]
-[energy whirling]
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
[blowing]
Hmm?
-[KAZUKI] Aw, jeez.
-[energy whirling]
[KAZUKI]
Enta. He kissed me?
-I'm done for!
-[exploding]
[gulps]
[KEPPI]
Desire, assimilated.
[KEISS ZOMBIE]
Now I'm double-dead.
What the... ? It's so late.
What happened?
Hold on.
I had a date today, didn't I?
I thought... [exhales]
But now
I can't seem to remember.
[REO] Humans truly are
a foolish lot, aren't they?
Clinging hopelessly
to such fragile connections.
[MALE VOICE] Incoming
transmission from the Empire.
[IMPERIAL BOSS]
Otterly unbelievable.
The amount of desire energy
transferred our way
has dropped markedly
as of late.
Allow me to remind you,
for the last time,
betrayal means death.
I do apologize.
Someone is interfering.
[IMPERIAL BOSS]
"Otterly" unacceptable.
I don't need your excuses.
I only need results.
[REO]
As you wish.
[KEPPI]
Pity.
Seems it's another silver dish.
Enta, can we talk about
that kiss for a second?
Listen, I was just...
It was a dare from
the soccer club, wasn't it?
I know it's not
really about me.
It's all about you!
[BOTH gasp]
[ENTA] I can't get you out
of my head, Kazuki.
The way you stopped laughing.
Stopped playing soccer.
Maybe you don't want to tell me
what you're going
through right now, but I...
I owe you...
for keeping me
going all these years.
Just this once I wanted
to help you!
-[frustrated yell]
-[KAZUKI inhales sharply]
[ENTA]
I love you, Kazuki!
I want to be
your Golden Partner for life!
[KAZUKI]
Uh?
[KEPPI]
Mm.
[KAZUKI]
I hear you loud and clear, Enta.
-[ENTA gasps]
-Golden Duo.
'Til death do us part, okay?
You mean that?
[BOTH laughing]
[BOTH]
Nailed it!
-[lips smacking]
-[KEPPI moaning]
-[ENTA yelling]
-[retching]
[KAZUKI]
Whoa, what's gotten into you?
[groans] Nothing. I'm great!
[ENTA]
Another fantasy, of course.
Really? Because
you look pretty messed up.
[ENTA] Oh, my clothes? I just
stumbled down some stairs!
[KAZUKI] Ha ha!
You sure can be a klutz, huh?
[ENTA laughing]
Guess so!
[MOUSE squeaking]
-[MOUSE squeaks loudly]
-[ENTA yells]
[ENTA]
Ah, it's no use! I give up.
I can't talk to Kazuki.
I'll never be able
to tell him how I feel!
Did something bad happen?
It doesn't matter anymore.
I'm giving up on him.
No more meddling.
No more expectations.
[ENTA]
Is that... ?
Don't tell.
I grabbed it
when he wasn't looking.
It'd be a shame
if he threw it away.
I'll never be able to run with
Kazu, so I shouldn't keep it.
But someday,
when he's not sad anymore,
you can give it to him.
[ENTA] But, no, I...
I don't have the right
to do that.
Sure you do!
'Cause you're the Golden Duo,
no matter what, right?
[ENTA inhales sharply]
[ENTA] Yeah.
You're right.
Thanks, Haruka.
[KAZUKI'S MOM]
Haruka! It's time to go!
-[HARUKA] 'Kay.
-[ENTA] Right.
By the way, I had a really
awesome dream last night.
[ENTA]
Yeah? About what?
Up in space,
there was a giant Nyantaro.
And I could ride around
on his back!
Then, we met the Little Prince!
-[ENTA] That's so random.
-[BOTH laughing]