[KAZUKI]
Toi!
Where am I?
Just think of it as the past.
Specifically, right after those
little traitors screwed us over.
The outside of
the circle is this way,
but it's down much,
much further.
A place with no connections,
no beginning and no end.
And that means
you have to give up
your connections to get there.
Is it really that easy?
[CHIKAI]
Of course.
Just shoot the Toi of the past.
All you need
is that gun of yours.
[KAZUKI grunts, gasps]
What is this place?
[KEPPI]
It's Toi's past.
I presume he's
erasing it bit by bit
as he travels
outside the circle.
--[BOTH gasp]
--[KEPPI] If he succeeds,
not only will he will erase
his connection to you,
but his existence as well.
I won't let him do that.
[gunshot]
[CHIKAI] Nice work.
Way to wipe it all out.
It can't hurt you anymore
if it never happened
to begin with, right?
[KAZUKI]
We got here too late.
Then what's next?
Where would he be going?
--Four years back.
--[ENTA gasps]
Just think.
If Toi really wants to break
his connection to us,
that's the place.
That day, when we first met
and he gave me the miçanga .
[ENTA]
I see.
--You remember after all.
--[KAZUKI] Yeah.
That really was
the start of everything.
If it wasn't for that miçanga ,
who knows how things
would've turned out for us.
The miçanga hasn't disappeared,
so we still have time
to stop him.
[IMPERIAL BOSS]
Who invited you?
Get "otter" here,
you poison-spewing pests!
--[gushing]
--[BOTH yelling]
[KEPPI]
Oh, no! [farts]
[BOTH]
Keppi!
[KEPPI] I shall try my best
to buy you some time.
Carry on without me!
I have faith in you!
[IMPERIAL BOSS]
My goodness. You stayed behind
in "otter" to let
the rats escape?
You must have a death wish.
You've had your way
for far too long.
We're going to settle this
right here and right now, Otter.
[IMPERIAL BOSS] Are you sure
it was your despair you cut out
and not your common sense?
As if I would lose to someone
as diminished as you.
I've already filled you
with despair once.
If you're so eager for me
to do it again,
I'll oblige!
This is it. Where it all began.
That's right.
Now put a bullet in little you
and your connection is gone.
After that, you'll be
outside the circle.
[TOI] I wanted to
play soccer.
I wanted to go pro.
I had my mom, my dad,
and my brother with me.
I thought I could do anything.
That everything
would work out fine.
Too bad.
Mom and Dad left us behind,
and their poor boy
shot a man dead.
[gunshot]
[TOI] But even after
all that, I wasn't alone.
My brother was
still there for me.
Yeah, right.
You really believe that?
I'm a bad guy, after all.
Obviously, I was just using you.
[TOI]
Still, I was fine with that.
I'd throw anything away.
Do anything.
Whatever it took.
What's wrong?
Still clinging to
those connections,
after you've come so far?
I made this connection
on my own.
I don't need you here to end it.
[gunshot]
Hmm. Bad guys are the ones
who survive in this world.
--Remember that.
--[IMPERIAL BOSS] Otterly.
[TOI]
Goodbye, brother.
Now, finally,
I can bring this to an end.
[gunshot]
--[yells]
--[clattering]
Kazuki!
[grunts]
[TOI]
Why are you here?
[KAZUKI]
To take you back.
I'm sick of you both. Go away!
[gunshot]
[gasps]
The miçanga !
[DARK KEPPI]
Dadadadadadadadadadadada.
Darkness!
[ENTA] Dark Keppi.
Damn it, he tricked us!
Toi.
[grunting]
[KAZUKI] I won't give up
on our connection.
No matter what.
Even if you cut me off,
I'll connect again and again!
[gasps]
[DARK KEPPI]
Dadadadadadadadadada.
Da-Darkness.
Erase all connections
from your memory!
[gasps]
We're falling? What now?
What's that thing?
[ALL yelling]
[KAZUKI]
I know what's it's like.
I wanted to leave
this world, too.
I wasn't connected to anything.
I didn't belong here.
But deep down,
I think I was
waiting for someone.
For a hand to reach out.
A friend to tell me
I was being stubborn.
Then, suddenly,
I found a way to smile again.
I can't lose our connection.
Not after all this.
I can feel it.
Our memories are fading away!
We have to stop this!
[ALL yelling]
[ENTA]
I know what it's like.
I wanted to leave
this world, too.
I've always watched
from a distance,
a coward, lost
in my own reality.
But deep down,
I think I was waiting
for someone.
A hand to pull me out
of all my hopeless fantasies
and into the real world.
I don't know when to quit.
So I'm not letting
go of anything.
Not a single one of these
smiles that we fought for.
Damn it!
It's all slipping away!
We can't give up now!
[ALL yelling]
[TOI] For a long time now,
I've wanted to leave this world.
I wasn't given the chance
to laugh or cry anymore,
and eventually I lost hope.
Deep down,
I think I was waiting.
For a bullet in the head to
free me from this life of crime.
[TOI]
And yet...
...even though I was sure there
was no place left for me...
Even though I was sure
I could throw everything away.
Stop it!
I can't lose you now.
Kazuki. Enta.
I've thrown enough away already!
No more!
Sara!
[BOTH]
[ALL]
Sara!
Sarazanmai!
[KEPPI]
Kero !
--[KEPPI grunts]
--[KAZUKI] All right!
--[ENTA] Kazuki!
--Okay, but what now?
[KAZUKI] We still have
this miçanga . That's enough.
[KEPPI grunts]
[KAZUKI] We just need to
give it to me four years ago.
[cracking]
[BOTH gasp]
[DARK KEPPI]
Dadadadadadadada.
Darkness!
[KEPPI] The time has come.
It seems I must
face my despair,
just like you brave souls.
This will be
the final Sarazanmai.
[ALL 3] ♪ Time to take back
what I need ♪
♪ I can't leave
'til I retrieve it ♪
♪ Our connection! ♪
♪ It hides a secret
that I must ♪
♪ let everybody see ♪
♪ Time to take back
what I need ♪
♪ I can't leave
'til I retrieve it ♪
♪ Our connection!
Precious secrets ♪
--♪ hiding in our history ♪
--[DARK KEPPI] Dadadadadadadada.
[ALL 3]
♪ Set them free ♪
♪ Carry on through! ♪
[ALL 3]
♪ How can I connect to you? ♪
♪ Share your love,
with a heart that's ever true ♪
[IMPERIAL BOSS] ♪ Deep inside,
I exist conceptually ♪
♪ Reflecting desire "otterly" ♪
[ALL 3 gasp]
[ALL]
♪ You can't stop me! ♪
[ALL 3] ♪ Burning hearts,
enter the fray ♪
--♪ Embrace the truth... ♪
--Nailed it!
♪ This is love ♪
♪ I can say,
because I feel it from you ♪
♪ Souls combine
stack up the plates ♪
--Nailed it!
--♪ Mystic ball ♪
♪ deciding our fates ♪
♪ Our wishes ♪
--♪ Our dishes ♪
--[KEPPI yelling]
♪ Sarazanmai! ♪
[DARK KEPPI grunts]
[KEPPI]
I have captured my desire.
Almost there!
[IMPERIAL BOSS]
Forgetting someone?
Damn it! I can't see a thing!
--Let desire flow!
--Never let it go!
Almost there!
Let's...
...go!
[KEPPI]
We're connected!
[IMPERIAL BOSS]
I am Otter.
I am a concept.
I cannot die.
[slowing]
You "otter" believe it.
The time has come at last!
Traverse it!
The River of Desire calls you!
[ALL 3 yelling]
[MALE VOICE]
The future is leaking!
[ALL 3]
I want to connect.
[TOI]
But we're out of time!
[ENTA] If we don't make
this pass, we're done for!
[KAZUKI] This goal is mine!
I want to take it!
[ALL 3]
I want to connect.
[KAZUKI]
But at this rate,
it's not meant to be.
[CROWD cheering]
[beeping]
[ALL 3]
I want to connect.
[TOI]
But I can't be forgiven.
[CROWD cheering]
[ALL 3]
I want to connect.
[ENTA]
But if nothing changes,
I'm afraid
we'll never meet again.
[CROWD cheering]
[ALL 3]
I want to connect.
[KAZUKI] But when I try to
tell them my feelings...
...I lie.
[CROWD cheering]
[ALL 3]
I want to connect.
[TOI] But if I think
you'll throw me away...
...I'll betray you.
[ALL 3]
I want to connect.
[ENTA]
But it's too late now. I can't.
I can't express it.
[TOI] It just feels like
you're all so far away.
[ALL 3]
I want to connect.
[KAZUKI]
So I'm not giving up!
[CROWD cheering]
[ENTA grunts]
I've had enough, okay?
I'm done with both of you!
[KAZUKI grunts]
It's over! Just go away!
--[KAZUKI] Even then...
--[ENTA] Even then...
[TOI]
Even then...
[ALL 3]
Even then, I still...
[SARA]
The dish is the vessel of life.
So long as it has form, someday,
it will wear down and break.
What they saw was not
the future. It was the past.
A future that could
have been a possibility.
[KEPPI] The great circle of
this world was preserved today.
And although the
future is ensured,
it is not necessarily
a bright one.
Thus is life.
Where hope and despair
walk ever hand-in-hand.
[gasps]
It's the Little Prince
and a princess, too!
[SARA]
You must never forget.
The future of this world
can only be claimed
by those who connect
their desires
through their shared
pain of loss.
[HARUKA] I get it.
It's my future to choose.
I'm gonna believe in that
and believe in my friends.
Because I care about them.
Sometimes I'm happy
and sometimes I'm sad.
But I know they feel
the same way.
That's why we're connected.
[MALE OFFICER] Don't come
back here again, all right?
You have a new life, kid,
and it begins now.
[TOI] This world is built
upon connections.
[TOI]
People share blood,
the city they live in,
even their desires.
Lucky to be a froggy!
Froggies are always lucky!
You'll be "hoppy" every day!
[TOI]
Everyone is connected somehow.
But everything in my life
has already ended.
I can't get back what I've lost.
[TOI]
Who the hell cares?
[KAZUKI] ♪ Time to take back
what I need ♪
♪ I can't leave
'til I retrieve it ♪
[ENTA]
♪ Our connection! ♪
[KAZUKI] ♪ Precious secrets
hiding in our history ♪
[ENTA]
♪ Set them free ♪
[gasps]
Welcome back, Toi!
[gasps] We've been waiting!
[TOI]
Why are you here?
--Huh?
--Oh?
Don't you realize
I'm sick of you two?
[ALL 3]
♪ Sing our song every day ♪
♪ A miracle, moments away ♪
♪ Hand in hand, come what may ♪
♪ We're ready for tomorrow ♪
♪ Souls combine,
stack up the plates ♪
♪ Mystic ball,
deciding our fates ♪
♪ Our wishes ♪
♪ Our dishes ♪
Sara!
[BOTH]
[ALL 3]
Sara!
Sarazanmai!
[boat horn honks]