[SARA] Good morning to you!
Sara Azuma here!
With my lucky selfies,
you'll be happy...
[KAZUKI'S DAD]
Any word from Kazuki?
[KAZUKI'S MOM]
He texted me last night
and said he was staying over
at Enta's, but that's it.
[KAZUKI'S DAD]
I never noticed before,
but I suppose
they are a bit alike.
[KAZUKI'S MOM] That might be
the only explanation we get.
[SARA]
Sachets?
Sachets? Well, okay!
Sachets again today!
[HARUKA]
Kazu! Wait!
You should give
this back to him.
I'll do that, thanks.
[SARA chuckles]
[SARA] That's all we have
on the plate for now!
Get Sara-cky!
[HARUKA]
Kazu.
[loud munching]
Kappas for life!
'Cause when you're green,
cucumbers rock the scene!
He's officially lost it.
[KEPPI]
Kazuki, raging like a tsunami!
Enta challenges him valiantly!
[ENTA grunts]
I don't have any
business doing sumo.
My business is yours, too!
[KEPPI] You're still in!
You're still in!
--You're still in, Kero!
--[ENTA yelling]
[ENTA] My naked skin
pressed against his!
Don't you hold back!
You know I want it all.
Kazuki, I...
I'm about to lose it.
[KAZUKI] Enta,
the Golden Duo never quits!
[ENTA yells]
--[ENTA] Another fantasy, huh?
--[KEPPI] A Kazuki victory!
[KAZUKI]
Enta.
Did you get hurt? Take my hand.
There's no way this is real.
--[snaps]
--[ENTA yells]
--I'm not dreaming?
--[KEPPI] Uh-huh.
[KAZUKI, ENTA]
Kappas for life!
[ALL laughing]
[SARA]
Next on our plate,
yesterday's flying
sachet incident continues,
without any sign of stopping.
Asakusa Police believe
a criminal organization
is responsible,
but they don't have any leads.
Sasheeeh!
Funny.
They're following up
on the story for once.
Usually they just drop it.
[ENTA]
I guess you're right, huh?
Don't talk to me! Hmph!
[ENTA] Hey, let's go
to the amusement park!
People can't see us,
so we can get in for free!
[gasps]
Hello, soccer ball!
--And why are we here?
--Just for a laugh.
It's where I used to change
into my Sara costume.
Man, that was
pretty stupid, huh?
Where'd I get that idea?
--[KEPPI] Kero !
--[KAZUKI laughs]
[TOI] You worked
pretty hard at it, though.
[KEPPI]
Now me!
[KAZUKI]
Well, it's all over now.
Come on! Let's have some fun!
-- Kappas for life!
--[KEPPI] Kero . Pole dance!
Play it cool, and just give him
a pass, like old times.
[KAZUKI]
Hey, Enta!
Let's do this!
Do you really mean it?
I was so sure
that you'd given up!
Your business is mine, too!
Don't you know?
The Golden Duo will never die!
Kazuki. Here goes!
[KAZUKI]
Enta!
This is my Miracle Shot.
Headed straight to your heart!
Kazuki!
Goal!
[crowd cheering]
[KAZUKI]
Hello! Enta?
[gasps]
I spaced out.
Okay. Here it comes!
Sorry, Enta.
I gotta use the bathroom.
Shouldn't get my hopes
up like that.
[TOI] You realize he's only
going to get worse and worse.
I can see that myself,
thank you.
Wait a sec!
There's a great
cucumber spot over here.
You're gonna love this place.
What the hell
is a cucumber spot?
[HARUKA]
Nyantaro! Come and eat!
Hmm?
Well, darn.
Shoulda figured.
We sure came late today,
didn't we? I'm sorry.
[meows]
[HARUKA]
Hey, Nyantaro.
I'm worried.
Kazu didn't come home.
[HARUKA]
I hope he gets my message.
Huh?
I don't remember
getting that app.
[REO]
Is that a bad boy, I see?
[HARUKA]
Hello, sir.
[REO]
Hmph.
Did you come here to arrest me?
[REO] Do you want to
make a confession?
I didn't mean to, but I took
Kazu's happiness away.
Kazu? Who?
He's my big brother.
He hasn't come home
since yesterday.
I see. I know that feeling.
I'm missing a special
someone, myself.
[HARUKA]
Are you a bad boy, too?
[REO gasps]
Of course not!
Why, he's the bad one!
He's betraying me again.
With that calm look on his
face, like nothing's wrong.
All his emotions spilled
right out. Like a broken doll.
[HARUKA] I want Kazu
to smile again, that's all.
I see.
Then why don't you show me
what's inside of you?
When I open the door,
what will I find?
Desire? Or love?
The future
can only be claimed...
...by those who can
connect their desires.
[NYANTARO hisses]
--Oh, shut up.
--[NYANTARO shrieking]
[ENTA] Come on! You have
to face the facts eventually!
[KAZUKI]
No, I don't!
Haruka has nothing
to do with me anymore!
[ENTA] That's not true!
He's still--
[ENTA yells, grunts]
[KAZUKI]
Nyantaro?
Haruka's gone. Huh?
Your dad got
knocked out or something!
[phone dings]
--[phone ringing]
--[KEPPI yells]
--That is not natural.
--[TOI] It's creeping me out.
Yes? Hello, kero ?
What unfortunate news.
Haruka Yasaka has been taken
by the Imperial Army.
Whoa, no way!
Uh, what's the Imperial Army?
[KEPPI] The enemy who brought
ruin to the Kappa Kingdom.
[TOI]
Why are they kidnapping people?
What do they do with them?
They're murdered and turned
into kappa zombies.
[gasps]
[KAZUKI]
I won't let that happen!
Come on. Let's save him!
We were expressly forbidden
to act on our own, you know.
Ha! You're slaying
me with irony!
We shall open a brand
new door for you.
[MABU]
Is it desire? Or love?
[REO, MABU]
Desire extraction!
[ENTA]
Otter Empire?
[KEPPI] Otters and kappas have
been at war for a long time.
This is merely the
most recent development.
Now follow me, if you would.
[TOI] Why did you have to
drag us into your mess?
[KEPPI]
Currently, we are entangled
in a struggle for shirikodama ,
or more specifically,
desire energy.
After crushing
the Kappa Kingdom and seizing
all of our desire energy,
the Otter Empire turned
to humans as their next target.
[TOI] So you're a survivor who
escaped from a ruined kingdom?
--[ALL gasp]
--A survivor who can produce
Dishes of Hope, as you know.
A gift that is mine alone.
If the Empire were
made aware of this fact,
they would most certainly
come for my life.
[ALL yelling]
[pounding]
Holy crap! What's that?
[KEPPI] Welcome to the secret
hideout of the Otter Empire!
[KAZUKI, ENTA, TOI gasp]
Where did they take Haruka?
[KEPPI] They put everything in
boxes, so he's in one of these.
[ENTA] But there's a million
of them! We can't open them all!
[TOI] Where the hell
are they going, anyway?
[KAZUKI]
Hold on.
[grunts]
[phone rings]
--[phone rings]
--[gasps]
[phone ringing]
[KAZUKI grunts]
It's that one!
[ALL grunt]
--[ALL panting]
--[yells] Stop!
It's a straight drop down.
What now?
[KAZUKI yelling]
[thuds]
KAZUKI]
Enta!
Just go, Kazuki!
Haruka needs you!
[panting]
[alarm blaring]
[grunts]
[KEPPI]
Kero!
--[grunting]
--[gate slams]
[ENTA]
Kuji!
This isn't over yet.
Don't lose hope!
Now haul some ass!
Hey, Haruka!
Your brother's here!
[exploding]
Haruka!
Noooooo!
[KAZUKI whimpering]
It can't be. We were too late?
[KEPPI] Do you truly want
to save your brother?
[whimpering]
You mean, he's not dead?
[KEPPI]
He won't be
if I transplant your
shirikodama into him.
I'm willing to help,
but I would not make that
decision lightly if I were you.
[KAZUKI]
But you can do it?
[KEPPI] Of course I can,
and it is the only way.
Hold on!
What happens to Kazuki
after you take out
his shirikodama ?
Will he die like
all the kappa zombies?
Don't let that happen!
The shirikodama allows
humans to form connections.
Without its presence,
their links to others
are completely severed.
They're ejected from the circle
that makes up our world.
Ejected? What does that mean?
[KEPPI] More than fading away
in the traditional sense,
it will be as if Kazuki Yasaka
never existed
in this world at all.
Every memory of you will be
erased and every event
relating to your time on Earth
will be completely undone.
That's worse than death!
I wouldn't wish that on anybody!
And that happens to the other
kappa aombies, too?
So we've just been erasing them?
Does that mean...
...Haruka's accident
would be erased as well?
[KEPPI]
It does, indeed.
I'd be gone. That's it.
I have to save him.
Please, do the transplant.
[BOTH gasp]
I won't try to stop you.
Muster up some courage,
and you may descend
into the pit on this.
True to my word,
I shall sever your shirikodama
and give it to Haruka.
I'm ready.
[ENTA]
Kazuki! Stop it!
Don't you move an inch!
[KAZUKI]
I get it now.
All my life,
I've been outside the circle.
If I was never born,
everything would work out.
This is my last chance.
Even if I can't connect,
I can make things right.
--[clicks]
--[clattering]
You can't do this, Kazuki!
Even if it brings him back,
it's not what Haruka would want!
It's all right,
once this is over,
he won't even remember me.
He'll be living
a much better life.
That goes for you, too, Enta.
Soon, you'll forget
all about me.
I am not forgetting you, okay?
You have got to
stop this, Kazuki!
[TOI]
There's no time!
[ENTA]
No!
[screaming]
[ENTA]
Kazuki!
[TOI]
Is he okay?
--I think.
--[TOI, ENTA] Up you go!
[KAZUKI, ENTA sigh]
--What the hell, man?
--[KAZUKI] Why?
Why did you get in my way?
It's my life, isn't it?
I can give it up if I want!
The world's better off
without me! Don't--
--[punches]
--[thudding]
Come on. Don't waste time
feeling sorry for yourself.
Think of another solution!
I'll protect you,
even if I have to
protect you from yourself!
[gasps]
But why?
I thought I threw that away!
Haruka gave it to me!
'Cause he never stopped
believing in you!
And he's waiting for you
to come and save him!
[FEMALE VOICE]
Result: Love. Box: Return.
Look at that.
[KEPPI]
Seems he's still alive!
The box came back up!
Haruka!
[gasps]
[ALL grunting]
[HARUKA] Dear Sara,
I had a lot of fun
connecting with you every day,
but I think it's best
for me to stop now.
So, this is my
last message to you.
[grunts]
[HARUKA]
But, before I say goodbye,
can I tell you
a secret about myself?
The truth is,
I did something bad.
There was a lady
that my brother Kazu
cared about a lot,
and I hurt her.
[KAZUKI] You're wrong, Haruka.
This is not your fault!
[HARUKA]
I was afraid she was gonna
take Kazu far away from me.
So I followed him even though
I know I shouldn't have.
[HARUKA]
That day, when he wasn't there,
I picked up something
Kazu's real mom left behind.
It smells just like Kazu.
Hi, there! You wouldn't happen
to be Haruka would you?
You need to leave Kazu alone!
Go away!
And don't ever come back!
She wasn't mad.
She just smiled and said,
"It's okay. Don't worry."
She looked
just like my brother.
He never said anything,
but after that,
Kazu stopped smiling
and threw out his miçanga .
I knew it was my fault,
but I didn't want to lose him.
No matter what.
I wanted to see him smile again.
He's done so much for me.
I'm so happy
that he's my brother!
So no matter what,
I'm never gonna give up on him.
I know he'll come back someday,
and I know he'll smile
again someday, too!
--Haruka!
--[ENTA] Kazuki!
We can't do anything
from down here! Got a plan?
Damn it!
We made it so far, too!
[clattering]
That thing's gonna
shred him up. There's no time!
[ENTA]
Think! Think!
[KAZUKI] We don't have anything
to work with!
Please.
No.
Come on, there's gotta
be something, right?
Yeah, like what?
[KEPPI] I know this will be
difficult for you,
but please take this
adorable body of mine and--
[KEPPI grunts]
[KEPPI yelling]
Got a pass coming
your way, Jinnai!
[KEPPI]
Kero !
[TOI]
Kick it to Yasaka!
He can stop
the crane if he hits it!
[ENTA]
Wait! He won't play anymore!
[KAZUKI]
Enta!
Gimme a pass!
[HARUKA] He can be
a little stubborn sometimes,
but once he sets
his eyes on the goal,
Kazu never gives up.
--Here it comes! You got this!
--[KEPPI yelling]
Thanks, Enta!
[HARUKA]
And even when he's grumpy
or he keeps to himself
a whole bunch, I don't mind.
Because I know he's
a nice person under all that.
Haruka!
I'm always here for you, 'kay?
I won't give up!
On either of us!
[KEPPI yelling]
[KEPPI grunts]
[KEPPI]
Kero !
[HARUKA] You act like
you're all alone sometimes,
but I'm not the only one who
wants to see you smile again.
Remember, Kazu,
you're in the middle
of a great big circle.
[grunts]
[KAZUKI, ENTA, TOI]
We did it!
I whiffed it again!
--This totally stinks!
--[bursting]
[exploding]
[ALL]
Sarazanmai!
[KEPPI]
Desire assimilated.
[NIOINO ZOMBIE]
Now I'm double-dead!
[MABU]
They stole our target yet again.
They've discovered
our hidden base as well.
This error could
very well jeopardize
the success of our mission.
[REO]
It's nothing to flip out about.
And that kid
we lost was useless.
All he had was love.
[laughing]
You're laughing. What is it?
Maybe he's not useless.
I owe him one.
You see that? That's our hope.
[ENTA]
Okay, forget cucumbers.
--Humans for life!
--[TOI] Agreed.
Hey, uh, I'm sorry.
I've kinda been a jerk.
Whatever.
Sure you don't want
to stay a kappa after all?
It's so weird.
I know I'm the same as before,
but I feel like
a completely new person.
This is the real me.
And hey,
I'm glad I have you.
Thanks, guys.
[screaming]
There you are!
[pained grunting]
[KEPPI]
My desire is shattering!
D-D-D-Darkness!
[MABU]
Reo, move out of the way!
Mabu, why? Why would you
sacrifice yourself for me?
[MABU] Let desire flow,
every last drop.
The future belongs to those
who can connect their desires.
Never let it go.
[REO]
Mabu!