♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(glass breaks)
(singing in Japanese)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(singing in Japanese)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Palm Beach.
Pleasant scenery,
old money, perfect spot
for a perfectly
respectable charity event,
not that this was one,
but it explains why
the people behind
this private auction
of smuggled antiquities
billed it as such.
It was a perfect cover.
♪
(gunshot)
Also, a perfect target.
And everything was
going perfectly too,
until a certain someone
showed up and pulled
what, for her, is an
annoyingly typical stunt.
When will I ever learn?
Anyway, she,
the hijacked hearse,
and all the stuff
in the caskets in back
have been missing ever since.
♪
(tires screech)
So, just another day
at the office, right?
Wrong.
Meet Cornelia.
She's the brains behind
the whole auction thing,
and more to the point,
the same girl who,
years earlier,
had taken a bullet for me
and died on the spot
right in front of my eyes.
♪
Yeah, I know,
my head hurts too,
which is why I hopped
the first plane
to South America
to pay a little visit
to the cemetery
where she was buried.
There were signs the
grave had been disturbed,
and when I opened
up the casket,
I was disturbed,
to say the least.
♪
Course, you could
say I was lucky.
I mean, sure, I was confused.
I was upset!
But at least I wasn't
attacked by an army
of the undead the way
Jigen and Goemon were
when they showed up.
But they're bright guys.
They discussed the
whole thing coolly
and rationally,
and came up with a plan.
They ran like a pair
of cheap nylons
screaming so high
chandeliers were exploding
all the way to
Tierra del Fuego.
And why not, I mean, come on...
zombies?
(typewriter keys clacking)
♪
I'm telling you,
Lupin's the key
to this whole thing!
We catch him,
it's a twofer.
Excuse me.
We came up with a name
behind that Starry Night
charity event.
Well, out with it, come on!
Seems the place was
booked in the name
of some guy who owns
a cemetery in Venezuela.
Well, what do you know?
All right, that's it.
‐I'm going!
‐Inspector, you can't believe
a thief of Lupin's caliber
would take up grave robbing.
Argh, you don't get it,
it doesn't matter to him
if it's a damn cemetery
or a cement factory!
Look, see that cockroach there?
That's him, that's Lupin.
You leave anything out,
anywhere‐‐argh‐‐
and he'll come after it.
♪
Hmph.
Anderson, get
that off my desk!
Right there!
Get it off,
get it off right away
before it looks at me!
♪
So, this is the scene
of the crime, huh?
This is where Zell had
his whole island of
Dr. Mengele thing going?
Yeah, but it looks
a lot creepier now.
Back then it was beautiful,
full of flowers.
You would've never suspected.
I suspect you're
going back there.
That's right.
Yeah, well, I suspect
you weren't listening
real good when we
told you about...
those whatever they were.
What, you never saw
a hypnotized corpse before?
What's that?
You wanna explain?
That was the subject
of Zell's research
for the Nazis,
his Holy Grail.
The idea was to
preserve a corpse
immediately after death
in such a way as to retain
control of its motor functions.
The brain would be dead,
but the body would live on.
(explosion)
♪
The appeal for
the Nazis was obvious.
The soldiers killed
in battle could be
immediately recommissioned
if you could find a way
to somehow control their bodies.
Eegh.
What the hell kind
of people come up
with this kind of crap?
So, you're saying
this actually worked?
Apparently, it did,
but I hope not.
I don't think Fujiko's
mysterious disappearance
was coincidental.
If she's anywhere, it's there.
See ya around.
When she took off...
...I think I managed
to plant a tracer on her.
I hope.
Let's see.
Yeah, look, she's there.
(beeping)
(metal clicking)
Huh?
Still waiting for
Lupin, are you?
It seems like you're
more anxious about it
than I am.
Hmm, tell me...
why is it you place
so much faith in that man?
Just about the only
thing I'm certain of
in this whole,
ridiculous world
is that I'm the love
of that man's life.
Love?
I...
♪
(shuddering)
Welcome to the Portals
of Eternal Peace.
From this point forward,
the departed must undertake
the remainder of
the journey alone.
All others are requested
to leave the area
at this time.
(mechanical whirring)
Number 46025 to cosmetics.
Number 31107
to the crematory.
This is nice
and peaceful.
Number 31107 to the crematory.
Wait, what did she say?
31107?
That's me!
♪
(muttering)
Oh!
Come on!
Damn it, Jigen, no one asked
you to nail the damn thing shut.
♪
(whimpers)
Why me?
(struggling)
(wood creaking)
You‐‐wait a minute.
Sergio, right?
I remember you!
Oh, man, that was close.
I mean, wow,
that was real close.
‐I mean, that was real‐‐
‐Yes, I know, come on.
(mechanical whirring)
I get it now, so that's
how you managed to smuggle
in all that stuff
without being detected.
So, Sergio, tell me something.
That can't really
be Cornelia.
Is it a robot or something?
(Sergio groans)
‐It...it is Miss Cornelia.
‐Huh?
The Doctor was
destroyed, desperate.
He marshaled
all his efforts,
a lifetime of research
to somehow bring her
back to life.
Once he restored
the electrical
currents to her body,
he implanted a device‐‐
a micro‐neuro
something or other‐‐
inside her brain.
He controlled the device by
means of a massive computer
in which he managed to
replicate all the contents
of his own consciousness.
She exists, but only
as an extension of
the doctor's will.
(groaning)
♪
So, if I understand you,
the body alone is
all that remains of her.
But is it that she has
no mind of her own
or is it that her mind
is being controlled
by her father and his computer?
I've told you everything
that I know, now please,
you must leave
here immediately
with that friend of yours.
Friend‐‐you mean Fujiko?
Tell me where she is!
Ta‐da, the cavalry is here.
Ah!
Quit clowning around
and get me out of here.
All right, all right.
Well, you coming?
That's it, not even
a "Thank you, Lupin"?
I'll take it in
saliva if you prefer.
You took your sweet
time about it,
and anyway, there's a fortune
waiting in the basement.
So, sorry‐‐hmph!
See you later.
Could somebody
please remind me
why in the hell it is
that I even bother?
♪
Well, she was right about him.
I just know he's
in there somewhere.
How do I get inside there,
that's the question.
Huh.
♪
All right, easy now.
Almost there.
Just don't look down.
That's it, one more step...
ah!
Damn it, I've come
too far to...agh!
♪
Hmm, not that these places give
me the creeps or anything but‐‐
(ghoulish hissing)
♪
(groans)
(shrieks)
(panting)
♪
Hm?
(panting)
Hmm, must've been a dream.
Yah!
‐It can't be.
‐Huh‐‐Lupin!
A‐ha!
It's amazing‐‐what, do you
get in through the cracks
like a freakin'
cockroach or something?
Hmm?
♪
(groans)
That's my simile!
Look, Lupin, all that matters
is that I'm here
and your ass is mine!
♪
(grunts)
Huh?
What the hell?
(metal creaking)
Lupin, get up.
Cor‐‐Cornelia?
♪
Put down the gun.
Please, don't do something
you're gonna regret.
Don't worry, I won't.
Cornelia, listen, I‐‐
(gunshot, Lupin groans)
♪
Wait, Cornelia!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Don't waste your
breath, Lupin.
♪
It's all over.
Go ahead, then.
I suppose if anyone has
the right to take my life,
Cornelia, it's you.
You already saved it once
by paying for it
with your own life.
It's yours to take back.
I gave up my life for you?
You really don't remember?
Your father had always
shielded you from
the true nature of his work,
but inevitably you
discovered the gruesome truth.
I was a prisoner.
We'd fallen in love.
We ran away
or we tried to but‐‐
Cornelia, I am warning you.
Step aside!
‐(gunshot)
‐(Cornelia gasps)
No, Cornelia!
That's impossible,
you're lying!
(gunshot)
That isn't the way
it happened, you shot me,
you killed,
it was you, it was you!
(Cornelia whimpers)
♪
Cornelia, I'm sorry, but...
it's true.
♪
Cornelia, please, come back!
Cornelia!
Wow, would you look
at all of those
just waiting there
to be unpacked.
Eenie, meenie, miney, mo.
(giggles)
(ghoulish growling)
(Fujiko shrieks)
(growling)
Come on, move your
samurai ass, man.
All right, all right.
(grunting)
Well, no sign of
the zombie squad.
Huh?
You were saying.
‐Huh?
‐Help!
Somebody please!
Fujiko, what happened?
You gotta help me.
Nice to see you, too.
Now, just calm down, all right?
Tell me, where's Lupin?
‐Crap, I‐‐
‐What?
He's still inside.
Huh?
You again.
I thought...
♪
Wait a sec, I get it.
He's not really alive.
He's just refrigerated.
What is life, Herr Lupin?
What?
Is this some kind
of trick question?
Consciousness is life, and
mine lives on as you can see.
The body is vanity,
nothing more.
Perhaps useful
as cannon fodder,
but otherwise just a clumsy
und vulnerable vessel.
Your life is trapped
inside that vessel,
a helpless prisoner.
Let me show you what awaits
it momentarily, Herr Lupin.
♪
(Lupin shudders)
I suppose I should thank you.
It was you who spurred
the triumphant culmination
of my life's work.
(mechanical whirring)
The will of a real man,
a worthy man, is only
strengthened by pain.
The desire to
save my daughter
and have my revenge on you
endowed me with
the will of a super man.
Witness now the
triumph of that will.
Not the final triumph.
Though, that will come too.
I can assure you with
Cornelia's continued assistance,
and you out of ze way,
that is only
a matter of time now.
Well, if you're looking
for congratulations,
it won't be coming from me
and not from
Cornelia either.
She hated everything
you were doing, Zell,
and you know it,
that's why she ran away.
This Cornelia is not
a romantic sentimentalist.
She takes after her father!
She has no will of her own.
She is you!
Tell her the truth, Zell.
Is it true what
he says, Father?
That I used to love him
and that you‐‐that it was you?
Cornelia, don't
be impertinent.
I have told you
what happened,
and you have
your instructions!
(Cornelia whimpers)
Try, Cornelia.
You can do it, remember?
♪
(shuddering)
Cornelia, you're resisting me.
Do not resist me!
Shoot him, shoot him, Cornelia!
(explosions)
(Cornelia moans)
I...can't.
I can't.
You must, I command you!
Do it, do it!
Kill him!
(gunshots)
(grunts)
We can't win this one, guys.
Come on, let's get out of here.
That's not the way a guy
makes this kind of call.
(ghoulish hissing)
And anyway, Lupin
is still in there.
Come on, Goemon.
♪
If that's how men are made,
then thank God I'm a woman.
Uh, on the other hand,
hey, wait up!
(panting)
(screams)
Jigen.
(Goemon grunts)
I don't understand.
(ghoulish groan)
(Goemon struggling)
Goemon!
Don't worry, it's okay.
I think that I'm all right,
but we really have
to find Jigen.
(Jigen whimpers)
Well, that was fun,
but where the hell am I?
♪
What's that?
Cornelia, get up
on your feet now!
Schnell!
Cornelia!
It's in there,
Cornelia, find it.
(animalistic growling)
♪
Yes, yes!
Do it, do it!
♪
(gunshot)
(Cornelia grunts)
Cornelia, no!
Jigen!
Sorry, Lupin.
She didn't give me any choice.
(Lupin whimpers)
Not again.
♪
(Cornelia whimpers)
Oh, Lupin...
Yes, I do,
I remember now.
We used to love each other.
♪
It was nice, wasn't it?
Our love?
Yes, it was.
(whimpers)
Don't be upset, my love.
That means I lived.
Thank you.
Thank you!
(breath shudders)
This...this is the end!
Ze end of everything.
Love is a flaw.
The soul of chaos,
the undoing of all great things.
There is no hope for man.
If you dare look man's
fate in the eye, Mr. Lupin,
look at your beloved right now!
Look, look!
(alarms beeping)
You're wrong, Zell.
Man himself is
a failed experiment.
Auf Wiedersehen.
(explosions)
(alarms blaring)
(crash, rumbling)
Son‐of‐a‐bitch, let's go.
Jigen, wait, I can't
leave her like this.
Damn it!
(heavy breathing)
What's going on, Goemon?
Why aren't they
moving anymore?
(ghoulish groans)
(growling)
I don't know.
Goemon, look!
(rumbling)
♪
Huh?
Sergio, I was afraid you‐‐huh?
I was prepared for
this for a long time.
The Doctor was a man of great
will and determination,
but Cornelia had
the same strength,
and her love for you brought
it out for the first time.
It was inevitable that
something would trigger it again
and make the device
he implanted in her
a battleground
between the two of them.
We can't really
control each other.
Even the things we love
the most we have to let go of.
But not from our memories.
Never from our memories.
Never.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
See, the thing
about chicks is
you gotta keep 'em guessing.
Don't let 'em get comfortable,
that way they'll never make
a complete fool out of you.
Then again, with some
you just strap on
the old Bozo nose
and play the pity angle,
which is pretty much
what I do in the next one
when I take up with an
intoxicating new partner.
Check out my suave moves
in Emmanuelle in Bangkok.
Catch you later!
♪