♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
(glass shattering)
(singing in Japanese)
♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
(singing in Japanese)
♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
(gunshot)
(gunfire)
♪
Oh, yeah, still got it!
Good shooting, Inspector.
Inspector Zenigata, please
report to the director
of Japanese operations.
Yup, that whole division
would just fall apart
without old Zenigata.
Reassigned?
What the hell
are you talking about?
I know this comes
as a shock to you.
You're kidding, right?
I mean, come on, taking
me off the Lupin case?
That's just some French idea
of a joke or something, right?
This is no joke, Inspector.
What's that?
These are your
transfer documents.
Let me see this.
Hmm, this is crazy.
Hmm.
".. a repeated
failure to arrest"?
What idiot wrote this thing?
It's all lies,
a bunch of ass‐covering BS!
In point of fact,
I wrote it myself,
but understand
something, Inspector:
It represents
the unanimous concerns
of the department.
(blows)
(coughing)
But why, tell me!
No, no, Inspector
no melodrama.
But, sir, how could
I possibly hope to improve
my job performance
if I don't know
what my deficiencies are?
I'm just asking
for a second chance.
And... and I'll bring you Lupin's
head on a platter, sir, I swear!
Come on, how many times
have we both heard you say
those very words, Zenigata?
Uh, I dunno, about
a thousand, I guess?
But sir, I meant
it every single time.
No points for sincerity
in this game.
Hmm?
Right, Mr. Director?
Sir, it's‐it's Fujiko!
That's Inspector Fujiko to you,
the very special agent
in charge of the Lupin case
as of this moment.
It‐‐it's some kind
of nightmare!
Mademoiselle Mine
approached us with
the outline of a mutually
beneficial arrangement.
In exchange for my assistance
in capturing Lupin, all charges
against me will be dropped.
Huh, Fujiko working for us?
Why, that's crazy talk!
Mais oui, crazy like
a fox, Inspector.
Think about it, Inspector.
I mean, nobody knows Lupin's
weaknesses better than I do.
Yeah, I suppose so,
but the whole idea's
totally reckless!
And yet, everything, Inspector,
that we've tried has failed.
Now, we must get creative.
It cannot hurt.
You can go back to Japan;
we'll call you and let you
know how it all turns out.
I swear, I'm gonna
have a friggin' stroke!
(typewriter clicking)
♪
(birds chirping)
(boat horn)
She won't; she'll be here;
she won't...be here.
Won't, be here.
Won't.
Hmm.
(blows)
Come here often?
No, but I'm willing
to inaugurate a new tradition.
(chuckles)
God, you're such
a smutty little monkey.
Why in the world
can't I resist you?
Oh, did I just hear you say
what I think I heard you say?
Have I waited that long?
I mean, are your senses
starting to deteriorate?
Nah, but let's test them
just in case, shall we?
(boat horn)
Well, that certainly
did not take very long.
That girl has got him eating
out of her little hand.
(chuckles)
(beeping)
Let's move in now;
intercept the boat!
♪
(boat horn)
It's like I'm in a dream.
Me too.
Can I get you something?
Well, a real waiter
would be a good start.
How'd you know, dammit?
For one thing, you look like
a frickin' Egyptian
ice cream vendor, Pops.
Yeah, well, if you're such
a smart guy, how come you can't
even tell when you're
bring set up, huh?
What, there's nobody
here other than‐‐
(gun cocks)
Huh?
Sorry, Lupin, I meant a lot
of what I said, but,
unfortunately, it's what
I didn't say I meant the most.
Heh, that one's gonna take me
a little while to parse.
Yeah, well, at least you're
smart enough to know when
to pack it in, so,
I won't be needing this
anymore, will I?
Well, since I mean
everything that I say,
I think I'll just shut up.
For your sake, I hope
that means you'll go quietly.
Hey, where are you going?
Don't be stupid, bye!
I really don't think
she has your best interests
at heart, Lupin.
You were able to deduce that
all by yourself, were you?
(boat siren)
(grunts)
♪
Now, I wonder what
they could be doing?
♪
He really is an incorrigible
cad, N'est ce pa?
♪
Wait, where the hell is he?
I lost him; he just vanished!
Perhaps he's just gone below.
Right.
(gunfire)
The guy's faster than you think.
Quick, get the net!
♪
Use any means
necessary to subdue him.
It's not him!
Hi, there, welcome
to my world, Director.
You, explain!
Well, uh‐‐
Wait, there he is!
(motor revving)
♪
I forgive you.
Well, I warned you, Lupin.
(explosions)
(yelps)
Son of a bitch!
(motor revving)
Freakin' Fujiko's already
bucking for a promotion!
(chuckles)
Close in!
♪
(gunfire)
(screams)
He's not going anywhere now.
(screaming hysterically)
(explosion)
♪
What the hell
have you guys done?
Lupin!
♪
Dammit, where is he?
Lupin!
Am I the only one around here
who cares about this guy?
Oh, what am I supposed
to do with myself now?
(groans)
♪
Oh, you idiot, why'd you
have to try to get away?
All right, bring in the winch,
let's drag him up now.
(electric motor whirring)
Gently, now.
I will steady it, Henri
you on each end.
All right, there, it's done.
Hey, what is
the condition of the body, men?
There's no body on board, sir.
What's that, you say?
Hmm.
♪
(gasps)
Of course!
Hmm, what is it?
I'll bet you anything
he went right in there.
Mmm, ah, get in
the sewer, men, quickly!
It might be too late;
he's hard to find
once you've lost visual contact.
Hmm.
(grunting)
(gasping)
Zenigata!
So, old Lupin slipped
right through your fingers.
Well, that sort of thing
happens to the best of us, sir.
Don't take it too hard.
Well, you seem to be
positively giddy about
all this, Inspector.
Um, uh, no, not at all.
I'm just offering a bit
of friendly consolation, sir,
from one who can feel your pain.
Well, he won't escape
for very long,
not with me on the case.
Let's get going.
Where?
Where do you think?
To his hideout, of course,
you big silly‐billy.
Huh?
Ah, but of course,
you would know
about that, wouldn't you?
So, perhaps, I am a silly‐billy,
but I don't mind,
since this time,
we will capture him for sure.
Oh, really?
My, that sounds familiar.
Enough, I hate you!
(yelps)
Damn it all.
You know, I'm starting
to wonder about that woman.
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
(birds chirping)
(tires screeching)
What the hell's
the matter with that idiot?
Does he want to die?
Why can't he just
do this the easy way?
(sighs)
She thinks she's got me wrapped
around her little finger,
but the joke, it will be on her.
(laughs)
♪
If they think I'm gonna
let him get away, hold on!
Who am I talking to anyway?
What the hell
are you doing here?
We're out of this, Lupin;
it's between you and Fujiko.
Guys, I barely made it here.
C'mon, give me
a friggin' break, will ya?
You should really just give up.
He likes having her chase him.
Lupin, you've seen
how serious I am,
don't push this too far!
Hmm, what a crock.
Come on, lover, it's time!
It's been good, but
all good things come to an end.
That's it, this time,
don't let him get away, men!
I really think
he's lost his mind.
It's simple, he just can't bear
the thought of anybody else
capturing him.
You been drinking?
♪
Here we go.
Hey, I've got my back
against the wall now, Fujiko!
(gunfire)
Do you wanna go
and get a bite to eat?
Yeah, I could go for a pizza.
Hey there, Fujiko,
if you want me so bad,
why don't you just
come and get me?
(gunfire, commotion)
♪
(grunts)
All right!
Move in quick!
We've got him now, come on!
(gunfire)
Who the hell you guys
think you're dealing
with anyway, huh?
(gunfire)
(chuckling)
(yelping)
Hey, get back there!
What are you doing?
I cannot believe
what I am seeing here!
You're a disgrace
to INTERPOL and that uniform.
Ah, bonsoir, I trust
all this is not disturbing
your afternoon catnap?
You're funny, come here,
I wanna ask you something?
Come?
That's right, in here,
just the two of us.
What's the point
of capturing him anyway?
I mean, we both know
he'll just break out
of any place you hold him
before sending him back
to face charges in Japan.
Oh, that's not true, actually.
You see, INTERPOL has designed
a very special place
for the likes of Lupin.
You are aware, aren't you,
that he's a gifted
safe‐cracker and lock‐pick?
Oh, this jail is beneath
the ground with steel walls
thick enough to withstand
a nuclear bomb.
The security
is state‐of‐the‐art,
not even the great Lupin
can break out of there.
That's all I need.
I'm going to go capture him now.
♪
Take your time, my dear.
I neglected to mention
that you will be joining
your erstwhile friend
in that special cell.
♪
Where is he?
Move, step aside!
This is it, Lupin,
we're coming in!
(gunfire)
(yelps)
Well, what are you waiting for?
♪
We've got him now!
Let's check the bathroom.
(knocks, clears throat)
Occupied!
(chuckles)
(flushing noise)
(laughs)
(pounding)
(yelps)
Hey, where'd he go?
♪
(grunting)
With any luck, Fujiko's
still out there and I can't...
speak of the devil.
You know, this is starting
to get really boring, Lupin.
Sorta nice having you
chase after me, though,
for once, you know?
Yeah, well, don't
get used to it.
(gunfire)
Okay, here he is, as promised.
Huh?
Did he offer any resistance
or did you come quietly?
Come on, just look at her!
I've never been able
to resist Fujiko.
(chuckles)
Take him away.
Huh... what is this?
(coughing)
Hey!
Uh, thanks a lot there,
Pops, but, uh‐‐
No one's gonna have
the satisfaction
of arresting you
other than yours truly.
♪
So, where exactly
are we going to?
♪ Nowhere, just truckin' ♪
♪ I've got my chips cashed in ♪
♪ Keep truckin' like
the doo‐dah man,
I keep truckin' ♪
Nice to see you're taking
this reassignment thing so well.
Ah, what the hell.
All I ever cared about
was capturing you
and well, now I gotcha.
Well, that's true, for at
least a little while anyway.
However, Fujiko's
pretty obsessive herself.
Huh?
Crap, why that little!
Hey, Fujiko, down here!
Well, I guess we're
doing this the hard way.
(gunfire)
(yelping)
(tires screeching)
Look out!
(yelping)
(sighs)
♪
I really gotta have
a talk with her.
Lupin, wait!
You're not going anywhere,
I'm bringing you in!
(grunting)
Damn it all!
Sorry, Pops, see ya!
I don't have all day, you know?
Our of the frying pan.
What do you say lets stop
this nonsense before
somebody gets hurt?
A little late for that.
Oh, come on,
don't be sore at me.
♪
Sore's the
right word, all right.
I really do owe you
a couple of good ones.
Come on, you knew perfectly well
what you were getting into.
Yeah, well, that's real easy
for you to say, isn't it?
Hey, just doing my job.
You sure about that?
You know I'd never hurt you
unless I really had to, darling.
(gunshot)
♪
(grunting)
Hmm.
So, this is it, huh?
Mm‐hmm.
He's resting quietly
in there right now.
We still have
some details to work out
regarding the prompt transfer
of you two back to Japan.
Slip of the tongue,
you mean his transfer,
right, because I‐‐
(gasps)
Unfortunately for you.
I meant exactly what I said.
You'll be going back to Japan
to face charges with him.
Are you kidding me?
INTERPOL does not kid around.
Wait a minute,
are you telling me
this whole thing was‐‐
Best to deceive
your friends if you wish
to deceive your enemies.
N'est‐ce pa?
By golly, sir,
that is so brilliant!
You're a genius, it's a real
honor to serve under you!
And you, you really screwed up.
What the‐‐Hey!
Do lose with a little more
dignity, Mademoiselle Mine.
All right, what the hay,
you can't blame me for trying.
Yes, well, you are
a plucky one.
Inspector, show her in.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Lupin, wake up!
Forget it, that tranquilizer
I shot him with
is awfully strong stuff.
Good thing, my dear, it's safer.
Oh yeah, the guy's gonna
be pretty sore with you
when he finally wakes up.
(laughs)
Yeah, I'll show you
just how sore I am!
(grunts)
Lupin, that's not
what we came here for.
I know, I know,
the Star of Antarctica,
I haven't forgotten.
That's good.
How could I?
It gets right up my nose
when amateurs like that bozo
in Amsterdam overreach
themselves like that.
Of course, he wasn't
gonna get away with it.
He shoulda stuck
to pirating cable
or whatever his real gig was.
Then, to make it worse,
he has to go and swallow
the damn thing as
the cops are closing in.
I mean, look at all
the trouble he's put us to.
So far so good,
though, you know?
Everything is going according
to plan, I mean, at least
we're here now.
Yeah, at least
there wasn't any chance
of a schmuck like that
ever finding his way
back into this place
after they dropped
the whole case
for lack of evidence.
All this time, it's been in
the world's safest
safe deposit box.
Waiting for its rightful
owners to come and claim it.
Well, I dunno about rightful,
but sure as hell deserving
after everything the two
of us have been through
to get this far.
I've always had a pretty good
idea where he hid it, too.
Come on.
I mean, if he ingested it,
where do you think he was
when he recovered it?
Oh, Lupin, look at it.
Had to hurt!
I'll report in as soon
as we get to Tokyo, sir.
Good, any trouble from Lupin?
Lupin, nah, in fact, the guy's
still sleeping like a baby
inside that port‐a‐cell thing.
And the girl, is she
behaving herself?
Seems like she's
resigned herself
to the inevitable.
I want her treated with
the greatest
possible consideration.
Her contribution was huge.
Excuse me, sir?
My dear, wise old grandmother
used to tell me that the man
who lives by deception
is destined himself
to be deceived in return.
Yes, well, thank you,
I'll be sure to bear that
in mind, my dear.
All right, sir,
we'll be shoving off now.
All right, then,
INTERPOL is counting on you.
Any time you're
ready to take off.
(engine revving)
♪
Bon voyage, have
a safe trip to Japan!
Yeah, bye‐bye!
Ha, bye‐bye!
Hmm, mon dieu!
You know, sometimes,
I think that grandmother
of mine is psychic
or something, it's uncanny.
(growling)
Get back here!
I mean, stop
the plane, somebody!
Hey!
Come back here!
(growls)
♪ All my four leaf
clovers can do you good ♪
♪ Funny, just when
I needed you to be lucky ♪
(grunting)
Catch ya later, pops!
♪
Glad to have you back
on my case, old man.
(grunting)
(engine roars)
♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
It's been said that eggs
are the perfect food.
Me, I can take 'em or leave 'em,
except when they're being used
to smuggle diamonds,
in which case, I almost
always take 'em.
Easier said than done, though,
when you've got Fujiko, Pops,
and Hong Kong's creepiest
criminal masterminds
standing in your way.
In fact, the whole thing
gets pretty clucking insane.
So, that's the title,
catch you later!
♪