♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(gunshot)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(engine whining)
Hm.
(ship horn blowing)
♪
Hm.
Hey, complements of the boss.
That's your only bag?
Mhm.
‐Thank you.
‐Sure thing.
(engine growling)
(watch ticking)
♪
'Scuse me, boss,
but your guest is here.
Ah, great, my god, look at you!
Come on in, come on in!
And you, back to the track.
Sure, boss.
(engine whining)
(tires squealing)
So, how's my time?
Hey, not too shabby, man,
you ran under a minute
and a half a lap.
Perfect, at this rate
I might just set
a new racing record
tomorrow, you know?
I mean, what did Lauda
average in '75,
2:20 a lap or
something like that?
(grunts)
Not that I have to break
the record or anything,
just winning this thing
will suffice quite nicely.
And yet records exist
to be broken, don't they?
Couldn't have said it
better than myself.
(tittering)
♪
(camera shutter clicking)
(typewriter clacking)
♪
So here's the machine
he's going to be driving,
12 cylinder Boxer,
500 horses,
a real monster, ay?
Well, he may not have
Grand Prix experience,
but Lupin's one hell of a driver
and if he's behind the wheel
of that thing tomorrow,
there's no contest.
That's what I want to hear,
now it's just a matter
of getting him to
play for team Nexus.
♪
Okay, the car's good
and I'm ready.
The only thing is with
a street race like this,
it's a lot more dangerous.
An accident is all
I can see stopping me,
so we really need to
study the course carefully.
Like the potential
for glare on some
of these curves for instance.
Jigen, Earth to Jigen!
Look, Lupin, I really got
no trouble helping you
out with this, but
there is another reason
I'm here, you know.
Huh?
I'm talking about the casinos,
man, I mean, come on,
you can't come here to Monaco
and not play a round of cards!
So, let's hit the tables
and then hit the books, okay?
Yeah, you got it.
Goemon, what about
you, are you in?
Hm, why not, I'll give it a try!
Are you saying you've
never been before?
♪
Hm!
(phone ringing)
Oh, really, that's
perfect, okay,
you just keep an eye on 'em.
(laughing)
Just as you said, my dear.
Good, now let's go
drive our ace wild.
♪
(spinning metallic sound)
Tried to warn ya, three aces.
Oh, blast it all, that's
seven times in a row,
you bloody pirate,
I've never seen such luck
in my entire life!
(giggling)
Sorry, old bean, but that's
the way it goes, aye, what!
Hey, maybe eight's
your lucky number, aye?
No, no, no, no, I'm down to my
eyepatch now, thanks to you,
it's quite enough,
have mercy, sir.
Um, come on now, aye,
the night's still young,
not that anyone could
actually beat me tonight
or anything, huh, huh,
huh, huh, come on!
Any takers, doesn't
anyone want to wipe
this smile off my face?
Sounds good to me!
I mean, to us.
Hm?
It's been a while, Lupin.
Fujiko, what are you
doing here in Monaco?
(giggling)
Socrates Nexus, meet an old
friend of mine, Lupin the Third.
Meh, so is that Greek
for "sugar daddy"?
Hm, he's just exactly as
you described him, my dear.
Darling, don't
let him get to you.
"Don't let him get to you,
darling," yeah, well,
let me tell you something,
Mr. Big Fat Wallet
full of wonderful,
I'll clean you out,
and you can take
that to the bank!
Hey, hey, Lupin, cool it, man,
poker's not a game
for the emotional.
She called him darling,
did you hear that?
(chuckling)
♪
(groaning)
I'll take three.
I call.
Straight flush.
(whimpering)
Three aces.
(deep sigh)
Full house.
♪
(breathing hard)
Hey, you gotta get a grip, man.
♪
(metallic chiming)
Son of a stinkin' hunk of‐‐
no, no, I really
must transcend this‐‐
Yeah, okay, I'll
raise you, Nexus!
I'll raise this much,
what do you say?
‐Hm.
‐Too rich for ya, hm?
Hm.
♪
Okay, he's holding four queens,
repeat, four queens.
So, you gonna call or what?
(laughing)
Sure, just thought I'd
sweeten the pot a little.
Hey, Lupin, walk away,
I'm telling you right now.
No, no way, man, not now!
Here and here!
And there, now, how's that, huh?
It's not enough.
Lupin, get a grip, man,
I mean, let go, not my pants!
This is all really entertaining,
but if you got nothing
to put down, then I'm, uh‐‐
Hold it, wait a sec,
I got a Formula machine
right out in the parking lot,
what do you say to that?
Lupin, don't!
Hm, you've got yourself a deal.
(tittering)
Four queens, read 'em
and weep, big shot.
Well, I won't say it hasn't been
a pleasure, Mr. Nexus, 'cause‐‐
The pleasure
has been all mine
and continues to be,
unfortunately for you.
Four kings, Mr. Lupin.
(screaming)
(grunting)
Transcend!
♪
(sneezes)
(sneezing)
It's all your fault,
you're the devil, man!
You're the one who
mentioned gambling!
I wanted to prepare
for the race!
Hey, nobody twisted your arm,
and what kind of
amateur bonehead
throws down his clothes,
and his friggin' machine?
This is just great,
after all the work
I put into that
stupid race tomorrow!
‐It's your own damn fault!
‐I know!
Stripped down and screamin',
just the way I like 'em.
How dare you show
your face around here!
I'd say keep your shirt on,
but it's a little late for that,
isn't it, nature boy?
Anyway, I have an
interesting deal for you.
A deal, really?
Hold it a minute, need I
remind you the last time
she brought us a
good deal was never.
Why, Jigen, what a
terrible thing to say.
You know I've always thought
of you boys as close relatives.
Yeah, that's what Lizzie Borden
said, just get on with it.
Socrates Nexus,
the guy at the casino,
has got Monaco in his pocket,
he's a major capo
in the mob around here.
What a surprise, and
here I had him figured
for an English professor.
He's hosting an exclusive
little party at the Grand Prix
tomorrow with a dozen of the
highest rollers in Monaco.
Exactly who are these guys?
Second and third
generation money, mostly,
compulsive gamblers,
all relatively new to town.
That's perfect, sounds like
old Nexus has himself set up
to preside over a first class
sheep shearing tomorrow.
Exactly my point,
and like I said,
these guys are all high rollers,
so Nexus will be moving
some major dough.
And when I say major dough,
I'm talking about enough money
combined to make
the royal family here
look like the Simpsons.
Oh, what I'd give
for a piece of that!
Jackie Stewart.
Wittman.
Lauda, it's a perfect set up.
Because amateurs like our
particular flock of sheep
always tend to bet
on the celebrity.
Oh, it's making me crazy,
I coulda been there,
I coulda beaten
every one of 'em!
(groaning)
Yeah, well unless you can
beat them all on foot now,
it's all over, so forget it!
(whimpering)
That's not
necessarily so, Jigen.
All that money concentrated
on big name drivers
makes for pretty nice odds for
a talented dark horse, like you.
In fact, that's the whole
plan, Nexus has prepared
to bet the farm on you,
Lupin, if you'll do it.
Now I get it, he didn't
want Lupin's dough,
he wanted Lupin himself,
and to get him,
he had to get his machine,
so if Lupin wants
to drive tomorrow,
he has to drive for Nexus.
That's right, but at least
everyone's on the same page
here, I mean, at the end
of the day, we all just want to
see Lupin win tomorrow, right?
Oh, that's not the point,
I mean, I know if I enter
the race I'm gonna win,
but why would I wanna win the
race if winning the race means
I'd be helping a
creep like Nexus!
No offense.
It's okay, Lupin, I thought
you might feel that way,
that's why I prepared
an alternate plan for you.
Huh?
What if we take all the money,
that way you can drive
in the race tomorrow and
you could pay Nexus back
for making such a public fool
of you in that utterly bogus
poker game you played tonight.
What, no way, you know for a
fact that that game was fixed?
Oh, that frickin' bastard.
All right, that's it,
gloves off, I am in!
♪
(phone ringing)
Yeah, he did, really?
Perfect, damn, you play
that poor son of a bitch
like a violin, don't you?
(chuckling)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(crowd cheering)
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen,
to racing's most elite event,
the Monaco Grand Prix!
We are just minutes
away from the start,
and while all the participants
look cool and focused,
the audience here today is
making no attempt whatsoever
to contain its excitement,
and who could blame them?
This year's field plays like
a who's who of racing royalty.
Our cameras are poised at
every point along the route,
and even high above it to
bring you every thrilling second
of the jewel in
the racing crown.
The royal family is just now
being seated in its box,
fanning the excitement
and keen anticipation
in this sold‐out stadium!
Will Lauda take the
crown a second time?
Not if England's
Wittman can help it!
Or the always dangerous
Stewart of the U. S.
Muah, muah, muah, muah, muah!
(giggling)
♪
(phone ringing)
Hello, Nexus residence.
Oh, hi there, boss.
So you got all the money in yet?
Yeah, it's all here, boss,
we're packing it up now.
We'll have it in the
casino safe within the hour.
It played out like I figured?
Yeah, you called it,
Lauda, Wittman, and Stewart
came up real big,
just like you said.
‐What about Lupin?
‐Lunch money, not even.
It's perfect, okay, get
that dough to the casino.
Wouldn't want
to take any chances
with other people's money.
♪
They've had plenty of time to
count it and pack it all up,
they should be moving
it out any minute now.
Blue Arrow to pit crew,
you guys in place, we're
about to get started?
Yeah, we're here.
All right, then, good luck,
and don't worry about me,
I got a feeling I can't
lose no matter what.
The drivers are
now all in place.
Gentlemen, start your engines!
(engine revving)
And...there's the flag!
(engines roaring)
A strong start
for the whole field!
(engines whining)
(tires squealing)
Hm, Niki Lauda,
no surprise there,
but if you want this position,
you're gonna have to
take it from me, buddy!
(chuckling)
Better enjoy the thrill of
victory while you can, Lupin,
because pretty soon you'll be
tasting the agony of defeat!
(engines whining)
Lupin in number three
leads the pack
with Lauda sticking
like glue to his bumper!
Okay, that's the last of it.
Good, let's get out of here.
I'll ride shotgun.
(grunts)
Geez, this thing weighs a ton.
(groaning)
♪
Yup, that van might
look inconspicuous,
but I'm guessing it's armored.
A bit of precaution that
will avail to nothing.
Yeah, real shame about that.
‐Come on.
‐Let's do it!
♪
(tires squealing)
(tittering)
Go ahead, pass me, I dare ya!
♪
Oh, look at that,
he cut me off!
Son of a bitch!
Hey, pull over!
♪
Someone's getting steamed.
Maybe he'd prefer
to be lightly seared.
Let's see.
(liquid spraying)
‐Huh?
‐What the hell?
(shouting)
(tires screeching)
Here's two shrimps
on the barbie.
Ah!
(screaming)
(fire roaring)
Son of a bitch!
(grunting)
Bastards!
Do you know who
you're messing with?
Hey, you bitch!
(grunt)
♪
Bye‐bye.
We got the dough.
All right, now just get
the hell out of town.
(moaning)
That double crossing
piece of crap,
she'll never get out
of this country alive!
Nexus will have her
freakin' guts for garters!
Say all the money was‐‐what?
It was Fujiko, boss!
Get them, you hear me, get them
and kill them and get the money,
and then kill them again!
♪
Uh‐oh, looks like we're
a little too famous
a little too soon, damn it!
♪
When they say Monaco's
a hard place to leave,
they ain't kiddin', man.
(engine whining)
Lupin, we can't get out of here,
every road is blocked off.
‐Damn, that was fast.
‐Tell me about it.
Whoa, hold on a sec!
(shouting)
(loud crash)
Hey, you know, one
of the other drivers
just gave me a great idea.
Okay, that tanker's
not easy to hide!
You check out the warehouse!
‐Look over there!
‐Right!
♪
Sure thing, Lupin, no problem.
Fujiko and I will meet you
at the pit in around 10 minutes.
Okay, man, now are
you sure you know
‐the spot he's talking about?
‐Mhm!
♪
See, with Lupin around,
there's always a plan B.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Lupin now leads Lauda
by an eighth of a mile.
He's just entered
the straightaway,
heading for the start.
Geez, man, what's
taking you so long?
Hey, bite me!
Okay, everybody, look sharp,
we gotta change all six
tires on this hot rod.
Come on, hurry up
with that airgun!
Top off the fuel!
‐Hurry up!
‐Got it!
Hurry up, hurry up!
‐Time's a wasting!
‐Come on!
Go, go, go!
See ya soon!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
‐Stop!
‐Whoa, what the hell?
(tires screeching)
Okay, you, outta the car!
Z‐‐Zenigata,
how in the world‐‐
didn't your momma ever tell
you not to cross in the middle?
Shut up, you leave
my mother out of this!
‐Just get out of the car!
‐Why?
Was I speeding or something?
Get out of the way, you loon!
(engine revving)
Whoa, what's the
matter with you?
Stop, are you crazy, cut it out!
You can hurt someone!
(tittering)
♪
(blabbering)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
It's Lupin and Lauda,
Lupin and Lauda
down to the finish!
Okay, you lucky stiff, don't say
I never did anything for ya!
♪
Oh, my god, Lupin's in trouble,
he's veering sharply
to the left!
He's crashed through the
barrier and into the water!
(splash)
♪
(grunting)
He did it, he did it!
It's the most dramatic
finish in years!
Niki Lauda of Austria
takes his second‐‐
‐Bravo!
‐Good race.
(cheering)
‐(groans)
‐Boss!
They was working together!
Damn it, they were
playing me all the time!
You bastard, Lupin, I swear‐‐
‐Nexus!
‐Huh?
♪
You seem perturbed, sir,
surely you won't have any
trouble covering our bets?
Uh, yes, I mean,
no, that is, uh‐‐
you see, Lupin has it.
Not that I was in cahoots
with him in any way, of course,
it's just, well, actually,
it's kind of hard to explain.
♪
Oh, we did it, guys,
we actually did it!
(laughing)
Ha, the slot machines of the
world are trembling in fear.
Speaking of trembling in fear,
I wonder what happened to Nexus?
(wind blowing)
No, no, it can't be!
I'm Socrates Nexus,
the Emperor of Monaco.
I can't be broke,
it makes no sense.
It's all a bad dream, isn't it?
Tell me I'm dreaming!
(sobbing)
♪
Spin that wheel, my good man,
Lupin's here to play!
♪
Red, six, red, six!
Hm.
(growling)
(laughing)
I like you, funny guy!
Sure, that's me!
(groaning)
The humiliation
is too much to bear,
there is but one way of honor.
I must kill myself.
♪
Whoa, whoa, Goemon, hold it!
It's only money!
And if you can help me
create a distraction,
I know where I can
get us a little more!
(drum roll)
♪
I can't believe I lost
all of that money!
Yeah, well, that was my
money, you big dumb jerk!
Help, she's gonna kill me!
You wish, killing's
too good for you!
All of a sudden, I'm
feeling relatively lucky.
Me, too.
‐Get back here, you coward!
‐It wasn't my fault!
You bastard, that was my money,
my money, my money...
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Hey, it's the Christmas episode,
so crack open a cask or two
of your favorite spirit
and get swept away in the
flood of goodwill toward men...
except him, of course.
It'll be a gas,
and a liquid,
and good solid
entertainment as always.
Join us next time in,
"The Sleight Before Christmas."
Catch ya later.
♪