♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(wood creaking)
♪
(gong)
(engine whirring)
‐That plane dropped something‐‐
‐What is that?
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(gasps)
"On the 16th of October
during the ceremony
for the 1,350th year
of the temple's founding,
I will humbly steal
its hidden treasure,
the Goddess of Mercy statue.
Sincerely, Lupin the Third."
♪
Chief, you gotta listen to me,
the only way we can protect
the Goddess of Mercy is to get
a couple of old reliable hands
on this, and that
means Zenigata, me,
teaming up with the very best
you got, Detective Hanshichi!
‐You're kidding.
‐I'm serious!
But Hanshichi, that relic?
With all due respect, Chief,
we don't have any time
for dilly‐dallying, and as
far as the ICPO is concerned,
I'm in charge of
Lupin, all right?
Hey, stop, thief!
Huh?
Oh, a purse snatcher,
okay, I'm on the case!
‐Halt!
‐Oh, crap!
Hey, evildoer, I said halt!
It means stop or something
in French, I think!
Well, too bad, gramps, there's
no way I'm getting caught
by an old fart like you!
(grunting)
(groaning)
(panting)
(whimpering)
Gotcha red‐handed.
No excuses,
sticky fingers, it's over!
I know, there's no excuse
for me, it's just...gah!
Tiaro, Haniko,
Shiro, I'm sorry,
I let you down!
What kind of father am I?
Sure, you're nearly starving,
but is that ever
an excuse to steal?
No, of course not,
never, please arrest me!
(blubbering)
♪
Such beautiful children,
and all of them so young.
♪
Ha, see ya, don't wanna be ya!
Wait!
Oh, what a time for
my arthritis to kick in.
It's been ten years now
and nothing's ever
been the same since.
(typewriter clacking)
♪
Hey, congratulations, old man.
Heard you blew
another one, good job.
Can't even grab a purse
snatcher, Hanshichi?
Maybe it's retirement time.
Yeah, it'd be a
great public service,
your crowning achievement.
♪
It's come to this, I'm an
embarrassment to the department.
♪
I'd retire today,
but nose reduction surgery
is so expensive.
Isn't sending a challenge note
before stealing something
kinda tipping your hand?
Not at all, Jigen, it's
just a sign of respect.
Respect, you?
I'm afraid I'm out
of this one, Lupin.
What, what are
you talking about?
You forget that my
dearly departed mother
used to be a devout
believer in the goddess
whose icon you're
planning to steal.
And you believe
the Goddess of Mercy
can, like, read
your mind, right?
I'm simply
uncomfortable with it.
Well, Jigen, old pal, I guess
that leaves just you and me.
It's nothing personal.
(chime)
I just want to
thank you for requesting
my assistance with Lupin.
I can't tell you
what it means to me.
Oh, it was nothing.
Nah, it's true,
everyone around here treats me
like some washed up old fossil,
but not you, Inspector,
you treat me with respect
and for that, I am
forever in your debt.
Oh, no, please, Detective,
that's quite unnecessary.
Today it's all about
career advancement.
Things like duty and honor
don't seem to matter anymore.
It's my moral obligation
to capture Lupin,
I can't rest till then.
It was ten years ago.
I was in the Tanigawa Valley
where Lupin's plane had crashed
after he pulled off a bank job.
Everyone said I was crazy,
but I climbed that mountain
in a blinding
snowstorm and then,
I came face to face with him!
Surprise, Mr. Lupin, your
legendary luck just ran out!
You just don't give up,
well, neither do I!
(grunting)
♪
(wind blowing)
I wouldn't try that
one at home, gramps!
I'm afraid I'm rather old
fashioned, I don't quit!
(growling)
Whoa!
That's very impressive,
but I think you missed
it by just a little bit!
Lupin, you're under arrest,
I order you to surrender!
I'll tell you what, throw
away that baton of yours
and I'll give you a hand,
what do you say to that, huh?
A baton is a policeman's
heart and soul.
If I threw this thing away
there'd be no point
in living anymore,
I'd have to cash it in.
(wind blowing)
(snow crunching)
You are one stubborn old man.
Crap, it looks like those feet
of yours are already frostbitten
and I bet that storm isn't
gonna let up any time real soon!
Can't carry 'em both, hm...
Oh, well, easy come, easy go!
And that's how my life was
saved by Lupin the Third,
but my career's been
crippled ever since
thanks to the arthritis
I developed as a result
of that frostbite.
♪
Now I'll have a chance
to show those so‐called
colleagues of mine what an
old timer like me is made of.
♪
Ah, my baton, the symbol
of my career, my whole life,
everything I believe in
in this entire world.
I'll get you this time, I will,
Lupin, I'll never give up,
I'll follow you into
hell if I have to!
♪
Believe me, I know exactly
how you feel, Detective.
♪
Uh, Detective?
(clears throat)
Is everything
all right with you?
I mean, Lupin will get away
if we don't come up
with a plan soon!
Yes, hm.
Well, um.
Hey, this tea stalk's straight
up, that's a very good sign!
I'm feeling good
about this case!
Great, look,
Detective, we need a plan!
♪ 99 bottles of beer
on the wall ♪
♪ 99 bottles of beer ♪
Keep it down, will ya,
this ain't a bar, buddy!
Just go to hell, you pig!
Just shut up, we're trying
to get some work done in here!
Who is that in there, guy
sounds like a real handful.
Nobody important, just
some drunk and disorderly
they picked up downtown, trying
to take on the whole world.
Ah, yes, those who can drink
away all the worries of life,
they're the lucky
ones aren't they?
We're not here to talk
about that drunkard,
we gotta get Lupin and damn it,
the guy's out there right now
preparing his next heist!
In fact, wait, what
am I talking about?
This is Lupin, he's all done
preparing, yeah, he's‐‐
(sizzling)
(yowling)
♪
Good heavens, Zenigata,
what's come over you?
I need water, I'm dying here!
(chuckling)
♪
Drunk Guy to Jigen,
come in, are you there?
Coming in loud and
clear, Drunk Guy.
♪
Okay, so now we can snoop on
all their internal meetings,
but the bad news
is Lupin's stuck,
how the hell's
he gonna bust out?
(grunting)
♪
(glass breaking)
Hey, this bar is even too
violent for me, pig man.
For the last time, just shut up!
Hm, that's Lupin!
♪
Lupin?
But why would he allow himself
to be caught so easily?
It's impossible, and
yet it's definitely him.
Well, I don't know what's behind
this and frankly I don't care.
I'm calling
headquarters immediately!
Wait just a moment, Inspector.
Uh, this man here is not Lupin.
Oh, and, uh, why is that?
Do you honestly believe
that a man like Lupin
would get drunk in public
and let himself get arrested?
I guess you have
something of a point there.
I mean, look at him, an idiot
with the face of a monkey.
No way that's my great
nemesis, it's insulting.
‐Not him?
‐That?
Some kind of master
criminal, with a dopey grin
and eyes like some kind
of a lovesick camel?
♪
Well, I, maybe I guess not.
Of course not, Inspector.
If you arrest him as Lupin,
we'll both be laughed
straight into retirement.
You can go, but don't let
me see you here again!
Bye‐bye, barkeep, thanks!
♪ 98 bottles of beer
on the wall ♪
Scary.
Amazing, man looks
just like him.
See ya, now where was I‐‐
Ninety‐eight, no...
Ninety‐twelve, yeah,
wait, it's impossible,
ninety‐twelve is bigger
than ninety‐eight.
Oh, well.
Drunk Guy to Jigen,
daddy's home, ha!
They just let you walk
right out of there?
That's pretty amazing.
I'm guessing that it's that
ten‐year‐old karma kicking in.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Ha, that green guardian's
mug could stop a bus.
I wouldn't talk, Inspector.
Why would you say
a thing like that?
My mommy thinks I'm handsome.
I'm just kidding you, Zenigata,
come on, let's get to work.
Mhm.
♪
Hm, very interesting,
the original seal from 1869
is still intact.
You see, this is exactly
why you're just the man
for this case, that's amazing.
Boneheads, it says so right
here in the damn brochure!
Hey, you, who are you
calling a bonehead?
You take that back
or this bonehead's gonna
have to defend the honor
of that other old bonehead!
Sorry about that, sir,
no offense intended.
(groaning)
It's crazy, I tell you,
why in the world would you
entrust security to a couple
of dinosaurs like those two?
You don't like it.
It makes no damn sense.
Hm, oh, it makes
sense, all right.
Think about it, Detective,
Lupin's a master thief,
chances are damned good
he's gonna swipe that thing,
and if he does,
or rather when he does,
somebody's gonna have
to take responsibility.
Now, if you want it on
your record, that's fine,
but I don't want it on mine.
I really underestimated
your craftiness there, Chief.
That's why I'm Chief, it's
essential that the crafty man
always be underestimated.
I have so much
to learn from you.
Mhm.
♪
What do you say I give
you a ride home, huh?
‐Been a long day, huh?
‐Thank you, Inspector,
but I'd rather be alone
if you don't mind.
Yeah, sure,
I understand, no problem.
I'll see you tomorrow night.
♪
Guy sure is one moody
son of a bitch.
No wonder no one ever
asks to work with him.
♪
‐You're under arrest!
‐(chuckling)
Hanshichi catch Lupin?
With that arthritis of his,
the guy couldn't catch a cold!
♪
(people chattering)
Ha, pretty clever for an old
school dinosaur like Hanshichi.
It doesn't matter, it won't
work, and he'll be blamed.
I can't wait to be rid of them.
They both make me sick.
♪
(chuckling)
(groaning)
Shall we begin our
journey now, my son?
Might want to get those eyebrows
straight before we do, Lupin.
Huh?
(chuckling)
(drums beating)
(wings flapping)
(chattering)
♪
(chanting)
(tittering)
Hold it!
Whoever you are, it's a
sacrilege to disturb us.
(laughing)
Very good, Mr. Lupin,
but clever as you are,
I can see right through
your whole masquerade.
Ay yi yi, it's Hanshichi!
♪
(click)
(whimpering)
Turn on the lights!
(shouting)
Hey, what the‐‐
Look, it's Lupin.
Ha, gotcha!
Victory is mine!
Why, you wily old bastard.
Hanshichi, I can't believe it.
(laughing)
Yeah, even the Goddess
wouldn't have known.
We took a page out of
your old playbook, Lupin,
so how's it feel?
It's not fair, disguises,
I mean, come on,
I mean, that's‐‐
Your own medicine,
how's it taste?
You want to do
the honors, Detective?
Yes, thank you, but I would
like to do it in my own way.
Ha, you old fool, no one
uses rope, how old are you‐‐
Hey, that's enough,
this guy just nabbed Lupin!
Congratulations, sir,
it's a great accomplishment.
Thank you, would you
mind holding this?
Certainly, sir.
(tittering)
Just what the hell
are you laughing at?
Seems like you really have
lost a step, Detective.
That guy you just
handed the statue to,
name's Jigen, ring a bell?
He's my partner.
Everyone after the guy with the
Goddess statue, he's a phony!
Holy cow!
♪
And it looks like the
anniversary match goes
to Lupin the Third,
my old friend.
I am going to wipe that gargoyle
grin right off of your face.
♪
You've been taking
your Geritol, old man.
Yaw!
Hi‐yah!
♪
‐Seize him!
‐Surround him!
(shouting)
‐Don't let him escape!
‐Let's take him now!
(whistles blowing)
(grunting)
♪
You don't know how much
this moment means to me
after all these years!
What, couldn't you hear or is
it your memory that's going?
Lupin, you're under arrest!
All right,
no funny business now.
Take it easy now, Pops,
you're not a young man anymore.
Can it, Lupin,
there's nowhere to go,
it's the end of
the line for you!
(grunting)
Crap, crap, crap,
crap, crap, crap!
Can't hang around with you,
Pops, gotta go, bye!
♪
(shouting commands)
(groaning)
♪
Hey, it was real nice of you to
let your little friends come out
and play, too, Hanshichi.
It was always meant
to be this way,
just you and me, one on one.
Sorry, but like
I told Zenigata,
I really can't stay
and play anymore.
Oh, come on now, Lupin,
you don't have to leave
in such a hurry, do ya?
It's been fun,
Hanshichi, really,
but I got everything I came for.
Oh, please don't go,
you owe me something,
we've known each other so long.
Keep this then!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
Ours was an epic struggle
worthy of a play.
Maybe I'll sit down
and write it someday.
(click)
(propellers whirring)
♪
No, no, I hate this part.
It's a little showy, I admit,
but I've always had a weakness
for the theatrical gesture,
as you well know.
Catch you later, guys!
♪
(laughing)
(tittering)
♪
Well, Zenigata,
look what happened,
we did as you said,
left it to Hanshichi and you,
and the whole damn thing
blew up in our faces.
Now what would you do if you
were in my position, Inspector?
Certainly a man of honor
would take full responsibility
for the whole thing.
I‐‐well, what are you saying?
Well, an honorable man...
would resign now.
But I can't, I can't!
Not until I catch
Lupin the Third!
Be quiet, you've
disgraced everyone here.
Chief, sorry, sir, to interrupt,
but we got a package for you
from Hanshichi in Hawaii.
Hanshichi, are you
sure it's from him?
Oh, it makes sense, all right.
Think about it, Detective,
Lupin's a master thief,
chances are damn good
he's gonna swipe that thing.
That's me on the tape!
And if he does, or
rather when he does,
somebody's gonna have
to take responsibility.
Now if you want it on
your record, that's fine,
but I don't want it on mine.
I really underestimated
your craftiness there, Chief.
That's why I'm Chief, it's
essential that the crafty man
always be underestimated.
I have so much
to learn from you."
(growling)
Of all the‐‐why you‐‐
You two better have a damn
good explanation for this!
Well, yes, why don't we just
sit down for a little bit,
Inspector, I'm sure we
can work all this out.
♪
What, it's‐‐it's empty!
Looks like it's from Hanshichi,
some kind of note.
Hm, let's see, it says,
"I decided that Japan's
too old fashioned for me.
Thanks for your help, aloha."
♪
Damn, he snookered
us, the old fart.
I only hope we're that
good when we're that old.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
These guys are bad,
they're the Gang of Five
and they wanna steal
some block prints from me.
No way, I just
stole them myself!
Anyway, our four can take their
five‐‐make that our three‐‐
well, two, really.
Anyway it's all
very complicated,
very funny and a very
big pain in the ass!
Catch you next time
in "Kooky Kabuki."
♪