♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(gunshot)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
The largest emerald
in the world:
the Black Panther.
So‐called because
light directed at it
from just the right
angle reveals...
What?
♪
There!
You see?
So real you could
swear it's alive.
♪
Whoa.
This is legit?
It's not some hologram?
Nah, looks like he could
just spring right out
of there, though,
doesn't it?
Good thing it's
just an illusion,
'cause I've got plans
for this pussy cat.
(meows)
(alarm sounds)
Ze Black Panther is gone!
(frenzied chatter)
Nobody gets out!
♪
Now what?
Plan B.
(sirens wail)
(crowd mutters)
Ze whole building's locked
down and surrounded, sir.
Security is confident
that no one has escaped.
I cannot wait to get
my hands on whoever
is responsible for zis.
It's an affront
to the nation!
Very good, sir.
Next!
Deep breath, please,
and hold it.
(takes deep breath)
You know, as long
as I'm here,
I've been getting this
little twinge in my knee
every time I‐‐
What?!
Get out of here!
Next in line!
All set.
Minor setback.
Yeah, but I think
you and I better
stay away from
here for a while.
Hang in there,
my sweet little pussy cat.
Next in line.
All right, you can go.
Next in line!
Ah, sir, that's it.
We've checked everybody,
including the staff.
Zey are all clean!
It just doesn't add up!
♪
Obviously we have
overlooked someone.
But who?
♪
‐Down the hatch.
‐Cheers.
Kanpai.
(slurps)
This is great, I mean,
this is the ultimate mother
of all birthday presents.
Can you imagine her reaction
when she opens it up?
You're giving me
the Black Panther?
Oh, Lupin, I love you!
Come over here,
I want to be your
little pussy cat.
First, I'm not a prop
for your sexual fantasies.
Secondly, you don't
have it yet.
Aw, come on, now,
piece of cake.
Hey, I'd say we left that
thing in very safe hands,
wouldn't you, Jigen?
Hey, you know,
I wonder how old
Fujiko's gonna be this year.
That girl should
really start thinking
about getting married.
Man, that emerald
would sure make one hell
of a wedding ring, huh?
(chuckles)
Just think of the beautiful
wedding dress she could steal.
(sighs)
Lupin.
Sorry to interrupt,
but if I were you
I wouldn't be calling
the caterers just yet.
What's up?
Hmm.
Huh, Inspector Conaiseau's
been brought in to take over
the Black Panther investigation.
This isn't good.
He's got some, like,
mystical connection
to the thing.
Every time it's stolen,
he finds it somehow.
Ah, it's just
a whole lot of crap.
I mean, take
a gander at this guy.
He's a cretin.
(chuckles)
(shouts)
Inspector Conaiseau, sir,
are you all right?
I am asked this
question quite often,
and I always say "yes,"
but actually, my nose
alas is clogged.
(chuckles)
(squish)
Sorry about that.
Hmm, um...
Hageito, Hageito!
Sacré bleu!
Where is that fellow?
Eh, I don't know,
but if you will just‐‐
Huh, what's that?
No, no, it's good
for him, huh?
But he's always
disappearing for some reason.
I'm sure he'll turn up.
Anyway, I wanted
to welcome you here.
I am Chief Shaquille.
A pleasure.
Oops.
I don't know
what I was thinking.
Don't know how you
balance police work
with a basketball career,
but my hat's off
to you, Shaquille,
not literally
but figuratively.
Yes, but back to the case.
Any idea about suspects yet?
Eww...
(laughs)
Have I got any ideas
about suspects, Chief?
Of course I do!
Forgive me, I...
This is my specialty,
you know?
It's Lupin!
Huh?
It's definitely him!
I'll bet you a hundred
bucks it's him!
Who are you?
Oh, yeah,
Inspector Zenigata, Interpol.
Sorry.
Ah, it's an honor.
Your reputation
precedes you, Inspector.
And I'll stake
that fine reputation
on this hunch!
It's him, all right.
(growls)
So, now detective work is
a competitive sport, I see.
Ah, well, yes,
but you know what they say,
the more the merrier.
Right, men?
Except for the
criminals, that is.
(laughs)
(growling)
♪
And where would you
be headed now?
Hey, you!
What am I, a suspect now?
Just back off, Conaiseau.
Hmph.
I was going to offer
some friendly advice,
but I can see you're
quite beyond help, sir.
Hmph.
‐Ha!
♪
Hmm, one always feels
as if one is being
watched in these places.
Hmm, that's Rodin
the Jackass, isn't it?
(shouting)
So, there you are, Hageito!
Where have you been?
(groaning)
Yah!
(laughs)
It's a good thing that
statue broke your fall, huh?
Hah!
(strained noise)
Sacré bleu!
Look what we've done.
Actually, I mean,
what you've done, Hageito.
It's not a gymnasium after all.
(growls)
‐Now, let's‐‐
‐Inspector Conaiseau!
Yes, uh, bonjour!
Coming.
Lovely collection,
by the way.
As for you, you vandal,
get gluing.
Here!
(grunting)
Ha‐ha!
♪
This is what he looks like.
Well, most of
the time, I mean.
Sometimes he's a woman,
or an Eskimo, or anyway,
have you seen him?
Uh‐uh.
Okay.
♪
Man, this heat is brutal,
but I gotta keep going.
(sighs)
♪
Just gotta keep
my eyes peeled.
So, after Fujicakes
and I are settled down,
I'm hoping you'll
still come by and,
you know, babysit for us.
(chuckles)
♪
Hmm.
So, where's the
regular cleaning crew?
Uh, well, they both
came down with some
kind of nasty stomach thing.
I was feeling a little
funny this morning.
You look funny.
Hey, wait a minute, hold on!
There's a police inspector
in the sculpture court.
Just work around him, okay?
We'll steer clear
of him, don't worry.
♪
Hmm.
Hmm!
Hmm?
‐What?
‐Don't worry, Inspector,
we're gonna stay
out of your way.
Wait!
Something smells.
(laughs)
Oh, it's me.
I shouldn't have had
the bean burrito.
Never again.
Woo!
♪
(struggles)
Huh, look, it's not there!
That‐‐that's impossible.
You saw me.
I hid it right in
the palm of his hand.
There's no way‐‐
Hey, you!
Hey, get away from
that sculpture.
Well, you heard the man.
Where did they‐‐
oh, well, never mind.
I'm quite positive
they did not notice
anything amiss.
(sniffs)
Huh, looks like old
Hageito did a halfway
decent job.
Mm‐hmm.
(knocks)
Hmm?
He didn't repair it,
he replaced
the whole damn thing!
♪
Oh!
It's not fair.
How could it just
disappear like that?
They say a thing can
only truly disappear
if it's being
watched, Lupin.
Well, it couldn't
have been stolen, Goemon,
'cause Jigen and I were
the only two who even knew
it was there at all,
for heaven sakes.
Hey, Lupin, I found it.
What, you mean it?
Yeah, that's right,
our old friend
the security guard
told me a guy
brought in a package
just about exactly
the same size
as the sculpture.
I know where this is going.
Mm‐hmm.
Then he comes back out
with the same package
saying he made a mistake.
Okay, so this guy
switched the real sculpture
with a counterfeit.
But who the hell is he?
Well, that's the real
kick in the pants.
Apparently, the reason
nobody was suspicious
was that it was that
Conaiseau's assistant,
that Hageito guy.
What?
Are you saying that
Conaiseau actually
has the Black Panther?
Hey, pal, your guess
is as good as mine.
But if he's got it,
why is he still
at the museum turning
the whole friggin' place
upside down, it just
doesn't add up.
Because he's shrewd.
Oh, yeah?
Not if he actually thinks
he's getting away with this.
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(gunshot)
(engine hums)
A less confident man
might be tempted
to question his
talent as a mentor.
You look like a man who
appreciates the finer things.
What can I do
for you, mon ami?
Well, you see, I...
I seemed to have
misplaced this fellow.
I wonder if you
might have seen him.
Huh, the weird guy?
In the back room.
♪
Hageito, it's me!
Come on out,
I know you're here.
Hmm.
No playing around now, my boy.
I don't have
time for this.
Hmm, maybe he isn't
here after all.
‐Huh?
‐(yelling)
Huh?
(men grunt)
This is not a convenient
time for a training session.
Now, tell me,
where is the sculpture
you took from the museum?
(grunts)
What, of course you do!
What do you mean you
don't have it, huh?
Why, you blithering
nincompoop!
You were just supposed
to fix the damn thing!
(shouting)
Now then, please
take me to it.
You do remember where
you sent it, don't you?
(grunts)
Have to rent a motorboat.
Can't be gone too long,
it'll look suspicious.
(engine hums)
It sounds like they're
getting ready to hit the road.
Yeah, you called it, Lupin.
I still can't
figure it, though.
This guy's nuts.
At least with Pops,
it's all, you know,
pretty damn... predictable.
Well, well!
Usually anyway.
All of you out of the car.
Now!
Well, what can one say
to a gracious invitation
like that except... floor it!
Hey!
Damn it all, get back here!
(gasping)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
Well, they don't
have it with them.
Then they must
be going to it.
Come on!
Nothing's gonna stop me.
(groans)
Neither rain,
nor sleep,
nor gloom of the night.
♪
Where the hell are
these guys going?
Beats me.
Better not be one of
those three hour tours
you hear about
on Nick at Night.
Yeah.
♪
Or that guy in
The Odyssey.
Isn't this where he
sailed around for, like,
20 years?
What was his name again?
‐Odysseus.
‐Gesundheit.
Yeah, what was his name?
‐Odysseus!
‐You all right, Goemon?
‐No, I'm trying‐‐
‐Hang on a second.
On that island up ahead
there's a sign.
It looks like it says
something like "Nature Camp."
Nature what?
Are you sure you've
got that right?
You're not gonna
believe this‐‐holy crap.
What is it,
what's the matter?
Well, it's‐‐
you gotta see this.
(gibberish)
Now, that's what
I call a nature camp.
Damn, I love my work!
Wha‐whoa, whoa, whoa.
We're gonna see
naked ladies!
Hey, Lupin, come on.
We're not actually heading
over there now, are we?
Oh, I thought I might drop in.
He's got the attention
span of a flea.
And a horny teenage
flea at that.
Oh, sounds to me
like someone's afraid
he might not measure up.
Oh, that's ridiculous, man.
My resemblance
to Dillinger
inspired me to
pursue this career.
What, his scrawny ass?
Okay, fine,
if it'll shut you up,
let's just go.
♪
(seagulls cawing)
(chuckles)
(mumbling gibberish)
Ow!
Well, every hero's
got an Achilles' heel,
and his just happens
to be in his pants.
Hmm?
Oh!
There!
(Hageito giggles)
Ah, wonderful, wonderful!
And not a scratch on it.
All we have to do now
is find a way to get
it out of here unnoticed.
Good heavens,
Inspector Conaiseau!
Oh, no!
It's the chief.
Ah, what a pleasant surprise.
I thought I detected
a kinship between us.
And I was right!
Come, let me introduce
you to everyone!
Zis way.
Come this way.
Funny thing, Jigen,
my eyes are killing me,
but I just can't bring
myself to blink.
Holy crap,
I can't believe it,
it's right here!
This is turning out
to be a real good day.
Ha‐ha!
(panting)
Oh, yeah, yeah.
This is the original, all right.
(laughs)
Let's get that rock
and get out of here.
(shouts)
(grunts)
What the hell?
Hey, Lupin, old buddy,
are you all right?
Oh.
That bastard took
me by surprise.
Leave him to me.
You just grab
the Black Panther
and beat it back
to the boat.
Come on, nature boy,
let's dance.
(grunting)
Hyah!
(shouting)
Okay, Lupin, move it!
‐Go!
‐But I... oh man.
Hey!
Bring back that
sculpture, you thief!
Hey, hey!
(panting)
Oh, damn, it's heavy.
Somebody give me
a damn mallet, huh?
♪
We'll keep this public
servant from nailing
your butt, buddy.
It's him and he's
all alone, weighted down,
and comin' right at me.
(chuckles)
Lupin, stop right there
and put your hands up.
(gibberish)
Zenigata!
Stop him!
(laughs)
Your time's up, Lupin,
I got you surrounded.
Now, put that down
and let's slip these on.
I don't know, a bit too
Mapplethorpe for me, Pops.
Hey, would you give
me a hand here?
Gotcha.
(Goemon grunts)
Hey, that's the Black Panther!
Damn it, Conaiseau,
I told you it was him.
Okay, Lupin, you're
coming with me.
‐Ow.
‐Oh, no!
What have you done,
it's ruined!
A‐ha, at last,
you're finally mine.
You bastard.
(grunts)
Ah, what'd you have
to go and do that for?
(groans)
Oh!
It's the Black Panther.
What is it doing here?
Mon dieu!
♪
Here, kitty, kitty,
kitty, kitty, kitty.
Here, kitty,
kitty, kitty.
♪
Oh.
Merde.
Hey!
(excited chatter)
Hold it right there.
(muttering)
Just, the thing
we wanted is in
the pool, it fell there.
Can't you read?
This is a restricted area.
Women only.
Where's your
registration tag?
Gee, I forget.
I guess you'll
just have to frisk me.
Oh!
That's no way
to charm a lady!
Like I'm gonna take
lessons from you!
♪
(bubbling)
(gasps)
Any sign of it?
Sorry, pal, there's
nothing down there.
Ah!
Damn it, it didn't just swim
away from here by itself.
Well, I suppose we
could drain the pool,
if you want.
Allow me to save
you the trouble.
I thought I saw you leave.
Mm, but you forgot
about Hageito, didn't you?
Ah, damn it, he got it.
It's three to one, Lupin.
Why don't we just
take this guy out?
Hardly worth the effort.
Huh?
You see, gentlemen,
what I have here
is the Black Panther,
and yet it is also
not the Black Panther.
What do you mean?
Well, I'll show you,
have a look, here.
♪
Huh, what's going on here?
Hmm, like all cats,
the Black Panther
was averse to
water, Mr. Lupin,
and in fact, more
than just that,
it seems he never
learned how to swim.
Are you saying?
By the time Hageito
recovered it...
the Black Panther had
already taken his place
with the heavenly choir.
♪
I devoted my entire
career to protecting
that rare creature from harm,
and today, sadly,
I failed him.
I'd like to be alone now,
if you don't mind.
(sniffles)
Well, that was a colossal
waste of our time, huh?
I'm afraid it may have
been even worse than that,
my friend.
(sighs)
Au revoir, Black Panther.
Yah!
♪
♪ Happy, happy birthday ♪
♪ Happy birthday, Fujiko ♪
I can't believe you guys
remembered my birthday!
Oh, baby, how could I
forget the one time of year
I get to spank you, hmm?
Actually, as great
as that sounds,
I can't stay.
I have plans for the evening,
and I have to get going.
Oh!
Lupin...
Can't you change
these plans of yours?
Lupin's really been
looking forward to this.
Look, I didn't know
where you guys were,
nobody called me.
And I didn't want to be
alone on my birthday.
So I made a date
with somebody.
A date?!
Who with?
I don't think you know him.
Inspector Conaiseau.
‐Conaiseau?
Between you and me,
I think he's a bit
of a bumbler, but he did
give me the most amazing
birthday present.
But it looks...
It looks just like...
♪
(Black Panther giggles)
Got to admit,
he's good.
You said it.
Yeah, this guy's working
the wrong side of the law.
Funny you should
mention that,
'cause he offered
to quit his job
and join up
with us just for me.
What should I say?
Tell him he should forget it.
We're fine the way we are.
(chuckles)
Here I am.
Sorry I'm late.
Even waiting for you
is a delight, my dear.
Oh!
Ah, I see you're wearing
your birthday present!
Your beauty is
a perfect setting for it.
I don't know how
I can ever thank you.
Wah!
Oh, no!
Not now, Hageito.
Can't you see I'm
right in the middle of‐‐
(shouting)
Whoa, look out.
‐The Black Panther, look!
‐You idiot!
Oh!
♪
Hey, wait!
Where are you going?
It's getting away.
♪
Wait!
Come back.
Oh, crap.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Just because
I'm good at my job,
everyone's blaming me
for knocking the whole
safe banking
industry on its ass.
Everybody's steamed:
customers, manufacturers,
weirdo baby‐head bad guys,
but somehow I'm the one
whose buns get steamed.
Typical.
For you, though,
it's a safe bet.
Catch you later!
♪