♪
(gunshot)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(shattering)
(engine revving)
(tires screeching)
♪
(gunshot)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(tires screeching)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
Whoa, damn it!
Who knew fire was
so freaking hot?
Lupin!
Hurry up, will ya,
I'm getting barbecued!
I'm doing my best,
Fuji‐cakes, hold on!
I'll have you out in a‐‐ow!
Come on, now,
you've got to hurry!
The whole place is
going up, please!
Sorry, it's too damn hot!
‐Lupin, quick!
‐Okay, I'm coming.
Lupin, you heartless bastard!
How can you do this to me?
I'm gonna put a curse on
you from beyond the grave!
Don't worry, I'll save ya!
You just hang in there!
♪
(whirring)
Hey!
(tapping of typewriter keys)
♪
Well, where the
hell did he go?
He's not exactly an
easy guy to capture.
Not a single print in here.
Totally empty.
Hmm, well, this thing
was definitely cut
by his Zantetsu sword,
there's no doubt about it.
Are you‐‐
What, are you saying‐‐
I knew it, there's
no other explanation.
Goemon's betrayed us.
(grunting)
Damn it!
It doesn't make any sense.
Damn, what the hell
is going on with him?
(chuckling)
Let's see you try to beat
this hand now, Lupin.
Today's synonym for wealth
is neither Rothschild
nor Rockefeller,
but Lupin, thanks to his
illustrious career as a thief.
It's just
old‐fashioned thinking.
We will no longer target
yesterday's robber barons.
He who controls Lupin's
purse controls the future.
With Goemon,
we'll be the greatest
thieves in history.
However, Lupin won't
simply give up.
But you can kill him, right?
I mean, that should be
a cinch for you, Goemon.
Or are you afraid of Lupin?
Answer me, what's the matter?
Cat got your tongue?
It's true, you're
afraid, aren't ya?
Ah, I'm sure that Goemon
is perfectly aware
of all of his new
responsibilities.
That's why I've invited
Lupin here tomorrow.
And then I have a
feeling that someone
will owe Goemon
an apology, right?
♪
Once Lupin's gone,
we won't be needing
these woodblock
prints anymore.
Ha!
♪
(waves crashing)
Goemon, kind of a creepy place
to meet, don't you think?
Don't tell me you're
challenging me to a duel.
Don't make light of it,
Lupin, it's the truth.
I'm sorry.
How come?
I've joined the Gang of Five.
Excuse me?
They have no decent arms.
With nothing but a
chain‐sickle, blowgun dart,
their wits, and their valor,
they've challenged you
and, so far, succeeded.
These are my
kind of warriors.
I see, and so killing me
is the proof of your
loyalty they demanded.
Once in a while, a man
just has to prove himself.
Yeah, well, not this
man, not now, see ya.
You cannot decline.
(grunting)
Ah!
♪
I see, you're really
serious about this, Goemon.
You really want to
kill me, don't you?
Better not hesitate.
Someone will die
when this is all over.
You or me.
(clanging)
(grunting)
♪
Forgive me, Lupin.
(grunting)
♪
Next time, I'm gonna
shoot you, Goemon.
♪
He failed us,
he's not worthy.
Come!
♪
Don't say anything,
Goemon, just listen to me.
We should run away together,
just the two of us.
You can expect nothing now
for the rest of your life
but to be endlessly
hunted by Lupin.
Come with me, quickly.
♪
(bird squawking)
Lupin's an injured lion now.
Goemon just put all
our lives in danger.
Maybe we should
cut our losses
and take off with the
woodblock prints right now.
Hurry men, get
me those prints!
‐Yes, sir!
‐Now!
Wait, they're not in here.
Mm‐mm.
Boss, they're gone!
Hey, where the
hell is Kikuko?
Damn it, it was her.
She betrayed us!
Ah!
I won't rest till I
find her and kill her.
♪
Wait, Kikuko, tell me,
why are you running away?
Later, please, hurry!
♪
(sniffing)
Everyone knows he
has a dog's face,
but only I know that he
has the nose as well.
(sniffing)
‐They went that way!
‐Are you certain?
What's the matter
with you guys?
Don't you trust my nose?
‐What are you waiting for?
‐Okay, come on!
Kikuko, I must know
where we're going and why.
Goemon, I'm in desperate
need of your help.
Right now we're going
to my father's place.
He's been waiting for me.
I mean, that is I hope
he's still waiting for me.
He‐‐he may already be dead.
Is‐‐is he ill?
Yes, the doctor said
nothing can be done.
He's just waiting
for the end.
♪
(sniffing)
He always wanted to see
the "36 Views of Mt. Fuji"
before he died.
He tried to steal
them himself once.
And that's why you
joined the Gang of Five?
Yes.
♪
I realize you owe
me nothing, Goemon,
but I'm begging you,
as a man of honor,
please help me get to where
my father is in Kisoji.
There's no one in the
world I can count on
and there's nobody I trust
as much as you, Goemon.
♪
Ah!
(grunting)
(thudding)
♪
Goemon, watch out!
Ah!
(grunting)
Oh!
No, Goemon!
Goemon, please wake up!
Wake up!
(gasping)
(laughing)
Of course you know the fate
that awaits a betrayer,
don't you, Kikuko?
(chain clinking)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(chain clinking)
♪
Now!
(grunting)
(coughing)
Hey, you just signed your own
death warrant, you traitor!
(water rushing)
So, Kikuko,
I take it you mean
that Damemon's
confronting Lupin
with inadequate weaponry
was nothing more than a ploy
to get me to join
the Gang of Five.
Yes, but I'm afraid to say
that even that
isn't all of it.
The goal is much
greater than just you.
And it isn't about the
"36 Views of Mt. Fuji."
Damemon means to
hold you hostage
in exchange for every
treasure that Lupin has.
He's taking everything?
Yes, and now I've ruined
his whole plan, you see,
for the sake of my father.
When Damemon finds me,
I'll be torn limb from limb.
♪
(beeping)
(whirring)
(birds chirping)
♪
Ah, isn't it wonderful?
It's so beautiful here.
Once you pass through that
valley, you'll be in Kisoji.
You should go quickly.
What, what are you
saying, Goemon?
Although it was Damemon
who manipulated me,
it was I who slashed Lupin.
I have to settle
this with him.
No, you've come too far.
What purpose could be
served by walking back
into the mouth of the dragon?
‐Listen!
‐You should get going.
I can't.
This is not what
you promised.
You told me you'd
take me to my father.
I know, but it's
different now.
Different, what's different?
I'm sorry, Kikuko.
Wait!
♪
Please, forgive me.
Goemon.
Oh, please, run away with me.
We'll go somewhere far away,
live a quiet life together
where no one will
ever find us, please?
That's not something I can do.
Why not?
Because I'm a man.
Just go, Kikuko.
Go to your father.
♪
Goodbye.
(gunshot)
So, we meet again.
This time, I'm gonna
blow your head off!
(gunshot)
Fight, Goemon,
you owe it to me!
♪
What the hell is this?
For having fallen for
Damemon's deception
and slashing you, the
only appropriate gesture
of apology is seppuku.
Therefore, I humbly
beg your assistance
in cutting off my head.
Sure!
It may not be exactly
how I saw this
playing out, but fine!
Lupin, hold it!
‐Quick!
‐Let's do it!
Lupin, here's some water.
Thanks, Jigen,
you're a mind reader.
(gasping)
It's all right.
If this is what
he really wants,
then helping him is a
true sign of friendship.
Shows he can count on us.
Okay, I'm ready, Goemon.
Now, all right, let me see,
around midway up
the neck, right?
Let's get this hair
out of the way.
Do you have any last words?
♪
‐No.
‐All right then.
♪
(gasping)
(clanking)
Damn it all,
this isn't any fun!
Come on, Goemon, let's
you and me fight it out
like real men, all right?
Put 'em up, let's go!
My pleasure!
(grunting)
Stop it, cut it out,
both of you, right now!
(gasping)
Hey, let 'em play.
(grunting)
♪
(grunting continuing)
(panting)
♪
Holding up pretty
good there, Goemon.
You too.
(groaning)
Well, I think
they've had enough.
♪
Oh, finally, I've made it.
Oh, ow, easy there, Fujiko!
That's the story, my
intention is to ask Kikuko
to return the prints to us
after she's shown
them to her father.
And what makes you
think a bitch like that
will honor the deal?
Kikuko is not who
you think she is.
She has a good heart.
‐Huh?
Hmm?
Damemon, show yourself!
Step forward so
I can kill you.
We'll handle him, Goemon,
you go on and get out of here.
Jigen's right, Goemon,
leave them to us.
I'm sorry.
I think old tight‐ass
has fallen in love.
Whoo, well, stranger
things have happened.
Has he got amnesia?
I mean, this is
the same babe
who tried to
barbecue me before.
(guns firing)
(running footsteps)
Kikuko, are you here?
It's me, Goemon, anyone here?
(water lapping)
Kikuko?
Kikuko!
Hmm?
♪
(gasping)
(thudding)
Not to put too fine
a point on it, Goemon,
but the "36 Views of Mt. Fuji"
are now mine and mine alone.
♪
Huh?
But how are you alive?
Kikuko, or whatever
you call yourself,
I'd appreciate the return
of those prints now.
I've come to my senses
and at last recall
the legendary story
of a young boy,
a villain who decided to
pretend that he was a woman
so people would
underestimate him
and he could
retire undetected.
Congratulations, Goemon,
took you long enough.
Hmm!
I've been living in disguise
since I was just a kid.
And it's been one
hell of a racket.
So if you want to go
all samurai on me,
go on, give it a try!
But, remember, I'm not
some delicate flower.
♪
(shouting)
(grunting)
♪
Huh, what the
hell is going on?
♪
Normally, I wouldn't require
a request to identify myself,
but I took my very first
bath in the River Seine
and I'm quite well known
at the Ritz Hotel.
I run an internationally
known robbery business
and I've earned a
well‐deserved reputation
as a master thief.
I am...
Hi‐ya!
Lupin the Third,
at your service!
Next up is a master
of the Magnum.
I can shoot around
corners and in the dark.
Want to stay healthy?
Don't make fun of my hat.
I'm cool enough to give
Dirty Harry a good scare.
My reputation for
misogyny is legendary.
(gun firing)
Name is Daisuke Jigen,
and I don't take no crap.
Now, a beautiful woman
whose breasts that have been
aptly compared to Twin Peaks.
I've also been blessed
with a naturally cute face.
I'm quite adept
at using them both
for purposes of robbery
and racketeering.
I'm Fujiko Mine.
Mwah, legendary femme fatale.
The next one up is
back from the dead.
I've returned from hell
with a bloody sword
to avenge the wrongs
that have been done to me.
I'm just a common
run‐of‐the‐mill thief.
Nothing special.
They call me Goemon
Ishikawa because...
(grunting)
...that is my name.
Bringing up the rear, it is
I, Interpol's heartthrob.
My style is clean‐cut
and righteous.
I go to work every day,
risking my life
to capture Lupin.
I live and die for justice.
I'm Inspector Zenigata.
What the‐‐
Think of us then as a
flock of five wild geese.
Of four ganders.
And one beautiful goose.
And although the sight of us
may be a little shocking...
...it is known
far and wide...
... we are...
...the better five than you!
♪
We concede.
You win!
♪
Hey, get back here!
You're under arrest!
♪
Sorry, but you'll
never arrest me!
You tell 'em!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Here's a switch, Pops
wants me to teach him
how to be a thief.
Can't say he's barking
up the wrong tree.
We go up against a
computerized security system
that's been programmed to
anticipate my every move.
Damn thing knows me
better than I do.
I just hope Pops
doesn't pick up any tips.
It's called the
"Alter‐Ego Maniac."
Catch ya later!
♪