♪
♪ Lup ♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪♪
This story started with
a single phone call.
(phone ringing)
The number you've dialed
is no longer in service.
Check your telephone directory
or the information operator
for the correct
number and go to hell.
(phone ringing)
You've reached Lupin's mouth,
his brain is still asleep.
Oh, then you'd prefer to
speak to somebody else, okay.
Jigen, phone!
It's for you!
♪
Uh, sorry about that.
Wait a minute, Fujiko?
No, and I really couldn't care
less where you are right now.
What is this, some kinda
friggin' guessing game?
‐Fujiko, I want Fujiko.
‐Broadway, huh?
‐That's real nice.
‐Listen, Jigen.
I'm with Dr. Pot at his
lab, you remember him.
You know, the strange guy
who comes to see Lupin
every now and then with these
weird gadgets he invents.
Uh‐huh, well here's the deal.
Now listen carefully, you
gotta be awake for this one.
He's come up with a robot
that cries diamond tears.
(machinery clicking)
Unbelievable, well at
the moment I'm wearing
a very pretty little number
made with thousands of them.
Dream, no, I'm wide awake!
Just tell Lupin what I said.
‐So, how'd it go, Fujiko?
‐Not at all well.
I wanted to speak to Lupin,
but all I got was an earful
of dismissive insults
from that bastard Jigen.
Someday he's gonna go too far.
Men, they can be so pigheaded.
Anything they haven't heard of
before can't possibly be true.
‐I believe in you, Doctor.
‐It's Gavott.
♪
In fact, I am swiping
it from yous right now.
(gunshots firing)
(screaming)
(typewriter keys clicking)
♪
(indistinct conversations)
(laughing and screaming)
Hey!
♪
Oh, Baby, Baby, Baby, Baby.
You are like my angel, I swear.
I could be that for ya.
‐Your beautiful blonde angel.
‐Could ya?
Well, then why don't you and
me seal it with a little‐‐
Uh‐uh, none of that
yet, lover boy.
Not until yous get me
some of them diamonds
from that diamond‐making robot.
Look at what your very
own lover boy brought ya.
Here's the deal, I held
up my end of the bargain.
Now watch out, your turn's next.
Oh.
A diamond's coming up, Baby.
Oh, it's freezing, turn it off!
Freezing water, sorry, Baby.
(laughing)
Yeah, I'll show ya sorry!
Ow, hey!
(maniacal laughter)
Shut ya yap, One Ear.
Do I amuse you, do
I make you laugh?
Now, go and get that
damn car ready!
Lady!
What the hell kinda
man are yous anyway?
‐Takin' it out on the kid.
‐Huh?
Okay, let me see if I got this.
A low‐life named Gavott
barged in in broad daylight
and made off with a
diamond‐making robot
so he could impress
his sort‐of girlfriend.
Yeah, well, I can relate.
Look, at the risk of sounding
like a broken record here,
are you really sure
those diamonds are real?
Mhm, but you forgot
condescending,
a condescending broken record.
Look, I'm telling you,
the guy must've sprayed
that place with hundreds
of rounds, and every one
of them bounded right off.
Maybe you've heard
of bulletproof paste,
‐but I never have.
‐But how did this Gavott person
find out about
Dr. Pot's new robot?
Here's what I heard,
Gavott was the one
Dr. Pot made the robot
for in the first place.
He supposedly wanted it to tend
bar in some joint he owns.
Yeah, well that would explain
how he knew about the robot.
♪
(car engines whirring)
(tires screeching)
♪
Hey, what the hell's the matter
with you, ya dumb bastard?
There happens to be other
friggin' people in the world!
Hmph!
Just isn't my day.
(laughing)
(car engine puttering)
Take it easy, I'm not here on
business, I'm taking in a show.
Rest assured, I'll
turn my attention
‐back to you after that.
‐I get the feeling
your travel agent hasn't
been here for a while.
The strip shows are gone.
That is what you're here for?
(grunting)
♪
Dang it all, I can just
tell he's up to something!
Hey there!
Taxi, taxi!
Police, you gotta
chase that car!
Sure.
Hm?
You know, for a large man,
he sure is a fast runner.
♪
Huh?
I don't get it, none
of Gavott's people
seem to be anywhere
around the place.
Got a problem with that?
Hey, watch it!
♪
(engine revving)
Just a little Liza Minnelli,
that's all, just a little break,
a little vacation, but
who do I have to run into?
Lupin, that's who, and now I
can't stop thinking about him.
Stupid ticket.
I can't use this now!
(engine buzzing)
I know that's him!
♪
Hey, taxi!
You again, just don't
leave me behind this time!
Sure.
♪
I want you to take me!
Hey, am I getting
through to you?
Uh‐huh.
♪
(tires skidding)
Hey, why don't you
learn how to drive?
You know there are
other freaking people
in the world, damn it!
What the hell's
the matter with you?
(shouting)
Oh, Baby, be reasonable.
First you grab the robot,
only no diamonds come out.
Then you grab the Doc,
but there ain't no robot.
‐You know what that makes you?
‐A third rate gangster?
No, a fourth rate gangster!
Hmph!
(laughing)
What's the big joke, One Ear?
You keep this up and pretty
soon you'll be changing
your name to No Ear, ya capisce?
‐Put that away!
‐He's got a big gun!
Oh, Joe, now don't you worry.
I'm gonna look out for that
one little ear of yours
just like it was my own
one little ear, okay?
Baby, you're gonna
spoil that kid.
Next thing you know he's
gonna want his own pony.
Heartless bastard!
(grunting)
No, Baby, please,
come on, watch this!
I wanna know who stole
that robot, Doc, talk!
I wouldn't tell ya even if I
knew, ya third rate gangster!
All right, old man, that is it.
I bet you did not know I
used to train for the ring.
They used to call me
the Minnesota Loon.
You get beaten in the
head a lot, Gavott,
or were you always a moron?
Take this, and this, and
this, and this, and that!
And one of these,
now one of those!
(growling)
Ahh!
♪
(screaming)
Wow, Baby!
Nice hook.
♪
Oh, Baby, you are
so damn beautiful.
Listen up, yous guys,
this broad ain't takin'
any more disappointments!
‐Find that damn robot!
‐Aye!
‐Yeah!
‐Right!
♪
I mean, even if a
thing like this worked,
what would a person
ever use it for?
Wouldn't have a giant
paperclip on you, would ya?
Not much of a super
electromagnet.
Huh, Dr. Pot's patented
automatic nose‐blower.
"To activate, just
hold in front of face."
Hey, get a load
of this, it's cute.
Ow, ahh!
Damn it!
Where do you think
Dr. Pot could be?
It's just that I want you to
see I wasn't imagining this.
Hey, be patient, I'm sure
he'll be back any time.
(gunfire)
What the hell is this?
The doctor's not in!
It's Gavott and his men
here to take back the robot.
Listen to me, Baby, that robot's
gonna be yours any second now.
What're you waiting for,
an engraved invitation?
Get in there!
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(gunshots firing)
Ah, shoot stuff!
Stop shootin'!
What're ya, blind?
There's no one here, ya big ape!
♪
Looks like that Lupin
was just too scared
to face me and ran away.
I don't give a rat's
butt about that guy.
I want that robot,
you promised, you know?
What're you guys doin'
just standin' there?
Lupin doesn't matter,
just find the damn robot.
Go!
A girl like I needs
diamonds and her own robot.
I just gotta have a robot
that makes diamonds!
It's gonna be all right,
we'll find the robot.
Don't start bawling, I
can't stand to see ya cry.
What're you saying, my
crying face is ugly?
Is that it, ya big gorilla?
That's it!
No, come on, hey!
What, look out!
Hey, come on!
♪
Boss?
Tell me you got the robot.
It looks like Lupin
got away with it.
So go and get it back!
Does that sound like
a plan to you, huh?
Yeah, thank you!
Don't look at me like that, I
am not the one at fault here.
If I had a better class of bum
working for me, I could've
easily been just about the
biggest boss in the whole world.
Uh, Baby?
Huh?
Hey, Baby!
Hey, where are ya?
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Man, poor Gavott, she's
really got him wrapped
around her little
finger, doesn't she?
I was sweatin' bullets
when she started throwing
these parts all over the place.
If only she knew what
she was trashing, huh?
She couldn't see through her
anger and greed that she
was holding in her hands the
very object of her desire.
Well, why don't we get to
work on old Humpty Dumpty.
That doesn't sound good,
all the king's horses and all
the king's men couldn't
put Humpty together again.
Don't worry, I've done
this twice before.
‐You've assembled a robot?
‐Nah.
‐A ship, and a tank.
‐A ship and a tank?
‐That's really quite impressive.
‐Yeah, I used to spend
all my allowance on those hobby
kits of model ships and tanks.
Huh?
You mean you've been talking
about model airplanes and toys?
Sure, keeps a young man's
hands outta trouble.
I forget, which orifice did you
say the diamonds came out of?
Hold it, Lupin.
Seems like there's a
step we didn't count on.
Her?
Let go of me, ya big lug!
I'm a lady, damn it, hey!
Caught her in the ladies' room,
which doesn't automatically
qualify you as a
lady, by the way.
She was looking for the robot.
What's this about a step we
didn't take into account?
Hmph, why, didn't your
friend Dr. Pot tell ya?
Go ahead, turn it on,
it's just cold water.
Hey, that's genuine velveteen!
So that means there's
a secret formula,
which explains the kidnapping.
‐Hello.
‐Yeah, what?
I really think that
you deserve that robot.
‐Huh?
‐Lupin!
Fujiko, please,
you gotta trust me.
Okay, Baby, here's the deal I
am offering you, so listen up.
We'll give you the robot if
your boyfriend releases Dr. Pot.
‐You serious about that?
‐Sure, scout's honor.
I'd never lie to a lady.
Jigen?
Well, in that case,
I guess I won't
send you the dry‐cleaning bill.
You know, as a real lady, I
could've used a real gentleman.
It's a shame, now
you'll never know.
And just cause Gavott lets
the doctor go doesn't mean
he isn't gonna
rub yous guys out!
And you, I'm gonna pluck
that beard off your face
myself before he kills ya!
Please tell me you were kidding
about giving up that robot.
♪
Guy's a dangerous gangster,
you know, and yet he says,
"Hey, let's meet on
the rollercoaster!"
The story I heard
is they met here.
She was slinging hot dogs
at a concession stand.
Ahh!
♪
You keep your appointments.
I like that in a guy, Lupin.
Now, hand over
the friggin' robot.
Yeah, well I don't like
anything about you.
First, you hand over the doctor.
I knew this G‐man once, a
smart aleck just like you.
Unfortunately, the guy
came to a real bad end,
but luckily for you, I
like you better than that.
So here's the deal, I'll
give you the doc first.
Okay, just like you said.
As soon as this car gets
to ya, get the doc out,
and send the robot
over in the other car.
Okay, Baby, now!
(machinery whirring)
Ahh!
(screaming)
(whooshing)
That thing's not
slowing down at all!
I think it's gonna crash
right into this car!
(yelling)
(explosion)
Ahhhh!
So who's the smart one now?
‐Lupin or Gavott?
‐You're a genius!
(helicopter buzzing)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(shouting)
♪
It's going backwards!
But Gavott, what about my robot?
♪
Hey, guys, go get him,
and smush him up good!
(angry remarks)
♪
Uh‐oh.
There he is, boys!
Let him have it!
(gunfire)
Stop, what's the
matter with you?
You wanna be Bonnie and Clyde?
Hey, believe me, we
would if we could!
(shouting)
♪
You big baboon!
Hey, would you cut
it out, ya raccoon?
‐What the hell does that mean?
‐Hey, guys, come on.
That's no way to
treat each other.
You two squabble so much,
you know, you really oughta
be married, and then
you'll live longer.
It wouldn't be fair if she won
the fight just by outliving ya.
Let's celebrate, take this!
‐Huh?
That's right, now
blow out the candles.
Uh...
(explosion)
♪
(groaning)
I don't mean to be ungrateful,
but didn't Goemon sever
this track just a
little while ago?
Minor oversight.
♪
Do you realize you're
exceeding the speed limit?
I'll take care of this,
you two watch the robot!
♪
(screaming)
Really, the most amazing part
was that you fixed
my electromagnet.
I just switched the batteries,
Doctor, that's all.
By the way, I took
this damn thing apart,
but I couldn't find it.
Which is the component
that makes the diamonds?
My very own patented
coagulating agent.
Gavott never put it in, that's
why he only got freezing water.
Now you'll see it work.
(machine clicking)
I don't know how
to tell you this,
but what you got here
is really only an ice cube
that more or less
looks like a diamond.
‐Huh?
‐Woo‐hoo!
It's an amazing advance
in ice technology!
Diamond‐shaped ice cubes, I
can't believe I'm a genius!
‐Oh, Lord.
‐My dear friend,
I can't express my gratitude.
Somehow you made that thing
work by taking it apart.
‐Thank you so much!
‐But what about the diamonds?
It was a lucky accident, it
could happen again though.
Around here, accidents
happen all the time.
♪
Gavott spent three
months in the hospital,
and came out a changed man.
He dissolved his gang and
found his true calling.
♪
The robot found work in a bar.
The two dollars an hour
was just bad negotiating.
Baby eloped with One Ear,
which was one ear too many
for anyone unlucky enough to
find himself shackled to her.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
When this famous conductor
brings down the house,
better watch where you're
standing, at least if you're me.
Why he's so dead set on
conducting me outta this world,
I have no idea, but I
have to find out fast,
'cause he starts attracting
some pretty well‐known soloists
to his orchestrated
effort to do me in.
Is this my finale?
Find out in,
"Baton Death March."
Catch ya later!
♪