♪
(gunshot)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(glass shattering)
(engine revs)
(tires screeching)
♪
(gunfire)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(tires screeching)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(traffic noises)
(sirens)
♪
(snoring)
Huh, you?
But, how the hell did‐‐
(yelps)
♪
You bastard, I'll‐‐
(grunting)
(guttural moans)
♪
(typewriter keys clicking)
What, did I just hear you right?
In Hawaii?
You want me to deliver
a presentation on Lupin's
whole career?
Precisely, the request
comes straight from the top.
There's to be an international
law enforcement
conference there.
You'll be a special
guest speaker.
Hmm, a special guest, huh?
That means that I'm sort
of a, you know, a VIP!
Mm‐hmm, that's right.
Thanks, sir, but I
just can't do it!
With all due respect,
fancy conferences
and exotic locations
are all fine and well, sir,
but my first obligation is‐‐
You damned fool,
this is an order!
It is?
Besides, this is
an incredible honor.
You are being recognized
as an expert internationally
on the foremost
criminal of our times.
Inspector, this should
be the proudest moment
of your career.
It's my proudest moment, huh?
Can I keep my frequent
flyer miles, sir?
I'd like to get to work
on the big speech,
if it's all right with you.
Request permission
to leave, sir.
You can do that
on the plane, Inspector.
There's your passport;
your flight leaves in two hours.
Well, get moving!
(jet roaring)
♪
Well, there he goes.
He's definitely
on board, I checked.
That's good news, Jigen.
That means things will be nice
and quiet for
a little while, anyway.
How about we toast to it?
That's great,
I'm looking forward
to just kicking‐‐
(grunting)
♪
(engine revs)
(tires screeching)
(door opens)
♪
Hey there, Beauty.
Guten tag, Jigen,
you haven't changed a bit.
Yeah, so what
the hell do you want?
Not here to kill you,
if that's what you're
worried about.
I'm here for Sideburn Boy.
Lupin, INTERPOL's decided
to put a bounty on your head.
You're kiddin' me!
That doesn't sound like them.
Too bad; you're getting
to be an embarrassment.
So, they came to me
to take care of it.
You are the best, Beauty.
Hey, wait, here's
a crazy thought:
Why don't you tell 'em
I couldn't be found?
If you can't find a guy,
then you can't kill him.
I will give you until tomorrow
to get your affairs in order,
make one last pathetic play
for Fujiko, stuff like that.
Nothing personal, you know?
It's all just business, bye‐bye.
♪
(tires screech)
Well, that's bad news.
New York's demon
detective is back.
I don't know how the hell
the guy ever earned a promotion.
I tell ya, INTERPOL
sure is going downhill.
He's just overcompensating
for that nickname, that's all.
Come on, Lupin,
you said it yourself,
Beauty's the best.
And that big‐ass gun he carries,
it's a . 44 caliber
Colt‐8 Python.
That's the most powerful
handgun in the world.
Lupin, come on,
let's just get outta here
for a little while, you know,
to somewhere like Tahiti
or something.
Hey, Fujiko,
I'm not Gauguin, you know?
I'm a thief.
You've got the wrong guy.
While I'm not an expert
in firearms, I can tell you
that the man carries the aura
of a dangerous killer.
Lupin, listen to me,
it would be suicide
to let pride get in your way.
This maniac is
a killer with a badge.
♪
(singing in foreign language)
(laughing)
Aloha!
Well, thanks!
The same to you, toots!
Mr. Zenigata!
Aren't you sweet?
(kissing)
Yuck!
So, I am a VIP!
There's only one thing missing,
and that thing is rubbing
my newfound celebrity
in the smirking chimp‐like
face of Lupin the Third!
Look, man, you gotta get
your ego out of this.
Beauty's just way
out of your league
and there's zero shame
in admitting it.
Jigen, you're making
too much of this.
Oh, yeah, you think so, huh?
Listen, it was
just six years ago.
♪
I was at the peak
of my powers, right?
Almost as cocky as you.
♪
(gunfire)
(tires screeching)
♪
Huh?
(gunshot)
(screeching)
(explosion)
(screeching, crash)
(panting)
♪
I ran, and I'm not
the least bit ashamed
to say it.
Think of it as
a tactical retreat, Lupin.
This is just a battle,
not the entire war.
Don't patronize me!
Look, you guys, if I don't
step up to this challenge,
then I'd better just quit.
You're a fool, damn you!
Dickhead!
He's a much better shot
than you, with a better gun!
You duel with him
and you're dead!
Old‐fashioned?
Yes, of course,
guilty as charged!
It's all about the law;
it's not about revenge.
Sure, part of me would love
to take on Lupin with
my bare fists and give him
a good thrashing or even worse!
But nobody hired me to be
judge, jury, and executioner.
It was the great
Charlie Chaplin, I think,
who said‐‐yeah,
this is it,
"Kill one murderer and you're
nothing but a criminal,
but kill a million criminals
and you're a heroic,
endearing little tramp."
That wasn't exactly it
but it's still true today!
(applause)
Thank you, thank you!
Really, take it easy, now.
His gun is better than mine?
What do you mean by that?
Look, this is your Walther‐‐
it's a great gun
and the double‐action it has
makes the P38 the best
automatic pistol
in the world.
The ballistic course of
the Parabellum is real stable.
It's a classic,
no doubt about it.
Then we agree?
Except that your Walther
doesn't shoot mags.
♪
For that, you gotta have a . 357.
Like this, the good old
Smith & Wesson . 357 Magnum:
a classic with cojones.
(gun clicking)
(gunshot)
(gunfire)
Jigen, I know that a . 357's
got the destructive edge,
but it just isn't as accurate.
Speaking of accuracy,
I noticed something about
that gun that Beauty was
waving around yesterday.
It's got a Venturi built on it
and that's used for cooling
the barrel so that the heat
won't affect your aim.
It's state‐of‐the‐art.
Your Walther P38
was originally manufactured
all the way back in the 1930s.
All I'm saying is Beauty's
got a . 44 Colt‐8 Python
that was made only
a few years ago,
and that's the difference‐‐
you do the math, Lupin.
This is Jigen's area
of mastery, Lupin.
To choose to ignore his advice
is to choose the path
of fatal folly.
♪
What, but that's insane?
Kill Lupin?
Yes, I swear that it's true.
So, they set me up
with this damn conference
while they dispatch Beauty to‐‐
Hmm, so, that's their game!
You've gotta do something,
Inspector, please?
All right, keep your shirt on!
I'll take care of this!
Sorry, guys, had to do it.
Anyway, one way or the other,
it'll all be over
by the time you find me.
For me, this is just
about being alive.
A guy can't run every time
some guy wants to do him in.
You just gotta face it.
(gun clacking)
♪
And find out whatcha got.
(engine revving)
♪
(tires squealing)
(yelping)
(engine revving)
(chuckles)
(yelps)
(screeching)
(gunshot)
(explosion)
Huh?
Agh, dammit, Lupin
took off to find Beauty!
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(fire crackling)
(engine revving)
(explosion)
♪
(grunting)
(chuckling)
Not bad, but don't
gloat just yet, Beauty.
I'm not handing myself
to you on a platter,
You've gotta take me.
Make my day.
(grunts)
(panting)
♪
Heh.
Better an execution
than a shootout, Lupin.
Believe me, a lot
less humiliating.
(gunshots)
Idiot.
Huh?
♪
(gunshots)
What the hell's going on?
Damn!
♪
(guns cock)
(gunshot)
♪
Playtime is over,
see you in hell.
Not so fast, Beauty, hold it!
Hey, I said wait!
Whoa!
(gasps)
Lupin, talk to me,
are you all right?
(grunting)
Come on, were you hurt?
Talk to me.
The sun, it's setting.
Seems kinda early for it,
but I guess it's just my time.
No, it isn't, Lupin,
it's not your time yet!
(chuckles)
♪
Proud of yourself, are ya, huh?
I oughta‐‐Beauty, you bastard!
He's a sadist too, killing's
not good enough for him,
I guess the guy has to use
hollow‐point bullets just
to make his victims suffer.
Well, is that the truth, Beauty?
You're actually using dum‐dums?
Those things are‐‐
Illegal, they have
been ever since
the Treaty
of Versailles of 1929.
I don't know a whole
lot of history,
but if it affects me,
I remember it.
Treaty of Versailles?
It's all coming back.
The police are forbidden
from using those!
Hey!
And your point, Inspector?
If the order is for
extreme prejudice,
it doesn't make any difference
if the guy suffers
a little but more.
I mean, he is
the enemy, isn't he?
(thunder)
(rainfall)
(continuous thunder)
Oh, just look at me,
I'm soaking!
What weather!
Oh, man, it was
so freakin' cold,
I was freezin' my ass off!
I know, the weather was biblical
in its ferocity and sense
of dark foreboding.
Listen to you guys:
bitch, bitch, bitch!
Look at me, what
the hell's going on?
I'm fine, so what's
with the funeral, well?
Hey, Lupin, you have no clue
how close you came to needing
that funeral.
Friggin' bastard was packin'
hollow‐points in that gun
of his, you realize that?
There wouldn't have been
enough of you left to pour
into that damn body cast
if just one of 'em hit ya.
♪
(gunfire)
(rumbling)
I dropped an adhesive
load on that rock.
♪
Just in time.
I can't believe it,
what kind of a sadist is he?
That bastard's really
gonna pay for this!
(grunting)
Hey, you just stay here
and get some rest.
(whimpering)
(jet roaring)
Incoming message for
Inspector Beauty of INTERPOL.
Inspector Beauty of INTERPOL,
please pick up your headset
for a message.
Listen to you guys:
bitch, bitch, bitch!
Look at me, I can't believe it!
What kind of a sadist is he?
That bastard's really
gonna pay for this!
♪
(growls)
Come in!
Where's Lupin?
Is this a trick question?
♪
What, well, let's just say
the thing's not a hoax
and I don't have any orders
to help you and I wouldn't
want to even if I did, and now,
I've got goodies to eat!
I'll still find him.
(gunfire)
Whoa!
So, you're the hunted?
How's that make ya feel, friend?
♪
(humming)
Why all the thermometers?
What are you doing?
I'm fighting fire with fire;
if he wants to use dum‐dums,
then I'll just have
to raise him.
My own invention:
mercury bullets!
Lupin, I don't think
you're taking this seriously!
There's no time
for joking around.
I promise I'm not joking around,
so come on, will ya?
Give me a hand
breaking these things.
Gently, now.
♪
Watch out, Beauty,
I'm comin' for ya!
I've never heard
of a mercury bullet.
I lied before, it's really
not my invention at all.
Believe it not, it comes
straight out of a book
by Ernest Hemingway.
Supposedly, just a single bullet
can bring down
a charging bull elephant,
that's how lethal this stuff is.
See, as soon as
it hits the target,
the impact releases the mercury
straight into the bloodstream.
♪
That's it, nothing he
can do about it,
taken totally by surprise.
Beauty won't even have the
time to know he's surprised.
By the way, Lupin,
what do you know
about mixing
explosives with mercury?
Nothing, I guess, why?
Lupin, it's dangerous!
Don't worry yourself, Fujicakes!
I'm nobody's smithereen.
♪
Jeez, have a little
faith, will ya?
♪
(wind whooshing)
I sure hope it
didn't ruin your day
to find out that
Lupin's still alive.
Lovely location
for our showdown.
Point is Dream Island's
a landfill, which make it
kind of a perfect place
for burying trash.
Big talk from a guy whose
specialty is turning tail!
(laughing)
You know, Beauty,
ever since that night,
I thought about facing off with
you and yet it only occurred
to me just yesterday
what your Achilles heel
actually is, and, you know,
it's kinda funny when you
think about it.
Huh?
That big piece you carry
is real scary, but the fact is
you need both hands just
to shoot the damn thing.
Wanna see just how big
a liability it is?
Anytime, pretty boy.
(gunshot)
How in the hell did you do that?
It's impossible!
Damn.
Jigen, I'm the best there is.
Why the hell do you think
INTERPOL picked me
for this assignment?
And on top of that,
they also promised me
a pretty nifty Christmas bonus.
Man, so this is how I end up.
Shame you can't
run away this time.
(cocks gun)
(screeching)
(engine revs)
♪
Listen‐‐
What the hell?
Look, there's a
pretty good chance
we're gonna die here,
but I say we give it
a shot, okay?
So, here's a little
present I made for ya;
it's a one‐of‐a‐kind bullet
with a mercury payload.
Use my shoulder.
(cocks gun)
Here goes nothing.
♪
Now, Jigen, do it!
(gunshot)
(agonized screaming)
Was it, uh, supposed
to work like that?
I'm not a chemist
or anything, you know,
but I think I mighta added
a little too much explosive.
Probably shouldn't do that kind
of thing when you're
in a bad mood.
(yelping)
Wait, she needs mouth to mouth?
Chest compression?
Hey, that's my job!
D'oh!
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Confused‐‐join the club!
It's enough to make you
pull your face off.
Giant monkeys,
human chess pieces,
or are they actually
normal‐sized monkeys
and we've all been
shrunk to the size
of Lupin collectables?
Either way, we're in a fix.
Join us next time as we live
to regret out latest search
for a mysterious treasure in
"Monkey King Business"!
Catch ya later!
♪