♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(gunshot)
♪
(women vocalizing)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
Over the centuries,
this paradisal corner
of southwestern France
has produced
millions of bottles
of the world's
most famous wines
and none more famous than
the vintage commissioned
by Napoleon himself for his
beloved wife, Joséphine.
Now the last remaining bottle
of this legendary Bordeaux
will be presented to the
President of the United States
this Christmas Eve
as a token of the
enduring bond between‐‐
Eh, what a waste.
Might as well give a Ferrari
to a ring‐tailed ferret.
That's heaven in
a glass, I'm guessing.
Come now, surely you don't
prefer that stuff to sake.
It's called sake
'cause it tastes like
you rung it outta
your tube socks.
And another thing, man,
don't call me Shirley.
I just can't imagine
a more romantic gesture
than creating a wine
for your lover.
I mean, if a guy
ever did that for me
‐I'd be putty in his hands.
‐Oh yeah?
Well, I'm no emperor
but I could get you
that very bottle.
Lupin, really?
You're not serious, are you?
Bartender, you have to
cut this man off now.
Hey, I'm serious and sober!
Oh, Lupin.
Goemon, one sip would
even convert you.
I'll bet one sip of that
stuff woulda been enough
to even convert Bill W.
But, Lupin, buddy, how the
hell are you gonna find out
exactly where it is?
Oh, that's the simple part,
I've already
figured that one out.
To the emperor of thieves.
(glasses clink)
And may the next toast be
with the liquid testament
to a legendary love
instead of this
purgatory in a snifter.
♪
(chuckles)
(typewriter keys clacking)
♪
A big glass of cheap wine,
bread you could
break your teeth on,
and they call this eating.
No wonder they can't win a war!
(laughing)
(groaning)
Ow, I'd kill for a double
cheeseburger and some fries.
(knocking)
A letter for you, sir.
♪
What, a letter, huh?
Nice.
I wonder if it's from Mother.
Lupin!
(growling)
Hey, Pops, you know
that famous bottle of wine
that's going to Washington
for the President?
Well, it's not;
Catch ya later, Lupin.
P. S. don't you ever
take that coat off?
That no‐good,
he's just taunting me!
(growling)
Damn you!
(car horn blaring)
Huh?
Uh‐oh.
Oh, wow, what did I‐‐
(whistling inconspicuously)
♪
Look at this, man,
nothing but vineyards
and chateaus as far
as the eye can see.
It's like going back in time.
You know, they've been
producing wine here
since Roman times,
but winemaking's
much older than that.
Hey, listen to me, will ya?
I should have a public
television show, you know?
‐Here they are.
‐Right on time.
♪
Worked like a charm.
Just announce
you're gonna steal it
and old Pops'll
lead you right to it.
That's a stroke of genius.
Aww, you big flatterer,
you're making me blush.
♪
This bastard
challenged me personally.
This is war!
Professional courtesy
dictates you include me
in your security team, please!
Trust me, Inspector,
these men are up to the job.
They're the very best.
‐There's no need to worry.
‐But I'm telling you,
I'm the only one in the world
who can capture this guy!
I know what you are saying
but then why have
you not captured him?
Uh...
Well, hm...
Well, I suppose as
a professional courtesy
you can observe.
Wow, really, Chief, you mean it?
Just try not to interfere
with the operation.
Of course not‐‐by the way,
where is that bottle of wine?
I'll take you there now,
just follow me,
Inspector Origami.
Hey, the name's not
Origami, it's Zenigata!
Okay, guys, time to play
Follow the Leader.
♪
Mm‐mm‐mm.
Grow up, will you?!
(chuckles)
Hm!
‐You too!
‐Uh, me?
Uh, I didn't see a thing.
Better cover you up.
‐Hm!
‐Bye!
(singsong chuckling)
♪
(siren wailing)
Hm?
‐(imitating French greeting)
‐What was that?
Just a local greeting.
He's saying hello?
Something of a local custom.
People are very warm
in these parts.
How nice.
Uh, parlez‐vous
Jacques Cousteau?
En va!
Ja!
(grunting)
‐Bon Jovi!
‐Chi‐chi‐chi‐chi!
Uh, chi‐chi‐chi‐chi!
How much longer do I
have to keep this up?
It is all up to you,
Inspector Epiglottis.
It's Zenigata!
♪
Ah, Zenigata led me
right to the chateau.
(car horn honking)
♪
And they got all the
guards stationed inside
so they won't draw attention.
Hopefully I won't
draw any either.
(engine revving)
(horn honking)
(door creaking)
Hello, bonjour!
What is it you want, old fellow?
Well, these barrels have to
get down to the wine cellar.
(grunting)
Oh, my back is not
what it used to be.
(grunting)
Yes, hard to believe, I was
once as strong as you two.
Okay, we get the
point, old timer.
(grunting)
Ahh.
Easy, boys, easy now,
I mean, uh,
they'll go along
quietly, they will.
As long as you
treat them nice, huh?
(laughs)
Oh, mon Dieu, they're heavy.
What is going on here?
(grunting)
Hello, bonjour, I'm here
with the wine delivery.
I say we check these
barrels out, Chief.
I mean, you never know.
I know my job,
Inspector Terracotta.
Zenigata, how many times
do I have to tell ya?!
♪
Here, let me see that.
Mais oui.
♪
Yeah, all right,
but check 'em all.
♪
Voilà.
‐Oui, it's okay.
‐It's wine, all right.
♪
All right, men, help him
get these into the cellar.
♪
(groaning)
Hey, slow down, you want
them to get all dizzy in there?
Dizzy?
Uh, fizzy, I said "fizzy."
Fine for Champagne
but not for this stuff.
(chuckles)
(grunting)
All right,
old fellow, so tell me,
where do you want
these things to go?
Well now, that all
depends, you see, mon ami.
Got to find three empty ones.
Oh no, you've got to be kidding.
Ah, it'll only take
a couple of hours.
Course, it could go
a little faster
with your help.
Hey, we are policemen,
not your servants!
Let us know when you are done,
we will escort you out.
Sacrebleu, can you believe it?
Eh, what an operator.
Oh, my back!
(chuckles)
Okay, the coast is clear.
♪
(sighs)
This'd be real homey
if I were a spider
or a corpse.
Actually, it's perfect
for wine storage.
You see, the
coolness and the dark
allow it to age
without spoiling.
So this must be the place
where Dick Clark lives.
Lupin, let's just grab this
bottle and vamoose, 'kay?
Sure, it's... uh,
right over there.
Uh, could you be just
a little bit more specific?
How in the world are
we ever gonna find it?
Well, uh, I'm pretty
certain the bottle's green.
♪
Well, that's a lot of help.
Ha, fooled you this time!
It's not even here, Lupin!
Wha‐‐damn it, what do you mean?
I knew you were
setting me up, Lupin.
You had no idea
where the bottle was.
But I turned the
tables on you, Lupin!
I had 'em take me
to the wrong place
and now you're hoisting
your own whatever you call it.
Petard, it's called
a damn petard.
Like I give a damn;
You're all under arrest!
Get 'em!
Stay where you are, put your
hands where I can see them!
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Here!
Grab some more!
(yelling)
♪
Lupin, you maniac!
Stop!
♪
Hey, stop!
Hungry, Pops, 'cause
a touch of flame's all we need
to make a flatfoot flambé.
Yeah, Lupin,
please don't do it!
Okay, but do me a favor and
just marinate a little longer.
Thanks, buddy.
So long, see ya.
You bastard, I'll get
you for this, Lupin!
Come now, Inspector
whatever your name is,
have a drink on us.
♪ Allons, enfants
de la Patrie ♪
♪ Le jour de gloire
est arrivé! ♪
(singing continues)
Hey, Lupin, knock it off!
Lupin!
You sure you're okay to drive?
Oh, sure, I'm fine, just fine.
Little bit of alcohol like
that isn't gonna affect me.
Lupin!
Cut it out!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
You guys are a couple
of lightweights.
(groaning)
Come on, man,
keep it down, will ya?
‐Eh, geez.
‐You know, just for the record,
I've never been hungover
from drinking sake.
Gee, you think maybe that's
'cause it tastes like crap?!
(groaning)
Ah, here you are, my dear
good friend and colleague,
Inspector Pennsylvania.
Mon ami.
Merci, thanks to you, the bottle
is perfectly safe with us.
Hey, Lieutenant, you think
you could get my name right
if I promise not to
throw up on your shoes?
By the way, Inspector,
would you like to help
us escort the bottle
to the White House
in Washington, DC?
Huh‐‐oh, yeah, sure, whatever.
(laughing)
Très formidable!
(groaning)
♪
Security's incredibly
tight on this.
Your tax dollars at work.
♪
Look.
(siren wailing)
♪
(grunting)
Pops must have really
impressed them yesterday.
Looks like they made him
part of the security detail.
(beeping)
Hm, hey, what's up, babe?
They're loading a big,
unmarked crate onboard.
Looks kinda suspicious to me.
♪
Ah, yeah, good catch,
we should look into that.
♪
Lupin, I'm gonna go
check it out, okay?
♪
Hey, what's in that big
crate we're taking on?
I'm not really sure
but it's supposed to be
some sort of Christmas
present from France
to the United States.
‐Like what?
‐They're not telling anybody,
not even highly placed
mucky‐mucks like yours truly.
Hm, a Christmas present, huh?
Better than wine,
whatever it is.
Aww, poor Goemon.
Okay then, what the hell, kids?
It's Christmas, ya know?
What do you say
we lift that too?
Now, Goemon, you get
on an earlier flight
and head over to
the airport near...
♪
‐Captain, hello, I'm Inspector‐‐
‐You are the policeman.
‐Yes!
‐Monsieur, instructor,
comment allez‐vous?
Oh, merci, actually, it's‐‐
Ah, bonjour, mon ami.
Oui, oui.
Mwah!
Damn it, what
the hell's the matter
with these Frenchies anyway?
‐Huh?
‐Bonjour.
♪
Ah, yes, Bon Jovi.
Hello, what about me?
Uh, no thanks, gotta run, bye!
♪
(engine roaring)
(tires squealing)
So it seems that Lupin
never showed up.
Probably too hungover to
see straight after yesterday.
(laughing)
Yup, I sure got the
better of him this time.
(engine whining)
Makes you feel a little
like Santa Claus
flying this kind
of mission, you know?
Thank goodness for Zenigata.
If it wasn't
for him, that Lupin
would be playing
Grinch this Christmas.
You can say that again, mon ami.
Anyone here like coffee?
Oh, yeah, I'll take
whatever you're serving.
‐Uck!
‐Oh, Miss!
I'll be right back.
Let's get this over with.
Now he's flirting with me!
Ah, you really can't
blame the old guy.
He's just feeling
his oats today.
Yeah, well, as long as
that's all he feels.
Oh man, this fake
nose is so itchy.
Scratch it later,
we got work to do.
Ready; Here goes.
(hissing)
♪
(yawns)
(snoring)
♪
Perfect, look.
Go ahead, say it.
You're a genius, Lupin.
♪
Ready to rendezvous, keep your
eyes peeled for that truck.
How the hell are we
supposed to know it's him?
♪
Hm.
That's him there.
Where?
♪
‐See, his loincloth.
‐Oh!
Must be kinda breezy
under that robe.
♪
Okay, chop‐chop.
Yes, sir.
♪
Okay, easy now.
Pardon me, Inspector.
♪
(all gasp)
Lupin!
We did it, Fuji‐cakes!
Yes!
Sorry, Pops, but all's
fair in love and war.
♪
Hoo‐hoo!
I got the wine, I got the wine!
(laughing)
Lupin!
Hey, wait up!
♪
(yawns)
(shrieking)
Hm?
Wait a minute!
What the hell's this damn thing?
Dear Inspector,
in recognition
of your nearly
successful efforts,
here's some really cheap crap.
Ha!
You bastard!
‐Look out!
‐Ow!
Hey, what the hell?
♪
(gasping)
He got me, damn it!
Hm, what is it?
‐What's wrong?
‐It's Lupin, Lieutenant.
Lu‐‐Lupin?
But once again
you have won the day.
Well, actually, I, uh‐‐
Ah, unbelievable, you are twice
the hero, Inspector Sanitation.
Um, well, I mean, uh‐‐
And modest too!
♪
It's not yet Christmas morning
but here at the White House
the president is about
to open a very special gift:
the famous Napoleon Bordeaux
presented to him by
the government of France.
Oh, this'll be great, man,
I can't wait to see this.
Old Pops must have decided
extreme discretion's
the better part of valor.
Oh, God, it's just
like a trainwreck.
I want to look away
but I can't.
This is the best thing
on TV since My Three Samurai.
It's really quite
exciting, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
What the hell am I gonna
do if they find out?
Crap, crap, crap, crap!
I'd like to offer
a special toast
to the great and
generous people of France
with whom we share the
most precious gift of all:
liberty.
Merry Christmas to all!
‐Merry Christmas!
♪
(chuckles)
(sighs)
Here it comes.
Bravo!
It's France in a glass.
Exquisite!
This wine's excellent.
The finest I've ever tasted.
Hmm?
(laughing)
What a maroon!
Guy wouldn't know a Bordeaux
from a bordello!
Well, boys, shall
we toast our success
with the genuine article?
♪
Hmm, I'd say it has
a distinctive bouquet.
♪
Mm, do I detect
a hint of citrus?
Well, it's been
200 years in the making,
I say we just
take our sweet time
and savor it slowly.
Here's to us,
Merry Christmas!
‐Merry Christmas, everybody.
♪
(retching)
What in the hell is that?
It's called
200‐year‐old vinegar.
And a colossal waste
of time and energy.
It would appear that
the joke is on us.
So, is this like one of those
Gift of the Magi things,
'cause I hate that story.
Inspector, you know Lupin and
his gang better than anyone.
Why would they pass
up a chance to steal
a priceless historical artifact
in favor of a
crate full of dolls
intended as Christmas presents
for underprivileged children?
Uh, it's really baffling,
that's all I can say.
What'd he say?
(grunts)
What the hell?
Oh man!
(doll laughs)
Oh, I had one of these.
It's despicable,
a new low for Lupin,
stealing dollies
from poor children.
And on Christmas Eve,
for Heaven's sake!
Everyone makes mistakes, Pops.
At least we do
something about ours.
Huh?
Lupin, what!
Just look outside.
Hm, what?
Where?
What the hell are those things?
Snow‐‐no, wait, no clouds.
Then‐‐
♪
Hey, you know, this giving
thing feels pretty good.
Somebody stop me!
Merry Christmas to all
and to all a good heist!
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Quick, what's wrong
with this picture?
Have I finally driven
the poor guy nuts?
Not too far a drive
for old Pops.
But the truth is,
there's a crucial fact
he doesn't know
the truth about
and a total fantasy
he thinks is true but isn't.
Is that clear;
I didn't think so.
Well, trust me, it all
hangs together very nicely
in "I Left My Mind
in San Francisco."
Catch ya later.
♪