♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(singing in foreign language)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
So, uh, you wouldn't
be aware of any reason
the cops would be
following us now, would ya?
I've been keeping
my nose pretty clean.
Oh, yeah, well
it wasn't your nose
you exposed on
the beach last night.
And I suppose you've never taken
a leak on a damn beach, Lupin.
Still I‐‐
‐Huh?
‐What is it?
Jigen, what's the matter?
It's the apocalypse,
I swear it is!
Okay, I'll bite, is
it Pops at the wheel?
Mhm, but that's not all.
Um, well, judging from
your reaction I'd say
he's got a gorgeous babe
riding along with him.
Yup, you've got it.
And you're sure she's not a
collar or anything, right?
Hey, maybe she's one of those
inflatable deals, you know?
Nah, she's real
and if she's a collar,
it's for impersonating a cop!
(grunting)
You're right, it's got
to be some kinda cosmic joke!
Or a dream, right?
No dream, it's just
good ol' Fujiko.
But why is she riding up front
and dressed like a damn cop?
Give ya three guesses.
Hey, wait a minute, I
just figured it all out!
What do you want to
bet me it's the guy
who's the impersonator here,
she's just messing with my head.
Hey, Lupin, just wake up,
man, this is Fujiko
we're talking about here,
and that bitch would
sell us out for cab fare!
You're wrong!
Damn it all!
(grunting)
The poor bastard, he saw
you sitting next to me
and completely lost it, huh!
Just step on it, okay?
Don't worry about it,
he'll never get away!
♪
Look out!
(car horns honking)
Whoa, watch it!
♪
Lupin, you gotta pull
over, Puma's after you,
we're only trying
to help you, I swear!
Fujiko is telling you
the truth, Lupin!
She's only here 'cause she's
trying to save your lousy life!
And I'll be damned if I'm gonna
let Puma get to ya before I do!
(groaning)
‐Puma?
‐Lucky me!
Well, what are you gonna do?
Well, I can't pass up the
opportunity to meet him
face to face.
You really must be out
of your friggin' mind, man.
Hey, it's the chance
of a lifetime.
Yeah, because no one who meets
him lives to tell about it.
Very funny.
Oh, yeah, this guy's
a real scream.
Fugitive file number 1058.
Enrico Mortenegra, alias Puma.
Freelance assassin
operating mostly
in Central and South America,
specializing in
high risk targets
such as government officials,
intelligence operatives,
and drug lords.
No known partners
or affiliations.
No standard modus operandi.
Each hit is purposely unique
and designed in execution.
Current status: wanted for
capital crimes in 17 countries.
Current whereabouts: unknown.
And nobody knows
what he looks like.
A top flight
professional assassin.
Yeah, I guess I won't
be sleepin' real well,
till I get this sorted out.
If I do.
Don't even be joking about that!
I'm not sure that I was.
♪
(growling)
(typewriter keys clacking)
♪
(engine humming)
This is Zenigata,
we just passed point two,
have your guys ready to close
the box at point three.
You of all people shouldn't
underestimate him.
I'm not, I'm doing this all
by the book just to lull him
into a false sense of security.
God help us.
♪
Ah!
Oh, crap!
♪
(laughing)
Hey there, Pops,
how's it hanging?
No dialogue, see, there's no
time, just put out your hands
for now, Lupin, and
save the chat for later!
Come on, Lupin, please just
let him catch you this one time?
So, I guess this means we're
going to be giving up together?
It does?
Sure, that's the power of love.
‐I love you?
‐You see?
I'm not foolin' around!
'Cause this is all you need.
You're going to need a doctor!
Just shut up, you two,
both of you!
Quit confusing the issue,
Lupin, you're under arrest
and that's that!
‐(tittering)
‐What do you know?
There's no need
to thank us, Pops,
you know we're always willing
to lend a helping hand.
‐(snickering)
‐See ya!
(coughing)
Catch you later!
Hey, wait!
♪
(helicopter whirring)
(grunting)
Damn it!
Just can't catch a damn break!
I warned you about them!
Hey, Fujiko, that's a
totally hot look for you!
Ask Pops if you can keep
the outfit when you're done!
♪
(birds squawking)
So where would you hit
me from, if you were him?
I don't know, I'm not him.
That's why I said,
"if", now come on!
From that sailboat
out there in the inlet
or maybe the lighthouse.
Boat's unstable though.
And the lighthouse
is a bit too far.
Of course, at night
with the lights on in here,
a blind man could hit
you from Boston.
Hm.
♪
(gunshot)
The guy's not overhyped.
(rapid gunfire)
♪
(fuse hissing)
(explosion)
(panting)
♪
Why don't you just
come out, Puma,
let's talk about it, you know?
Nice meal, glass of wine,
we can work it out.
Yes, this hide and seek
is unworthy of us all.
Hey, garçon, some
more wine here‐‐whoa!
‐Damn it!
‐Son of a bitch!
That's why I told you
to stay out of sight, Lupin.
That's it, I'm sick of this‐‐
(gunfire)
(exclaiming)
Crap!
Well, I got to give
it to him though, I mean,
that's pretty damn good shooting
from that kind of distance,
you know what I mean, Goemon?
‐Whoa!
Lousy son of a bitch!
And the inscription on
the headstone should read:
"Here lies poor
Lupin, Fujiko‐less.
At least if she visits
he can look up her dress."
Thanks, I thought so.
That's it.
And one more thing,
where's the cemetery?
Good, thanks!
Who the hell was that?
Nobody, just a funeral home.
‐Who died?
‐Somebody's gonna die.
Yours truly.
What are you‐‐huh?
Look, guys, it's fate, when
you number's up, it's up,
and I don't want to go out
cowering in fear, okay?
Since when do you
just give up, Lupin?
Come on, don't you
go and patronize me.
I'm outmatched.
At least I get to
pick out my own coffin
this way, you know?
Hey, you're just
upset, come on, man.
I will go after him myself.
Damn it, just shut up,
just leave me alone!
This is what I want, hmmmph!
♪
It's my own damn life
and my death.
Hold it there!
I mean it now!
Come on, what are you‐‐
♪
(digital beeping)
Hm, a flying pun.
He bugged us?
It's totally embarrassing,
the guy overheard you arranging
your own funeral,
where's your pride, man?
Doesn't matter.
♪
Come on, Puma, take
me out, I'm ready!
♪
"Here lies poor
Lupin, Fujiko‐less"!
So you were listening to us.
Hey, come on out,
I wanna see your face!
You shouldn't,
everyone who sees it dies
that's the way it works.
Except whoever
ordered the hit on me.
I don't make any exceptions.
What are you saying?
What I said before, everyone
who sees my face dies!
Must cut into your
repeat business.
It's not about volume.
Where are you anyway?
(sinister laughing)
Huh?
Over here!
Wrong way!
♪
(gunfire)
(screaming)
(splash)
They always want
to see the face.
(laughing)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪♪
‐Lupin, hey!
Lupin!
♪
He's been shot!
Lupin!
Holy crap, just look
what he did to him!
♪
There is nothing you could
have done, his internal organs
were just riddled with bullets.
Fix him up, doc,
you gotta fix him, okay?
I'm afraid it's
too late for that.
Am I, uh...
Who the hell are you?
Mr. Lupin I believe called me.
I'm delivering
the item he requested.
Can you sign for it?
(sobbing)
Puma, show your face,
you son of a bitch!
Where are you?
♪
(crying)
(gunshots)
♪
(grunting)
(sobbing)
♪
(police sirens)
Chief, fill me in,
what do you got here?
Well, sir, we got a DOA,
and we got his partners here
waiting to be interrogated.
Hold on, are you
saying Lupin's deceased?
You think I was born
yesterday or something, huh?
The only dummy around
here is the DOA!
♪
Huh, the old coffin
gambit, Lupin?
Come on, you big con artist.
Alright, open her up!
♪
‐Yeah, that's our guy!
‐No!
Hey, Lupin, get up, come on!
Hey, Lupin,
cut it out, will you!
Come on, I'm not kidding
Lupin, this isn't funny!
Damn it, Lupin‐‐
Inspector, please, maybe you
should control yourself?
You can't really be dead, I
never told you this before,
but I love you!
What am I going
to do without you?
You were my whole
reason to live!
How could you do this to me,
I hate you‐‐no I don't!
I don't, I'm sorry!
(sobbing)
Please don't leave me, Lupin.
♪
‐It's alright, Inspector‐‐
‐No!
(gunshot)
Puma, I'll get you,
you son of a bitch!
Hey, get back here, will someone
please get after that maniac
before he shoots up
half the damn city!
Hey, wait, I only‐‐
‐Ow.
‐Yo, Pops.
"Yo" yourself, you damn
bastard, I oughta‐‐
(growling)
‐I oughta‐‐
‐What the‐‐
What the hell kind of
partners are you anyway?
How could you just let
him go and die like that?
(growling)
♪
(crying)
(blubbering)
♪
We'll be together soon.
(tires squealing)
♪
Tiger, this is Puma, come in.
Tiger, here!
‐He's dead.
‐Are you sure?
The guy's maggot bait now.
Alright, I'll have the
money here, 10 tonight,
be good to finally
meet you face to face.
Very good, the pleasure
will be all mine.
Cheerio!
(sighs)
"Here lies poor Lupin,
Fujiko‐less.
At least if she visits
he can look up her dress."
It should be wearing
off anytime now.
And you're sure there's no
chance he could have suffocated?
A body in this kind
of suspended animation
requires very little oxygen.
(blows out air)
You better be right about that.
(chuckling)
(gunshots)
♪
(gasps)
Mommy.
What a nap!
Are you alright?
You tell me.
Muah‐‐
Hey, what the hell kind
of greeting is that?
I mean, especially after
that touching tribute
that I gave you on my headstone.
Yeah, real romantic.
Hey, that's just crass!
Don't fool with me young
whippersnapper, I'm in no mood!
Now you get out
of here right now,
or this time I'll
bury you for real!
(grunts)
(footsteps)
Come on, they're moving you
to maximum security.
(tires squealing)
By the way, I've got
some things of yours.
This is a set up.
What's the matter with you guys?
Don't you get it?
Yup, I'm alive and kickin'.
‐Pretty neat, huh?
‐You friggin' bastard!
You know what you
put us through?
Sometimes you gotta
even fool your friends
to fool your enemies.
Lupin, I'm sorry.
Whoa, don't do that, at least
wait until after we get Puma!
How are you planning
on that one, Lupin?
Remember a few days ago, when
he took his first shot at me,
and he blew up the boat when
Goemon came after him?
Well, in the middle of all
the chaos I noticed something.
There was something else
in the water that night,
another smaller boat, slipping
off into the darkness.
I kept it in sight.
And lo and behold, it tied up
next to another boat out there.
♪
(water lapping)
Go ahead, count it if you like.
Not necessary.
How's that?
Think about it.
Tell me what did he look like
when you killed him, huh?
Just like...that!
(groaning)
♪
(footsteps)
‐What the...
‐Poor sucker
thought he was paying me
back for beating him
out of that Vienna
job years ago.
Funny thing about
karma though, you know?
That voice!
You see, Puma, somehow it always
seems to hit you from behind.
What, is that Lupin?
Not me, though.
(gunshot)
♪
(sizzling)
I wanted to see that face.
(grunting)
Just once, before I say
hasta la bye‐bye.
(explosion)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪♪
Some crap about a stolen
crown in the next one,
but it's just an excuse
for whole lot of ugly guys
to do a whole lot of
really pretty fighting.
Guns, sticks, knives,
one of 'em's even got
a deadlier forefinger
than my second grade teacher.
Yow, get him, Goemon!
Anyway, join us next time
for "A Rumble Royale,"
catch ya later!
♪