♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(shattering)
(singing in foreign language)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪♪
♪
(indistinct chattering)
(laughing)
Alakazam.
Hmm.
♪
(laughing)
Huh?
♪
Hmm!
Well, she is very good,
you got to admit.
Oh, what's the big deal?
♪
(indistinct chattering)
Yeah!
You could mix
paint with that.
Mm‐mm.
Hey!
♪
Woo‐hoo, yeah!
(laughing)
♪
Shake it!
Shake your booty!
Hmm?
♪
Hmm.
Mm?
♪
(giggling)
Hello and goodbye.
(grunting)
Quickly!
♪
Hey, let me go, hey,
watch your hands!
Stop it!
Hey, what the
hell's going on?
Ooh, oh, damn it!
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
Hey!
Do you have any idea
where Lupin went?
Huh, where did Lupin go?
(honking)
♪
Yo!
Lupin!
♪
(tapping of typewriter keys)
(groaning)
It's a smoother ride in a
belly dancer's back pocket!
Hey, let me out!
I'm afraid I can't help you.
Don't play games
with me, you bossy‐‐
What the‐‐Pops!
Lupin, let me out of here!
I can't, hey!
Lupin, you're under arrest!
You're out of your mind.
(grunting)
♪
Ooh!
Argh, you get‐‐
Hey, take it easy, Pops,
I didn't do it, I'm innocent!
Oh, yeah, you're innocent?
Well, then, tell me,
who the hell‐‐
On your feet.
The commander is waiting.
Who?
♪
Welcome, recruits.
(laughing)
Uh, thanks, I guess, but did
you just say "recruits"?
Yes.
I think there's
been a mistake.
We don't even live
in this place.
This is not a problem.
You don't need
to be a citizen
to serve in our armed forces.
I'm not serving in
anybody's damn army.
I'm Inspector Zenigata
from Interpol.
Now you listen to me!
I want to speak to
your superior now!
The commander
has no superiors.
Yes, no man is
superior to the people,
except those like me
who are the people.
And this people's army
that you command,
it isn't the real army?
Ours is the real army because
it is the righteous fist
of oppressed people
of this country.
It is an honor to fight
for such a glorious cause.
Gee, lucky me.
♪
Listen, Commander, I really
wish you all the best
with this big
bloodbath of yours,
but, unfortunately, I'm not
going to be sticking around.
Ah, I understand.
Well, it's up to you.
But I should warn you,
the only way out of here
is up those steps over there.
♪
(clanking)
Help me, ah!
Help, help me, please!
I really don't want to die!
Help me, please!
Please, stop!
I'm too young to die
and too handsome
and charming and...
♪
Okay, if you have to
go, you have to go.
I totally respect that.
And you're sure that's
the only, only way?
There's no, like,
camel taxi or anything?
I'm so glad you
decided to fight
for the revolution after all.
You start basic
training this afternoon.
Hey, hey, wait a minute!
There's no way in hell I'm
gonna bunk with this guy.
Goes double for me!
Such petty rivalries
are nothing but
a bourgeois luxury
which a true
revolutionary must abandon.
Plus, I hate you.
Huh?
Damn, I haven't felt
so trapped and hopeless
since the last time
I went to Disneyland.
But at least when
I was at Disneyland,
nobody ever forced me to
share a teacup with Goofy.
You'll be sharing
a cell with rats
when I get you back to Japan!
Yeah, well, be
that as it may,
it'll be the land of
the setting sun for you
if you stick around
here and end up
in the middle of some
revolutionary uprising.
But what about
my poor mother?
And that's why we've
gotta break out of here.
What, you mean
escape from here?
Shh!
Quiet, what is the
matter with you?
It's a crime to escape.
I guess it's goodbye then.
You're not going anywhere!
I got you right in
the palm of my hand
and I'm not letting‐‐
No wonder you
never caught me.
(sighing)
(laughing)
Rise!
Get up!
Fall in!
♪
Some new volunteers
have just arrived.
Hmm, wait.
Huh, I don't see him.
There's no way he could've‐‐
Now, hmm.
Looks like we're
one private short.
Any idea where your
friend could be?
‐Kill me!
‐Huh?
I wanna die!
Come on, please!
Somebody just cut the rope.
Come on, do it!
Just do it!
Kill me!
Come on!
♪
Has he lost his head?
You some kind of crazy guy?
Hello, only a crazy
person would want
to stay in a place like this.
Quiet, you can die in
battle like everybody else!
You're all gonna die!
‐Ya hear that?
‐Shut up!
That's not true.
Save yourself!
This guys is nuts!
(grunting)
Ha!
♪
Now...
If any one of you
moves a muscle,
your commander's gonna
be wearing his hat
around his neck.
Uh, uh...
Pops, grab their guns!
Come on!
They know you're with me now!
You've got no choice!
You schmuck!
That's it!
♪
(laughing)
If you really want my head,
you can have it,
my crazy friend,
but your triumph
will be brief.
Look around you.
(laughing)
You see?
The revolution's a
serpent with many heads.
Sooner or later, it
bites you in the ass.
(laughing)
♪
(sighing)
So, what will it
be, my friend?
Death now or death later?
♪
Damn it.
All right, you in the hat.
Uh, Pops, that's you.
Down!
‐Now you.
‐Oh, no, really,
that's not...
All right, get up.
Now take these
troublemakers to tiger cage
and throw away the damn key!
Yes, sir, come on!
Okay, this is bad.
♪
This is very bad.
I never thought I'd live
to hear myself say this,
but I'd actually
rather be in Disneyland.
Oh, Mommy.
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(rustling)
Oh!
It's kicking up the sand!
We gotta get out
of this place.
This whole thing
is your fault!
You know, Pops,
just blaming me
isn't going to help us
out very much here.
Hey, Sparky, you awake?
Hello, yoo‐hoo, over here!
Hey, shut up!
People are trying to sleep!
Hey, have you ever
thought about braiding
those nose hairs of yours?
You thirsty in there?
(spitting)
Okay, Pops, now
hold on real tight.
Help, somebody!
Hey, people are sleeping.
Oh!
Okay, Pops,
let's go, come on!
No, you're gonna
get us killed!
I hate to clue ya,
but these guys
don't believe in
rehabilitation.
Now come on!
(grunting)
Okay, you ready?
One, two, three.
♪
Hey, not bad, Pops.
Come on.
Damn it, find them!
There they are!
(shouting)
♪
(grunting)
‐Run!
‐Go and get
the damn horses ready,
they're getting away!
♪
(heavy breathing)
‐Hot.
‐No kidding.
♪
Oh, wow, Pops, look.
Civilization.
Hmm?
They'll have water!
And girls and stuff!
Huh?
Damn it, they're here.
What, who?
There they are.
Shoot them on sight.
The same for any
villagers they talk to.
Ya!
(panting)
♪
Here!
‐Crap.
‐You said it, Pops.
What do we do,
what do we do?
They're gonna be
here any second now.
‐Halt!
‐Not here, sir.
Let's go, hurry!
♪
(grunting)
(chicken clucking)
♪
No way, I'm not
some common criminal.
Well, I'm an
uncommon criminal,
and it's a damn good thing
for you that I am too, Pops.
Now let me‐‐
I can't just ignore a
robbery when I see one.
Shut your eyes then.
Justice is blind, right?
Yeah.
I can't see a damn thing.
That's the spirit.
‐What the...
‐Huh?
Uh, hi there.
Hey, got a donkey
thief down here!
(shouting)
Wait, wait.
This guy is a thief.
But don't worry
because I'm a policeman!
But we're chained
at the neck!
Come on, Pops, we've
got to get out of here.
These guys aren't
stupid, ya know?
(shouting)
♪
(grunting)
This whole damn
thing is your fault!
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, I just got another idea.
Huh?
No, uh‐uh, no way.
(growling)
♪
Hello.
Hello!
‐Wait.
‐Damn it.
Is that lovely
creature yours?
‐Yes, she is.
‐Ah, well,
you wouldn't be willing
to part with her now,
would you, my friend?
Here, look, I'll
give you my donkey
and a quart of pickled
goat testicles, huh?
Uh, well, that's, uh...
They are of the
very highest quality.
Yeah, well, so are mine!
What in the‐‐
You bastard.
Ah!
I am going to make a real
woman out of you, you phony!
Ah!
Come back here!
You!
Ah!
(sighing)
I want a divorce.
♪
Turn left up there
and we're home free.
♪
What do we do now?
Just keep going.
It'll look suspicious
if we turn back.
♪
Wait a minute.
(chuckling)
Yes, this one's
got meat on her.
Oh, not again.
What would I have
to pay for her?
Trust me, you don't want her.
Why not?
Uh, well, I mean,
it's just, you know,
I love her so much.
(crying)
All right, get going.
Thank you, what a nice man.
(chuckling)
Huh?
(growling)
Ah!
Oh, Mommy!
It's them!
(shouting)
♪
(panting)
It is too unstable.
(grunting)
Go around!
There's a train coming!
I'll race ya down there!
Get this damn chain off us!
Uh, run that last
part by me again?
We can use the wheels
of the train to cut it.
Hey, good thinking.
Not that this hasn't been
a deeply satisfying bonding
experience or anything.
Here it comes.
Come on!
(grunting)
(train chuffing)
Ah, man, please,
come on, hurry!
(whistle blowing)
(train chuffing)
That's it!
Okay, Pops, now you get
ready to grab this thing.
‐But when?
‐Now!
Here!
(grunting)
Fire, fire!
Damn, look out!
♪
Lupin, I can't!
I'm not gonna make it!
You go!
Give me your hand,
Pops, come on!
(whimpering)
Lupin!
Pops!
♪
(grunting)
Come on!
♪
Uh!
Tell me your weaselly
friend is on his way to.
Look, I told you before,
he's not my friend!
I'm a cop and that's it, hmm!
Well, whatever you do
know, we'll find out.
‐Hey, Pops!
‐Hmm?
Hmm?
♪
All right now, in the
name of the revolution,
don't miss him this time!
♪
What the hell is
that maniac doing?
Pops!
Better clear out of there!
Now!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Move it, move it, move it!
♪
(shouting)
(grunting)
(exploding)
(shouting)
(fire crackling)
♪
Now don't get any ideas.
I'm taking you
straight to jail.
You understand?
‐Ya got it?
‐Hey, uh, Pops?
‐What?
‐Uh, well,
I really gotta go.
Too bad!
Ah, come on, you're
just being mean.
I'll be real quick, okay?
Come on!
Thanks!
Make it snappy!
Hey, what the hell's
taking so long?
Huh?
What the‐‐
(gasping and laughing)
Sorry about that!
But I told ya, I really,
really had to go!
Woo‐hoo, see ya!
You bastard!
Get back here!
Damn it, Lupin!
Bye, can't catch me!
I'm gonna get you!
Get back here!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
They're blonde, they're
Nordic, they're frisky.
They're Anita and Latica,
Swedish twins locked in
a catfight to the finish
over a fortune in
hidden Viking booty.
But don't worry, no booty
stays hidden very long
when I'm on the case.
Woo‐hoo, I feel like I died
and went to Valhalla.
Catch ya next time
in "Twins Pique."
♪