♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(singing in foreign language)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(birds squawking)
♪
This is the area.
So what does 350,000
karats come to?
Well, it all comes
down to the quality,
but I'd say about, um‐‐
let's see now, first
you'd have to divide the‐‐
‐About $900 million.
‐Exactly!
But our best shot‐‐
really our only shot‐‐
is to snatch them on their
way to this research center
near San Jose.
♪
Once they're inside,
they're loaded onto a missile
for delivery to Puerto
Rico, and that's it.
It's a real short flight,
and the security
on the Puerto Rico end
is American military.
Huh, and how long does
it take from San Jose
to arrive at the
research center?
A couple of hours, you think?
Give or take.
‐Well?
‐Guys?
$900 million in
cool diamonds, man.
It's a no‐brainer.
‐Uh‐huh.
‐Agreed.
‐That settles it.
‐Let's do it.
Hear, hear!
(clacking)
♪
(birds squawking)
Uh, yes, who is it?
Zenigata from Interpol.
I'm looking for the
office of the commissioner?
Well, you've found
it, Mr. Benihana.
Francisco Tarombo,
pleased to meet you.
That's your new assignment
right over there,
Inspector Benihana.
Uh, excuse me, Commissioner,
but it's Zenigata.
My sincerest apologies,
Mr. Benihana!
Oh, you did it again.
It's Zenigata‐‐Zen‐i‐gat‐a.
Ben‐i‐han‐a.
No, no, it's Benihana!
Uh‐‐I mean‐‐
Anyway, take a look
at these, Inspector.
Excellent work,
wouldn't you say?
‐Why it's amazing!
‐Think so?
‐Yes.
‐Good!
To maximize the security, you
and I are the only individuals
who will be privy
to this operation.
Uh‐huh.
The importance of this mission
to the people of this
country is enormous.
We're counting on
you, Mr. Benihana.
Uh, yeah.
♪
They're just leaving
police headquarters.
How's everything over there?
Everything's in place.
‐What about Lupin?
‐He got in all right,
as far as I know.
♪
(humming)
Yeah, that's them.
♪
Okay, ready?
On three.
♪
One...
Two...
Three!
(explosion)
(yelling)
(splashing)
Oh, my.
Back up‐‐back up now!
(explosion)
Oh, yeah!
That's it, man!
♪
They've cut us off
in front and behind.
♪
Hmm.
The fuel tank‐‐aim
for the fuel tank!
♪
Stuffy.
That's them!
Please, allow me.
Shoot it down!
Someone!
(guns firing)
♪
There.
Hey, look over there,
man, he's got it.
♪
What the hell's he doing?
(chuckling)
Gotta fly!
(growling)
Ahh!
Phew!
♪
Hey, I want
headquarters right away.
And tell 'em it's an emergency!
At once!
Thanks for all your
help, you big dummy.
♪
And now, the moment
you've all been waiting for.
Ah!
Hey there, Sorry to
disappoint you, Lupin!
You're under arrest, my friend!
Hold on, now, wait a minute.
Weren't you in the car?
That was just an
inflatable dummy.
Tarombo and I cooked the
whole thing up together.
Clever, huh?
♪
So then the diamonds
weren't ever on board?
Of course not.
They were sent to the research
center in an unmarked car.
I got ya!
Yah!
Shall we?
Well, see you later, Pops!
Take care!
(grumbling)
Get back here!
♪
I can't believe it!
When did he get so crafty?
Well, if they're at that
research center, it's all over.
Are you kidding,
it isn't over yet.
‐Huh?
‐Hmm?
If we quit now, it'll look bad.
Couldn't hold our
heads up in bad society.
Mhm.
Well, hmm, I guess
if you're saying
you actually have an idea.
My head's full of ideas,
that's why I'm crazy.
Come here, listen up.
♪
Lupin, I'm in love!
You are?
I‐‐
With the idea, but
you're kinda cute also.
(tires screeching)
(growling)
Hi, Chief, see you got the
tiger with you again today.
My, how impressively
observant of you.
(chickens clucking)
(growling and clucking)
(whistling)
Oh, so you decided
to take a little
unscheduled snack
break, did you?
You're getting as bad
as the rest of the staff,
and don't slouch like that!
Please stand still.
Scanning for
unauthorized materials.
(humming)
Thank you.
Please state
today's code phrase.
I want my daddy and mommy.
I'm scared, and
I want to go home!
Voice print and
code phrase confirmed.
Please insert I. D. card.
♪
‐Little further.
‐I got it, I got it.
Looks good.
♪
Well, the diamonds are safe
and nothing else matters.
Lupin's out of the picture.
You never know with Lupin.
The missile travels
at mach five over water.
It'll be in Puerto
Rico in seconds.
Even Lupin can't
snatch it out of the sky.
‐Well, can he?
‐Uhhh.
Of course not.
Come on, now, this isn't some
Hollywood fantasy, Benihana!
♪
We have received a flight path.
Looks like there's some
islands along the route.
Right here.
I can figure out
when it'll pass over
by calculating
everything backwards
once we know when
it's gonna launch.
I have it flying at just
50 meters about sea level
to avoid any radar detection.
Mhm.
♪
Amazing what they can
do with microtechnology.
(phone ringing)
Yeah, what is it?
Chief, we got
a real problem here.
That cat you brought
in with you this morning
isn't Shishimaru.
All right, but listen‐‐
keep this under
your hat, you hear?
This could be very sensitive.
I'll take it from here.
Mhm.
(chuckling)
Well, that was close.
Now how about those
clothes of yours?
(clacking)
What?
♪
Well, good morning,
Chief, and how are you?
Uh, good‐‐good morning.
Busy day today, sir.
Conference call with
General Brunner's group at 9:30,
and then an
engineering department
budget meeting at 11:00,
and then you have
lunch with a Bill Moran
from Green Bomzo and‐‐
are you all right, sir?
Yes, of course, why?
‐Uhh.
‐Just cancel everything!
‐But sir!
‐You heard me.
Inform all departments
that we're launching
that missile today.
Go on, now, get
to it right away!
Yes, sir, sorry, sir.
Now get to it!
(sighing)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(laughing)
Well, if simplicity's
the soul of beauty,
then this one's a masterpiece!
All we need now is
now is the launch time.
All right, so tell me, what
time's the launch set for?
Everything's good
to go at 10 o'clock.
Uh‐huh‐‐hmm.
♪
(chuckling)
I think you're
gonna wanna change
that launch time, Commissioner.
Why?
Uhhh.
'Cause this one just heard
everything, and she's a spy!
She's Lupin's main squeeze!
Probably got some sort
of transmitter on her!
Lupin's hearing
this whole thing!
Come on, where is it?
‐Hey, what are you doing?
‐Quiet, you!
A‐ha, see?
What'd I tell ya?
Wait, don't!
(static)
That's pretty good, Pops.
I underestimated you.
♪
Hey, Security!
Get this one
locked up right away!
Yes, sir, coming, sir!
All right, then.
‐We'll reset the launch for‐‐
‐Hey, hold it!
Don't say anything
out loud, Commissioner.
He just might have the
whole damn facility wired,
so that means ex‐nay
on the alking‐tay.
Wow, so how about
something like this here?
Mhm, that's it.
Good, now we're back on track.
Thank you!
(engine rumbling)
‐Fuel check.
‐Checking fuel!
♪
At least they didn't find this,
but it's no use to me in here.
I gotta figure out
a way to get it back
into that control room.
Hmm.
♪
Hmm, I don't like it.
This doesn't make sense.
I'm sure that
something's gone wrong.
(grunting)
(beeping)
Hmm.
Well, well, I see they've
encrypted all the communication
about a new launch time.
(buzzing)
Huh?
Pardon the interruption, Chief,
but there's been a breach!
What kind of breach?
A spy working for Lupin.
By the way, where's Shishimaru?
Well, he must've, uh, uh‐‐
who is this man?
I'm Zenigata from Interpol
here as a special
security consultant,
and I have a good
hunch that Lupin himself
is somewhere
inside the building!
Hey, hey, hey!
Stop it, will ya?
Inspector Benihana, stop it!
But you see, he's a
master of disguise, sir,
‐I mean, I just‐‐
‐But this is the Chief
of the Research Center!
No one is above suspicion.
That's the Interpol credo.
Hmm.
Interesting.
If no one is above suspicion,
then what about you yourself?
‐Myself?
‐Yes, just to be consistent.
♪
Very well, then, I'm
satisfied, Mr. Benihana, is it?
Hmm?
Inspector, I'd like you to
check out Mr. Tarombo now.
Hmm‐‐oh, no, sir!
That really won't be necessary.
Oh, do you feel that
you're above suspicion?
Of course not, no!
I mean‐‐well, let me just‐‐
(laughing)
I didn't hurt you,
did I, Inspector?
(groaning)
(crying)
Now, it's time to rescue Fujiko.
♪
Man, that smarts.
Even my mother hasn't
tweaked it that hard
in a real long time.
♪
‐I'm here to see the prisoner.
‐Yes, sir!
♪
‐Huh?
‐Uhh.
(grunting)
♪
Ah.
Hey, Fujiko!
You might as well tell me.
I know he's in here somewhere!
He got discouraged
and went back to Europe.
Oh, yeah?
Do you really think
I'm some kind of moron?
I know this guy!
He doesn't get
discouraged, the bastard!
Now come on, out with it!
(roaring)
Huh?
So he's back, is he?
I'll bet it's him.
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
He came back for me.
All right, well‐‐
Don't go, darling.
Oh, Pops, come on,
can't you tell?
When a girl's just teasing you?
That's all I'm doing.
You're so adorable, oh!
How could I deny a
man like you anything?
It's simply impossible!
So, uh‐‐
Oh, just like a big,
squishy ball of putty
in your strong, manly hands.
I've been having the
naughtiest dreams about you,
you know that?
And you know what I'm
doing to you in those dreams?
This!
(laughing)
Why, you little‐‐
Oh, I won't say it.
Dimmit all!
‐Sorry, did that hurt?
You men are all
the same, I mean,
do any of you even own a mirror?
Now what the hell's
that supposed to mean?
A mirror‐‐you see, that's‐‐
hey, it's almost time now!
Hey, all clear, Tiger.
(growling)
♪
Hey!
Come on, stop it,
cut it out, Lupin.
There's plenty of
time for this later.
‐Quit clowning around.
‐Right.
Okay, come on, let's go.
(indistinct talking)
Come on!
You guys, hurry up, will ya?
If we don't have
the damn launch time,
how the hell are we
supposed to do this thing?
Sixty seconds!
All systems go.
Excuse me, sir,
I'm still convinced
that Lupin's somewhere
here on the premises.
Can't we reset this
thing again to be safe?
Hmm?
Will you please let me
do my damn job, Benihana?
Leave me alone!
Can't you see there's less
than a minute left till launch?
I'm under a lot of
stress here, Inspector.
Are you trying to help this
effort or sabotage it, huh?
Uh, well, it's just that I‐‐
I'm extraordinarily
busy in here!
Now, go away!
Well, did you catch it?
Eleven hundred
hours, 30 minutes.
(creaking)
Coming on 30
seconds to ignition.
Please initiate final countdown.
Okay, we're at 29, 28‐‐
Anyone ever tell you you're
a rotten conversationalist?
(buzzing)
Here we go.
Jigen, come in, it's Lupin!
You guys ready?
‐Here it comes.
‐Oh, yeah!
Where the friggin' hell were ya?
No time for that!
I ran the calculations!
Intercept time is
11:30 and 24.622 seconds!
Boohoo!
T‐minus 14, 13, 12, 11, 10,
nine, eight, seven, six, five...
Good luck, and
don't screw it up.
...two, one, zero.
Ignition.
(explosion)
Launch completed successfully.
Initiating
trajectory adjustment.
Trajectory adjustment complete.
Holding at 50 meters.
(water dripping)
Well, that's that.
She dares me to look
in the mirror, huh?
I don't know, I look
just as good as any guy.
♪
Why, that little‐‐
All right now, baby,
keep your fingers crossed.
Okay, you ready?
When have I not been prepared?
♪
Go!
(grunting)
(clattering)
Yeah, got it!
♪
(chuckling)
Sir, something's wrong.
We just lost all contact
with the missile!
No, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No‐‐huh?
It's all my fault.
They planted this
device on me somehow
when I wasn't looking, I guess.
♪
Oh, I'm just like a big,
squishy ball of putty
in your strong, manly hands.
♪
(yelling)
(laughing)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Ah, yes, it's a
tale as old as time.
You got your beauty
and your beast.
No, wait, there he is.
So what does that make me?
I'm the schmuck who
gets to drag his ass
to the ends of
the frickin' Earth
to do battle with the beast,
'cause I was set
up by the beauty
who turns out to
be a conniving bitch!
Catch ya next time
in Heroes and Vixens.
♪