♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
(glass breaks)
(singing in Japanese)
♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
(singing in Japanese)
♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
(elephant trumpeting)
(wings flapping)
♪
The National Office
of Ecotourism welcomes you,
and we hope you thoroughly
enjoy your stay here
in the world's largest
wild animal refuge.
That's her shaking hands.
Elsa Lockhound.
And that hood
ornament there?
That's the black pearl?
Mm‐hmm.
I'm so pleased you
decided to come.
It's all right,
but I still can't believe
we came all the way
to Africa for it.
‐Me neither.
‐Huh?
Of all the gin joints
in the world, right?
Huh?
Fujiko!
What, uh, brings you here?
Look, Lupin, neither
one of us came here
to bag a rhino,
so let's just cut
the cute stuff.
We both know perfectly
well why we're here,
but unfortunately,
someone else does too.
See?
Huh?
Oh, crap.
He wrote her to volunteer
his services.
Why in the world
would he ever do that?
Hey, Zenigata may be
a damn fool, Lupin,
but he's really not
a complete idiot, you know?
Mmm.
Hi!
Everything all right?
So, what do you say,
we all work together
on this one, Fujicakes?
Could be sort of fun,
don't you think?
Sure, have you got
a game plan then?
Well, I was thinking
you and I could confab
about it up in my room.
‐Huh?
(growling)
(shrieking)
Holy guacamole!
♪
(growling)
Hey, King Kong.
This is a private party.
(groans)
All right, stick 'em up.
(roars)
(whimpers)
♪
Mrs. Lockhound, I...
(groans)
Huh?
You know, I always
kinda hoped old Pops
would someday
find his soul mate.
Cut it out, let me go!
What are you trying to‐‐whoa!
Hey, look out.
I'm not interested, all right?
(ape grunts)
♪
Nothing is ever
easy for me.
(roars)
(typewriter keys clicking)
♪
(guests shrieking)
Jigen, come on,
they're getting away.
(grunts)
I can't believe this.
(Fujiko chuckles)
♪
Huh?
That gorilla's not
actually driving, is he?
♪
(tires screech)
Uh, Lupin, aren't we
supposed to be chasing them?
Huh?
You think they're
mocking us?
This is embarrassing.
All right, hold on.
(tires screech)
Huh?
♪
Hmm.
(grunting)
Well!
That's pretty good
driving for a monkey.
Hey, come on, man.
I'm starting to get
genus envy here, sheesh.
Hey, buddy,
I said for a monkey.
Yeah, yeah.
God, you're sensitive.
♪
‐Huh?
‐What the hell?
They were right here.
Well, if they can drive,
maybe they can fly.
You've seen the
Wizard of Oz
too many damn times.
♪
All right, so what's
your theory then, huh?
♪
Damn it all!
This just burns my butt.
Gorillas, for God's sake.
Don't take it so hard.
They're supposed to be
very intelligent, you know?
Compared to other
animals, Jigen.
They're supposed to be smart
compared to other
animals, not to me.
Hey, you know,
I've got a good idea.
Yeah, really, what?
I think we should go ahead
and throw another party.
What?
What do you mean
another party?
You know, just like
the one the other night,
except this time
spread the word
that I'll be there
wearing a bunch
of expensive jewelry.
I'll bet you anything
they'll show up.
What do you think?
Brilliant!
I'm not what you call
a party animal,
so count me out of this.
He's right.
Have either of you two
ever seen Goemon
try to dance?
It's frightening.
Hey, you just stole the
Tear of Venus, didn't you?
Uh, well, yeah.
Good, I'll wear that.
Uh...
And that gold, big necklace
that vanished in London
a couple of weeks ago.
And say, wasn't that
Cartier bracelet job
your work?
I don't know
what you could mean,
but be my guest.
In fact, there's a whole
bunch of other stuff
you might wanna
take a look at.
(clears throat)
There's no need
to brag, Lupin.
Let's head back
to the hotel
and get started.
♪
Well, we're all set.
Let's do it.
Any sign of Fujiko?
Not yet.
Thanks for waiting.
Oh, mommy, look at you!
(Lupin purrs)
I take it you approve.
You look like an angel
or a goddess or something.
Uh‐oh.
So, who in the hell put
Pops on the guest list?
Oh, not him.
Look, Lupin, I know this
is a delicate subject,
but, well, I hope you
know that's basically
our 401k she's
wearing tonight.
Don't worry about it, Jigen.
All will be well.
Now, let's party!
(chuckles)
(humming)
Lord Popinloo.
Zenigata, sir, Interpol.
Ah, to what do
I owe this honor?
Well, you see,
your Lordship,
I heard about
this affair,
and I'm volunteering
my services to you,
for security purposes, that is.
Completely free
of charge, sir.
How very kind of you.
My pleasure.
‐Um...
‐Uh...
Yes, sir.
They say you're
dating a gorilla,
which is perfectly
fine with me,
but it might cause
a stir if she were
to attend this evening.
Uh, well, you see,
that was, uh...
Stop that!
You see, your Lordship,
that was a misunderstanding.
I'm a very simple man.
It's all about
Lupin for me.
Inspector Zenigata,
your personal life
is of absolutely
no concern to me.
Do you follow me, sir?
Well...
Any arrangement that you
have with this Mr. Lupin
regarding the gorilla
is your affair, Inspector.
I merely ask that you not
flaunt your proclivities
in front of my guests,
if that's all right.
Good heavens.
Damn it, if this gets
back to Interpol,
I'll be pulling
parking meter duty
in friggin' Bombay!
♪
‐Hmm?
‐Jigen, over here.
So, you decided
to help out, huh?
I'd love to see
Lupin learn a lesson.
But certainly not with
a fortune that's partially mine.
Well, if those monkeys
show up again,
I'm ready for 'em.
Don't worry.
Well, see you.
Huh?
Hey, Goemon, hold it!
That's just it, I can't.
He is human.
Hmm, all right, good.
We got every
entry point covered.
Watch your backs there.
(wheels squeaking)
Hold it, hold it!
What is this?
It's something
for the party.
Lady Popinloo ordered it.
Huh?
Hmm.
Okay.
♪
Hmm.
Now, ladies and gentlemen,
a gift to the
nation's children
from Lord and Lady Popinloo.
(applause)
It is a gift of
unprecedented largesse.
In fact, nothing even
close to this in scale
has ever been attempted
in this country.
Yes, well, anything for
the little ones, naturally.
Why didn't you mention it?
Trust me.
This is gonna be great.
Ah, perhaps his Lordship
would now be so kind as to...
(growls)
(shrieking)
I got this one.
♪
(growling)
Gotta get out of here, I‐‐
Lupin, help!
(grunting)
Whoa!
♪
Lupin, where are you, help!
Hold it!
You're all under arrest!
Easy now, big fella.
Just hold it right there.
(grunts)
Help, somebody help me.
Please!
Wait, it's too risky.
Okay, let's go.
♪
That's Jigen and Goemon.
That means Lupin!
All right, go get
me that damn jeep!
Yes, sir.
♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
So, Jigen, what
happened to Lupin?
I don't know, I lost him
in the crowd back there.
Huh?
Son of a bitch.
Hey, Lupin!
Pull over!
Yeah.
That's gonna happen.
♪
Hmm.
If you can't drive
this thing, I will!
♪
Hey, where's Lupin, huh?
No idea, shouldn't you be
after those gorillas, though?
Hey, look!
If you want, we can help
you cut 'em off up ahead.
Good.
(tires screech)
♪
(grunting)
All right!
With kamikaze spirit!
♪
(groaning)
(crash)
Ow.
Damn it.
I really hate
those friggin' monkeys.
(engine chugging)
(mechanical whirring)
♪
‐What's that?
‐Huh?
Holy crap!
‐Hello!
Jeez, man.
What the hell
happened to you?
You mean after I found out
some bastard stole my car?
Well...
this is where we
lost those apes before,
so I thought
I'd check it out.
Yeah, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on!
(groaning)
(crash)
Ow.
Jeeps aren't supposed
to roll over so easy.
Hey, Lupin,
you're under arrest.
Whatever you say.
Hey!
♪
Jigen, step on
the damn gas, will you?
I'd love to,
but we're on empty, pal.
Oh, no.
Crap.
Well, it is a lovely
night for parking.
No offense, but
I'd prefer a gorilla.
Come on!
Hey, you and Pops
could double‐date.
(chuckles)
♪
Damn it, Lupin, I warned
you about this, you know?
‐No, you didn't.
‐What?
Admit it, you were
casting aspersions
on poor Fujiko.
Oh, yeah?
What the hell's
the difference?
You owe her an
apology, if you ask me.
It appears that these
tire tracks are fresh.
♪
That's their jeep!
(grunting)
I think the jungle
is getting to him.
They're nearby.
I am sensing something,
like large creatures.
Damn it, you're good.
Look at that!
Look at what?
Yeah, look in that cage.
Yeah, but there's only one‐‐
Shh!
That's weird.
How come only
one's in the cage?
Wait a minute,
what's this?
Oh, man.
Well, that explains a lot.
That son of a bitch.
What kind of low life
scumbag would exploit
animals like that?
Wait, I agree with you,
but hold your fire.
Right, there's at least one
more of those guys, you know?
We start shooting
and Fujiko becomes
a human shield.
Poor Fujiko.
Yeah, well, it's
always about Fujiko.
Hey, look.
Whoa.
That settles it.
We'll just wait
until after dark.
Hmm.
He's gotta be around
here somewhere, damn it!
(jungle animal sounds)
♪
(dog barking)
Shh!
(trees creaking)
What's with them?
I don't know, they've
been acting weird
all day long.
I don't see nothing.
Come on then.
Boss wants to get moving.
All right, all right.
Boss?
There's another one?
Well, hail, hail,
the gang's all here.
♪
Hmm?
So, you wanna settle up
or are you guys starting
to like living in those suits?
(laughs)
No way, and don't
get any ideas about
paying me in bananas either.
I don't know, I mean,
I think it looks
pretty good on you, Ralph.
Suits you, you know?
♪
Ah, well, boys,
between the Lockhound piece
and all of Lupin's loot,
I'd say it's been
a pretty damn
successful safari.
I should go big game
hunting in Africa more often.
Oh, man, Fujiko,
you are one bad mama jama.
Anyways, so there you go.
I promised you
10,000 a piece.
Oh, baby.
‐Hey, what the hell?
‐Son of a bitch!
What is that?
Ralph, look outside!
You look outside!
I'm so glad I got
a couple of big,
brave men with me...
Jigen!
(shouting)
(rumbling)
♪
(screaming)
(yells)
What the...
I'm thinking this baby
could use a nice moonroof.
Hmm.
♪
Nice work.
(grunts)
Now, I admit that's
a very inviting pose,
but maybe some other time.
Lupin, I...
Check your bag?
No, wait!
‐I mean‐‐
‐Yes?
I wanted to apologize.
(growling)
♪
(shouts)
Jigen, look out behind you.
Thanks!
(grunting)
(squawking)
I hate to say
"I told you so" Lupin,
but this is just
so freakin' typical.
I mean, first she
betrays our confidence,
then she rips us off,
and then on top of that,
she tries to have us killed.
Yeah, a real multitasker,
that Fujiko.
That's not funny.
Hey!
Let's see if she can fly!
Lupin, don't
just stand there!
Hey, look, come on now, Jigen.
I mean, all's well
that ends well, right?
Huh?
(shooting)
Lupin, there's no way
out of this one,
so just give up!
You guys got exactly
one minute before
we open fire!
Lupin, you hear me?
I'm not fooling around!
All right, I gotcha.
♪
Come on!
It would be crappy
to see the whole thing
end this way.
All right, if that's
how you want it, Lupin.
Ten, nine, eight‐‐
Hold on tight, Fujicakes.
Good, that's it.
Maybe even a little tighter.
Hey, Lupin, we're
kinda waiting over here.
Oh, sorry, guess
I got carried away.
All yours, Goemon.
Sixteen...
What the?
(grunting)
‐Uh, sir?
‐What?
Perhaps you should move.
(Zenigata shouts)
(crash)
Ow.
Damn you, come back
here right now!
Lupin!
(groaning)
♪
Sayonara, toots.
Lupin!
I can't hold on,
I'm gonna slip!
Give me your hand, I can't‐‐
No, no, Fujiko, hold on.
Don't let go,
I'll think of something.
Just give me a second, okay?
I'll just hold this
thing like this...
(grunting)
(Fujiko and Lupin shriek)
No!
I‐‐I'm gonna be sick.
♪
Oh, Lupin.
You should've
dropped me instead.
You see, now,
that's the difference
between the two of us.
Oh, really?
What's that?
For me, that was
a very small price to pay
for this.
(Fujiko giggles)
Oh, Lupin.
♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
Why are bats pooping
poison all over us?
Who are the Fuma ninjas
and why do they hate us?
What's hidden inside
the dead guy's castle
that's guy Goemon acting
like a hopped up Samurai
at a piñata party?
And perhaps,
most mysterious of all,
what's up with this?
It's all part of...
"The Riddle of
Tsukikage Castle."
Catch you later!
♪