♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
In the last days of
the Tokugawa Shogunate,
the Shinsengumi were
the Shogunate elite guards
fighting against
the advancing forces
of the Meiji
Restoration government.
They fought
bravely to the end
but died along with
the Shogunate itself.
Their naval ship
the Banryu Maru,
with its legendary
golden cannon,
was taken out of the castle
and scuttled in the open ocean
near Tsugaru Strait, condemned
to drift along at the bottom
of the sea for all eternity.
No man has set eyes on the
Banryu Maru or its priceless
golden cannon since that day.
♪
(chuckling)
Isami Kondoo the Third
and Lupin the Third,
it does have
the ring of a rather
formidable partnership,
doesn't it?
(giggling)
As a small gesture of my
gratitude for your assistance
in arranging this meeting,
please accept this.
Purple pearls for me?
You must be psychic, I mean,
how else could you know
they're exactly what I wanted?
Just listen to her, will ya,
sometimes I wonder how the hell
that girl lives with herself!
Well, I suppose
as long as we're here,
we might as well take a
look at those old documents
you say were passed down
by the descendants
of the Shinsengumi.
Wonderful‐‐Okida, the documents!
Yes, sir, here they are.
♪
How do you do, gentlemen?
I am Soshi Okida.
(typewriter keys clacking)
♪
This isn't some kind of joke.
Mr. Lupin, I'm a businessman.
When it comes to making money,
I have no sense of humor.
According to my research,
the golden cannon would
conservatively fetch between
$70 million and $80 million
on today's black market.
The contract I negotiated
with Mr. Kondoo gives us half.
She robbed me,
but then I suppose
that's your specialty, isn't it?
♪
You are strong in
both body and spirit,
but even you cannot
vanquish the sea current.
Who goes there?
♪
(dolphin squeaks)
Hey, Jigen, they
got seals around here?
How the hell should I know?
♪
Lupin, look in there,
it's just big enough
for a ship to pass through.
♪
Huh, think this is it, the long
lost pathway of the Banryu Maru,
dragged along by sea currents
for hundreds of years?
Well, we should know
for sure any minute now.
Mhm.
(current whooshing)
(grunting)
(wood creaking)
Disappointing, Mr. Lupin, but
everything's hype these days,
why should you be different?
Yeah, well, there was just
one little thing left out
of your job description.
A lethal sea current!
I know it's different
from the usual type
one encounters at that depth,
I'm perfectly aware of that.
I don't think you are.
Eighteen skilled divers
have already died
assisting in this
little endeavor.
Paints a grim picture,
but I thought Lupin the Third
was in a class of his own.
I didn't get that
way being an idiot.
Better luck with
number 19, toodles!
Well, Kondoo, you
screwed up big time!
I realize it may appear
that way to your eyes, John,
but if my research has
revealed anything about Lupin,
it's that he can be
counted on to eventually
get his hands on literally
anything he wants.
So now that he's got
a glimpse of that cannon,
believe me, all you and I
will have to do is wait.
That self‐confidence of yours
could be the death of you.
♪
I got to beat the
power of that current
or somehow get
it to work for me.
♪
(ship's horn blowing)
(wipers whizzing)
(dolphin chirping)
♪
Come on, I'll show ya!
(giggling)
♪
Hey, let me take a shot.
(clacking)
♪
Whoa, pretty amazing.
Hey, ring man,
here's some money,
let these kids use it up.
Huh‐‐thank you, nice man!
Wow, yeah, thanks a
lot, sir, see ya later!
(laughing)
♪
The guy in the convertible
that just went by
seemed kind of strange.
Let it go, I'm not in this one.
‐(yawning)
‐'Kay.
♪
(loud crash)
(metallic tapping)
Okay, just about Jigen time.
All set.
(helicopter blades whirring)
♪
(scraping metal)
Hm?
Oh, very funny, John.
We'll be arriving any
minute, and I'm hoping that
for $200 million, you're good
for more than a few laughs.
Don't you worry about it,
this whole thing is going
to go down smoother than
a stiff shot of single malt.
Nice tough guy patter.
I hope you can walk the walk.
Okay, man, anytime now.
All right, let's
see what we got!
(current whooshing)
Do it, why are you waiting?
Not time yet.
(water hissing)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(loud crash)
♪
That's it, we did it, right?
Lupin, you're a genius!
Who, me‐‐well, if you insist.
(electric hum)
♪
(beeping)
What were you doing
in there, anyway?
Nothing, just kicking
the tires‐‐I mean,
who needs a golden cannon
if it doesn't work?
All set over here.
Okay, Jigen!
(chain rumbling)
♪
(chuckling)
Finally, history
turns a new page.
Well, for once, everything
goes according to plan.
Yeah, hold that
thought, Fujicakes.
Oh, hell, we should have seen
this one coming a mile away.
(whoosh)
♪
(explosions)
Let's see, we've got spear
guns, they've got bazookas,
any one else not
liking these odds?
Dammit, I can't die, I have
a hair appointment tomorrow.
Don't worry, I saw this coming
and prepared a little
surprise for these guys.
(explosions)
Hey, what the hell's this stuff?
I dunno, looks like gas.
Okay, detonate the explosives.
Don't let those guys
get out of here alive.
♪
(metal sliding)
Not that saving my life
wasn't enough or anything,
but you know, just out
of idle curiosity,
what are you planning
to do about the cannon?
Oh, I'm still taking it,
Fujicakes, don't you worry.
Really, you mean it, oh, Lupin,
I love you, I love you!
‐Oops, I forgot!
‐I'll take what I can get!
Move it, come on, hurry up!
(gushing water)
(explosion)
(loud thuds)
(bubbles squelching)
A toast to Lupin,
our silent partner!
(high‐pitched beeping)
♪
(loud crash)
What was that, what the
hell's going on up there?
I'm not sure, sir,
I think we've run aground!
Dammit, where the hell is Okida?
Somebody find him right now!
Looks like the guy
purposely abandoned his post!
What?
Okida?
Where the hell have
you been, Okida?
The damn ship's run aground,
you're supposed
to be on the bridge!
I don't answer to you anymore,
Kondoo, you're a traitor.
Here, this was supposed to be
about the cause, remember?
‐Well, you...
‐Shut up!
You bring dishonor to your own
grandfather, who was decapitated
by those bastards of the
Satsuma and the Choshu!
Don't you know
we're in Haikodate?
This is where
our ancestors fought
to defend the Shogunate cause!
The story of the Golden Cannon
has been passed down to us,
it is the symbol of
our proud line's hope
of reestablishing
the Shinsengumi,
and you would sell our
legacy to the highest bidder!
Listen to me, Okida,
you're living in the past.
What did you say?
What could you possibly hope
to achieve by resurrecting
the Shinsengumi now, Okida,
in the modern Japan of today?
An independent
Hokkaido, that's what!
Destiny roars from the
mouth of the Golden Cannon!
(chuckling)
Fire!
(grunting)
(splash)
What in the world?
♪
No, not seals, Shinsengumi.
Um, hey, funny coincidence,
I just decided to retire.
So, um, all the best on
this whole Hokkaido thing
and I'll be seeing you
around, okay, cheerio!
(groaning)
Okida, only money talks.
(grunting)
♪
(sobbing)
Thank you, sir, thank you for
bringing our dream back to life.
Enough, it's not time yet,
our battles have barely begun.
Sorry, sir, no more tears
until Hokkaido is liberated.
♪
Well, if I were in an opera,
I might be really moved,
but right now a sight like
that just give me the creeps!
It's a good time for
us to get a move on
before those guys
get it together.
Jigen's got a good point,
we'll go and take care of them,
while you pilot the ship,
does that work for you?
Uh‐huh!
What's happening,
why are we moving?
(gunshots)
Protect the cannon at all costs!
‐Fight for Hokkaido!
‐Hey, Lupin,
you better step on it.
Yes, sir, aye‐aye!
(gunfire)
(groaning)
(panting)
(reed melody)
♪
(gunshots)
(grunting)
Real nice, work
there, way to go!
You know, we're
going backwards‐‐
(whimpering)
Hey there, weirdest thing,
first the engine lost power,
then the whole damn ship
started going in reverse.
You think they got it
used or something?
Well, whatever, I'm sure
I can get it working again.
Hey, what's the matter,
you cold or something?
Huh?
Octopus, a gigantic one!
Lupin, dammit,
let me out of here!
‐Lupin!
‐Geez, sorry...
‐What's the matter with you?
‐Excuse me, but‐‐
(Fujiko screaming)
Jigen, Goemon!
Octopus, octopus!
What the‐‐octopus, what
the hell's he talking about?
Huh?
(whimpering)
(gunshots)
Not even a scratch.
(reed melody)
Huh?
♪
I am Goemon Ishikawa.
I'm afraid I must
force you to desist.
And I am afraid I cannot allow
anyone to impede our dream.
♪
(growling)
You fought well, but
your weapon didn't.
‐Look out!
‐(groaning)
I can't see them, can you?
(roaring)
♪
(reed melody)
(roaring)
♪
Huh?
Goemon, you're alive!
My life has no purpose!
Lupin, Okida's going
to blow up the ship,
you gotta get out of there!
Huh?
The Golden Cannon's a dream,
it is no one's commodity,
it's not for sale!
‐Oh, shut up!
‐No, hold on!
The guy's completely out
of his mind, let's bounce.
Long live Shinsengumi!
♪
Come on, you coming?
Yeah, yeah!
(splash)
♪
Hokkaido will be free!
(explosion)
(whistling sound)
♪
Some dreams wither,
others go kapow!
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Yup, we're in the US next time,
where the billionaire
owner of a football team
also happens to own a priceless
sapphire known as Solomon's Eye.
Of course I want the rock, but
enough to kill the guy for it?
That's what everybody thinks,
including the pesky little
detective running the case.
Can I juke the kid and score
before time runs out?
Find out in "You're Sapphired!"
Catch ya later!
♪