♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(gunshots)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Mmm, this is so nice.
‐I could sit here all day.
‐(sigh)
‐(laughing)
‐(cooing)
You know, this is
the birthplace of Casanova.
The original belt notcher.
No, he was the world's
greatest lover, my dear.
Casanova was a veritable
Santa Claus of sex,
gladdening the hearts of
countless women with‐‐
his big bag of tricks.
You know I've got a rather
sizeable sack myself
and it's all for you.
Come on, Lupin.
How the hell are
you gonna see the signal
if you can't take your eyes
off friggen Fujiko?
Reach in, come on,
grab something.
Oh man, look at him, somebody
get me a hose, this is ridic‐‐
‐Here he comes.
‐Huh?
♪
Where?
To the right.
♪
Yeah, looks like our
ship has finally come in.
Yeah, sit on my
knee, little girl,
have you been
naughty or nice?
♪
They're here!
Whaa, whaa, whaaaa!
(crashing)
(boat horn tooting)
♪
Don Martino, on the surface
just a rich, rough and tumble,
Sicilian rancher with a simple
country boy's love of horses.
That's Saint Junior,
his Kentucky Derby winner.
So much for surfaces.
That guy's one of the most
feared men in Sicily.
And what he really loves
is fine art and rare gems,
mostly other people's
fine art and rare gems,
if you know what I mean.
Just like us.
Except he's a bad guy,
a real bad guy.
Like I said, no one
in Sicily messes with him.
Huh.
♪
Unfortunately,
he's in Venice now.
(typewriter keys clicking)
♪
(train whistling)
The Trans‐European
Super Express
shuttles between
Paris and Venice.
This is how Don Martino gets
his stuff out of the country,
under the guise of transporting
Saint Junior to France
for the
Arc de Triomphe Trophy,
quite ingenious, really.
You lost me there,
I don't get
why he's got to ship it
all the way to France
‐in the first place.
‐It's simple.
Because the Italian
police may be many things,
but they are not morons.
They figured out
there's more to Martino
than meets the eye.
They're getting
their ducks in a row.
Of course, so he's under
pressure to hustle it
all out of the country
and convert
everything questionable
to good old untraceable cash
before the police swoop down.
Simple and effective.
Except for one thing‐‐
it's a public conveyance
and who knows what kind
of shady characters
might happen to be on board.
Ooh, baby, I just love it
when you talk like that.
How's your half
gainer these days?
(together)
Huh?
Why?
‐Crap.
‐Damn, Zenigata.
And somehow I doubt if
he's here on his honeymoon.
Good work, okay we've
all got our assignments,
let's go.
Police‐‐you the
one I spoke to?
Yes, sir, they're in 209.
♪
(grunts)
Hands up, all of you!
♪
Hmm?
Huh?
Rrr‐huh?
(drapes flapping)
♪
‐(boat horn tooting)
‐Crap, crap, crap, crap!
(sigh)
Huh?
♪
Paging passenger Bruno.
Mrs. Bornia Bruno, please pick
up the white courtesy phone
by the ticket office.
(wheels squealing)
♪
(hooves clomping)
(laughing)
Ah!
♪
I'm so hungry I could
eat a damn horse.
Somebody get
that porter in here.
Apparently, he believes
having his own private car
makes him less vulnerable.
It's not such a
bad idea, actually,
the problem is he's not exactly
dealing with amateurs here.
The thing about Lupin is he
can take your biggest strength
and turn it into your biggest
stumbling block, you know?
Ooh, better get shakin'.
Let's go.
(train whistle blowing)
See you later!
Goodbye!
Hey, train dudes,
like, wait up, you know!
Here!
(exclaims)
Guess we're sharing
this compartment.
Come in, sit down.
Uh, no, man, it's like,
you know, later.
(sigh)
‐(screaming)
‐Yeah!
Ooh!
Dirty hippie!
Huh?
(whistling)
I could swear I heard
a woman scream out here.
(sigh)
Excuse me,
‐but I thought I‐‐
‐(scream)
Ow.
(train whistling)
♪
Jigen, can you see
with your hat like that?
Guess we'll find out, huh?
Hey, Jigen, listen up.
Remember that map?
Mm‐hmm, yeah,
what about it?
You must have
left it in the hotel.
Zenigata found it
and he's on the train.
What, really,
no that's impossible,
I'd never make a rookie
mistake like that.
There's a simple way
to resolve this.
Yeah sure,
I got it right h‐‐
Where the hell is it?
‐Oh, man.
‐Don't sweat it.
Pops will be looking for us
and luckily we're in disguise.
I'm sure he's clueless
about Martino.
Hmm.
But why go by train?
Either his car's
in the shop
or he's playing some angle.
He's got to be up to
something no good,
damn Lupin.
Hey, you know
that really hurt.
That'll teach you.
Teach me what?
That when I'm playing
a role, watch out.
Really, I'll be sure to think up
more stimulating parts for you.
(giggle)
I don't know, I think if my
parts were any more stimulating,
you'd explode.
Cute, hey by the way,
did you know Jigen
left the map in the room
and now Pops is here?
Yeah, I ran into him before.
I was wondering
how that happened.
It's a real
pain in the butt.
But we'll be okay if
we both stay in character.
I didn't realize
you two were friends.
Ahh!
Oh no, it's‐‐
Oh, we're not friends.
Oh, in that case,
do you mind if I join you?
That'd be groovy.
Hello again,
name's Zenigata.
Sorry about that earlier,
let me buy you a drink.
I always heard that older men
knew just how to treat a lady.
I guess I'm just an
old‐fashioned girl.
I don't know about that,
but whatever your fashion is,
I like it.
Say, aren't you old enough
to be her, you know, Pops?
Huh?
(exclaims)
Bummer, man,
you got arthritis?
I mean, like I'm totally down
with the whole Gray Panthers
thing, man, you know,
power to the people.
Whatever‐‐so anyway,
Miss, I‐‐
Bye‐bye.
Yeah.
(sigh)
(train whistle blowing)
♪
Simplon, it's the
world's largest tunnel.
Runs under the Alps
for about ten miles.
Should take about 13 minutes
to go through the whole thing.
You sure that's enough time
for you to do your thing?
I mean, thanks to
me you've got Pops there
to help you
if you need a hand.
Right.
Okay, we're
pulling ahead now,
we'll be in position.
Good luck.
♪
(sigh)
Now, Fujiko will do
what she does best.
(knocking)
What do you want?
Hi there.
Hmm, leopard never
changes his spots.
Okay, Lupin, fun's
over, come on out!
(scream)
(fighting)
Get out of here,
you pervert!
Carry on.
♪
‐A man!
‐Excuse me, I'm‐‐
(kissing)
Thanks.
♪
Sorry.
So you say we met
at a party in Rome, huh?
Why, you bad boy, you've
all ready forgotten me?
You must flirt
with a lot of women.
Mmm, I'm very jealous.
Oh, don't be that way,
let's toast to
new beginnings, eh.
‐Mm‐hmm.
‐All right.
That sounds great.
Hey, I heard you've got
Saint Junior on board with you.
That horse has made me more
money than my last divorce.
I'd love to meet him
and thank him personally.
Where do you keep him,
back here somewhere?
Listen, Miss, he's
not real comfortable
around beautiful
ladies like yourself.
Kind of shy, you know.
Hmm, you're not being
serious, are you?
I don't know, are you?
‐(smack)
‐Oh!
You!
(laugh)
Should have kept your
mouth shut, little girl.
Don Martino don't
go to Rome no more.
Him and the Pope
don't see eye to eye.
Tell us, come on,
who are you working with?
And if you don't talk,
let's just say Don Martino
won't be the only one who won't
be able to recognize your face.
(laughing)
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Two, three.
‐Time's up.
‐Soften her up.
Thanks, boss, this
one will be a pleasure.
(door thumping)
Hmm?
‐Who's there?
‐Hmm.
Inspector Zenigata, Interpol.
Hello.
Sorry to bother you,
gentlemen,
but I'm on the trail
of a notorious thief
and I have reason to believe he
may be on this train somewhere.
You're not saying
we're thieves, are you?
Uh, no well, of course not,
certainly not.
Uh, well,
hello there, Miss‐‐
Oh, hello, I was just checking
out the carpet in here,
I just can't
resist a good shag.
Thanks guys, catch you
in the club car.
Thanks for your cooperation.
(growls)
So, you're actually
on a case, Inspector,
how exciting!
Oh yeah, exactly
how excited are you?
You know that jockey's
outfit back there
was giving me ideas.
You're really amazing,
I mean it.
You just saved
my life in there.
Aw shucks, all in
a day's work, ma'am.
So, what did you
pick up in there?
I'm pretty certain they've
got everything packed away
in the last car with the
racehorse, Saint Junior.
Just what I was
hoping, good work.
You should
probably lay low now.
Come on.
(door opening)
(gasp)
Uh‐oh.
Hmm?
Say haven't I seen
you somewhere before?
Hey, that makes you‐‐
why you're‐‐
You're Lupin,
hold it right there!
Nope.
‐Grrrr!
‐Whoops.
Hey, get back here, you!
(panting)
(growls)
Coming through!
Hey, watch it!
All right now, nice
and easy, Inspector.
I mean, Lupin.
Dammit, now you've
got me confused!
Oh, right here,
let me help you.
Now you see, Pops,
I'm the handsome one
and you're
the guy people mistake
for an ape in a trench coat.
Why you little‐‐arghh!
Getting off?
(yelling)
Watch that first step.
It's a doozy!
Dammit, but anyway, that
train's going to Paris
and you can't do
a thing about that!
(water lapping)
(train chugging)
(birds singing)
They ought to be entering
the tunnel right about now.
(train chugging)
(whistle blowing)
That's it, they're here.
Right, here we go.
♪
Come on, come.
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
♪
Okay.
Just eight cars.
Hot damn.
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
‐What the‐‐?
‐Hey, where'd it go?
What?
The car, it's‐‐
What the hell is going on?
Well, it just
kind of, you know.
Eh, what's happening?
Come on!
(train coupling)
‐What the‐‐?
‐(laughing)
Huh?
You know, it never fails.
The right stuff's
in the middle of the tunnel
and somebody gets screwed.
Who the hell are you, anyway?
Lupin.
And for the record,
my grandpa would have kicked
your butt even worse.
Oh yeah, we'll see
whose butt gets kicked,
you cocky little‐‐
Ah‐‐temper, temper.
Don't want to burst a
blood vessel or anything.
Believe me, you'll want
to save that for later.
You're dead, you hear?
Get him!
‐(gunshots)
‐Catch me if you can.
Come on, Fujicakes.
Hey, good buddy, let's throw
that big banger in gear
and highball it out of here.
10‐4.
Hi.
♪
(gunshots)
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Damn, can't get
a clear shot, boss.
You want we should go up top
and take them in the truck?
Nah, we'll hit the back car,
they won't be expecting that.
Let's go.
Hmm, ah, I'm just a big sucker
for the pitter patter
of little feet.
♪
So, Mr. Smartmouth
thinks he's the only one
that knows his way
around trains, huh?
Arrivederci.
Huh, what the‐‐?
♪
Jigen, turn around!
(brakes screeching)
Oy.
Jigen, we can't
back up fast enough
to catch up with him.
We've got to get
this thing off the tracks
and hit the road.
It's up to you, buddy.
(metal clanking)
(hydraulics lifting)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(glass shattering)
(gunfire)
I want him dead!
♪
He hit the console,
we're out of control!
(together)
Huh?
I did what?
♪
(train chugging)
Hey, there's another
train coming at ya!
Great, the brakes
are out on this thing!
Lupin, listen, you've
got to get out of there,
you're gonna crash
on that bridge up ahead!
Get over there first
and blow up the bridge!
No, you're insane,
don't do it!
You're going to
plunge into the gorge!
Just do it, will ya,
not that I don't appreciate
your concern, sweetheart.
Did you think I was
talking about you,
it's the loot
I'm worried about.
(sigh)
Hey, you think you can save the
witty repartee for another time?
Oh, all right, just blow up
the damn bridge, okay?
You got it.
♪
(yelling)
Boss, it's coming
right at us.
We got to get the hell
out of here, come on.
No, no, it's just
fine, you guys go.
I'll stay here, my jewels
will protect me, won't you?
(laughing)
Just me and my
beautiful jewels.
Hmm?
Should we stay here?
What about the boss?
♪
Hmm.
They don't love you, only I do.
Only me!
(laughing)
♪
So this is the most feared man
in all of Sicily, huh?
Pathetic.
(brakes screeching)
♪
Damn, not enough time.
Throw it.
(grunts)
♪
(gunfire)
(explosion)
(screaming)
(screeching)
Ah!
Lupin!
(gasp)
(neighing)
(laughing)
(splash)
♪
Lupin, it's a
pleasure to see you.
I assume you have something
to share with all of us?
‐Yep, here it is.
‐What?
This is all of it?
I don't get it, you're
saying that's all there was?
I mean, that won't even
cover the truck rental.
Martino went nuts and
I just, I don't know,
you know, something hit me.
You mean like on the head?
Well, I think he means
somewhere else.
Pity never did
a man any good.
Nah, it's not that.
But don't worry, I'll make
it up to you guys, I promise.
(whinnying)
♪
The conditions are
perfect for today's running
of the Arc de Triomphe Classic.
The horses and their mounts
are just approaching
the starting gate.
You know something, with
anyone else this would be nuts,
but with Lupin,
all bets are off.
I'm beginning to think maybe
he did get hit on the head,
I mean, what's he
trying to prove?
Perhaps that he's
master of his own soul.
‐Here we go.
‐(fanfare)
(flags flapping)
A clean start all around.
Saint Junior, the favorite,
is in lead by a length.
Ah, but here comes
Social Gal sprinting up
from four lengths back.
Hey, Lupin!
What the?
Bet you thought you could
get rid of me, huh, Lupin?
Nah, I knew as long as
you landed on your head,
you'd be just fine.
Ah, just shut up and pull
over, you're under arrest!
What do you say we make it
a steeplechase, huh?
Giddy‐up!
♪
Hey, where are you
going, get back here!
Toodles!
I'm warning you‐‐whoa!
♪
‐Ugh.
‐(tickets ripping)
(sigh)
Somebody shoot me.
I got you, I got you!
You're not going
anywhere, Lupin!
Get‐‐whoa!
Hang in there!
‐Whoa!
‐(neighing)
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
This old guy's the grandson
of one of Japan's
greatest artists.
So when he comes to me
with his last dying wish,
my heart goes out to him.
Unfortunately, it's a setup.
A really brilliant one.
I mean, anyone
can set a trap,
but baiting it's an art,
and this guy is
a master at baiting.
Check out Now Museum,
Now You Don't.
Catch you later.
♪