♪
(gunshot)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(shattering)
(engine revving)
(tires screeching)
♪
(gunshot)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(tires screeching)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(tires screeching)
Huh?
♪
Inspector Zenigata,
what can I do for you?
Yes, Professor,
it's very urgent,
concerning Lupin the Third.
Well, enter this way.
Huh?
Uh.
♪
Uh...
‐Huh?
‐Surprised, Inspector?
You know how I obsessed
I am with security?
Now, if you don't
want to get lost,
proceed to the right.
Mamma mia!
All this inside an airplane?
♪
(grunting)
(whirring)
Ah, welcome, Inspector.
You see, what's amusing
is that by continually
manipulating the
arrangement of the corridors,
I can create a
maze with no exit.
A man can go totally
nuts in there!
This computer generates
the combinations.
Even Lupin himself
could never penetrate it
in a thousand years.
Uh, yes, I'm sure,
but, well, you see,
I've just
received information
that Lupin's here
in Hawaii right now.
You think he may be
after my collection?
Is that it, Inspector?
He won't get away with it,
though, Professor Hunter.
I'm not concerned.
Lupin may be a
criminal genius,
but I'm a criminal
psychologist.
I have purposely
designed a safe, you see,
that Lupin couldn't
possibly break into.
♪
Ah, you mean this thing here?
Yes, only one person in the
world can access this safe,
and that's me, Inspector,
the great Professor Hunter.
♪
Huh, wait a minute.
Isn't that...
♪
Don't touch that!
This safe is controlled
by that same computer.
If even so much as a particle
of dust is removed from here,
you'll be hit by
100,000 volts.
Really, 100,000?
Hmm, now you see, I've
disengaged the alarm.
I gladly look forward
to Lupin's arrival.
His failure will
prove he's nothing
but a common criminal.
(laughing)
One of my ancestor's
famous flinging pennies.
He was a policeman
in the Edo period.
He used to throw
these at the crooks.
This belongs in a
museum of criminology.
It shouldn't be used as
bait to lure Lupin with.
Hmm.
Forgive me.
(tapping of typewriter keys)
♪
Hmm?
(beeping)
There's a car approaching.
Huh?
Crap, I was just
starting to unwind.
♪
(tires screeching)
Guy's good.
Oh, it's Pops!
That's weird, I thought
he was a speed‐a‐phobic.
That's not all either.
Take a look at his face.
(tires screeching)
My apologies, Inspector,
but I cannot permit you
to come any closer.
Move it, underling.
Hmm.
Unforgivable,
prepare yourself.
(grunting)
♪
Ha!
I must be dreaming this.
♪
He can't, no way.
(clanging)
(engine roaring)
(gunshot)
(grunting)
Want to keep playing?
(chuckling)
♪
‐Uh‐uh.
‐Huh?
♪
Get in.
You're not him,
you're an imposter.
Take off that mask.
Knock it off!
(car door opening)
Lupin!
Not coming out, huh?
Well, then,
I'm gonna come in.
Huh?
(exploding)
That's a cute toy, but
it won't work on me.
♪
Come on out, Lupin.
(gun firing)
(grunting)
♪
I wonder what's
gotten into Pops.
He's having a
pretty good day.
♪
Look at you, bested
by an old man.
You should be ashamed.
What have you got to
say for yourselves, huh?
‐Lupin, behind you.
‐He's right behind you.
Whoa, Pops, well,
isn't this embarrassing?
Not really, see?
I'm serious now.
(laughs)
Ugh.
(sighing)
Can someone take
this tape off?
(crying)
♪
Hmm?
(engine roaring)
(splashing)
Please, Lupin,
I'm‐‐I'm beggin' ya.
Are you really serious
about this, Pops?
You want to be a thief?
Mmhmm, see, I found
a flinging coin
that once belonged to my
most honored ancestor,
Inspector Heiji Zenigata in
Professor Hunter's collection.
That's right, flinging a
penny was his signature move.
It's just another
penny to anybody else,
but to the Zenigatas,
it's a family treasure.
'Kay, so what you're saying
is you want to steal it?
Mm, mm, mmhmm.
♪
Please, you're
the only one alive
who can break into
his safe, Lupin!
Please, I'm beggin' ya!
Just this once!
I'll never ask
you another favor!
Hey, guys, whoa,
that's amazing.
It looks exactly
like the real Pops.
But what's it for?
It's not Halloween.
Hey, bet ya think that's
pretty funny, Fujiko!
Whoa, it's amazing, I mean,
he even gets angry
exactly like him too.
I'd hope so, I mean,
seeing as it is
actually Pops himself.
Look, you can't
fool me, Lupin.
Of all things I'm
sure of in life,
I'm sure that
Pops is our enemy.
Well, you know
what they say,
"Yesterday's enemy
is today's friend."
Come on, seriously,
you're kidding, right?
Uh‐huh, ha!
♪
I admit, it's quite daunting.
Oh, yeah, I've never
seen the likes of it.
I don't know, Lupin,
I heard that plenty of
guys attempted this before
and none of them
ever succeeded.
This Professor Hunter guy,
he's an academic, you know,
so he knows how to
do his homework.
Word is he researches
absolutely everything
about your strengths
and weaknesses,
right down to your
favorite toothpaste flavor,
and then he feeds it
all into his computer.
And you're in there,
buddy, count on it.
So, in other words, the
computer is my alter ego.
So I'll be both assaulting
and defending the safe.
Hmm, interesting.
(beeping)
I'm no academic,
but I've done
a little research of my own,
and what's inside
isn't worth much.
Certainly not worth the risk.
Sorry, guys,
but count me out.
Lupin, I have to concur.
I have a bad
feeling about this.
Sorry.
Yeah, I guess that
makes three of us.
This thing's like
your evil twin.
I know, I understand,
it's just the challenge is
too irresistible for me.
Well, if they won't help
ya, you still have me.
We're the only real
men here, Lupin, huh?
(engine starting)
♪
Sad thing, you know, but
nowadays without money,
there's no love, Lupin.
I sure hope you're
wrong about that, Pops,
but whatever happens,
I'm not gonna lose this one.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(beeping)
Ah.
♪
These disguises won't
be doing us much good.
Huh, what do you mean, why?
Our faces aren't enough.
We still have the same
weight and walk the same way.
Are you saying...
This floor is part
of his computer.
That means as long
as we walk on it,
he'll know exactly
who we are, right?
Warning, Lupin the Third
has arrived on the premises.
Well, well, welcome,
Lupin the Third.
Do come right in and prepare
yourself for a long stay.
(engine starting)
(whirring)
(droning)
You know, I think
we've been here before.
In fact, this is
the fifth time.
Fifth time?
Yeah, it makes sense,
think about it.
If the computer controlling
this maze is my alter ego,
it can anticipate my every
attempt to find an exit
and block me
before I get there.
♪
So every step we
take is futile.
Yeah, but don't worry.
From now on, you're gonna
decide which way to go.
♪
What‐‐what, me?
I mean, but...
The computer doesn't know
a thing about you, Pops.
The workings of your mind
are a complete mystery to it,
so it's at a disadvantage.
♪
Hmm.
(grunting)
Oh, good gravy, this
place sure goes on and on!
(thudding)
The behavior of
Lupin the Third
does not correspond to
the subject profile,
nor does it fit with
the recognized parameters
of normal human psychology.
Hmm, try as you may, Lupin,
you will never
beat my computer.
(whirring)
Looks like we're finally out.
Bet you're pretty glad you
let me come along with ya.
♪
Ah!
Hmm.
♪
(zapping)
Hey, I've already got
a hole there, Lupin!
♪
(zapping)
All right, yeah, we did it!
(shattering)
(whirring)
Huh, what in the world?
It's a self‐repair program.
♪
Hmm.
(chuckling)
Hunter logging in.
Come on, it's me, damn it!
(sighing)
♪
Come on, Lupin, come on.
We're almost there.
Think of something, please.
My whole fate depends on it.
(sighing)
Looks like the professor's
damn fingerprints
are the only way to
crack this safe, Pops.
I'm sorry, but sometimes
you just have to acknowledge
when you're beat and move on.
But you can't quit now!
The only honor left at this
point is to concede defeat.
Honor?
Ah, the honor of the
whole Zenigata family
will be tarnished
now over this.
How am I ever gonna
apologize to them?
(crying)
Ever since you
first approached us,
I smelled something fishy
about the whole deal.
So what's really
going on, huh?
♪
It's the most
embarrassing thing
a Zenigata has ever done.
And I'm a police officer.
So you wanted me to
break into this safe
and return this thing?
Hmm.
I know, Lupin,
I realize I put you
in a terrible position,
but I want to assure
you of something.
I'll be with you in
this till the end.
I'm certainly gonna
be fired for this,
and you'll retire in shame.
There's a kind of
symmetry in it, I mean,
when you think about it,
it's fate or something...
‐It's too early to give up.
‐Maybe we weren't intended...
Huh?
♪
Yeah, hold on.
This thing is gonna
be worth much more
than either of us
ever thought.
♪
(laughing)
They must have just
given up and run away.
(laughing)
♪
Huh?
You never know how
the game is gonna end
till the last move,
wouldn't you agree?
Too smug too fast, Mr. Lupin.
The computer may have had
a complete psychological
profile of you,
but I've never lost a game
of chess to the computer.
In other words, my intellect
is still grand master
against the likes of you.
Now approaching
the state prison.
The stakes of the game
are now fully
apparent, Mr. Lupin?
Uh‐huh, but you see,
humans have emotion,
something that computers
and sometimes even professors
have been known to fail
to take into account.
♪
(gasping)
I don't understand this.
It's from my collection.
This just can't be.
(gasping)
(chuckling)
But where did I
make a mistake?
Ah!
Human error, Professor,
chaos theory 101.
Goes back to what I was
saying about emotions.
You see, you broke into
your own safe for me.
I didn't do anything.
You came unglued when
you saw that penny,
and you were so flipped out,
you forgot I was
right behind you.
You opened it for me.
♪
(panting)
I haven't lost yet.
I'm the only one who
can operate this plane,
therefore, I'm afraid,
I will manage to escape
while you remain here
to rot in prison.
I'm afraid that you
still don't get it.
It's my pals who have been
piloting this tub, Professor.
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(gasping)
In this battle of wits,
you were outdone.
(grunting)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Ow, ow, ooh!
♪
Hey, Lupin!
♪ I ain't got any worries ♪
♪ I ain't got any money ♪
♪ Love seems to follow
wherever I go ♪
And the best part is
Fujiko came to rescue me.
Yeah, well, don't
get the wrong idea.
I happened to find a
buyer for some of this.
Hey, Lupin, wait, daggonit!
You never said anything
about stealing the collection
when we were done!
Hey, Pops, take it easy!
You'll get your
share, promise.
Ah, what's the matter
with you, are you crazy?
Every one of you is
under arrest for robbery.
Got ya red‐handed!
Huh, you gotta be kidding.
(grunting)
(whooshing)
♪
Huh?
I don't get it, yesterday
I caught you guys so easily.
What's going on here?
You know, it's obvious
you're not the same.
You're different than
you were yesterday, pal.
What the hell do
you mean by that?
Yesterday, you were
willing to become a thief
just to return
a single penny,
so you gotta be just as crazy
now if you want to catch us.
So long!
(engine starting)
Come back here!
Catch ya later, Pops!
♪
One of these days, that guy
is gonna make me so mad,
I'm gonna just‐‐I'm gonna
just, I mean, I'm gonna...
Ah, daggonit, Lupin,
get back here!
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Next time, Jigen
risks his life
for a beautiful prima donna,
something I seem to do
just about every episode,
but, hey, I guess
he's been too busy
to watch the damn show to
learn from my experience.
Anyway, there's a
priceless diamond,
a race to the border,
and the whole shebang.
What's not to like?
Next time, we're
"Gettin' Jigen with It."
Catch ya later!
♪