♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(gunshots)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(echoey chanting)
♪
Welcome to the Museum
of Ancient History,
Egypt's gift to the world.
All the artifacts
displayed here
date from the era
of the old kingdom,
roughly 3,000 years ago.
Ancient Egyptians dreamed
of crossing the Nile River
in a boat and living on its
west side after their death.
From this arose the custom
of mummifying their bodies
and placing gold
and treasures in the grave
for them to use
after they crossed over.
Jeez, man, talk about
stealing candy from a baby.
I mean, the friggin' grave
robbers here had it made.
Evading capture is easier
that evading your karma.
(giggling)
♪
In this gallery,
ladies and gentlemen,
is what many have called
the greatest discovery
of the last century,
the incomparably exquisite
burial accessories
of King Tutankhamen.
Exquisite doesn't begin
to do you justice.
Here you are,
are you mesmerized?
Mm‐hmm.
♪
(typewriter keys clicking)
Okay, so the security's a little
tighter than we anticipated.
Guard contingent's the usual.
But the laser system's
state of the art and then some.
And it's not just
the doors and windows.
These guys have got a
tight, well‐designed grid
covering every damn room
in the whole place.
♪
So what you're saying is even
if we did manage to break in,
we still wouldn't be able to
get anywhere near the case.
Oh, now, hold your
horses, sweetcakes,
there is one way.
The pedestal is
anchored to the floor,
but the case isn't
anchored to the pedestal,
giving us just
enough daylight to‐‐
Hey, am I talking
to myself here?
Yes, in a sense.
Hey, what the hell's
the matter with you guys?
Earth to Jigen,
could you crawl up
out of that
water pipe for a sec?
Sure, I guess, but you should
try this, it's really good.
(growls)
Did you guys retire
when I wasn't looking?
Yeah, out with it.
You guys are starting
to creep me out.
Well?
Guys, whatever it is
we can talk about it.
I mean, we're like
family here, right?
Then prepare yourself, Lupin.
(grunts)
Do you know what that is?
Uh, uh, a bad joke,
I'm hoping.
The dull shadow on this sword.
♪
‐Huh.
‐The shadow of death.
It's an omen of mortal
danger in your present path.
♪
Come on, man,
that's crazy, see.
Jigen, tell me you don't
believe in all this stuff.
Me, nah.
It's just my athlete's
foot acting up.
Oh, really, then why be
such a baby about it?
Hey, a little respect
if you don't mind,
I know these feet like
the back of my hand
and when they itch like this,
something bad always happens.
I'd be careful what
I say around them,
they're very sensitive soles.
Oh, brother.
I liked you better when you
were creeping me out, Jigen.
This is really pathetic.
All right, then,
guess this one
will have to be a
two‐man job, Lupin.
Sure, okay, yeah.
And don't come begging
for a cut of this later.
‐Hmm.
The golden mask itself
wears a mask of beauty
obscuring its true face.
♪
Not to sound too much
like Goemon or anything,
but with swift
enveloping wings,
implacable death
will swoop down
upon any who dare touch
the grave of Pharaoh.
Hmm?
It's carved in a pot they
found inside Tut's tomb.
I read about it
in a brochure.
Inshallah, you two.
That basically means good
friggen luck, pal.
Yeah, well same to you, pal.
What a wacko,
can you believe that?
They're both nuts.
You said it, baby.
With swift enveloping
wings, he swoops in and‐‐
doesn't score.
♪
(humming)
Well, Tut, you may have
been a great king of Egypt,
but I'm a pretty
damn good thief.
(ticking)
(saw humming)
(straining)
♪
(laughing)
That's it, beautiful,
rise to meet your new master,
King Lupin The Third.
Ah!
(air escaping)
Gotcha!
(reel winding)
You're a very naughty boy.
Come on, you.
(helicopter blades whirring)
♪
Hey, good work, baby.
Mmm‐hmm.
Wha, hey, dammit, Fujiko!
That wasn't
the friggin' signal!
You trying to kill me?
Aw, were you worried
about me, that's so sweet.
(kissing)
♪
(paper press chugging)
Lupin!
(gasping)
Of course, why didn't
I think of it?
Grrr!
The weasel just went through
Israel to cover his damn tracks.
Grrr, crap, crap,
crap, crap!
Hey, I need a seat on the
next direct flight to Cairo!
If that's your idea of a joke,
sir, it's not appreciated!
Listen, I don't know what the
hell you're talking about, pal,
but I need a‐‐
This is an
Israeli airport, sir.
There are no direct flights
to any Arab country.
Grrrr, look, you,
this is the last time
I'm gonna ask you nicely.
Get me a flight to Cairo!
Security, hurry,
we've got a lunatic!
(punching)
No, wait, please, I'm one
of the good guys, really!
‐Cheers.
‐Here's looking at you.
Yeah, the second most
beautiful face in the room.
What a charmer.
Hey, Fujicakes
knows I'm only kidding.
Jeez, Louise, you guys really
need to lighten up a bit.
Anyway, I know
just what he means.
Something about this
guy really brings out
the concubine in me.
(kissing)
Really, well now that
gives me an idea.
Hey.
Tada, now who's your daddy?
Hey, man, that's
going too far.
I know you're trying
to impress Fujiko,
but you're putting all
of us in danger here.
Fear not, O bearded one.
If I ran out of royal subjects,
who would I have
to worship me, huh?
Ah, my royal theme music,
nice touch.
‐Thanks, guys.
‐Huh?
♪
This is getting just a little
too weird, don't you think?
Mm‐hmm.
(vocalizing)
I haven't heard
this for years.
Thousands of years.
Thanks, you're very talented,
but don't call us,
we'll call you.
♪
Uh.
Eh!
♪
Okay, that's enough.
Cut it out.
(crashing)
♪
(grunts)
I got him.
Here, let me.
(gasp)
♪
I'm afraid that this is
beyond the realm of medicine.
What, are you telling me this
is the curse of the Pharaoh?
What did the inscription say?
Oh, now you're
interested, huh?
Here, read it for yourself.
"The curse of the Pharaoh.
Strange deaths
plagued the excavators
of Tutankhamen's royal tomb.
In 1922, British
archaeologist Howard Carter
discovered the royal burial
chamber of King Tutankhamen
in the Valley of the Kings.
Soon after that,
Lord Carnaby,
who helped finance the
excavation, died mysteriously.
A short while later,
two art experts
who visited the tomb
also died suddenly.
Howard Carter himself died
inexplicably in 1923,
screaming, 'It's all over,
I can hear the calling.'"
Some things shouldn't
be fooled around with.
Read on, over the years
20 different people
died mysteriously.
You know what the only thing
they had in common was?
The Tut research.
Uh, it's nothing
but ghost stories.
Think Lupin would agree
with that right now?
I‐‐uh.
(groaning)
(shuddering)
What the hell's
the matter with him?
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(speaking Japanese)
It is a curse.
Well, if it's no use
calling a doctor, Jigen,
what the hell can we do?
We've got to do something.
Look, I'm no expert,
but if it was me,
I'd get that fricken mask
back to the museum pronto.
Such a gesture might serve to
pour oil on the troubled water.
It would seem a
good place to start.
No!
There's got to
be another way.
I mean, swiping it was
a masterpiece in itself.
Hey, you asked,
we answered.
‐Live with it.
‐I can't.
Besides, I know Lupin
would never agree to that.
It's against
everything he stands for.
The shadow of death
is getting darker.
‐(banging)
‐Huh?
♪
Lupin!
(gasps)
Oh, my God.
♪
Where'd he go?
I got an idea,
but if I'm right,
he's sicker than we thought.
I hate to say it, but these
feet are itching like crazy.
Let's go!
(murmuring)
♪
Yeah, that's him all right.
What the hell is he up to?
Impressive, it's a deceptively
difficult climb up there.
The guy's possessed.
He could probably
bench press Shaq.
Well don't just stand there
feeling inadequate,
He's our friend,
he's in danger.
We've got to help.
Help, what do you suggest?
Hmm.
Lupin, darling.
Could you come here, please?
♪
Ah!
(gasping)
What's wrong with him?
♪
Loyal subjects.
I am your king awakened
from 3,000 years of sleep.
Bow down to thee.
♪
This is exactly
what I was afraid of.
I have a bad
feeling about this.
Out of the way!
Move it, move it,
one side, coming through!
‐Uh‐oh.
‐(cars speeding)
All right,
leave this to me.
Lupin, get down,
you're under arrest!
Believe me, don't
make me come up there!
Grrr.
♪
Spirits of the great
kings, protect me.
Send not this roaming
soul hence again.
Don't you worry
about it, Lupin,
Old Pops is here to make
sure your roaming days
are over for good.
♪
I don't know about you,
but I got nothin'.
There's nothing to be done,
it's no use troubling your mind.
The entire thing's
in other hands now.
(groaning)
Lupin, I'm gettin'
really pissed off here!
Thank you, great kings.
I am delivered
from my enemies.
I rise!
Huh?
(gasping)
♪
It's the spirit of Pharaoh!
I know we're superstitious,
but are we
this superstitious?
Look, he's attached
to something.
Huh?
Son of a...
♪
(engine rumbling)
Huh?
♪
Just another cheap stunt,
huh, Lupin‐‐dammit!
(gunshots)
Come on!
♪
(shouting)
Fujiko!
Don't let him get away!
(exclaiming)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(yelling)
(car exploding)
♪
(honking)
‐Ah!
‐(gunshots)
♪
Hold on!
(crashing)
(exploding)
♪
(groans)
Grrr, damn you, Lupin!
♪
The sun sets and
the sun rises again.
The same sun
the Pharaohs worshiped
thousands of years ago.
Yes, you know our lives really
are just the blink of an eye.
‐Hmm?
♪
(sigh)
How's he doing
down there, anyway?
Once he knew we were headed
for the Valley of the Kings,
he smiled and
fell fast asleep.
Fujiko, is that the‐‐
Mm‐hmm, I'm so
ashamed of myself.
I just hope it's not
too late to return it.
♪
He fell asleep in my arms
babbling and shivering
it was unbearable
seeing him like that,
frail and frightened.
He was clinging to me
like a newborn baby.
Hey, are you all right?
Me‐‐yeah, sure.
It's just,
you know, I mean‐‐
he is the world's greatest
thief, after all.
♪
Yeah, that's right.
So, hurry up and get this
thing back where it belongs.
Done, take good care
of our boy, okay?
Mm‐hmm.
♪
(shouting)
Shh, take it easy now.
Ah, my face,
where's my face!
Lupin, please darling,
you'll only hurt yourself.
It's okay, baby,
I'm with you.
(exclaims)
(speaking in foreign tongue)
I've got to do something,
he's getting worse.
(yelling)
Excuse me, is there
a pharmacy nearby?
Uh...
Hey, Fujiko!
Oh, God, Zenigata!
Don't you dare
move a muscle.
Now, where's Lupin?
Of all the
people to run into.
Talk about bad luck.
Oh, please, please let
us go, just this once.
Fat chance, what do you take
me for‐‐King Tut's curse,
that's ridiculous.
(laughing)
(exclaims)
Ow.
Lupin, come on out,
the game's up.
Crap, where'd he go?
Crap, crap, crap!
He got away!
So, admit it, you were
just playing for time
with all that crap about the
mask having a curse on it.
No, it's true.
Look at that.
♪
Huh?
The blood on
the cuffs is his.
He had to yank
his hands free.
You know as well as I do,
Inspector, that if Lupin
were in his right mind, he could
just slip right out of them.
Hmm, you know you
got a point there.
So then, where would he be?
He must be in the
Valley Of the Kings.
(gasp)
(laughing)
Much obliged, Fujiko.
Well, Lupin, whether or
not you were cursed before,
it doesn't matter 'cause
you sure as hell are now!
Dammit!
So now it's
grave robbing, huh?
I guess that's what
you're reduced to
when you've ripped off
every living person
on the face of the Earth.
Where does it all end, Lupin,
animals, stuffed
animals, cartoons?
♪
The sun rises.
Yeah, with any luck at all
it'll mean a new day for Lupin.
We've done everything
we can at this point.
♪
It's disappeared.
(clock bell chiming)
Hey.
Don't.
Coochie coochie,
coochie coo.
Come on, stop it.
Huh, Lupin?
You were expecting
maybe King Tut?
Lupin!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
♪
So long, royal family.
Boy, I feel
like I'm waking up
from a 3,000 year old dream.
Believe me, it was
more like a nightmare.
Come on, princess.
♪
Maybe it's true,
I swear I hear voices.
What if it's really the ghost of
Tutankhamen calling out to me?
What if I end
up just like‐‐
Ooh!
(crashing)
(groaning)
No, it's just
a trick, gotta be.
Lupin!
So, how was I?
I mean, as a king.
Sick and scary.
I mean, you know,
before that.
Oh, you want
to know about‐‐
Uh‐huh.
No, you didn't bring out
the concubine in me.
(sob)
You were goofy.
You should have seen yourself.
Damn.
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
It's a trip, man, alone on
a train with a groovy chick
and damn, where'd
he come from?
Buttin' in again as usual.
But I just keep on truckin'
as long as
there's ugly bad guys
and a whole trainload
of stolen paintings,
even old Pops
can't harsh my buzz.
Meet me on the
Disorient Express.
Catch you later.
♪