♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(glass breaking)
(Japanese lyrics)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(Japanese lyrics)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪♪
♪
(boat tooting)
Whoa‐ho‐ho.
(gasps)
(louder gasps)
♪
(excited chatter)
Xièxiè.
♪
Huh?
Uh, have we met
before, my dear?
No, we haven't,
but I've always been
one of your
biggest fans, Master Chin.
How sweet of you.
Please excuse me
for just one moment
while I wash off my makeup.
Certainly.
(water running)
♪
You're not from
around here, aren't you?
Huh?
♪
Huh, uh, huh?
Hmm.
♪
Well, I'm not exactly
a slouch at the old
sleight of hand
myself, Master Chin.
Now there's nothing
left for me to do
but wait and listen.
♪
(typewriter keys clicking)
Uh.
♪
It's so damn hot.
Yep, that's him all right.
♪
I got you now!
(laughing)
Yep, sampan tells me
it's my lucky day.
(snicker)
♪
Ah, yeah, this is better.
Hmm?
Grrrr.
Oh no, not him.
♪
Hmm.
Wa‐ha!
(applause)
Hey, this guy's
pretty damn good.
‐Ah‐ha.
‐Huh?
So's that guy.
♪
And now for my
next trick, my friends,
I will require a courageous
volunteer from the audience.
I will, I will, I'll do it!
‐Hey!
‐No wait, not him!
‐Please?
‐Hold it right there, Lupin!
Lupin?
‐Huh?
‐What are you waiting for?
Hold it!
You're going to jail!
Sorry, occupied.
(struggling)
Oh well, all right then.
Our brave volunteer might
actually want some company.
This one's dangerous,
extremely dangerous, in fact.
Observe.
(dramatic grunting)
(gasps)
What have become of our
brave volunteer, my friends?
Observe.
(drum roll)
(laughing)
(shrieks)
What's Calista
Flockhart doing here?
(speaking Chinese)
♪
You have no idea how
grateful I am, thank you.
That's fine.
Anyway, I have a small favor
to ask of you in return.
You do?
I'm aware of your reputation.
You are Lupin the Third,
are you not, sir?
That's right.
How would you feel about
finding this person?
Whoa, I imagine I'd
feel pretty happy about it.
(giggle)
Her name is Coran, she
should be about 60 by now.
I've tried everything
I can, and well,
I'm afraid at this point
I don't know
where else I can turn.
Please, help me.
Well now, it is a bit
of a bait and switch,
but what the hell,
okay, I'll do it.
You did save my
sorry ass after all.
Oh, now it is I who
am grateful, Mr. Lupin.
Hey, Coshusan, sorry,
didn't know you had company.
You are never, ever to
call me that in public!
I thought you was alone.
But tell me,
how did it go?
Couldn't do nothin'.
Just as I expected.
Who's that?
His name is Lupin.
Huh, you mean like
Lupin the Third?
Shh, no, his grandfather.
Coshusan, Coshusan,
where have I
heard that name before?
Ugh!
Oh, be careful.
Uh, be careful?
That's it, hey what the
hell's the matter with you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
The "thaults" all mine.
In fact, I'm sure it must
have been all my fault.
Let me make it up to you.
Nice try, so long.
You're leaving?
♪
Wha?
Dammit, my wallet!
Oldest trick
in the damn book.
Grrr.
Uh, that's all?
What's this?
How can this be?
How can she be
a pickpocket?
♪
She's too beautiful.
Huh, holy crap!
Huh, that's great,
but didn't she say something
about leaving Hong Kong
for some shoe sale in Paris?
♪
Huh, I wonder
if she lied to me
or if her plans just changed?
Well, I think I
should go find out.
♪
This message came
in for you, Miss.
Huh?
He's waiting
in the lobby.
Really, huh?
♪
Hey, did she buy it?
Mm‐hmm.
So now, what's the little
minx been up to lately?
"Hmm, Coshusan is a
young research assistant
at the Ramen Museum
where Peking Man's bones
were formerly housed.
Since then, he's undergone
quite a remarkable
physical transformation
and reinvented himself as
master magician Chin Tonnan."
Huh.
Remarkable's
an understatement.
♪
And what's this for?
Hmm.
I don't know about getting
Lupin involved in this.
Just leave the
thinking to me.
Trust me, he's completely
in the dark, as is Coran.
Thanks to me she still believes
that Peking Man's skull
was actually that
of her beloved husband
who was killed in the war.
Peking Man's skull.
Huh, now I get it.
It was Coshusan who
stole it from the museum.
But why'd you give
it to her anyway?
Simple, I knew that the black
market value of the bones
would only
appreciate over time.
So then I needed to store
the bones somewhere secure
and I thought to myself,
what on earth
could be more secure
than the ancestral crypt
of a good family?
Huh.
But the war
changed everything.
The family was ruined,
the crypt was emptied,
and she and the bones
both disappeared.
Ah, I get it.
Very interesting,
so that's it.
♪
Uh‐oh.
Let's mess with
her head a little bit.
♪
I'm gonna have
to ask that waiter
what this mystery
man looked like.
♪
Dammit all!
Aah!
I don't care, check
every hole in the city!
I know for a fact that weasel's
somewhere in Hong Kong!
This just doesn't
make any sense at all.
Why is Zenigata's frequency
coming over my radio?
Uh‐‐where'd this come from?
"Warning?"
"Warning, Chin's an ace
at making things disappear.
Hate for you
to be one of them.
Love, Lupin."
Ah, Lupin?
Grrrr.
♪
Now for a little homework.
So, what have we here?
Okay, "sinanthropus
pekinensis,
a prehistoric man
of the Pleistocene.
Its bones were found
near Beijing in 1929,
but disappeared
during World War II
when scientists attempted
to secretly ship them
out of the country
to protect them
from the occupying
Japanese army."
Hmm, ah, a major mystery
of the 20th century,
and probably worth a
fricken fortune by now.
Yeah, but what the hell
are you gonna do with them
when you find 'em?
Argh, "do with them"?
What the hell do you think
I'm gonna do with them, huh?
I'm gonna keep them in the
damn Lupin the Third Museum!
You know, I think you're a
little crazy from the heat, man.
I just came here for a
leisurely holiday in Hong Kong.
A leisurely holiday, huh,
sittin' in a hotel room
drinkin' scotch all day?
Hmm.
How about you?
Grrr, ugh, fine,
you two just sit here
and vegetate all day!
♪
We've got a freakin' heat wave
and this lunatic wants to chase
after a bunch of old bones.
♪
(gunshot)
Sorry, lover, but now
that you've gone ahead
and stuck your
nose in my business,
I really have no choice
but to keep tabs on you.
(beeping)
(ship tooting)
Man, it's no fair.
The picture Chin gave me
was the only damn clue I had.
Fricken pickpocket,
where are you, huh?
Come on, baby.
I know it was
somewhere around here.
♪
Hey, that was Lupin!
I know it was him!
It has to be him.
Hey, stop that guy!
Hey, get back here, you,
or I kick your‐‐
Hiya!
Ah, shut up!
Argh!
You hold it right there, you!
Oh, crap.
(whistle blowing)
♪
Dammit.
‐Over here.
‐Uh‐oh.
There he is!
‐Okay, careful now.
‐Oh, mommy.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Well, well, well, hmm.
A rat in the sack.
(laughing)
Yes, the moment of truth
has finally arrived, Lupin.
It may have been
a long time comin',
but at last,
you're under arrest!
Okay, get him, boys.
Yah!
♪
Hey, aren't you...
Grrrr, I'm taking
you in, sister,
for obstruction of justice.
Grrrr!
♪
It's Bruce Lee in drag.
Yah!
Yah, yah!
♪
Wow, very cool stuff.
Consider the pickpocketing
thing forgotten.
Come, quickly.
Where are you going?
This way.
Oh, I knew that.
Hurry.
Won't fall on me, will it?
Agh, brr.
Hey, wait, freeze!
You're under arrest.
You for helping him and you for,
well, just about everythi‐‐
Argh, wahh!
♪
So, tell me your name.
Shanran.
I've been looking for you.
Think you can give me back
that picture you took from me?
I've been looking
for you, as well.
Huh?
Tell me what you were doing
with this in the first place.
Oh, well, I'm just
returning a favor to someone
by helping him find
this person, that's all.
Why do you ask?
Do you know her?
Yes.
That woman is my mother.
What, are you kidding me?
Here.
Look.
I'm afraid that I‐‐
but I mean I‐‐
I don't believe it.
Why in the world wouldn't you?
Excuse me,
but it's just that...
Your father,
he died 40 years ago
and you're not nearly 40.
My mother remarried
after the war ended.
I'm the product
of her second marriage.
Oh, I get it now, sorry.
♪
Okay, that the place?
Yes, sir.
So then, your mother,
do you see her often?
I mean, does
she live around here?
‐She's dead.
‐Oh.
‐It's been 15 years.
‐Sorry.
Where is she buried?
She wasn't buried.
Oh, uh then
she was cremated?
Her ashes are at
the Kofuku Temple.
They're in a
communal charnel there
along with those of her
first husband and my father.
Sorry to ask, but do
you happen to have anything
that would prove
everything you just said?
You mean like a contract
from the temple?
Like this?
Yeah, this is exactly the kind
of thing that I was loo‐‐
(laughing)
Oh, yeah,
alone with a girl.
Hey, come on in,
Pops, have a seat.
You're just in
time for the show.
Now, just an
ordinary table cloth.
Right.
But then... abracadabra.
(drum roll)
The guy's damn good.
Where the hell did he‐‐
Lupin, dammit!
Grrr.
Quick, he's getting away!
Okay, I got the bus' number.
Hiya!
♪
Hey, what in the world
was that all about, anyway?
Hands in the air right now.
Like this?
Ugh!
‐Ahh!
Hiya!
Lupin, hold it!
I had something
else to tell you!
♪
Sorry, Chin, but thanks
to this little contract,
those old bones
are as good as mine.
(horn honking)
I'm telling you, Coshusan,
Lupin should have
been in touch by now.
And I'm telling you this,
this is a tough assignment,
even for the great Lupin.
‐Bull.
‐Oh?
♪
Who the hell?
Aren't you the one who‐‐
Mm‐hmm, your biggest fan.
In fact, next to Peking Man,
you're my favorite old fossil.
I assume that's the real
reason you sought me out.
I think you and I should
enter into a partnership,
Peking Man
Limited Partnership,
a third of which
will be my share.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
If that's so, then you should
mind hearing that right now
Lupin's well on his way to
snatching those old bones
right out from under you.
He what?
What is this thing?
This is how
I'm tracking him,
but I don't
want to bore you.
I mean, you have no idea
what I'm talking about.
Well, the truth is‐‐
We all know
what the truth is,
so let's just
cut to the chase.
Lupin may have
a head start on us,
but he doesn't know
we're on to him.
And he's not looking
to sell the bones.
That's where we're different.
Only things I collect are gems,
precious metals, and cash.
So, partners?
♪
Partners.
Good.
(bells ringing)
Let's see now, 1035,
1045, 1047, ah, 1048.
♪
Okay, this is it.
Mm‐hmm.
Aaah!
What the?
Ah!
Bastards!
♪
Ah, guess that
dissolves the partnership.
Sh!
That's him!
This has been
a real breeze, man.
I think you're my lucky charm.
Yee‐aaah!
Thanks for everything, Lupin.
You son of a b‐‐
♪
Hey, Fujiko!
See there, that's what
happens to nosy people.
Grrrr.
♪
How do you feel about
the pinch hitter rule?
Hey, I had him.
‐Grrrr.
‐Yeah, right.
I did!
You were cowering.
I was crouching
ready to pounce.
‐Grrr!
‐Hey, look up there.
Huh?
(helicopter blades whirring)
I want you to protect
that urn with your very life.
Yeah‐‐huh?
Some kind of chopper
closing in on us.
Gotta be that damn Lupin.
Hmm.
Yep, that's them all right.
Good work, Jigen.
Once again, we have
Fujiko to thank
that this whole damn thing
went friggen haywire.
You're my hero, Jigen.
Well, hey, it is
a little bit more fun
than hanging out in an
air conditioned movie theater.
♪
‐Ah!
‐Oh!
(whistle blowing)
A freakin' checkpoint!
The same cop who
was chasing Lupin.
Police, hold it right there!
♪
We meet again, Inspector.
Hey, you're
that magician guy.
Yes, I apologize
for the other‐‐
‐Huh!
‐Listen, you.
I want to know where that
guy is you made disappear,
you understand?
Come on, out with it!
‐Don't play games with me!
‐I don't know, really.
‐I'm giving you one last chance!
‐I don't know.
Dammit, now we got
to go through Pops
to get that damn urn back.
Wait, I got an idea.
Come on, spill it!
Please, let go.
Tell me now, come on!
Oh‐‐huh?
♪
Oh, isn't that the guy
right over there?
Huh?
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
What the hell?
Aah!
Somebody grab that guy!
You're not getting away!
Gotcha!
(laughing)
♪
Okay, let's get
one thing straight here,
you drop that urn
and I'm gonna drop you.
I won't drop it, I swear.
Grrrr, all right, I'm
coming to get you, Lupin.
Grrrr, hey, careful what
you're grabbin' hold of!
Hey, Lupin, keep it
steady down there.
All right,
you're under arrest!
Now, come on.
Sorry, but my hands
aren't free right now.
♪
I'll have to settle
for your foot then.
I can't control this thing.
♪
(glass breaking)
(groaning)
Where the hell are we?
(footsteps running)
What happened?
That's Zenigata.
Officer, were you here
when this thing occurred?
I was just down the hall,
sir, having a bowel movement.
Thank you, officer,
that's too much information.
I'd say I really
urned this one.
(snicker)
Urned it, that's a good one.
Easy now, Inspector,
are you all right?
Lupin!
I even had the
handcuffs on him.
No, don't tell me
the bastard's gone!
♪
Keep the change, man.
Really?
Sure.
Good evening, all your
company's arrived, Mr. Lupin.
Mmm, thanks very much.
Here, that's for you.
But‐‐uh?
Please.
It's over $1,000 dollars.
Yeah, well the bones
rolled my way today.
Take care now.
♪
(whistling)
Honey, I'm home.
Okay now, thanks
for waiting, everyone.
Uh.
Someone die or somethin'?
What the hell's
going on here?
Hello.
Shanran?
Perfect, it's appropriate
you should be here
to witness
the great unveiling.
She's got a little
unveiling of her own for you.
Huh?
Unfortunately, I didn't have
a chance to tell you this
before you ran off yesterday.
You see, there
was a terrible fire
at the Kofuku temple
about ten years ago
and everything, including
the Charnel House,
was completely destroyed.
If that's true,
then what's in here?
It contains treasured
remnants of some of my
more recently
deceased relatives.
So, I'll bet a
nice belt of scotch
is sounding pretty good
right about now, huh?
♪
Sorry, Jigen,
but I don't think
there's enough damn
scotch in the world.
♪ Lupin the Third ♪♪
Next time, me buckos,
it's plunder down under,
or anyway, that's the idea.
But our plans go asunder
when Pops makes a plunder
that knocks the whole
thing on its ear.
And G‐man and Fuji
are off in Miami,
which makes for a real
screwed up double whammy.
It's all a big pain
in the rear‐‐ouch!
Catch you later in "Lion,
Cheatin', and Stealin'."
♪