♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(glass breaks)
(singing in Japanese)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(singing in Japanese)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Wow.
(bats screech)
♪
Professor, you
won't believe this.
We just got all
the results back,
and the stratum where
the casket was discovered
is 2,000 years old.
Hmm.
Well, gentlemen.
I'd say that means
we have a genuine
archeological mystery
on our hands here.
Yes, and a medical one too.
Yes.
(struggling)
Over here.
Gently.
Oh!
And if this is indeed
what it appears to be,
gentlemen, then the
mystery is perhaps
less one for us to ponder
than it is for
the theologians.
See this devout young woman?
If the golden statue
of the mother of Christ
she's clasping there can
be taken at face value,
then her exemplary faith
has somehow kept her alive
in a state of suspended
animation for 2,000 years!
Well, it's damn strange.
Hmm.
(car approaches)
Professor, the
transport has arrived.
Ah, the medical
establishment
back at Tokyo is
understandably anxious
to have a look
at this young lady.
And as for me, well,
I'm going to subject
that statue to every
test that's even
remotely imaginable.
Men, please be extremely
careful with that now!
Don't worry, Professor.
That thing is in
good hands now.
Who might you be?
Inspector Zenigata
at your service.
Pleased to meet you.
So, this is really it?
You can take it from me,
you've got a priceless
artifact and a pretty
girl on your hands.
Even if she's only
technically alive,
that's catnip to Lupin.
But, now that I'm here, sir,
you might say that the cat
in question's been fixed.
(cackles)
Hey, you!
Damn it, get back here, you!
That's government property!
D'oh!
(typewriter keys clicking)
♪
(cards being ruffled)
Uh, I'm out.
Sorry about that, Lupin.
But, you know, you
just can't fight fate.
There's just something
ominous about this one.
Every friggin'
sign points to it.
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
Hey, Jigen, let's try
the sticks one more time, hm?
(moans)
What is it, Goemon?
Tell me, would you?
(speaks Japanese)
Basically, a rough
translation of which would be:
Don't be such an idiot.
Lupin, see?
Give me a break!
It's just a bunch of sticks.
Why don't you just
read the entrails
of a deformed cat fetus
while you're at it, huh?
You guys should be
ashamed of yourselves.
The whole enlightenment
thing was wasted on you.
♪
(bat screeches)
(wings flapping)
♪
Well, how is our patient?
Um, all her vital
signs, Doctor,
appear to be normal.
Extraordinary!
Huh?
Nurse?
Ah, where did she go?
Tell me something, would you?
Was that window
open before?
♪
(wolf howls)
All done for the day?
Mm‐hmm.
Now then...
this baby here is gonna
help you sleep easy at night.
(lock clicks)
Once you lock it,
anyone else who
even touches it is in for
the surprise of their life,
or perhaps I should
say a big shock!
(yelps)
Like that.
And anyway,
that surveillance
camera there will be
running 24 hours a day
just in case.
I'm counting on
you, Inspector.
Mm‐hmm.
Because, Inspector,
inside that safe
is an object whose value
is quite possibly
beyond calculation.
It is truly priceless.
Just you leave it to me.
Yeah, please, Professor.
Leave it up to him.
(chuckles)
Just be sure to keep
the statue safe
in that contraption,
then make sure good
old Zenigata monitors
the video and then,
well, we'll see
just who ends up
being shocked.
♪
(bats screech)
(glass breaks)
(lock clicks)
(chuckles)
(wolf growls)
♪
Hey, did you see that, Jigen?
Sure did.
(horse gallops)
A carriage without
a driver led by a lone wolf
doesn't make any sense.
♪
Yeah, and did you see
that friggin' coffin
sitting in the back
of that carriage?
I should've listened to
those damn sticks of yours.
Although, on the subject
of the obligations
of friendship,
the sticks remain silent.
Lupin is still our friend.
(bats screech)
Now...
(lock clicks)
Huh.
(chuckles)
And that's it.
Hot damn!
(slurping)
Impossible!
(groans)
Damn it, Lupin!
Lupin!
There.
I'd like to thank the Academy,
and all the little people
who made this possible,
especially a certain Inspector.
(wolf growls)
You don't really want me.
I just wet myself.
(growls)
(grunts)
Lupin, I know you're
here somewhere!
So...
(growling)
Eh...
Yah!
Get back here!
Son of a bitch.
Look there.
It's that carriage again.
(horse galloping)
♪
Damn, if only that
friggin' carriage
would just pull
the hell over,
I can catch him!
♪
(tires screeching)
(crash)
Damn it, are you insane?
What in the hell is
the matter with you,
you freakin' moron!
♪
All right,
come on out, bub.
I got a bone to
pick with you.
Hold on, wait just a second.
Huh!
Oh, man.
I hope it's not...
Whoa.
Amazing, get a load
of this babe.
There's something that
doesn't seem quite right here.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
She's alive!
(wolf growling)
♪
(gulps)
Her pulse is fine.
Her complexion sure
looks like crap, though...
(hiccups)
You, uh, you are
a real doctor, right?
Yeah, I'm pretty
sure that's right.
Wait just a second.
She's got a couple
of things on her neck.
A couple of "things"?
(laughs)
Just hickies I'll bet.
(bat screeches)
♪
Hey, you know something?
That's the same friggin'
wolf that tried to kill me.
Probably working for Lupin.
If I could only stay
on his tail long enough.
♪
(snoring)
So, how you feeling?
I can't believe it!
Huh?
(curtains flapping)
Hmm.
Hey, mystery girl!
Uh, yoo‐hoo,
where are you?
Come on back now.
Hey, I mean it!
Let's face it, you're
really not in any shape‐‐
Really?
I think my shape's just fine.
Yes, why, of course it is.
In fact, I just wanted to
find you to tell you that.
That is, if that's
all right with you.
(chuckles)
Shut up and
kiss me, you fool.
Yeah!
All righty, then, sure.
Yup.
Oh, you know
who's your daddy.
All right, then.
Pucker up.
Mm, come here.
(hissing)
Stop, Lupin, no!
Leave him alone!
(growls)
You, get away from him.
That coochie's
a blood‐sucking bitch.
What in the hell is the
matter with you guys anyway?
Now, you take that
back right this minute
or I'm gonna‐‐
(laughs)
I'm afraid that your
furry friend is right.
Not that it really
matters anymore.
You see, I've just
given you the kiss
of eternal life,
and you are one
of us now!
Come away!
(cackling)
♪
Watch it!
Wait!
‐Damn.
‐Come on, let's go.
♪
(evil cackling)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
Hibachi Village?
Heburai Village.
It means "Hebrew."
Oh, yeah, right.
This is where they first
found the casket, huh?
Hmm, did you hear
something over there?
(guitar playing)
♪ You ain't nothin'
but a hound dog ♪
Yeah!
♪ Won't you wear
my ring, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, baby,
in the ghetto ♪
Huh?
Hi there, and welcome
to Graveland, little darlings.
Yeah.
Well, this is the very
spot where Jesus
met His maker.
Well, where He met
Him again, you might say.
So, the whole thing in
the Bible about Golgotha...
just a big lie?
I wouldn't call
it a lie, baby.
I prefer to think
of it as a myth, mama.
Just like Elvis dying.
(grunts)
(guitar pings)
Fujiko?
Are you all right?
I mean, that was bizarre.
Thanks, I'm better now.
Better than what?
What happened?
Well, I actually
came here looking
for that golden statue,
and I happened
to run into Lupin,
but he didn't leer at me,
or try to cop
a feel or anything.
It was very disturbing.
Well, the guy's had
a pretty rotten day.
I mean, he's
a friggin' vampire now.
What?!
Tell us, where is he?
Over there.
Mount Onahini.
There's an old castle
overlooking the lake.
(lightning strikes)
(rain pounding)
Oh, come on, guys.
This is the pits, literally.
I mean, it's starting
to smell like Pavarotti's
armpits in here.
Yeah, well, I'm sorry
about that, pal,
but when it comes
to vampires, I don't
take any chances.
I mean, I know your
family's been Shinto
for, like, 10 generations‐‐
‐Longer.
‐But that doesn't mean
crap to a vampire.
You know, there's something
very offensive about that.
(sighs)
No way to get up
that mountain tonight.
Only an idiot would
dare to attempt it.
What the hell
am I doing up here?
I'm scared of thunder,
I'm scared of heights!
(wind blowing)
And I really, really
need to scratch my butt.
(yelps)
Don't look down,
don't look down!
Ah!
(shrieks)
(screams)
Hey, somebody help!
♪
(evil cackle)
(fire crackling)
(window creaks)
♪
(Fujiko shrieks)
Jigen, Goemon!
♪
Ah, dammit,
he's getting away.
(Fujiko screams)
Lupin.
Help!
I was kinda hoping that
this whole damn thing
was some sort
of a nightmare.
Well, at least Fujiko
doesn't have to worry
about Lupin not
wanting her anymore.
(lightning strikes)
(motorboat hums)
(piano plays)
♪
(steps approaching)
Ah, Countess Camilla,
the lovely mistress of my soul.
That which you requested
I humbly present to you.
Tell me, are you
thoroughly pleased
with your slave?
Hmm.
I truly am, yes.
And what may I do with her
now that she
belongs to us?
You may go now
and prepare yourself
for a special celebration.
I want you to make
a very good impression
on your new family.
The girl will make
a lovely offering.
(laughs)
♪
Oh, yeah, piece of cake.
Perfectly accessible
for anyone who can
turn into a bat.
Hmm.
Hey, Goemon,
look down there.
♪
(door creaks open)
I have prepared
myself, Camilla.
Is the hour yet upon us?
It is, my eager one.
And even now
the music I play
penetrates beneath
these stone floors
to summon your
brethren who have
long lain in slumber there
awaiting this moment.
♪
(casket lid rumbling)
(bat screeches)
♪
Actually, it all began
over 2,000 years ago.
On another magic night
in a shabby stall
at the edge of Bethlehem,
my mother, Mary,
gave birth to twins,
a boy and a girl.
I was born with fangs.
♪
My father, Joseph,
was afraid and abandoned me
in a cave.
There, I was befriended
by the bats and suckled
buy a she‐wolf.
Years later, as a dire omen
of my future intentions,
I absconded with the sacred
golden statue of my mother.
I traveled for years,
but growing weary of it,
finally brought my
peregrinations to an end
at Heburai Village where,
like your brothers and sisters,
I settled down
for a long sleep.
And your twin brother?
Lupin, you must understand
one thing very clearly now.
In your new family,
it is forbidden
to even mention
the name of my brother.
♪
Welcome, my beloved
brothers and sisters.
Tonight we celebrate not only
our long‐awaited reunion,
but also the initiation
of our new brother,
Lupin the Third.
And to consecrate this event,
behold the living sacrifice!
(evil laughter)
May her death
inaugurate a new era
in which our family
finally reigns victorious.
(lightning strikes)
♪
Oh, pardon me.
Goemon, what are
you doing here?
We heard about this
party from the ferryman.
Sounded like a lot of fun.
Yeah, that's right, man.
And since we figured
the crosses and the garlic
didn't work on you,
this party must be
open to anybody.
Ah, dammit.
What's the matter with you?
They can see our
reflections in the mirror.
Uh‐oh.
If these three
are any indication
of the quality
of resistance
we can expect to meet,
we can conquer the world
after dinner and be all
tucked up in our
coffins by dawn.
Hey, that's insulting!
(Goemon grunting)
♪
Hurry now, Fujiko.
Come on!
Well, prepare
for a feast now,
brothers and sisters.
Yes, it's all you can suck.
(gunshots)
(grunting, growling)
♪
(hissing)
(glass breaks)
♪
No way out.
That's right, my friend.
Eat some garlic, bitch.
(screeches)
♪
(shrieks)
(screams)
Whoa.
♪
Well...
I sure won't be
needing these anymore.
You mean you were
just pretending?
Wait a minute, Lupin.
You were bitten by
that bitch, weren't you?
Something just happened
to come between us.
(church bell rings)
Oh, man, you have no
idea what I went through
to get this.
But since there's
a possibility you do,
I'm giving it back to you.
I need it more than him.
(struggling)
The sticks were sure right!
(speaks Japanese)
‐Huh?
‐Someone's coming.
Here!
(door creaks)
Feel kind of
cheesy about this.
Last time I prayed,
it was for a two‐wheeler.
It's Zenigata.
So, uh, I don't know
if you're up there or not,
but I'm starting to wonder
if I'm in the right line
of work and I just
thought maybe you could,
well, I don't know,
sort of, well...
Show you some sort
of sign, is that it?
Huh‐‐ah!
Hey, this prayer
stuff really works!
♪
Wow, I really can't
believe this!
(laughs)
I mean, I do believe,
of course, I do.
Look, I don't want
to be greedy or anything,
but there's this guy...
I know of whom you speak!
He's far away
in Death Valley.
Oh, oh!
Death Valley, thanks!
I gotta get to Death Valley!
I'm gonna get you
this time, Lupin.
Oh, boy!
This is gonna be great!
(laughs)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
A lovely party
full of lovely people
wearing lovely
brooches and crap,
and then wouldn't
you know it?
A bunch of smelly
apes have to burst in
and ruin the whole thing.
I hate it when
that happens.
Someone's gonna have to
teach these brutes a lesson,
and I swear as soon
as I stop cowering
behind the bar,
I'm gonna find them.
You just see if I don't.
Next time in
"Gorilla Tactics."
Catch you later!
♪