♪
♪ Lup ♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
♪
(glass breaks)
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
♪
(gun clicks)
Maybe I should
bring this too.
♪
Better safe than sorry.
Um...
Mm‐hmm.
♪
This is great!
I can't believe it.
I finally found
his hideout.
Today, after
years of failure,
I'm finally gonna
cuff the bastard.
Hmm?
♪
What... what...
Hey, what's going
on here anyway?
♪
Uh, listen, you better
come along with me right now.
Pops, I can't play right now.
Sorry!
Gotta go, take care.
Oh, wait, Lupin, hey!
♪
Not so fast, wise guy.
(grunts)
Whoa!
(yells)
Help, somebody help!
(explosion)
Hang in there, guys.
I'm on my way.
Lupin, this is gonna
sound real weird,
and it is.
We're being held in
some little remote burg
in the sticks somewhere.
Place called Gemallschaft.
It's not even
on the map.
Real spooky place.
Try to find us, will you?
It's not looking good.
(typewriter keys click)
♪
So, that's it?
Gemallschaft, huh.
(bell tolls)
Looks just like any other
peaceful, boring village.
(car door opens, shuts)
(engine revs)
(tires screech)
Hmm, did I say peaceful?
More like comatose.
Anyone home?
♪
What in the freaking
hell is that?
♪
(man yells)
Huh?
♪
‐Loser.
‐Serves him right.
♪
(door creaks open)
‐Sister Labina.
‐We're not worthy!
Sister Labina!
Thank you.
♪
Reflect upon number 108,
the path to enlightenment
lay before him,
but he put his trust
in his feeble mind
instead of his faith.
Let this serve as
a lesson to all of you
who wish to avoid
the fate of number 108.
The sound of a bell
will bring peace
to all those of
childlike innocence.
There is no other
way but this way.
(bell tolls)
Come forth 106 and 107.
What?
Please take this carcass
from my sight immediately.
Peace.
♪
So, you said something
about being held prisoner.
What gives?
Yeah, well, I was
mistaken about that, Lupin.
It's really just
a place to pursue
spiritual enlightenment.
Well, that's all
fine and good,
but you're not
into it or anything?
Well, actually Lupin,
ever since I arrived here
I've been thinking about
the benefits of a more
righteous life.
You two are just
messing with my mind.
Would you give me a break?
Righteous, you?
Inner peace is nothing
to mock, Lupin.
You might try it yourself.
Um...
I am talking to
Goemon Ishikawa, aren't I?
It takes a little while.
You'll understand.
Are you guys afraid
of something?
Is it her?
Is it that woman?
Are you worried that
you'll end up like him
if you disobey?
Well, have no fear,
Lupin's here.
After all, she's just
another woman, right?
(whirring)
How dare you, Lupin.
Take it back.
Recant or die.
Okay then, okay,
whatever you want.
♪
(echoed footsteps)
(whack)
♪
Labina, is that
your real name?
♪
Just what the hell
are you up to?
My calling, my job.
Just helping all
the villagers here
attain inner peace.
Right, inner peace
my skinny ass.
My two friends
have gone crazy.
Ah, you mean numbers
106 and 107?
Hey, they have
names, you know.
Goemon and Jigen.
And I'll be taking them back
home with me now, Sister.
That's fine.
Providing it's what
they want to do.
Huh?
Don't you have numerous
sins of your own to repent?
You could move in here
and start a whole new
life for yourself.
Yeah, or a whole
new afterlife,
as the case may be.
I know the idea takes
some getting used to,
it does, but you'll
adjust, or not.
♪
Heavenly, just heavenly.
Here 107.
Now, tell me honestly,
does that smell
divine or what?
It's all fresh, picked
from our own garden.
♪
Hah, well,
what a surprise!
Nice and easy now.
Don't try any
sudden moves.
Ahh!
Hot, hot, hot, hot.
Where are you?
‐Huh?
(grunting)
Hah, there,
I finally got you.
Aren't you gonna
try to escape?
Isn't that basically
how we play this?
Hey, Jigen, why would
we want to escape?
Because, well,
because, um...
it's your destiny,
it's what you guys do.
Lupin, we both know it's you.
‐Huh?
‐Come on, now.
You gotta believe us,
we're all done with
that life of crime.
♪
And both of you really
believes what you're saying?
‐Mm‐hmm.
♪
I refuse to believe this.
This isn't like
either one of them.
Hmm.
♪
That bell again.
How often does
that damn thing ring?
(bell tolls)
♪
Huh?
Jigen, uh, Goemon?
Where'd they go?
♪
Hey, guys,
kinda early, isn't it?
(moans)
Aw, come on,
it's ridiculous.
What's the matter
with you guys?
Are you trying
to piss me off?
Come on, get up!
‐(Goemon and Jigen scream)
‐Get out of there!
Ah!
(whirring)
Hey, guys, are you
feeling all right?
You're a demon.
No, really, I'm not!
(panting)
Yes, you are.
You're trying to deprive us
of a peaceful sleep!
Hey, let's calm down
and talk this thing out, okay?
(cocks gun)
(Lupin whimpers)
(gunshots)
Hey, hey, Jigen,
careful there.
Demon, die, now!
(screams)
(glass breaks)
Hear the bell,
the peaceful bell.
Such a peaceful sound.
They weren't kidding around.
I was really damn
lucky to get out of there
with my life.
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
(bell tolls)
♪
Welcome, my brothers
and sisters.
May you greet
the new day
with a renewed commitment
to follow the teachings,
and thereby attain
inner peace‐‐
(yawns)
I got to admit,
I did have an unusually
peaceful sleep last night.
Modern technology's
really a wonderful thing.
Okay, today...
I got to expose that nun.
♪
(shoots hook)
Starting with this thing.
♪
Hmm, seems like there's
nothing out of the ordinary
about it.
Hey, wait a minute.
That's weird.
The sound's not right.
Let's see.
♪
A speaker, I don't get it.
Why not just have
a real bell?
Hmm?
♪
Interesting.
Hmm, I wonder...
(plays tune on organ)
♪
Mm‐hmm, I think I got it.
(two notes)
Whoa!
♪
Huh, beginner's luck.
(echoed footsteps)
Gemallschaft experimental
village reporting.
No glitches to report.
We remain on schedule.
As of this posting,
over 100 test subjects
have been successfully converted
and are ready for transport.
The initial stage
of the Lupin project
requested by the president
is also underway,
expecting a positive result.
What result, hmm?
(gasps)
(chuckles)
I, but, how did you know?
Hmm.
Wow.
♪
This is some set up, Sister,
I gotta hand it to you.
It's very impressive.
‐Hmm.
‐Don't touch that!
What's this?
Hypnotherapy
during sleep
and the effect of
audio waves on the brain.
Very interesting documentation.
So, you wanna tell me,
Sister Labina,
exactly who the hell
you really are?
I have a doctorate
in psychology.
Which makes all these
villagers, what?
Just guinea pigs?
Well, yes, more or less.
To make them more
susceptible to suggestion.
Understand?
And the point of all this?
There's a big market
for such people
all over the world.
Soldiers and workers
who are willing to do
what they're told
without any question.
Willing drones
for the military
industrial complex.
Now, there's just
one thing I'd like
to know about you, okay?
Why is it that the
hypnotherapy bell
had no apparent
effect on you?
I'm a real easily
distracted kind of guy.
I gotta have it
real quiet at night.
I find these things
do the job.
Hah, well, I must say,
you were very lucky,
for a while, anyway.
Uh...
so I guess this is it, right?
Bye bye, Lupin.
Luck's fickle.
A terrible waste of
a promising guinea pig.
(shoots gun)
Sorry, Sister, didn't
mean to lose my head.
Toodles!
What the hell was that?
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
Very creative, Mr. Lupin.
But you're never going to
get out of the village alive.
(bell tolls)
(chatter)
(panting)
♪
Excuse me, 106, 107?
‐Yes, Sister Labina.
Come a bit closer, my brothers.
Yes, Sister.
Be good boys now
and go to sleep.
‐Uh...
(coughs)
Sorry, but I'm really
doing all this
for your own good, fellas.
♪
♪ Lupin, Lupin,
Lupin, Lupin, Lupin ♪
♪
♪ I'm the one
everybody's waiting for ♪
♪ Lupin ♪
♪ Scream for me ♪
Actually thinks
he's getting away.
♪
I'm sure she thinks
she's got some other
surprises in store for me.
♪ Lupin, Lupin,
Lupin, Lupin, Lupin ♪
Yeah, there it is,
I knew it.
Whatever it is,
it's history.
♪
(explosion)
(tires skid)
And that is that.
♪
Oh man, that may
not be that.
♪
(tires screech)
Whatever it is,
it's persistent.
(engine revs)
♪
(loud splash)
Okay, pal,
catch me if you can.
♪
(bubbling)
Damn, I didn't mean it.
♪
(yelps)
Yah!
♪
(snoring)
So, Lupin, do you see
now that it's futile
to try to escape from here?
Last chance now.
Would you care to accept
our invitation and join
our brotherhood?
You heard me, Sister.
No one's gonna tell me
how to live my life.
Too bad then.
Wake up 106 and 107.
♪
Kill that man
for Sister Labina.
You're not really gonna...
(whirring)
(whimpers)
Wait, Jigen,
come on, wake up.
(gun clocks)
Hey, guys, it's me.
Hey!
What about all the
good times we had, huh?
♪
Peace.
There's no way out now, Lupin.
Either your friends kill you
or I bring you back down
here and we finish the job.
(laughs)
(groans)
Damn‐‐what?
♪
Cornered in a damn bubble.
What have I got to lose?
(gunshot)
(chuckles)
(gunshots)
(metal clang)
Oh, no, damn it all.
The bell!
(groaning)
My head is pounding!
Somebody, you gotta
stop it, please!
♪
I can't believe it.
It was working!
Working so well!
‐I‐‐
‐Until it failed completely,
that is.
♪
I really should've
expected this.
I was told you were
a very special case.
I suppose I should
be flattered, but...
Somehow I'm not really.
You know, I'm rather
special myself.
♪
You'll pay for this!
(grunting)
Boy, you don't give up.
♪
Uh, huh?
Whoa, some psychologist.
Count on it, Lupin.
We'll meet again someday.
I'm coming for you.
I don't know,
I'm kind of old fashioned.
I like to be the
aggressor, you know?
Oh, please.
That thing's not
gonna work on me.
We'll see.
♪
(gasps)
No, it can't be.
(gas hisses)
Have a gas, Labina!
♪
Oh, no, I have
to get out of here.
No!
♪
Bye now, see you,
wouldn't wanna be you!
♪
(screams)
Why do I feel like I just
had a real bad dream?
Hey, Jigen, I was
living in your bad dream.
Sorry, Lupin.
Oh, don't worry yourselves.
So, guys, tell me the truth.
I mean, sure, you were
hypnotized and all,
I know that, but wasn't
there a small part
of each of you that
enjoyed scaring
the crap out of me?
Yeah, I guess,
on some sort of
subconscious level,
it did have its appeal.
All human relationships
are rather complex.
Ah‐hah, I thought so.
Well, lots of luck
finding your way home.
See you later!
Hey, Lupin, wait.
Come on, I was kidding!
Come back here!
Come on!
‐Lupin!
♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
So, let's see, what
happens in the next one?
I shoot Fujiko
and kill her and...
Wait a minute,
did I just say that?
Holy crap, what have I done?
It all started out
so innocently too.
We were just trying to rip
off this billionaire guy.
And, well,
I'm running out of time.
It's call "Charity
Begins at Home."
Catch you later!
♪