♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(shattering)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
"Dear Diary, how are you?
I'm fine.
In fact, I'm wonderful
'cause today's the day
I've been waiting
for my whole life.
Well, not my whole
life, but most of it.
At least three years."
Wow, there it is.
It's beautiful.
It says there were
only 12 ever made.
Hand‐carved stamps,
I never heard of such a thing.
Coincidentally,
or magically,
every known owner of
the Cinderella Shadow
has either been a princess
or gone on to become one.
Well, they say
Grace Kelly had one
before she was
Princess Grace.
Get out of town.
Ah!
No touching the case
now, sweetheart.
Oh.
Hmm!
As soon as I have
you for my very own,
I'm gonna have a
big princess party
with everybody in
beautiful ball gowns
and bowing to me and
giving me stuff, and...huh?
(screeching)
(gasping)
(indistinct chattering)
(screeching)
(shouting)
♪
(screeching)
Aw, it's just a big,
smiley kitty cat.
Oh!
♪
Ah!
Wait!
(grunting)
No!
(humming)
(gasping)
Damn it, shut this
place down now!
(screeching)
(tapping of typewriter keys)
♪
(whirring)
So how'd it go down there?
Well, let's just say
you're gonna have to start
addressing me as,
"Your Extreme Loveliness."
Actually you're
already a royal pain.
There's just one
minor complication.
‐Hmm?
‐Uh, well, ya see...
What the hell?
Now what's this all about?
‐Hmm.
‐Lupin?
‐Ask her.
‐I want my stamp.
‐Give it to me!
‐Are you crazy?
Hey, get off me, will ya?
Give me my stamp now!
Well, no one said it was gonna
be easy being a princess.
Seriously, Jigen,
I'm gonna fall!
All right, hold on.
♪
Okay, let's go.
Uh, Lupin, what
is going on here?
Well, I'm...not really
sure myself exactly.
Look, I'll handle it.
Listen, kid,
you're real cute,
but you're not tall
enough for this ride,
do you understand?
That's right,
we may seem nice,
but we're really mean!
Yes, but being mean
to a little girl
isn't very smart, you know.
‐Hmm?
‐Why, you little...
Hey, here's Goemon.
‐Holy crap.
‐Uh‐oh.
Hey, with or without
this little blackmailer,
we've got to get
out of this place.
(grunting)
Just leave them all to me.
I'll catch up with
you guys later.
Thank you, dress‐wearing man.
Hold on.
(whirring)
(grunting)
(shouting)
Hmm!
(groaning)
♪
Good day, gentlemen.
(tires screeching)
Hey, excuse me, sir?
Kid, listen, I know you're
just trying to be polite,
but when you say, "Sir,"
it makes me feel kind of old.
But, sir, I mean,
you are kind of old.
Hmm, whoa, whoa,
hold it, time‐out here!
Any chick in
the world would‐‐
I mean, I'm at the
peak of my, uh‐‐
Careful, Lupin, we're in
enough trouble already.
Uh, right.
Here's how it works.
Now because I'm the one
who took the stamp, you see,
that makes it all mine.
It belongs to me.
Capiche?
But just for now, right?
Um.
'Cause if I take
it away from you,
then it'll belong to
me, isn't that right?
'Cause that's the rule for
robbers, right, sir, hmm?
Hey, kid, don't start
calling me sir.
Oh, not you too.
And why not,
am I supposed to be
too old to care or something?
Oh, Jigen, it doesn't
really matter at all.
The main thing is how are
we going to get rid of
Pippi Longstocking back here?
But, ma'am, my name is Alice.
(groaning)
She got ya, ma'am.
There's nothing
funny about that.
I think it's a hoot.
Okay now, children,
let's just‐‐
Hey, what's that up there?
It looks like the cops.
Uh, if it was just us, man,
I wouldn't be so concerned.
Oh, damn it.
'Course I'm just
a little girl,
but, hmm, I'd have to
say that this puts me
in a very
interesting position.
(whistle blowing)
Right there, thank you.
‐License, please.
‐Here you go.
‐Mr. Policeman?
‐Hmm?
Yes, little girl?
‐What's the matter?
‐Well, sweetheart,
some bad men took something
that wasn't theirs,
and now we're just
trying to find them.
Oh, we can help you.
Really?
Some men in a car were driving
very fast near the museum.
My mommy saw the whole thing.
(gasping)
‐Is this true?
‐Tell him, Mommy.
Uh, well, I‐‐
What did you see?
Well, it was, uh...
Mommy, don't you want to
help them catch the bad guys?
'Course.
You mind coming with us?
Uh, sure.
Mommy's gonna be a big hero.
That's right,
sweetheart, she sure is.
Call me when you're
done, uh, darling.
(siren wailing)
Bye, Mom, see you later!
Whoo, well, that was
certainly close.
Now, listen, Alice,
that was a bad, bad thing.
Yeah, I know, but she
was the only other girl.
Only one girl can
be the princess.
(sighing)
♪
Quick, come on!
Hey, Lupin, you really
think this is gonna work?
Hey, we are faster!
Uh, physically anyway.
Ah, crap.
(chuckling)
♪
I'll bet you're
starting to miss
your mommy and daddy
now, aren't you?
‐Nah.
‐Uh, then, how about this?
I'll just pay you
for the stamp
since you insist it's yours,
then you can use the money
to buy dolls or
dresses or whatever.
Yeah, sounds fair.
But that stamp is really
worth lots and lots of money,
and if you think I'm taking
a personal check, you're nuts.
Fair enough, luckily, ready
access to large sums of cash
has always been one
of our hallmarks.
That's right, kid,
you better believe
we're well known in
the banking profession.
Ain't it the truth?
♪
(tires screeching)
Now, you stay here, Alice,
while we withdraw
some money, okay?
Mmhmm.
Feel like I'm in an old
one‐reeler or something.
Return of the James Brothers,
scene one, take
one, and action.
♪
‐Wait!
‐What the...
Don't move!
It's a keepsake picture!
Okay, everyone smile!
I'm not smiling.
I'm gonna keep
that one forever.
(gun firing)
Damn it!
Whoa, Mommy!
♪
(guns firing)
Look out!
(groaning)
♪
There, now that's a serious
chunk of change, little lady.
I'll say, in fact,
if you ask me,
Uncle Lupin's being
a little too generous.
Yeah, oh well.
We're friends, right, Alice?
Mmhmm, and now
I can just buy
the princess stamp back from
you and you won't be sad.
Hey, I'm not
selling the stamp!
Ah, no fair, give
me‐‐give me my stamp!
(shouting)
Hey, Jigen, do something,
will ya, she's gaining!
She may be small, Lupin,
but inside she's a woman,
so if you ask me, we might
as well just give up now.
Ugh!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
That's them all right.
I don't get it though, I mean,
straight‐up bank robbery
is just not his style.
What about kidnapping, is
that out of character for him?
Hmm.
The little girl shown
in the picture there,
Alice Henderson, only child
of a prominent local family.
She's been reported missing
since early this morning.
Anyone demanded
any ransom yet?
The family says it
hasn't been contacted.
However, I think
we can safely assume
that she hasn't
joined Lupin's gang.
Does that sound reasonable
to you, Inspector?
Hmm, but I just can't believe
that Lupin's capable
of doing such a thing.
But you can pursue whatever
case you want against him.
I don't really care,
I just want him.
Hey, wait, I'm no kidnapper!
This is bad for
our reputation.
I mean, if anything,
she kidnapped us.
Well, if you ask me, I'm
not sure that's much better
for our reputation.
Hey, aren't ya hungry?
I think I just
lost my appetite.
Listen, Alice,
you gotta call home
and tell everyone that you
were absolutely not kidnapped
and that you followed us of
your own free will, okay?
I really like you guys
'cause you're funny.
We're not kidding around.
Look, kid, we may steal stuff
and, well, you know,
shoot stuff, but, uh...
Kidnapping is real bad.
I guess I'm just too
little to understand.
Too bad, make the
damn call anyway!
Huh?
Hmm.
Uh...
Uh, stop, don't cry.
Please.
‐Okay.
‐Um, uh...
Uh...
Promise me you
won't run away again
when I'm on the telephone.
I promise you, Scout's honor,
cross my heart
and hope to die.
'Kay!
Wait right here.
Is that true, were
you really a scout
when you were a little kid?
Well, actually,
more of a lookout,
and I'd say the
coast is clear.
♪
Thank God.
Bye!
Hey, wait!
Uh‐oh, I hope he's got
a real low deductible
on his car insurance.
‐You hit something?
‐No, I...
‐Crap.
‐Hey!
There's no driver!
Oh!
That doesn't look too bad.
♪
I wonder what's keeping them.
I couldn't care less what
happens to those guys.
They can just
drive into a canal,
as far as I'm concerned,
and you can quote me.
Hmm.
The Shadow is asleep so
we know they are safe.
That is at least
for the time being.
Shh, listen.
(muffled siren wailing)
You wouldn't have.
My parents are out of town,
so I asked the police
to come pick me up.
You‐‐
(gulping)
Think fast, buddy!
Uh.
(sirens wailing)
(laughing)
Man, it's Pops!
Damn it.
They sure like running.
Hey, wait for me!
♪
(tires screeching)
Dollars to donuts, Chief,
Lupin's in there somewhere.
If you're right, then once
we get all the exits covered,
he's a rat in a bag.
He's a master of
disguise, though,
so your men had better
be on their toes.
Ah, don't worry, Inspector,
I read the file on him.
I'll just see to it
that my men don't make
the same mistakes you have.
Mistakes?
You mean like that
moustache of yours.
♪
Hmm.
Hmm!
♪
Uh, wait just a
minute, you two.
Inspector, the hostage
we're looking for
is a little girl,
not a little boy.
Where'd you find
those stinky rags, huh?
Hey, that's uncalled for.
We stink these rags
up all by ourselves.
Kid, let me talk
to the kid here.
Listen, son,
now isn't it true
that you're actually
a little girl?
Dad, the strange
man is scaring me.
Let me try again.
Now if this man is
threatening to hurt you,
I can protect you,
so don't you be afraid
because I'm a policeman.
You promise you won't
let him hurt us?
Huh?
It's my job.
Grab him!
Now then, you can
tell me the truth.
My dad's a terrible man.
He took away the
pendant that I won.
Uh, well, I, uh, I mean...
I won it and
I should have it.
Hmm.
Just what kind of
father are you?
That's despicable!
Now give it back to him.
But...
Now, listen, I'm a very
busy man, so just do it!
Rotten, little...
There!
Thanks, Lupin,
I mean, uh, bye!
Did he say...
Get him!
Huh?
Leave this to me,
you go get the girl.
Alice!
Lupin!
An amusement park.
Well, I am not amused.
Hmm.
Wait a minute!
Mr. Lupin, sir!
Here I am!
(grunting)
♪
All right, now, fun's
over, give me the‐‐
(laughing)
Over here!
Oh!
Aren't you too big
for this ride?
Why, you little‐‐
Hey!
Wee!
(laughing)
Hey, get over here!
Bye‐bye, Lupin!
See ya, wouldn't
want to be ya!
Huh?
(shouting)
♪
(laughing)
Hey, Mr. Lupin, sir!
Look at me now!
‐Huh?
‐It worked!
What?
It really worked!
I'm a real princess, see?
Hi!
Ah!
♪
(laughing)
Pretty pink pony!
Got ya, this has been
lots of fun, princess,
but I'll take
that pendant now.
Fork it over.
(whimpering)
(laughing)
Uh, unbelievable.
Ya, ya!
(laughing)
(mouth warbling)
(sighing)
♪
Ya, giddy up, ya!
(yelling)
(shouting)
Ooh, ya!
‐Come on!
‐He can't hurt us.
I'm a princess!
(shouting)
This is fun!
(screaming)
♪
(grunting)
Your Highness, I'm afraid
your revels now are ending.
Oh.
(train whistle blowing)
♪
Now, no more playing around,
okay, this is serious.
Got it, I want that
stamp right now.
(crying)
Hey, that won't
work this time.
You're gonna be really
mad at me, Mr. Lupin,
because I dropped the
pendant and lost it.
You what?
It must have fallen out
of my pants pocket.
Oh, it did, huh?
That's right, take
all of my clothes off
if you don't believe me.
Come on, go ahead.
Uh, no, no, really, Alice,
that won't be necessary.
But then...
I mean, there's no way
we could ever find it.
Lupin!
He's got the girl!
Hold it right there!
Oh, man, ah!
(panting)
‐Which way?
‐Right there.
You mean he's in the...
Why, you‐‐
♪
I'm not letting you get away!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Hey!
Get your hand off my nipple!
Lupin!
I'll get you!
Oh, this is ridiculous,
it's gonna take forever.
I really don't see
why the hell we can't
just wait for daylight.
‐Oh, man.
‐What?
Oh, man!
What, what the hell is
so damn funny, Lupin?
Hello, Lupin!
‐Look over there.
‐Huh?
Oh, no.
Wait a minute,
you think that...
Stamp, mailbox?
Hmm.
There is nothing in there.
(bell ringing)
Is that for me?
How'd you know?
‐Thanks!
‐Bye!
This is the most excitingest
moment of my entire life.
Now I have the princess stamp
and I even outsmarted
Lupin the Third!
Ah, but how come his
name is on the back?
"My dear Princess Alice,
After hijacking
the mail truck,
I had second thoughts.
I mean, I'm just happy
being the prince of thieves,
but fair warning, Princess,
when your dream
does come true
and you don't need
the stamp anymore,
I'll be back for it.
So keep it
somewhere safe for me
and I'll be seeing ya.
Your friend, Lupin the Third."
(laughing)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
She may be a geeky
four‐eyed freakazoid,
but this rookie
cop's got game.
And she takes it right to us
after we pull a
big job in Paris.
Not much of a team player
as poor Pops finds out.
But take it from me,
her one‐on‐one moves
are a revelation.
Catch ya later in
"Revenge of Le Nerd."
♪
♪ Lupin ♪