♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(glass breaking)
(Japanese lyrics)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(Japanese lyrics)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(flashbulbs clicking)
Yeah, give the one in green
a little smooch
on the hand, will ya?
Yeah, that's it, right,
just like that.
Great, now the other la‐‐
yeah, that's beautiful.
Right back‐‐a little kiss.
♪
(sneeze)
‐Hmm?
‐Huh?
Who's there?
Come on out.
Go around.
(gun cocking)
♪
Yah!
(grunts)
♪
(groan)
Don't let them get away!
Fire!
(gunfire)
♪
Don't let them get away!
(gunfire)
Oh, missed 'em!
♪
Dammit!
Come on,
it's over, let's go.
Come on!
Yeah.
♪
(splash)
Get 'em, dammit, come on!
(gunfire)
I wonder what that could be?
It's just fireworks, darling,
don't worry your little head.
(ship's horn blowing)
(typewriter keys clicking)
♪
(water lapping)
Damn it all, Lupin, why'd
you have to go and sneeze?
You got some kind of friggin'
allergy or somethin'?
Dammit, there they go.
We shouldn't be stealing
masterpieces like that anyway.
They belong in museums
where the whole world
can appreciate them.
Hmm, yeah, maybe
you're right.
I don't care
about the damn art.
Hmm, I'm confused.
We were trying to steal
all that crap, weren't we?
Mm‐hmm, definitely.
But not to own it ourselves,
just to swipe it away
from that friggin'
animal, Onabes.
♪
I hate him and
so should you!
♪
He's a thief, too, except he
does it the old fashioned way,
at the point of a gun.
(gun cocking)
(grunts)
(gunfire)
(groans)
♪
(snickering)
(glass shattering)
(grenade exploding)
And worse, everything he owns
and every single
piece in that collection
was paid for in blood.
It's an affront to art
and the art of theft.
♪
I agree, only
there's one thing,
how the hell are you gonna get
back onboard the damn boat?
I mean, you're pretty,
but you ain't that pretty.
(snicker)
Oh yeah?
That's right, pal.
Just let this one go, Lupin.
(ship's horn blowing)
(sigh)
♪
(intercom beeping)
Sorry, sir, there appears
to be a shipwreck survivor
floating off the
starboard bow and‐‐
Just leave him to the sharks.
Very well, sir,
but it's not a him,
it's a young woman.
Huh, that's totally different.
What the hell are you,
some kind of unfeeling monster?
Yes, sir, I mean no, sir.
Very good, sir.
♪
There she is.
Here, ma'am.
(panting)
♪
This way, ma'am.
Presenting, sir,
Miss Alexandra Marie,
whose father was the owner
and captain of a yacht
which was struck by
a tanker a few days ago.
No other survivors.
(screaming)
♪
You idiot, can't you see
the girl's been traumatized!
Get a stretcher!
Yes, sir, right away!
‐Miss Marie?
‐Thank you.
Please, you really
don't have to thank me.
♪ I ain't lucky
if you don't love me ♪
The poor angel.
♪ I'll keep trying,
till my love starts turning ♪
♪ Till someday maybe
you'll love me ♪
♪
What the hell?
Sole survivor?
I just don't like
the smell of this.
Now, don't you worry, hon,
you're gonna be just fine.
You're just a little
exhausted from your ordeal.
I'm gonna give you
a little injection,
some vitamins, mostly.
You'll be in
the pink in no time.
Why not do it in the arm?
Oh, now, there's no need
to be embarrassed,
you're a big girl.
Now, you might feel
a little sting,
but it'll be all
over in a second.
♪
There.
Grrrrr.
Hold on now, hon,
just have to make sure
we get every last
drop of this into you.
‐Grrrrrr.
‐That's it.
Take it like a man,
since you are one.
Come again?
What the?
Hey, Fujiko.
You‐‐ow!
Son of a bitch!
♪
Bet you thought
that was funny, huh?
Come on, how could I resist?
Look at this thing,
it's huge!
Here, have a taste
of your own medicine!
‐(phone ringing)
‐Huh?
Hello‐‐oh, hello, Mr. Onabes.
Mm‐hmm.
Is our little angel
feeling better?
Much better already.
This one's got a very
strong constitution.
Wonderful news.
Invite her to be my guest
at my table tonight for dinner,
say about 8:00?
I'm sure she'd be
delighted to join you, sir.
Let me know if there
is anything she needs.
Yes, like a big,
strong billionaire.
(snicker)
I never thought of you
as the gold‐digger type,
but it suits you, somehow.
Yeah, yeah, very funny.
What are you doing here?
My God, you really have
turned into a blonde.
Touché, that's
a dumb question.
There's a van Gogh in there
that I've always thought
would look particularly
nice in my bedroom.
♪
Hey, as long
as you're here,
why don't the two
of us partner up?
We coordinate and
cover for each other.
This could be easy.
Normally, I'd love to,
but next time, okay?
Sorry.
Hmph.
Now, excuse me, I have to
go practice my bimbo giggle.
(giggling)
Yeah, that's getting better.
Sure, laugh all you want,
but I'll laugh last.
♪
Tell me, how's my
little angel feeling?
Well‐‐
You know, dear,
it must be fate
that we happened
to be passing by here.
I'm the luckiest
girl in the world.
Oh, child, just feel
how rough your hands are.
Yes, it was simply
brutal out there.
Yes, my dear, and loneliness can
be terribly brutal to the soul.
That's the reason
I've always been
such a great
believer in matrimony.
Miss Marie, the moment I saw
you, you seemed to be rare
like a creature
from another world.
You're not like the others.
That's kind of you.
Not at all, when
you get to be my age,
you call them
as you see them.
Yes, Inspector,
what is it now?
Yes, sir, I just got word
from the Paris Metropolitan
Police Department
that Lupin's probably weaseled
his way onto this ship
posing as a woman, they say.
He's a master of
disguise, Mr. Onabes,
and I wouldn't
put it past him‐‐
‐I'm so scared!
‐(crashing)
How dare you further
upset this young lady!
And after everything
she's been through!
Bring that thing over here.
Right away, sir.
(wheels squeaking)
Hmm?
What are you doing?
Quiet, I'm going to show you the
floor plan of the museum room.
Perhaps that will
put your mind at ease.
In the completely
unlikely event
this ship should ever
be at risk of sinking.
When the water
reaches a certain level,
the entire museum suite will
be automatically jettisoned
from the rest of the ship
and can then be directed to
alight anywhere on the globe.
So don't talk to me
about this Lupin,
he couldn't possibly lay his
filthy hands on my collection.
It's impossible.
But I'm telling you he's‐‐
I remind you, Inspector,
you are only here
at the insistence
of my insurance company.
All right, if that's
the way you feel.
(grumbling)
Now, how about some
champagne, my dear?
Love some.
♪
Don't toast your
success just yet, Lupin.
(water running)
Here I come, Lupin.
Yeah, I'm going over this
whole tub top to bottom.
Got to go, got to go,
got to go, got to go.
Damn, I gotta go.
Oh, sorry, Miss, pardon me.
(humming)
Huh?
♪
Was that a...
Lupin, I've got you
now, you bastard!
Help, someone!
Get back here, you!
Help, somebody, please!
♪
Help, help!
There's no escape, Lupin!
♪
Uh‐oh.
Crap.
Ha‐ha, nice and easy now.
I wouldn't want to wrinkle
that nice dress of yours.
This is not a good thing.
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Hello, anyone!
Hello?
‐That's fine, scream.
‐Help me!
Hey, anyone, hey!
Looks like it's
just you and me.
‐(laughing)
‐Huh?
♪
Lupin!
Damn it all, get back here!
You're under arrest!
(shouts)
You're not getting
away from me this time!
(gunshot)
(yelling)
Hey, Fujiko, thanks.
♪
Good God, are you all right?
Oh, yes, but this awful man
attacked me out of nowhere.
There, there now.
Hey, Lupin!
(whimpering)
All right, I warned
you, Mr. Zenigata.
Now I'm afraid I'm going
to have to insist
that you leave this ship.
No, Mr. Onabes, please!
Hey, I can explain!
This is all her fault,
I mean his fault!
You see, she's‐‐
Poor Lupin.
He's actually vain enough to
thing I did it to help him.
When will he ever learn?
♪
How does one pick one's
lucky star, Miss Marie?
I mean, there are
millions of them up there,
but somehow or other,
you just know.
You're so deep.
And full of it,
like an outhouse.
Or maybe he's
building up to something.
Either way, I've got
to get moving here,
so time for a little
nighty‐nightcap.
♪
(giggle)
‐Instinct.
‐Huh?
Sorry, I was just
lost in the stars.
Did you say instinct?
(giggle)
Yes, if we could
just follow our instincts
we will never be lost.
Uh, I'm a little lost.
I've decided to pick a bride
from among the guests on board
and I'm relying on
instinct to help me choose.
Hmm, how bold and
romantic of you.
How friggin' pathetic
and disgusting.
‐Miss Marie, I, um‐‐
‐Good evening, sir.
Ma'am.
Hmm.
Well then,
shall we have some?
Why not, the night is young.
Look, the bubbles are
like stars in the sky.
But we don't have
to pick just one,
we can have them all.
♪
To you, angel.
Get ready to walk a mile
in my heels, Lupin.
(swallowing)
That's right,
guzzle it down, you pig.
♪
This tastes a little funny.
They say it's a
very amusing vintage.
Maybe that's it,
guess I just need someone
to help me
lighten up a little.
Just hurry up and pass out.
You‐‐why, you're effervescent.
(yawns)
You're right,
I've never felt so zippy.
(giggle)
Amore.
What does that mean?
It means I want you,
I must have you!
Let me take you
and start a family.
‐Agh!
‐(glass breaking)
I absolutely refuse
to let you up, Miss Marie,
until you promise to marry me.
What, that's impossible!
(kissing)
Dammit!
(smack)
(yells)
Just snap out of it!
Oh, yes, flip me
like a hamburger, baby.
What?
Come here, do it again!
No, stop it!
♪
(gargling)
‐(laughing)
‐Huh?
Fujicakes, thank God!
Freshening up for your
next round of tonsil hockey
with Onabes, are ya, huh?
Hey, did you?
Yep.
Instead of going
down for a long nap,
the old horny toad's now
got enough Spanish fly in him
to keep the two of you
busy for at least a week.
You did what?
Yep, and to think it
could have all been avoided
if we had just teamed up.
‐Why, you‐‐
‐(footsteps running)
Huh?
Yeah!
There you are!
Please, come back!
‐Don't run from me!
‐Get away from me!
♪
Dammit, Fujiko!
Please, I mean, what
about the other guests?
What other guests?
(yelling)
(giggling)
I see you!
♪
Wait, just think about it.
There are so many women here
who are so much prettier.
It's no use, I made
my choice‐‐instinct.
You need to know, I have
a dark side, Mr. Onabes.
I know everything
I need to know, Angel.
Nothing you can tell me can
possibly change the way I feel.
But my breasts,
they're not real!
I don't care.
And my rear end, it's got
a plate in it, really!
I don't care.
I'm a slut, I sleep around,
I'm a walking Petri dish!
I don't care!
Dammit, all right then,
I'll give you
something to care about.
I'm not even a friggin' woman!
Oh, well, nobody's perfect.
(yelling)
(splat)
♪
(growls)
All right,
you win, I give up.
But premarital sex
is out of the question!
(wings flapping)
(bells chiming)
♪
Hmm.
(humming)
(snicker)
♪
Hey, Lupin, what's gonna happen
to that van Gogh I want?
Fujiko, please.
This is the most important
moment in a girl's lifetime.
I hate you.
♪
... and for poorer.
In sickness and in health,
for as long as the
both of you shall live?
I do, yes.
For as long as the
both of you shall live?
Hmm.
Yes, I do.
‐(giggle)
‐Ah.
(bells chiming)
So, he finally
hooked her, hey?
What, what do you mean?
We're talking Fujiko, right?
Huh, what do you mean
it's not Fujiko?
It's Onabes,
are you insane?
He's a guy, Lupin,
and you're a guy!
And if you were
that kind of guy,
well, you could have
friggin' told somebody!
I thought we were friends.
Grrrr, hold on, Jigen.
Wait a minute, give me
a chance here, will ya?
Hey, you still there?
What the hell?
Ahh, come on, man.
(dialing)
(ringing)
We're not here, sorry.
It's a ruse, you idiot!
Now listen to me.
I need you guys to
bring a transport chopper
to the pier at 10:00 tonight.
That's 10:00, understand?
(phone hanging up)
I heard it all
from over here.
No need to repeat it.
♪
Oh, sweetie, just going to
change, I'll be right back.
Of course, pumpkin,
go right ahead.
♪
Now, please remember,
sweetie, what you said.
Uh, give me
a clue, would you?
You promised not
to drink too much
because tonight is such
a very special night.
‐(giggle)
‐Huh?
Oh, my, I'm such a lucky guy.
(laughing)
That one will keep
you young or kill you.
(laughing)
♪
Hey, now where
are you going?
Come over here and
join us for a drink.
No, thank you.
Congratulations,
Mr. Onabes.
My husband and I want you
to join in the celebration.
Please help
yourselves to a drink
or some cake
in the dining room.
I'll be happy to keep
an eye on things here.
Thank you, ma'am.
Yes, and congratulations.
Oh, you're welcome.
Have fun, boys.
I love cake!
I can't believe it.
I never would have thought
I'd be competing with Lupin
at my own game.
♪
(water lapping)
(rumbling)
Is that the ship?
No, is it an earthquake?
I say, sir, are your feet
feeling a bit chilly?
My feet?
Well yes, now
that you mention it.
(yelling)
♪
Ah, it's just
about pickup time.
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Sorry, darling, I'm taking
this as my divorce settlement,
so have your people
call my people.
♪
Dammit, Marie,
come back here!
Grrr, you made a sacred vow!
(yells)
I told you I was bad.
♪
Hello, nurse!
Hey, you mean
you're not a...
(laughing)
‐♪ Lupin The Third ♪
‐Hey, Lupin, wait a second.
‐Is my van Gogh in there?
That's not fair,
I called dibs on that.
Lupin!
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
It's girls, girls, girls
in the next episode,
but wait a minute,
this one turns out to be 60.
And this one's in cahoots
with a couple
of sleazy characters
trying to jump my claim
on a priceless
archaeological artifact.
I know, shocking, isn't it?
And this one's just
plain‐ass dangerous.
Oy, catch you later
in "Jumpin' The Bones."
♪