♪
♪ Lupe ♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(gun shots)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(whistling)
I'm the only one with
a reason to be happy!
Knock it off!
And I am pretty darn happy.
(laughing)
Good, we'll toast
to your success
once we get back home to Japan.
That's right,
and I'm gonna spring
for the best one they got!
(slurping)
Hmm‐‐what the hell's that?
♪
What's going on here?
Look, whatever it is, we‐‐
♪
(hissing)
All right, guys,
let's break it up!
Clear the road!
(zapping)
(screaming)
(groaning)
(grunting)
(yelling)
What the freakin' hell?
Suicide beams!
♪
(panting)
(clacking)
♪
What do you mean you're
not gonna get involved?
You're the Chief of
Police, for Pete's sake!
And the victims were your men!
It sounds like the
work of the Basala Army.
I wouldn't wanna tangle
with them if I were you!
Basala Army?
The Basala Army are thugs
who have the whole of
India living in fear.
Just a single shot from
one of their suicide beams,
and it's all over.
‐If they have Lupin‐‐
‐Well, stop 'em then!
If Lupin dies, my whole
life's over with, you hear?
And if you won't help, then
I'll just go after him alone!
But really, my dear
Inspector Zenigata,
you must think about this:
If your aim was this far
off shooting at your own head,
how in the world do you
expect to hit any of them, eh?
(groaning)
I see you're a
boxers man, Mr. Lupin.
Well, if it isn't the Suicide
King himself, Basala Lavahna.
That right?
Hmm, how do you know me?
You're too humble‐‐you,
sir, are a very famous man,
although I suppose "notorious"
would be a better word
for a crackpot scientist
turned murderous gangster.
(grumbling)
Hey, watch your mouth, you!
All right, what do
you want, Basala?
You stole 20,000 diamonds and
hid them somewhere in India.
I want you to tell
me where they are.
Jigen, what the hell
is he talking about?
Hmm, you got me.
We can do this easy,
or we can do it hard.
(groaning)
All right, all right, let go!
Very good, now talk!
Where are the diamonds?
♪
Now unless you want a
complimentary tracheotomy,
you're gonna let us go.
You really wanna see
if one of your bullets
is faster than this knife?
Wait, hold on‐‐I‐‐I‐‐I‐‐
All right, sunshine,
get over here.
♪
How do you like my
boxers now, Basala?
Not as much now.
(yelling)
Apparently you will
acquire another demonstration
of my suicide beam!
♪
How's that old joke go?
"I went hunting for an
elephant in my boxers"?
(zapping)
(trumpeting)
Maybe he didn't like the joke.
Nobody likes that joke.
Tell me where they are,
and I'll switch it off!
Hey, you want diamonds?
Here's a crazy thought,
go to a jewelry store!
I cannot tell if you are
courageous or just an idiot.
Maybe this will help.
(buzzing)
In any case, it comes
down to the same thing.
You either talk or you die.
(grunting)
♪
You comfy?
You know, something
just doesn't add up.
‐Go on.
‐You and me and Goemon
were the only three
people in the whole world
who knew about these diamonds,
so how the hell did
Basala get tipped off?
Hint‐‐it starts with an F.
Fujiko?
I'll bet she's in it
with the Basala Army
up to her cleavage!
Jigen, you've got it all wrong!
I'm‐‐
(whimpering)
This is getting old real fast.
Let's call 911.
Hey, Goemon!
Lupin to Goemon!
♪
Goemon, please, come in!
S. O. S., S. O. S.!
Dammit, he's probably
meditating or something.
Oh, please, Goemon, please,
snap out of it, will ya?
Well, at least one of
us is perfectly serene.
I can't hold on.
Don't jostle me
if you wuss out.
I'm holding up pretty good here.
You thought the
elephant joke bit!
What the‐‐
Huh?
I know, I know, how
can you ever thank me?
Well, cash is always welcome.
That's my Fuji‐cakes!
Fujiko, you're a guardian angel!
We were done for!
‐Come on!
‐See, what'd I tell ya?
She's totally on our side.
‐Yeah, we'll see.
‐Hmph.
♪
Hey, look at that!
Yup, the Taj Mahal!
♪
You think the locals
might be a little shocked
to find out this
is Basala's hideout?
By the way, Fuji‐cakes,
I'm impressed that you found us.
Well, thanks to this.
I just happened to be
here doing some sightseeing
when I heard your
S. O. S. to Goemon.
You guys happen to
be incredibly lucky.
Yeah, well, not anymore.
‐Let's go!
‐Get them!
♪
Damn, where did they go?
All right, everybody get out.
♪
They're hiding somewhere
in here, I know it.
Go ahead and kill
the whole herd!
We cannot do that.
‐It would be a big sin.
‐Very bad karma.
What are you damn
fools waiting for?
These cows are very
sacred animals to us.
Fairy tales!
I order you to
slaughter this herd!
Whoa there, easy now.
Just about there.
Superstitious idiots.
All right, I'll just do
it myself if I have to.
(motor rumbling)
Damn!
♪
After them!
They're getting away!
♪
What's up?
You're kinda quiet.
I, um, was just
wondering if you were ever
planning on telling me
about all those diamonds.
What are you talking about?
I overheard them talking about
it when I ran to your rescue,
so don't you try and pull
your innocent act with me,
you greedy, ungrateful,
rotten son of a bitch!
Where the hell are they?
Don't fall for it.
She has a very nasty habit
of betraying us, Lupin.
That is so unfair!
I've turned over a new leaf!
I did risk my life
to save you, after all.
♪
So that's how you
wanna play it, huh?
Lupin, even if you were
the last man on Earth
and I was the last woman,
I could never love you
after this, you hear?
Never!
That's the last straw‐‐goodbye.
Fujiko, no, wait, hold on!
Come on!
Come on, let's not be so hasty!
Oh, Lupin, I love
it when you trust me.
Really?
(giggling)
The diamonds are in Kolkata.
Really?
And where exactly in
Kolkata would they be?
It's a classic case of
hiding in plain sight.
In fact, all you have to do is‐‐
Can't you see what
she's doing, man?
She's got you
wrapped around her!
You stay out of this!
No way!
(grunting)
‐Damn, it's a sinkhole!
‐Ah, help!
Fujiko, help us!
Lupin!
(panting)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Lupin, oh my God, no!
Lupin, Jigen!
(crying)
Why all the tears, my dear?
It's this sinkhole!
It just swallowed them both up!
Please, you've got to save them!
It's too late, my dear.
Did you happen to make
any progress with them?
That's cold.
Our understanding was
that you would find out
where the stones are hidden.
All he said was the
diamonds are in Mumbai.
Mumbai?
He was just about to tell
me more when he fell in.
Very well‐‐that is actually
more help than you realize.
I suggest we leave immediately.
‐I'm out of this.
‐The diamonds have suddenly
lost their luster for you?
I guess I'm not as
cold‐hearted as you.
It's a tainted legacy now.
Very honorable‐‐just make sure
you do not whine about it later.
Go!
♪
Something smells here.
No woman would ever
pass up diamonds.
♪
I'll come back here
and spread diamonds
all around in your
memory, Lupin, how's that?
Bye‐bye!
(engine starting)
(yelling)
Yeah, what'd I tell ya, Lupin?
We put on a little charade
and that bitch exposes
herself for exactly what she is.
Damn, that's it.
I'm never‐‐huh?
Jigen, over there!
What the hell is that?
♪
Well, it looks like
our friend Basala
is off on a treasure hunt.
That means Fujiko's in danger!
‐I‐‐
‐I thought you said
you were finished with her!
Look, I know she's no good,
but that doesn't
matter‐‐I love her!
♪
That damn woman!
That is the road to Kolkata!
♪
Could all of you please
get out of my way?
Now?
"In plain sight"‐‐
those were his words.
How can we search for
anything, let alone diamonds,
when it's so crowded?
You have to learn to be patient
and to bide your time
in these circumstances.
Meanwhile, it is very nearly
bathing time in the Ganges.
I have an idea.
♪
What part of "get
the hell out of my way"
don't you understand?
It's Basala!
♪
Just keep your eyes on
her until she kills herself.
♪
(engine rumbling)
Listen, I want you to
dig up all of Kolkata
if you have to‐‐understand?
Now, go!
(rumbling)
(shattering)
Hey, Fujiko!
Hey!
♪ Lupe ♪
What the‐‐hey!
Ah!
♪
♪ Lupe ♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
‐Mhm?
‐Boss, Lupin is here!
Yes, well then, I've
got a surprise for him!
I want her alive.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Hey, Fujiko!
I love the color
of potassium cyanide!
Potassium cyanide?
It looks so tasty.
No!
Don't, Fujiko!
Fujiko!
♪
I'm afraid you've been
snookered, Mr. Lupin!
That was a deathly
bomb of suicide beams.
Your friend, Miss
Fujiko, is over there.
Fujiko!
I furnished her with the
antidote to the suicide ray.
Now you are infected
with it, my pesky friend.
It's too late, Mr. Lupin.
Why don't you take aim at
your own head, my friend?
Go on!
♪
(gun shot)
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, just trying to off myself.
Seriously, what's up?
I'm off to the afterlife.
See ya!
Wait, Lupin, hey!
(chuckling)
(grunting)
Oh, look at them!
(buzzing)
Sir, we found the diamonds!
‐Good, where?
‐The Yoga Center!
Stay right there‐‐
I am on my way!
(grunting)
♪
Move, you bastard!
(groaning)
So, what is this?
This crazy person is just
sitting on the diamonds!
We can't get him off, Sayeb!
Get away!
‐Fire a suicide blast at him!
‐Right!
Now!
(buzzing)
Dammit, he has obtained a
state of perfect equilibrium.
The beam cannot effect him.
Into the gondola right now!
♪
♪ I can't wait to die ♪
♪ It's so nice to die ♪
♪ Happy guy, la‐la‐la ♪
Lupin, quit movin', will ya?
You're gonna‐‐
Wee!
(grunting)
Yeesh, that sure
was a close one.
Lupin!
This rope's for you.
Don't move a single muscle.
A rope, that's cool!
Please, can I have it?
You're just surrendering?
Uh, here‐‐
I'm gonna die!
Wha‐‐what the hell is going on?
Hey!
(yelling)
Hmm, that's bizarre.
It's like all of a
sudden I don't even
wanna go on living anymore.
Yeah, what's the point in
just chasing after Lupin
and never catching
him year after year?
There is no point!
What the hell's going on?
Can't you tell?
It is contagious!
Come on, we all
gotta go sometime!
What do you say we
go together, huh?
‐Come on, Jigen.
‐Thanks, but no thanks.
♪
He'll be waking up soon.
(yawning)
(groaning)
(yelling)
♪
Oh, my golly, no!
Forget him‐‐the diamonds are
the only thing that matters.
Now, open the trunk!
♪
‐Ahh!
‐What‐‐what is it?
Oh, it's cow dung!
Cow dung?
Don't just stand
there, get rid of it!
♪
There, now try to kill yourself!
Hey, I could bleed to death
if I could bite my tongue!
Hey, hey, hey, stop
it, you damn maniac!
Hey, Goemon, you got anything
you can shove into his mouth?
Um, this might do
the trick for now.
Ah, perfect.
Man, I've wanted to do
that for a long time.
♪
Huh‐‐either he's bought it,
or that crap cured him!
Hmm, perhaps it's karmic
repayment for mad cow disease.
Hey, guys, what's going on?
You know, I just ate something,
but I can't exactly
remember what it was.
Hmm, it was from a cow.
Ah, yeah.
Some kind of local burger, huh?
It was great.
Huh?
Basala, he's
getting away, come on!
No one humiliates
the Basala Army!
(buzzing)
♪
What the hell happened to me?
Hey, wait a minute.
There's another hole!
Now, I wonder
how that got there.
♪ Lupe ♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
Okay, steady...
and light it!
♪
Ahh!
Oh, this is very bad.
♪
Hey, Lupin, you lied to me.
Why did you say the
diamonds were in Kolkata?
I didn't lie, they're in
plain view, just like I said.
Then I'm gonna laugh last.
♪
You'll see!
Obsession, thy name is Woman.
I'm not sure she'd still
want 'em if she did find 'em.
Shh, keep it down.
♪
20,000 cows, one diamond each.
Safest place in all of India
if you're looking
to hide something.
It might not be real
pretty when it comes out,
but the great
thing about diamonds
is they clean up real nice.
♪
(horn blowing)
See you holy
heifers in Yokohama!
We'll set you all up
on a nice farm somewhere
and make sure
you're real well‐fed.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
In the next episode,
Goemon loses his mojo
when his Zantetsu sword
mysteriously disappears,
and when Jigen and I
find it, we wish we hadn't.
Oh, Mommy!
It's slashing through the
sky shredding a tenuous piece
in war‐torn Central Africa.
Tune in next time to see
if The Yam is
Mightier Than the Sword!
Catch ya later!
♪