♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(gunshot)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(approaching jet engine)
(screeching tires)
(mixed voices)
Goodbye, Inspector,
nice to see you again.
Thanks, but I'm not
that guy any longer.
Huh?
(psychotic cackling)
Oh!
♪
(growling)
That old guy's entire act
was technologically obsolete!
Now, I'm state of the art!
(unhinged chuckling)
That's him right
over there, sir!
(grunts)
(chuckles)
(grunting)
Ow.
Ah, glad you could make it.
I am Inspector Goya
of the Metropolitan Police.
Ah, yes, Zenigata.
(chuckles nervously)
I seem to have a‐‐
(chuckles)
Number 18, thumb cuff!
Here, I'll just‐‐
But how did you...?
It's just my own little
modest contribution
to modern
crime‐fighting technology.
♪
Remember when I seemed
to turn and close my coat
after your man here
pointed me out to you?
I call 'em Zeni‐gotchas!
Catchy, huh?
Well, so much
for old dogs and new tricks.
Yeah, but Lupin, we're talking
about Pops here, remember?
He's not exactly Rin Tin Tin.
Huh?
♪
(typewriter clicking)
Hey, Goemon, we're
gonna go catch a bite,
you wanna join us?
♪
(doors open)
Okay.
He would rather starve,
you know, than go a day
without his damned
pickled radishes
and miso soup.
(chuckles)
(engine revs)
♪
(mixed chatter)
(claps)
(aroused groaning)
♪
Hey, what's that
just off‐stage?
Marry me.
What was that?
I wanna have your children.
Ugh, you're hopeless,
you know that?
Hmm?
How many are there, huh?
Finger joints?
Uh, well, uno, dos‐‐
It's a trick question,
forget it!
(grunts)
The point is it
really doesn't matter,
just as long as you're sure
to nail at least one
on each hand.
(chuckles)
♪
(claps)
Oh, baby, come on!
Did you forget about Fujiko?
(groans)
Oh, God.
♪
(claps)
She can't keep her eyes off me!
Ugh, yeah?
Well, nobody can.
You're making a spectacle
out of yourself.
♪
Ha, see that?
(laughs gleefully)
Actually, I wasn't
winking at you.
Crap.
(chuckles)
Huh?
No way!
You don't think...?
Uh.
♪
(applause)
Hey, sorry, Jigen,
but I guess her aim
isn't too good, you know?
Or, just maybe,
there's one other
possible explanation.
Yeah, what?
Oh, that she threw it to me
instead of to you, on purpose.
Now, that's just crazy talk.
(chuckling)
♪
Huh?
(screaming)
♪
Sleeping gas!
Got it!
♪
Gotcha!
Hmm?
♪
Look, they're taking the girl.
I know, just keep still!
♪
Huh?
Hey, Jigen, wait,
give me a hand here!
Damn, how the hell
did that happen?
(grunting)
♪
Look, handle it yourself,
I've gotta go.
Hey, get back here!
♪
(mumbling)
A‐ha!
There they are!
Is he there?
Yeah.
(chuckling)
♪
(door opening)
Ready?
♪
H. V. Myer, could swear I know
that name from somewhere.
(grunts)
♪
(gunfire)
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Take it easy, hold your fire.
Yeah, listen to your boss, boys.
So, what do you want?
All right, hardware
on the floor,
hands where I can see 'em.
Come on, do what the man says.
Hurry up.
♪
(gunfire)
(chuckles)
Still can't resist
the circus shot.
So, von Myer, tell me,
how's the whole snarky scumbag
thing working out for ya?
You know, can't complain.
Uh‐huh, I'll bet not, I mean
bottom‐feeding would be
kind of a recession‐proof
business, wouldn't it?
(chuckles)
Let's just cut to the chase,
I'm here for the girl.
You can't have her.
Why not, what's she to you?
Well, she's my
favorite employee,
or she was, that is,
until she took it
into her head to resign.
Get her.
Does she have
something of yours?
Guess you could say that.
I wouldn't lose
my head over her;
even you could
do better than that.
(cocks gun)
If I were you,
I wouldn't worry
about anyone else
losing his head
over her, Myer.
♪
Point taken.
Hey!
(chuckles)
♪
Myer's not going
to be following us;
don't worry about it.
Why not?
Let's just say that your
resignation's been accepted.
(chuckles)
So, you any good at darts?
I've been told my aim
is absolutely deadly.
I'm a big fool for
good hand‐eye coordination.
It's a gift.
Whoa, hey!
Whoa!
Damn, you'd think one
of those keys woulda fit!
I don't dare set foot
outside wearing
this fershlugganah
thing on my pinkie.
I mean, what if this is some
sort of weird code that says
I wanna be spanked
by a skinhead or something?
Hmm.
Allow me.
No thanks, really, I'll wait.
(stammering)
Well, that's something anyway.
Hold on, hold on, I know.
Maybe if I just, you know?
(chuckles nervously)
(screams)
♪
It can't be, I mean I‐‐
Oh, wait, ah!
Huh?
(growls)
You.
Hey, kidding,
just kidding, you know me,
always with the jokes!
Hey, I bet your
blood sugar's getting low.
Why don't we‐‐
(stammering)
Goemon, what are you...?
Huh?
(chuckles)
(sighs)
(doorbell rings)
Huh?
If that's Jigen,
I swear, I'm gonna‐‐
Hi.
Well, if it isn't
the miso and radish girl.
Wait.
What's your problem?
You're the one who begged her
to go on this stupid errand!
I know, but think about it,
it doesn't add up at all;
her flight to Tokyo didn't leave
until late yesterday morning.
There's no way she
could be back this quickly.
I'm sure she's got
a perfectly good explanation.
Uh, right, Fuji‐cakes?
Mm‐hmm.
But unfortunately,
what I'm about to reveal
is pretty explosive.
Ew!
(nervous tittering)
(screaming)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(explosion, screams)
♪
Fujiko!
What the hell?
Long time, Lupin!
You again?
Get a life, huh?
I keep trying, but every time
I get close, it seems something
or, should I say,
someone, gets in my way.
Last time, you
single‐handedly
scuttled my whole
drug‐smuggling operation.
Before that, it was...
but why dwell on the past?
I mean, I wouldn't want you
to think I was obsessed
or anything!
Look, just get to
the point, will you?
What is it you want?
Okay, let's talk
about that, Exhibit A.
I believe you're
already acquainted.
She's not my type, really,
too high maintenance for me,
but to each his own.
So, if she's worth anything
to ya, you can come and get her!
Ah, sounds like a challenge!
Look, you just get
your ass here by midnight
or she can kiss hers goodbye!
Okay, and just
where would that be?
Since Barcelona was where
we first crossed paths,
I thought it would be nice
to bring things full‐circle.
Anywhere in particular?
It was right here, Lupin,
don't you remember?
Yeah, right.
Then get moving,
because you've got
exactly 10 seconds, mister!
(gasping)
A‐three and a‐two
and a‐one and‐‐
(explosion)
♪
Sheesh.
You're still wearing that rose?
Of course.
Isn't it wilted?
Not really.
Pretty creepy‐looking
for a church.
Why'd you wanna come here?
No reason in particular,
it's just a famous landmark.
(bell ringing)
♪
It's not like him
to concede defeat so graciously.
Don't you worry about it;
I've got you covered, my dear.
For how long?
You tell me.
I don't deserve you.
Ah, that's just
the sangria talking.
And anyway, I can handle
that loser in my sleep.
I'm sure you're right,
it's just that‐‐
it's just that what?
(gasping)
God, I knew it!
Knew what, what is it?
What's wrong?
Von Myer!
I'll handle this!
(bullets ricocheting)
(gunfire)
(boat horn)
Huh?
Help me!
How in the hell did he...?
He told me to tell you‐‐
Wait, just let me.
(gasping)
He wants to meet, doesn't he?
Midnight tonight
at the same cathedral.
If you don't‐‐
Never mind, I know how
the rest of it goes.
I think I got the point.
Except‐‐
What is it?
Be very careful, von Myer's
a master of disguise.
Oh, yeah, good to know.
Hmm, very interesting.
Don't do it.
Hey, don't worry about me.
My love!
♪
(watch buzzing)
Hmm, okay, just about zero hour.
You still pouting?
You promised me that there
would be a Japanese restaurant
here in Barcelona.
Look, I apologized.
An empty apology
for an empty stomach.
Goemon, I said I'll
make it up to you,
now are you coming or not?
(stomach growls)
I'll take that as a no.
Dammit!
I'll be going now.
(bell ringing)
(approaching footsteps)
Okay, I'm here,
let's get this over with.
With pleasure!
(gunfire)
♪
Ha, you wasted
your disguise, von Myer.
If you came here
for a battle of wits,
I sure hope you
brought some backup.
♪
(gunfire)
Sounds just like him.
♪
Damn, when she said
"master of disguise,"
she sure wasn't kidding.
Hmm.
♪
Wait a minute,
maybe it really is him?
Hey, listen!
Whatever it is, forget it!
No, wait, hear me out!
Look, just shut up!
Now, if you really are
the real Jigen‐‐
I said shut up!
(chuckles)
(gunfire)
Son of a bitch.
♪
You ready?
Count of three.
One, two, three!
(gunfire)
♪
(gasping)
(groaning)
♪
Heh, what did I tell ya?
Each shot through
the heart, I'll bet.
My only regret is they can't
hear me gloat about it.
Yeah, well, we can't
have everything,
I mean, I never got to rip
his heart out and stomp
on it either.
(chuckling)
I guess you're right.
(chuckles)
This one'll kill 'em.
Well, guess old Sam Peckinpah's
got nothing on us, huh, pal?
(chuckles)
She's some piece of work, huh?
Guess that explains...
hey, you okay?
Mm‐hmm.
Then, let's go.
♪
Huh, Mr. von Myer!
Those guys you croaked,
it's them!
Hmm, what the...?
♪
(gunfire)
(tires squealing)
♪
(gunfire)
(mixed cheering)
(applause)
Huh?
Sure sucks being you, later!
Hey, Jigen!
And there's more
where that came from!
(grunts)
♪
Go ahead, send some men
over to the bull ring, pronto!
I'm sitting on some
pretty big news here.
Hey, get back here!
(mixed commotion)
♪
Take it easy, whoa!
It's the red jacket, isn't it?
Shut up, I gotcha now!
(grunts)
♪
See ya!
There's nowhere to go, Lupin!
♪
Uh...
(screams)
(bull bellows)
Help, somebody, please, help!
(grumbling)
You're doing great, Pops!
Toodles!
I'll get you!
(screams)
Olé!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
So, somewhere in
the feeble brain
of a senile old Nazi is
the key to a hidden treasure;
it takes the performance
of my life to pry it out
of the guy, and, of course,
that's when the stuff
really hits the fan.
See ya next time in,
"To Be or Nazi Be."
Toodles!
♪