♪
♪ Lupin the third ♪
(gunshot)
♪
♪ Lupin the third ♪
(bird screeching)
(birds chirping)
Home is like a river,
constant, and yet
never the same.
(bird squawking)
Huh?
Holy‐‐ah!
(rumbling)
Can there be no
respite from this?
♪
Hm, not a soul.
Something in this
bodes ill for Sensei.
I must hurry there.
(panting)
♪
‐Goemon!
‐Sensei!
Shizen Sensei!
Sensei!
♪
Goemon, take this now.
I give this‐‐
Who did this?
Tell me!
(explosion)
♪
This act will not go unavenged.
(waves crashing softly)
♪
It feels strange with just
the three of us, doesn't it?
Yeah, but still, we should
be happy for Goemon.
This is a big deal for him.
He hasn't seen his
sensei for ten years.
What exactly is the big
deal, some sort of reunion?
The sensei is finally
presenting him
with the full mastery
book of Iga Ninja arts.
Huh, kinda like a diploma.
One that contains the secret
essence of the Iga Ninja arts.
You know, I've heard rumors
of an Iga hidden treasure.
It's possible that mastery book
has a map showing
where it's buried.
That is so crass, Fujiko.
We're talking about a noble
ancient tradition here.
This from the prince
of pillagers himself.
(grumbling)
Now, children, behave.
I'll tell you what
worries me is that
that other guy's
still back there too.
Oh yeah, good old
what's‐his‐face Jinkuro.
Man, I swear that guy's
nothing but bad news.
Excuse me, hello!
Opal stimulants, antiques,
patented software,
and other copyrighted material.
Maybe another time.
What do you know
about this Jinkuro?
He trained with the same
master, and has always
been intensely
competitive with Goemon.
‐Are you sure?
‐No thanks.
So what're you saying,
you think Goemon might be
in some kind of danger
from this guy?
Yeah, it's possible.
Hey, mister, this one's a steal!
Okay, okay, what do you want?
I sell it to you for one dollar.
Here, keep the change.
Anyway, the point
is this Jinkuro guy's
really got it in for Goemon.
Nice watch, can I see?
Hey, what the‐‐
(laughing)
Damn!
(muffled remarks)
Ah, crap darn it!
Pick up the tab for
us, will ya, Pops?
Thanks, you're a real pal.
(grunting)
There's a little
crème brûlée left.
Lupin, you thieving
good‐for‐nothing!
I'm gonna get you!
(birds squawking)
Sensei, I should've known
to protect you from Jinkuro.
You must free your heart
of bitterness toward him.
Sensei, how can I?
You know the answer
to that, Goemon.
‐I‐‐
‐Goemon.
To be one with the
breath of nature,
this is the one fundamental
precept that must be etched
upon the very soul
of the Iga Ninja.
Wise men know that which
blooms in springtime
and bears fruit in
autumn must (indistinct)
wither up and die in winter.
Nature renews itself
after death each year,
but that which has passed
does not return, Sensei.
Perhaps not in the
same form, Goemon,
but am I not here?
I will remain with you
within your spirit forever.
‐But‐‐
‐You know that this is true.
Come on out, Goemon!
Jinkuro.
It's been a while, old friend.
Why'd you do it, why'd
you kill the sensei?
You're the one who
killed him, Goemon.
Hm, what do you mean?
Well, that's what
everybody in Iga is saying.
That you just couldn't wait
to get your hands
on that mastery book.
That's a lie!
They all begged me to be
the instrument of justice.
I can't deny them.
Justice is with me.
Ha, let's just
get this over with.
(wind blowing)
♪
Impressive, I heard
you went soft.
♪
(grunting)
You bastard!
♪
‐Coward.
‐You're living in the past,
but the one who stayed
behind has moved on.
Give me the other
half of the map.
‐I decline.
‐I'd think very hard
before I threw my
life away on some
abstract principle like honor.
But if that's what you
really want, Goemon,
hey, I'm here for ya.
(laughing and gunshot)
What the?
Big mistake, monkey‐face.
Yeah, now there's
the three of us.
You got lucky this
time, boy scout.
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, take it
easy, we'll get him.
‐You okay?
‐He's fine.
Guy just sprained his
dignity, that's all.
♪
So this is what all
the fuss is about.
We've gotta get the other
half from Jinkuro somehow.
Hey, Lupin!
Lupin, I just found out
that Pop's followed us
all the way back from Hong Kong.
Oy vey, that guy's a
major pain in the butt.
Yeah, and he's already
coordinated with the local cops.
Ah, and the good news would be?
That they brought Jinkuro
in a little earlier today.
Uh‐huh.
What, no way, you really
gotta be kiddin' me!
This is not good!
‐Pops and Jinkuro together?
‐Probably cuttin' a deal
with that snake in
the grass right now.
Like maybe sparing his life
in the Sensei Shizen
case for instance.
Yeah, probably in exchange
for a little cooperation.
He'll act as a decoy
to try and lure us out.
Well, we're not gonna
make that mistake.
Right, Goemon?
Where did he go?
I, I don't know.
Damn it, man, what the
heck is going on with you?
♪
We're all set here, sir.
‐Can we load the prisoner now?
‐Mhm.
Thanks for the escort,
chief, you can rest assured
your great cooperation
won't escape the notice
of my superiors at headquarters.
I appreciate that,
Inspector, be careful.
Absolutely.
‐Okay, come on.
‐Hold it.
‐Huh?
Jinkuro, prepare to die.
Yeah, I'm sorry, Goemon,
but that's not gonna happen.
Now!
♪
You're in this together?
The enemy of my enemy,
as the old saying goes.
(snickering)
♪
Damn you, Jinkuro.
I really hope I'm
wrong about this.
Yeah, well we better
step on it anyway.
♪
Let him have it, fellas!
(shots firing)
(coughing)
♪
Sensei, forgive me.
♪ Lupin the third ♪
(shots firing)
(coughing)
All right, that's enough.
Hold your fire!
Hey, Goemon, put
your weapon down.
Never.
(car horn beeping)
What the‐‐
Good gravy!
No, get away!
(mixed shouting)
This is it!
Hey, Pops.
Jigen, quit fooling around
and get ready to grab Goemon.
♪
Men, don't let them get away!
Goemon!
♪
Inspector, if that's what
you call protecting me
from Goemon, then
color me unimpressed.
Take it easy, remember who
you're talking to here.
‐I wrote the book on these guys.
‐Yeah, what's the title?
An Exercise in Futility?
(chuckling)
Watch it, you!
Maybe you should take it easy.
Save your energy for working
out some kinda plan here.
I don't take very kindly to
gettin' advice from murderers,
Jinkuro, especially
ones who are dumb enough
to get caught, you know!
So why don't you just save
your energy for the showers!
Dead guys don't shower much.
(waves crashing)
(evil laughter)
(yelling)
Hey man, would you keep it down?
You're starting
to scare the fish.
How in the world could I
possibly be quiet with Jinkuro
alive and well, and
protected by the police?
At least we know where he is
while we figure
out what to do next.
Yeah, Lupin, but what in
the hell do we do next?
Lupin, please put
down the fishing rod
and try and come up with a plan.
That's what I'm doing.
Fishing just happens to be
the way some of us meditate.
Oh, this might
cheer you up, some.
Whatever deal he
cut with Zenigata,
he's still going on trial.
Maybe the justice system
will live up to its name.
What kind of justice?
Living out his life
to a ripe old age?
Oh yeah, oh yeah, I
got something here!
Yeah!
Hey, I completely understand
how you feel, Goemon,
but there's no need to take it
out on this poor little fish.
Hey, come on, Goemon,
just hold on, will ya?
Lupin's gonna come up with
something, he always does.
See, look at that,
that's a good sign.
He's going deep now, and
in a few seconds‐‐yes!
He's tapped into
something, and‐‐
oh yeah, here it comes!
Three, two, one.
‐Hey, I got it!
‐Well?
Can I call him or can't I?
Okay, just lay it on us, man.
Goemon, I'll flush out
your quarry, and after that
you'll find peace
one way or another.
♪
Your Honor, it's our
position that the evidence
will show to an
overwhelming certitude
that it was indeed
the defendant, Jinkuro,
who brutally murdered his
former master, Fuutarou Shizen.
In fact, Your Honor, he
has admitted to the crime,
and is cooperating
with the prosecution.
Isn't that right, Jinkuro?
Yes, that would be correct.
I'm anxious to pay my debt
to society, Your Honor,
and would appreciate
an immediate finding
of guilty, if that's okay.
That bastard's probably
got his prison break
all mapped out already.
Hey, cool it, if
Zenigata spots us now
we won't be able
to do a damn thing.
I know, I know.
Your Honor, counsel
for the defense.
The defense may now
address the court.
Your Honor, I submit that
the prosecution is attempting
an end run around
the judicial process
with this so‐called confession.
However, they are still
obligated to meet
the burden of proof
in this matter.
I agree, a confession
is not sufficient.
I'm assuming that you're
prepared to submit
substantial evidence
to support this plea.
Of course, Your Honor.
In fact, there's a wealth of
compelling physical evidence
to support our case,
which we'd be delighted
to begin sharing
with you immediately,
beginning with the
murder weapon itself.
Move to submit people's
exhibit number one.
That sword is the murder
weapon the defendant used
to brutally attack and
kill his former teacher.
And it was a particularly
gruesome murder, the work
of a sick, vicious,
depraved animal.
Here's exhibit number one.
‐Hm?
‐Huh?
(gasping)
Is this some kind of a prank?
(laughing)
♪
Silence, or I'll
clear the court!
Keep it moving, counselor.
We have here a photograph,
Your Honor, which places
the defendant, Jinkuro,
at the murder scene.
♪
Precisely within the coroner's
estimated time of death.
‐Ahhh!
‐Yes, Your Honor.
It's very disturbing stuff.
Are you trying to make a
mockery of my court, huh?
That's you!
(crowd laughing)
Quiet in the court, quiet!
Take your seat
immediately, counselor,
or I'll find you
another one in jail!
Your Honor, now I'd like
to enter into evidence
the defendant's own
statement of guilt.
It was offered freely
with no coercion
on the part of the
police or others.
Hm, let me see.
(screaming and laughing)
Quiet, quiet,
quiet, quiet, quiet!
Now, I'm prepared to
render my verdict.
♪
The court sympathizes with
the defendant to the extent
that his life has been
publically threatened
by another in retaliation
for the crime
which he has alleged
here to have committed.
Prison would certainly
seem to be a safer place
for the defendant
given the nature
and specific origin
of said threat.
Hold it!
But prisons are for the
guilty, and the prosecution
has failed to make its case.
Therefore, due to a
complete lack of evidence,
‐case is dismissed.
‐What, that's ridiculous!
I'm as guilty as sin I tell ya!
I killed him with my own
hands, I'm a real bad guy!
(sighing and gasping)
♪
Don't gloat too soon, Goemon.
Hmm.
This court is now adjourned.
♪
There, Goemon,
he's all yours now.
(wind blowing)
♪
Jinkuro, this time a fair
fight with witnesses.
Whatever, boy scout,
let's do it.
♪
(grunting)
(thunder rumbling)
Valiant, but that
arm is getting weaker.
(lightning cracking)
♪
Jinkuro, this is your
final breath on earth.
You should prepare yourself.
Bite me, boy scout.
♪
Check mate.
You're downwind and your
witnesses can't see.
It's a numbing agent,
but at least when I kill you,
you won't feel
anything but shame.
♪
Something's wrong.
We're coming, Goemon!
No, I must do this myself.
You're such a sap.
♪
I myself must bring
this to a conclusion.
♪
(maniacal laughter)
Oh, damn!
Long way down.
(evil laughter)
♪
It's simple.
Just be one with the
breath of your death!
♪
(screaming)
‐Goemon!
‐Are you all right?
Sen‐‐Sensei.
♪
Let's see now.
According to this map,
well, uh...
Come on, man, would you give
someone else a whack at it?
Huh?
Hm, uh, hold it!
‐Hey guys, it's right here!
‐You're kidding.
You mean we've been staring
at it this whole time?
Yup, Goemon, do your stuff.
Bisect this thing horizontally.
(thudding)
It's hollow.
Oh yeah!
♪
"What's contained herein
would be wasted on a fool."
What the hell does that mean?
It means you should
let me open it.
Very funny, Jigen.
What the?
"Fortune favors cheerful homes."
♪
"The man who can laugh
upon opening this box
has truly achieved
mastery in the greatest
of all the arts,
the art of life.
This is my legacy
to you, Goemon."
(chuckling)
Guess you gotta be an
Iga Ninja to get the joke.
I don't know, I'll bet Fujiko
will find this whole
damn thing very funny.
(laughing)
‐Bye, Sensei.
‐Sensei.
(laughing continues)
♪
♪ Lupin the third ♪
Next time, we discover paradise
is kinda like
Disneyland with hookers.
But just like that other magic
kingdom, this one turns out
to be nothing but an evil scheme
to suck a man completely dry.
Think I'm exaggerating?
Hey, we didn't call this one
Lupin in Paradise for nothin'.
Catch ya later!
♪