♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪♪
♪
Stop!
I said hold it right there!
All right, Lupin.
♪
(grunting)
(laughing)
Oh yeah, finally,
drinks on Zenigata!
Hey, pretty good
Monkey King disguise.
You look just like him.
Hey.
♪
What the hell?
Do I know you?
We're visiting with
the International
Folk Culture Academy.
Oh, so you're teachers
or somethin', is that it?
There was an article
about you guys, wasn't there?
That's right.
We're dressed in period costume
to reenact the journey
of the Monkey King and his gang
along this route
1300 years ago.
Wow.
Well, are you gonna take
these handcuffs off or not?
I'm so sorry.
You see, the truth is,
I thought you were Lupin.
I'll get you out
of those things right now.
It's an honest mistake.
♪
Why'd you make us
come all the way out
to the middle of
nowhere like this?
Movies first,
questions later.
(projector whirring)
What are you, gonna climb
Mount Everest or somethin'?
No, but ever wonder what's
on the other side of it?
Well, it turns out there's
a little country over there
called Kima Senkoku.
Rumor has it there's
a lonely, neglected treasure
locked up in the palace there.
Just breaks my heart.
I remember hearing about
this place as a child.
You can't find it on any map.
It's been closed to visitors
for a thousand years,
and there's only one
way into the place.
Right there.
I went there and checked
it out for myself yesterday.
♪
(gasps)
Those guys really gotta
work on their hospitality.
But for the first
time in 1300 years,
they suddenly decided to
let a small group of scholars
into the country.
They're retracing the
steps of the Monkey King.
Thanks a lot for the
escort, Inspector,
but we'll take it from here.
But somethin's
still botherin' me.
Why, is there
somethin' the matter?
Call me crazy, but my
sixth sense is tellin' me
Lupin's gonna try
to get in here too.
‐(laughing)
‐Huh?
(laughing)
Damn, you're good, Pops.
‐Gotta give you that.
‐Ah!
Oh no, don't tell me
you're really‐‐
Yup.
♪
D'oh!
But wait, how‐‐I mean,
how in the hell did you‐‐
It wasn't you before,
and now it is.
Remember that pit stop?
♪
Well, that's what
modesty'll get ya,
and they kindly
gave us their visas,
so we're all set to go.
Take care, Pops.
It's been a real hoot.
Bleh!
Ha, they forgot
I have a car!
Hm‐‐huh?
Whoa, hey, wait!
Ah, whoa, no, help, hey!
Huh?
(trembling)
♪
Hm, man, that's really gotta
be the weirdest visa ever.
Hey, we're from
the International
Folk Culture Academy.
Lupin, dammit!
Hold it right there.
♪
Crap, crap!
Crap!
Lupin, don't go in there.
You don't know what
you're gettin' into.
No one's ever come
out of there alive.
Thanks, Pops, but there's
a first time for everything.
Catch ya later!
Okay, you wanna die, fine, fine.
♪
Hm, so this is Kima Senkoku.
Looks nice enough.
What's all this?
(gasps)
♪
Could it be?
Yes, it could.
♪
It's gold.
Oh, and, Lupin,
look, it's everywhere!
(gasping)
♪
Hey, wait, just think about it.
If that's the stuff
they leave lyin' around,
imagine the kind of
treasure they must be hidin'
in that palace of theirs.
More, there's
more over here.
I can't believe it.
Greed is a terrible thing.
Eh‐‐hey, someone's coming.
♪
Whoa, now that's my kind
of precious treasure.
You must be from the Academy.
Kinkaku and Ginkaku
welcome you.
♪
Kinkaku and Ginkaku?
Uh, does that mean we're
trapped in a Monkey King story?
♪
So, you're the Monkey King, huh?
Yes, Kinkaku, it is I.
♪
(gasps)
That wouldn't be a gourd?
No, this is only for sake.
See?
Please, honored visitor,
take off your
Monkey King mask now
and enjoy some refreshment.
(grunting)
Hey, this isn't a mask,
it's a one hundred percent
natural monkey face.
You're very handsome.
Ah, in that case.
Wait, man, you're such
a sucker for women.
Don't drink that.
Hey, listen, can you tell us
what the maharajas want with us?
Uh huh, they simply wish
to play a game of
chess with you.
Come on, you're kidding.
Chess was brought to our
country by a very holy man,
and it's become
a national pastime.
Will you accompany us now?
Oh, yeah, yeah, sure.
We'd all be honored.
Hey, you do know they're
talking about shogi,
the Japanese version
of the game, don't you?
Hey, look, Jigen, all I
know is they're saving us
the trouble of
breaking into the place.
Huh?
Is sake supposed to do that?
(grunting)
(coughing)
♪
That's weird.
I wonder where
they all took off to.
Hey, wait a minute,
they're probably already
on their way to the damn palace!
Those rat bastards want
to cut me out of my share.
Of all the nerve!
Oh!
(groaning)
(grunting)
Hm.
Huh?
♪
What do you know, they even
captured Lupin the Third.
Hey, I know you,
you're Joe, aren't you?
(grunts)
Huh, and you were a
hitman named Dom, right?
Hm, I get it.
We all snuck in here
looking for treasure,
and then every single one
of us ended up getting caught.
Huh.
Ooh, smells good.
Ah.
(grunts)
It's awful!
Haven't these guys
ever heard of salt?
Pretty sharp, Sherlock.
You'd better get used to it.
The whole damn
country's just mountains
everywhere you look.
There ain't a grain
of salt anywheres.
Maybe they're just
lookin' out for your health,
you know, a low salt diet.
(heavy footsteps)
This can't be happening.
♪
Huh, quite a surprise, eh?
Let me explain.
That wasn't just
knockout gas you inhaled.
You've all been shrunk now
to the size of chess pieces.
How the hell can that be?
I don't believe it.
♪
‐Whoa!
‐Still think it's some kind
of trick, you arrogant
little pipsqueak?
Well, we've enslaved
the whole country,
so if it is a trick,
it's a pretty damn good one.
Let me go.
♪
‐Lupin!
‐You want to kill him?
Move so much as an inch
and I'll tear him to pieces.
♪
I challenge you to a game
of chess for our freedom.
Interesting idea,
but as far as I'm concerned,
you're already a pawn,
so it'll have to be
a game of human chess.
Did you say human chess?
We needed a chess piece.
You see, chess is how
we choose our maharajas,
so we set a little trap
and you walked right into it.
You should be honored to take
part in this momentous ceremony.
You may not be playing
for your freedom,
but at least it's
a game of chess.
(laughing)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Hey, be a lot more fun
if we played for the treasure
as well as the
maharaja position.
The whole kit and caboodle?
♪
Yeah, sure I mean
the whole thing,
every last bit our ancestors
stole from that holy man.
‐You scared?
‐Big talk.
Put your money
where your mouth is.
You're on.
A fu, right there, ha.
Eight‐four.
Six‐eight, king.
What the freakin' hell?
♪
You force me to
resort to the kyo.
Nine‐two.
Move it, kyo.
Hey, I'm talkin' to you.
Why, you little...
Hm.
Okay.
Move.
Goemon, are you all right?
You big jerk.
Get back to your squares.
Whoa!
Time to stop playin' around.
Watch this,
four‐three, kaku.
♪
Hey, what the hell?
Ow, no, please!
Get your hands off me, come on!
Ow, ow‐‐okay, okay.
♪
(yelping)
Come on, kill the guy!
Looks bad, Ginkaku!
(grunting)
♪
Got him at four‐three!
Yeah, just try to beat that.
Just watch, Ginkaku.
You're a dead man.
Hey, since when is
chess so deadly?
I don't know, I never
learned how to play.
We better get out of here before
they make us fight Goemon.
Yeah, let's do it.
(gasps)
(trembling)
(snickering)
Bye bye.
(screaming)
Ha, you guys'll get the
same if you try anything.
One way or another,
it's a fight to the finish.
(angry grunt)
Go destroy the lance,
bearded one.
(grunting)
♪
Hey, are you guys
tryin' to kill each other?
No, don't worry,
Lupin, it's an act.
♪
Hold it, stop.
You with the lance
and the bearded one,
don't you two think we can
tell when you're fakin' it?
They think they're clever.
Ha!
Hey Jigen, Goemon.
‐Yes?
‐What?
(grunting)
Jigen, Goemon!
Answer a direct question from me
and you're sucked up
into the gourd automatically.
Terrible way to have to die,
dissolved in acid.
♪
They're...
No!
Two‐seven, hisha!
Now check or else!
(grunting)
♪
(screaming)
Now three‐six gin, go!
Ah!
♪
Wow, this place is huge.
Those bastards
better still be here.
♪
(grunting)
(screaming)
Ow!
(laughing)
Now that's more like it.
Yes, but look at him.
He's worn out.
And this should
definitely finish him off.
Kaku at five‐five.
Check!
♪
Hey, that's gotta be
against the rules!
(grunting)
Wait just a minute!
Huh?
♪
Hm, what do you mean,
"Wait a minute?"
Dammit, Ginkaku,
I can think, can't I?
Don't know, can you?
(grunting)
Nah.
Oh, all right,
what the hell.
(laughing)
You'll lose anyway.
I'm takin' a break.
Hm, there must be
a way to win this.
Hm, my thoughts exactly.
♪
Huh.
Sure looks like
a treasure chest.
♪
No, that's not it.
Huh?
No, where is it?
I know there's a move.
♪
This is it.
Stupid book!
♪
What the?
Where'd they go?
(angry grunting)
(shouting)
♪
You little bastards!
Ah!
(trembling)
Lupin!
Huh?
♪
Ooh, Fujiko!
Come on, hurry up!
This way!
♪
Well, at least we'll
be dwarves together.
Dwarf, but Lupin‐‐
Ah...
It's all right.
(laughing)
♪
(heavy footsteps)
What was that?
Where are the other guys?
Dead.
Dissolved in acid.
(gasps)
(snoring)
♪
In this thing.
We got to at least
get their bones back,
give 'em a proper burial.
♪
(panting)
Ginkaku!
Hey, wake up, will ya?
Come on now.
♪
(snoring)
Huh?
Ginkaku, listen.
The Lupin piece escaped.
Huh?
He can't have gotten very far.
♪
All that dwarf stuff's
just a bunch of bull.
They just sit inside and
manipulate giant robots
of themselves.
Why, those little...
Lupin, I've got
the treasure chest.
Let's get out of here.
Just this one last thing, okay?
Whoa!
Come on, Lupin,
it can't be done.
I know, I'll just answer
my own question.
That you, Lupin?
Yeah.
(grunting)
(panting)
♪
Jigen, Goemon,
I just can't look.
They didn't deserve
to die like this.
Lupin!
Over here.
Hi.
Holy crap!
You're actually alive?
(grunting)
Just do it and get out!
Huh?
Hm, a female piece.
This should liven things up.
Ah, help, Lupin!
Help me now!
(shouting)
♪
Lupin!
Oh no!
(laughing)
What a shame.
♪
Hm.
(laughing)
Looks like even their
bones have dissolved.
(whistling)
‐Hm?
‐Huh?
Huh?
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪♪
(laughing)
You're supposed to be
dead, you little bastard!
Yeah, but we had other plans.
♪
Yeah, he's pretty
handy with that sword.
What's up, Ginkaku?
Cat got your tongue?
Hello!
Huh‐‐oh yes, I, uh‐‐
(grunting)
(screaming)
(angry grunting)
Ginkaku!
Why you little!
Huh?
(angry grunting)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Nobody gets away
from me, understand?
Nobody!
Lupin, he's gainin' on us.
Hey, jettison
anything that's heavy.
(angry grunting)
♪
What's he doing,
that's my gold.
This is your fault!
What the hell's wrong with you?
We still got the
damn treasure chest.
Isn't that enough?
♪
(screaming)
(thud)
(explosion)
♪
Phew, that was close.
No one's ever
going there again.
♪
Easy.
(grunting)
♪
Maybe it's jewels
or something like that.
Hm.
♪
Huh!
Pops, how did you get here?
Didn't think I'd
just go away, did ya?
Well, this time
you can just relax.
Nobody's gettin' arrested.
Happy new year.
Whoa, all I can say is
a good turn like that's
enough to entitle a guy
to a cut of the treasure.
Thanks anyway, but that's
goin' a step too far.
♪
Huh?
Does someone want
to explain this?
Huh?
Oh!
‐It's salt.
‐It's all relative.
Something in short supply
is sort of a treasure.
Oh...
Hm.
Oh, you guys!
Y'all risked your
stupid lives for that?
What are you, crazy?
♪
No, just a few pieces
short of a set.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Huh?
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
The roulette wheel's spinning,
and I keep on winning,
but where some see
a jackpot, I see a snack,
not the all‐you‐can‐eat buffet
that's invariably hidden away
in the vault where the
management stashes its take.
I mean, that's
where the cash is.
Man, you'll roll in the aisles,
go so helplessly wild,
you'll forget
there's an elevator,
so wear underpants,
it's called "Games of Chance,"
and for now, I'll say,
"Catch you later."
♪