♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(gunshot)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪♪
♪
(chiming)
For centuries, this place
was just another remote
Middle Eastern backwater.
Picturesque, but dirt poor.
Easy prey for various
warlords and imperialists
and other plagues that swept
through here like sandstorms.
But then,
about 100 years ago,
vast oil fields
were discovered here,
and in the blink of an eye,
the country was transformed
into a modern nation.
And not just any
old modern nation,
but in fact one of
the richest countries
in the whole damn world.
Uh, Professor, is all
this going to be on the test?
Very funny.
That's all vaguely
interesting, Lupin,
but what the hell
are we all doing here?
The government got
an extortion note recently.
It's supposed to be a secret,
however, I have my sources.
What'd the note say?
What do they want?
It said cough
up $100 million
or I'll blow up
all the oil fields.
Hundred million?
That's a nice round number.
You figure the government's
gonna pay that?
Yeah, that's
where we come in.
We just stake
out the drop off
and then boom, we swoop in
and snatch up the dough.
But they must have top notch
oil field security.
Why should they even worry?
(explosion)
‐Whoa!
‐Arrgh!
‐(glass breaking)
‐(screaming)
Arrghh!
♪
(yelling)
That's why
they should worry.
Yeah, so much for
top notch security.
Ah, security.
It's a wonderful thing.
You're pathetic,
you know that?
(smack)
(typewriter keys clicking)
♪
No flaw in
the security system.
Are you completely
insane or just stupid?
I'm neither, Minister,
I'm simply reporting the facts.
My men observed
no strangers anywhere
remotely near that oil field.
And yet the
whole thing blew up.
They saw that!
Most likely
it was an accident.
If this was an accident,
I'm Queen Elizabeth.
You, you're from the
intelligence division?
Mohammed Hasan, mm‐hmm.
And what's your
evidence of sabotage?
As your men may
or may not have noticed,
there was an operator
missing at the exact time
of the explosion.
There's a high probability
he's the one who
delivered the explosives.
That's impossible.
All of the
operators go through
a thorough body inspection.
But your machines don't scan
inside the body, do they?
Inside the body?
Hmm‐hmm.
This is your missing
operator's ulcer medicine.
We found it in his apartment.
He took one
of these every day.
Now watch.
♪
What are you doing?
This is a detonator.
(explosion)
‐Ooh!
‐Argh!
You see, your missing operator
may not have ulcers anymore,
but he doesn't have
very much else, either.
Are you telling
us this poor wretch
was turned
into a suicide bomber
without his knowledge?
Who's behind this,
why that's diabolical?
Actually, we're
pretty sure we know,
but it's not much comfort.
Really, who?
Spit it out,
for Allah's sake.
Lawrence The Third.
‐Wha?
‐Who?
As in D.E. Lawrence?
Yes, apparently the grandson
of Lawrence of Arabia
is eager to make his
own mark on the world.
What is known about this man?
Well, I‐‐
The first Lawrence
was a war strategist
without equal.
If his grandson
is anything like him,
then...$100 million could be a
bargain compared to the costs
we risk incurring
in sheer chaos.
Hmm.
There's no time!
You need to decide this now!
You're head of security,
what do you say?
Giving in to
terrorists is madness,
it will just embolden him
and create an
army of imitators.
We need to find him
and make an example of him.
Hmm.
‐If I may interject?
‐(gasps)
There is but one solution.
Your Highness, we're honored
by your presence, sir.
A thousand blessings
upon your family,
and may you rule for‐‐
Please, dispense
with the formality.
As you know, gentlemen,
the oil fields are what
keeps this country alive.
It is indeed the very
blood in our veins.
We will pay this ransom
and pay it gladly.
Oh, my thinking exactly, sir.
♪
Just take care of it.
(laughing)
Ah, yes, it's good to
be the king, but hot.
At least you didn't
have to strap your boobs.
No thanks, but it
did work like a charm.
Did you see the way
those guys hit the deck
when we walked in there?
I think that was
Lupin's favorite part.
Mm‐hmm.
(laughing)
Okay, freeze!
Huh?
Move away from the car.
Come on, you heard me.
But Pops, we can't do both.
That's right, you just
go ahead and mock me.
It's just gonna make
slippin' these sweet babies
on you all
the more pleasurable.
Okay, but watch that step
on the way down.
Step, which one?
(gunfire)
Aagh!
Hya!
♪
You know.
Aargh, oompf.
Ow.
That one.
Come on!
You bastard!
Get back here, Lupin!
♪
This way.
Lupin!
Huh?
Hey!
(crunching)
♪
Hmm, where the
hell did he go?
Hide and seek, huh?
Well, all right.
Hmm.
Ah, very sorry
to disturb you, sir.
‐(mumbling)
‐(scream)
Who did this?
It was three men
and a woman.
They stole burkas
and they also‐‐
So it was them disguising
themselves as women, huh?
Could you untie
me now, help!
(pounding)
♪
Hey, wait, Lupin's jacket.
And Fujiko's blouse.
And Goeman's pants.
I've got you now.
Now, listen here.
Everybody take
off your veils!
Oh, uh gee, gee.
Please, I didn't
mean you any harm.
It's all a big mistake.
(laughing)
Pops is really in for it now,
they're not amused.
(laughing)
I can't watch.
(bashing)
Aaghh!
Get out!
Ow.
(train whistle blows)
(explosion)
♪
"Lawrence of Arabia,
real name T.E. Lawrence,
British soldier,
archaeologist, and writer.
Born 1888, died 1935.
During World War I, passionately
dedicated to the Arab cause.
He helped organize a guerilla
force of desert nomads
in their revolt against
the Ottoman Empire
and led them to victory."
To say that he's revered
in this part of the world
would be a massive
understatement.
Wonderful.
That means Junior's
followers are probably
crazy wild‐eyed fanatics.
What the hell
are we getting into?
I say the greater the challenge,
the greater the glory
and anyway, guys,
$100 million dollars
is plenty enough to bring out
the fanatic in me.
(truck chugging)
He certainly knows how to pick
a spot for this kind of thing.
I didn't even know
this place existed.
Right.
They should be here
any minute now.
Ha, over there.
♪
Let's get right
down to business.
I have been sent here
by Lawrence the Third.
Did you bring
the $100 million?
Yes, it's right here.
♪
All right now both of you,
get away from the Jeep.
And how do we
know you won't just
blow up the oil
fields again, huh?
Mr. Lawrence is descended
from British gentlemen.
And you can trust that
his word is a sacred bond.
‐All of you, let's go!
‐Hey, slow down, Sparky.
‐What's your hurry?
‐Who are you?
Lupin the Third, descended
from a gentleman thief.
So kindly
hand over the dough.
You insolent camel turd.
Shoot them dead, now!
(gunfire)
♪
‐♪ Lupin the Third ♪
‐Cover me!
‐(gun cocking)
‐Drop it.
Dammit.
♪
Very wise.
Drop your guns
or he dies.
Arrgh.
On the count of three.
One, two‐‐
Thank you.
Now we'll just take
the money and be on our way.
(laughing)
‐(gunshot)
‐Ow!
Huh?
‐(laughing)
‐Huh.
Now, please kindly drop
your guns, gentlemen,
and had the money over here.
What the hell?
(laughing)
Excellent work, Ali.
Now, grab his gun.
Uh, I think I'm starting
to get the picture here.
A bit late,
but yes, it's true,
I am Lawrence the Third.
And as cunning as your
grandfather, I see.
You're rather cunning
yourself, Mr. Lupin,
but unfortunately, your
impersonation of the king
only aided my plan.
A true gentleman always admits
when he's been bested.
‐Congratulations.
‐Thank you.
All right,
proceed as planned.
I have a small gift
for you, Mr. Lupin.
Small, but powerful.
Hmm?
But I don't have an ulcer.
Ah.
Well then, think if it as kind
of an anti‐anxiety pill.
You take it and then I won't
have to worry about you
chasing after us.
You crazy son of a bi‐‐
(gulp)
(coughing)
Right, we're finished here.
Move out!
♪
Hiya!
Okay, Goemon,
you take his right leg
I'll take his left one.
Doh, doh, hey guys.
Ow, ooh, ooh, ow, ooh.
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(feet pacing)
We did everything we could.
You know that, Jigen.
Yeah, I know, I know.
Poor Lupin.
Ugh, Land of Goshen.
‐Hmm?
Ugh.
What happened,
are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine, but that horse
laxative almost did me in.
Given what you've
suffered through, Lupin,
there's truly no
disgrace in retreat.
I agree, it's just like what
you said to Lawrence, Lupin,
a real gentleman admits
when he's been defeated.
I'm not beat yet.
Say, what's
this really about?
It's about my big fat ego,
Fujiko, that's what.
He humiliated me and I'm not
gonna let him get away with it.
Look, I wouldn't mind
paying the guy back myself,
but we don't even
know where he is.
Ah, but that's
where you're mistaken.
Hmm?
All you need
to ask and voila...
He's not the only one
with access to technology.
♪
A transmitter?
Yeah, he was too busy gloating
to see me attach it.
(beeping)
♪
He's at 35 degrees north,
145 degrees east.
Hey, guess who
just located us?
Tell me it's not Pops.
‐Yep.
‐Oh, dammit, not again.
Oh, jeez,
this is embarrassing.
Hmm, yeah, this
has got to be them
in this room right here.
‐Up one, right?
‐Mm‐hmm.
Thanks!
(panting)
Ha!
Hmm?
One, two, three, four.
Hold it!
Yes, is anything the matter?
Well, you see,
I'm looking for...
Dammit, what
if I'm wrong again?
I don't want another beating.
(pounding)
Mmm‐mmm‐mmm,
forget it, no way.
Are you okay?
No, I mean yeah, I'm fine.
‐Sorry.
‐Good day.
I mean, what are
the chances anyway?
♪
And yet we can not
rest on our laurels.
This is just the beginning.
But we promised
no more attacks.
He only mentioned
oil fields to me.
He never said anything about
the rest of the country, did he?
(fire crackling)
Don't look so glum.
It won't be long before
everything they own
will fall to us.
A toast to our
auspicious beginnings.
(Arab toast)
(yelling)
♪
Ah, yes, yes.
(lewd giggling)
♪
My God, she's lovely.
Who is that girl?
They tell me they're
from the Emirates,
passing through here on
their way to the capital.
I want her.
♪
Ha.
Lovely.
♪
When she's finished here, Ali,
show her to my tent.
As you wish.
♪
(parrot screeching)
Did you wish to see me?
Ah, yes, my dove, come in.
I've been waiting.
I am honored
to be summoned here,
but, my Lord, I fear
that I am not worthy.
My favor makes you worthy.
Look at me.
I want you to remain here
and live with me.
You mean?
Yes, I am wealthy
and powerful.
More than you can imagine.
You could have
anything you want.
I just don't
know what to‐‐
I mean that it's so...
‐I'm so happy!
‐Hey!
‐Huh?
‐Hold it!
If there's gonna
be any stripping,
I want to go first.
What?
Lupin!
You're going to wish
you stayed away.
Hey, bloody hell,
who are you?
Well, I'm the
disarming distraction.
And in the words
of Regis Philbin,
who wants
to be a millionaire?
(laughing)
Hey, man, what the
hell's so damn funny?
It's just the way you keep
walking into my trap.
We found that
bug you planted.
You might as well
have sent us a telegram
telling us you were coming.
If you're so smart,
then how come
you're surrounded?
‐Ali.
‐(snap)
(gasps)
♪
(laughing)
You were saying, Mr. Lupin?
(wind blowing)
On my signal!
Ready.
‐Aim!
‐No, please, don't kill me!
I don't want to die,
kill them instead!
They're the ones who threatened
me if I didn't help them.
Fujiko, stop it,
what are you doing?
Hey, man, she's finally
showing her true colors.
Hey, bite me, it's
every man for himself now.
Please don't kill me, I swear
I don't even know these guys.
Really, please!
Shut up and have some
dignity, for God's sake.
(makes a raspberry)
Real mature.
Ali, have your men
release the girl.
But she pulled
a gun on you?
Yes, she's a spitfire,
but I can handle her.
I'm looking forward
to handling her.
Huh, release her.
And let's deal with
the others tomorrow.
That should guarantee
an inspired performance
from her tonight.
Dammit, oh, Fujiko,
you traitor!
Grrrr, grrr!
Call me what you want.
I'd rather be a traitor
any old day of the week
than be a loser.
Hey, you're really screwing up
your karma, you know that?
♪
You are one ruthless,
cold‐hearted, she‐devil.
And that's what I love
about you, ha‐ha‐ha‐ha.
I just know when to cut
my losses, that's all.
And you're much, much, more
my kind of man anyway, darling.
Well, the proof of the pudding's
in the eating, they say.
Ah, and am I
your little pudding?
Wait a sec, I mean,
let's savor it, shall we?
‐The night is long.
‐(giggling)
♪
Speaking of which, to make
sure you don't peter out
after a few hours,
I brought this.
My God, you really
are a woman who...
(chuckles)
...really knows what she wants.
Which do you recommend?
Well, I do have a favorite.
All right, give me that one.
All right, lover.
♪
Ah.
Come on,
my pudding, hurry up.
Here I come.
♪
Mmmm.
Feed me.
(purring)
Hurry, darling,
oh, Lawrence, I can't wait.
Listen, Pudding, I'm gonna
let you in on a secret.
My name's not Lawrence.
The whole thing's
just a big scam.
But the name's worth gold
around here, so I took it.
And it's been like
open sesame ever since.
Thanks to those
fools out there,
I live like a king.
(yawn)
I've got power and money,
and now I've got you.
You and I are just birds
of a feather, aren't we?
(laughing)
Let's flock together.
(snoring)
(laughing)
And you're just
a flocking fool.
That aphrodisiac was
one part castalbaum,
one part sleeping pill.
Some of your own medicine.
♪
Now, where the heck
is that remote?
Ah, here it is.
Yes.
♪
Stop!
I was just...
Don't worry, we heard
the entire story.
Hand over the
trigger switch, please.
Now just leave him to us,
and you and your friends
will be released at once.
You really mean that?
I'm a man of my word.
True gentlemen come
in many different aspects.
All right, here it is
and thank you.
All right, men.
♪
Betrayal is not
to be tolerated.
Didn't he always say that?
Huh?
(all agreeing)
What, but hey, what
about all the money?
Hey, I wasn't exactly
in a strong bargaining
position or anything.
Yeah, but couldn't you,
you know...
What, take on the whole group
of them in alphabetical order?
Well, it's not like it'd be
the first time or anything.
‐(rumbling)
‐Huh?
Hey!
(gasps)
(explosion)
(cheering)
♪
May the spirit of the true
Lawrence rain down all.
(praying in Japanese)
♪
Hey look!
Huh?
You think he heard us?
‐Woo!
‐Oh, yeah!
(cheering)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪♪
It's Fujiko's birthday
and the search is on
for the perfect gift.
I swing by the local nudist
colony to pick up something,
but then Pops shows up
and everything goes to pieces.
But once again, my legendary
charm saves the day.
Sort of.
Anyway, check me out
in "My Birthday Pursuit."
Catch you later.
♪