♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(glass breaks)
(singing in Japanese)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(singing in Japanese)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Hmm.
♪
Exquisite.
Yes.
♪
No doubt about it.
It's genuine.
Of course, I know
better than to ask
how you came to be
in possession of it.
But this indeed
Orion's crown.
♪
Ah, crap, I should've
guessed she'd be
after this too.
‐Hold on.
‐Hmm?
Are you sure about this?
Of course I am.
That's what I just
said, didn't I?
I've been appraising
stolen jewelry
since you were in short
pants, young man,
and I won't have you
impugning my professionalism.
(laughs)
We're all professionals
here, ladies and gentlemen.
So...
if the crown's authenticity
has been confirmed for us,
I'm now prepared to accept your
bids for the crown of Orion.
Wait!
Mr. Tatsumaki,
the floor is yours, sir.
Far be it from me to impugn
anybody's professionalism,
but if this guy's right,
then we're talking about
a floor of $10 million
for this thing.
I wouldn't consider
any less than that.
Then I need confirmation
on one more small point.
Was this item
personally stolen by you?
Yes, sir, it was.
Mm‐hmm.
That means far more to me
than any damn appraisal.
I've done business
with Jaguar many times.
This is not a man
who deals in fakes.
Are you deaf?
That's what I just said,
you big, bloated baldy.
(groans)
That man is a good
customer of mine,
and a personal friend.
Someone teach this
weasel some manners!
Well, go for it.
Mm‐hmm.
♪
Hey, come here you!
(groaning)
♪
Hey, newbie.
Why don't you take a turn?
(chuckles)
♪
(water swishing)
I think I'm gonna barf.
That's enough.
We might need the old
fart later, Jaguar.
Know what I mean?
Your endorsement of my
integrity is appreciated.
Mm‐hmm.
But now, at last,
ladies and gentlemen,
let the auction commence.
Ten million.
‐10.1.
‐10.2.
‐10.3.
‐10.5.
‐10.7.
‐11 million.
12 million.
(shocked muttering)
Well...
going once.
♪
$12 million going twice.
(groans)
$12 million going three times.
12.1.
(muttering)
12.2 million.
12.3!
12.7!
Agh!
13 million!
Going once...
going twice...
13 million.
Going three times and...
Congratulations, Mr. Tatsumaki.
The Orion's crown
is all yours.
Jaguar?
Yes?
I wonder if I might
ask a favor of you.
Anything at all.
What can I do for you?
I assumed 12 million
would be more than enough,
so that's all I brought.
I can have the remaining
million here in a day
if you can wait till
then to close the deal.
All right, then,
I will give you until
11:00 tomorrow.
♪
I gotta give those guys
some acting lessons.
I'm gonna be sore
for at least a week.
♪
Sorry about that, old man.
How you doing in there?
Who the hell
could that be?
Hang on just a little
bit longer, okay?
Business hours are
from 10:00 to 6:30.
‐Lupin.
‐Fujiko!
(giggles)
What a ham you are.
Why, thanks.
I'm hoping that your
game plan is a lot
more subtle.
That is, if you're
trying to beat me.
Ballsy bidding, by the way.
But what if you
actually won?
You weren't really gonna pay?
No, of course not.
But I knew Tatsumaki
only had 12 million on him,
and the delay is gonna
buy me the time to snatch
the crown and the money.
Damn, why the hell
didn't I think of that?
‐Ah, shoot.
‐What's the matter?
Nothing really, but...
Wait, you were gonna
steal the crown
from Tatsumaki on
his way back to Japan,
weren't you?
But now, no thanks
to this recent delay,
your whole plan
is screwed up.
Uh, that's it.
That's right, I'll just
let her think she's won.
You can read me
like a book, babe.
It must just break your
heart you're not in Braille.
We'll let him think
you're overconfident.
I'd say you beat me
fair and square this time.
Congratulations, baby.
I'm happy for you.
You really are a gentlemen.
That's me!
So, how about a little‐‐
Aah!
(grunts)
See you later.
(laughs)
By the way,
what's the deal
with Jigen and Goemon
working for thugs
like Tatsumaki and Jaguar?
You guys have some
kind of fight?
Nah, just went
our separate ways.
Boy, that is such a shame.
(airy laugh)
♪
I just lied to
the girl I love
just so I could beat
her in some dumb game.
It's hard to be
a man these days.
(bell rings)
How's it going, Lincoln?
(chuckles)
Just trim my damn
beard, would you?
Sure, you got it.
Hey!
So, I got a good one.
Guy walks into
a barber shop, right?
Mm‐hmm.
But the barber's
in disguise!
It's really just
a former friend
who wants to kill the guy!
Lupin, hey,
hey wait a minute!
Hope I don't get
carried away
and actually hurt
you or anything.
Look, man, I'm sorry, but
I had to make it look good.
They were watching me.
And as a matter of fact,
they're watching me right now.
Huh?
Hmm, I can see what
you're up against.
Tell me what you've
picked up, Jigen.
Not much.
As you can see,
Jaguar's pretty paranoid.
He's got this
prosthetic hand,
the left one.
You know how I'm always
polishing my gun?
Well, that's how he
is with that hand.
It's gotta be more there
than meets the eye.
And the enforcer
dude, Black Cat,
he's a friggin' psychopath.
Thrill killer type.
Got a thing
about his shoes.
Polishes 'em like
Jaguar does with his hand.
No idea what's
up with that.
Hmm.
‐One guy with a hand.
‐Hey, watch it!
♪
What in the world?
Get up here.
Oh!
♪
Coochie, coochie, coo.
Lupin, don't be
such an idiot.
Don't like being
dunked in the water?
You know that I was
constantly being watched.
And you still are.
Hmm.
♪
Now, take it in slowly.
Right.
So, has Tatsumaki
got his money yet?
No, but it's supposedly
coming in from Rome
sometime this afternoon.
I'll bet he's planning
on getting the crown
into Japan by ship
after that, right?
No, he never repeats himself.
I overheard him
on the phone.
From what I could make out,
it sounds like he's
planning on dismantling
the thing for transport.
Great, I'll bet Fujiko
knew that all along.
What are you thinking?
That we better grab
that damn thing
before it happens.
That's...
easier...
said...
than done.
Hmm.
It's gonna be quick.
♪
Hey, he's right over there.
Hurry up.
Well, don't worry.
I'll think of something.
♪
To good business.
Kanpai!
And now, allow me
to be the first
to congratulate you
on your purchase.
Well, it's now or never.
Hmm?
♪
Old Pops?
The ultimate party pooper.
Now!
(canons shoot)
(coughs)
Crap!
The police!
(coughing)
Let's take 'em out!
(shooting)
(grunts)
What are you men
waiting for?
Shoot back!
(gunfire)
♪
(struggling)
No, please!
(Tarzan call)
Huh?
(grunts)
Whoever that damn
monkey is, get him!
(shooting)
This doesn't look very good.
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(whimpers)
♪
(yelps)
(gunshot, glass breaks)
‐Come on, hurry.
‐Gladly!
Oops, clumsy me.
(groans)
I don't know why
I even bother with you.
Because I'm so pretty
you can't help it.
And that's why.
I admit you do
inspire strong feelings
from deep within me.
Feelings of pity
for a total moron.
(sighs)
(gunfire)
How the hell did Pops
find out what was going
on here tonight?
I tipped him off,
that's how.
I said that you were
involved in a big deal
with Tatsumaki and Jaguar.
He got so loud he almost
punctured my eardrum.
So, all of this mayhem
just adds up to one
big fat diversionary tactic.
Exactly.
And if you wanna
go in on it,
the cut is 70/30.
Hey, that's no fair.
(explosion)
(coughing)
That's it, let's go!
Yes, all right then.
Meet me by the
fireplace in my study.
(groans)
(Fujiko gasps)
Who the hell
are you people?
(winces)
(gunfire)
♪
Move in!
Attack!
♪
(chatter)
They're here somewhere.
Be careful, watch your‐‐
(explosion)
Ow.
The fireplace, of course!
I should've known.
Well, just don't
stand around!
I wanna know where
this damn thing leads to!
They couldn't have
gotten too far yet.
Well, he got that
part right anyway.
I couldn't see what
Jaguar did to you up there.
Hey, what are those?
Acupuncture?
Yikes.
I'll tell you, it's
a damn good thing
I tried to cheat you, huh?
♪
(dog barking)
So, what is this?
Nanny's day off?
Everyone's looking
for Fujiko.
She's a loose end.
And yet, not nearly
loose enough.
Yeah, well that briefcase
came up light by 200 grand,
and everybody got
sweated out pretty bad.
That was you,
wasn't it, you bastard?
It was either you
or it was Fujiko.
I did it, but she inspired me.
She was trying
to cheat me.
Yeah, well, it sure
caused a lot of trouble.
Tatsumaki said that
Jaguar should swallow it.
And Jaguar's all like...
"Really, how in the hell
do you figure that?"
Tatsumaki said,
"It happened
under Jaguar's roof,
and anyway, the deal
was already closed."
Jaguar exploded like
a frustrated child,
pounded the table and said
he'd never do business
with him again.
Oh, yeah?
I swear I thought
Jaguar's hand
was just gonna fly off.
Tatsumaki was all
flushed and snorting
like some rutting
old water buffalo.
(snaps fingers)
Hey, I got it!
This is perfect.
‐Hmm?
We can't just stand by
and let these two
wonderful friends
fight like this.
What, why not?
'Cause it's not in our
best interest, that's why.
You're saying I should
reconcile with him?!
Yes, I am.
Mm‐hmm, I am.
The next nearest bid
was a couple million off.
Walking away now over
200 grand is just like
cutting off your nose
to spite your face.
Hmm, you might be right.
I don't know,
Tatsumaki's
pretty ticked off.
Yeah, well...
You can leave that to me.
It may take some diplomacy,
but ultimately,
Jaguar will see
where his interests lie.
Hmm.
Then go ahead.
If you can pull this off,
you can consider
yourself an associate.
Great, and just
one more thing,
buy him off with
a fake crown until
he comes up with the 200.
Are you joking?
You want everyone to know
that Jaguar can be cheated?
The price was 13.
You gotta squeeze this guy.
A real man values honor
above everything else,
and you, sir, have been
dishonored publicly.
Counterfeit dough, is it?
‐I don't like it.
‐Yeah, well, he witnessed
the appraisal.
Anyway, it's gonna be
dark inside that warehouse.
And I can always find
something to shoot at
if it looks like
we're going to need
a little distraction.
Hmm.
(boat engine hums)
Ours is a business
of bastards and cutthroats,
but true friendship
will always endure.
I feel the same way,
my dear Tatsumaki.
And then I think‐‐
what's that?
Don't worry,
don't worry,
it's just me.
The old fool.
Am I interrupting?
‐Yes!
‐Hmm?
Oh, well, I'm sorry.
You see, it's just
in my entire career,
I've never seen such
a beautiful thing.
And I was hoping you
might indulge an old man
and allow me one last peek.
Hey, don't even
think about it!
I don't like this
at all, boss.
That was way too hot.
Hmm?
All right, I'll just...
Wait just a minute.
This is a fake!
‐What?
And this money is a fake!
What did you say?
(growling)
(gunshot)
(gunfire)
♪
It's a nice view
from up here.
That's right,
let him have it!
(gunfire)
I'd say my work here
is just about...
I'm just in the way here.
Jigen, Goemon,
I'm outtie!
(gunfire)
(telephone rings)
Zenigata.
Hey, Pops, it's Lupin.
What's shakin'?
Hey, you still there?
‐Yeah!
‐Yikes!
Take it easy, will you?
You're gonna blow
out a vocal cord.
Just what do you want?
Well, gosh, I mean, if you're
gonna be all grumpy about it.
I was gonna tip you off
about a real juicy scene
going down at warehouse six
with Jaguar and Tatsumaki
and both their gangs.
But now I don't think
I'm going to do that.
(chuckles)
(groaning)
♪
(grunts)
(whack)
♪
You're dead.
(groans)
Huh?
♪
(groans)
Come on, give me your
best shot, twirlin' boy.
(grunting)
(chuckles)
(shouting)
(groans)
You know what?
We really don't get
nearly enough credit
for all of the good things
that we do in this world.
Mm‐hmm.
And after we die,
they'll all be wondering
why things really suck.
♪
You don't need
a crown for that head.
You need a silo.
♪
What the‐‐?
(gasping)
♪
No!
No way.
Someone beat me to it.
♪
Well, guys, I'd love
to stick around,
but there's so many
chumps and just
so little time.
Au revoir.
(laughs)
(engine turns over)
(sirens approaching)
That was close!
Hey, that was Fujiko!
And it's a good bet
Lupin's onboard with her.
You guys cover
the warehouse.
I've got some
deep sea fishing to do.
(chuckles)
(boat drives by)
Huh, Fujiko!
Hey, come on!
They're getting away!
I'm getting a bad
feeling about this.
♪
Fujiko, cut the
damn engine, now!
Crap, I don't get it.
What the hell's
Zenigata want with me?
Shouldn't he be after Lupin?
♪
(Zenigata laughs)
(Fujiko shrieks)
No, not the crown!
(yelps)
Okay, that's it!
They're all right.
They'll be up
any second now.
Take my word for it.
They're just playing possum.
There, see!
Okay, get the rope on 'em.
♪
(chuckles)
Yes!
I did it!
I finally bagged Lupin.
Hey, these are nothing but
inflatable dummies, Inspector!
What?
(growls)
Hey, something's
attached to it!
(explosion)
♪
Ow.
(gasps)
Lupin, help me, please.
I'll split it with you.
Okay, Fujiko.
But none of this
70/30 crap.
Straight down the middle.
No way, you can forget it.
Fine, be that way.
Wait a minute, maybe
if I go down for her...
Hey, wait up!
♪
(dog barks)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Hey, here's a tip:
If you're gonna steal
something from a dead guy,
make sure the dead
guy's actually a dead guy
and not a napping
2,000 year‐old
vampire evil twin,
'cause, well, that
could really suck.
See for yourself in...
"But Your Brother
Was Such a Nice Guy."
Catch you later!
♪