♪
♪ Lupin the third ♪
Hey!
I tell ya, he's in there!
‐I don't care.
‐Yeah, get the ticket.
Is special event
by invitation only.
‐You'll have to leave now.
‐Now be a good boy
and take a hike, or we'll
have to lock you up.
Damn tourist.
Lupin's in there, ya jerks!
♪
I'm from Interpol, what's
the matter with you idiots?
You think you're so
tough with those‐‐woo!
♪
These Russkies aren't
very friendly, are they?
♪
‐Hey, Lupin, there it is.
‐Oh yeah.
‐She's amazing.
‐She?
♪
We didn't come
here for the girl.
Are you clear on that, Lupin?
We're here for the
Teardrop of Aurora,
the diamond on her
head, remember?
I know, I know, she's really
something else though.
I mean, no wonder they call
her the Flower of Moscow.
♪
One performance over,
one about to begin.
♪
(applause)
Yeah.
Got it?
I got the teardrop.
♪
Let's go, Jigenski.
(alarm blaring)
Jigen!
(gunshots firing)
♪
‐You all right?
‐Son of a‐‐
bastards clipped me.
♪
All right, hold on, Jigen,
I'll be right there!
Forget it, I'll be fine.
Go on, or we'll both get killed.
No way, I'm not leaving you!
Lupin, you got five minutes
to rendezvous with Goemon.
Get your ass over there,
leave this to me.
‐I'll catch up with ya later.
‐Hang in there, man.
Stay alive and
we'll get you out!
♪
‐Over here!
‐Wait.
‐Aren't you‐‐
‐Later, this way, quick.
♪
Where am I?
(grunting)
(footsteps approaching)
If you don't mind,
I find guns scary.
You're that ballerina
chick from last night.
Yes, my name is Monika.
Why'd you save me, Monika?
I'll explain it to you
later, we have to go.
Guess I don't have much
choice but to trust ya.
♪
Why'd you stop, keep going.
Shh, just play along.
Open up, it's mandatory
vehicle inspection.
What is this thing here?
You're going to have
to open it for me.
That's a very large trunk
you have there, lady.
‐They're my ballet costumes.
‐Hm?
Hey, you're that ballerina,
aren't you, huh?
♪
You'd never guess, but
I'm huge fan of yours.
May I have autograph?
‐Sure.
‐Thanks.
Okay then, you can go now.
They've got checkpoints now on
all routes leading out of town.
Yeah, well, my buddies
are long gone.
They wouldn't have been dumb
enough to stay here in the city.
What's your excuse,
dumb or just lame?
Oh, a ballerina with
balls, I like that.
♪
What?
You really are
cautious, aren't you?
A lot more so when
women are involved.
Sporting more than
one injury I see.
Nah, just the way it is, women
and betrayal go hand in hand.
Not this one, I'm on your side.
Yeah, and why is that exactly?
Because this time tomorrow
we'll be man and wife.
Whoa, whoa.
‐What did you just say?
‐Here.
♪
Huh?
All you have to do is
put your photo in there
and we'll be Mr.
and Mrs. Ivanov.
‐Are you trying to defect?
‐Yes.
My soul can't live here anymore.
Let me come with you.
It'll be a border
run for two, huh?
I think that we would
make terrific couple.
I would really love for my
partner to hear you say that.
(humming)
Wouldn't you just
love to see me dancing
wearing something like this?
I tend to prefer the real
thing to bad imitations.
What did I do to deserve
a mean comment like that?
Boy, that prima ballerina must
have been a real knockout.
Not you, gah!
It's the diamond, the
damn diamond's a fake.
Huh, do you mean this?
I mean, not only is the
frickin' thing a bogus bauble,
but I let Jigen get
captured lifting it!
I just totally
screwed up this time.
‐He didn't get caught, Lupin.
‐What's that?
I scouted around,
there's no record
of him being detained anywhere.
Yeah, but then where did he go?
Have you considered that
he might have switched this
with the real diamond,
that he just betrayed us?
No.
Jigen's not at all like you.
♪
This really sucks, I mean,
it was gonna be hard enough
rescuing the guy if
we knew where he was,
but what the hell are
we supposed to do now?
♪
That should hold up fine, we
should really get going now.
♪
You look nervous,
what's the matter?
Never been on a
honeymoon before?
This clown over
here, that's Lupin.
He's been designated a menace to
about 187 different countries.
No scheme too elaborate for him.
If he wants it, he takes it.
Guy with the hat
next to him is Jigen.
Trigger man, armed and
extremely dangerous.
Hm?
‐I knew it.
‐So what's it say?
‐Have you located Lupin?
‐This incident occurred
in Russia, Inspector, it
is not matter for Interpol.
Interpol sent me here
to capture Lupin,
and that's exactly
what I'm gonna do!
Mother Russia has absolutely
no interest in joining Interpol
or any other such organization!
How 'bout as kind of a favor,
since I'm such a nice guy?
‐Out!
‐Come on, comrade.
I'll throw on some
Japanese vodka.
Please, I'm beggin' ya!
Set up priority
dragnet on these two.
Check every airport, highway,
train station, and port.
I don't want them
getting near the border.
(train whistle blowing)
♪
Is it me or does this
train seem right out
of From Russia With Love?
Necessity's the
mother of invention.
An airplane would
be too obvious.
Yeah, there you go,
you'll do well anywhere
with that kinda
spunk and ingenuity.
When you go against
security forces
you're either creative or dead.
Then we better stay creative.
♪
We're coming to the
border very soon.
Yeah, there will
be an inspection.
There's nothing to worry about.
They'll look at the
passports and move on.
That would be nice.
Sorry to disturb you, we're
crossing the border soon,
we need to check your
luggage and passports.
Thank you for your cooperation.
‐Hold it.
‐Huh?
Supposed to check our
luggage, aren't ya?
Security!
‐We gotta bounce.
‐But there's no place to go.
Unlock this door or we'll shoot!
♪
‐Yeah, piece of cake.
‐No, Jigen, I can't!
♪
♪ Lupin the third ♪
(gunshots firing)
Hey!
Notify border patrol right away!
(train rumbling)
Thank you for saving my life.
It's too soon for
talk like that.
Next station, this whole train
will be crawling with guards
turning the whole place upside
down looking for you and me.
So what do we do now?
Well, uh, how's
your vertical leap?
You're asking a ballerina
if she can jump?
Oh yeah, right.
Okay, we're gonna grab on to
that overpass right there.
You'll be fine,
just think of this
as the grandest jeté
of your whole career.
On your mark, get set, and go!
(panting)
(grunting)
‐This damn shoulder.
‐Oh, Jigen, here.
Give me your hand.
♪
Was close.
You're like my
guardian angel lately.
Believe me, Jigen,
I'm no one's angel,
and you don't owe me a thing.
If anybody's been
blessed it's me.
‐You know, I‐‐
‐Hm?
♪
What is it?
Never mind.
Well, what do you say?
We got quite a trek
ahead of us, you ready?
♪
Hmm, looks like they really
put some thought into this.
My guess is the new Road to
Berlin would be too risky.
So that leaves
Austria via railroad.
Still, just to be safe
I want the fugitive
alert in every county.
Yes, sir.
♪
‐Get that, Lupin?
‐Sure did.
Let's just hope
their theory's right,
and Jigen's not on
his way to Berlin.
They said, "they," do you think
Jigen's traveling with someone?
That is not his standard
operating procedure.
Hm, you know, you might
have something there.
♪
It's a beautiful day,
with a little luck,
we could make it across
the Czech border today.
The Czech police will
be looking for us,
but if we can cross
into Austria‐‐
Say, assuming
this all works out,
what are your plans
after it's all over?
Uh, I want to make my way
to the United States.
Yeah, well, makes sense, I mean,
if you're talented enough to be
known as the Flower of Moscow
back home, I'm sure the
American ballet world
would greet you with open arms.
(birds chirping)
What's so great about
the United States?
The freedom there.
Yeah, if you can
afford it, that is.
Jazz, disco, and musical
theater, and all the fashions
from everywhere,
America has everything.
Gangs, drugs,
violence, pornography.
Yeah, they got a lot
of everything there.
♪
It's so quiet.
The quiet is my
second great love.
♪
You know, I never
saw myself in a scene
like this with someone like you.
♪
(wind howling)
(fire crackling)
Oh, got something to eat.
Oh!
Jigen, you should ask for help.
It was feelin' a
little loose is all.
Here.
It all comes down to tomorrow.
Yep, cross into Austria,
then into America.
Very exciting.
♪
Freedom's just on
the other side.
Yeah, it seems pretty
sparsely guarded.
I think that we're in luck, but
don't forget, every damn guard
at every damn border crossing
has pictures of both of us.
‐So, then what now?
‐Well, you tell me, Monika.
I didn't come this
far just to give up.
‐No turning back, understand?
‐Mhm.
I'd sure like to see Lupin's
face when he finds out
that I died in the company
of a beautiful ballerina.
♪
Huh?
(engine buzzing)
Hey, border crossing, stop!
(gunshots firing)
♪
This is it!
What do you know,
right on schedule.
I've been looking
forward to this.
♪
Damn it!
‐What're you doing, Jigen?
‐Now listen,
you're just gonna have
to trust me on this, okay?
All right, whatever you say.
(screaming)
Jigen, I'll be waiting!
♪
Might wanna reconsider
that, Monika,
that wait could be kinda long.
♪
You know where you can put that.
One day world will thank us
for getting rid of
capitalist parasites.
♪
Ready, aim...
‐What a way to go out.
‐Fire!
(explosion)
Huh?
‐Look, exploding snow!
‐Idiot!
Somebody set off a
charge on the hill!
‐I knew that!
‐Run!
(yelling)
Huh?
(grunting)
‐Lupin!
‐Yeah, it's me, who else?
Goemon's waiting too.
Let's see if we can escape
together this time.
♪
Huh, look, it's a blimp.
Crap, they got away!
Cease fire!
They're already in
Austrian airspace.
♪
Welcome back, Jigen.
Yeah, why the great stone face?
I mean, a few words of
thanks are usually customary
at times like this you know.
Hey, I didn't ask
for any of your help.
In fact, you blew
it for me, Lupin.
I was hopin' I'd seen the
last of your damn monkey face.
By the way, Jigen, were
you traveling alone?
♪
I can't believe
you're here with me.
You know I wouldn't have missed
this for anything in the world.
♪
You're the most reliable
man on the planet,
I don't know how I
can ever thank you.
I don't know what I
did for you to thank me.
You smuggled the
Teardrop of Aurora
all this way just for me.
Hm?
♪
Just calmly do what I say.
Take off your jacket.
Underneath your bandage there's
a stone wrapped in cotton.
I'm surprised you never noticed.
Now please, hand it over to me.
♪
Was it your plan from
the very beginning
to use me as a courier?
Wasn't it you who told me
freedom isn't exactly free?
I think you
miscalculated just a bit.
I doubt it, a performer
can tell the difference
between an act
and the real thing.
Now hand it over.
Looks like my partner
gets the last laugh again.
♪
Pardon the interruption,
but here's the deal.
Hand it over and I promise
not to say, "I told you so,"
and you get to live, Monika.
♪
(sighing)
Guess I'm out of my league.
Not bad for an amateur.
♪
I only really saved you one
time, and you saved me twice.
What do you say we
call it all even?
I don't know what to say.
Hm, gonna remember this
one for a real long time.
♪
What the hell's the
matter with you?
I was supposed to give that
to Fujiko, you big jerk!
Huh, give me a break.
What the hell do you see
in that woman anyway?
Huh, well, I mean, yeah,
sometimes she betrays me,
but, uh, that's all
just part of her charm.
Damn, Lupin, you're
really pathetic.
‐Hm, what'd you just say?
‐Nothin'.
My shoulder's killin'
me, that's all.
You're just jealous,
Jigen, I can tell!
Softy, romantic, big phony!
Oops, wait a minute,
almost forgot.
♪
Hm, Mr. and Mrs. Ivanov.
Here's a divorce.
♪
♪ Lupin the third ♪
This next one's just
too weird for words.
It's sort of Twilight Zone
meets House of Wax
meets an exhausted writing
staff under deadline pressure.
I can't even tell if the
villain's a real woman or not.
I mean, can you?
Thank goodness some things
are always predictable.
You won't forget this one,
it's "Madame Prefers
Them Hand‐Dipped."
Catch ya later!
♪