♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
(glass shattering)
(singing in Japanese)
♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
(singing in Japanese)
♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
(boat horn)
♪
(siren wailing)
Hmm.
♪
Hey, what's going on?
Oh, the harbor master's
given mandate to perform
random inspections as part
of our anti‐smuggling effort.
So, we'll just be poking
around for a little bit.
♪
Just go right ahead;
knock yourselves out.
♪
(grunting)
Hmm.
Can't find a speck of dirt,
let alone, diamonds.
Are you sure this
is the right ship?
I mean, how reliable
is your source on this?
Well, Jigen, it doesn't
get any more reliable.
I got in from Kou Chin Ko's
own lips when I broke
into his house.
I do far more painful things
to humans every day.
(cackling)
Well, then, you figure
maybe it's possible
they already moved the stuff?
Nah, I've been tracking
this old tub
for weeks, you know?
Really?
Yup.
So, have you found
whatever it is
you're looking for?
(chuckles)
Hey, over here.
Hmm, what is it?
Something's behind here.
It's hollow.
Huh.
(gunfire)
What have we here?
You gotta be kidding me.
I'm afraid it appears
the yolk's on us, old friend.
I'm not laughing.
Ha, those prized birds
are for Mr. Kou Chin Ko.
Not exactly
contraband, are they?
(clucking)
Here, hate to see ya
leave empty‐handed.
Oh, no, we couldn't possibly.
♪
(chuckles)
So long, suckers!
♪
(typewriter clicking)
(chuckling)
♪
I'll have you know, my dear,
that no one is more devoted
to the art
of fine dining than I am.
And what have I learned
from all this, you might ask?
♪
That in the humble
egg of the hen,
nature has, in fact,
provided us with
the ultimate dining experience.
Oh.
Surround yourself with three
things for happiness:
Some delectable things,
strong things,
and things of unusual beauty.
And, as I happen to have
all three with me this evening,
I pronounce myself
the happiest man alive.
(laughs)
That's very sweet of you,
Mr. Kou Chin Ko, but the honor's
truly all mine.
I mean, how often
is a girl asked
to dine with the man
they call the emperor
of the Hong Kong Night?
Well, for you,
it could be very often.
Guess three times
a day at least.
(chuckles)
♪
As a matter of fact,
if it's convenient for you,
it would be my pleasure
to have you come by
my house tomorrow.
I'd be absolutely
honored to come.
Your beauty,
my chef's delicacies,
and the martial arts competition
I've scheduled
should guarantee us both
a very happy day.
(giggles)
Can I tempt you, dear?
Raw?
Oh, no, really,
that's not necessary.
How do you like them,
sunny‐side up?
(grunts)
(chuckles)
♪
(sizzling)
(gasps)
♪
Okay, so far,
so good, that's her.
Now, all I have to do
is wait for Lupin to show up.
Until then, just blend in
and don't draw any attention
to yourself.
Can I take your order now, sir?
Yeah, I want Lupin,
and if you can't
bring me that, go away!
Huh?
(sneezes)
I'm freezing to death out here!
Hmm.
And, man, there sure
ain't anything happening.
Let's pack it in and go
get a bite somewhere.
Nah, nah, come on now,
don't be so impatient.
Hey, look!
Huh, what, what is it?
♪
Looks like
the hen house is on the move.
♪
(squeaking)
Bingo, the Dragonbaum Garden;
that's Kou Chin Ko's place.
♪
Well, you must be right;
guy wouldn't be unloading
a bunch of chickens
in the middle of the night.
Yeah, the guy is a weird one,
but I don't think he got
to be king of the Hong Kong
underworld on weirdness alone.
(waves crashing)
(birds chirping)
Gonna be a lot
of activity there today
with that big martial arts
invitational going on.
(whistles)
That's a pretty
good setup for some
behind‐the‐scenes wholesaling.
Mm‐hmm, but we'll have
all the angles covered.
♪
I see us walking away
with the diamonds
and the blue ribbon.
♪
Now, listen you,
I'm with INTERPOL,
so don't mess with me!
Look, I saw the girl
with your boss last night,
so I know she's here, and that
means Lupin's here somewhere!
I got a warrant for him!
I don't care if you're from
the North Pole and you work
for Santa Claus;
you'll not enter this house.
So, take a hike!
♪
Are you threatening me?
I should give you fair warning
that even though I work
at INTERPOL, you're tangling
with a certified black belt!
Yeah, you tell him, Pops,
go Japan, woo‐hoo!
Huh, wait a minute, that's him!
Hey!
(grunts)
(groans)
Now, whaddaya say to that?
(screaming)
♪
(groaning)
(caterwauling)
Took four of ya,
though, didn't it?
♪
(various grunts)
Hmm?
♪
Place looks like
damn function room
in a Chinese restaurant
in North Dakota!
♪
Well, looks like Little
Big Man's finally arrived.
(applause)
And looky what he's got
hanging on his arm.
Well, well.
(chuckling)
That's where the little minx
disappeared to out
of the blue, Jigen.
Looks as though we've got
ourselves some competition.
(applause)
(chuckling)
(nervous tittering)
(chuckles)
(applause)
(grunts)
(nervous tittering)
No, please, I‐I‐‐
No, help!
(yelping)
(bloodcurdling screams)
♪
(gasping)
(gong crashes)
As life begins with
the incredible egg,
true beauty begins with
exquisite physical strength.
(egg cracks)
Those as strong as you
are human masterpieces.
Welcome!
(cheering)
And now, let Kou Chin Ko's
martial arts
invitational challenge
commence immediately!
Or, as they say
on Bourbon Street,
(speaking French)
Mm‐hmm.
♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
Nobody's gonna keep me
from nabbing Lupin!
I don't care where the hell
I have to break into!
Whoa!
♪
Now, one for the money,
two for the show,
three to get ready,
and four to go!
Whoa!
(buzzing)
(explosion)
They're in there?
Hey, wait a minute;
what the hell are these?
I don't believe it.
He actually keeps the menus
from every one of his
frickin' favorite restaurants!
And locked away in his
friggin' safe, no less.
Makes sense; sports stars
need big trophy rooms,
this guy needs
a big crapper.
You really think he'd
be hiding 'em in his bathroom?
I'm not sure I'd put
anything past this freak.
Hmm.
"You're even more handsome
when you're naked.
You're even more handsome
when you're naked."
Holy crap, that's so bizarre,
even I can't top it.
(grunting)
♪
Goemon Ishikawa!
Heh, the Japanese samurai
is doing very well, isn't he?
(derisive grunt)
Patience; if the samurai
makes it to the final contest,
I'll see to it you get
to challenge him.
(chuckles)
Meanwhile, Lupin and Jigen
have just disappeared.
I'd better get moving here.
Excuse me.
♪
(grunting)
Huh, we've turned
this whole place upside down.
Yup, and the wheeling
and dealing should
be starting anytime now.
I just don't get it.
(laughs)
Couple of them sewer rats.
Those two are going
to wish they had stayed put
where they belong.
The one in the red jacket
known as Lupin the 3rd.
They pose no threat,
but the sight of such vermin
offends my eyes.
See to it they're eliminated.
(chuckles)
♪
Come on, Lupin.
It's a bust; let's just
get Goemon and go home.
I'm not ready
to give up on this.
(groans)
Well, hello, there, gorgeous!
Well, now I don't suppose
you'd know were
the diamonds are, hmm?
Hey, you two, get a room, huh?
Huh, someone say "get a room"?
Yeah, a secret room, too,
just like on the ship.
(mass clucking)
Well, cock‐a‐doodle‐doo.
Never knew you were
fluent in chicken.
Oh, I'm real good
with fowl language,
I just wish these
damn birds could speak human.
Yeah, and if they could,
what do you think they'd say?
(grunting)
Maybe, "Nice knowing ya"?
I see our little rat problem
has been successfully addressed.
Except for the fat
little egg‐shaped one.
He's fat because he's smarter;
he knows where
all the cheese is,
or should I say
in this case, the diamonds.
Hmm.
Sign them both up
for the swim team.
Uh.
(grunting)
Yes, well,
all right, Daimangon.
You've earned
a little recreation.
(affirmative grunting)
Not too big a mess, please.
The cleaning girl's
not in till Monday.
(gong crashes)
(chuckles)
After you, old buddy.
What, am I supposed
to thank you?
What a guy!
It's Daimangon
versus the sewer rats!
(grunting)
♪
Hey, two against one, no fair!
A three‐minute egg
must boil for three minutes.
You really find out
who your friends are
when you're getting
an ass‐whuppin' by
a human gorilla.
(yelping)
♪
(laughing)
Mr. Kou Chin Ko,
I'm afraid the customers
are growing impatient.
Later!
(laughs)
But Mr. Kou Chin Ko, please,
the hens are just about to race.
All right, you grill them
nice and slow now, Daimangon,
and, after the egg auction,
we'll have them with
a little Hollandaise sauce,
all right?
Egg auction, what the hell
does he mean by that?
(clucking)
If it's what I think it is,
this guy's a cluckin' genius!
(grunts)
Whoa, see ya, Jigen,
watch your ass!
Hey, Lupin, hey, dammit!
(yelps)
Chick‐chick here
and a chick‐chick there.
Here, a chick,
there, a chick,
everywhere a chick‐chick.
(clucking)
I hope you enjoyed
the entertainment,
but now, let's get
down to business.
Are all of you prepared
to begin the auction now?
Yeah, I'm ready, but ain't
you forgetting something?
Where the hell are the diamonds?
I may be a little eccentric,
but I'm not insane.
It's all right here,
right in front of you.
Huh, huh, huh?
What are you talking about?
Yeah, come on, Kou Chin Ko,
what the hell's the game here?
This is no time for
a snack, we're all very‐‐
Holy‐‐
Wow, so that's how you hid 'em?
Gentlemen, things are not
always as they seem.
Granted, the process
is somewhat painful
for the chickens themselves,
but who cares about that, eh?
I do far more painful things
to humans every day.
And pain's a good thing,
builds character.
(cackles)
♪
Well, since the cat's
already out of the bag.
(meowing)
Huh?
(yelping)
(growling)
♪
(humming)
(growling)
May I cut in?
Huh?
You know, a bit earlier
would have been kinda nice,
not that I'm ungrateful.
(grunting)
♪
Get him, you fools!
My eggs!
Get him, stop him now!
Please, those are my eggs!
(gunfire)
♪
Now, I've got a plan.
Oh, it's you!
Over here, quick.
♪
Strung it myself.
You see, admit it now,
you really do care
for me, don't you?
About these, I do.
♪
Yup, she's crazy about me.
(gunfire)
Yikes, forgot all about them!
There he is, quick!
Sorry, boys, three
at once is really unsafe!
Look, I'll show you why.
No, don't you do it!
(screaming)
(panicked yelping)
♪
(chuckles)
Huh, hey, uh.
Ah, yeah!
Hey, what's with all the eggs?
It's a long story.
Where's Goemon?
(chuckles)
(grunting)
♪
Come on, I've got
your trophy right here!
(chuckles)
Uh‐oh!
♪
I got ya completely surrounded!
It's all over, Lupin,
so come out now!
You're rats in a sack, ya hear?
Rats in a sack!
That friggin' blowhard's
so full of hot air.
I don't know,
he looks pretty...hmm.
Hot air, blow hard.
Got an idea?
Mm‐hmm.
(whistles)
Fan out, they're here somewhere!
Please, tell me it's not him?
Catch ya later, Pops!
Lupin, dammit, get back here!
You're under arrest!
(growls)
♪
Our eggs are all
in one basket
and our chestnuts were in
the friggin' fire, man.
And that's why we're
such a great team.
Speaking of fire,
by the way, blow harder,
we're losing altitude!
(blowing)
I still can't believe
this whole thing.
Lemme see one of those
friggin' eggs, will ya?
Ah, my little Fabergé, yes, I‐‐
Huh?
Uh.
Hmm.
Ugh!
Now that thing's
not a chicken, right?
♪
Oh, man, I can't believe
I didn't see this coming!
♪
It's Fujiko; she wouldn't
just abandon a basket
and leave, after all.
♪
I know you're probably
sore with me, lover,
but think of it this way:
I mixed up a new body masque
with all those egg whites,
so at least the next time
you see me, I'll be
even harder to resist.
(giggles)
You know it's all
your friggin' fault!
You just can't think straight
when you're around
that damn chick!
Not with a big head.
The other one's
a steep trap though.
(agonized screaming)
♪
(sighs)
The famous lights of Hong Kong.
Yeah, like a bunch
of diamonds somebody dropped.
I think it was us.
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
Someone had the bright idea
of transporting a fortune
in high‐grade industrial
diamonds in a freakin' missile!
No, really,
it was a bright idea.
I hate it when that happens.
Now, you know me,
I love a good challenge,
and for a guy who found
the technical jargon
of The Jetsons hard
to wade through,
this one's a big challenge!
It's called "Payload"!
Catch ya later!
♪