♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
(gunshot)
♪
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
(truck rattling)
♪
Look, I've spent my
whole career chasing Lupin.
That's not exactly something
to brag about, Inspector.
Well, it makes me the world's
leading authority
on the guy.
Yeah, or something.
Hey, just what...
(groans)
Out of my great respect
for Interpol, however,
I'll give you one chance.
After that,
we do it our way,
and I sincerely hope that
meets with your approval.
Herr Leading Authority!
Mmm.
Hah, what could be
more fair than that?
I've been waiting
a long time to slap
a pair of cuffs
on that guy
and haul his buns
in front of a judge.
Don't bother, we'll
just shoot him here.
What?
Man, are you crazy?
Huh?
I'm going to pretend
I didn't hear that, Inspector,
but consider yourself warned.
In the words of
our great leader,
you're either with us or
you're little ass is grass.
♪
(grunts)
(sneezes)
I'm being mocked,
I can just tell.
Someone somewhere
is having great fun
at my expense.
Und it just makes me
want to grab a quill...
(groans)
... und stab an inflatable globe!
(pops)
♪
(sneezes)
Now I'm getting a cold.
What's next?
I had to ask.
(grunts)
(gunfire)
(glass shatters)
Wow!
Fujiko, today's not
Friday the 13th, is it?
No, and since when are
you superstitious anyway?
You're the one who
always said you make
your own luck in life.
Man, you're annoying.
Or, I guess, I'm annoying.
Okay, with this
Walther P38
and two machine guns,
the two of us together
are gonna make enough
luck to take on the whole
damn Jahidian Army.
♪
One, two, testing, testing.
Huh?
Hey, that's Pops.
Never thought I'd be
happy to hear his voice.
Now, listen,
and listen good, Lupin.
I'm your only hope here.
These guys want you dead,
but I just want
to take you back home
to stand trial.
Oh, he can have a trial,
as long as we get
to kill him first.
You can tell he has
no idea he's being used.
I'm sure that's 'cause
he has no idea who
his new friends are.
Those guys are ruthless.
That's putting it mildly.
The commander out there,
Hess, tortured his own sister
to death for treason.
Imagine how he deals with
people he doesn't like.
No, I won't,
and you shouldn't either.
You're only torturing yourself.
It went bad, that's all.
Yeah, but still,
I can't stop playing it
over and over in my mind.
The whole thing's
so damn stupid.
(crowd cheering)
♪
(clears throat)
It's our destiny!
Our sacred obligation!
Our duty!
The great noble Gahuenga race
must now rise up.
Under certain
divine supremacy!
(crowd cheers)
♪
(grunts)
(helicopter blades beating)
(shutter snaps)
♪
All right,
take it in lower.
Much lower.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, I got it.
Left breast pocket.
And, man, it's big.
♪
Ugh!
Let's rescue it from
that hideous setting.
Down one more time, Jigen.
And try to hold it!
Now, let's see if the
rubies are biting today.
Any who would foolishly
doubt our claim
to genetic superiority
need only look at us
with the eyes free
of the cataracts of envy!
We are gorgeous!
Hah, am I right?
The cheekbones, the jaw,
the noble earlobes.
(winding spool)
All right, almost,
just a little to the right.
Ah, yeah, good.
A coincidence?
No, it's in the genes!
In the genes!
(crowd chants "Hatler")
♪
Huh, they really adore me.
How's it going, Lupin?
Are you close yet?
(crowd continues chant)
Yeah, I'm there.
Whoa, Jigen,
what's going on?
The wind's picking up.
I'm trying to steady her out.
Huh?
(crowd chants "Hatler")
(crowd shouts in disgust)
As I was saying...
Get them!
Yah!
(gunfire)
(helicopter blades beating)
(fire crackling)
(gasping)
(grunts)
(explosion)
♪
Quick, you guys
get Jigen out of here.
I'll do my best
to buy some time.
I guess he's right.
♪
(gunshots)
(groaning)
♪
(gunfire)
Ah!
♪
Yeah, come on,
I got you right...
(soldiers chuckle)
(yelps)
(groaning)
Huh?
Fujiko!
I thought I told you
to get the hell out of here.
Ooh, you're gonna
discipline me now?
♪
Man, I really hope
those two guys
got out okay.
You know, you're
a pretty amazing guy
all worried about
Jigen and Goemon
when your own life
is hanging by a thread.
I just want them to come
back and rescue us,
that's all.
Right.
(bell tolls)
(marching)
♪
So, you seeing anyone?
Nah, you?
You kidding?
Who's got time?
(grunting)
I hear you.
Are we too career‐oriented?
I'm telling you,
he's a master of disguise.
Large numbers tend
to work to his advantage.
Just give me four
of your best guys.
Und will there
be anything else?
With these things, I've got
all the hardware I need.
(magazine clicks)
I'm certain that Pops
is going to get a courtesy
shot at us.
♪
(whimpers)
(water bubbling)
The problem is when
old Pops comes back
empty‐handed, it'll
be you and me against
the barbarian hoard out there.
‐I hear something.
‐What is it?
Goemon and Jigen.
I could swear I heard
them calling us now.
Oh, man, I wish it were true.
It's like they're
somewhere nearby.
Lupin, Fujiko.
(grunting)
♪
Hey...
‐Huh?
Careful.
Hey, looks like we're in
the basement of the castle.
Hmm.
Ugh, what were
the friggin' chances?
I mean, jeez.
All right, drop it, Lupin,
it's all over.
That's right, Lupin,
there's really no point
in trying to put
up a fight when
I'm your best chance
of getting out of
this mess alive.
Take him, boys.
Easy now.
(malicious chuckle)
♪
What the‐‐where
the hell is he?
‐Pee‐a‐boo.
‐Huh?
‐(gunshot)
‐Ah!
(grunting)
Eins!
Zwei!
Drei!
And whatever the hell
"four" is in German.
Now, Lupin, the more
you make Hess mad,
the harder it's all
gonna be for you.
As a matter of fact, Pops,
that's my whole game plan.
There's no hope so I might
as well go out with a big bang.
Ah, Lupin, you can't be
serious about that now, can you?
In fact...
(chuckles)
...you're coming with me!
(grunts)
Ow.
Clumsy me.
No hard feelings, Pops.
(gasps)
♪
You've had your
chance, Inspector,
und now the only
trial he'll see
is trial by fire.
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
Commander squad!
Jawohl!
Lupin is to be
shot on site.
If you fail, I expect
you to shoot each other.
Jawohl.
Your Excellency, good news.
The great insult
to your dignity
is about to be avenged.
They assaulted
the dignity
of the whole nation!
Oh, of course.
Hmm, why am I having
such a hard time
getting people to see that?!
I need a little "me time."
♪
They're playing
our song, darling.
♪
(shouts)
You're dead!
Fujiko, listen here.
Huh?
There's no reason for
both of us to die here.
I'll make a deal with him.
Ugh, but Lupin!
Yo, Pops, you still here?
Listen, I'm not gonna
let you take me alive,
but I'm sending
Fujiko out.
I want your word
you'll personally
take custody of her
and see to it that
she gets back to Japan safely.
I'm not leaving.
All right, now flash
the searchlight three times
if we have a deal.
Good, at least you won't
die like a rat in a trap
just 'cause I screwed up.
Get going.
Forget it.
Hey, it's my last request.
But I...
No more words.
♪
(Fujiko sighs)
It's all good now.
Whatever else happens,
it's all good.
(Fujiko screams)
(grunts)
Fujiko!
(gasps)
♪
(gunshot)
Here, don't look.
Hmm, it doesn't
seem to be poisoned.
You're lucky.
(gunfire)
Well, it looks like you're
stuck with me after all.
(gunfire)
(muffled screaming)
Didn't I tell you
he would snap
if we murdered the girl?
Hmm.
See for yourself.
(gunfire)
(muffled screaming)
(yells)
(grunting)
That's it,
down to the pistol.
How in the world
am I supposed to create
my own luck now?
Hey, it's a beautiful night.
We're all alone.
Most guys would call
that pretty lucky.
Hmm.
Mobilize the tanks now!
Jawohl.
(yelling in foreign language)
Not the tanks,
you big gorilla!
Can't you see,
that's just what he wants.
He thrives on chaos.
(motor engine rattles)
♪
Come on, now, come on.
(rumbling)
♪
I have a confession to make.
I'm kind of glad
that guy stabbed you.
You know, Lupin,
you probably wouldn't
want to put that
on a Valentine,
and yet somehow it's
the sweetest thing
I've ever heard.
This is General Hess of
the Jahidian National Army.
You have until first light
to surrender unconditionally.
(wheels squeaking)
After that, the castle
will be destroyed
by the artillery
that you see.
‐Lupin.
‐Hmm?
Promise me something.
What?
When it comes
down to it,
you know, at the end,
I'd feel better if it
was you who took me out.
♪
That's asking a lot, you know?
Any plan that comes
down to my sewing skills...
Mmm.
♪
Ah, damn it,
see what I mean?
♪
It's dawn, Fuj.
This is either the dumbest
idea we've ever had
or, no, it probably is.
Two men look out
through the same bars.
One sees the mud,
one sees the stars.
♪
Uh‐huh.
Your friend has chosen
a terrible death, Inspector,
and yet not nearly
as terrible as I would
have preferred.
Ready on my command!
Fire!
(artillery fire)
Okay then, I think we
can now safely conclude
that Hess wasn't bluffing.
Do you think you can
get a line on him
through all that smoke?
Sort of.
‐(gunshot)
‐Ah!
That does it!
Oh, now I'm really mad!
(blasts)
(rumbling)
Hang in there!
At least till
I can get you.
(explosions)
And there are still
two left for us.
Are you sure?
Uh, you know, I mean...
Uh‐huh.
♪
Fujiko, I...
No more words.
♪
What the hell?
I mean, either the stairway
to heaven is out or...
‐Huh?
♪
Or we're saved.
Gee, they sure know how
to cut it close, don't they?
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
What is that thing?
(muffled shouting)
So, their friends are back.
Artillery!
On my command!
♪
Huh?
Your Excellency, wait,
don't shoot at it!
Hold your fire!
♪
His Excellency.
(German phrase)
♪ I ain't got
any worries ♪
♪ I ain't got any money ♪
♪ But luck seems to follow
wherever I go ♪
Why, zat little...
♪
♪ Didn't even know
they came ♪
Argh!
Damn it!
♪ I can't be lucky in love ♪
♪ All my four leaf
clovers can be no good ♪
See you later, Lupin,
you'll be hearing from me!
♪ Couldn't help
but loving you ♪
You did what?
Who's responsible?
I want the man in
my office immediately!
Ze man is already
there, Excellency,
because it was, well, you!
Me?
Are you crazy?
That's it, Hess!
It's the firing squad for you!
Excellency!
(banging)
Feeling overworked?
Opportunities in
toxicology are wide open.
(laughing)
Thanks for the
hospitality, General,
and good luck!
Woo‐hoo!
Look out, Lupin,
here I come!
(laughs)
♪
Heh, I've been
meaning to ask you,
how'd that flesh
wound of yours heal up?
I'm as good as new.
Really?
Ooh, I'll just...
Lupin!
Whoa!
♪
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no!
♪
Hey, we've done all
we can for the guy.
He's on his own this time.
(shouting)
Whoa, what's that?
Hey, wait a minute!
‐I can't stop!
‐It's Lupin!
Whoa!
Ahh!
Wait, please help me.
Get away from me.
Whoa!
(groaning)
♪ Lupin the 3rd ♪
Watch out.
Goemon's out
for revenge
when his ninja master
gets murdered.
This one's got everything.
Bit stakes,
big action,
big laughs,
no girls, though.
Not a damn skirt in sight.
So, I said, "Hell with it!
Give it to Goemon."
Turned out pretty good.
Kid's got potential.
Check it out,
it's called
"The Last Mastery."
Catch you later!
♪