♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(gunshot)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(horn blaring)
♪
(bell jingling)
Hmm?
Hmm.
(laughing)
Ya, come on, baby,
come to Daddy now.
(chuckling)
Ha‐ha, great whites
off the starboard bow!
(chuckling)
Lupin!
Yeah?
You rang?
We didn't come to Germany
so you could be a
Peeping Tom, you know.
Hey, I told you guys
I'd reveal everything
once we got over here.
Doesn't this qualify?
Ooh, I think I caught
me a feisty one.
Maybe she'll invite
me for a drink.
Hey, you, I'm gonna
wring your neck!
Guess not.
Ah!
Oh, man, that's cold!
I still don't get why it
took you guys 20 minutes
to haul me back on board.
Actually, we could have had
you out a lot sooner, lover,
but everybody agreed
that cold water
was exactly what was needed
to cure your voyeurism.
In fact, we're gonna
keep some handy.
Very funny.
(speaking German)
Okay, hold it there.
Old ferret face
there is our man.
(sneezing)
Hitler's secret assistant
Cloytsen Genhardt.
And, now, as if he
wasn't ugly enough then,
this is him today.
So this guy is like
the last living link
to Hitler's hidden stash, huh?
Interesting.
It's incredible.
He's been keeping this
secret all this time.
Do you think he's planning
on taking it to his grave?
Oh, not if we have
anything to say about it.
Agreed, I presume
you've located him then.
Of course I have.
The bad news is
he's in East Berlin.
What, East Berlin?
Isn't that a little ironic?
War's over, guy says,
"Hey, they may be commies,
but at least they're fellow
homicidal totalitarians."
Yeah, well, that's
real sweet for him,
but we got squat for
contacts over there.
I just don't like the odds.
That's why we'll
have to bring him
over to this side, see?
Except there's this little
thing called the Berlin Wall.
Guns, mines, barbed wire.
Yeah, but walls
are like rules.
They're both just
there to get over.
(shouting)
(tapping of typewriter keys)
♪
(bell chiming)
Say, "Cheese."
(indistinct chattering)
So, this is the famous
Berlin Wall, huh?
Come here, let's take a
picture of it for a souvenir.
With all due respect,
I'm a detective,
not a model,
and we're not here
for sightseeing.
Don't tell me my job!
I know we're after Lupin!
He's been my life's work!
Yes, I know, you
must be frustrated.
Perhaps we could go over
the evidence together.
There is no damn evidence.
There's no damn crime yet.
I just got a tip they
were here in Berlin, jerk.
Then it would seem
prudent that we coordinate
our efforts with
the local police.
Yeah, well, far be it
from me to contradict
a rising young
department bureaucrat,
but no clock‐punching
beat cop is ever gonna be
the one to grab Lupin.
No, that's gonna take
someone a little more‐‐huh?
Hey, what's up there?
Ah, that's a surveillance
post for keeping watch
over the east
side of the wall.
Really, hot diggity damn.
Let's go, that building
looks like the perfect spot
for eyeballing this
whole side of the city.
‐Come on!
‐Nuh‐uh.
We have to get approval
from the local authority.
Ah, come on, get the rule
book out of your butt.
Mmhmm.
That's it.
All the deadly
deterrents money can buy.
♪
The wall itself is
only 15 feet high.
♪
Yeah, but there's a
whole field of land mines
on the east side
and lookout posts everywhere.
And let's not forget
the attack dogs.
That's not a problem,
all we need is
a good hundred‐yard
running broad jump
over the mines and the wall,
and we're home free, right?
Yeah, real cute.
Hmm, they'll let us
through to the east side,
that's no problem.
But we can't take
anything suspicious with us
to help us get our
guest back over.
I know, we just need
to‐‐you know, I mean,
the answer is always
out there if you just...
Hey.
What if we just
flap our wings?
Oh.
♪
Huh?
What is that?
Oh, that, it's just
some aerobics equipment
for my wife here.
‐For exercise?
‐That's right.
I start to lose my figure
if I miss even a day.
Yeah, blows up
like a Zeppelin.
Don't know what we'd
ever do without this baby.
Fact is if we don't
get moving soon,
you're gonna need the Jaws of
Life to get her out of here.
Halt!
It's for my scrapbook,
you officious little twerp!
Huh, oh, my God, it's Pops!
Hey, hold it
right there, you!
Halt, passengers
must stay on board
until the inspection is over!
But I'm a cop,
you freaking idiot,
I'm here on
official business.
Here, look at my badge!
Inspector, please,
the man is just trying‐‐
Hey, four‐eyes,
I can handle this.
It's real simple,
we're the good guys, see?
Gotta run, Pops,
and, hey, good luck
with the scrapbook,
you sentimental fool.
Auf Wiedersehen!
Get back here, Lupin!
(thudding)
Hey, hey, get off me!
I almost had him this time,
but what the
hell do you care?
I know, you're only
following orders.
Seig Heil!
♪
‐So is that him?
‐Yeah, that's our guy.
Just taking out the
trash like any old fart.
Who'd make him out for a Nazi
fugitive with a big secret?
Perhaps he's a lot more
clever than he appears.
It's true, you never know,
so keep your wits about you.
In the meantime, Fujiko and
I will prepare phase two.
(engine puttering)
How'd it all go,
according to plan?
Yeah, check out
the back seat.
He went down easy, like
a hot cup of green tea.
Yeah, whatever.
All systems go here?
My friends,
prepare for liftoff.
♪
And thank you for
choosing Air Lupin.
Let's do it.
Yeah, right, what the hell.
The moon is too
bright for my liking.
Huh?
(grunting)
♪
Did I just see what I‐‐
Never mind.
Okay, if they spot us, we're
dead meat, so be careful.
Got it.
Let's rock and roll.
(grunting)
♪
Hey, keep your
hands to yourself.
♪
Oh, yeah, who's the man?
That would be me,
yes, indeed.
♪
(wind howling)
Whoa, getting
gusty over here!
Watch your cargo, Lupin!
Yo, Gramps, cut it
out, I can't see!
Hey, stop it,
wake up, will you?
You're gonna get us both‐‐
(shouting)
Lupin!
Lupin, get your nose up, man!
(yelling)
(barking)
Oh, Mommy!
(siren wailing)
This can't be good.
(shattering)
It's a good thing I
had this baby with me.
Where's Lupin?
Right under Fujiko, over there.
Lupin, you all right?
Talk to me.
I'm a little busy right
now, I'll get back to ya.
(gun firing)
Let's set off some fireworks.
(gunshot)
(exploding)
Hey, keep your fin up!
Ah, I'm doing my best!
♪
Just don't touch down
whatever you do!
Trust me, I'm trying!
Lupin, just hang on!
You're almost there!
I really, really,
really hate land mines.
♪
Oh, someday they're
gonna tear down this wall
and the world will
be safe for crooks.
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
This is it!
Hey, use this!
♪
Whoa, thanks for the lift!
‐Fujiko, what happened?
‐I don't know.
‐Over here.
‐Huh?
Oh.
Geez, man, you look
pathetic up there.
So, tell us, did you
save the package or not?
Such touching concern.
I ought to take
Rip Van Schicklgruber here
and throw him back
over the wall.
♪
Heil Hitler!
Look, you may as well
salute Napoleon, my friend,
or Genghis Khan, 'cause none
of them are here anymore,
so let's cut to
the chase, okay?
Stop!
(laughing)
You don't want me to crank
this up a notch, do ya?
Look, he's really not
gonna miss it now, okay?
I think I just soiled myself.
Your turn, Goemon.
Here, allow me to assist you
in changing your clothing.
(shouting)
(whimpering)
(stammering)
Now then, ancient
one, kindly reveal
the whereabouts
of Hitler's legacy.
If you could tell me
who this Hitler is.
♪
I don't know, Lupin.
We're getting as old as
him sitting around here.
Boys, boys,
haven't you heard
that you can catch
more flies with honey?
Just what kind of flies
would you be talking about?
Why, Lupin, you naughty boy,
what ever are you suggesting?
♪
(shouting)
Hey, ladies, this way!
We got a rich widower
with a heart condition!
With a little cash,
a guy like you
could make a girl very happy.
Sure, and a lot of cash
spreads a lot of joy, huh?
And a whole lot of booze.
And all the poultry that
any man could desire.
Oh, yeah, anyway,
if we just split
the whole thing five ways,
life could be very sweet.
(grunting)
Nein, don't you know we
Germans are the master race?
If we are to be worthy
of the great honor
of world domination,
I will tell you our
Aryan souls must be pure!
A real party animal.
Yup, every city's got one.
A filthy, disgusting,
degenerate, sleazy
side of the tracks.
Yeah, it's kind of late.
Maybe we should get
back to the hotel.
No way, it's a tough job,
but somebody's gotta do it!
Right here is where
the bad guys are,
and it's up to us to
case every inch of it.
Now, be a pal and pose
with those transvestites.
Come on, it's
for my scrapbook.
I'd never do that,
I'm a police officer.
Fine, fine, whatever.
But don't just stand
there like a big stiff.
Smile at least or
something, come on!
This is my smile.
Big surprise.
(camera shutter clicking)
Oh, Lupin!
In that car there, it's Lupin!
Come on, let's go, let's go!
Oh, no.
♪
See there, gonna hang
back just enough.
Don't want to lose them.
(growling)
(tires screeching)
♪
(birds chirping)
Oh, yeah, this
is just perfect.
Here you are, Inspector.
I notified the local police.
They're standing by to provide
any assistance
we may require.
Ah, now if I just knew what
that little weasel was up to,
it would help me
get the jump on him.
Ah, yes, I figured that out.
This is the picture
you took last night.
Who's the old buzzard
conked out in the back seat?
It took some digging,
but it turns out he's
Cloytsen Genhardt, 75,
former Nazi bodyguard
and special officer
assigned to Hitler's
personal detail.
He's been living
quietly in East Berlin
under an assumed name.
What do you think
they want with him?
They're after Hitler's loot!
♪
How's it going in there?
‐You break him down yet?
‐I don't know.
I'm pretty good at my job,
and I'm not getting anywhere.
What, I don't buy it,
what are you saying?
I tell you, Lupin,
I think the old guy's
got amnesia or something.
It could be possible
that the fall of Berlin
and Hitler's death were
just too much for him,
and he blocked it all out.
Oh, that's just
great, a mental case.
Now what the hell
are we gonna do?
I say we pack it up
and pretend this entire
thing never happened.
Hmm, I like the
pretending part.
I just wish I knew
how we could use that
to our advantage.
His back's against the wall,
and the great Lupin's
drawing a big blank.
So he's lost his memory
and we need to bring
it back somehow, right?
Where are you
going with this?
1945.
It seems your mind is
the latest to suffer
the effects of
excessive strain.
Guys, we're gonna
make a movie.
‐A movie?
‐What?
Exactly.
A boffo blockbuster
I call "Hitler's Last Day"
produced and directed by me,
also starring me, of course,
and introducing Cloytsen
Genhardt as himself.
(exploding and drumming)
(exploding)
♪
(snoring)
(exploding)
What the‐‐what's
going on here?
(whimpering)
Ah!
♪
(exploding)
(whimpering)
Sir, it is imperative that
you evacuate here immediately.
Huh?
The Russian troops
have already proceeded
as far as Kadrichstrasse.
Time is of the essence,
will you please come with me
to the air‐raid shelter?
Well, yes, but...
(bomb falling)
Oh!
Schnell!
Gentlemen, Officer
Genhardt has arrived.
Hmm?
Oh!
But how is this possible?
Come on in here, Cloytsen.
We have all gone in and said
goodbye to our dear Führer.
You should go inside
and do the same thing.
But, how can this‐‐
Schnell, he's waiting.
Uh, jawohl.
Huh?
(gulping)
Huh, Mein Führer?
♪
Heil, Mein Führer!
Heir Cloytsen Genhardt,
my most trusted friend.
♪
Entrusted with my life,
with secreting
my own treasure
located deep in
the Black Forest.
Pardon me, sir, but
the correct location
is 40 nautical miles
off Logos Island
in the Mediterranean!
Seig Heil, my Führer!
I love you!
Hmm, Logos,
of course, I misspoke.
(chuckling)
‐Huh?
‐Yahoo!
We did it, that's
a wrap, everyone!
We're done!
Seig Heil!
Um, what are you
saying, Mein Führer?
Huh, what the‐‐huh?
‐He pulled it off.
‐Great performance, Lupin.
Arnold Schwarzenegger's
got nothing on you.
Danke schoen.
That's Wayne Newton
for, "Bite me, baby."
(drumming)
Lupin, I think you
forgot to say, "Cut."
Hey, guys, that's it.
We're all done, you can
sign out with the AD.
‐What the...
‐Hey, Lupin,
you owe these guys
overtime or something?
Thank you for all your hard
work on "Hitler's Last Day."
Now get ready for the sequel,
the last day of
Lupin the Third!
Oh, no, Pops!
Look around you, Lupin,
all the extras in this movie
got their acting training
at the police academy!
What the hell?
♪
Oh, boy.
(laughing)
Gotta say I owe
you one, Lupin,
wanted to play with a real
tank since I was a kid!
Lupin, this is General
Zenigata of the Allied Forces!
You are surrounded!
I hereby demand your
unconditional surrender.
It's pretty good, huh?
Yeah.
(laughing)
What's that?
That's the aerial
photography unit
you hired for
your damn movie.
That's our ticket
out of here.
But how do we get to it?
A good director always saves
something for a grand finale.
And cue the pyrotechnics.
(coughing)
Now move!
They're getting away!
Go get 'em!
(engine puttering)
There they are, don't
let them get away!
(grunting)
Blockade the damn runway!
(whirring)
♪
Lupin, look on the left,
they're cutting us off.
Oh, look, guys,
it's a block party.
We can't take off!
Oh, yeah, we'll see
about that, hang on.
(shouting)
‐Very smooth, Lupin.
‐Thanks.
What will we use
for a runway?
Runway, you want a runway?
Geez, man, picky, picky.
Damn it, that lunatic
is gonna use the Autobahn!
♪
(shouting)
We're gonna hit that...
...truck.
Road hog!
You know, kids, the
Nazis built the Autobahn
for emergency use but,
somehow, I don't think
this is quite what
they had in mind.
(crashing)
Sayonara, Pops!
Shoot down that damn plane!
(booming)
♪
(grunting)
(water lapping)
(bubbling)
♪
Eureka!
(birds squawking)
(clicking)
Voila!
This is it, my friends.
You know, it's moments like
these that make a guy proud
to be a violent criminal.
Hurry up and open it.
All right already.
Here we go.
What are they,
stock certificates?
I don't think so.
♪
These are report cards.
Math, 25 points
out of a hundred.
Geography of Germany,
whoa, talk about
coloring outside the lines.
"Behavior: Student does
not play well with others.
Hygiene, very poor."
This was his secret stash?
He murders half the world
and he's ashamed of this?
Oh!
Didn't he want
to be an artist?
I guess, but he
sucks at that too.
♪
(speaking German)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Stamp collecting can
be a sticky business,
especially when you're stuck
with an infernal
three‐foot philatelist
with a voice like a
cat in a Cuisinart.
I thought the
Geneva Convention
outlawed torture like this.
Ah, somebody shoot me,
I've met my match.
She's the little
princess of darkness.
Catch you later!
♪