♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(singing in foreign language)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Okay, Jigen, try and guess what
I'm thinking about right now.
World peace.
Uh, come on, man.
Look, I'll give you
the first letter,
then you guess
the second and so on, okay?
The first letter is F.
And...
U.
Ah, see, that wasn't so hard.
Come on, Jigen,
it's a six‐letter word
and it starts with
an F and a U.
Fungus.
Ew, ugh.
Gee, you wouldn't be thinking
about Fujiko, would you?
Am I really that predictable?
Ah, well, what the hell
then, who cares.
(laughing)
(engine revving)
♪
♪ Lucky, I can't
be lucky in love ♪
♪ All my four‐leaf clovers
can't do me any good ♪
♪ Funny, just when I need it ♪
♪ Lucky, couldn't
help but loving you ♪♪
Slow down, would you?
‐I can't.
‐What do you mean you can't?
Hey, the freakin'
brakes are out, see?
What?
Well, don't just tap 'em.
I'm not just tappin', look!
Then how come
it's not stopping?
Because the brakes are out!
Watch the road!
Ugh.
♪
(exclaiming)
(tires skidding)
(screaming)
Uh, call me superstitious,
but next time you're
thinking about that broad,
don't actually say
her name out loud, okay?
♪
‐Lupin.
‐Huh?
‐No.
‐Hey.
Don't say it.
Look, it's Fujiko.
Ah, crap.
♪
(typewriter keys clicking)
Fujiko, you're lookin' great!
‐Where you been?
‐Dammit, Lupin.
(chainsaw buzzing)
I thought you had some kind
of new levitation technique.
Oh, that, well yeah.
But hey, you could have
just asked, you know.
You didn't have to go
and cut the damn brake line.
I'm sorry about the
car, Lupin, but I just‐‐
Hey, better cut
to the chase, babydoll.
Hey wait a minute,
he can't call you babydoll.
Who is this guy?
The profilers
just call me X8.
He's my new boyfriend.
Hold on, I mean hey, I thought
I was your boyfriend, Fujiko.
Oh, please, come on.
Why on Earth
would I want my children
to look like Curious George?
That's just‐‐
that's crazy talk!
‐Lupin!
‐Hmm?
I really hate to butt in,
but Paul Bunyan's
almost done down there.
Do you think
I'm monkeyish, too?
Lupin!
What's he doing?
Hello, he's trying to kill us.
(yelling)
(chainsaw buzzing)
Agh, now you tell me.
Hey, hey!
(yelling)
It's true, look there!
♪
♪ La la la la ♪♪
Good gravy, let me see!
Ah, you see,
just as I told you.
Hmm.
It's the damndest damn thing
I ever saw in my damn life.
♪ Floating, just floating ♪
So, do I or don't I
walk on water?
I'm gonna give that bitch
a piece of my mind.
Hey, no, watch it.
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
♪
(waves lapping)
Hey, Goemon, look
at what happened, pal.
(wood snapping)
(splash)
Alright, now watch carefully.
(film projector whirring)
They're falling.
They're thrown clear
of the car, which explodes.
When then, they gently
float down to Earth,
bobbing just over
the water like pixies.
Professor,
how do you explain it?
Hmm.
Well, there have been cases
of electromagnetic anomalies
brought on by
prolonged or even sudden
and rather dramatic
changes in body chemistry,
and these can, theoretically,
produce atypical phenomenon.
What in the hell
does that mean?
Every single body contains
a small amount of electricity,
but it is relatively
weak so one doesn't stick
to one's refrigerator.
But one's amperage could be
increased by various means.
By perhaps diet, say,
and even some certain
environmental factors.
If a sufficient positive
charge is generated,
well, it could then react
against a positive
charged field,
causing the body
to appear to float.
I see.
And...
However, a charge
that was strong enough
to actually accomplish
this feat would kill a man.
But somehow
it didn't kill them,
so you'd better
figure it out.
Now, Miss Fujiko, if you can
deliver this technology to me,
it will be worth
50 million Francs to you.
‐Really?
‐That's right.
Then get your checkbook ready.
You in?
Mm‐hmm.
Come on.
Hmm, real piece of work.
She'd sell out her own grandma.
But she will lead us
right straight to Lupin.
Or she'd better anyway
for your sake, Baron.
Now relax, Inspector,
she's hardly the whole scheme;
merely one player among many.
♪
What?
Lupin!
But‐‐
Wait, Inspector.
These are two of my men.
Hmm?
Amazing what they can do
with prosthetics today.
Have a look, won't you?
Go right ahead, Inspector.
You're kidding me?
Hmm?
Hey, this guy even acts‐‐
Careful there, Pops.
(laughing)
As you can see, they've
studied their subjects
with close
attention to detail.
I've always believed
in doing one's homework.
Congratulations, gentlemen, A+.
♪
(wind blowing)
Okay, here they come.
‐You ready?
‐Uh‐huh.
Ciao.
♪
Okay then,
that's one down now,
one to go.
♪
‐Don't move.
‐Who are you?
The profilers
just call me X8.
Now we're gonna take a walk.
Hands in the air,
don't turn around.
Huh, who the hell?
Name's Jigen, but
you can just call me
Sominex8.
(water rushing)
All right, Chanel No. 5,
or whatever you're called,
I want to know
who put you on to me.
Who are you workin' for?
You won't get anything
out of me, mister.
You don't think so, huh?
(exclaiming)
I'll make you sing like
a damn castrato, my friend.
(grunting)
Go on, give me your
best shot, Lupin,
or whatever your name is,
it doesn't matter.
Pain means nothing to me.
Is that so?
Yeah, well here comes
plenty of nothing.
So then, you're just
a punk after all,
a pathetic, sadistic
little punk, aren't ya?
Uh‐huh, and what's
your point, huh?
(electricity sparking)
(groaning)
(evil laughter)
(water pouring)
♪
Ah, damn you, where
the hell did you get that?
My mother gave that to me!
Oh yeah, this
piece of junk, huh?
Lupin, if you dare...
Bastards.
Guess we must
have hit a soft spot.
You better start talkin',
or the toy piano gets it.
My orders were to
uncover the secrets
of the levitation technique.
Who sent you?
I can't tell you that.
Hey, maybe this
will help you out.
♪ Who sent you
to follow me? ♪
(screaming)
♪ Could it be some
victim of my larceny? ♪
♪ Or some guy whose kid looks
a little bit too much like me? ♪
(screaming)
♪ Da da da da da ♪♪
You better kill me.
Tough guy.
‐(rumbling)
‐Hmm?
Ah!
(exclaiming)
(grunting)
(screaming)
Close one.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Dammit.
Hey.
Baby...doll.
That's right.
♪
Well, it worked.
Just like a charm.
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(sighing)
Take it easy now, you've got to
save your strength for Lupin.
Lupin.
I'm gonna rip out his heart!
(grumbling)
Oh, you poor thing.
Baby.
(screaming)
Get away!
Professor, something's wrong.
Electrified, that's impossible.
(grunting)
Then again,
I could be very mistaken.
(electricity zapping)
That bastard.
I'm going to kill him.
It seems to be working.
Will everything be,
well, you know, intact?
Ah, yes, I assume you
refer to his hoo‐hah.
No, his hoo‐hah‐‐huh?
(yelling)
(screaming)
No, ach, du lieber!
(electricity zapping)
(exploding)
Friggin' son of a bitch!
♪
Lupin, you bastard,
where are you?
Lupin!
Fujiko!
♪
Ah!
Here he comes.
‐Fujiko!
‐Oh no.
Stay away!
Fujiko!
Let's try a little
louder, shall we?
This ought to help.
Please don't!
(screaming)
Lupin, you're dead meat!
You're a sick bastard, Lupin.
I'm gonna put you
out of your misery.
Hey look, a little piano.
Let's have a sing‐a‐long.
No, stop!
X8, this is our song, remember?
(toy piano keys tinkling)
Lupin!
(piano keys tinkling)
No, Fujiko!
My God.
What have they done to you?
Bastards!
That's it,
Miller Time for us, man.
Yeah.
♪
What did I say?
Now he'll stop at nothing
to hunt down Lupin.
Brilliant, eh?
Huh?
Hmm, oh yeah, sure.
♪
(computer beeping)
So that's been the game.
They were both played and now
they're counting on loverboy
to lead them to you.
If he doesn't rip out
your heart and eat it first.
Man, Pops in league
with creeps like that.
That's a sad turn of events.
Guess we finally
drove 'em nuts, huh?
Hey, how the hell did you ever
attach those transmitters
to Fujiko and old Ex‐Lax?
Well, you know I was a
champion spitball marksman
back in my old
school days, of course.
So I just nailed 'em with
a couple of hot blow darts
on our way down from the cliff.
♪
(beeping)
Yep, I'm so glad
I stayed in school.
Uh, I can't take it,
it's driving me crazy!
What are you kvetching about?
Her dot and his dot
are like one big happy dot!
Would you just relax?
That's easy for you to say.
Mm‐hmm, I know.
♪
Oh, yeah, this just
might come in handy.
(piano plays)
Cheers, Inspector.
Come, drink up.
Sorry, but I guess I'm
feeling kind of queasy
about this whole damn setup.
I mean, just the thought of
cooperating with you people
turns my stomach.
But we all have to
follow orders, I reckon.
I suppose I should take that
as a compliment, Inspector.
(buzzing)
‐Hmm?
‐Huh?
Put him through.
Baron, that Goemon guy's
just commandeered a chopper.
Well dammit, man,
get after him then.
Yes, sir.
Well then‐‐
Professor, what's that?
Uh, this?
I'm just tinkering, you know,
to pass a little time.
Baron, X8,
I've got Jigen.
Ah, where are you?
Charcoal Jack Beach.
(sinister laughter)
‐Hmm.
‐Splendid.
Ah, good as new.
♪
You don't mind if I borrow
these, do you Professor?
♪
(whistling)
They've got Jigen, let's go!
♪
(waves crashing)
So, recognize these, you
scum sucking piece of crap?
You tell me where Lupin is
and I won't
have to use 'em.
Go ahead.
(growling)
(electricity buzzing)
Thought you were above
that kind of thing.
Huh, who's there?
(gunshot)
You!
And now, before you do
something you're gonna regret,
take a look at these.
You were played.
That real nice
guy you work for
just wanted to give you a little
extra incentive to find me.
Huh?
Your mother's piano, Fujiko?
He pushed every single
one of your buttons.
You're playing me!
It's all because you're
obsessed with Fujiko.
Well, I don't deny that part.
‐Still...
‐Huh?
(piano keys tinkling)
Would the same guy who
tortured you with this thing
really go to all the trouble
of tracking it down,
repairing it,
and returning it to you?
Huh?
Mmm.
(piano tinkling)
Huh?
It really has been repaired.
And on a weekend.
I could charge you
extra for that,
but I won't.
Okay, but what
makes you so sure
the Baron was
behind all this, Lupin?
Well, if you
don't think it's true,
you can just ask the Professor.
Last time I saw him,
he was sharing a room
with those masks.
Dammit, those
lousy friggin' bastards!
They're dead!
The cop was a patsy, too.
‐That was sweet.
‐Huh?
There you are.
You just lost me
a fortune, you know.
And just how much do you think
the Baron would have paid
for this little trick, huh?
Oh, come on, balloons?
Mm‐hmm.
My own patented
formula, of course.
Okay, that's it!
Get your hands up, now!
Look who's here, Fuj.
Our old buddy.
And no funny business, flyboy,
or I'll have to ground you!
(chuckling)
Little joke there,
oh forget it.
You can figure it out
in a jail cell.
(yells)
Get in the boat, now.
♪
Thanks.
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Damn, that was close.
Hey, Lupin!
See you, Pops, thanks.
Don't forget
to water the plants!
(laughing)
Lupin!
(panting)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Lupin, there's no way in hell
this thing's gonna float.
Ah, did I hear
someone say float?
(air blowing)
(water crashing)
Lupin, you guys
get back here right now!
Sayonara.
D'oh‐‐you!
Lupin!
Dammit!
Oh!
♪
So tell me,
did you invent this
or did you steal it?
Well, I guess that depends
on which one would
really impress you.
I guess I'd have to say
if you invented it.
Okay, then let's just say
that I invented it, shall we?
Okay.
Argh!
♪
Then you can just
make yourself a new one.
But Fujiko!
What, you didn't lie, did you?
Of course I did!
Argh!
♪
Don't worry, Lupin!
I'll catch you!
(groans)
(chuckling)
Mommy!
A‐ha!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪♪
So, if hell is other people,
what the hell do you call being
chained at the neck to Pops?
Ultra hell, mega hell?
Venti hell with
an extra shot of damn?
Well, if you want to see just
how far the mighty can fall,
check out the next episode,
"Morocco Horror Picture Show."
Catch you later.
♪