♪
♪ Lupe ♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(gun shots)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
These mafia guys all make
a pretty decent living.
I don't get why they always
live in dumps like this.
Guess 'cause it was
Capone's old stomping grounds.
What is the nature of this deal
they want to strike with us?
Camone was being evasive.
He obviously didn't wanna
talk about it over the phone,
but it's a big deal.
♪
Hey, Camone, let's get talkin'!
Camone, is that you?
We're here as promised!
Warm welcome.
Hey‐‐hello?
(grumbling)
Wait up, Lupin.
(machinery whirring)
(gun shots)
♪
(rumbling)
(grunting)
Dammit.
You're just
wasting your bullets.
That's an armored tank.
You don't stand a chance!
Yes, leave this to me.
We'll meet back at the
place we talked about.
Right.
‐Let's bounce.
‐This is war!
♪
(machinery humming)
Huh?
(whimpering)
♪
So, the famous Zantetsu sword.
It exceeds its reputation.
Mr. Sherlock, we can get
our hands on that sword,
and we can mess up that
whole African peace deal.
Yes, this could give me a
leg up on those damn diplomats
who've been ruining the
arms trade for years now.
That's right, and I
got everything in place!
Excellent.
Then let's not waste any time.
I want that thing
airborne immediately.
(clacking)
♪
Yeah, hold on.
Well, that's a cute getup!
‐Real funny.
‐You know, Lupin,
a simple glance at a
calendar would've helped you.
If you'd only remembered your
age and known what month it was,
you'd have thought twice
about going for a swim.
Dr. Fujiko, your bedside
manner really sucks.
And close the door, will ya?
It's freezing in here!
‐Huh?
‐Care package.
Oh, yeah, bourbon!
You know, I'm starting
to feel better already!
Ah, woo!
That's nice.
Come on, Goemon, have some!
Nothing but sake for me.
To me, whiskey just
tastes like antifreeze.
Just what the
doctor ordered, man.
That's right, if it tasted good,
everyone would want some.
It gets so cold here
this time of the year.
Well, just to shut
you guys up, then,
and to be gracious to
Fujiko for bringing it,
just a little sip.
So, what's the verdict?
It's very good!
Damn, now we gotta share it!
Another round for
my friends, Miss!
Me too, me too!
Hold on, I'm not
your waitress, you know.
Hey, come on, you knew we
were drunks when you married us!
You know the truly great part?
I don't care if
I ever get better!
Don't you tempt fate!
It can be cruel!
♪
(snoring)
(groaning)
♪
I'm sorry about this, Goemon,
but a million dollars
is a lot of money.
♪
So Camone's just the
middleman for Sherlock.
Why in the world would Sherlock
pay a million
bucks for that sword?
(phone ringing)
Good morning, Zenigata speaking.
What‐‐in a hotel
in broad daylight?
Who the hell is this?
The point is, he's here now.
Aloha!
(tires screeching)
‐No, Goemon, stop!
‐Take it easy, man!
She may have put the
sleeping pills in the drink,
but it was I who
kept asking for more,
and now the sword, my
very soul as a samurai,
is gone!
I egged you on!
It doesn't matter,
the responsibility
is solely my own!
Don't force me to
live in shame, Lupin!
That's worse than death to me!
(sirens blaring)
It's Zenigata!
Finally!
Sorry, Goemon,
just cool your heels
at the police
station a little while.
Come on, Jigen, we
gotta find Fujiko fast!
Hands in the air!
‐Huh?
‐Just let me die!
Let me die!
There it is, a small,
pilotless aircraft,
and armed with that sword,
it'll be the one weapon
in the whole world
with the power to put
that damn peace treaty
in the shredder forever.
As soon as the
fighting starts up again,
those tanks of yours are
gonna go flying off the shelf!
And life will be good again.
Not for them, of course.
♪
(grunting)
Huh?
♪
(explosions)
(yelling)
(rumbling)
(indistinct talking)
(siren blaring)
♪
Well, fellas, if you
can't take the heat.
♪
This assembly said we should
trust them, and we did!
Now we see how
trustworthy they are!
I object!
Our neighbor is trying
to annul the treaty!
If he wants war,
we'll give it to him!
(chuckling)
(engine whirring)
♪
We need the immediate
intervention of the U. N.
to avert a war.
♪
Hey, Lupin, the sword!
Huh‐‐wow!
You're right‐‐how
is that possible?
Well, follow the money
is my rule of thumb,
so I say we should check
out the Sherlock Armaments.
Profit.
Yeah, he stands to
gain the most from this,
so that rat Camone
and he must've been
in cahoots together.
Okay, then we should
probably go and pick up Goemon.
♪
Goemon, I don't know
what's bugging you,
but you haven't
eaten for a week,
and that's not good for you!
I went to a lot of trouble
to get that Japanese
food brought in here!
Please, tell me you're not
trying to starve yourself?
That would be really bad for
your health and my conscience!
Yeah, what is it?
They're moving this prisoner.
Huh‐‐let me see.
All right, get up.
Well, this all
seems to be in order
as far as I can make out.
Prisoner is to be
transferred to Central Africa?
What in the‐‐
Hey, wait a minute,
what's this about Africa?
♪
I just thought a
little sightseeing
might rehabilitate
him, you know?
Dammit, Lupin, you bastard!
I‐‐
♪
Hey, you get back here, you!
Huh?
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
Goemon, you're not thinking
of actually fighting with that.
♪
That guy's a
total mystery to me.
Guess I just got no idea
what it means to be a samurai.
Jigen, take her lower.
♪
They're sure not
kidding around, are they?
Those guys were
armed to the teeth.
How in the hell
did Camone do it?
I don't know, but
that's one more big reason
why we gotta find him
and that sword pronto.
♪
(zapping)
(machinery rumbling)
(crackling)
That makes the order
eighty new tanks
ready for shipment
to Central Africa.
Excellent, move them out.
Uh, yes, Mr. Secretary,
I apologize for the delay
and we're working
at full capacity,
but four days, all
120 of them guaranteed.
Yes, goodbye.
I love it.
They're both
bleeding each other,
and you're bleeding them!
You are the Merchant of Death.
Don't call me that.
I'm an entrepreneur
just like any other.
Some make widgets, I
happen to make a killing.
♪
They have no shame.
They used the Zantetsu
sword to start a war
raking in huge, obscene profits,
and I just get a measly million.
If I get some pictures
and then blackmail them,
I have a good feeling
they'd be more than willing
to sit down and
renegotiate my contract.
(explosions)
It's like a letter
opener with balls,
this Zantetsu thing.
Huh?
Crap!
Okay, Lupin, you
want a taste of this?
Be my friggin' guest!
Whoa, what's that?
A remote control drone
with a Zantetsu sword?
Hey, don't be grabbin'
the wheel like that.
You'll thank me later.
Didn't you see that?
There it is!
♪
(whimpering)
Hey, Goemon, this
is your stupid sword!
Can't you do anything?
No, not up here.
On the ground, it's
a different thing.
♪
Jigen!
Lupin, get your hands off the‐‐
Ahh!
(clattering)
Okay, sword, do you stuff!
♪
Hey, Goemon, you know
technically boneheaded stunts
don't count as harakiri!
♪
(guns firing)
(whimpering)
Goemon, run!
♪
That way, into the jungle!
Look out!
♪
Okay, I think we lost it.
(panting)
Okay, Goemon, how the hell do
we beat this thing of yours?
Yeah, like fire or water
or anything like that?
That's just it‐‐the thing
about a Zantetsu sword
is it doesn't have a weak
point or Achilles heel.
Huh?
(rustling)
(grunting)
Oh, that bastard!
Guess I'll call it a day.
Can't do too much in the dark!
(whirring)
♪
A remote control Zantetsu sword.
All I need now are some pictures
of the damage at the bases.
♪
Wake up.
What, where‐‐where is it?
Is it back again?
No, listen, I
remembered one thing
my sword isn't
able to cut through.
Really‐‐that'll help us.
So, tell us, what is it?
Devil's tongue.
He's talking about that yam
paste stuff you cook with.
‐It's a joke, right?
‐It sounds incredible,
but I swear I'm not joking.
I must've tried
a thousand times,
but I could never cut
through that squashy stuff.
How are we supposed
to find a restaurant
out here in the jungle?
But we really don't
need a restaurant, Lupin,
we just need some friggin' yams!
But in the middle
of nowhere find a yam?
Why the hell not?
Look, it's our only hope.
I say we get digging!
♪
All the way to
Africa to dig for yams.
♪
Here you go!
(grunting)
Ow, that burns!
Gotta spread it while it's hot.
It gets too hard when it's cold.
♪
(squawking)
(birds chirping)
Hmm?
(laughing)
Stupid broad.
(tires screeching)
(grunting)
Dammit!
Huh‐‐what the heck is that?
Lupin, haven't had enough, huh?
Okay, sick 'em, boy!
You're, uh, pretty
sure this is gonna,
you know, work, aren't ya?
‐We'll see.
‐Hmm.
♪
Yippee!
See that‐‐that was amazing!
It's a bad dream.
Yeah, right, a bad
dream, that's all it is!
♪
Incoming!
(chuckling)
Take that!
♪
(grumbling)
Charge!
♪
They came up with a
defense against this thing
in the middle of the jungle?
What the heck did they use?
(rumbling)
(yelling)
Yes, Camone, bow down
before the power of the yam!
The power of the what, you say?
And now, fellow yam
jockeys, after Fujiko!
After me, why?
That's crazy.
I'm familiar with crazy.
‐This ain't it.
‐I think it's only fair
we let Goemon deal with her.
Hear, hear‐‐what's
it gonna be Goemon?
♪
Oh, that's awful,
what the hell is it?
A little devil's tongue
for a diabolical girl.
Devil's tongue?
(spitting, laughing)
(sirens blaring)
What the devil?
Pull it over!
Camone came clean, Sherlock!
You're going away
for a long time!
No!
(grunting)
♪
(explosions)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Okay, I get why the guy on
the ground doesn't look happy.
He's dead, but how come everyone
living in this hicksburgh
looks just as bad?
Could it have
something to do with her?
Sister Lavina
seems nice enough,
but she sure has a
strange effect on people,
including my best friend‐‐yikes!
Next one's called
"Church of the Poison Mind."
Catch ya later!
♪