♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(tires squealing)
♪
Crap!
Crap, crap, crap, crap, crap!
I heard you arrested Lupin,
is that some kind of joke?
We have him in custody.
Yeah, yeah, that's great,
but how in the world
did you capture him?
Well now, you see, that's
the interesting thing,
he actually turned himself in.
Did you say‐‐
What kind of fool
do you take me for, huh?
(key clicks in lock)
‐Sir...
‐Lupin!
(gasps)
Hey, Pops, nice of you to drop
by, what are you in for?
Good gravy, Lupin, you're
actually locked up!
Very good, so tell me, what
eventually gave it away?
Was it my handsome face?
Handsome, that monkey face of
yours would even scare away
other monkeys, you idiot!
Now, why don't you just tell me
what this is all
about it, Lupin.
Ah, you're so cynical,
I'm just taking responsibility
for all my myriad
of transgressions.
Get off it, Lupin, we both
something smells around here!
See, that's the whole
point, I'm a bad person
and it's high time society
exterminated such a pest.
What about Jigen and Goemon,
is this thing just
supposed to distract me,
while they pull
of some big heist?
Inspector, Jigen and Goemon
turned themselves in to us
at the same time, they're right
here in these next two cells.
(growling)
Jigen!
But‐‐
Goemon?
(snickering)
♪
I gotta figure this one out.
It's either a very a good day
for law enforcement... wait.
There's no way, this
is Lupin, after all.
Hey!
♪
Hm.
Ah‐ha, man, I'm good!
Somebody told me this old
guy was locked up here.
Clyde Barrow, best of the
bank robbers way back when.
So those guys are planning
to smuggle you out of here
for some reason.
(metallic bang)
(typewriter keys clacking)
♪
You ought to transfer
Clyde Barrow
out of this prison as
soon as you possibly can!
Hm, all right, Inspector,
I'll humor you on this one.
Get Barrow in here, right away.
Mhm.
We'd better hurry, that Lupin's
a slippery little devil.
Dammit, Chief!
You gotta listen to me!
‐Sure.
‐You can't take your eye
off of Lupin even
for a second, got it?
(footsteps)
Everything all right?
Nice and quiet, sir.
(gasps)
He's not in there,
open it up now!
♪
Find him, cover at the exits!
Go, you idiot!
Stay calm, Chief, my instincts
are telling me that Lupin's
still here in this
jail cell somewhere.
♪
Hm?
It's textbook Lupin,
false wall, maybe?
Maybe...
over here!
(whimpering)
♪
Darn it all, Lupin,
where are you?
Why, that clever little weasel.
‐Gotcha!
‐Fancy meeting
you here, Inspector.
If this guy does escape,
we'll all be out of a job!
Yup, Lupin's there sleeping like
a baby, just like I said, Chief.
You're kidding!
Go take a look for yourself!
(growling)
Officer, I'd feel better
if we got this man
to Alcatraz right away.
Gotcha, Inspector.
Gah!
♪
No, this can't be!
(snickering)
♪
Tell me, Lupin, why would
a master thief like you
want to go to all the
trouble to get an old codger
like me out of prison?
It's my policy
to treat old farts
just like you with respect.
Nice sentiment, and
here I thought you had
some kind of ulterior motive.
♪
Well, now that you mention it.
Over there.
‐That thing?
‐Mhm.
They call that
a bank these days?
Yeah, well, appearances
are deceiving,
that's actually the main branch.
They're building their whole
headquarters from the ground up.
In the meantime, they're
operating out of that trailer.
Stupid, not that
I'm complaining.
♪
(chomping)
The plan was to
break in tonight.
The safe is in the left end
of the trailer as you enter it,
but then we discovered a real
strange thing about it
that presented us
with a kind of problem
that could be an opportunity.
An opportunity for me?
Yeah, the thing is, there's
absolutely no written record
of the combination anywhere,
and only the head of the bank
and his myna bird know it.
‐You're kiddin' me, right?
‐Nope!
The bank president's
an extremely cautious man
and not just a little bit
eccentric either,
so he decided he was gonna
teach his beloved bird
the combination of
the safe just in case
he kicked the bucket
unexpectedly.
Now rumor has it, Clyde, that
you used to run a pet store.
So do you think you could
persuade that bird to sing
a little request for us?
Well, that depends,
how much is in the safe?
I'd say it's about
600 million, you know,
give or take a few million.
Wait a minute, what did you say?
600 million, we'll hit
'em tonight at midnight.
Between midnight and 1 a. m.,
security cycles on the hour
so we'll have to be
fast and efficient.
The split, Clyde, the split,
for crying out loud!
If it ain't down
the middle, we're out!
Tell 'em!
♪
Oh, I can't believe‐‐it's you!
(kissing noises)
Yeah, so how do I look, huh?
Uh, Clyde, what is
this enormous object?
Bonnie Parker‐‐hey, Clyde,
what in the hell is the matter
with these guys, ain't they
never heard of the famous
bank robbing team of
Bonnie and Clyde before?
I tell you, the school
system in this country
has gone down the drain.
Yeah, I've heard of 'em,
did some real damage
way back in the Depression,
that is before they
got riddled full of holes
by the feds in a shootout.
(gunfire)
Real bad day, no doubt,
but dead, forget about it!
We are the genuine reincarnation
of Bonnie and Clyde.
♪
So, uh, we really
splittin' down the middle
with old balloony and the
birdman if this thing pans out?
No way, I mean, did you
listen to the two of 'em?
Couple of nuts.
Once he gets us in there,
we'll just find a way
to conveniently disappear.
I get very bad vibration
from that partner of his.
Hey, lover boy, you remember
that dream of ours?
We were gonna quit
robbin' all those banks
and then buy a little island
of our own in the Pacific?
Build a love nest where you
could raise all the damn birds
you ever wanted?
Remember, we used
to talk about that.
How could I forget.
Well, our ship's just
about to come in, honey.
Say, you wouldn't be thinking
what I think you're
thinking, would you?
Wouldn't I, come here.
What you got in mind?
Ha, we steal the whole bank,
Clyde, lock, stock, and barrel.
Could you say that
again in my good ear?
Did you ask yourself why I
got this here big rig, Clyde?
It's because we're gonna
hook that whole bank trailer
right up to it and
then drive it away.
But there aren't any
tires on that trailer.
You can't just drive
that thing away
if there aren't any tires on it.
Then I guess someone's gonna
have to put those tires back on.
(chiming)
Okay, you guys, that means,
we've got exactly one hour
before that patrol circles
back this way again.
That's not a lot of time.
Um, how about if I keep an
eye out for that patrol car?
Sure, great.
(grunting)
♪
(creaking)
'Kay, old man, now it's
time to do your stuff.
Oh, well, ain't you
a sweet little fellow.
Ah!
Don't let him get away!
Oh, dammit!
♪
Come back here!
Hey, it's that myna!
Hey, lover boy, come on, hop in!
You did it, whoo‐hoo!
Dammit, they outsmarted us!
Hey, wait up!
(truck humming)
Hey, get back here
you‐‐you damn crooks!
Not only did we do it, baby,
we even got the damn myna!
Come here, you!
(kissing noises)
(laughing)
♪
Stop that, watch
the road, will ya?
Wee!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
Damn it all, I can't
believe I let my guard down
just because those
guys are so old!
I believe I'm on record
as having had a bad feeling
about this from the start.
Goemon!
Just cool it, Lupin,
you got bigger problems
right in your rearview mirror.
Hm?
♪
It's Pops, oh, great.
So I guess old fashioned,
straightforward bank robbery
isn't enough for him anymore.
Now he has to keep it
fresh for himself
by making off with real estate.
♪
(tires squealing)
Come on, step on it, will ya,
think this is a dang parade?
♪
Um, don't look know, but
Pops is blowing right by us.
Huh?
♪
Huh, I was sure he was after us!
Well, then who
the hell is he after?
‐I'm so confused.
‐Faster, come on, will you?
Hey, wait a minute,
why don't I see Lupin?
Because Lupin's
behind us, Inspector.
Then turn around!
(brakes squealing)
(loud crash)
Hey!
(growling)
You just stopped right
in the middle of the street!
You saying you got
a problem with that?
You're damn straight
I got a problem with that,
you dumb moron!
Cool it, or I'll haul your ass
straight down to headquarters!
Could get ugly, maybe someone
should call the police.
♪
Lupin might just need
some help getting the point.
(metallic clicking)
(whimpering)
(tires squealing)
(crash)
♪
(lightning striking)
(rain pelting)
♪
Where the hell did he go?
(carnival music)
What the‐‐!
Hey, police, turn
that dang music down!
No turn‐off for miles.
They won't be able to disappear.
(carnival music)
♪
Huh...hm.
Hey, Lupin, check it out.
‐Look.
‐Yup.
It's a truck hauling
kids' toys, so what?
Yeah, well, it
looks like the paint
on the side is washing away.
He's right, try and pull
up alongside the truck,
if you can.
Hey, what‐‐uh‐oh!
Honey, we got us a problem.
All the paint's coming off
the side of the truck!
(carnival music)
Oh, yeah, knew we'd find 'em!
Now keep your eye on
them this time, dang it.
♪
(tires screeching)
What's the matter, you're
supposed to be following Lupin.
Against regulations.
See, that was the state line, if
you want to keep following him,
you're gonna have
to make arrangements
with the Kansas
State Police now.
Sorry, but that's
the way it is, Inspector.
Fine!
(growling)
The hell with ya!
(rain pelting)
(growling)
(church bells ringing)
("Wedding March" plays)
♪
Oh, darling, promise me
that nothing will ever
come between us.
I promise.
Oh, you're so wonderful.
Huh?
A pervert!
(tin cans rattling)
I'm Zenigata, I'm working
on a case for INTERPOL.
I'm hot on the heels of
the notorious and obnoxious
Lupin the Third, and I'm afraid
I'm going to have to ask
for your cooperation.
But I mean, Detective, can't
you see we just got hitched?
You wouldn't want to obstruct a
police investigation, would ya?
In most cases, no.
All right then, you're both
deputized, come on, move it!
Well, I guess they did say
for better or for worse.
♪
(panting)
(grunting)
♪
How you doin', Clyde?
I've been better.
♪
Huh, looks like
they dumped it here.
No safe, hm.
Pretty good for guys their age.
I'm sure they haven't
gotten very far.
Well, the good news is, there's
nowhere here to spend it.
♪
Huh?
I, um, wanted to
express my appreciation
and best of luck
in your new life!
♪
(grunting)
Hey, let's try to open it,
maybe seeing millions in cash
will give us what we need to
make it the rest of the way.
Sure.
♪
Whew.
Okay, now, my friend,
the combination.
What is it?
Come on, now, you're
ticklish, huh?
Come on!
5963.
5963, thank you,
little birdie.
Yes, thank you very much,
Clyde, very helpful,
couldn't have done
it without ya!
♪
Lupin!
And thanks to you, Bonnie,
you're an extraordinary woman.
Feel free to take that
any way you'd like to.
Okay.
(grunting)
♪
Oy gevalt, what are you
guys waiting for, huh?
Oh, yeah, right, sorry.
Good luck trying to
move that thing, guys.
Yeah, yeah, we can handle
it, just watch, see?
(groaning)
♪
30 seconds until launch.
29 seconds, 28, 27, 26,
25, 24, 23, 22,
21, 20, 19, 18‐‐
Hey, Commander, better
take a look at this,
looks like civilian intruders
in the target area.
Huh?
... 13, 12, 11,
10, 9, 8‐‐
It's too late to
halt the countdown,
I'm afraid they're
in God's hands.
... 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0.
Ignition!
(engine roaring)
Hm?
Anybody else hear
that strange sound?
No, not really.
(missile hums)
It's a missile!
We've stumbled into
a missile testing range.
What?
(crash)
(screaming)
♪
Duck!
(explosion)
♪
Now, that's a solid
piece of work,
I mean, that missile
didn't even dent it.
Well, it's time to
open her up, I guess.
And you guys would have
walked away with half of this
if you hadn't been so greedy.
5963.
(ding)
(gasping)
What the‐‐it says, "Sorry,
you guys, but you're a day late
and just about 600
million bucks short."
Signed Bonnie A. Parker.
What?
Huh, then who the
heck is this Bonnie?
Hm.
(screaming)
Guess you caught me, Lupin.
Fujicakes!
Well, I had to try, after all,
it was 600 million dollars,
but I guess Bonnie Parker's
the winner this time.
♪
Old man, let me give you
a little piece of advice.
From now on, just
stick to myna birds,
they're a whole lot more
reliable than women are.
Oh, how could you do it, Bonnie?
Dang it, how the hell am I
supposed to get off this thing?
Hey, please, somebody help me!
Whoa‐‐Lupin!
Stop this crazy thing!
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
There's a ghost ship
at the bottom of the sea,
dragged along for all
eternity by deadly currents.
Yo‐ho‐ho, no way, right?
Except this particular ghost
ship at the bottom of the sea
dragged along by deadly
currents happens to have
a priceless golden
cannon on board.
Think I'll be able to resist?
Check out the unsurprising
answer to that one in
"Deadly Dreamers."
Catch ya later!
♪