♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(glass breaking)
(singing in foreign language)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(singing in foreign language)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(boat horn blaring)
♪
(hydraulic whirring)
(rapid gunfire)
Armor‐piercing bullets
and flame throwers.
Even dynamite.
♪
(dynamite exploding)
Completely useless, hmm.
Now watch this
next one, it's great.
♪
(hissing)
Knock a man on his
ass for hours, hmm.
Every scenario has been taken
into account, Inspector.
You might say it's
completely Lupin‐proof.
(laughing)
But the thing is,
Inspector Penguin,
‐still not nearly enough.
‐Huh?
Look, I'm the top
authority on this guy
and I say you are
underestimating him!
Wait a minute,
I'm not sure I follow.
Are you actually
suggesting, Inspector,
that the capabilities
of this common thief
exceed those of Australia's
finest engineers?
Yeah, in fact, that's
exactly what I'm suggesting.
‐What was that?
‐Lupin is a kind of genius,
he's a man who
accomplishes the impossible.
He's cunning, handsome,
diabolically charming,
‐and one of the most‐‐
‐Inspector!
Just listen to
yourself for God's sake.
An outside observer
might conclude
that you were
in love with the man.
I admit to sort of
a perverse admiration.
You've obviously‐‐
‐Admiration, my ass!
‐Huh?
Why don't you
just admit it,
you are in
love with the guy.
And you always
have been, haven't ya,
you big egomaniac!
(grunting)
♪
What in the name of
Ned Kelly's going on?
♪
Hey, Pops, the inspector
was filling me in on the specs
of his very impressive
new armored truck.
Not intentionally.
You're under arrest!
I'll catch you
later then, mate.
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
♪
(gunfire)
(typewriter keys clicking)
♪
Hey, if you ask me, man,
the whole thing sounds like
way too much trouble.
♪
Friggin' birds can't
get close to that thing,
and I don't think I can pull
off the backless look, either.
♪
I mean, not that
it doesn't look
absolutely stunning
on you or anything,
but it does take a certain
androgynous quality, you know.
Ugh, I swear I'll beat you
with your own hat.
(laughing)
♪
Huh?
I'd say it looks like
there's "mutton" we can do.
Oh, man, I'm on today.
(sheep bleating)
Hey, I just figured it out.
What, what are
you talking about?
You'll see‐‐whoo!
But the truck's all ours!
(sighs)
♪
What, you're still
going through with it?
Certainly, why shouldn't we?
Why shouldn't‐‐
ooh, I don't know.
Maybe 'cause Lupin knows enough
about your precious truck now
to build one for himself.
I'd say the more anybody knows
about how that truck is built,
the less likely
they are to attack it.
But this is Lupin, you!
I never!
(grunting)
What are you,
a frickin' madman!
My apologies, Inspector,
I just wanted to make sure
it was really you this time.
All right, I think I get
the picture here, Penguin.
I'll just stick to my job
and you do yours!
As director of this museum,
I must say, Inspector, that
that exchange did little
to inspire confidence
in the security measures
you've come up with
for this transfer.
He's quite an
odd duck, that one.
It'll be a scandal
for this museum
if on the way to the
Foundation Day festivities
the very symbol of this nation,
The Sleeping Lion,
were to be lost.
Don't worry, sir,
the police department
has a stake in this
as well, you know.
We'll get this thing
to Darwin in time and intact.
I got to hurry up
and figure out a way
to keep this away from Lupin.
‐G'day, sir.
(grunts)
Huh?
♪
(snickering)
All right, easy now.
Steady as she goes, boys.
♪
Do be careful, that's it.
All right.
♪
(door closing)
Cargo hold's ready to
be locked, Inspector.
Thank you.
(lock clicking)
(helicopter blades whirring)
All right, that does it.
Off to Darwin
with you now, boys.
I'll be in regular
radio contact with you,
so keep the walkmans off.
Yes, sir.
(helicopter blades whirring)
♪
(beeping)
Just cleared Sydney, sir,
nothing to report.
Excellent work,
just stay alert now, men.
♪
(mooing)
(lighter flicking)
Okay, just about time.
(car engines revving)
♪
(sheep bleating)
Come on, get a move on, love.
Mmm.
(humming)
Sir, are you there, come in!
Of course I'm here,
what is it, what's the matter?
Well, sir, it's
a herd of sheep, sir.
You know, blocking the road.
Idiot, what do
you expect me to do?
Move 'em, dammit all, arg!
‐Huh, hmmm?
‐(sizzling)
(yells)
(horn honking)
Hey, are you deaf, you gotta
clear these sheep outta here.
Sorry about that, mate.
'Fraid it might take
a little longer than usual.
I'm a couple
of hands short today.
All right, guys,
everybody out.
Let's make quick
work of this now.
‐Oh, man.
‐Oh, jeez.
(snickering)
Hey, you!
♪
‐Who, me?
‐Yeah, don't lolly about,
we're trying to make
Darwin by nightfall.
Sure thing, General,
glad to help.
Now would you mind backing
this contraption up
a few yards for me?
(snickering)
All right now,
General, here we go.
Keep coming,
keep coming, that's it!
Come on.
That's right, that's
right, keep coming.
That's it, right‐o.
‐You got it now.
‐This will take a while.
There's nothing stupider
than a damn sheep.
In that case,
let's look around,
they're not goin' anywhere.
A little more, that's it.
Keep coming,
you're doing fine.
Okay, you ready now, Jigen?
Any time, man.
Let's do it, then.
All right, that's great.
Hold it right there, General.
♪
I'm starting to think
bad thoughts, Bruce.
Mm‐hmm, nothing
to worry about, mate.
It's perfectly natural.
The sheep's
a beautiful thing.
‐Huh?
You didn't happen to notice
where the truck went,
did you, Brucie boy?
It's the truck, sir,
it's‐‐well, it's gone away.
Gone away!
What the‐‐is this
your idea of a joke?
(yelling)
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(hydraulic whirring)
It was all some kind
of an elaborate trap.
You might as well come
out peacefully, boys,
you're not going anywhere.
Did he say
come out peacefully?
They're the ones who'll be out
peacefully in just a minute.
(switch clicking)
Come on out now,
we won't hurt you.
♪
‐Huh?
‐Son of a bitch,
they're gassing us, man.
♪
Look at 'em.
Nighty night, fellas!
Poor suckers had no idea
what the hell they
were messing with here.
Let's have a look‐see.
♪
There you go.
Surprise.
♪
How could it just
disappear, you idiot?
Ah, well, I guess we were
all distracted by the sheep.
Oh, I suppose it
just rose into the air
and floated away, huh?
‐(helicopter blades whirring)
‐Wait, it could have been
airlifted by someone.
We thought about that,
but we asked the chopper guys
and they didn't see anything.
Dammit, this
is very mysterious
and I hate mysteries.
Nancy Drew's okay.
No, I'm not talking about books,
you blithering nitwits,
I'm talking about unsolved
crimes like this one!
Yes, sir!
♪
‐What's going on out there?
‐They're flipping out.
Okay, phase two.
♪
So, are they still out?
Whatever that gas was,
it's stronger than
the frickin' golf channel.
(laughing)
(drill whirring)
(saw whining)
‐Huh?
(pickaxe dinging)
(grunting)
Son of a bitch!
Ah, this is ridiculous, Lupin,
we're not even puttin'
a dent in this thing.
Don't be a wuss.
Gotta keep at it!
♪
It's too damn bad,
I really think I was
starting to make some progress
before the stupid
pickaxes broke.
Dammit.
And to think I could have gone
to Miami with Goemon and Fujiko
instead of sweltering in this
frickin' hell hole with you.
Hey, if they didn't want
to come along with us,
then I don't want
to be with them either.
Gidget and Moondoggie,
hope they wipe out
right into a school
of giant jellyfish.
(laughing)
Really should have tried
this way to begin with.
(lock clicking)
No, you idiots, that's no use.
(yawning)
Well, any luck yet?
Why don't you see if there's
another opening somewhere?
Man, sure could have
used Goemon's friggin'
Zantetsu sword
this time, huh?
‐Hmm?
‐I said Goemon's sword
would have come in handy.
‐Huh?
‐I know, it's a real bummer,
but no use crying
over spilt milk.
‐We just got to‐‐
‐Lupin, you better get up here.
What is it?
Ah‐‐ah, look, it's
right down in there,
it's impossible
though, I mean‐‐
(laughing)
Don't mind me, Lupin.
Tell you what, you can just
think of me as a special prize
that comes with every
box of Cracker Jacks.
Uh, thanks, but
I think I'll pass.
You cook this up
with the Penguin?
Penguin‐‐ha, that pompous ass,
are you kiddin'?
Right, I warned him you'd get
your hands on this shipment
one way or the other,
but he wouldn't listen to me.
So come on, open it up,
what's keepin' ya?
For a cop, you know,
you're pretty damn diabolical.
(laughing)
He is evil.
You know, I don't think
he started out that way,
I think we had
something to do with it.
(beeping)
Over here!
♪
What do you say,
think we should
just forget about
this whole thing?
But how in the hell
could we do that
even if we wanted to?
But look, we can't open it
without getting
arrested by old Pops.
Hmm.
(laughing)
What's the matter, Lupin?
Don't tell me
I've stumped ya.
I don't think I could
take the shock.
(laughing)
(gasping)
Huh?
Help, can't breathe.
(gasping)
Hey, what's with him?
I don't think Penguin
ventilated that space.
It looks like
he's suffocating.
Hey, Pops, can you hear me?
You got to
get out of there.
Open the door from inside.
I can't, there's no way to open
this damn thing from inside.
Oh, crap, I can't‐‐
This is terrible,
I can't just sit here
and watch the old guy
friggin' suffocate, Lupin.
Hold on, Pops, we'll
get in there somehow.
♪
All right, Jigen,
keep an eye up top.
Gotcha.
♪
Bad news, man, they found us.
What, all right
into the truck, quickly.
All right, detonate it.
(explosion)
All right now.
See anything, sir?
There they are, quick now.
What are you
waiting for, move in!
No, you idiots,
that's no use.
Dammit, get after them!
♪
(gunfire)
Damn, Jigen, it sounds like
the friggin' Fourth
of July out there.
So tell me, how's our
stowaway holding up, anyway?
Uh, I've seen him look
a whole lot better.
(gasping)
♪
Hey, save your
ammunition, bloody idiot!
Just surround it.
♪
I can't watch this.
If we don't open this
damn door pretty soon,
he's gonna bite it.
If I knew how to do that,
I would have.
We could return the thing.
After all this work?
Damn it to hell, this
whole thing's screwed up.
He's a decent guy.
Think I don't know that?
You know what, man,
I think he would do
the same thing for you.
Yeah.
It's true, isn't it?
(sighs)
♪
(helicopter blades whirring)
Uh, looks like they're
heading over to Ayers Rock.
Copy that, now don't
lose sight of 'em.
♪
Well, the armored truck just
stopped over there, Inspector.
♪
Lupin, you're
completely surrounded.
We're behind schedule
now thanks to you,
so just come on out.
All right, you've
sealed your own fate.
♪
Ah!
"Golden Lions come and go,
but a good man's
worth surpasses gold.
Don't celebrate
too soon though, Jack,
'Cause just like Arnold,
I'll be back.
See ya."
What?
Catch you later, mate.
Ah, go!
Get them, you idiots!
Excuse us, coming through.
Fire!
You can't be serious, sir?
Hey, Penguin,
let Zenigata out!
Huh?
That's impossible.
How could he,
it doesn't make any sense.
♪
Inspector, my God, are you?
Inspector,
Inspector, wake up.
(groaning)
Where's Lupin?
He gave up and ran away
when he realized
he couldn't break into
this impenetrable truck.
The lion is safe,
Inspector, you and I won!
Ha!
♪
He did this for me?
Can't believe it.
(fireworks exploding)
(fanfare)
♪
Quite splendid.
Indeed, and if my men
don't find him out there,
well, the dingoes will.
(laughing)
Huh?
Look out, Deacon, it's Lupin!
Security!
Get back here!
(glass breaking)
♪
Give up, you'll
never get rid of me!
You know, I've got some
nifty features, too, mate.
Yeah, like what?
Like ejector pants.
(yelling)
(splash)
Fire, dammit,
fire, fire, fire!
(gunfire)
Yah!
Yeah, got him, sir.
Nice work.
(laughing)
Better luck
next time, Penguin.
We can't let them get away!
Now, on the double, hurry!
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
♪
That guy's almost
as annoying as Pops is.
Drive all you like, Lupin,
but you're not
going bloody anywhere!
♪
(tires skidding)
All right, Lupin,
we're even now
and the game begins anew.
Yeah, that man's the last
of a dying breed, Jigen.
You can say that again.
Kind of like‐‐ah‐choo!
‐Serves you right.
‐Huh?
I mean, didn't
your mama ever tell you
not to go out
without your pants on?
Huh?
Oh, man.
(laughing)
Just can't keep
'em on, can you?
I guess not.
(laughing)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪♪
Uh, it's totally embarrassing.
Utterly aggravating.
Downright shocking.
Fujiko‐‐we didn't
have a picture of her‐‐
double crosses us again
and now this guy's
gunnin' for us.
A creepy hit man with a stink
of rotting corpses on him
strong enough to stop
you in your tracks.
Catch you later in
"Diamonds and Minks."
♪