♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(gunshot)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(chattering)
♪
Dammit, who dealt this mess?
Yeah, yeah, here it comes.
No, really, I don't have squat.
Yeah, so what, am I supposed
to take pity on ya?
(chuckling)
(humming)
(overlapping conversations)
(chuckling)
Every other inmate here
would kill for the opportunity
that I've offered you.
You know that, don't you?
I didn't know
you swung that way.
Most amusing,
but I'm talking
about the opportunity
to hold your fate
in your own two hands, my dear.
It's what else
they'll be holding,
that's the problem.
Pride dies quick in here.
Warden, warden!
Hmm?
Mister, beg your pardon,
but there's been an escape
from the west block just now.
Okay, let's go.
Yes, sir.
Hmph.
♪
(siren wails)
(panting)
Which one was it?
Inmate Sarton, number 1980.
Got a date with
the chair tomorrow.
Oh, well, fool's just moved
his date up is all, huh?
Hmm, 1980, right?
When will they ever learn?
♪
The problem is that there's
never enough left of any
of them to prove to the others
that this is what happens
when they fail.
(whooshing)
♪
Huh, what's that?
Look out!
I know, but it's too... hold on!
(screaming)
Hey, ya stinkin' souse,
go sleep it off somewhere else!
Huh?
He looks like
some sort of prisoner!
What the... hell?
Do you think he's...?
No, he's alive,
he's got a pulse.
Hey, buddy, are you all right?
(grunting)
♪
Hey!
So long, suckers!
That does it, no more
good Samaritan for me.
Huh, what the...?
(whooshing)
Watch it!
♪
Man, what was that thing?
(explosion)
No, please, no!
All in all, I'd say
I've had better days.
I dunno, man, I mean
that little rocket bomb
was definitely meant for us.
I'd say we got off pretty easy.
How could it be for us?
We don't even
know anybody here.
Uh, boys?
Uh, it seems we do know
at least one person here.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Who are you talking about, who?
Fujiko.
What?
"Lupin, I'm in trouble.
I screwed up
and now they've got me
in some weird prison here.
I helped JD plan his escape,
and in return, he promised
to get this message to you.
The warden's had his eye
on me from day one.
So far, that's all,
but he's a serious nutcase.
Please, please, come,
and be careful!"
Ah, Fujiko's in trouble,
things are really looking up!
Uh, I guess we'll always know
how to cheer you up now.
She was right.
That's one strange prison.
I mean, this has got
to be the worst security
I've ever seen.
So, then how come Fujiko
needs help to escape?
I'd say that's
a very apt question.
Gee, thanks a lot, man.
Look, the point is,
when a lady asks to be rescued,
a true gentleman never asks why.
Hmm?
(gunshots)
Agh, don't shoot!
Of course not.
Just calm down, everybody.
Now, I see you've all
got your hands up, very nice.
All the money's in the safe!
Money's of no concern to us.
Would you kindly
point out the alarm?
It's right over there!
Thanks!
(alarm ringing)
(humming)
♪
Now our processing procedure,
gentlemen, requires that we
first obtain a little
sample of your DNA.
Okay!
Si, señor!
(yelping)
Samples retrieved!
Just what the hell
was that all about?
Sorry, they can be
a little overzealous.
Let's go.
Well, he did apologize.
Least they took yours
from your head.
(chuckles)
Hey, I've seen one
of these before.
The next time you see
one will be the last.
♪
Some kinda missiles, huh?
But funny ones, apparently.
That's right, but I'm about
to let you in on the joke.
(snaps)
These are for you,
in a manner of speaking.
For us, but?
Exclusively, as a matter
of fact, you see.
The sample on top
is the one we took
from you, for example.
Each device is equipped
with a DNA analyzer
that transmits your unique
genetic profile to the missile's
tracking system, like so.
Now, Mr. Jigen's sample
and Mr. Goemon's.
I don't like
where this is going.
And now we're ready
for a little test drive.
Hey, wait a minute!
And... go!
(all yelp)
Hey, turn 'em off!
How in the hell?
Son of a bitch, get away!
(laughs)
You see, my background's
originally in children's
toy design, but I've always
enjoyed recreational sadism.
Well, it's always nice when
you can combine your interests!
Yes, well, you and your friends
will have plenty of time now
to develop some new interests
of your own, unless, of course,
you should be foolish enough
to attempt an escape.
Hey, hey, call 'em off!
Come on, now, get away!
Don't worry,
they can't hurt you.
We haven't armed 'em yet.
Did I forget to mention that?
Must've slipped my mind.
Lovely footwork, though.
Perhaps you should
take up ballet
while you're in here.
(cackles)
You bastard, you
think that's funny,
you no good freakin'
sick son of a bitch?
Yeah, and your
execution's gonna be!
Execution, just hold on.
We're all in here
for attempted robbery.
Yeah, well,
look around, Dorothy,
you're not in Kansas anymore!
♪ Follow the thread‐‐
Hey!
What?
It sounds like Fujiko!
Hmm, you know her?
Uh, let's just say that she
would be happy to know I'm here.
Ah, well, it'll be good
to see her smile.
♪ It's a labyrinth lousy
with darkness and dread ♪
♪ But follow the thread,
follow the thread ♪
Well, if it isn't
the songbird of Alcatraz!
Lupin, you're here!
Oh, I just knew
that you would come!
Yeah, well coming's one thing,
but getting out of here
is gonna something else again.
Yeah, you sure can pick 'em.
You mean you came
without a plan of escape?
Yeah, well, sorry,
but the whole
damn thing's your fault!
Hey, I got us into this
and I'll get us out.
Lupin.
Yeah?
I'm sorry.
Hey.
You see, it's just that when JD
decided to leave,
you were my last hope
and I wasn't sure
you'd show up.
And if I simply never heard
from you again, I'd have
my life and my freedom
and what the hell good
would it be?
It is said that love
is the only game
that is not called
on account of darkness.
So beautiful.
I hate to be
the skunk at the opera,
but does anyone know
how we're gonna get
the hell outta here?
I'll sleep on her‐‐I mean it.
♪
Ow, talk about remote places!
You have to admit, Inspector,
it's a quantum leap as far
as prison security is concerned.
Yeah, but killin' 'em's
kind of barbaric.
I'm sorry, I must've
misunderstood.
Did you say
you were from INTERPOL
or Amnesty International?
What, hey, now
that's outta line!
These four guys happen
to be the key to a string
of crimes longer
than that chin of yours!
Tell me, do you get such
assignments often, Inspector?
Because I must say,
your diplomatic skills
are negligible.
No, but I work for diplomats
who work for people who work
with people who can make
your life pretty miserable!
Hmm, succinctly put,
Inspector, I must say.
Warden, breakout!
Three of them, sir!
Numbers 3333, 3334, 3335.
New arrivals, sir,
the bank robbers!
What did you say?
Rotten luck, Inspector,
but now that they've escaped,
I have no alternative.
What, but I thought we‐‐
What was a diplomatic issue
is now a matter
of prison security.
Uh.
But out of respect
for your long
and frustrating history
with this gang, perhaps you
would like to be the one
to push the button yourself.
And sink to your level?
Very well, Inspector.
They're dead in any case, so.
Hold it, wait!
It shouldn't be fun.
(grunts)
Goodbye, Lupin,
Jigen,
Goemon.
(sighs)
(whooshing)
(panting)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(panting)
(whooshing)
♪
Damn, those things are peppy!
Right behind ya, Goemon!
Run!
♪
Well, I guess I got
all of my exercise
for the week, anyway.
Yeah, I'm good through,
well, pretty much the rest
of my friggin' lifetime.
(whooshing)
♪
(panting)
Take!
That!
Suckers!
Ha!
Man.
You see, guys, it's what
I'm always saying:
You gotta believe,
you gotta have faith,
you gotta‐‐
(screaming)
(whooshing)
(panting)
♪
I can't...keep this up
much longer, Lupin!
Hold on, man, I've got an idea!
(splash)
(whooshing)
(beeping)
♪
(chuckles)
Looks like
once again I've...hmm?
(whooshing)
♪
Dammit!
Hey, take off your jackets!
Follow me!
♪
See, I knew it!
They're confused!
Their little brains
can't take it.
They can sense the DNA,
but all they can see
is discarded clothes.
(chuckles)
Uh, Lupin?
Yeah?
Knock‐knock.
Who's there?
Land‐shark.
(yelping)
(groans)
(motor roars)
♪
Crap, do you think
they heard that crack
about the little brains?
♪
Would you stop swerving and
maybe I can draw a bead on 'em?
♪
Now, let's try to end
this one like Jaws!
(gunfire)
♪
It's no use, Jigen!
Dammit!
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(yelps)
♪
Hold on!
Whoa, what are ya...?
Hey, I said hold on!
(motor revving)
♪
This looks perfect!
Why do I feel like
I've been here before?
Yeah, well that Roy Scheider
act didn't get us anywhere.
(motor revving)
♪
So, how long can those things
go before they run out of gas?
You know, Inspector,
one might be tempted
to suspect that your sympathies
lie with the criminals here.
Hey, that's a load of crap!
Come now, you're on edge,
Inspector, admit it.
Look at yourself, you've
been pacing around here like‐‐
It's just that‐‐
Just that... what?
Look, I'm a hunter
and Lupin's my prey,
but there are, well,
certain rules.
A sort of an understanding.
Ah, yes, I see:
he doesn't try to kill you
and, in return, you do
exactly the same, right?
That's right.
But, Inspector, surely
you see that all of this
would have played out
exactly the same way
whether you were
here today or not.
(sighs)
And then, once we've
lured them down there,
we'll just seal the shaft up.
With what?
(clears throat)
Huh?
♪
Now, we use most of these
to act as a charge.
♪
Is that going
to leave you with enough?
Uh, well, let's see.
Yeah, I'm good.
You sure?
What, you don't think
I missed him back there, do ya?
Uh‐uh.
Okay now, we're all set,
and, hopefully,
for the last time.
♪
Okay, let's go.
Huh?
Where are they?
They could still be chasing
after the boat, I guess.
It's getting chilly.
Go get your clothes then!
I think Lupin should get
all of our clothes.
Hey, I didn't hear you
coming up with any ideas.
You've been nothing but dead
weight on this whole thing.
Dead weight, is that‐‐
(panting)
In the hole!
(screaming)
(whooshing)
No, no!
(gunfire)
(rumbling)
Maybe we should split up
now just to be safe...
well, relatively safe.
See you all back
at the ranch, all right?
Yeah.
Yes.
There still isn't any
confirmation signal?
Now, you see how you're tortured
with hope, my dear Inspector?
By denying it
to these prisoners,
I'm performing
a humanitarian gesture.
(laughs psychotically)
I'm in hell.
(whooshing)
(slap)
Never had to force
myself on a girl,
but in your case,
I'm willing to make
an exception.
Go sit on a missile, you freak.
It's time you stopped
grieving for Mr. Lupin.
I'm your new best friend.
I'll never stop
grieving for him;
he was everything
a slimy wimp like you
could only dream of being.
Ha, not smart enough to beat
my missiles, though, was he?
I thought that was impossible.
In this case, you'd simply
have to figure out a way
to get them to crash
into each other
and then...boosh!
But that would take a truly
gifted mind like mine.
Warden, that woman's an inmate
and you've just taught her how
to bypass our security system!
Don't worry,
as I just explained,
it would take a genius
to figure out the logistics.
Hey, are you out of your
freakin' mind or what?
You stupid, arrogant bastard!
I even figured
it all out by myself!
What?
First, you take one
industrial‐grade rubber band.
This is perfectly absurd;
you're a madman, who hired you?
Admittedly, it's all
a bit Coyote and Roadrunner,
but it works!
(laughs)
I'm ordering you to report
to the infirmary for
a psychiatric evaluation.
Hey, I'm not crazy, I'm...
just me!
(gasps)
Ta‐da!
(explosion)
Lupin!
Hang on!
Quit staring down my slip
and pull me up!
(explosions)
♪
Hey, Pops!
Huh?
You okay?
Take care, see ya later!
Hey, hey, Lupin, get back here!
Hey!
Well, at least he's alive.
Thank goodness for that.
No, no, get away!
(screams)
Help, somebody, please!
(screaming)
(chuckling)
I got a sample of his hair
during one of his little
annoying visits to my cell.
It's gone haywire, stop it!
Somebody, please!
(screaming)
Hey, somebody took my car!
Lupin!
Crap!
Crap, crap, crap, crap!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
No, don't adjust your set,
it's true, Jigen really does
get a love interest
in the next one,
which is all well
and good in theory,
but since it only
happens about once
every hundred episodes,
well, let's just say
that when that much
backed‐up testosterone
is finally released,
it's not a pretty sight.
Catch ya later in
"Shot Through the Heart"!
♪