♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(humming)
What was I thinkin'?
Little hair of the doggy,
that's the stuff.
Good evening,
billionaire Pomade Jors,
who was being treated
at a New York clinic
for an undisclosed condition,
was struck and killed
by a runaway truck yesterday.
This news could have
serious implications
for financial markets
here and abroad.
Some billionaire bites
the big one, so what?
Would he have cared if I died?
Huh?
♪
Where's Lupin?
Whoever you are,
I should warn ya
you're foolin'
around with Interpol.
♪
I see you're someone who
gets right to the point.
(gunshot)
♪
All right, tell me what you want
with Lupin, you backshooter!
He steal your voice
or something?
Huh?
Wait a minute.
♪
Whoa, you're a woman!
What the hell's going on?
(gunshots firing)
♪
There!
Hey, guys, shouldn't we
be out stealing something
or running for our lives or, uh,
I don't know, something?
I feel like I'm in
a rest home here.
You've been on vacation
two hours, Lupin.
Tell him, Goemon.
Hm, we're artists.
We need an occasional
clearing out of our minds.
And for that you
need a nice, quiet,
peaceful environment like this.
(gunfire)
Whoa, get a load of this!
It's Pops, and he's
being chased by somebody!
And there's a girl
with him, and she's hot.
What the hell isn't wrong
with this picture?
Well, if you're right it's
the end of the freakin' world.
♪
Huh!
This is too weird.
♪
Hey, I've been lookin' for you.
Uh, contrary to what
you might have heard,
my bedroom's not a drive‐thru.
Are you too cheap
to go for the valet?
Will ya let me‐‐
(explosions)
Wanna tell me who the
hell these guys are?
‐Mob, New York City!
‐You're kidding!
You'll figure
something out, right?
Good idea, okay,
guys, it's Plan X.
Right.
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
Lupin, allow me to
introduce Mrs. Laura Jors.
Whoa, hold on, Pops, is she
related to that Pomade Jors guy
who just kicked
the bucket recently?
Uh‐huh, she's his widow.
Thanks for the help.
And now you're under arrest!
Hey, hold on,
don't you remember?
I'm the one who rescued
you from the mafia.
Can it, okay, I'll
look the other way
just this once if
you do me a favor.
What kind of favor?
I'm prepared to
beg if I have to.
You gotta help Laura,
she's caught in a jam!
My pride doesn't matter
to me, only Laura's safety.
Um, why do I get the feeling
there's a lot more to this?
This is the capo dei capi of
the New York mafia, Alec Cabane.
Jors was a kingmaker in
international politics,
and not just
'cause of his money.
He kept dirt, major dirt on
all sorts of world leaders
locked up in his vault
in that machine there.
Cabane raided the
vault somehow, and well,
made off with the machine.
But he found out the
machine was voice‐coded.
He needed a specific print,
his wife's vocal print.
He's not gonna stop till
he gets his hands on her,
and once he's done with her,
well...
That's a touching story,
but I still don't see
how we fit into this.
She does speak, doesn't
she, I mean, it's weird.
She hasn't said a single
word the whole time.
‐Take a look.
‐What's this?
That's the whole thing,
it's a very sophisticated
explosive device, and Jors
implanted one in her heart.
In her what?
What kinda creep was this guy?
Yes, you see, I made
your lovely voice
the key to the whole thing.
Well, one of two keys, you
can't activate it by yourself.
If you try, you will get
a nasty surprise, Laura.
You never needed a pacemaker,
I paid off the doctor
to implant a tiny bomb
inside you that would explode
if you ever accessed
the machine.
♪
Not instantaneously,
but after a minute.
It's really nothing
for you to worry about,
just a safety measure.
As long as the machine
hears my voice first,
the signal to
activate the device
inside of you
will be overridden.
You see, my dear Laura,
this way you can never
betray your husband.
(laughing)
(engine revving)
♪
That answer your question?
The kind of pathetic creep
who doesn't even trust
his own wife, that's who.
The way I figure it,
Cabane stages the accident,
rips off the machine,
then gets a surprise.
Man, if the guy
weren't already dead,
I swear I'd kill him
with my own two hands.
What the hell was
he thinking anyway?
He was old, he had
to see this coming.
All Cabane has to do is grab her
voice on tape and she'll die,
no matter how far away she is.
Well then, it's smart
for her to keep quiet
for at least the time being.
Yes, I would suggest
proceeding with extreme caution
when dealing with
an enemy like Cabane.
He won't stop.
♪
All right, you can count me in.
So I'm guessing what you want
is to have that device of his
first stolen and then destroyed.
I'm in your debt.
Hey, Pops, how come this
one's so personal for you?
‐Uh, well‐‐
‐You're in love with her.
I'm a public servant,
that's crazy!
(laughing)
♪
Cut it out, come on!
What, you're kidding me!
Lupin, where'd he come from?
‐I don't know, boss.
‐Damn it all!
He's gotta be after them
friggin' files, damn it!
No way he's moving in
on this one, no way!
‐I did all the work, me, I‐‐
‐Boss, what is it?
‐What's the matter?
‐It's his stomach again.
‐Get his medicine!
‐Here you go, boss.
Hey, wait a minute, I know
exactly what I'm gonna do.
♪
(grunting)
(screaming)
♪
Sorry, Lupin, but Cabane hired
me to protect this thing.
And you know what a pushover
I am when it comes to money.
(chuckling)
You're one in a million,
Fujiko, take him out.
(engine whirring)
Bye, Lupin, hope
you rest in peace!
Don't be too mad, 'kay?
Don't worry, Fujicakes,
for a guy like me,
death's nothing more
than a minor setback!
I'll pay some company to
put, you know, like flowers
and crap on your
grave every month.
Mwah!
♪
Big talker, that's
all he was in the end.
Speakin' of which,
now it's Laura's turn.
Get it, her turn to talk!
(evil laughter)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
What, this better not
be some kinda trick!
Lupin's really dead?
♪
Just stating the facts,
not making it up.
I dare you to look me
straight in the eye and say it!
I don't have time for this,
now hand her over or else.
No way, Fujiko, if you think
I'm just gonna hand Laura over,
you've got another thing coming!
Look, Inspector, this
is all very touching,
but I've been in here
over four minutes already,
and Cabane's men are
gonna be storming in here
if I'm not out
after five minutes.
Sorry, but you know
these mafia types.
They're a bunch of hot heads.
Come on, Fujiko, that's the
oldest trick in the book!
Dear me, I was afraid
it would come to this.
All right then, don't
say I didn't warn you.
So, how would you like to
spend your last half a minute?
Uhhh, hm.
You can just nudge
me when you decide.
(groaning)
All right, I've made up my mind.
(frog croaking)
Ahh!
That's sick!
What's the matter with you?
You forget how long I've
been tracking you guys.
I know everything about
ya, all your fears!
(screaming)
Quick, Laura, follow me!
♪
Hey, they went down here!
(water splashing)
Crap, which way do
you think they went?
Shut up and let me
listen for 'em.
That way!
♪
That's no excuse!
"Sorry, boss, the guys
ran away and I lost 'em."
What the hell do you guys
think I pay yous for?
To be as freakin'
useless as the cops?
Have some professional pride!
‐Not again!
‐Are you all right, boss?
Find the damn girl, and
don't come back till you do!
It's a wonder I
get anything done.
Lying on that alleviates
your stomach thing?
I didn't get to where I am
today by taking a lot of stuff
for granted, get what I mean?
I ain't moving
until I unlock this.
‐What a big pain in the butt.
‐Hey, speak up!
‐I can't hear ya!
‐Oh, never mind.
Just some girl stuff is all.
♪
(snoring)
‐Huh?
‐Uh, I, uh,
I was just getting
a little warm is all.
Excuse me while I take
a little look around here.
♪
Thought I'd be the first to die.
I don't need Lupin!
I just need to be Zenigata!
That's always been enough,
and it'll still be enough!
I'll protect you
all by myself, Laura,
because when you're in love,
you have the strength of 10 men,
or 11, or 10 guys and 3 midgets,
or‐‐let's see now.
♪
(snoring)
(wind howling)
♪
(panting)
Hold on, I'll help ya up.
♪
Laura, no!
(shouting)
Ow!
Laura.
Laura, don't die!
No, no!
(crying)
♪
‐But I was sure I was‐‐
‐Shh, no talking.
We're probably being followed.
Those Cabane guys
could be anywhere,
but don't worry,
I'll protect ya.
Oh, it's hopeless!
We should just give up.
Never, Laura.
I love to hear you say my name.
(crying)
Say it again.
♪
Oh, Laura.
Ow, ah, ah!
Who heard of a
pitchfork in a barn?
Huh, hm.
It's a mic!
Who's there, darn it, come out!
♪
Laura, oh no!
Laura, talk to me!
Come on, Laura, please!
You can't give up now, please,
I‐‐Laura!
Laura, please don't die.
(crying)
♪
Pops.
I‐‐we tried.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, Lupin's alive.
Look, if you wanna get
those bastards, hop in.
♪
If you're a little surprised
to see Fujiko here,
we'll fill you in.
(engine buzzing)
(laughing)
That's more like it, I
take back all that stuff
about yous being morons
and mooks and such.
Fact is, you're
gonna help me run
the whole friggin' world now!
‐Everything ready there, Fujiko?
‐Mhm.
All right then, here we go.
‐Never, Laura.
‐I love to hear you say my name.
‐Say it again.
‐Huh?
Shut up!
That should be enough.
(evil laughter)
Hey, it's stuck to something.
Damn thing won't open.
Course it won't, Cabane!
It's a fake, the real
one's right here!
I, Goemon Ishikawa,
say to you, "Ha‐ha."
What the‐‐why the hell
are they still alive?
Kill them again,
and get that machine!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Now the good part.
♪
And by the way, that crap
about taking back that crap,
I take back that crap!
♪
Somebody get that now!
Go on, lower it down!
Yeah, good, easy now,
don't hurt my baby.
(machinery whirring)
Huh?
(grumbling)
Don't just stand there,
move it right now!
♪
Say, by any chance would this be
what you're looking for, Cabane?
It was right in your
room where you left it.
I don't know why on
earth you'd abandon it.
‐Let's jump 'em.
‐Just say the word, boss.
Wait, so what, you're telling
me the tape was a fake?
Fake, no, uh, well,
that is, I did screw around
a bit with the frequency.
Slowed it down just enough to
make the voice unrecognizable.
Weird how a cold bastard
like him could create
a machine that was so sensitive.
That's keenly
observed, my friend.
Yeah, well thanks
for the information.
Now all I gotta do is kill‐‐
(groaning)
Damn it, get my medicine!
Here it is, boss, right here!
♪
Now, listen, we can
make this thing messy
or you can walk away alive.
You've gotta be kidding, Cabane.
I mean, after we went
to all that trouble.
Then again, I do like my butt.
Most guys do in my experience.
Yeah, you know, I mean,
what would be the point
in keeping all this crap
now that Laura's dead?
Thatta boy, now I'm
gonna be a real mensch,
and spare ya your life.
So take a hike before
I change my mind!
Thanks, it's been
a real, well, blast.
♪
Pst, Pops, come on,
we gotta get outta here!
Amateurs, all right,
come on, hurry up.
Let's do this thing.
Never, Laura.
I love to hear you say my name.
Say it again.
♪
Oh, Laura.
(explosion)
♪
(yelling)
Hey, take it easy, Pops.
I'll be happy to set you up
with somebody when you're ready.
No, thank you!
Just beat it.
I'm lettin' ya get away,
that was the deal,
but we're not pals!
Tomorrow the whole darn
thing starts all over again!
You hear, you little weasel?
Loud and clear.
Sheesh, catch ya‐‐
I mean, catch me later!
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Pops is all bent outta
shape 'cause we sprung
this old‐timer outta prison.
Not her, her I'd like
to spring into prison.
But she and the old guy think
they're Bonnie and Clyde.
Don't ask, and we happen to need
'em for a heist we're planning,
so unfortunately,
it's a package deal.
Somebody's gettin'
schooled in this one.
Find out who in,
"Can't Beat the Classics."
Catch ya later!
♪