♪
♪ Lupin the third ♪
(tires screeching)
♪
You won't get away, Lupin,
this time your ass is mine!
Darn it, what're
you waiting for?
Fire!
(gunshots firing)
No offense, Pops, but
don't you ever get tired
of hearing yourself say that?
That's right, Lupin,
just keep it up!
They just eat up that
wise guy stuff in prison!
Fire!
♪
What the hell?
(engine puttering)
(siren wailing)
I call it my sticky
rice takedown!
‐You're under arrest.
‐Mhm.
Impressive work there, Pops,
but sorry, not
quite good enough.
(engine whirring)
Huh?
♪
(grumbling)
Will you get off me?
Mother said there'd be days
like this, just not this many.
Good thing I'm so undauntable,
'cause this kinda thing
could really drive ya crazy.
♪
Lupin, well he lives
up to his hype.
Madame, I have a
feeling that you and I
are in for a wonderful time.
(laughing)
Doctor, feel free to begin
your preparations at once.
Sweetheart, you've been very
good enjoying that lollipop.
♪
(yawning)
Man, I'm beat.
Huh?
♪
Hm, strange, I thought I knew
this neighborhood like
the back of my hand,
but guess I'm gonna
have to take a detour.
‐Oh, Lupin, don't go.
‐Huh?
This can't be.
♪
(shouting)
I can't believe
I'm saying this but,
you might wanna
consider a reduction.
♪
Fujiko.
(giggling and yawning)
♪
Huh?
‐Did you sleep well, sir?
‐Hm?
Madame X is waiting for you
whenever you're ready, sir.
‐Madame X?
‐Yes, sir.
Excuse me, sir.
Hold it, hey!
♪
Mmm.
What a feast.
♪
Now, Madame X, or
whatever your name is,
why don't you fill me in
on what's going on, 'kay?
It's as it seems,
no more, no less.
If it is as it seems,
then you're telling me
that Monster Fujiko
is actually real.
♪
Mhm, exactly.
Oh, please, it's
a trick, admit it.
A trick, I don't know what you‐‐
Sure you do.
A trick, B. S., a lie!
(laughing)
♪
Well, I think I'll faint now.
I assure you, nothing you've
seen here is a trick, Lupin.
You know, the simple truth
is that there's a wealth
of things in this world
that we're unable to explain.
Yeah, like just what
the hell it is you want.
♪
Your life, Lupin, that's all.
Very funny.
Take a look.
(rumbling)
♪
Huh, what's with
all the wax figures?
It's a hobby of mine,
more of a passion actually.
I love to make wax
figures of celebrities.
♪
‐They're incredible likenesses.
‐They should be.
I mean, all I really did was dip
the actual celebrities
in molten wax.
‐Impossible.
‐Not at all, Mr. Lupin.
(cackling)
♪
It's simple, a matter
of counteracting
the forces of decay.
This elixir keeps human
tissue supple forever.
(machinery whirring)
Fujiko!
‐Hey, I'm‐‐
‐Don't worry,
she's just sleeping.
So, you're planning to kill us,
and add us to your
damn collection?
Very good, you don't
miss a thing, do you?
Yes, how could my collection
be complete without you?
Without you and
your gang that is.
I mean, when it comes
to celebrity criminals,
no one comes close, right?
You're one twisted bitch,
but we're celebrated
for a good reason.
Fujiko!
Hang on!
(gunshots firing)
♪
What the?
I'm not so sure about that.
So far, your technique's pretty
obvious, not that it matters.
You'll never get
out, alive, that is.
Mars!
(machinery beeping)
(growling)
Ah, he's playing,
I think he likes you.
Bite me!
♪
Hang on, Fujiko,
it's gonna be just fine!
This isn't goodbye!
♪
(growling)
(grunting)
♪
(screaming)
Just surrender, Lupin.
Surrender to the unknown!
(evil laughter)
♪
Huh?
(water dripping)
♪
(heavy footsteps)
Nice monster.
Oh, mommy!
♪
(grunting)
I can't breathe!
♪
Oh, damn it, where are
those guys when I need 'em?
Help me!
(maniacal laughter)
♪
♪ Lupin the third ♪
Something's not right.
It just isn't like him.
I know, it's been two days
now without even a word,
and usually the problem
is you can't shut him up.
Well it is Lupin we're
talking about, so presumably
he's found a woman
he just can't resist.
Yeah, let's hope so.
But even Pops has lost
track of him, you know?
And he's been watching
us like a one‐eyed cat
at a damn fish market.
It's starting to get to me.
Now where in blue blazes
has Lupin got to?
Huh?
(helicopter whirring)
What the hell?
♪
Huh?
‐Here!
‐You!
I don't want it!
(ticking)
Jigen, hold on!
Wait, you don't know
what that thing is.
Huh?
"We have Lupin, your only
chance of seeing him again alive
is to come to the old
foreigner's cemetery
‐at midnight tonight."
‐It's certainly a trap.
Yeah, but it doesn't
matter, we've got no choice
but to walk straight into it.
That guy is such a pain.
♪
Hm, he sure is persistent,
you gotta give him that.
While that's very admirable,
I recommend evasive action.
♪
(wind howling)
They should be here
right about now.
Good.
(birds screeching)
Yikes, I don't get it.
Why the hell would
they wanna come here?
It's not Halloween.
♪
Could it be spirits?
(groaning)
♪
Goemon!
(evil giggling)
♪
Oh man, that hurt.
(grunting)
Thanks for coming, guys.
It would've been a whole
lot more effective
if you two hadn't
gotten caught though.
Hm?
Hey, this is all
your fault, man.
‐Where the hell are we anyway?
‐Huh?
It's all over, Lupin,
end of the line!
You're under arrest, don't
even think about trying
to get outta here,
it's impossible!
Congratulations,
except you realize
that getting away part
applies to all of us.
That crazy lady's gonna turn
us all into wax figures.
Even Fujiko.
They got her upstairs locked up.
Hey, don't, come on,
get a hold of yourself.
Easy for you to say, Jigen.
I don't know what's happened
to me, with all of my skills,
I still couldn't escape
from this place.
I never thought I'd see the day.
Look at you, Lupin,
you're just pathetic.
Bet you haven't even tried
the most obvious thing.
No, hold it, Pops, wait!
(shouting)
Help me, please!
What the hell's
going on here, Lupin?
Unfortunately, this kinda
thing happens all the time
around here, she's like
some kind of evil witch.
That's just great, either of
you guys wanna lend a hand?
What is it, Goemon?
I think I just figured it out.
That's wonderful, but I
still need a damn hand!
‐Ah, screw it.
‐I think it's safe to assume
that there's a kind of
telepathic power at work here,
and that we have to confront
it and neutralize it
if there's to be any hope of
our getting out of here alive.
Let's go find this witchy
bitch and get outta here.
(grunting)
(gunshots firing)
♪
My goodness, Lupin,
you just don't know
when to give up, do you?
Well, Doctor, I assume
everything's all set?
Yes, just about, go
ahead and bring them in.
♪
(rumbling)
‐Uh, Goemon?
‐You need to remain calm.
All right, you guys calm
down, I'll freak out!
Ahhh!
(screaming)
(panting)
(sighing)
Man, that was close.
We were just lucky
that time, Lupin.
We have to find her
before our luck runs out.
(evil laughter)
♪
Well, now that everyone's here,
why don't we get things started?
First come, first preserved.
No, wait a minute, please!
‐Goemon!
‐It's not her.
She's not the one controlling
things, she's a decoy!
Huh, I'm a bit confused.
You should see yourself.
All right, what do you say
we get this show on the road?
♪
Hey, wait a minute,
what about me?
I'm not one of these
guys, I'm a policeman!
‐I was just following them!
‐You're just a bonus then.
Ah, uh‐‐urgh!
A bonus, that's it,
I'm not gonna stay here
and be insulted by‐‐
♪
Doctor, there's
a change of plan.
The first wax figure
will be Zenigata.
An excellent choice, Madame,
in fact, in his case,
the process will help smooth
out his irregular features.
(machinery whirring)
(shouting)
Pops, oh no!
You‐‐well actually,
you look way better,
but‐‐okay, that's it!
I'm sick of this,
I'm gonna die anyway!
Jigen!
(gunshots and laughter)
Hey, try zeroing in on
the machines instead, 'kay?
♪
(cackling)
Lupin, Goemon!
♪
They can't help you,
it's all over.
All right, Doctor,
you can go ahead now.
(laughing)
Please, no, wait, don't do it!
(electricity crackling)
♪
Come on, Goemon, think
a little faster, 'kay?
Damn, come on, center yourself.
‐Where is it coming from?
‐Wake up, Goemon!
I don't know why I love wax
figures so much, who cares?
It's my own little
fetish and I love it!
‐What're ya waiting for?
‐Goemon!
♪
Aha.
(yelling)
♪
(gasping)
(explosions)
Done.
♪
Goemon, what're you doing?
Get us out!
Run, now!
♪
(evil laughter)
Looks like it's just you
and me now, my children!
♪
Don't you get any
ideas about escaping.
You're mine, you hear?
♪
Forever!
(laughing)
♪
(wind whistling)
So, it was the
little boy all along
who was the original
source of the telepathy?
Mhm, he ran the whole show
from the very beginning,
and he planted illusions
in our minds to keep us
convinced we couldn't
escape from there.
You know, I wonder
where he came from,
and how it was he ended
up being used as a pawn
by that insane
Madame X and the doctor.
When you think about it,
you really can't help
‐feeling sorry for him.
‐Yeah, he most likely thought
the whole thing was
a game, you know?
A pretty scary kinda game.
I wonder if she actually
died in there, you know?
♪
So, what do you think we
should do with him, Lupin?
Well, I'm tempted to
leave him like this.
He's such a pain in the ass.
Tempting, yes, but that's
a little bit too cruel.
♪
Welcome back to
another happy ending.
Tootles!
I don't know, he still acts
like a big block of wax.
Oh yeah, well you
ain't seen nothin' yet!
You hear me?
I'll follow you straight
into hell, Lupin!
Ahh!
♪ Lupin the third ♪
Exactly how much trouble
are diamonds worth?
A whole bunch if the next
episode is any indication.
We're captured, tortured,
shot with suicide beams,
chased all over India by
a ruthless gang of thugs.
Any normal person would
quit and get a real job,
but that's not me, as you know!
It's called, "Holy Cow."
Catch ya later!
♪