♪
♪ Lup ♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(glass breaks)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪♪
So, this is it,
the famous Tiffany's.
Somehow I expected something
a little more impressive.
Looks just like any
other jewelry store to me.
Yeah, the storefront's
almost shabby.
You better take
a look at this.
Come here.
Ah!
They put it all into
the merchandise, I see.
Wow!
Are you hearing that?
It's bulletproof
and double‐pane glass.
And the frame is solid titanium.
(grunts)
And freakin' iron walls, too.
Well, if you ask me,
that's overkill.
I mean, what are
they so scared of?
If you got some kind
of thing about theft,
you shouldn't be in
the jewelry business.
Yeah, you know,
it could just be
we'd be doing them a favor
by running them out
of the jewelry game.
Hey, yeah, you got
a real point there, Jigen.
I agree, I suggest you
give it a try, Mr. Lupin.
♪
Perhaps a private tour
of the store would help
you make up your mind.
Please, come in.
♪
Tiffany & Company has
never been broken into
since the store first opened.
If you were successful,
it would go down
in the annals of history.
That would be nice,
but who are you,
if you don't mind?
I'm Margaret Tiffany.
I own this place.
I'm also a successful
newscaster on one of
the local channels.
Call me Maggie,
everyone does.
(typewriter keys clicking)
♪
Now, Maggie, I must've
misunderstood.
You're saying you intend
to report a live burglary
on Christmas Eve?
Can you imagine
the ratings on this
when the competition's
airing some schmaltzy
Christmas show?
But Maggie, an exclusive
on the live commission
of a felony puts
the station in
a delicate legal position,
to put it mildly.
It's collusion!
But if the store
he's robbing is mine,
and nobody else has
legal standing to object,
then where exactly is
our liability on this?
Uh, well, you could
make the case it was
a holiday‐themed
stunt for publicity.
Mm‐hmm.
(muttering)
(tires screech)
Right here, here,
he's in here.
Let's get the story, come on.
‐What room is he in?
‐Right there!
Well, what have we here?
Look, Jigen, it's our
friends from the media.
Tell me, what newsworthy
thing have we been
accused of today?
(grunts)
Man, that hurts.
Didn't you say you'd
stayed here before?
What the hell is the deal?
You couldn't get in
this place 10 years ago.
It's kinda gone
downhill, hasn't it?
Oh, gee, you think?
You really gotta
get out more, Jigen.
Mr. Lupin, I have
great news for you.
You and your friends
will be breaking
into Tiffany & Company
this Christmas Eve.
Huh?
You got the wrong guys.
This isn't a working
vacation for us.
We're here to enjoy Christmas.
Yeah, he's right.
Even thieves have a right
to a well‐deserved break
now and then.
Oh, but it's all set.
The station's going
to have a live broadcast.
They're already selling ads.
Maggie, we have no intention
of participating in this stunt.
Just who decided this?
Well, I did.
Huh?
You're insane.
♪
Ah, now, this is more like it.
I wouldn't think of
having my stars
stay in anything but the
finest hotels in New York.
Let's go!
Well, it beats the hell
out of that last place.
‐Wanna take a look?
‐Hmm.
♪
I picked this room
just for you.
I hope it meets
your requirements.
Huh.
♪
Wow, I've been in
a lot of great hotels,
but this room is in
a class all its own.
This suite is really amazing!
I think it'll do.
I wanna make sure
you enjoy yourself
in the style to which
you're accustomed,
so I've arranged for
$100,000 in spending money.
Did I hear right?
Mm‐hmm.
Will it do?
Look, Maggie, this is nice,
but you can't bribe
us into this.
Uh...
It would be polite
to at least take
a look at it since I went
to all the trouble.
Sure.
♪
Just cab fare, really.
That's real nice of you.
Yeah, big heart.
(airy laugh, groans)
Hey!
Are you and I talking
about the same thing?
Uh, yeah, sure.
The bounty she's
displaying, honest.
What kind of boob
do you think I am?
And then finally...
here's the check
for your appearance.
I'm leaving the
amount blank for now.
The deal is, if you make off
with the entire inventory,
you can fill in any
amount you wish.
$50 million,
half a billion,
anything!
I've told you, we're
just here to have
a little holiday fun.
♪
Yeah, a nice long holiday
in prison is a downside.
I don't like it.
Hey, we gotta get going.
We're gonna miss
that flight to Panama.
♪
Where's he going?
Forget it, it's fishing.
Nothing could stop
him from that.
I see this all the time.
Rich people like you
always make the mistake
of assuming the rest
of the world is as
motivated by money as you are.
Too bad, it was a cute
idea for a special.
I would've watched it,
but it's not to be.
Guess not.
What the hell,
long as I'm here,
I guess I might
as well stay a while.
I'm not sure that's
such a great idea.
Oh, and why not?
Wouldn't everyone
mistake you for a hooker?
Well, it's been a pleasure.
Ugh!
(groans)
I hate that freakin' bitch!
That settles it,
I'm moving in here for good.
♪
No, tell me you're kidding!
Canceled, can't be!
It was a perfect opportunity!
Arresting Lupin on television!
In primetime!
Look, it's Fujiko.
Huh?
Have you ever spent
the holiday season
here in New York?
It's really quite lovely.
Huh?
Well, welcome.
So, did you have
any luck finding
a more suitable hotel?
I'm still there.
What have you got here to help
a cheap slut look more classy?
I'm sure it's out of
your price range, but...
how's this?
Ah, that's an amusing
little bauble, yes.
I'll take it.
I'm getting carpal tunnel
from writing so
many checks lately.
Thanks for your help.
So, how much?
A hundred thousand
before sales tax.
Huh?
Having a fire sale?
There.
Hmm, there's just
a little matter
of a missing zero
on this check, ma'am.
What?
It can be difficult
writing checks
when you're not used to it.
It's nothing
to be ashamed of,
it happens with
lower‐end clients like you.
Frightfully careless of me.
You certainly earned
your salary today.
Whoa!
Hey!
That's it, show that
swordfish who's boss, man.
(grunting)
(water splashing)
(yelps)
I was so close.
Step aside, sonny boy.
Here.
Now, watch and learn, fellas.
Excuse me for
interrupting you, gramps,
but that thing doesn't
seem to have any line on it.
Now, you see a plain old line
is just gonna break on me.
Can't argue with that.
But how are you gonna
catch any fish?
An electronic device.
It disables the critter
so I can just pluck him
out of the water
when I feel like it.
Electronic, huh?
Mm‐hmm.
I think up ideas
all the time.
The name's Jebopee.
You probably know
some of my stuff.
Yeah, for instance,
this little light saber
thing‐a‐majig works too.
‐Look!
‐Huh?
Huh?
It's a shame, never did
get a patent for this
thing‐a‐mabob, and that's
why I'm still so poor.
That's how it goes, I guess.
(chuckles)
Yup, now just sit back
and marvel at the amazing
power of the Jebopee
light saber sport fisherman.
♪
Ah, there he is.
(laser buzzing)
You see that?
Told you, like a charm!
♪
(chuckles)
This line won't ever break.
Huh?
Ah!
(explosion)
(coughing)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
Hmm, yes, I'll take this.
Is that right?
Uh, miss?
Actually, you've written
too many zeros on this.
Huh?
♪
Mr. Lupin, this
message arrived for you.
Thank you.
"No idea how,
but there's no money left.
Come back to the Plaza
just as soon as you can."
That's the most expensive
hotel in all of New York!
That's where all the
damn money went, Fujiko.
I'm right, aren't I?
It's crazy, isn't it?
Hey, what's up?
Man, I'm not gonna
get into this with you.
Fujiko's your
burden, thank God.
Gee, what a pal.
♪
I've arrived.
So, what the hell
is going on?
Oh, Lupin!
Oh, my darling.
If you love somebody,
you forgive them
no matter what they do,
isn't that right?
Um, what do you mean?
Well, it's just that
I've been writing
a lot of checks lately
and the bank called,
and they said they need
a million dollars
by tomorrow.
A million bucks?
And even though I didn't
feel right about it, I...
Oh, pretty please promise
you won't get mad at me, Lupin.
Why?
Mad about what?
I...
sort of got my hands
on this check from Maggie.
‐What?
‐Huh?
♪
Good afternoon,
and happy holidays
from all of us here
at DDT Television,
where we're proud
to present an exclusive
live broadcast
of an actual robbery
here at the famous Tiffany
& Company headquarters
in Midtown Manhattan.
It's our Christmas
present to you, our viewers.
Camera crews are
setting up inside
and outside the famed
jewelry retailer.
With the chiming of the bells
at St. Patrick's
Cathedral at midnight,
history will be made
as we find out if Lupin
can outwit Tiffany's security.
And speak of the devil.
Here's the celebrated
thief himself.
(groans)
♪
Oh, yeah, this is better
than the Fourth of July!
Yikes, Pops, what the
hell are you doing here?
I'm gonna cap my career off
by arresting you in front
of a worldwide audience.
I'm gonna be the
hero of this show!
Zenigata!
But Pops, I always thought
you had a face made for radio.
Hey!
Uh, in the spirit
of fair play,
you will show us
the set up, won't you?
Okay, why not?
It's not gonna help
you a whole lot.
Here!
‐Huh?
♪
Like it?
Not even a cockroach
like you could get in.
It's true!
Allow me to demonstrate
for you with this.
(alarm bells ring)
Well, thanks to your
shopaholic girlfriend, Lupin,
we're in big trouble now.
Hmm.
We'll figure something out.
Don't worry.
Lupin, let's face it.
It's impregnable.
They thought of everything.
I'm afraid your friends
are right, Mr. Lupin.
Yes, this could be
a red letter day
for Inspector Zenigata.
(tires screech)
Hi there, Lupin, what's up?
Fujiko, are you nuts?
What the hell is this?
It's a Rolls.
Have you ever driven
one of these cars?
The ride is just so smooth.
Hey, Fujiko!
Aw!
If Zenigata doesn't
get me, she will.
I mean, what's wrong
with the subway?
Huh?
Oh!
Hmm, not only is nothing
wrong with the subway,
but, in fact,
it's just perfect.
(chuckles)
♪
(gears squeaking)
I can't exactly say
this is how I envisioned
spending my
Christmas Eve this year.
Hmm, it does seem a bit
sacrilegious, Lupin.
I know, I know,
I'm just glad
you guys are here.
(drill whines)
Look, I just
represent Interpol,
but this is your city, Chief.
You gotta mobilize some
of your men on this thing.
I'm telling you,
this is a real
slippery criminal!
But even Lupin won't
be able to break
into Tiffany's, Inspector.
It's a waste of
city resources.
If and when something
trips that alarm,
we'll deploy.
Besides, it's
Christmas Eve, Inspector.
Goodwill toward men.
Argh, you just don't get it!
Speaking of which,
why don't you join
my family for dinner tonight?
There is no Christmas for
the guy on Lupin's trail,
so no thank you.
This guy's gonna be on
stakeout the rest of the night.
Goodbye!
♪
(tonal ringing)
I don't wanna hurry
you or anything,
but hurry up!
That bell's gonna be jingling
at St. Patrick's very soon.
I'm aware of that.
So, Mr. Jebopee,
how much longer
do you think?
Hold on, it's
just about ready.
Yeah, well,
I'm ready anytime.
(groans)
♪
(bells toll)
We're counting on you, Goemon.
Mm‐hmm.
(metal cranking)
♪
(grunts)
(grunting)
♪
Hmm?
(screams)
♪
(rumbling)
Ah, tell me this
isn't happening!
♪
(chuckles)
Nice work,
very nice indeed.
♪
Lupin, you'll never
get away with this,
you hear me?
Wow, how many company
cars have you been through?
Well, there goes the
old Christmas bonus!
Oh, yeah, you're gonna
get what's coming
to you, Lupin.
So just laugh it up
while you can!
Keep it down a bit, will you?
We're about to do
a little night fishing.
Huh?
(groans)
Well, that's one
nuisance out of the way.
Now, let's crank
this up a notch.
Yeah!
(laser buzzing)
♪
Like shooting
fish in a barrel,
but they're not fish,
so go ahead and
fire at will.
(lasers buzzing)
♪
Now, these would add
a very festive touch
to anybody's Christmas tree.
Whoa, look.
Diamonds, rubies,
is that an emerald?
Like my little
invention, do you?
Kind of fond of it myself.
Should've got the Nobel Prize
if there was just
an ounce of justice
in this world.
(lasers buzzing)
♪
It can't be!
Oh!
"Merry Christmas,
the jewels are in
the hand of
the goddess of liberty.
Lupin the Third."
Does he mean the statue?
Lupin!
(panting)
Ah, the bastard
did it again!
Huh?
He leave this?
Hmm, guy's too cocky
for his own damn good
or my good, for that matter!
Lupin!
(jingle bells ringing)
♪
Merry Christmas
to everyone!
Merry Christmas!
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪♪
Next time we really
bring out the big guns.
This one's got hot chicks
with elephant trunks,
hot studs in
boxing trunks,
thrills, fills,
chills, an old nemesis,
and a treasure so huge it'll
literally make you sick.
Join us as we try to rescue
a kidnapped princess in
"Return of the X Factor."
Catch you later!
♪