♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(gunfire)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(grunting)
(growl)
♪
(yelling)
Ugh.
♪
‐Pull.
‐(gunfire)
Another.
‐Pull.
‐(gunfire)
Wha?
‐Pull.
‐(gunfire)
(snicker)
♪
Fujiko, I know
I'm an old man but...
Take a hike, gramps.
Fujiko, I love you,
will you marry me?
(growling)
You're trying to
muscle in on my woman.
She's too young for you,
she's too beautiful.
Stay away from her.
You young punk!
♪
"Hey guys, I don't know if
you've heard about this or not,
but the Sirloin is the first
of an entirely new class
of super luxury liner.
It's absolutely incredible.
It makes the Queen Mary
look like the Minnow.
Anyway, she's leaving
for Lisbon on the third
for her maiden
around the world voyage,
and since it sounded like
a great excuse for a reunion,
I took the liberty of booking
passage for all of us.
So, don't send regrets,
just be there.
Lupin."
♪
(typewriter keys clanking)
(fanfare)
♪
(fireworks)
The Sirloin is the most
spectacular passenger
ship ever built.
At a cost of
one billion dollars,
it took five
years to complete.
It weighs 250,000 tons.
It's 1,500 feet long
and 200 feet wide,
has 130 passenger cabins
and can cruise up to‐‐
Gourmet restaurant,
multiplex theaters,
pool, cocktail lounges,
ski jump, football field,
racetrack,
state of the art security.
This ain't no boat,
it's friggin' Las Vegas
with seagulls.
And I say let
the good times roll on.
(surf crashing)
I hope everyone is having
a great time today.
Now we're gonna be playing
some of your favorite songs‐‐
Ha, I thought I'd find you
listening to elevator music.
It's five years later, Goemon,
and you're still
listening to that crap.
Yes, and five years later
you still haven't quit
smoking, have you, Jigen?
Perhaps you need
a little assistance?
Here, let me help you.
(Japanese lyrics on radio)
Hmm?
♪
Tiffany
cigarette holder, nice.
I'm guessing some rich
old fart lost track of it
while you were holding
his other cigarette.
It's nice to see your wit
hasn't lost any of its dull
edge in five years, Jigen.
Looks like Lupin's
lost a step, though.
Used to be you could set
your watch by the guy.
Truth is it used
to really cheese me off‐‐
‐(screaming)
‐What the?
Someone's committing suicide!
Nah, the airplane's too low,
just check out the attitude,
someone's gonna
make a grand entrance.
Whaaa!
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Whaa hoo hoo hoo!
♪
Oh, crap!
(tooting)
(coughing)
To our reunion.
Kanpai.
‐Cheers.
‐Here's mud in your eye.
Sorry to be late, I had
a minor matter to attend to.
Tell me about it,
I'm guessing you probably
had to lift a
Van Gogh or even two
to pay for all of our tickets.
‐Huh?
‐Hey, whatever.
Any guy who's willing to shell
out this kind of scratch
just to treat his old
friends to a good time
is aces with me.
Hey, wait a minute,
what do you mean,
whoa, back up, what do
you mean, treat you?
Uh...
Huh?
Well, I hate to
break it to you guys,
but I got one, too.
"My darling Lupin,
you've been in my dreams every
night for five long years.
Oh, darling, I can't bear
being apart from you any longer.
I simply have to
see you immediately.
Rendezvous with me on
the Sirloin on October 3rd
and I promise I'll make
both our dreams come true."
Oh please, this doesn't
sound anything like me.
Or smell like you.
(sniffing)
What's that?
Not even a trace
of Chanel No. 5.
Trust me, I nearly sucked
the entire thing up my nose.
So this is just
a steaming pile of‐‐
Very bad karma.
Exactly, my friends, we've
all fallen into someone's
very ingenious trap.
Not you though, you figured
it out for a trap, Lupin,
and you waltzed
right into it anyway.
What the hell's up with that?
I don't know
about you, Jigen,
but I like to know
who my enemies are.
The sooner
he shows his hand
the sooner
I can show him mine.
We must remain
as vigilant as the owl.
Exactly.
Ah‐ha!
I've got you cornered at last!
(laughing)
Zenigata, at last!
Oh, Pops, it's been so long,
let me kiss you all over.
Mwa mwa mwa.
Oh, that aftershave
drives me wild.
Hey, I heard you
were transferred
to some Podunk crap hole
after the last time I slipped
through your fingers.
Pretty slow in the sticks
for a fine investigative
mind like yours,
but I'm sure you didn't
let the tedium get to you.
Hmm.
♪
(humming)
Yeah, well, these are your
transfer papers, wise guy,
straight to maximum security!
Read it and weep!
Let me see this.
"Inspector Zenigata,
we've received intelligence
that Lupin The Third
will be on board
for the maiden
voyage of the Sirloin.
Given your knowledge
of the fugitive,
you're assigned as the ship's
temporary interim
investigating officer.
You are to watch
for this known felon
and arrest him
if you spot him."
Temporary interim
investigating officer?
Wow, that's pretty impressive.
Do you get a shiny
badge and everything?
It's not necessary, my friend.
With this arrest warrant,
all I need are these
little handcuffs, you see?
Now, come along!
Hey, hold on now,
are you really Lupin?
That's what my momma calls me.
Oh yeah, so why'd you surrender
so easily then, smart guy?
I'm just humoring you.
You don't have any authority
to arrest me on this ship,
Inspector Zenigata.
Are you blind, I have
a warrant right here!
I know, and it's
a lovely one, too,
except for one little thing.
There's no watermark
and as you know,
without a watermark,
it's not considered legal
in a court of law.
Huh, it's a forgery?
How in the world
could that have happened?
Well, what do you know?
It looks like Pops
here has been lured
into the same exact
trap as the rest of us.
Oh, damn it, I was so close!
Why does this
always happen to me?
It's not fair, I tell you,
it's just not fair!
Hey, take it easy, Pops.
There's not much any
of us can do right now
but hang around and wait.
Sit down, have a drink,
take a load off.
Why should I, huh?
‐Because you have no choice.
‐(knuckles cracking)
Grrr!
Let's shake on it.
You are not‐‐
shake with you on what?
Our temporary interim
alliance agreement.
Here's the deal, listen up.
Right now, we join forces
to defeat our mutual enemy
and then after that,
I'm all yours.
What do you say?
Pops, do we partner up or not?
Hmm, well, all right,
but how the heck
do we smoke out
these bad guys?
By just sitting back,
enjoying the cruise,
and playing dumb.
Sooner or later, they're
bound to make their move
and then we'll
see what's what.
So what do you say, old man,
are you in or are you out?
Hmm.
Deal, come on, we'll seal it
the good old fashioned way, huh.
Hmm.
Hey, either
I'm really loaded
or the ceiling's
getting closer.
What, the ceiling?
(creaking)
Whoa, one side!
Watch out!
Aagghh!
Good gravy!
(screaming)
(crashing)
♪
Damn.
My sentiments exactly.
♪
(evil laughter)
Did you see that?
They scattered like roaches.
Oh, God, I love it.
Welcome to my roach motel,
Lupin and company.
Checkout time is never!
(evil laughter)
(footsteps)
Damn tooth throbs
like hell these days.
Happens whenever I get jumpy.
Getting too old
for this crap.
Hello, welcome,
come right in.
You're about to
experience the very latest
in pain‐free
dental technology.
See?
(hydraulic motor whooshing)
Excuse me, this is an
emergency, out of my way.
Huh?
Ah!
(screaming)
Huh?
Hey, Doc‐‐where'd he go?
Doc!
Where is he?
(gasping)
(screaming)
What the!
‐(yelling)
‐(gunshot)
Hmm.
These are hard times
for innocent bystanders.
What kind of amateur
are we dealing with?
Welcome, sir,
right this way.
‐Many thanks.
‐Mm‐hmm.
(moaning)
I respectfully request
that you loosen your‐‐huh?
(laughing)
Die!
Die, die!
♪
You foolish man.
I am a Jito‐Ryo master.
Allow me to reunite you
with your ancestors.
(yelling)
(punching)
(springs bouncing)
(splash)
Lupin.
Hmm?
♪
Huh, it's a trap.
Hold on, don't jump, Fujiko!
♪
Ah!
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
♪
Arrgh!
(heavy breathing)
Very funny, Lupin!
Fujiko, you don't understand!
(splash)
(yelling)
Lupin.
♪
(gulls screeching)
So the clinic,
the sauna, and the pool.
These guys
are really shrewd.
(grimacing)
Easy there, Fujiko,
I'm still very tender.
Oh, poor baby,
is this better, Lupin?
Ah, yes, that's
much better, Fujiko.
More.
Disgust rises
from deep within me.
So what do you guys figure
their next move is gonna be?
‐I'm getting kind of‐‐
‐(footsteps)
Huh?
Speak of the devil.
Arrggh!
(stammering)
A letter arrived for you.
(screaming)
One can never be too careful.
Well well, another invitation.
Ooh, a special dinner show,
the most spectacular
show we'll ever see.
♪
Oh, mmm.
It's the same old thing,
fine china for them,
a Styrofoam cup for me.
That's a devastating
gown, Fujiko.
Grrr.
You have to have patience,
Fujiko, my love.
Whoever these guys
are, my guess is
we'll be making their
acquaintance very soon now,
like it or not.
But you must have
some kind of a hunch.
I can do better than that.
Just take a look at the
emblem on that invitation.
A scorpion?
Exactly right, the Scorpion.
(together)
Hmm, the Scorpion?
That's what I said.
Its demise was
apparently exaggerated
as was that of its
leader, Mister X.
♪
(crazed laughter)
Brilliant deduction, Lupin.
And now as a reward,
allow me to treat all of you
to a spectacle
years in the making.
I call it
Road Rage II, The Sequel!
Crap, crap, crap, crap!
(evil laughter)
I haven't seen you
in a long time, my friends.
How long has it been?
Exactly five years,
if I'm not mistaken.
That's right, Lupin.
It was five years ago.
(motor racing)
Remember, you completely
destroyed the Hilder Speedway,
a little pet project that
cost me $50 million to build!
(exploding)
(tires screeching)
(groaning)
I nearly died myself, but I
had my burnt and mangled body
painstakingly repaired
by the most advanced
experimental technology.
And now, out of
the ashes of my dream,
I have been resurrected as
your worst bionic nightmare!
I must say I'm delighted
to see you again,
especially after all this time.
Time to say goodbye, Lupin.
(laughing)
This is no joke!
Oh, I don't know, Exy,
I mean you spent $50 million
to lure me to Hilder
and now a billion
and change on this gambit.
You may be a gifted maniac,
but you're a lousy businessman.
And I'll keep on spending
everything I have
until you've been exterminated!
Ooh, the obsessive type.
Allow me to demonstrate
exactly what you're up against.
Who's your daddy?
Oh, God, oh crap,
oh Mommy, help me!
And now get ready for
our feature presentation
starting me and a bunch
of expendable day players.
But Mister X, mere mortals
versus a super being,
where's the drama?
Right here‐‐an assortment
of assault vehicles
plus an armory's worth
of devastating fire power
are being provided
to you for your use
to keep things from
getting too predictable.
This should prove entertaining.
It's show time,
take your places!
What's the matter?
Do you all have stage fright?
Allow me, the proud oak
is strong like a man.
But the cyclone
is wise like a woman.
Grrrr.
Huh?
Grrrrr!
Ooh, that tickles.
Uggh.
(gasps)
You bionic fruitcake,
the show's over!
Eat lead!
(gunfire)
(laughing)
(repeated gunshots)
Huh?
(yelling)
Let's do it, Fujiko.
(glass breaking)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Ha ha, bring it on, Lupin.
You can't defeat me.
♪
(tires skidding)
What the?
(groaning)
(car exploding)
(skidding)
(crashing)
(exploding)
(gasp)
(flames flickering)
♪
(water pouring)
You think I'm
unable to swim, Lupin?
Jigen, Goemon,
get out of the water!
♪
(gunfire)
(zapping)
(screaming)
(moaning)
♪
(groaning)
Come back.
♪
Damn you, Lupin.
You'll never leave
this place alive!
(beeping)
As soon as I detonate
this remote control,
the entire ship will
explode in a massive fireball,
then you'll be
dead for sure, Lupin!
You hear that?
(biting)
♪
(exploding)
(screaming)
Quick, this way!
Lupin, where are you?
Damn it, Lupin!
(ship exploding)
(horn blowing)
(waves lapping)
♪
It's unbelievable.
A billion dollars‐‐
it's all gone,
sunk in the ocean for what?
All for revenge,
what a waste.
I just can't get over it.
Oh, Pops, the constant
pain in the rear
who hounded me across seven
continents is gone forever.
It's really true
what they say in the song,
you don't know what
you've got till it's gone.
Everybody's got
to go sometime.
It's all just
a long goodbye, Lupin.
Zenigata is now
with his ancestors.
Poor Pops.
Lupin, you weasel,
we had a deal!
Get your butt over here!
Grrrr!
Pops, is that you?
We thought you were dead!
Oh, I could kiss you,
you big lug.
Let's get out of here, guys.
The chase is on again, woo hoo!
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
♪
Ya, ya, ya!
Wait, Lupin!
(sputtering)
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Come back here, you!
Ah, Rio de Janeiro.
Beautiful girls,
beautiful beaches,
beautiful city.
The prison accommodations
aren't exactly five star,
but I won't be staying long.
Check out my early
checkout technique
in the next episode,
Buns, Guns,
and Fun in the Sun.
Tootles.
♪