♪
(gunshot)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(shattering)
(engine revving)
(tires screeching)
♪
(gunshot)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(tires screeching)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
Do you, Sir William Hafner,
take this woman
to be your wife
now and for as long as
you both shall live?
I do.
Ah, and you, Fujiko Mine,
do you take this man to be
your lawfully wedded husband
now and for as long
as you both shall live?
♪
Yes, I do.
(applauding)
(bells chiming)
(cheering)
♪
(wind howling)
(clicking)
Smile.
♪
Oh!
Oh, Fujiko!
Lupin.
♪
Fujiko.
(tapping of typewriter keys)
♪
Fujiko, you can't be serious.
You're not really gonna
marry this guy, are you?
Sure I am, why shouldn't I?
Why shouldn't you?
Now I know you're kidding.
There's no way you
haven't heard the rumors
about this creepy
slimeball, right?
Yes, I know that every
woman that he's married
has become a
homicide statistic
within just a few weeks
of tying the knot.
Well, so what the
hell are you thinking?
I'm well aware of the
risk involved, Lupin,
but it's worth it
to get my hands on
that man's incredible
jewelry collection.
Now that could
be just a rumor.
I mean, come on,
no one's ever seen it.
What if it's all some game?
I can look out for myself.
You should worry
about your own safety.
He's famous for
being jealous, Lupin.
He wouldn't take kindly to
all this freeway footsie
with his fiancée.
Ha, serves him right!
What, is he afraid
someone else might pull
a poke and croak
before he gets to?
I mean, it's amazing, this
guy is a genuine psychopath.
(honking)
Hey, ya freaking lunatic,
just back off, man, will ya?
I'm trying to have a
moment here, ya know?
I wouldn't mess
with the man, Lupin.
Discretion may very well be
the better part of
valor this time.
So what are you saying?
You can't possibly
mean this is goodbye.
Sure I can, toodles!
Here, for you!
An early contribution
to your funeral display.
(gun firing)
(tires screeching)
♪
Lupin.
That maniac,
I knew he'd be upset,
but I never imagined
the guy had this in him,
I mean, to actually kill her.
(grunting)
Get down here, you coward!
Do the right thing for once!
Turn yourself in!
Fujiko.
Hey!
I said, "Get down here!"
Huh?
♪
What in the world could have
driven him to such a pass?
♪
Come on, get in!
Hurry up, will ya?
♪
Lupin, what's the matter?
Just climb onto the ladder!
No way I'm gonna let the
guy who ruined my life
just watch me turn tail.
Whatever comes next, I'm
gonna take it like a man!
You're not acting like a man.
You're acting
like a little kid
who's seen too many
cornball chick flicks!
All right, hands up!
I can't tell if you want
to be caught or not,
but you know what,
I really don't give a hoot.
It doesn't matter
either way.
You know, that pretty much
sums up how I feel too, Pops.
What's left to give
a hoot about anyway?
You're talking in riddles.
What the heck does that mean?
Time for a thief
to hang it up
when some guy steals
his reason to live.
Just take it easy now!
Lupin, stop!
Think about what
you're doing!
Stop!
See ya, Pops.
Whoa, hold it,
come on, Lupin.
Hey, wait a minute,
come on, don't be‐‐
Hold on, here I come.
We're gonna be together
forever now, Fujiko,
just like we
were meant to be!
No, Lupin!
♪
Lupin!
Ah!
(rumbling)
♪
Such is the power women
have over the ordinary man.
What a fool.
♪
(engine puttering)
Would it be too soon, my
lord, to begin searching
for the next addition
to your collection?
Not at all, feel free.
And what of Fujiko?
The usual, sir,
lying in state.
And then once tomorrow's
service is over,
the lady's body
will be eternified.
The most excellent complement
to your lordship's harem.
Quite.
But since I didn't
kill her myself,
she'll never be quite the
same as all the others.
I'm still much too
irritated for sleep.
If you have need of me,
I'll be in the harem.
♪
(door opening)
(whooshing)
(creaking)
Ladies, your lord and master
is in need of some solace.
♪
Mary, darling,
charming as ever.
My compliments to your
tailor, my dear Jessica.
Every one of you is
beautiful as ever.
Not so much as a wrinkle
or a trace of cellulite.
Each one of you was harvested
at the very peak
of perfection.
You have all spoiled me.
(chuckling)
♪
Fujiko!
Hey!
Can you hear me?
You know it's me, Lupin!
Wake up!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Fujiko, come on, wake up!
Fujiko, come in, it's Lupin!
Ah, damn it.
Come on, will ya?
Quit sleepin' on the job.
Hey, give it a rest, huh?
You know damn well
that's strong stuff
you shot her with, so
it's gonna take 24 hours.
That's just the
way it is, Lupin,
so take a walk or something.
Yeah, I know,
it's just that she's in a
very compromised position,
and Hafner's a
complete maniac.
I'm just worried
about her, I guess.
Yeah, well, it is
a risky strategy.
We were all aware
of that, Lupin.
The whole thing
was her dumb idea.
She convinced me it was the
only way we could figure out
where Hafner's
jewelry collection was.
Then she must be
comfortable with the risk.
That was quite an
Oscar‐caliber performance
you gave out there
on the roof, Lupin.
You had even me convinced
you completely lost it
for a minute or two.
Why thank you very much.
I had to give it my best.
Hafner's always
been very paranoid
about gold‐digging bimbos
bamboozling him
out of his fortune.
Time for a thief
to hang it up
when some guys steals
his reason to live.
Lupin, stop!
Think about what
you're doing!
Stop!
See ya.
Whoa, hold it,
come on, Lupin, hey!
Yeah, I remember when
I saw that smoke,
I thought, "Wait a minute."
♪
Hold on, here I come!
We're gonna be together
forever now, Fujiko,
just like we
were meant to be!
(hissing)
♪
(exploding)
He should be more paranoid
of preposterous dramaturgy .
Opera fan, probably.
Everybody's a critic, but
I accomplished the mission.
Hafner thinks I'm
out of the way.
Once Fujiko's funeral
is over tomorrow,
we'll see who buries who.
(bells chiming)
♪
(sniffing)
There's not even a
scrap of his body left
for somebody to bury.
Not so much as even a bone.
Huh?
Come, come.
Here.
Sit.
(barking)
Eh, not him.
Crap, what in the world
will I do without you?
Yeah, they're just leaving
for the mansion now.
Rumor is there's
a graveyard hidden
somewhere on the grounds.
It would make sense, nothing
is quite as inconvenient
as an accidentally exhumed ex.
No one's ever seen it though.
♪
Okay, guys, it's been an hour
since her body was
brought inside.
There's no sign
of any activity.
I'd give Fujiko
another buzz about now.
Right.
(rapid beeping)
Fujiko, you awake yet?
Come on, answer me.
Can you hear me?
Are you there?
Fujiko, wake up!
Ugh, damn it.
(rapid beeping)
♪
(sighing)
Fujiko, that you?
♪
Lupin, it's me.
What the hell's going on?
Where am I?
Finally.
Damn, you're a heavy sleeper.
What do you mean
where are you?
You're in Hafner's mansion.
Hmm, it's hard to believe.
The place is so
sparsely furnished,
I thought I was in some
afterlife waiting room.
(gasping)
(groaning)
Hey, Fujiko?
(sighing)
Fujiko, what is it?
You okay?
Fujiko, if you can hear me,
turn on the transmitter.
(groaning)
Okay, good to go.
All right, I'm going in.
Just keep monitoring her
location for me, all right?
(wheels squeaking)
The sterilization
process is complete.
Well, then, let's
prepare Miss Fujiko
to take her honored place
in the harem, shall we?
I must say though, her
taste in men is far better
than her taste in jewelry.
What a horribly
tacky thing this is.
All right, Lupin, just keep
heading north from there.
(clattering)
Ah, yes.
My darling Fujiko, this is
the happiest day of my life,
well, since my
last wedding day.
(chuckles)
Bring her to the hareem.
Yes, sir.
Hmm?
Hey, what the‐‐it just
went off, Fujiko's light.
What, how can that be?
Think it was Fujiko?
How the hell should I know?
All I know is it's
off, it's gone.
Damn it, now I've
got to search
the whole place for her.
We don't have
that kind of time.
♪
Fujiko, where are you?
Fujiko!
Hold on!
Where is she?
Hey, Fujiko!
We've got company,
Jigen, hit the dirt!
(guns firing)
Damn it!
Sorry, but you're gonna
have to finish this one
without your hat,
now come on.
They've got no idea
what terrible fury
they've just unleashed.
♪
(grunting)
(groaning)
♪
Hey!
(wheels squeaking)
♪
Here you are, my darling.
May you be eternally
comfortable.
Ah, if only she
could see herself.
(gasping)
Ah!
How can this be?
Where am I?
Uh, mm...
I guess I must have
fainted on the way home.
Are you going to
leave me down here?
Thank you, darling.
♪
All real, and
I'm proud to say
I loved every one of
them as much as you.
You're saying
you married them
and then you murdered them
all, and now I'm next?
Yes, afraid so, but
look at it this way,
of all the most beautiful
women throughout history,
you few will be spared
the cruel humiliation
of living to see
that beauty fade.
You know it would
kill you, wouldn't it?
(gasping)
You thought you
were very clever,
but all you achieved was
giving me the pleasure
of killing you myself
with my own hands.
Now, my dear, you don't
want to be frozen forever
with that look on your face.
Lupin, help me!
I regret to inform you
that Lupin is in no position
to save you now.
Don't worry, my darling,
I promise to be
relatively gentle about it.
(laughing)
♪
Crap.
(laughing)
Ah!
(whooshing)
(water lapping)
I don't get it.
There's no place
left to look.
I've checked the
whole damn mansion.
There's no footprints, tracks,
or anything leading the way.
She's got to be inside.
Damn it, what did we miss?
(sighing)
Come on!
Hmm, your hat.
Huh?
♪
Hey, where the hell
did that come from?
No, it's totally ruined.
You know, it looks
clean for once.
I thought it fell
in the fountain
when we fought those guards.
Hmm, they're both
connected somehow.
Great, freaking chlorine
is gonna bleach my hat.
Hmm?
(grunting)
♪
(shouting)
(cracking)
(whooshing)
What the hell?
‐Hmm?
(laughing)
Ah!
Are you saying you're
too good, is that it?
You insult me and
every girl in this room!
(laughs)
No, please, I‐‐
Yes, now that's an
expression worth preserving.
Sincere, beseeching.
(gasping)
Huh?
(growling)
♪
Lupin!
Rough wedding night, Fujiko?
‐I warned ya.
‐Bastard.
So you were in this together.
You've heard the
expression, what is it,
till death do us part?
Touching, and how apropos.
Really, okay then,
let's get to it.
No, killing a man
is not my style.
I have people, or rather
I should say a mannequin
to handle annoyances
like that for me.
Yes, one of them is fake.
♪
So you see, Lupin, I wouldn't
move a finger if I were you.
♪
(gun firing)
Oh!
I won't let anybody
defile my brides.
(groaning)
♪
‐Hey!
‐Oh, no!
Wait a minute, Lupin.
Hafner's jewelry
collection, get it?
It's all those
engagement rings.
Forget it.
Come on, unless
you want to die.
♪
Unbelievable.
All that trouble for this.
You know, as long
as you're already
dressed up for it and all,
it'd be a shame to waste
such a nice wedding dress.
Sorry, but it just
wouldn't be right.
It's too soon after my
husband's tragic death.
I'm still in
mourning, you know.
And I've got assets
to go through.
♪
Hmm, I thought
the white knight
was supposed to
win in the end.
You know, Lupin,
I'm not really sure
Fujiko's the
fairy tale kind of gal.
If you want a happily
ever after with her,
you just might
have to kill her
then hope for the
very best in heaven,
you know what I mean?
You're right.
Bang.
You said it.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
A note from an old flame
has got two surprises.
First, the old
flame is Jigen's.
Second, well,
you're looking at her.
No, she wasn't a nun
then, but she is now,
and she's calling in a favor.
No big deal, just
dropping into the middle
of an African war zone
and rescuing the most
wanted man in the country.
Don't miss the next one
when we come face‐to‐face
with pure evil in
"Dark Charade."
Catch ya later!
♪