♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(gunshot)
♪
(women vocalizing)
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
♪
(lightning cracking)
(bats screeching)
(door creaking)
"My dear sir, I have enjoyed
following the reports
of your audacious exploits
for many years now.
My family, the Gabriels,
are of noble, Austrian stock,
and have owned a one‐of‐a‐kind
gem for generations
known as Dracula's Tear.
I would consider
it the highest honor
if you would consent
to accept my invitation
to steal it.
I attach only one
condition to this offer,
that the theft be conducted
aboard my private dirigible,
the Hendenburg.
♪
I have invited, as witnesses
to your latest master stroke,
a selection of the world's
greatest living detectives.
Sherlock Holmes III.
(gunshot)
♪
The American, Philip Archer.
(glugging)
(belching)
♪
Kosuke Kindani of Japan.
Kosuke, get
to work right now!
And of course,
your life‐long nemesis,
Inspector Zenigata.
Hoping this challenge piques
your professional interest,
I remain yours truly,
Gabriel The Thirteenth
Earl of Grossglockner."
(bell tinkling)
Is there something you'd like
for me to do, Your Lordship?
See this is
delivered to Lupin.
Ah, yes, Your Lordship.
Anything else?
Yah, the Hendenburg.
Tell me, how's
the work coming along?
Have my designs
been implemented?
Yes, just as
Your Lordship specified.
I can show you.
I shot this just this morning.
What do you think,
Your Lordship?
Ah.
Magnificent.
I'm really quite a genius.
It's not only a fitting
capstone to my career
as the world's preeminent
authority on dirigibles,
but it's the perfect trap
to catch the infamous Lupin.
It's also a monumental
testament to the superiority
of the Teutonic peoples.
Ja, it's really quite a
noble destiny for vermin
such as Lupin.
Perhaps he'll write
from prison to thank me.
(laughing)
(typewriter keys clicking)
♪
(fanfare)
We're broadcasting
from a private airfield
near Grossglockner, Austria,
which Lord Gabriel,
the Earl of Grossglockner,
has graciously
opened to the public
so the whole world might
witness the historic lift off
of his truly
magnificent creation,
the Hendenburg Blimp, as it
makes its maiden flight
across the Atlantic.
The Earl, whose hobbies include
an avid interest in criminology,
has invited a few
of his personal heroes
to join him for this
memorable occasion.
First to arrive is
Sherlock Holmes III.
Hmm, yes, appears to
be steps of some kind.
(murmuring)
Next, the American,
Philip Arch‐‐
Whoa, good heavens!
Why can't I come along, huh?
Friggin' blimp's
no place for a dame.
It's dangerous.
‐Whoa!
Ah.
Mwah.
So long, toots.
‐Welcome, Mr. Archer.
‐Thanks, doll.
‐Oh, my.
‐I'm all right.
(murmuring, bell tinkling)
Yes, and here
rounding out the guest list
is Kosuke Kindani,
Japan's reclusive
and unconventional
criminal investigator.
Whoa, good thing it's
tied down and everything.
Looks like it could
just float away.
Cool.
And now, with its distinguished
company all on board,
it's finally time
for the Hendenburg‐‐
Hey, hold it, I'm coming,
I'm coming, I'm coming!
Oh yes, we almost forgot
Inspector Zenigata of Interpol‐‐
Dammit all, I just...
‐‐as did everyone else,
apparently.
Anyway, he appears
to have arrived
just in the nick of time.
And now, this is it.
The mooring ropes are
disengaged and retracted.
The engines are started.
And a new century begins
much as the last one did
with the hopes and
dreams of millions
born aloft on a cloud of gas
piloted by
one extraordinary man.
A man of vision,
a man of destiny,
a man whose early
years of struggle
would make for an
inspiring mini‐series.
♪
(exclaiming)
Damn, that hurts.
Brings to mind an old
case of mine, you know,
fascinating story.
Can't remember it, really,
something to do with
a crime, I think.
That's so weird, I mean like
'cause the exact same thing
happened to me once
except in my case
the things that happened, you
know, were happening to me.
(glugging)
Hey gumshoe, you want
to share whatever it is
you're bogarting over there?
Sure, it's for my
foot fungus, drink up.
Argh, dammit, these
looney tunes are no match
for Lupin and his gang,
they're just gonna
get in my way!
Gentlemen, dinner is served.
♪
Hmm, yes, definitely a dining
implement of some kind.
A bit showy, whatever it is.
Hey, think about it,
rich guy in a wheelchair,
blows it all on blimps,
doesn't take Freud
for God sakes.
♪
‐Uh, you know, I was...
‐(glass breaking)
Hmm, what a total bummer.
This is not good, whoa, I
think I lost my napkin, dude.
(belch)
Huh?
Welcome, my
distinguished friends.
Where in the hell's
that voice coming from?
Uh.
♪
‐Hmm.
‐Hm.
‐There!
‐It's the moose.
(gunshot)
Hey, were you
aiming at that?
(snickering)
Well done, gentlemen.
‐Huh?
‐Whoa!
Sorry about the napkin, dude.
Forget the damn napkin.
Gentlemen, I am Lord Gabriel.
Ah yes, of course, well.
Ah, at last.
Take your seats, please.
It is an honor to have you
all aboard the Hendenburg.
I trust you all
enjoyed your meal.
We can retire now
to the solarium
for a game of Twister.
The hell with that.
I mean, I don't
want to be rude,
but I didn't come
here to have fun.
I came here 'cause you
promised to deliver Lupin.
Yeah, I'm with
old foot fungus here
unless you're talking about
naked drunken Twister
'cause I'm always up for that.
Rest assured, gentlemen,
Mr. Lupin will
certainly be joining us.
You asked if the food
was satisfactory.
Speaking as an Englishman,
I must say I really don't know.
Hmm, so where is this thing,
this Dracula's Tear
that Lupin's after?
It's right in front of you.
What, I don't
see it, mm‐mmm.
Funny thing
about Bela Lugosi,
frightful drug addict you know,
and yet he screwed Clara Bow
and wrestled a rubber octopus.
Yeah, and so‐‐
it's so obvious.
Dude, you hid that thing
behind your monocle, didn't you?
Huh?
Brilliant deduction, gentlemen.
But I don't get it, how‐‐
‐Yeah!
‐See.
This monocle is a
polarizing lens, gentlemen.
It completely obscures the
brilliancy of the gem.
So tell me, do
the dames go for that?
Blimp dude, you're awesome.
So tell me something,
your Lordship,
what happens if Lupin
manages to find it in there?
Ja, good point, Inspector.
This is why I've arranged
to have the eye sealed shut
with a special plastic
after midnight.
Did you just say
what I think you said?
Lupin has only until midnight
to steal this treasure.
After that, not even the
greatest thief in the world
could pull it off.
Quite brilliant,
really, I must say,
it's got me pondering
the best orifice
for my stamp collection.
Uh, no way, I'm not
gonna touch that one.
‐Three hours left.
‐So, come on, Candy Land,
Mousetrap, Hungry Hippos, hmm?
(lightning crashing)
♪
Why don't you just
slip me a mickey?
I mean, you got
anything a little peppier?
You know, something like‐‐
(singing sloppily)
Aargh!
Another drink for you,
Herr Archer?
Mmm?
Only thirty minutes left.
Maybe Lupin's not gonna
show up after all.
♪
Mmm‐‐huh?
What the‐‐what's that?
Lupin!
Grrrr.
Hey, that says, "Here comes
Lupin The Third," in Japanese!
Uhh, uhh, he's here now!
‐Huh?
‐Cool.
Ah, yes, I felt certain
he wouldn't disappoint us.
I say, anyone care to
accompany me to the loo?
Ah, yes, there's one
in my study, follow me.
♪
(pendulum swinging)
You figured all
the angles, haven't you?
This is a test of
Mr. Lupin's skill.
He'll have to
locate the stone,
break through this iron mask,
and then steal it,
all in front of four
renowned detectives.
Yep, I think Lupin The Third
has finally met his match
in old Gabriel The Thirteenth.
I had a match once, used
to light my pipe with it.
Fascinating.
So now we wait, gentlemen,
and it won't be long now.
(pendulum swinging)
(clock chiming)
‐Huh?
‐What the?
‐Whoa.
‐(gunshot)
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Hey, who turned out
the damn lights?
What's going on?
There, now are we all here?
Good, how about you, sir?
Are you all r‐‐
Sir!
Lord Gabriel,
what's the matter?
♪
(scream)
His eye's gone!
Ah, ah, ah!
Dude, what's up?
He's dead!
‐Whoa!
‐Good heavens.
I could use a drink.
Nobody move!
Whoever did this
is right in this room.
Nobody's goin'
nowhere, understand?
‐Move it!
‐Hey!
Surely you're
not accusing one of us
of this heinous deed?
That's right.
Ouch!
Look, I was the
closest one to the door
when the lights went out.
Nobody came
in from outside,
so the only
possible explanation
is that Lupin disguised
himself as one of you guys
sometime before Gabriel brought
us all in to the study.
Hmm, perhaps it was me,
fascinating!
But dude, you're
totally clueless.
Oh, I've got
clues all right.
Remember that gunshot?
Someone's got a hot piece.
♪
All right, Archer, hand that
thing over nice and easy now.
I'll show you mine, Zenigata,
if you show me yours.
Huh, what, what
are you talking about,
I'm a cop, for goodness sake.
Oh, yeah right, a dirty cop.
What the hell was I thinkin'?
That's right, that's just
plain crazy talk, Archer,
you need to dry out.
I hope you've all
seen The Mousetrap,
because if not, I'm about
to spoil the ending for you.
It was the
policeman who did it.
Uh, but well‐‐
Let's take a look
at that gun of yours.
Hey!
‐Come on now.
‐No, hey, what are you doing?
Shut up, get over here,
hands up, now.
Yeah, that's a good boy.
You're barking up
the wrong tree, Archer.
Hmm, this is yummy.
Huh?
Let's see if we
can find a scone.
What the hell's
going on over here?
His blood tastes just
like strawberry jam.
(slurping)
It is jam.
What's going on here?
Are you dead or alive?
Wake up right now, you‐‐
(gasping)
(bouncing)
Neat trick‐‐
hey, I got one,
how'd the dummy
cure his hangover?
Like this.
Great, now we're missing the
stone and the old blimp nut.
(laughing)
Huh?
I meant that fondly.
You fell right
into my trap, Mr. Lupin.
What, he's here?
Let me at him,
he's all mine!
Oh, ja, he is right here.
Stop playing games now!
Tell me which one's Lupin!
Oh, I'll do better than that,
I'll show you.
(motor whirring)
‐Hmm?
♪
So, they were all
in it together, huh?
That appears to be the case,
Inspector Zenigata.
That's right.
We're a team.
It's Lupin!
♪
And Goemon!
And Jigen!
Very clever indeed.
And yet, not
quite clever enough.
They're all yours, Inspector.
Grrrr.
Uh, aren't you forgetting
one more important person?
Oh yeah, Fujiko.
I didn't really
want to bring her,
but somehow it always
ends up costing more
when I leave
her out of things.
Impossible, I had my butler
check the whole place.
Oh, Quasimodo?
I'm afraid your
hunchback is Notre Dame.
She disguised herself
as my butler?
What a gal, huh?
Yeah, she and that rock
must be over Iceland by now.
Hmm, or thereabouts.
(laughing)
She did what?
♪
Bye bye, Lupin.
I'll keep it somewhere
safe, I promise.
Just don't start getting any
ideas about a cavity search.
Then what in hell's
embedded in my eye socket?
Hey, you're a smart guy,
what do you think it is?
It's a fake.
When you nodded off
listening to me play,
I figured why wait
till after midnight
when it would only be harder
with the iron mask and all.
It was surprisingly easy.
I mean, do all you guys
sleep like Rip Van Winkle,
or is it just tough being
a rich old blimpophile?
But then why did you
hang around afterwards?
Well, after all,
we were your guests
and you've been so generous
it would have been rude
to leave before
you played out your hand.
We may not be royalty,
but we do have class.
You insolent parasites, grrr!
Whoa, hold on, don't blow
a gasket there, Your Lordship,
I got this one.
You're under arrest, Lupin!
‐You're coming with me!
‐Sorry about that, Pops,
but a good guest always knows
when it's time to leave.
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Huh?
(gunshots)
I don't know what the hell
those shutters are made out of,
but we're not gonna
get through there.
Please tell me
we had a plan B.
‐Attention passengers.
‐Huh?
The Hendenburg will now proceed
via autopilot to Greenland,
where I and several
dozen policemen
will be looking forward
to your safe arrival.
Danke schön.
(propeller whirring)
♪
Enjoy the trip, Mr. Lupin,
it will certainly be your last.
To Greenland
on a self‐piloted blimp.
Can't really say
I saw that one comin'.
Seems like robbing
a sleeping old coot
should have been easier.
♪
(waves crashing)
(reels clunking)
♪
What's the prognosis?
Nah.
I wouldn't want
to override it,
not unless you
want to wind up
like the first Hindenburg.
Damn it all,
what are we gonna do?
‐Just give it up!
‐Huh?
There's no way out
of this this time, Lupin.
We're puttin' you
on ice for good.
And I got your
mittens right here.
That's very kind, but
you might want to save those
for that cold day in hell
when I admit defeat.
(laughing)
Why don't we share them,
you know, one a piece?
(laughing)
♪
To me!
Oh yeah, I can't
toast to myself.
(laughing)
Huh?
‐Him?
‐Huh?
I found this poor bastard
all tied up in a closet.
Fujiko must have
stuffed him in there
right after she
knocked him out.
Of course, thanks, Fuji‐cakes.
Hey, guys,
last favor, I promise.
(groaning)
♪
As the majestic air ship glides
in on its final approach,
one almost feels
a pang of nostalgia
for the golden era
of international lawlessness
which is about to draw
to a dramatic close here.
♪
International
law enforcement agents
scramble into position.
♪
And we're just moments
away from the capture
of these notorious
and glamorous criminals.
♪
And yes, here they are.
I believe I
see them all now.
First off is‐‐Sherlock
Holmes III in handcuffs?
No, no, it must be
Lupin in disguise.
What a delightful scamp,
we'll miss him.
It's a humbling end
to a spectacular career.
The trademark
brashness now gone,
these high flying highwaymen
can't even bear
to show their faces.
And now, the unassuming
blimp enthusiast
who made all this possible.
Lord Gabriel,
your feelings right now?
Please, call it a dirigible,
the word "blimp" is so vulgar.
(crying)
And there you have it.
The pedantic,
pampered aristocrat
misses the point entirely.
(crying)
It's so far gone.
(blubbering)
Stop, hey, wait, wait, stop!
They're getting away!
Get me down from here!
Come on, hurry up!
(yelling)
♪
Good show,
Mr. Lupin, nicely done.
Couldn't have
done it without ya.
Yes, well, frightfully
bad for business, you know,
if it got out that
you had us all tied up
for the entire flight.
Well, I hope you don't
think I'm showing off,
but I have one more
trick up my sleeve.
Voila.
(laughing)
Lupin, get back here,
you hear me!
Lupin!
And... blastoff!
(explosion)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Oh, the humiliation!
See ya, Pops, you
can keep those mittens!
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Oh, dammit, I‐‐
(yelling)
♪ Lupin The Third ♪♪
Oh, man, how did
I get so ugly and mean?
Is that really me?
Something funny's going on
and I don't mean
ha‐ha funny like this.
It's shocking, it's exciting,
it's "Smack Me Up The Head
And Call Me Patsy."
Catch you later.
♪