♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(gunfire)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
It is said that in
the realm of the senses,
Rio is the capital city.
I'll take Chicago any day.
Hmm, I'm sure the stockyards
are a big turn on
for a guy like you, Jigen,
but that's my kind of
steak tartare down there.
The topless kind, oh mama.
Down, boy,
it's a business trip.
Hey, all work and
no play makes me you.
There's the famous statue
of Jesus on Corcovado Hill.
It's friggin' huge.
Yeah, and that's a good thing
'cause we're gonna be testing
His infinite capacity
for forgiveness.
♪
Gentlemen, I give you the
Maracanã Soccer Stadium,
biggest in the world,
holds 250,000.
That's incredible,
and you say the game tomorrow
is all sold out, huh?
Standing room only, my friend.
Big grudge match
with an American team.
I'm telling you,
it's practically
a national holiday here.
I don't get it,
stupid sport if you ask me.
Not nearly enough scoring.
So that's 250,000 times roughly
$40 per person for admission,
which brings the total
to something like
10 million simoleons.
And the soccer lotto typically
triples the box office take.
(laughing)
It's perfect,
nothing but a bunch of
plastered yahoo soccer zombies
standing between us and ten mil.
It lacks a certain
element of sport.
Well at least someone's gonna
run up a big score tomorrow.
Here comes Lupin
with the kick.
Goal!
(typewriter keys clanking)
(motor chugging)
(honking)
(skidding)
(engine roaring)
(crashing)
♪
(siren wailing)
(engine whining)
(tires skidding)
Hey, what the... waaaa‐‐
ow, ooh, ow, ow.
Grrr!
(horns blaring)
Damn traffic's the
same everywhere you go.
Can't you do something?
Come on, get creative,
I'm in a hurry.
Huh, what the?
(crowd rumbling)
Look, it's the Mammoth,
the New York soccer team.
They're here for
the big game tomorrow.
Hey, that's Pierre
signing autographs.
You're on your own, buddy.
Huh?
Hey, you, get
the hell back here!
♪
(whistle blowing)
Hey, where's headquarters?
Hmm?
♪
(sighing)
Zenigata, Interpol.
Welcome, sir,
straight ahead.
♪
Where's Lupin?
Hmmm?
Ah, you don't waste any time.
You must be
Inspector Zenigata.
Yeah, sorry, I...
I am Olivera,
Chief of Police for Rio.
Welcome.
Thanks, uh, yeah,
likewise I'm sure.
Crashed right into
the big Christ statue.
Totally drunk.
Open bottles everywhere.
Wine, whiskey, gin,
Schnapps, rum.
Jeez.
And their injuries?
Couple of weeks,
they'll be just fine.
So, how are
our guests doing?
Fine for now, they're sleeping
sound as little drunken babies,
but waking up's gonna hurt.
Have you verified
the I. D.‐‐what the?
Of course, with the information
you sent us from Interpol.
♪
(laughing)
Oh boy, it's
Christmas in July!
Everything I asked Santa for.
(laughing)
You look pathetic!
Hey.
Oh, Pops, is it a dream?
Huh, this is too
rich for words.
I mean getting Capone
on tax evasion is one thing,
but nabbing the great Lupin
on a drunk driving charge.
(laughing)
Love to spar, but the truth is
I'm still feeling kind of‐‐
(belch)
♪
Yeah, well laugh
it up now, wise guy,
'cause where you're going
the only one smiling
are the worms, trust me.
Oh no, guys, he's threatening us
with 20 years up his butt.
Nuts to you,
you're finished!
(door slamming)
(laughing)
♪
Brazilian women are ótimo.
(mumbling)
What's wrong, Inspector?
We're surrounded by delicacies
to tempt every appetite,
and yet you look dyspeptic.
I don't know
what dyspeptic means,
but something about
them isn't right.
They're real.
Oh, you're talking about Lupin.
I can't put my finger on it,
but I'm telling you something
here definitely stinks.
I've got a nose for this.
Hmmm, smells
all right to me.
He's just too smart
to get caught that easy.
What are you saying,
that our guests may opt
for an early checkout?
I don't know.
(laughing)
You're a worrier, Inspector.
It's actually
quite charming.
But I assure you, ours is the
most secure, escape‐proof prison
in all of Brazil.
First of all,
the medical ward is wired
for four‐point round
the clock surveillance.
And then, if by some miracle
they did manage to escape
the ward undetected,
we have a few tricks of our
own to give them the shaft.
Going down.
Huh‐‐arrgghh!
♪
And any attempt
to help from the outside
will be met by a
row of machine guns
mounted at every
entrance and exit.
Now if you're still uneasy,
perhaps you need a doctor.
(laughing)
All right.
Now, you are in Rio
and you are my guest.
Let us eat, drink,
and tomorrow,
I will show you around
my beautiful city.
Well, all right.
♪
(metal tapping)
For once, I can honestly say
it was good to see old Pops.
More to the point,
he saw us.
So now, we have an alibi.
When's Fujiko arriving?
3:00 tomorrow.
Hey, knock it off in there.
That tapping's
driving me crazy!
Oh, sorry there, pal,
but you're not officially
crazy until you go
blahhhhh blahhh blahhhh!
♪
Welcome to the famous
Copacabana Beach, Inspector.
Isn't it beautiful?
Endless beaches!
Endless blue sky!
And endless
naked female flesh.
Now don't tell me you didn't
notice that, Mr. All Business.
It's paradise, my friend,
plain and simple.
My job is to keep
the snakes out of Eden,
if you know what I mean.
Damn it, I wish I knew
what that Lupin was up to.
♪
Aagghh!
You jerk!
(slap)
♪
(knocking)
(tires squealing)
♪
Hi there,
hospital linen service.
I've got some sanitized sheets
and gowns for the prisoners.
Hold on, what happened
to the regular nurse?
She had a bad
case of the flu
so they had to send her
home for the day.
I'm her replacement.
Mmm, okay, come on in.
♪
Good, right on cue.
This is it, guys,
magic time in cell block A.
(whistle blowing)
(crowd roaring)
(yelling)
All right, you can go in.
(dinging)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
In their green road uniforms
is the New York Mammoth
led by superstar Pierre
in number ten.
In white are
our hometown heroes,
the champion Brazil Juntos.
About five minutes into the‐‐
Hospital linen service.
Sure, it's the door
at the end of this hall.
Here.
I'm here to
change the linens.
(sigh)
Huh?
(laughing)
Mamma mia!
(screaming)
‐Hey!
‐The slime ball!
Beautiful crossing pass
to Pierre on the right flank.
Lupin, behave yourself.
Got to be believable.
So, where is it?
Under the sheet on the cart.
Great.
Get off of me!
(slap)
She sure can
take care of herself.
Hope it hurts, try it again
and I'll do some real damage.
Now hurry up and change.
Okay, okay, keep your
shirt on‐‐or not.
Hey you, what the heck
do you think you're doing?
Oh, hi there.
The nurse is delivering
some fresh clothes for us.
Hmm?
I can see that, wise guy.
I'm sorry, but if you
want to see me naked,
you're gonna have to hand over
chocolate and cigarettes
like everyone else around here.
Looks like we're ready
to go back to action!
Juntos have possession!
Okay, Fujiko, now.
♪
Brilliant defensive play
from both teams' back line.
♪
(projector whirring)
All right,
I'm all done in here.
Okay, move on.
♪
Ah, all tucked in
in their nice clean jammies.
♪
See you later.
Take it easy.
♪
(unintelligible announcing)
To Pierre!
Goal!
(crowd roaring)
Don't turn around.
Hmm?
Told you so.
Ow, ugh.
Pierre working the ball down
the field with blazing speed.
And the kick.
Goal!
(siren blaring)
(throat clearing)
Hey!
Ugh.
Hmmm‐‐arrghh!
(tires screeching)
(siren blaring)
(groaning)
The Mammoth juggernaut
keeps rolling.
Tight pass, a long kick.
A brilliant save!
Ah, ah!
Damn it all, I know
he's up to something.
What the hell is it?
(phone ringing)
What?
The whole
box office cleaned out
and the lotto!
What do we know
about these robbers?
Who are these guys?
The guys who did it,
you nincompoop!
You better get a clue,
you hear me!
Ooh, ooh, Chief, Chief,
ask me, I know!
It's Lupin, it's Lupin!
With all due respect,
you're insane!
Lupin is in jail!
That interception
was a thing of beauty.
(buzzing)
Hello.
Yeah, Degama here.
Yes, Chief.
I'll see.
Yeah, Lupin is here,
he's bouncing around
on his bed like
a monkey right now.
(projector whirring)
Now, you see, exactly
as I told you, Inspector.
No, can't be,
something's wrong.
The guy's evil, I tell you.
♪
Come on, Fujiko,
gun it, will you?
Lupin, I'm really
not in the mood
to pay a $40 million
speeding ticket.
♪
‐Come on, come on!
‐Here.
♪
Grrrr, ha!
I knew it, I should have
listened to my own instincts!
Damn it, I can't believe I was
fooled by this, he's a crook!
(crashing)
Hey, you up there, wake up!
You got a break‐out down here!
Yes, sir.
(siren wailing)
Lupin, I think
they're on to us.
(sirens wailing)
That's why God
invented backup plans.
Turn it around.
I want road blocks
set up everywhere!
Nothing in this freaking city
moves without
my approval, got it?
The whole department's
reputation is on the line here!
Judging from the film,
I'd say they were
gone about 40 minutes.
They hit the box office,
loaded the cash
in a stolen truck,
then planned to hide
the truck somewhere
and return here
for a perfect alibi.
But something screwed up
and they didn't
make it back in time
which means Lupin
and his scumbags
are probably somewhere between
the stadium and the prison.
(knocking)
Come in!
Excuse me, Chief,
but we need you to authorize
a flight permit to transfer
the Corcovado Christ
to the factory for repair.
The transportation
crew is ready
and awaiting
clearance for takeoff.
Oh yes, that's right.
It must have slipped my mind
with this other mess.
Very good, I'll
issue it right away.
Hold it, Chief, what's all
this about a flight permit?
For the repair
of the Christ statue
Lupin crashed into
on his drunken joyride.
Are you talking
about that huge monument
on top of the hill?
Mm‐hmm.
This statue right here.
It is the pride of our city.
Ah‐ha!
‐Hmm?
‐That's it!
It's almost exactly halfway
between the stadium
and the prison, see?
The distance is about perfect.
Chief, how big is
this statue, anyway?
About 120 feet.
Is it solid or hollow inside?
There's a small chapel inside
that holds about 150 people,
but it's been closed
ever since the accident.
Damn it, Lupin, I'm gonna
kick your weaselly butt!
Listen, Chief, that truck's
been inside the statue all along
and that transportation crew
is actually Lupin and his gang!
Wha?
♪
Hey, yo, we're
burning daylight here,
what's the freaking hold‐up?
Still waiting for clearance.
Should be any time now.
Lupin, straight ahead.
(sirens wailing)
♪
Lupin, you're busted!
Get down off that statue now!
Well, can't say I'm shocked.
He's as reliable
as the seasons.
More like
a recurring butt rash.
Jigen, hurry up.
(blades whirring)
Uh oh, trouble.
(helicopter whirring)
Hurry, move, move, move!
Fire, fire, damn it!
(gunshots)
(rock breaking)
No, get back here, you!
Oh, man, I think we've finally
driven him over the edge.
Aarhh!
Ah, reinforcements.
Come on now, bring him down.
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(gunshots)
♪
Lupin, give it up,
it's no use.
We're gonna blow you
out of the sky.
♪
Lupin, you wouldn't have
a backup backup plan?
Oh sure, just turn around
while I pull it out
of the usual place.
♪
Aaarrgghh!
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
♪
It's a miracle.
It's ironic, isn't it.
You might say
heavy handed even.
Zenigata's gotta be having
puppies down there.
Mwa, au revoir.
(blades whirring)
Damn, that Lupin.
♪
Ah!
(cheering)
Lupin, you can't hide forever!
I'm gonna have
the last laugh!
Well at least
it's all going back
to the good people of Rio, huh?
And that Pierre's going
to get struck by lightning.
Huh?
Just kidding.
(laughing)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Ah, Fujiko,
she can turn any man
into a slobbering beast,
so just imagine
the effect she'd have
on an actual slobbering beast.
On second thought, why risk
pulling a brain muscle
when you can just
catch the next episode
of Lupin The Third,
Fifty Ways To Leave
Your Fifty Foot Lover.
Tootles.
♪