♪
♪ Lup ♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(glass breaks)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
Let me guess,
it's something in there,
is that right?
You kidding me?
Now, what could I possibly
want in the White House?
Then what's the big mystery?
You didn't bring me
all the way out here
just for sightseeing, did you?
Not that I'm complaining.
A date's a date,
but ours don't usually
end up so well.
I mean, at least for me,
if you catch my drift.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Forget it, I didn't
mean a thing.
Huh?
Uh...
♪
Uh, what is that?
You have heard
of the Black House?
No, actually, I haven't.
Well, it was built
for Don Kecchi.
Remind you of anything?
♪
Well, cheers!
Hmm, cheers.
(slurps)
So, what's all this
about the amazing
Mr. Don Kecchi?
Haven't you read
the newspapers lately?
Huh?
Look.
Hmm.
"Mr. Don Kecchi,
richest man in America,
makes surprise announcement.
Will give away his
entire fortune to charity
the billionaire said Saturday,
a total of..."
One billion dollars.
The guy's insane.
So, Lupin,
what do you say, huh?
Feel like teaming up?
Hmm.
That's some sort of
trick question, isn't it?
Then you'll partner
with me on this?
Well, I don't do rough stuff,
and I flat out refuse
to rip off a good guy,
that's my policy, Fujicakes.
But if you had to choose
between me and your policy...
Well, the policy, see...
That's it, Lupin.
That's the very last straw.
♪
Hey, Fujiko, come on, wait!
Fujiko, come back!
Come on!
Fujiko, wait!
Come on, can't we
talk about this?
Hold on.
(gasping)
What the...
I can't...
(shrieks)
I'll save you!
♪
Whoa!
She's gone.
Disappeared right
before my eyes.
(typewriter keys click)
♪
Take it easy, would you?
I'm simply trying to
get this unpleasantness
over for both of us.
I'm just not buying
it yet, Lupin.
So, I'm lying, is that it?
I didn't exactly
say that now, did I?
I'm saying why kidnap
someone who's more
trouble than she's worth?
Hmm?
Hey, what is it?
‐(hissing)
‐Huh, what the‐‐
It's that same stuff,
the stuff that
kidnapped my Fujiko.
Huh?
It's just normal fog, man.
I wish that were true.
Careful, it's a demon.
You'll hear me out if
you value the life
of your lady friend.
Goemon, move!
Hold it.
He must want something.
Let's listen to him, okay?
The price of your
friend's ransom
is Don Kecchi's fortune.
So, you read
the paper, too?
The Black House.
You have two days, no more.
After that, don't bother.
Your friend will be dead.
Two days.
♪
What the hell are we
getting ourselves into?
Well, I sure hope you
guys believe me now.
Maybe, but what the hell
does a demon want with money?
I'm guessing it's the
person who controls him
who wants the money.
♪
Well, shoulda seen
it coming, I guess.
I mean, the guy
is a thief after all,
but even this
seems beneath him.
Well, Inspector Zenigata,
what do you think?
That sort of thing
is his calling card.
You're right, he often
does this kind of thing.
No doubt about it.
Something bothering
you, Inspector?
What doesn't fit
the profile is...
he never steals
from good people.
So, are you telling me
I'm a bad guy because
Lupin's targeted me?
I didn't mean that!
Certainly not.
You're a famous
philanthropist, Mr. Kecchi.
Hmm.
People like to call me
a scrooge or a miser,
but they're ignorant.
You have to save money
before you can do
any good with it, Inspector.
They're just idiots!
And don't you worry,
I won't let Lupin
steal even a penny
from you, sir.
(rumbling)
That bastard, dammit!
I'm gonna throw
the book at that guy!
Doesn't he have any
conscience at all?
(grunting)
♪
(chuckles)
(groans)
Lupin, you bastard!
♪
Huh?
(bang)
♪
Wait!
Go ahead and
shoot me, Lupin.
Break your whole
code of honor
in one fell swoop.
♪
Ciao.
You can keep everything
that falls on the ground.
Fujiko, you can't
betray us like this!
What's betrayal
got to do with it?
The only thing I'm
loyal to is money.
Land it now or I'll shoot.
I swear!
Sorry, I know you
too well, Lupin.
There's no way in
the world you could
ever shoot me.
(gunshot)
(Fujiko gasps)
(gasps)
(helicopter blades beating)
♪
(sighs)
You're right, the old
Lupin couldn't have
shot you like that.
What did I do?
She's dead, you killed her!
I saw it!
You monster!
What do you gotta
say for yourself now?
Fujiko!
You're having a real
good day, Lupin.
You've just gone
straight over the edge.
Fujiko, I'm sorry.
♪
Hey, just where
the hell do you
think you're going?
Get back here!
(shoots)
Hmm?
What?
What the‐‐
I don't get it,
I mean, what the...
Hell is going on?
I really couldn't say.
All I can say
is that I'm pretty
damn certain this whole
thing is some sort of trap.
A trap, really?
Yeah, not only that,
it's an incredibly
ingenious trap as well.
Huh?
They disappeared.
Freeze, right there!
You're a murderer, Lupin,
and you damn well know it!
Hey, Pops, let me explain.
It wasn't me that did it.
(gunshot)
Listen, I know you're only
trying to do the right thing,
but just hear me out!
(gunshot)
Sorry, Lupin, you're
not gonna talk your way
out of this!
Lupin, he's not in
the mood to listen to you.
And I'm not
counting to three!
(gunshots)
♪
Huh?
(grunting)
So, anything interesting
in today's newspaper?
Oh, just that the FBI is
after us for killing Fujiko
and ripping off Don Kecchi.
And the real guys got away.
Somebody is pulling
off the perfect crime.
The question is...
who have we pissed off lately?
Or who stands
to gain here
from the money being stolen?
‐Huh?
Betcha everything
clears right up
as soon as we
find old Fujiko.
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
How long were you planning
on making your bride wait?
♪
They say money can't
buy you happiness,
but it's your money that
bought you my companionship
until death do us part.
Once this illness takes me,
you'll be very happy
and very rich.
All because I came up
with a way to cheat
those charities
out of the money
you promised them.
And this is how.
With a 3D projector,
I created the illusion
that Lupin broke in
and stole it all.
You can't be expected to donate
what you don't have, hmm?
You're as good
at stealing money
as I was at earning it.
Thank you.
But you better not
underestimate Lupin.
You can't leave
any incriminating
loose ends lying around.
Loose ends?
You mean like a
witness, for instance?
Is that what you're saying?
Witness?
(grunts)
♪
(gasps)
Aren't you terminal?
Strange, somehow
the doctors got hold
of some other
guy's tissue sample.
(chuckles)
You lied to me.
Yes, I'm afraid
I'm a terrible liar.
The secret to my success.
Now, think about it,
why would someone
like me ever need
to marry anyone?
(laughs)
(ticking)
(board rattles, splash)
Dammit, Lupin.
I never should've
betrayed you.
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
(explosion)
Given the choice,
I've always put
my trust in money
rather than people.
Money won't let you down.
A 3D idiot protector?
Video projector.
You're the idiot!
Watch it, lady,
you're treading
on pretty thin ice
with me as it is.
It makes holograms.
It was all totally fabricated.
Nothing more than just
a manufactured illusion.
That's all it was.
Oh, Mr. Charity, right.
But Lupin, you're even
madder that he tried
to kill me, aren't you?
I was so scared.
Aw.
It's definitely
war now, Fujicakes.
This Kecchi guy is toast.
You're so wonderful.
♪
He has no idea just what
he's gotten himself into,
but he's gonna find out
soon enough, I tell you!
♪
Huh?
(chuckles)
Look, I found
a penny on the floor.
A whole penny,
and it's all mine!
And I'm never gonna
let you go away.
(laughs)
♪
(mechanical whirring)
(grunts)
♪
(chuckles)
Ah!
What a fool I was
to give all this
away to charity
just because I thought
I was going to die.
(chuckles)
This is mine!
My money!
(laughs)
I'll never give you up.
Whoa, guy's got issues.
He's also got
a lot of money,
so now that he's
shown his true colors,
you in?
Oh, yeah, count me in.
But stealing his
dough isn't punishment
enough after all he's done.
Just what do you
have in mind?
A little tit for tat.
Anyone who sets me up
gets the same in return.
(chuckles)
(windows creak)
♪
(mechanical whirring)
Hah!
(taunting, giggling)
Got it!
Did that look okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Got this thing
secondhand, so who knows.
Let's see.
I sure hope it works.
Hey, this is really
amazing, isn't it?
Wow.
Oh, yeah, Kecchi's gonna
have a freakin' heart attack.
Don't worry, I'll take
care of running the machines.
Sorry, but all of you
are under arrest.
Take it easy, just
testing it out, Fujicakes.
Don't do that, okay?
♪
(high‐pitched ringing)
(mechanical humming)
Hmm?
Someone's in the bedroom.
(groans)
(gasps)
♪
My money, that's mine, no!
(chuckles)
Somebody help, hey!
I'm being robbed!
♪
Inspector, it's Lupin,
he's right in there!
Oh, yeah?
A‐ha!
Hold it right there!
Don't move!
(gunshot)
♪
What the...
Oh, no, it broke!
What the hell are
you doing, Fujiko?
(gasps)
(gunshots)
This is dangerous,
better stand back!
‐This way, quick!
‐Move it!
How long can I keep
up this charade?
Dammit, if I could only...
Maybe I'll just...
Huh?
Now we're really
up the creek.
Lupin, what's happened?
Now, get this guy out of here!
Jigen, get us out
of this, will you?
Hey, don't look at me, pal.
It was your freakin'
girlfriend, Fujiko,
who got us into this
whole damn mess.
Kecchi's back.
Don't even think
about it, Lupin,
just hold it right there!
Oh, thank you.
He almost made off
with all my money.
Wait, what did you just say?
Ugh...
Uh, come on already!
Yeah, what do you mean
he "almost" made off
with your money?
Well, he broke in
here again, that is.
But I'm all cleaned out.
Ahh!
♪
I don't understand.
Are you absolutely
sure about that?
You sure you weren't
trying to hide this money
so you wouldn't have
to give it to charity?
No, all of my money
was stolen from me.
Are you saying Lupin
returned this money to you
after he stole it from you?
No, that doesn't
make any sense.
Actually, that's typical.
Loves to play head games.
It's best you get all
of that money donated
as soon as possible.
Now that I know
he's been arrested,
I'll do it very soon.
Today's best while
we have him in custody.
You know, you're
a lucky man this
worked out so well.
You were always lucky
with money, weren't you?
I used to think
so myself, but that...
that damn Lupin
broke my lucky streak!
(cries)
That's all over, Mr. Kecchi,
water under the bridge.
Now, where the hell is
that damn reset button?
(screams)
‐Hey, wait!
‐Get him!
Sounds like old Kecchi's
blowing a gasket.
Greed is certainly
a terrible thing.
I'll have some of
my men come gather up
this money, Mr. Kecchi.
Don't worry.
(whimpers)
So long!
Huh?
Hmm?
(groans)
Hey, who the hell are you?
I'm Inspector Zenigata!
And just who
the hell are you?
(screaming)
Huh?
♪
Hey, hold it right there, you!
Wait a minute, Inspector.
He's actually returning
all the money that he stole.
(mechanical humming)
Somebody wanna tell me what
the hell is going on here?
Is she trying to screw
this thing up or what?
Go ahead, fry me again.
I don't care, I just
want the damn money!
Now I'm gonna give
you one more chance.
Tell me who you are!
‐Well?!
‐Hey, I told you,
I'm Inspector Zenigata.
Useless piece of...
(grunts)
I did it!
I fixed it.
It's working!
(taunts)
(groans)
Why, you wait!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(screaming)
(explosion)
Hey, you!
Get back here!
(panting)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(grunts)
Ah, phew.
(laughing)
I got you back.
My money!
Good evening.
We're here to pick up all
the money that you're donating.
You're taking my money?
(cries)
That's it, a billion smackers.
This Kecchi's gotta be a
freakin' saint or something.
He's sure got his
priorities straight.
Oh!
♪
Good, you triple checked
everything upstairs, didn't you?
Yes, sir!
Come on, then,
let's get out of here.
(moans)
Lupin, hi.
You're Fujiko!
Hey, don't play that game.
The charade is over now,
and I want my share.
It's all there,
a billion, right?
Yeah, that's right, a billion.
All of it on
its way to charity.
Oh, no!
You're him!
That's right,
and the moral is
that justice always wins.
(screams)
(chuckles)
Check that out.
Oh, yeah, I just
can't get enough of this.
Ah, karma.
Still, it seems a bit harsh.
Yeah, well, too bad.
Come on, let's go.
Come back!
Damn it!
Is that you, Lupin?
I'll kill you!
Get back here!
I want my share!
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
It's the Christmas episode.
I know it doesn't look it,
but trust me,
this is no fish story.
So grab your friends,
and start dreaming
of sugar plums.
Big, juicy ones!
No, not that kind.
This time I've got
something pure,
something more
eternal in mind.
Diamonds!
Next one's called
"Christmas at Tiffany's."
Catch you later!
♪