♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(gunshots)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(partying)
♪
With a personal fortune
topping five billion dollars
and nearly as many ex‐wives,
self‐made investment guru
and indefatigable playboy,
Howard Heath, claims to
at long last found true love.
According to informed sources,
a wedding is imminent.
The beautiful and
extremely lucky bride‐to‐be
is something
of a mystery woman.
She's been ensconced at the
Hotel Jamaica under an alias.
But sources identify her
as one Fujiko Mine.
The impending ceremony
will reportedly be
a simple private one
in keeping
with the elderly Heath's
penchant for ravaging
his young brides
within seconds
of tying the knot.
Ah, this is perfect.
I mean, Lupin's
crazy about that girl.
I guarantee you
he's gonna flip out
when he hears about this.
Mm‐hmm.
I see, and you're pretty
confident he'll waste no time
making his way
here to Jamaica.
Oh, yeah, he's not gonna
give her up without a fight.
You can take that
to the bank, buddy.
And we're gonna
be ready for him.
I want this
city cordoned off.
Cordoned off!
(choking)
(wheels screeching)
Title!
(typewriter keys clicking)
♪
Helping us to
ensure that you enjoy
a safe and carefree
stay here in Jamaica.
The Security Set 3,000
represents the very latest
in security technology.
Those not wearing
identity concealers‐‐
Ah, ahhh!
Hey, hold on, one side!
Sir!
What's the matter
with you morons?
You let a guy through
wearing a damn Reagan mask
for God sakes!
What are you all,
twelve years old?
Who's Damn Reagan, sir?
Imbecile!
Look, just step aside
and get back to place,
suckyface, will ya!
Let's go!
(running)
Hey guys, how come the chief
was getting off
that plane from France?
Hmm, huh, follow those guys!
♪
All clear.
Great idea, huh.
Worked like a charm.
Ha.
(laughing)
Huh?
Ah!
Dammit!
Hey, you could've
had the trench coat, but no.
Thank you.
Huh?
Kindly identify yourself.
You need more than kindness,
sir, if you don't know who I am.
We'll just verify it
if you don't mind.
I'm Howard Heath,
you ignoramus!
Yeah, how's that
workin' out for ya?
If you dare come near me with
that ridiculous contraption
I'll sue you for
public humiliation
and for defamation
of character!
And I never, ever sue for
less than ten million dollars.
You said ten million?
Hold on.
Let's see here,
Fifteen bucks a month times‐‐
(throat clearing)
Uh, uh, I'd have
to be Barnaby Jones.
Grrr.
Huh, hey!
My darling, it pains me
to have to say this,
but I'm breaking
off our engagement.
Ah, excuse me?
You're kidding, right, I mean
is this some kind of a quiz?
Unfortunately, darling,
a man in my position
has to be exceedingly careful
and so I commissioned
a background check
which indicates you're
already deeply involved
with a man named Lupin.
Deeply involved?
He's deeply delusional
if he says that we're lovers.
Perhaps I've been the
delusional one, darling.
I mean, you're a
beautiful young woman.
How could you be expected
to resist such an exciting,
handsome young man, hmm?
Oh, he is nothing
but a vain little boy.
Mmm, you're a man.
Oh, surely you
protest too much, my dear.
I hear this fellow is charming,
witty, brave, brilliant,
a paragon, in fact all
the manly virtues and I‐‐
‐(laughing)
‐What's so funny?
Hey, I was just getting
warmed up there.
I'm sure, but if you
spent half as much time
on prep as you
do on self‐promotion
you'd know that Heath's been
laid up for three days now
with some weird fever.
He couldn't make his way
over here on a gurney.
Oh, well, but that
just goes to show
what a bad idea
this is, Fujicakes.
I mean, come on,
the guy's so old
he probably made his
fortune in buggy whips.
Let's just say
we forget the whole‐‐
Sorry, but the prospect
of a few clammy gropes
won't put me off this one.
Oh, this isn't
just about money, is it?
What are you after here?
It's a ruby the
size of a baseball.
It's incredible.
He got it a little while ago
from this strange guy
who just showed up here right
out of the blue one day.
(laughing)
Enjoy it.
I should mention that
folk legend cautions
against admiring it by
the light of a full moon.
Something about a fatal curse.
All superstitious
nonsense, of course.
(laughing)
♪
So just save
the sermon, okay?
I'd marry Heath's grandpa
to get my hands on that thing
and nothing's gonna stop me,
not even you.
Damn, I love it when
she talks like that.
(bird squawking)
Always kind of hoped
she'd come around one day
and see the light.
I don't know, guess the guy's
got to be some kind of
billionaire or
bad boy these days.
Huh?
♪
So lovely, smooth, bewitching.
Come to me.
♪
Sorry, old man, really hate to
drop in unannounced like this,
but that's kind
of the whole idea,
know what I mean?
Argh, huh?
What the hell?
Aaagh!
(yelling)
What the?
(rumbling)
Huh?
Help, someone help me!
Help me, arrghh!
Heath, you all right?
Hey.
Oh, my God, what happened?
Arggh, arggh!
A‐ha, looks like you
aced the competition.
Or should I say iced?
Slow down, Inspector.
You know I'm not a killer.
I walked in on Heath
two seconds before you did.
He was like this
when I got here.
Let go of me!
See ya!
Hey, he's getting away!
♪
Aagh!
(yelling)
♪
Oh, my darling,
I'm so happy.
You're so beautiful
and smooth and beautiful
and you smell like paradise
and I'm never
gonna let you go away.
Oh, God, this
is torture, come on.
This is pathetic even
by your standards.
I mean, spying
on sleeping widows
through heating fence, Lupin.
First of all,
just inheriting something
doesn't make you a widow.
And by the way, I'm giving
you the benefit of the doubt
by assuming your fiancé really
did bequeath you that thing.
And secondly,
there's a difference
between spying on someone
and watching over them,
the latter of the two
being characteristics
of saints and
white knights and such.
What's happening
to me, Lupin?
I'm not sure, but
the moon's full again
and unless you're really dying
to see that expired ex of yours,
I'd lose that rock of his.
A dark intent resides
within its luminous form.
You must forsake its
materiality or be consumed
by its quintessence.
You want to run that
one by me again, Goemon?
No, not really.
Hya!
♪
Look, your sword!
(whimpering)
Uh‐oh.
(wind blowing)
Huh?
What's that sound?
That twister again.
It's‐‐
Aagh!
(screaming)
They're freakin' birds!
Goemon, what the
hell's going on?
Jamaican hummingbirds.
A swarm of them.
Lupin, help!
(screaming)
Fujiko, I'm right here,
I'm right here!
Get 'em off me!
(scream)
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
♪
(towel wringing)
Hmm?
(sniffing)
What the hell are you
doing over here, Goeman?
When a fever like
that proves impervious
to every stratagem
of western medicine,
it's time for a little jiruto.
What the hell is jiruto?
It's a broth of
pregnant earthworms.
Bleach!
Man, you've got
to be kidding me.
Watch and learn.
Hmm?
No way, hey, Goemon!
Stop, what the hell
are you trying to do?
Hasn't the poor thing
suffered enough?
Lupin, spare me your ignorance.
More to the point,
spare her.
If I don't get her
to drink this right away,
she'll be food for worms.
No!
(struggling)
(gun shot)
Hmm.
Grrr.
Hey, Jigen, nice of
you to show up, man.
I mean, come on in,
pull up a chair, have a smoke.
Don't mind Fujiko, she's
just dying over there.
But hey, don't let
that harsh your buzz.
You don't even care.
That's it, isn't it?
You've been sucking on the
world's fattest doobie somewhere
while we've been‐‐
(laughing)
Huh?
♪
Let me see this thing.
(sniffing)
Mmm, oh yeah.
Well, that
settles it, Goemon,
he's high.
Hey, man, I know you're
worried about Fujiko,
but jeez, give me
some credit, will ya?
I had to hop a puddle
jumper over to Haiti
for a couple of days to check
out a hunch I had about this.
They got this
weird cult over there,
some black magic thing.
Anyway, they use
this native plant,
Purple Andromeda,
in all their rituals.
It's an hallucinogen,
like acid or Psilocybin.
Really powerful.
Just a whiff will do you.
The problem is
it's really unstable.
And if you don't
cook it just right,
it'll really mess you up.
Sometimes animals get into it,
it makes 'em crazy,
stampeding and stuff.
Anyway, I heard
a rumor over there.
Somebody stole they eye
of one of their sacred idols.
(sniffing)
It was a giant ruby,
and this one happens to reek
of Purple Andromeda.
You think someone
was feeding that stuff
to those hummingbirds
that attacked us?
Mm‐hmm.
According to local legend,
there's some kind
of curse on this thing.
Anyone who steals it or even
has it in his possession
is supposed to die some
sort of horrifying death,
courtesy of the idol.
That's all I need to hear.
What are you doing?
Just what I do best,
stealing something.
I don't think
that's your color.
♪
"Take this ruby as
a symbol of my love."
Now that the curse
is on me instead of her,
all I have to do
is get to Haiti,
find the cult's temple,
and return the ruby to the idol
before I die a horrible death.
It's a noble plan and there's
elegance in its simplicity,
but I think I detect a flaw
and it's a fatal one.
Lupin.
Oh, man, no fair,
who knew they could show up
in the middle of the day!
(rattling)
(screaming)
(waves crashing)
♪
I'm guessing they
don't like visitors.
Then again, if you're
an evil twisted drug cult,
that probably makes sense.
Man, I'd really hate to
be their Sparkletts guy.
Wake me up when you two are done
postponing the inevitable.
♪
(birds squawking)
Whoa, watch it birds!
(yelling)
♪
Hey, that looked like them.
Nah, it can't be.
My brain's just rattled
from this damn donkey ride.
I mean lots of
people go hang gliding
into remote drug cult temples
all the time and then‐‐
Doh, it is him!
‐(yelling)
‐(braying)
I don't suppose there was
anything in that local legend
about a secret ski lift to the
top of this thing, was there?
There's got to be something
we haven't thought of.
I mean it's not impossible.
Whoever pinched that ruby
figured it out.
Sure that's great,
rub it in.
Not only is it
a personal failure,
it's also a professional
humiliation.
Never lose hope, my friend.
♪
Yeah, that's a
nice sentiment, old man,
but talk is cheap.
What do you got?
Perhaps nothing more
than an old folk tale,
but it is said that
many many years ago
pirates laid waste to
what was then a monastery
at the top of that cliff
by digging a secret passageway
from somewhere here
at the foot of the mountain.
Hold it, where's the entrance
to this passageway?
They say that
many years later
a young boy was poking at a
rock somewhere right around here
when quite by accident it‐‐
(rumbling)
♪
Holy open sesame.
Now that's more like it.
Thanks, we'll take it
from here, old fella.
Just one last piece
of advice, my friend.
What's that?
They say there
are none more cunning
at protecting their property
than those who themselves
acquired by theft.
Be careful, my friend,
and may heaven protect you.
Thanks.
What do you say,
shall we, boys?
After you.
(rock sliding)
A‐ha, hold it
right there you‐‐
Oopf.
Ow.
(footsteps)
Huh, hey guys, look out!
Watch out!
Hya ha!
Nice work, Goemon.
♪
(yelling)
Lupin!
You all right?
♪
Well, I'm doing better
than old Indiana Bones here.
♪
Huh?
(struggling)
There.
Whoa!
Ugh, agh!
(sighing)
Doh!
(together)
Eeeee.
♪
(rock sliding)
Hmm.
Hey, lookie here.
♪
Hmm, looks like
we found our guy.
♪
A little birdie
told me you were ticked off
about this whole eye thing.
Actually, it was
more like a billion
homicidal drug‐crazed birds,
but anyway, I'm here
to return it to you
and I'm willing to forget
the whole thing if you are.
Here you go,
handsome, go nuts!
Hey that was
just an expression!
(together)
Agh!
Insolent infidels.
You defile my sacred shrine
with your very presence.
Hey, I know that voice.
You're not fooling me.
I saw the Wizard of Oz
a hundred times.
Oh, all right,
very well then.
Just trying to have a
little fun for heaven sakes.
♪
Him again!
That's right, Jigen,
our model is sporting
a fanciable fashion statement
from the Jean Pierre
Ponzo collection.
It says, I'm a
little bit witch doctor,
and a little bit
Carmen Miranda.
Hey, you shut up.
Ooh, touchy huh?
What do you want with us?
My business here
is only with you.
You want to clue me in?
With pleasure.
Many years ago my
father was appointed
head of the sentinels here.
But a short time later,
your grandfather, just like you,
violated the sanctity
of this place
in pursuit of
that same gemstone.
As he should have expected
if he weren't so arrogant,
he proved no match
for the powerful magic
that resides here.
He escaped with his life,
but empty handed.
My father was blamed
for the breach and beheaded.
Ever since that day, I have
dreamed of nothing else
but visiting revenge
upon the Lupin family,
applying myself to my
studies in the dark arts
and biding my time until
fate could be my ally.
And then the stars aligned.
Once that awful
Heath became besotted
with your friend Fujiko,
the ruby did the
rest of the work.
(laughing)
Now behold my sentinels.
Arise!
(growling)
♪
Huh?
Hmm?
♪
Bleech.
What in the hell
are those things?
These are the most loyal
rotaries of this sacred order
whose devotion
extends beyond the grave.
(groaning)
Zombies!
Kill them.
(gun fire)
Hwa, hwa!
♪
They just keep coming.
Feel free to chime
in at any time, huh?
Hell, I don't know, Lupin,
why don't you take out
the big ugly Cyclops.
Let's see what happens.
Well, I don't
have any better ideas,
so what the heck.
How dare you deface
our sacred idol,
you filthy heathen.
Hey, he can't protect you
from that stuff, old man,
that's plastic explosive,
get away!
(struggling)
(exploding)
Run!
♪
(crashing)
(crackling)
(panting)
♪
Hey, I know it was my idea,
but what do you want?
I was surrounded by friggin
zombies, for God sakes.
Anyway, you don't
want that thing.
It's nothing but bad luck.
Yeah, but still.
I must say I admire your
(speaking French), Lupin.
I mean, you blew up the
temple of an evil deity
and yet, just look at you.
Ah, what's he gonna do to me?
It can't be worse
than watching Fujiko
throw herself at old man Heath
or diddle that dumb rock.
Oh, you can't
really blame me, can you?
I mean if diamonds
are a girl's best friend
well then, something that rare's
got to be more like a lover.
Oh, sweetheart‐‐
‐Huh?
‐Is that...
Hey, it's Pops.
My darling, you're so
smooth and silky and stuff.
Even smoother than Mommy,
and don't tell her,
but I think you even
smell a little better.
It'll be our little secret.
My ruby, hey!
Cool it, Fujiko,
are you crazy?
Listen, do you hear that?
Huh?
Eee.
(yelling)
Eeee.
Coming through!
Look out!
(yelling)
Eee.
Hey, there you are!
Fujiko, come on!
(yelling)
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
There's this old rich guy
and he's got jewels
implanted in his head
and he rides around in a blimp.
And he invites all
these famous detectives
to ride around with him
in his blimp
so they can watch
him capture me.
But then things get weird.
Well, okay, more weird.
It's the Obligatory
Blimp episode.
Did I mention
it's really weird?
Catch you later.
♪