♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(gunshot)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(excited chatter)
♪
Oh, my God!
I just love your ring.
(laughs)
Thank you, that's
very kind of you,
but, in fact, the truth
of the matter is
it's a custom made
safe by Marukin.
A Marukin, huh?
Well, I'll drink to that.
(gulps)
The stone is kept
inside for safety.
Oh, wow!
Isn't that absolutely fabulous?
(gasping)
♪
‐Good night.
Goodbye now.
Thank you so much
for having us.
Oh, what a pleasure.
Yes, good night.
‐Good night.
‐Ciao.
Drive safe.
Well, it's a lot of work
doing this every year,
but they are our most
loyal customers.
Some even loyal to a fault.
Hmm?
Hey, another round, barkeep.
(cackles)
You wouldn't have a crane?
This is very awkward.
‐Hello!
‐Oh, dear.
We're so glad you
could make it tonight.
Really.
But well, everyone else
has gone home, you see,
and...
Are you trying to kick
me out of your house?
Is that what this is, hmm?
No, never, absolutely not.
I wouldn't dream
of such a thing.
Customer's always right.
(laughs)
(slurps)
(hiccups)
(groans)
How about some music?
♪
I still have some
work to do, sweetie.
You go ahead and turn in.
♪
‐(crash)
‐(shriek)
♪
(groans)
I trusted you, Marukin.
"Safest safes in the world."
Isn't that your slogan?
Well, tell that to my wife.
Look at this!
"Love, Lupin."
And here!
Guess who?
Oh, and I love this one.
Neat hiding place.
I've lost everything
thanks to you, you fraud!
Oh, Lupin.
I even lost the love
of the woman I left
my second wife for!
(cries)
I'm ruined.
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(chuckles)
And away we go!
♪
Says Marukin Safe's
going bankrupt.
The whole thing's your fault.
Congratulations, Lupin.
Hmm, what are
you talking about?
It says the decline
in consumer confidence
led to slowing sales,
return of merchandise,
and lawsuits.
Other than that, though,
business is great.
You're such a bad person.
Hey, capitalism needs me.
I inspire product innovation,
and that means new business.
I get it.
You're like one of
those criminal CEOs.
Such a true believer
that you're actually
willing to lie, cheat,
and steal for capitalism, right?
What a guy!
(Lupin chuckles)
Right, that's me.
Just another
starry‐eyed idealist.
And seducing married women,
is that part of
the grand plan, huh?
(Lupin yelps)
‐What?
‐(buzzer)
D'oh, damn it.
Thanks a lot.
What the hell are
you talking about?
Says here the guy's
wife has been
in some kind of a romantic
delirium ever since.
You are such a jerk.
The woman was upset.
I just calmed her
down a little
like any gentleman would.
‐(chuckles)
‐Oh, sure!
Can I help it
if I'm polite?
I've had it with you!
Aw, come on, Fujicakes!
You didn't keep the
disguise on, did you?
'Cause that's really
a disturbing image.
You see, now, this is
why chivalry is dead.
♪
(shuddering)
I hope you're happy, Lupin.
You've brought down
a noble name!
Wait, of course,
I forgot about my masterpiece,
the ten‐year safe
at the Mitsoboshi Bank.
It'll open automatically
for the first time
in a decade next week.
Ha‐ha!
(grunting)
I could publically
challenge him to crack it.
Why not?
It's a brilliant idea.
A black belt title fight
between good and evil.
Think of the publicity!
And best of all,
nothing he attempts
could possibly succeed.
He'll be humiliated.
And after that,
with my reputation
restored to me,
Marukin Safe will rise again!
(jet plane flies overhead)
(wheels screeching)
Ah, it's good
to be home again.
(horn honks)
Hmm, boy, I'm sure
not looking forward
to telling the chief
that I've lost track
of Lupin again.
Hmm?
Ha!
Hey, that's my paper.
"Marukin to Lupin: Crack This."
This is great!
I haven't lost track
of you after all.
♪
This guy just can't
lose gracefully.
Yeah, what are you gonna do?
Anybody in this room
doubt what Lupin
is going to do?
Hey, I have a reputation.
I need to protect it.
This is kind of
reckless, though, isn't it?
I mean, the playing field
is not exactly level.
When did you become
such a wussy, huh?
But why risk it when
we don't even know
what's in there?
Because I destroyed
the man's name,
and it won't sit right until
I show it wasn't just luck.
‐Huh?
♪
Inspector Zenigata, Interpol.
I believe we spoke
earlier this morning.
Thank you very much
for coming.
I'd have understood
if you declined.
I must imagine
you're not too happy
about this stunt either.
I can assure you,
that's putting it
most mildly, Inspector.
(Marukin laughing)
Oh, you have nothing
to worry about.
(groans)
I want you to arrest
this man, Inspector!
He's an accessory!
Accessory to what?
There's not going
to be any crime
committed here,
you know that.
I don't,
nobody does anymore.
That's why the board
has just instructed me
to inform you that
we're canceling our
long‐term agreement
with your company.
(laughing)
It'll just be more expensive
when you come back to me.
In exactly 10 minutes
from now that safe
is going to open
automatically.
And when the world
learns I foiled
the great Lupin the Third,
my factories will
be working overtime.
Unfortunately, the safe's
already been opened.
Sometime this morning.
That's impossible!
Maybe it just opened
a little early?
No, I'm afraid not.
We checked, the safe
was definitely forced open,
and the contents were
meticulously removed.
It was my masterpiece.
It was the most advanced
design in the world.
The code, the materials.
Impregnable.
I poured my very soul
into that project,
designing and redesigning,
obsessing over
every detail!
And now the fruit
of all that labor has
been laid to waste
by a common thief!
Well, there's a lot of
things you can call Lupin.
He's a thief,
and a womanizer,
and a bastard,
but he is not common.
No, he's one‐of‐a‐kind.
It sounds like
you admire him.
(groans)
I want to see it!
Show me the safe, I insist.
Come on, show me!
Very well.
(mutters)
There's your impregnable
safe, Mr. Marukin.
They ripped right through it.
(heavy breathing)
It can't be!
It can't!
(cries)
I would pity you,
but in this case,
you brought it on yourself.
To say nothing of the
damage you've done to us,
challenging Lupin was
an arrogant, desperate,
irresponsible stunt.
On the other hand,
it's no shame to be
made a fool of by Lupin.
It happens to the best of us.
I want to meet
this man, this Lupin.
I want to find out
how he did this to me!
Ah!
Take me to him!
Where is he?
I demand you tell me
where he can be found!
I...don't know.
(wails)
Lupin!
(shouts)
(groans)
♪
Thank you, Inspector.
Please, don't let me
keep you from your work.
I suppose we share in the blame.
Putting too much of
our trust in technology
when it's the human
factor that's crucial.
Although, apparently
even the police are
of little use once Lupin
gets his sights on you.
Ugh, yeah, well,
I'm gonna get him,
just you wait
and see, bub!
Huh!
(chuckles)
Olly, olly, income free!
We did it!
Okay, you can come out now.
So, Pops is back, damn it.
That was a shock.
Tell me about it.
I was trying to keep
a straight face.
Hey, it's about time
for that safe to open.
Have a seat.
Hey, that's right, let's see.
I was really worried
he was gonna try
to crawl inside.
(grunting)
Yeah, it would've been
a real short trip,
I'll say that.
Hey, we're down to
10 seconds right now
and nine, and eight,
and seven, six,
five, four, three,
two, one.
Bingo!
(door creaks open)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(gunshot)
♪
(birds chirping)
Ah, nothing soothes
my soul quite like
a long stroll through these
haunts of ancient peace.
♪
‐Huh!
‐Hey there.
Can I help you?
Ah, well, you answered
my first question.
You're Fujiko.
But I've never met you before.
How do you know my name?
(chuckles)
This is how.
Ugh, where in the
world did you get‐‐
I got it from Zenigata.
But you don't
look like a cop.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Marukin's son,
Tetsutaroo.
And you've been so upset
all your hair fell out.
No, I just thought
it would look cool.
And it does!
Thank you, anyway,
I wonder if you'd
introduce me to Lupin.
It would mean
the world to me.
Why do you want
to meet Lupin?
Well, he's the man who
defeated my father!
I'm finally free of that
oppressive old tyrant!
So, you want to thank him?
Exactly, and don't worry,
I made sure no one
followed me here.
So I figured he's just
a grateful young fan.
What harm could there be?
Huh, so the safe cracker
cracks a safe maker,
and the safe maker's son says
"thanks" to the safe cracker.
(laughs)
So where is Lupin anyway?
Oh, yeah, he's in the sauna.
Where else?
So, it's Tetsutaroo, right?
I was named after
my grandfather.
Would you mind if
I asked you something?
Go ahead, ask me anything.
Thank you.
I mean, it's just,
was there a reason
you targeted my dad's safes?
A reason?
Not really.
No reason?
Hey, turn it down!
That's hot!
Tell me.
Tell you?
(Lupin groans)
Cut it out!
Why him?
I‐‐I don't‐‐
Look, they're the best, right?
I mean, come on.
I just wanted to...
Wanted to what?
Test your skills
or something?
Yes.
Sort of a game to you?
Yeah, I mean, no.
I mean, whatever.
Well, while you were
testing your skills,
my family was suffering
devastation and shame.
(Lupin straining)
Oh, stop it,
turn it off, please!
And then when you
couldn't beat my father
fair and square,
you cheated!
Hah, yeah.
Well, I could've broken
into that safe blindfolded,
and I didn't.
And you wanna know why?
It was out of
compassion for your father!
That's a desperate lie.
You don't care about
anyone but yourself.
(Lupin screams)
Hot, hot, hot!
Cut it out, will you?
Okay, you're mad, I get it.
What do you want
from me, an apology?
I want you to accept
a challenge from me.
No tricks this time.
From you?
That's ridiculous,
you're like 12.
What are you gonna
challenge me to?
A game of Frogger?
The challenge is to break
into a safe I've created.
You created?
(laughs)
You're joking, right?
I mean, come on,
that's just plain silly.
(Lupin whimpers)
I'm sorry, was that
a yes or a no?
That was a desperate
cry for help by a man
being attacked by a fetus.
Yes or no, Mr. Lupin?
Just turn it down!
Okay, do we have
an agreement?
Just a little lower,
if you don't mind.
Phew.
I take it that signals
your acceptance.
‐I won't do it!
‐Huh?
(chuckles)
Have it your way, then.
Whoa!
(straining)
You're a tough man, Mr. Lupin.
Maybe a little
tenderizing
will bring you
to your senses.
(shrieking)
So, all of this is
just to avenge
your father's honor,
is that right?
A noble instinct,
but I'm afraid
you're overmatched.
You're a sweet kid,
but shouldn't you
be in school?
You're gonna fall
behind in geometry.
Huh, the son
of a great man
is always underestimated.
Take a look at my
latest design.
A handcuff safe.
Very imaginative.
You really are
your father's son,
but it still doesn't
make you a match for Lupin.
Hey, Fujiko, could you
get the darts out
of the board for me?
Lazy.
(gasps)
What are you doing, Junior?
Get these things off.
There are only
two ways out of them.
You can use the key
or just cut off your hands.
Very funny,
you're a riot.
Now, give me the key.
Unfortunately, it's not
in my possession just now.
Hey, cut the crap, kid,
and get those
cuffs off of her,
and get 'em off of her
right now or else.
But even I can't remove
them without the key.
Please, get these
things off now!
Where the hell's
the key, Junior?
Locked inside the safe I made.
You bastard!
So that's how you're
gonna get Lupin
to accept your
little challenge?
So, Fujiko, how attached
are you to those hands?
(ceramic shatters)
Don't even joke
about that.
Since when did you develop
a sense of humor anyway?
Well, all right.
It was just a thought.
And as for you...
prepare yourself.
It's time.
Goemon, forget it.
Lupin, what happened?
You look terrible.
Man, are you all right?
I've had more
relaxing saunas,
but yeah, I'll be okay.
Looks like you have us
over a barrel, Tetsutaroo.
You're a pretty
determined guy.
Right on both points.
And so?
Well...
I'm the same way.
The more cornered I feel,
the harder
I fight to escape.
(gulps)
But like you said,
I have you over a barrel.
Actually, I just said
it looks like you have
us over a barrel.
And looks can be deceiving.
Oh, please, Lupin.
Don't turn this into
some kind of a macho thing.
This kid's just not worth it.
Ah, patience now,
sweetheart.
Come here.
Okay, somebody start timing me.
Let's see now.
A hairpin?
What do you take me for?
Don't make me answer that.
(laughs)
Hmm.
♪
Is there something wrong?
Don't worry, little lady.
I'll have you
out in a jiffy.
Heh‐heh.
Hmm.
♪
You need a hand or anything?
Nah, nah, you kidding?
A piece of cake, actually.
I just felt more
like donuts today.
(chuckles)
Phew.
Ah, let me just...
(gulping)
Ah!
Phew, nothing like
a tall glass of juice
after a near‐fatal sauna.
Excuse me, but I thought
you might like to know
that you now have
no choice but to accept
my little challenge.
Why's that?
Because there was
poison in that glass
of juice you just guzzled.
(crash)
Coincidentally,
the antidote is in
the same safe as the key
to the handcuffs.
Ah!
Hold on, I'll get the
combination out of him.
Wait, Goemon, hold on.
My reputation will
be ruined if I have
to torture a kid
to save my skin.
But a dead guy can't
enjoy his reputation.
Oh!
No!
So, am I to infer
from all this
that you've agreed
to accept my challenge?
(groans)
Just get me to
the safe, Junior.
(birds cawing)
(car approaching)
Hurry up, Jigen.
I don't feel so...
Hey, Junior,
where the hell
is this thing anyway?
Right there.
♪
(tires screech)
Ah, no way!
What the hell is that?
This is your safe?
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
Neat, isn't it?
You know, stripped
down to their essentials,
all safes would look
like this, actually.
In fact...
the beautiful thing
is that opening it
is as simple and
straightforward
as the design itself.
Yeah, whatever.
Now let's crack this egg.
(gunshots)
Hey, Jigen, cut it out.
Jigen, hey,
it's not working, man.
Come on, we gotta try
some other strategy.
Now, don't panic.
Just stand back.
(metal clinks)
Whoa.
All right, now you can panic.
Okay, okay, so we'll just
do it the old fashioned way.
Lupin, there's not
much time left before...
Could we talk
a little later, Fuji?
I'm kind of busy.
Hey, man, try the drill.
(drill whines)
♪
So, are you ready
to admit defeat?
To a punk like you?
Never, never, never.
Never, never.
Lupin, please,
it's just not worth it.
I just can't give in.
I won't do it.
There are worse things
than death, you know.
How dare you, Goemon.
That's your friend
you're talking about.
Oh, my eyes
are getting blurry.
♪
All right, you swear
this isn't just another
one of your tricks, is it?
You'll just die.
It's really so obvious.
(laughs)
Ah!
What's the trick?
Open sesame!?
Oh!
(wind blows)
Huh?
(Lupin shrieks)
‐I don't believe it.
♪
Oh!
Open sesame.
If I ever talk
about having kids,
slap me.
You are victorious, Mr. Lupin.
Hey, Junior.
You were right, Mr. Lupin.
I am not ready
to challenge you yet,
but one day I will be,
and then I'll be back.
Tetsutaroo.
Your father Marukin
is a man of honor,
and a master at his craft.
And now, today,
you proved worthy
of that legacy.
That's a very
high compliment.
I'll tell my father
what you said.
♪
Hey, Lupin, you think
you could've opened
that damn thing
if you hadn't been
a delirious babbling
basket case?
Why not?
I'm something of a master
at my craft too, you know.
Genius works in
mysterious ways.
You know, you forget men
have a sensitive side too.
Open sesame, come on.
Just a little bit, come on!
You jerk!
(smacks)
It was worth a shot.
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Of course, you crawl on
your belly over broken glass
to be all alone
with Fujiko
in a romantic old
castle, who wouldn't?
But what if you were
chased there and surrounded
by an angry army
of jackbooted thugs?
See, for me,
that's even kinkier,
which is why I deserve
her and you don't.
I call this one
"Hell Toupee."
Catch you later.
♪