♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(gunshots)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(people chatting)
♪
"Dear Sir, I'll be
dropping by at 3:00 a. m.
the day after
tomorrow to relieve you
of the Star of Versailles.
Best regards,
Lupin The Third."
And you say this
priceless heirloom,
The Star of Versailles,
is some kind of diamond, right?
I'll say it's
some kind of diamond.
It's 50 friggin' karats.
Ugh.
Where do you keep this thing?
Right here in this wall safe.
All right, well, don't
take it out for any reason.
Meantime, I'll put a
security team together
and we'll see you back here
sometime before
3:00 a. m. Thursday night.
Whoa, slow down.
I mean, you're just
gonna take this guy,
Lupin's word for it?
And what if he
shows up before that?
No need to worry,
Mr. Beaucoup,
Lupin likes to
think of himself
as some sort
of a gentleman thief.
If he says he'll be here
at 3:00 Thursday morning,
you can count on it, trust me.
Well, if you're sure.
Just don't cut it
too close, okay?
Good night.
♪
Bonsoir, Monsieur Beaucoup.
Huh?
Surprised?
How the hell did
you get in here?
What's going on?
Who the hell are you?
(laughing)
Who else?
‐Lupin, of course.
‐(gasping)
‐Uh, buhh, buhh.
‐Shut up.
You know what I'm here for
so let's cut to the chase, okay?
Be a good boy
and give me the key.
But the note you sent
said Thursday at 3:00 a. m.,
and you're supposed
to be a gentleman.
I know, it's bad manners
showing up early like this.
Shameful.
I don't know what's
gotten into me lately.
A‐ha.
You son of a bitch.
Maybe I'm hanging out
with the wrong crowd.
Well, I don't suppose you'd
want to adopt me, would you?
♪
(gun cocking)
Now don't‐‐don't move.
Or what, tubby?
Or this.
(gunshot)
See, the thing is,
you'll never hit anything
shaking like that.
Nah, if you really want
to hit something,
you got to be calm.
‐(gunfire)
‐(groaning)
(blowing)
(laughing)
(clock chiming)
(typewriter keys clicking)
♪
Reporting live from the
blood‐soaked crime scene
is Happy Time news
reporter, Chet Bly.
Inspector, is it true you found
Lupin's fingerprints inside?
Arrgh, now listen
to this, Lupin,
I know you're watching,
you sick bastard.
Well the fun and games
are over, you hear?
You're nothing but a
cold‐blooded murderer now
and I only hope they
bring back the guillotine
just for you!
Whoo, man, I've
never ever seen old Pops
this ticked off, have you?
Yeah, well he's not the
only one who's ticked off.
Isn't that right, Goemon?
You betrayed both your
principles and your partners
for that bauble.
What, what are
you talking about?
You don't seriously think I
was behind that heist, do you?
Just save it
for the jury, Lupin,
they found your fingerprints
all over the joint.
Wait just a minute.
You know damn well
how easy it is
to fake fingerprints,
we've done it ourselves
on at least a hundred capers.
Can you look me
straight in the eye
and deny it on your honor?
Of course, look, it's simple.
Somebody found out about
the note I sent Beaucoup
and used it to set me up.
Anyway, I'm really
sorry for the guy,
but my conscience is clear
and since we're
here in France anyway,
I suggest we shift
our focus to a new target.
One already in your
sights, I presume?
Anyway, there's another jewel
called The African Queen.
It's a large ruby.
Makes Beaucoup's rock
look like a tiny tie stud.
Merci beaucoup.
(dog barking)
Ah.
Please, make
yourself comfortable.
My God, what a boring party.
Ah, but meeting you
was quite stimulating.
Hey look, when you offered to
bring me back here for a drink,
I assumed you
meant from a glass.
But I'm wealthy and French,
what more could you
possibly want, mon chèri?
To feel loved, of course,
mon petit escargot.
Your little snail?
You could show me
that jewel you mentioned.
That would make me feel
very close to you.
But mon chèri,
please be reasonable,
The African Queen
is a family heirloom.
I see where we stand.
No, no, please wait.
Very well,
I'll show it to you.
♪
(lock clicking)
Six, four,
seven, three, bingo.
Now if I can just keep
the little snail
in its shell until‐‐
‐(glass breaking)
‐Huh?
Who the hell are you, answer!
I'm Lupin The Third
at your service
and I hate to be a royal pain,
but I'm here to snatch
The African Queen.
Get out of here!
Lupin?
(struggling)
You think you can stand
there and laugh, do you?
Well, I'm afraid the ultimate
laugh will be mine, not yours.
(gunfire)
Okay, buddy, if that's
the way you want it
then that's the way
you'll have it.
‐Huh‐‐argh!
‐(grenade exploding)
What the hell was that?
♪
(gasp)
You should have run away.
Ah!
(siren wailing)
(laughing)
(clock chiming)
(murmuring)
Hey, put it down!
What the hell's
wrong with you?
I'm talking to you is what
and I'm telling you
none of us are buying this
cock and bull story of yours.
So someone is running
around impersonating me,
I mean, what's
so hard to grasp?
I am something of
a celebrity, you know.
He dresses like you,
he sounds like you,
and he's got
your fingerprints.
Yeah, but he's not as
handsome, according to you.
So what, you're
a master of disguise
and I didn't say
handsome anyway.
Ah, what about you?
You were trying to steal
The African Queen without us.
I'd say that represents a
pretty serious breach of trust,
huh, guys?
Huh?
‐Mm‐hmm.
Whatever, you
guys stick together
and I'll stick
to my principles,
like not working with killers.
Hmph!
Arrgh, what a
hypocritical bitch!
Grrr, principles my ass.
‐Hmm.
There you are,
bonjour, gentlemen.
Huh?
Good, thanks for
coming, Dr. Normil.
I can see what you're
talking about already.
Lupin seems
to be quite upset.
Yeah, I think we've got a minor
problem on our hands, doc.
Pity, hmm.
♪
(doorbell ringing)
Doctor, it's been a long time.
Lupin, come in.
Thanks.
♪
Please, make
yourself at home.
Is scotch all right?
Uh, yeah, thanks.
Ah, here we are.
Glad you came, it's
been far, far too long.
Yeah.
À votre santé, your father
and I were so close,
you really should think
of me as an uncle...
and a bad host.
I left the food
in the kitchen,
I'll be right back.
♪
Gentlemen,
you can come out now.
♪
I sure hope you're wrong
about this, doc.
Well, we'll know soon enough.
Now, what you are
looking through here
is a one‐way mirror,
so he cannot see us
from the other side.
In a few seconds it
will be exactly midnight,
the time both
murders took place.
(ticking)
(glass breaking)
(gasping and sputtering)
What the friggin' hell?
Oh, dear.
(growling)
I'm afraid that my original
hypothesis was correct.
This is a textbook case
of Hyde's Disease.
I've never heard of it.
It's a rare
and little understood
psychophysiological disorder.
Something about midnight
seems to trigger his attacks.
So, doc, are you
saying that he's the one
who's been running around here
editing the local phone book?
Well, I'm not a policeman,
but it seems plausible, no?
He's really not
to blame, however.
With Hyde's Disease,
the victim has absolutely
no memory of these episodes.
Anyway, it is best to leave him
here with me for the present.
You two go back
to your hotel, eh?
♪
Take good care of him,
will you, doc?
Of course, bonsoir.
(laughing)
So, everything go
according to plan?
Mm‐hmm.
Good.
Ha, they were
remarkably easy to deceive.
Hard to believe, I mean,
a couple of pros like that.
Well, I am an old
friend of the family.
(laughing)
You were, anyway.
You know,
if this was good enough
to con a couple
of cons like that,
we just might win
an Academy Award.
Ah huh, I could be
Geffen and you Katzenberg.
But right now, I'd suggest
that we check on our little
Robert Downey, Jr.
(mumbling)
♪
This I gotta see.
How much of that stuff
did you slip him?
(laughing)
Enough.
Yes, and he'll have
absolutely no memory
of anything that's happened.
Yeah, or of anything
that didn't happen, either.
Exactly!
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(phone ringing)
Bonjour, monsieur,
this is your wake up call.
I don't remember
asking for a‐‐
What the?
♪
Ah!
How did she get in there?
Wait a second, the tape!
Yeah.
Thank God
I had this set up.
♪
All right, here we go.
Man, oh, man.
Okay.
There, okay now.
Come on now, let's see
who's setting daddy up.
Hmm, let's get
comfortable, huh?
Hmm, who is she?
Come here.
(laughing)
(sputtering)
What's going on?
(laughing)
Huh?
What happened to my face?
♪
(screaming)
I murdered that girl?
How can this be?
(laughing)
Mon dieu, I was
hoping I was wrong.
About what?
Lupin, please listen to me
and try to remain calm.
I'm sorry to have
to tell you this,
but there is no doubt now
that you have something
called Hyde's Disease.
Hyde's Disease?
It's not well understood,
but it causes the personality
and even the physiognomy
to change dramatically
under certain conditions.
In your case, something
about the hour of midnight
seems to bring it on.
I'd love to
offer you some hope,
but as I said,
it's a mystery.
(sigh)
♪
Now even he believes it.
What a chump.
He'll spend the rest
of his life on the run,
wracked with guilt over
crimes that you commit.
(laughing)
♪
(gunshot)
(crying)
And the one‐man
crime wave continues.
Murders!
Robberies!
Hijackings!
Stealing ice cream from‐‐
What the hell's
going on with you, Lupin?
Just get a hold
of yourself, will ya?
Lupin is no more responsible
for these crimes, Jigen,
than you are for the weather.
Damn, well we
gotta do somethin'.
You just have to kill me.
What's that, Lupin?
It won't stop
until I'm dead.
Please, I‐‐I'm begging you,
there's no other way.
Huh?
Please guys, Jigen, Goemon,
there's no one else
that I can ask.
♪
Hmm.
Thanks, just make it quick.
Hahh!
Aagh!
Ooh, that was close.
Huh?
Hey, stay still, will ya?
(gunfire)
Sorry about that,
force of habit, I guess.
Third time's the charm.
It's ridiculous, no.
Hmph.
‐Jigen, please?
‐Nah, count me out, too.
Kill your own damn self.
Hey, guys, wait.
Please, I‐‐
(sigh)
♪
It's been fun, till now.
(gunshot)
Argh, oof.
Damn it, can't a guy
kill himself in peace?
Hmm?
Sorry, Lupin, but I
just can't let you do this.
♪
Ah, I thought you left.
Make up your damn mind, will ya?
‐I have.
‐Ah.
Goemon and Jigen told
me what's going on.
Then you know
I have to do this.
No, I don't.
I know you, Lupin,
and even if you are sick,
I can't believe you're
capable of murder.
I'm sorry, but you're gonna
have to prove it to me.
Prove it to you?
Mm‐hmm.
♪
Arrgh.
Just take it easy.
Easy for you to say.
What time is it now?
Exactly 11:58.
Fujiko, please,
you got to get out of here.
No way, this was my idea
and I'm staying right here
till I see for myself
what's going on with you.
That's just frickin' insane!
Come on, don't be an idiot,
what if I am a serial killer?
I've thought about that.
If it turns
out to be true,
I'll just have
to kill you.
Then I'll kill myself.
There's really no other
ending that makes any sense.
Fujiko.
You can't, I mean, please.
Our two lives have
been entwined for so long.
Fujiko, huh?
(sputtering)
Ah, midnight right on the dot.
‐(sputtering)
‐(buzzing)
Lupin.
Sorry I have to do this,
we'll be together soon.
No, wait, it's a‐‐it's a‐‐
Ah‐choo!
‐(buzzing)
‐(gasp)
I knew I was right,
you're not a killer.
In fact, you're even
allergic to death.
Yee‐haw, I'm alive,
I'm alive, I'm alive!
(laughing)
I'm alive, yeah!
Fujiko, sweetheart,
you saved me!
Come here, you.
Are you crazy,
there's no time for this.
That doctor lied,
he set you up!
He's behind all of this.
(sputtering)
(laughing)
Is that Lupin?
(snicker)
(laughing)
(screaming)
I can't believe he'd
do anything like that.
Listen, Doctor, you
better be sure about this.
Unfortunately, I am.
And many more people will die
if we don't act
right away, Detective.
You understand?
Mm‐hmm, mm‐hmm.
Hmm.
♪
There you are.
Well, you look pretty happy.
Does that mean the cops
are comin' along for the ride?
Of course, why
should they doubt me?
I am a renowned
psychiatrist, after all.
‐Ah.
‐Yes, sir?
Double cappuccino,
s'il vous plaît.
You know, maybe they will bring
back the guillotine for Lupin.
Well, his good fortune was
bound to run out some day, eh?
And after your
plastic surgery,
we'll be able to retire
on our good fortune.
(laughing)
Interesting
prognosis, Doctor,
but you might want
to get a second opinion.
(birds chirping)
Ah, welcome, Inspector.
Our serial murderer
appears to have fallen
right into our hands.
You sure that's him
down there in that house?
Yes, I saw him enter
with Jigen earlier
and‐‐a‐ha,
there he is, look!
Give me those.
You're right, it is them!
This is so great.
I've been waiting for this
moment for a long time.
Huh?
♪
Doc, look there, he's‐‐
he's doing it again!
♪
And, and the same with Jigen!
I was afraid
this might happen.
It has reached
the contagious stage.
‐Inspector?
‐Huh?
All the men are
in position, sir.
All right, let's move!
Bonne chance.
♪
(laughing)
(door crashing)
Come on, boys.
‐Huh?
♪
Stay where you are!
‐Freeze!
‐Don't move!
♪
Inspector, to what
do we owe this pleasure?
Shut up, Jigen!
You and Lupin
are under arrest.
Me, Jigen?
You are having
a joke with me, no?
Listen, I ain't Lupin,
you big baboon!
Oh, you think
you're real funny, huh?
Well, ha ha ha ha!
Are you feeling
all right, Inspector?
Oh, I'm just fine, thanks.
Take him away!
I'm Normil, I am.
‐You're making a big mistake!
‐Let go, let go!
I'm not Lupin!
(struggling)
(laughing)
I finally caught you!
Ha!
You got the wrong
guy, you idiot!
Damn it all!
This is ridiculous!
Stop it,
let go of me at once!
There is a mistake,
let me go!
Help!
♪
Magnifique!
Great work, Inspector.
Thanks, Doctor,
you were a lot of help.
You're quite
a hero yourself.
Oh, it was nothing, adieu.
(siren wailing)
And bon friggin' riddance.
(laughing)
Woo‐hoo, it worked,
you're amazing, Lupin.
I am, aren't I?
Fight film with film,
that's what I always say.
Old Pops is gonna be
really disappointed,
but at least he didn't go away
empty handed, you know.
That's right.
Hey, Fujicakes, by the way,
did you mean it last
night in the hotel room
when you said you'd
sacrifice everything for me
if I was gonna die?
It just came out
of me, I guess.
Well, I don't know if you
still feel the same way,
but uh‐‐hey,
what time is it?
It's 12:00, why?
(sputtering)
Ah!
You idiot, it's twelve noon.
♪
Don't go!
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
The next episode's
utterly preposterous premise
concerns a charismatic
and mysterious madman
who extorts millions
and millions of dollars
out of a Middle Eastern kingdom
by threatening to stage
devastating terrorist attacks.
Very hard to swallow,
if you ask me.
Anyway, it's called Sheikdown.
Catch you later.
♪