♪
(gunshot)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(glass shattering)
(engine revs)
(tires screeching)
♪
(gunfire)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(tires screeching)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
At the far end of a silk road
lies the kingdom of Cocodad:
an impoverished patch of dust
with a population of only 3,000,
covering a total area
of less that 100 square miles.
Why would I wanna
go there, you ask?
A girl, of course!
A princess, Yasmin was her name,
and on the occasion of
her 20th birthday celebrations,
there was this...incident.
♪
(cheering "Yasmin!")
(gunshot)
(gasping)
♪
(helicopter whirring)
(yelping)
Princess Yasmin, quickly, come!
It could be a bomb!
♪
(gasps)
Look!
(hissing)
(all yelping)
(coughing)
♪
(helicopter whirring)
Yasmin!
♪
(typewriter clacking)
Onward, men!
For Cocodad!
Onward!
♪
(airplane engines roaring)
Charge!
(explosions)
(screaming)
Everyone fall back, now!
♪
(thumping)
Hmm.
Huh?
We need a master thief.
What was that you said?
A thief!
Since she was stolen from you,
you must hire someone
who will steal her back!
Hey, is this some
kind of bad joke?
This isn't some kind of
freakin' employment agency, pal!
This is freakin' Interpol;
we're police here!
That's quite enough, Inspector.
Huh, but, sir,
you can't possibly‐‐
Interpol is merely offering
its assistance to the kingdom.
Huh?
♪
So, what do you
think of this one?
He'll do the trick.
Uh, well, if I may, sir,
I don't think
this one's really‐‐
He's my recommendation,
any objections?
No, sir, I just‐‐
I didn't think so.
For some reason, in those days,
I was under the impression
that chicks really dug boxers.
Damn, he's big!
(ding)
(grunting)
(panting)
(groaning)
So much for my boxing career.
So, Prime Minister
Kashim's request
came along at a good time;
it promised travel
to an exotic land,
a beautiful damsel in distress,
and, as he put it,
the very jewel in
the kingdom's crown
as a reward.
What was left of my brain
was totally psyched.
I hopped the first flight
out of Paris with my pals,
Jigen and Goemon
and the ever‐tantalizing Fujiko.
♪
Hi there.
Hey, so, what's your name, babe?
It's Marilyn.
(aroused groaning)
♪
Is that really
the Prime Minister's plane?
Well, it's not the most
up‐to‐date of models,
but most modern modifications
have been nothing
but bells and whistles.
It's pre‐whistle.
Say your prayers.
(engine starts)
(yelping)
(engine roaring)
Hey, it might be nice
to fill us in on things
before we die.
What do you mean, I‐‐
Don't try that
innocent act on me!
You know just
what I'm hinting at.
The take, what are
we getting paid?
Well, why don't
you just ask him?
(growls)
It's a joke, right?
Curry, like the kind
of curry you eat?
That is correct; in our country,
curry and rice is considered
more precious than rubies.
A gift fit for gods
and you will eat
to your heart's content.
This dish is the very jewel
in our kingdom's crown
and we offer it gladly to you.
Uh, Miss Fujiko?
Look, I appreciate
the generosity,
but I can't handle the carbs.
Bye!
♪
I guess you really
can't blame her, you know?
I mean, a girl's
gotta keep her figure,
but you guys like
curry, don't ya?
Hmm, well, you can't make
a curry dish too hot
as far as I'm concerned.
And you, Mr. Goemon?
Actually...
I don't believe
in any faddish diets.
(sighs)
(claps)
♪ Whose curry without
a side order of pickles ♪
♪ Or without floppy rice ♪
(gong crashes)
♪ Or without the curry ♪
You are called
Lupin, am I right?
Go ahead, please, begin,
I prepared it personally.
(grunts)
Your sovereign thanks you
very much, Kashim.
I'm just glad that I have played
a small part in rescuing
our dear princess, your majesty.
Hmm, how do you find it?
Hard to miss it.
(gags)
♪
(rumbling)
(screaming)
Guess who's coming to dinner.
(helicopter whirring)
♪
(projector clicking)
Oh, my poor, sweet princess!
Greetings, everyone,
and especially
to you, Mr. Lupin.
I had a feeling from the start,
a hope actually, that you'd get
mixed up in all this somehow,
but, sadly, we won't be meeting
since any plan of a rescue is
an exercise
in wishful thinking!
♪
As you can see, I have
surveillance cameras
in place that detect
all intruders
and then guide chaser cannons
and ground‐to‐air missiles
to destroy their targets
with pinpoint accuracy!
(psychotic laughter)
(explosion)
♪
Still, I know you won't be able
to resist trying, Mr. Lupin.
In fact, I'm counting on it!
(psychotic laughter)
♪
My sweet daughter!
(sobbing)
(gasping)
(tearing)
♪
(machine powers down)
Yasmin, Yasmin!
(sobbing)
(growls)
Damn it all!
So, who is this maniac?
You asking me?
No idea.
Right, come on, Lupin,
don't play dumb.
You took this gig because
you knew who was behind it
from the get‐go.
Hmm, could be.
Uh‐huh, so, to recap here,
it's just the three of us
against an impregnable
computerized death machine
controlled by some crazy guy,
who, for the moment,
we'll just call...
hey, wait a minute,
you think it could be...?
(laughs)
Except, there's just
one thing about that:
It's not possible.
Yeah, well, more things
than Heaven and Earth, Horatio.
Anyway, we'll find out
as soon as we break in there.
Oh, yeah, great plan,
we break into the place.
Don't know why I
didn't think of that.
This from a man who just came
from dining on curry fit only
for the immortals.
We're blessed;
it'll be a piece of cake!
(laughs)
Okay, all set,
you ready over there?
Mr. Lupin, where on
Earth are you going?
Off to rescue
the princess, naturally.
Why do you ask?
With these mirrors
and all of these bulls?
Certainly.
Why, you think I took too many?
Move out!
(bulls mooing)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(yelps)
Oh, it's you, Inspector!
Was that Lupin?
Yes, but please, saving
the princess must be
the paramount concern!
Don't worry, Kashim,
I'll capture everyone,
including whoever
took the princess;
it's killing two birds
with one stone,
'cept they'll be jailbirds now!
(laughs heartily)
(whistles)
♪
(explosions)
Okay, right over there.
Aimed at the missiles, right?
Hope I'm right about it.
(whooshing)
♪
(beeping)
(whooshing)
(explosion)
(chuckling)
Here comes another.
(whooshing)
♪
(explosions)
Lupin, you're under arrest!
Incoming!
(explosion)
Man, talk about being
at the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Someday, Lupin, I swear I'll‐‐
(grunts)
So, the missiles saw
images of themselves
reflected in the mirrors
and they targeted
themselves as the intruders.
Is that it?
Yeah, that's it.
No front door, no back door,
no emergency exit?
What the hell's
the matter with this place?
Poor design; we'll have
to make an entrance.
That won't be necessary!
I'm a gentleman,
and a gentleman
does not turn away visitors!
(rumbling)
After you pass
through the entryway,
you'll find arrows
along the walls
that will lead you
to the princess.
There are, of course,
a few surprises
awaiting you along the way.
Navigate them successfully
and I'll be waiting for you!
Huh?
(maniacal laughter)
♪
(door creaking)
Quick!
(panting)
(grunting)
Agh, he's stuck in the door!
♪
(panting)
(sighs)
What the...?
Where did my hand go?
Your hand?
Huh?
Had me worried there.
Jigen, don't you ever
do that to me again!
Sorry, man.
We've got company.
Hey, look, it's the princess!
♪
Or that's what they
want us to think, anyway.
It's more like they're all
just decoys of Princess Yasmin.
Only one way to find out.
No, hold it, Goemon,
it's too big a risk to take.
(grunts)
♪
(groaning)
Huh?
(rumbling)
What the hell?
♪
(panting)
(yelps)
(screams)
♪
Man, I thought I was a goner.
I second that.
Oh, boys?
♪
If we were in
a damn amusement park,
I might be amused, but we're
just sittin' ducks here!
(screams)
(grunting)
♪
(screaming)
Huh?
(yelping)
(whooshing)
(laughs)
♪
(pounding)
Oh, now this is
just getting surreal!
(trumpeting)
I have no idea why
I'm saying this,
but why don't you
go find the princess
while we deal with this?
♪
Hmm.
(yelps)
What the‐‐hey, help, help!
♪
(crashing)
On the one hand, the climax
was shamelessly predicable.
(gunshot)
David triumphing over Goliath;
standard populist fare,
but the hero underestimated
his opponent and so it seemed
like a climax was merely
a turn in the plot!
The defeated one,
it turned out,
was defeated, but temporarily!
(beeping)
(buzzing)
(explosions)
He had no intention of dying,
indeed, he could not,
not until the man known as
Lupin had been dispatched
to Hell's scrap heap
of history's cocky young heroes!
Bravo; I laughed, I cried,
I got my Christmas cards done.
Hey, let's get
to work on the sequel;
that is the reason
we're both here, isn't it?
To write the next,
and hopefully final,
chapter in the epic struggle
of Lupin versus Mr. X?
Yes, it is.
You haven't changed
a bit, Mr. Lupin.
I'd return the compliment,
but that burka
makes it kinda hard.
We have to keep things fresh
if we're going to sustain
the franchise.
Of course, that
extends to the ending
of this installment as well.
Got it, so where is
the princess anyway?
Come out on top this
time, she's all yours.
Really, that's great,
let's get to it then.
Very well, let the games begin!
Take one; they're identical.
Now, pull the trigger
and shoot the water
at the highest velocity!
When the water attains
the right speed,
it becomes as hard as a diamond!
I call it my Water Saber.
Hey, just what the hell is this?
It's the twist, Mr. Lupin,
the diabolical twist!
Gives me a psychological edge
and delights the audience!
(grunting)
♪
(yelping)
(chuckles)
Well, we met
the enemy and he is us.
(grunting)
Hold it, I got a foolproof plan
to settle this whole thing.
(grunting)
♪
Game, set, and‐‐
Hold it right there,
nobody makes a move
till I know which one's
the real Lupin.
Jigen, listen,
I don't know how the hell
you're supposed
to figure this one out,
but let me tell you
just one thing:
No way I'm letting
this guy kill me.
If you're my friend,
you'll do it yourself.
(gunshots, grunting)
Damn it, how did you know
I wasn't the real Lupin?
'Cause the real Lupin
would never say something
all sappy and noble like,
"Kill me if you're my friend."
He'd be squealing for
his life like a little girl.
♪
Hey, Jigen.
(gunshot)
(grunts)
♪
You take it from here, pal.
You got it!
Princess, Lupin the Third,
at your service,
and a long story comes
to a happy ending
for everybody, my dear!
(psychotic chuckling)
You bastard!
Kidding, kidding,
just messin' with ya.
(gasps)
Pervert!
Whoa.
I think she's
tougher than Mr. X.
(chuckling)
Oh, crap.
You completed your assignment
most satisfactorily.
I hereby proclaim,
therefore, a reward.
You may finish what remains
of your curry and rice.
Yeah, well, about that‐‐
Hold it right there, Lupin,
I got your reward right here!
(whispering)
Very good, sir.
Huh?
It's an extra spicy
curry in your honor,
courtesy of Mr. Lupin.
Just these three servings;
it's a sacred tradition.
Then, you are free
to leave the country.
I'm gonna get him for this.
(yelps)
(chuckling)
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
You'd think I'd get sort of
a kinky thrill out of being
pursued by
an assassin named Beauty,
but no such luck;
it's a guy, and I'll admit,
he does get my heart racing,
but that's more about
his monster Colt . 44 Python
than anything else he's packin'.
Check us out next time
in "Beauty and the Deceased."
Catch ya later!
♪