♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
(snoring)
♪
(phone ringing)
Hm?
Zenigata.
Hey man, how's it hangin'?
I was just, uh...
I refer to that
big wad of drool
hangin' from your chin
right now, you slacker.
Then again, in your
dreams is the only place
you're ever gonna catch me.
Wait just a second!
Lupin?
Oh!
Eee!
♪
Toolin' down the road, top down,
crankin' the good stuff.
This is the reason
God invented America.
Oh please, what are you, 14?
Hey, I remember how we
used to hit the clubs together
every other night.
What the hell happened, Jigen?
Yeah, I used to
suck my thumb, too.
Classical music
is the only stuff.
♪
(classical music)
Hm.
♪
Hm‐‐huh?
‐Please.
‐Hey!
Enka's the stuff.
Listen to this.
(Enka music)
(sighing)
Mm.
♪
‐Lupin, stop the car!
‐Huh?
Leave it to Pops
to strike a discordant note.
Stop the car!
Listen, Lupin, let's
not do this the hard way!
♪
(laughing)
I see you're not the kind
who believes in
taking any chances.
Frankly, that's where
a good deal of our business
still comes from.
We built our reputation
on having the most secure vault
in the country.
It's where we get
our motto from:
You're in safe hands.
I'll have my secretary
make arrangements
for the delivery.
Thank you very much
for your time, sir.
Not at all,
it's been a pleasure.
♪
Goodbye for now.
Goodbye.
(laughing)
♪
Hm.
Hm, this get‐up's pure gold.
They don't even think
to suspect anything.
♪
Damn, a traffic jam
at the racetrack?
(horns honking)
♪
(laughing)
Well, well, well,
serendipity.
That smirk's
going up in smoke.
Huh?
♪
(horns honking)
Hey, what's the deal?
You freakin' blind?
I'll hold him down for ya.
Dammit!
Lupin!
And what in the hell
are all these damn cars
doin' here anyway?
♪
(crowd noise)
And they're off, it's
Centerpoint and Golden Boy
neck and neck, leading
third place Lightfoot
by a length and a half.
Coming out of the first turn,
Centerpoint just
ahead of Golden Boy,
Golden Boy coming up
from the outside.
Centerpoint pouring it on now,
Centerpoint pulling away.
Well, that explains
it all right.
It's opening day.
But how the hell am I gonna
find Lupin's gang here?
Golden Boy and Centerpoint,
Golden Boy
and Centerpoint,
neither one's gonna
give any ground,
and Lightfoot holding steady
at two lengths back.
What a haul.
Golden Boy making a break,
pulling ahead!
He's‐‐wait a minute,
there's something‐‐
some kind of banner,
I can't quite‐‐
There's some kind
of writing on it.
‐Give it.
‐Huh?
Hm.
"Happy opening day,
especially for me.
Love, Lupin."
Dammit, why, that little weasel!
♪
Little weasel lured
me here, dammit,
just so he could announce
what he was gonna do
and humiliate me.
Well, he's not gonna
get away with it‐‐
not this time.
Oh, please tell me this
is some kind of a prank.
No, I'm afraid this
is deadly serious,
and speaking of which, where are
you transporting the money?
Delivered by armored truck
to the Metropolitan Bank.
By armored truck?
That's at least
30 miles from here.
Hm.
♪
Hey, I've got an idea.
(whispering)
♪
Now remember, this isn't
some punk purse snatcher
we're dealing with here, okay?
You gotta be on your
toes with this guy.
♪
(laughing)
Jigen, hit it!
Hm.
(vibrating sound)
Hey, why you stoppin'?
I can't get the thing to move.
What the hell?
(grunting)
Okay, now it's all yours.
Go ahead and peel out.
Mm‐hm.
(creaking)
♪
Hey, what do you
know, it worked.
♪
Wanna have a look at what
we actually scored here?
I'll do the honors.
(grunting)
Huh?
(laughing)
Well, now who's
publicly humiliated,
huh, Lupin?
So we only stole you?
(laughing)
That's right.
As a matter of fact,
the money is making
its way right now
through the storm drains
all the way to the bank.
No way out of this one.
Go!
You heard him, go!
♪
No, dammit, don't shoot!
We want these guys alive.
♪
Good gravy!
Hey you, get the harbor
patrol right now!
We gotta drag this river.
Yes, sir.
Dammit!
♪
(sneezes)
You know, I think the whole
thing went pretty well.
(sneezes)
And that was really the best
plan you could think of?
Gotta keep your eye
on the prize.
After all, the whole idea
was to divert his attention.
Remember that,
and that's what counts.
Because now Zenigata's
going to be practically
living on that boat
until they recover our bodies.
Exactly.
(sneezes)
♪
Oh my.
Yes, I see.
It's a gift from my parents'
golden wedding anniversary.
Ah, amazing.
They're magnificent.
Why, thank you.
Uh, my point was in addition
to their worth as precious gems,
they also have great
sentimental value.
Why, certainly, I completely
understand, of course.
As I told you before,
the security
of such highly valued items
is the very cornerstone
of our business.
Your treasure is our treasure.
Very well then.
I should be going.
I'll drop by in the morning.
Mm‐hm.
♪
Thank you so much
for all your help.
Goodbye now.
No trouble at all.
It's been a pleasure.
♪
I'll see to it that it's
ready for you to collect
by seven tomorrow morning.
Thank you,
that will be fine.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Hey you, anything at all?
Nothing over here,
just garbage.
Huh, I don't get it.
I mean, we saw all the blood,
so we know for a fact that
at least one of 'em's injured.
Huh‐‐wait a minute!
What if the whole damn
thing's a big trick?
What am I saying,
of course it's a trick!
After all, this is Lupin.
Bastard's at the bank!
♪
Huh?
Hold it, wait!
(panting)
Uh, and who are you?
Of course, I'm Inspector
Zenigata with Interpol.
And why have you
come barging in here?
Oh, well, you see, there's
this robber named Lupin,
and he's boasted that he
intends to target the gate
for the big opening
day at the track.
I just thought he
might have snuck in here.
You haven't noticed
anything unusual,
or, well, uh...
(laughing)
Oh, Zenigata, did you say?
And do you know just
where you are, Mr. Zenigata?
Why, you're staring at the
famous underground vault
at the Metropolitan,
the world's most secure bank.
(laughing)
Yeah, look, I know that,
but this guy, I mean, he‐‐
‐Ah.
‐Huh?
What are ya‐‐
(alarm blaring)
Huh?
What happened?
I was merely demonstrating
the sophistication
of our security system
for this gentleman.
As you observed, Inspector,
it doesn't take much
to trigger the alarm,
and in fact a handkerchief
or even an insect
would have done it.
Hm.
And that's just
one feature of many.
This vault door, for instance,
operates on the same
time lock system
as the military's missile silos,
so that money is very safe.
Now, have I managed to
put your mind at rest,
Inspector Zenigata?
Well, uh...
Now, until seven o'clock
tomorrow morning,
Inspector Zenigata,
even I can't open it.
♪
(sighing)
Have they found anything?
I'm afraid not, Inspector.
Hm.
♪
(ticking)
(grunting)
‐Hey.
‐Sorry,
I gotta scratch my butt.
Well, wait till we get out.
We gotta get goin' anyway.
‐Come on.
‐All right, all right.
Careful now, if you even
breathe on this freakin' floor,
that's it.
♪
Well, this sucks,
we're a good 15 yards
from where we want to be.
♪
Yeah, it may suck,
but I suck better.
♪
You've gotta be kidding me.
(laughing)
Now I've seen everything.
Hey, stick with me, kid,
you'll see even more.
I'm sort of an encyclopedia
of stupid human tricks.
(sneezes)
Ah!
♪
Phew‐‐well, save it
for Letterman, will ya?
Hoo...
Very good advice.
♪
Hm.
Goemon, I just
don't understand
how you can sit
there so calmly.
I just can't help worrying
about him, you know?
Hm.
I mean, what if he suffocated
or got caught or something
before he could finish the job?
♪
Okay, man, pass me the drill.
Right.
♪
All right, all done with that.
And now, a little
solid nitro like so,
and because cleanliness
is next to godliness,
there.
♪
‐'Kay?
‐Right.
♪
(explosion)
Huh?
Just me or did you
guys feel that, too?
Eh, just the subway.
‐Yeah!
‐Crap.
Yeah, must have been it.
♪
(laughing)
Yeah!
♪
Ah!
(laughing)
Hm.
Three thirty already.
♪
Hey Lupin, we gotta
rock 'n roll, man.
Okay, gotcha.
♪
Dammit, it's almost dawn.
Hey, what the hell's
goin' on over there?
It's the current,
it's real strong here.
They probably
drifted downstream.
Well, why didn't you
tell me that before?
Ah, then look down there!
♪
(ticking)
I guess those guys could
still be at the bank.
But even they couldn't‐‐
or could they?
♪
(ticking)
(laughing)
(phone ringing)
Dammit, who the hell's
callin' us at this hour?
Mm‐hm, you were here earlier.
Is there anything
I can do for you?
‐Listen!
‐Huh?
I still think it's possible
that Lupin might be
over there somewhere.
Yeah, but that's
just not possible.
I mean, I'm lookin' at
the security monitors right now,
and I'm tellin' you,
this place is quieter
than a freakin' morgue.
Why, has there been some
kind of new development?
No, but that's just it.
We've been draggin'
the damn river all day,
and there's still
no sign of the bodies.
Well, like I said,
I wish I could help you.
Tell you what,
I know this sounds crazy,
but take a look inside
the vault for me, will you?
No can do, Inspector.
It's on a time lock.
Nobody can get inside
there for an hour.
(ticking)
Okay, this is the last one.
Good.
♪
Son of a bitch.
Wouldn't you know it?
Last one.
Stay cool, man, we'll get it.
Easy does it now.
♪
Damn piece of crap.
(gasping)
(sighing)
You gotta help me out here.
Really, I'm beggin' ya.
I'm down on my knees, buddy.
I've been after this
Lupin guy for years now,
day in, day out.
It's all I ever do.
It's my whole crummy life.
Not even a life,
it's a living hell.
I can't even kill myself 'cause
I can't meet my ancestors.
You gotta help me!
All right, all right,
just take it easy now.
Take a breath, pal.
We'll see what we can do for ya.
Larry?
Mm‐hm?
(sighs)
(grunting)
Hm?
Hey, Lupin, someone's out there.
Here, grab this.
Quick!
(footsteps)
(sighs)
Never a dull moment.
(ticking)
Now, I really hope you're
satisfied, Inspector,
because I'm not runnin'
down any more hunches for you.
You get it?
(hangs up)
Good heavens, what have I done?
(crying)
♪
Hey, hey!
Inspector, come on!
We found 'em,
we found the bodies.
♪
Out of my way!
Hey, wait!
♪
That bastard, I knew
he wasn't dead!
(angry grunt)
‐Dammit!
‐Hey there, Pops.
Just want to say that
we really appreciate
the all night vigil‐‐
very touching‐‐
but the good news
is we're not dead,
so, well, catch you later.
By the way, this tape
will self‐destruct
and destroy a lot
of other things, too,
in five seconds.
‐Good luck, Pops.
‐Clear the area, everyone!
(explosion)
(grunting)
So I was right,
he is at the bank!
Ah!
♪
Thank you again for everything.
Glad to be of service.
Well, goodbye now.
♪
Ah, if only all of my
clients could be like that.
♪
(alarm blaring)
"Don't blame yourselves.
The vault's all mine."
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
Sure beats playin' the ponies.
The guy even said,
"Glad to be of service."
Yeah, they really got the whole
customer service thing down.
So true, Jigen, so true.
Cops.
Gee, I wonder
where they're goin'.
(growling)
(siren blaring)
♪
Huh?
Wasn't that Pops?
You gotta love
that guy's dedication.
You're an inspiration!
Kind of ironic, I guess,
but there you have it.
You just keep on truckin'.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
Next time, I fall in love
with Jackie O, or maybe not.
I don't know, my head hurts.
It kinda looks like her,
and it sure feels like love,
walkin' in the rain,
puttin' on a little show
for perverts with binoculars.
Oh, he's not,
he's trying to kill me?
Actually, you know, that
kind of adds a touch of kink.
Anyway, catch you later
in "Snake Charmer."
♪