♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(gunshots)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Well, Lupin old buddy,
I know this is all real
romantic and everything,
but still, just keep
your hands on those oars
if you know
what's good for you.
Oh, that's real funny, Jigen,
but I'm strictly
trolling for angelfish,
if you know what I mean.
Give it up, take a
look around you, man.
It's all couples around here.
You don't stand
a chance, Lupin.
♪
(grunt)
Huh?
Hmm.
(wolf whistle)
Whoa, how the hell
do you do that, Goemon?
Ahoy there,
prepare to be boarded.
Hey, buddy,
what are you doin'?
Excuse me, bikini inspector.
(metal clapping)
Zenigata!
I got you now, Lupin,
you're all mine!
(laughing)
♪
Here you go, guys,
take her away.
She's just your type.
♪
Son of a...
(motor roaring)
The little ones,
I throw back.
But you're a keeper, Lupin.
Yep, catch of the day.
I should have listened to
my dear old grandfather.
He always said,
"Stick to real women, sonny."
Damn good advice.
You know, another one of
his favorite sayings was,
"Watch your step."
Ooh, ow, hey cut it out!
Stop it, will ya!
Arrgh, what the
hell are you doing?
Woah, a beach coming up!
Huh?
Argh!
(handcuffs jangling)
Are you out of your mind?
There, now watch
your step, sonny.
Hey, Lupin, what
the hell are you...
Now push.
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
(screaming)
Hey, stop,
where are you going?
‐Toodles.
‐Hey, come back here!
♪
Keys.
Here they are.
Whoa!
(honking)
♪
Bye‐bye, don't
forget to write.
Love you, let's
do lunch sometime.
Lupin, stop this truck!
(typewriter keys clicking)
(birds singing)
(elevator dings)
Huh, hmm.
Not exactly
standard procedure
but sometimes
it takes a thief.
(handle jiggling)
Hmm.
And it is a damn pretty plan
if I do say so myself.
‐605.
‐Yes, sir.
I wonder what old Pops
is up to right now?
Ooh, probably
wishing he knew Italian.
That truck was headed
for the border.
Good.
(door closing)
♪
Hey, I wonder what gas station
they stole this key from.
I'm looking forward
to a hot shower,
an even hotter masseuse‐‐
‐Huh?
‐Hmm?
Ah, come in, Mr. Lupin.
The masseuse looks perfect,
but I'm pretty sure
I declined the hairy guy
in a wheelchair
deluxe package.
You're in the wrong room.
The hell we are.
This man is
telling the truth,
it is not our room.
I'm telling you,
this is 605.
But only because Ringo here
changed the room number.
You're quite as nimble as
they say you are, Mr. Lupin,
and yet you are
totally unaware
of Inspector Zenigata's
trap, aren't you?
Hmm, he's back?
The Inspector's
waiting for you
right in the next room
with open arms
and I don't think
that he's going to
give you a message, either.
Lover.
What, Fujiko?
♪
Oh, man.
I can't wait, this
is gonna be so good.
♪
(laughing)
No mint on your pillow
tonight, Lupin!
(laughing)
You let your
guard down, Lupin,
it's not like you.
You were very lucky
we were here.
And tell me why, exactly,
are you here, Fujicakes?
We have a proposition, 'kay?
Mr. Lupin, I want you to
consider being my partner.
Small job,
you don't need him.
Big job, why the friggin'
hell does he need you?
(curtains closing)
Wait, first thing's
first, gentlemen.
(projector whirring)
This is the main branch
of the First Switzerland Bank
here in Zurich.
It houses a massive
gold depository
from which I intend to withdraw
a massive quantity of gold.
(whistle)
Obviously, it's heavily
guarded around the clock.
State‐of‐the‐art security.
Motion detectors
and security cameras
cover every inch of
the approach to the vault.
Vault looks pretty standard,
shouldn't be
too hard to crack.
Seems like any professional
should be able to open it up.
Not so fast, looks
can be deceiving.
This is the only
man who can open it.
Nice schnozz.
He is the bank president.
There's a retinal
scanner on the vault
and his profile is
the only one it recognizes.
Really, well ain't
technology a hoot.
Why don't you just tunnel in?
Well, actually,
we considered that.
But as it happens,
there's an old sewage pipe
directly under the vault
and it's still accessible.
What do you say, Mr. Lupin?
Well, the heist itself
seems easy enough,
but you're still
gonna have to
get the gold out
of the country, pal.
Yeah, you got a slide
for that, big shot?
Oh, I'm a very
meticulous man.
Hmm, and a cagey one, too.
(snoring)
Hmm?
All right, here we go!
(door creaking)
Yoo‐hoo, looking
for me, big boy?
Hmm, hey, Lupin,
put that down!
Whoa!
You keep trying, Pops,
at least the law of
averages is on your side
if nothing else.
‐Hang in there.
‐Goddammit, Lupin!
Get back here, grr!
♪
(water running)
It's directly
above us, gentlemen.
It's show time, step on it.
Jigen, kindly step back,
if you know what
is good for you.
(shouts)
(creaking)
Whoa!
(crashing)
♪
Grr, it's Lupin!
He's responsible for
this, I just know it!
Damn that guy, grr.
Okay, we held up our end,
so what's the big plan for
smuggling all this stuff
out of the country?
One thing at a time.
The first step
is to melt it all down.
♪
I don't remember this
being part of the deal.
Now, carefully
pour it into that mold.
Ah, so that's
what's in this thing.
Where's the friggin' hole?
Here we go.
Alley oop.
♪
Great, so now it's one
humungous chunk of gold.
And now it's even
more conspicuous.
I'm really startin'
to worry about this guy.
♪
Fine, that should do it.
Okay, break the mold.
(struggling)
(banging)
(rocks tumbling)
Huh?
♪
Now the pièce de résistance.
Hmm, I've got to admit it,
it's a trick worthy
of my own devious mind.
Amazing.
♪
Okay, gang, that's
the last of it.
Let's roll.
Ooh, I just love
the look of it,
but I'm afraid a solid gold
van might draw attention.
Oh, no, tell me we don't
have to paint it now.
Only the gold part.
♪
Hey, Lupin old pal,
I hope you know all of this
is coming out of your share.
Oh yeah, partners my eye.
More like his slaves.
(yelling)
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Okay, you can go.
Mwa, much obliged.
(engine humming)
♪
This guy's sharp,
he might even be
more clever
than you are, Lupin.
I must say his scheme
is quite zen‐like
in its simplicity
and elegance.
Yep, this guy's like
on a whole other level.
Maybe you'd like me to
pull over to a hotel, huh?
You three could get a room.
Oh, don't be
so grumpy, Lupin.
We just crossed into France
without a hitch.
Everything's going just fine,
don't you agree, sweetheart?
Yeah, good old Pops must
be having Dalmatians.
You got to figure
that he knows
that it was us
behind this caper.
‐(whistle blows)
‐Hmm, road block ahead.
(blowing whistle)
Destination?
We're on our way to Nice.
Not anymore you're not.
(laughing)
Z‐‐Zenigata, but how?
Surprised, Lupin?
That gold job back in Zurich
had your name
written all over it.
Gold, we don't
have any gold.
Take a look.
Oh, I'll take
a look, all right.
Now, let's see what's inside.
Nothing very
interesting back there.
I'll be the judge of that.
(grunting)
What the‐‐?
(air hissing)
Hey, what the hell?
(pop)
Ah‐choo, pepper, choo!
It's full of pepper!
Ah‐choo!
I'd see someone
about that cold, Pops.
(tires screeching)
‐Hey, stop!
‐Hey, they're getting away!
Come back here!
They heard us say Nice.
We'd better cut
over to Mont Blanc
and go through Italy
just to be safe.
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
The way we're going,
we'll be in Torino tomorrow.
♪
(siren blaring)
What?
That's persistence.
That's it, pull over now!
(gunshots)
(skidding)
Ah, look out!
♪
We don't have any time
to change the tire.
We got to ditch the van.
Are you nuts?
And just leave
the gold here?
Of course not, we'll
come back for it later.
No way Pops will
figure this one out.
Okay, the three of us
will distract them
while you guys run off
in the opposite direction.
That sounds good.
♪
Hold it right there.
D'oh!
Lupin!
Wha?
(waves crashing)
What the heck's this little
water hazard doing here?
I think they call it
the Mediterranean.
Nowhere to run, Lupin,
it's the end of the line.
You really need to think
about getting a life, Pops.
Tell you what, Lupin,
I'll get a life
the day you get
life behind bars!
Well if that's
the way you want it.
Whoa!
Get back here, you!
‐Lupin, help!
‐Later, Pops.
Dammit, you weasel!
I'll get you someday,
it's just a matter of time.
So tell me something,
do you have any idea
how we're gonna
get out of this?
I hadn't actually
given that any thought.
Don't you think all this
is more than a coincidence?
What are you talking about?
It's as if Zenigata knew
everything we were going to do
before we did it.
I think someone's
tipping the guy off,
know what I mean?
You mean our partner?
I'm telling you,
it's enough to make me
want to shave my beard off.
Well so much for the proverbial
honor among thieves.
That guy's a dirty rat.
Can we deal with him later?
For now, let's
get back to the van.
Last one in moves to Detroit.
Let's do it.
(yelling)
(splash)
♪
Look, guys, it's still here.
Woo hoo hoo hoo, oh baby,
if you were a girl,
I'd marry you.
Man, you said it,
I'd say this babe's
got a heart of gold
and then some.
‐(laughing)
‐Cute.
Come on, guys, let's fix
that flat and split.
(metal snapping)
‐Hmm?
‐(laughing)
You're all mine now, Lupin.
Thanks for the tipoff.
Pretty damn clever of you.
A solid gold getaway car,
that's brilliant.
Well, Pops,
you finally did it.
You caught us
fair and square.
Jigen, Goemon, show the lucky
gentleman what he's just won.
Darn it, we almost
got away with it, too.
Hah!
‐Huh, there's something wrong.
‐How, what's the matter?
This metal isn't gold.
Hmm, what, you've
got to be kidding?
Uh‐uh, our partners
switched the van on us.
They‐‐they got us again.
Well, Lupin, I guess that
makes us both idiots, huh?
That's a kick in the pants!
(laughing)
Hmm?
Dammit, Lupin,
where the hell are you?
Get back here,
get back here right now!
(gulls screeching)
Poor Lupin, he must
be very upset with me.
But, well,
business is business.
(laughing)
To what shall we toast?
It took a lot of teamwork
to accomplish this.
A toast to us.
To us.
Now it's time I should go
and turn all that gold
into hard, cold cash.
Just let me go
powder my nose.
That won't be necessary.
And why not?
Because, my dear, I'm afraid
it's your nap time.
You‐‐you can't mean that‐‐
I'm afraid, my dear, you were
far too drunk with success
to notice just
what you're drinking.
You son of a‐‐
(gasping)
♪
You're standing up.
You were only using me,
weren't you?
Yes, to get Lupin
to help me, of course,
but as you said,
business is business.
‐(laughing)
‐Damn you.
The truth is, my dear,
I'm a very good businessman.
(laughing)
Uh.
(groaning)
Food...water...sunscreen.
Oh man, I'm so glad to be out
of that friggin' forest.
Walking all night,
starving to death,
I can't take another step.
Whoa, a restaurant, woo hoo!
(moaning)
There's nothing like
a nice, juicy steak.
Or some delicious hamachi.
Or a nice fresh
Beaujolais Nouveau.
(sigh)
When I catch that weasel,
I'm gonna pluck his
beard hair out one by one.
Hmm, huh?
Hey, Lupin, look‐‐
it's the golden van!
Jigen, man, come on, get real.
I mean, there's got to be
hundreds of vans like that
all over the city.
Hmm?
Wait a second,
I know him from somewhere.
Hey, that guy's the president
of the First Bank
of Switzerland.
Something I can
help you with?
Drop the act,
Mr. President,
I was still conscious when
you ditched the disguise.
Nobody double‐crosses me.
And for the record,
I liked the old face better.
Well, well, well,
look who's here.
Lupin!
So I guess all of us were just
actors in his little play.
Just give me five minutes
with this guy, Lupin.
Nah, let's not turn a farce
into a tragedy, pal.
'Fraid it's too late
for that, Lupin.
Huh?
♪
I got you,
I got the golden van,
and I've got a pair
of pretty bracelets
with your name on 'em, Lupin.
Sorry, Pops, but this
is your man right here.
(yells)
Quick, let's get
this van in gear!
‐Huh?
‐No hard feelings, Lupin.
Wait, Fujiko!
Come on, get in.
Hey, dammit, stop!
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
(honking)
Freakin' Fujiko, you know,
you just can't
trust that broad.
She sure does
keep it interesting.
♪
(shouts)
Hey, stop the damn car,
do you hear me?
Pull it over,
pull it over!
Nag, nag, it's all he does.
♪
Wha‐‐stop!
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
Oh yeah, mama, work it.
Shake that thing
for your daddy.
(honking)
Huh!
(tires screeching)
(screams)
‐Waah!
‐Fujiko!
(tires screeching)
(yells)
Fujiko!
(water gurgling)
(gulls squawking)
(motor rumbling)
Poor Fujiko.
Are you crying for me?
‐How sweet.
‐Heh?
Oh, Fuji‐ooji,
you're still alive!
Of course, help me out.
Poor baby, grab my hand.
Hold it, Lupin, no way.
She belongs down there
with the sharks.
Hey, come on guys,
nobody's perfect, right?
Everyone makes mistakes.
Come on, Jingy.
Hey, Go‐Go.
Oh, I'm really so
ashamed of myself, guys.
Huh, unbelievable.
It was a brilliant plan,
the whole thing was my idea.
Shut up, you, if you're
so friggin' smart
how come you're here
and Lupin got away, huh?
So, Zenigata gets the gold
and we get the girl.
Uh, don't rub it in.
Yep, that's my department.
♪
Any score's
a score in my book.
♪
♪ Lupin The Third ♪
So this mad inventor
guy named Paolo
threatens to train
his earthquake maker
on the Leaning Tower of Pisa
unless he receives
lots and lots of lira.
But I steal the lira
and things get complicated.
Did I mention Paolo's
really, really ugly?
No dummy though,
like some people.
Next episode: Shaky Pisa.
Toodles.
♪