♪
(pool balls clacking)
(gunshot)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(glass shattering)
(engine starting)
(tires screeching)
♪
(gunfire)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(tires screeching)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(knocking)
Who's there?
It's me.
I'm afraid you're
gonna have to be
a little more specific,
I have a lot of female fans.
(gasp)
(choking)
Huh?
Fujiko?
Wha?
Hmmm.
♪
Mmm, mmm, mmm,
what's the occasion?
I shall be attending
the Kyoransky concert.
And since when
are you a fan?
Since he gave
me this personally.
I had dinner with
him the other night.
I may not know much
about classical music,
but I know sexy
when I see it.
A guy like that could strum
my banjo any old time.
How long did it take you
to come up with that?
You're not jealous, are you?
Of what?
♪
I have box seats,
you can all come with me.
His conducting
is a show in itself.
We'll just wait for
the video to come out.
You can have that box
all to yourself.
Gee, that's too bad,
but I understand.
A diamond‐studded baton
doesn't change the fact
that you find
the music boring.
Hmm, hmm?
You know, Lupin, I don't
know if I've told you,
but I've been
a big classical music fan
ever since I was a kid.
What‐‐you've always been
a ballads kind of guy.
Fujiko, I'm happy
to escort you.
Am I dressed all right?
It's wonderful.
Don't wait up, Lupin.
Uh.
♪
I never told you
about this, Fujicakes,
but I very nearly
took up the bassoon.
(choking)
And I very nearly
took up with a baboon.
Very funny, hmm.
(typewriter keys clicking)
♪
(water spraying)
(applause)
Hasn't even begun yet
and I'm already dazzled.
Wasn't I right?
That thing's
worth two million
if it's worth a penny.
(gasp)
‐(snoring)
‐Didn't you mention
that you were a fan
of all this classical crap?
(yawning)
But they can stay up all night
for some kung‐fu epic.
(snicker)
Hmm?
♪
Incredible.
I've never seen such passion
wedded to such technique.
♪
(snoring)
Hmm?
Fire!
‐(gunshots)
‐What are you doin'?
Aagh!
♪
Don't let
him get away!
(gunfire)
♪
(glass shattering)
(yelling)
♪
‐Aargh!
(crashing)
Looks like Pops
is getting serious.
Better hope so, 'cause
if that ain't serious,
I don't know
what serious is.
‐(applause)
‐Sounds like a standing ovation.
Huh?
Why the hell'd
I pull this out?
(applause)
Kyoransky's even more
impressive than I imagined.
No other artist's work has
ever affected me so deeply.
(applause)
Huh?
(match striking)
‐Hmm.
‐(fire crackling)
I can't get that
concert out of my mind.
Throw on some music,
maybe some Kyoransky.
All right, I don't get it.
What do you
see in that guy?
You're kidding me?
I mean Kyoransky's
a master practitioner
of a sublime art form.
How in the world
could you leave
in the middle of
such a performance?
What are you
talking about, you crazy?
Old Pops was there
and he just snapped.
He was just
spraying lead around
like there's no tomorrow.
Don't you remember?
At a Kyoransky concert?
Oh, man.
Genius at selling himself.
♪
(yelling)
Aaargh!
♪
Die!
Hey, I take it back!
The guy's a
genius, all right?
Aaah!
(needle scratching)
(panting)
‐Wha?
‐Huh?
What happened?
Same thing that happened
at the concert, I'm guessing.
Your mind is being manipulated
by this music somehow.
That's why you all
missed the action.
I was hypnotized?
Yeah, that's why Pops
was acting so strange.
Huh?
♪
Just stay here, Fujiko,
you'll be all right.
I'm gonna take this.
♪
You sure about this?
Uh‐huh.
I mean it all adds up
when you think about it.
A freak attack on us
and hundreds of witnesses
suddenly come down
with amnesia?
Goemon stayed, too.
(humming)
I feel as if I've witnessed a
performance of the ages tonight.
Fantastic.
Huh?
Uh.
‐Argh!
Huh?
♪
(screaming)
(gunfire)
(panting)
♪
What in the world
did I just do?
Nothing, just tried to
Cuisinart us to death, pally.
No hard feelings,
you weren't
in your right mind.
I think it's high time
we paid a visit to the guy
who's messing
with us, though.
♪
Ah, welcome,
I've been expecting you.
You're timing's impeccable.
Come in, I never
lock the door.
Hmm, Mr. Lupin.
(door opening)
Very gracious of you.
Now just who the heck
are you, anyway?
Who am I?
I conduct the
International Philharmonic.
Oh, so the whole murder thing
is just sort of a hobby,
is that what you're saying?
Think of it as an
insurance policy on my part.
Come on, cut the crap.
What's this all about?
I pay a lot
to insure my baton
and I want to make sure that
anyone who thinks of stealing it
pays a high price.
(laughing)
And you thought I
wanted to steal it?
I'm not stupid, I know
when I'm being set up.
I just want to
figure out your trick
for manipulating
people's minds.
Even more difficult.
Good luck with that.
Very sporting, but I
try not to rely on luck.
Please, kindly
use the other door.
Huh, oh, one for entering
and one for exiting.
Hmm.
♪
(glass shattering)
♪ Lupin the Third ♪
♪
(porcelain rattling)
Huh?
Uh.
♪
What the?
Argh!
♪
(glass crashing)
(yelling)
♪
(crashing)
Does he replace
all those chandeliers
every time he kills somebody?
(engine roaring)
(laughing)
This one's especially
fun to play with,
I wish the crescendo wasn't
approaching so quickly.
♪
Sorry to barge in,
but it's important.
It better be,
what is it?
Kyoransky filed a
report with the police
just this morning, sir.
And last night,
Lupin broke in there
and tried to steal
the diamond baton!
Dammit all!
Double the
security immediately!
This department can't
afford an embarrassment
like that on our hands.
Would you authorize
bazookas and tanks, Chief?
Whatever you want.
Thank you, sir,
I'll be in touch.
That's it, Lupin,
you are finished!
(birds singing)
(bull mooing)
Okay, people,
looks like we're ready.
This is Concert
On The Grass, take one.
Nice and steady,
Bobby, all right?
It's magic time.
Okay.
Here we go, Maestro.
And, roll it.
♪
(tank rolling)
Lupin, the masquerade's over!
Take off the disguise!
Thanks a lot.
This wig itches.
♪
Yeah, well you
won't be thanking me
in a second, wise guy.
Take a look behind you,
you're completely surrounded!
(laughing)
♪
Uh.
It's really I
who should thank you
for taking part in
this unique performance.
♪
(banging)
(mooing)
♪
Huh?
(whimpering)
(clopping of hooves)
(mooing)
(bleating)
Huh?
♪
(groans)
I got to admit,
even though I thought
it was the enemy at the time,
I swear I'll never take
the word bull in vain again.
♪
That's a wrap.
Notice the way he
swings that baton around,
you know at the top?
His wind up is very unique.
I am invoking
the goddess of music.
Betcha anything that's
part of the trick.
Hmm.
Hey, not bad.
But what I really
want to do is direct.
Huh?
Oh, man,
I can't believe it.
Here, listen.
It's a virtually
inaudible sound cue,
like a dog whistle
coming from the baton.
It must stimulate or disrupt
some part of the brain
when you're not expecting it.
Here it comes.
There.
That's it.
And then at the instant
the music commences,
people are slaves to
whatever he wants of them.
Huh?
♪
If my suspicions are right,
we'll find that our maestro
planted that sound cue
into every record
he ever made.
Let's see.
Okay, now, let's
just connect this
to the sound
meter like so.
And then,
let there be music.
‐(pulse)
‐Ah‐ha, look.
That one was
the video audio track.
The next one's
gonna be the record.
(pulse)
♪
You're the man.
(laughing)
♪
Oh, man!
(laughing)
I can't‐‐
Somebody help me!
(laughing)
♪
‐(gun cocking)
‐Huh?
♪
Sayonara.
‐(click)
‐Huh?
(chamber clicking)
♪
I was sort of expecting
something like this.
That's why I emptied
out all your bullets.
Huh?
♪
Grrrrr!
I gave yours a little
adjustment too, Goemon,
just in case.
♪
Leave him to me.
No wait, no please, don't!
I'm begging you, Fujiko!
Please come on, you don't
know what you're doing!
You actually love me,
you really do, honest.
You think I'm cute and
kind of pathetic and uh‐‐
Huh?
(gasping)
I, uh, I hope
you understand.
I um, it was just sort of
a precautionary measure.
Uh‐‐
Give me those!
‐(giggling)
‐Shut up!
Ugh.
Oh, stupid adolescent.
♪
Well, excuse me.
Lupin, I'm so
ashamed of myself.
Hey, not your fault.
Anyway, take a look at this.
Okay, I don't understand.
It's a straining
ladle for cooking.
I know that, but
what are you gonna do,
challenge Kyoransky
to a bake off?
No, not exactly, but
I might just have a way
to scoop him up
with this thing.
‐Hmm?
‐Cover your ears, guys.
Good, all right.
(humming)
Boom!
(pulse)
Kyoransky's
baton didn't emit
nearly as much sound as that.
Watch out, Maestro.
You're gonna get
conducted right off stage.
(engine roaring)
A predictable
finale can be redeemed
by inspired play, Mr. Lupin,
so try to put
your all into this.
‐Fine.
‐Very well then,
Beethoven's Third Symphony,
a requiem
for Lupin the Third
conducted by
Momenitz Kyoransky.
How about telling me
who you really are, first?
Not at all, my father
was Momenitz Mulchy.
When he was alive,
he was a master jeweler.
♪
(gunshot)
But you killed
him in cold blood.
♪
I only kill
in self defense,
which means
I don't regret it.
I've been biding my time until
you were drawn here to me.
I knew you'd never
succeed in resisting
the allure of this baton.
Okay, then, enguard.
Ha, what do you
think you're doing?
Oh, I know what I'm doing.
You see, I figured
out how it is
you manage to control people
with that glittering
baton of yours.
It emits a high pitched
sound like a dog whistle,
but you see, the thing is yours
only produces a single tone
whereas mine on
the other hand has um‐‐
one, two, three‐‐
boy, there's a lot.
Anyway, mine's a much better
whistle maker than yours is.
(laughing)
Well, you're amusing
if nothing else,
I'll concede that to you.
Let the amusement
commence then.
(wind blowing)
(tanks vibrating)
(grunting)
(humming)
Boom!
(yelling)
Ha!
♪
Fire!
(cannon blast)
♪
Hmm?
Huh, what's going on?
(fire smoldering)
You want to fill me in
on what just happened here?
Let's see if you can guess.
The first clue
goes like this.
♪
♪ Lupin the Third ♪♪
Serves the
little twerp right,
I mean after all,
he burned me on a job
we did together years ago.
Now he's out of the joint
and it's payback time.
But wait a minute,
that's me in the joint,
on death row, too!
Damn, how'd that happen?
Good question, except I ain't
singin' for no one, you hear?
Find out for yourself
in "Everybody Loves Ramen."
Catch you later.
♪