♪
♪ Lupin the third ♪
(gunshot)
♪
♪ Lupin the third ♪
(birds chirping)
♪
Hey, Lupin.
Phew, how much farther, man?
Uh, well, not much.
Hey, are you sure that
that map's reliable?
Made it myself.
‐Then we're doomed!
‐Huh?
(unintelligible singing)
Let's ask this
upstanding citizen.
(drunken blabbering)
‐Look, I'm dancin'!
‐Uh, excuse me, Baryshnikov.
Is there a palace‐like
building located
somewhere around this area?
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah!
So how's that
humble pie tasting?
So tell me, is there anything
to these rumors we heard
about some fabulous treasure
hidden in that place?
(speaking gibberish)
Well, there you have it.
Hey, it's true, but I
don't even give a crap, ha!
Are you rich or just crazy?
I'm just a guy that
loves being a guy, yup!
(hysterical laughing)
Well that was illuminating.
(giggling)
Hey, get back here, you!
You think you're
any better than me?
You think you'd
do any different?
(burping)
And they gave me a
nice present, so there.
Wonder what it is.
♪
What the?
(coughing)
Help.
♪
(sighing)
‐Huh?
‐Hey!
‐No, please help!
‐She's getting away!
‐Somebody help me!
‐Hold that thought.
‐Huh?
‐Hey, come on, man.
‐Hey!
Keep your eyes on the prize.
(whimpering)
Let go of me, let go!
What the hell's
the matter with you?
You should be
ashamed of yourself!
Someone's being attacked
for goodness sake!
Oh, get back here!
‐Hey!
‐Don't make me the bad guy here.
Look, I'm as gallant
as the next crook,
but it's gonna be dark soon, and
you're the one who's always‐‐
‐Lupin!
‐It won't take five minutes!
You can time me if you want!
Woo‐hoo!
♪
(grunting)
Come on.
♪
Get that guy!
(shouting)
♪
‐Seconds, anyone?
‐Wait up!
‐Hey!
‐Come on!
All right, all right, geez.
‐Oh, please, sir, wait!
‐Huh?
I don't know what to say, I
don't know how to thank you.
‐You just did.
‐What I mean to say is
my older sister will gladly pay
you back for your gallantry.
Thanks, but there's no need.
It was all in a day's
work for me, my dear.
Please, sir, it's a
matter of honor for me.
Sorry, but I never save a girl's
honor twice in the same day.
Oh, please!
Oh, look at that, someone's
got a new playmate.
Now listen, cupcake.
We've got some important
business at the palace,
so maybe you might just‐‐
I happen to live in the palace.
You must be our house
guest, I'm so happy!
Come on, now you can
meet my big sister!
She'll know a way
to pay you back!
Jigen!
Come on, man!
♪
(growling)
(giggling)
(whistling)
Humana‐humana.
(speaking gibberish)
♪
(indistinct conversations)
Oh mommy, I gotta get
your decorator's name!
Excuse me now while
I go get my sister.
In the meantime, please
make yourself at home.
I hope you're hungry.
♪
He's here with a partner.
He fights well, you know.
♪
Don't worry, Lupin's weaknesses
are as impressive
as his strengths.
Hey, as long as I'm right here,
would you mind if I took
a quick look at the treasure?
Oh, why not?
We are sisters after all.
♪
It's so important having someone
you can trust completely.
It can be such
a dangerous world.
‐You know?
‐What're you doing?
Shut up.
You know, you do get points
for ballsiness, sweetheart,
but you lose them for stupidity.
Now who the hell are you?
♪
What about agility, I should
get some points for that.
Now show me where the
real treasure is, sister.
What's so funny?
I'll tell you what's so funny.
You're a very beautiful girl,
but you think exactly
like a man, don't you?
All my treasure
is right in here.
How can that be?
‐Drop it now!
Good work, girls.
Your disappointment
is purely a matter
of ignorance, I can assure you.
But why should you
take my word for it?
I'm happy to share some
with you, in fact, I insist.
♪
Look at her mewing and stamping
her little foot in
embarrassment to us.
Come on.
Hold her head.
That's it.
Hm.
Ew, ugh.
♪
(laughing)
How does that song go?
"You can check out
any time you like,
but you can never, ever leave."
Hey, watch it, you little minx!
Here you go!
What's the matter, big boy?
‐Scared of the water?
‐Hmm.
♪
You can't argue how this
whole thing's played out.
Uh, but it sort of
looks like you'd like to.
Hmph.
And what could you
possibly be upset about?
I don't like it.
Don't know why, but I don't.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Looks like I have my
work cut out for me.
Oh man, and I thought
your sister was pretty.
Yeah, she's pretty and
very young, which is why
I'm so anxious to
convey my gratitude.
Look, we get it, lady, but you
didn't have near enough time
to lay this all on just for us,
so what's the deal here?
Hey, Jigen, geez man, where
the hell are your manners?
♪
Girls, just ignore Jigen.
It's his time of the month.
I'm glad at least one of you
is pleased with our hospitality.
Oh, I'm more than
pleased, I'm pleasured.
A man of wit I see.
Then I'll impose on
you to suggest a toast.
Well, I'll try.
♪
May virtue never
be its own reward.
(chuckling)
That's nice,
but it certainly packs a wallop.
Well, then you just go ahead and
rest your head right down here.
Ah, this is just like when
I was a little baby boy
nuzzling with my dear mama.
You're still a baby yearning
for your mommy's breast.
It's true, you're so
amazingly understanding.
Ow!
(giggling)
Hey, what the hell happened
to our game plan, Lupin?
Will you play a game with me?
Look, I'm talking about the
treasure, or did you forget?
But I've already got
everything I want.
What the hell's wrong
with you, snap out of it!
We've got work to do
here, let's do it!
Hey, what the hell's
wrong with you, man?
These people have
been good to us, man,
and now you want me to
help you steal from them.
I mean, what's up with that?
Ah, I could just‐‐
oh, damn it, ah!
Jigen, I'm warning
you, do not attempt
to harsh my buzz or else.
That's right, let's just nuzzle.
Nuzzle, nuzzle, nuzzle.
Hey, Lupin!
Now, now, Jigen, there's lots
of other girls, you know.
That's not it, I'm saying
we don't have time
for this crap,
ya freakin' moron!
Oh, I've got lots and lots
and lots of time for this stuff.
‐Well, I don't, okay?
‐Okay, too bad.
‐Bye‐bye!
‐That's it, I'm outta here!
Well, if you really
must leave us,
then please accept this present.
♪
Thanks.
Damn it.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
(growling)
I mean, I've seen this
guy make a complete ass
of himself around women
before, plenty of times,
believe me, but
this is the first time
he ever let it get
in the way of work.
‐Huh?
‐No, please, help!
‐What?
‐All right,
just take it easy now, okay?
Hey, what the hell's
he doing here?
(yelling)
♪
Guess you folks had no idea
who you were messing with, huh?
You can run, but you can't hide!
Either that little blonde
cupcake's having a real bad week
or something fishy's going on.
You must let my
sister repay you.
That's really not
necessary, miss.
Please, it's a matter
of honor for me.
It's just up ahead.
I gotta warn Lupin, I knew
something was going on.
It's just his time of the month.
Who gives a rat's
butt about him?
That son of a gun can
just stew in his own‐‐
(growling)
Huh?
♪
What the?
What just happened here?
‐You should thank him.
‐Hm?
♪ Lupin the third ♪
♪
The cruel fate that he
assumed was intended for you.
I don't understand,
what do you mean?
First, tell me, what
happened to Lupin?
In the middle of the job,
he decides the real treasure
is buried under
Mount Venerious.
Unbelievable, so who's this?
You actually met him
on the way up here.
He had the misfortune
of opening his gift.
There's no way this old
guy is Baryshnikov man.
The blonde girl looked
like she was being attacked.
‐I just couldn't stand by and‐‐
‐So it is a scam.
You know, I thought that
incident with Zenigata
looked awfully familiar somehow.
‐Jigen, over here.
‐Huh?
What about these two?
I assume they look familiar too.
You again‐‐Goemon, what're ya‐‐
hey, hey don't!
♪
Holy cross‐dresser!
Just as I thought.
‐Bizarre.
‐And yet, it's less disturbing
than the other way around.
It makes you wonder if there
really is any kind of treasure
in there or if it's all
just a bunch of Amazons
pickin' off the male
population one at a time,
and turning 'em into impotent
old schmegegges like that guy.
(sighing)
And the same thing will happen
to Lupin too if you and I
don't find a way to get
back in there very soon.
Huh?
♪
Oh, damn.
You gotta admit it, Pops.
Trailin' me, it's first
class all the way.
Yeah, but this place
really takes the cake.
Almost makes me wish I weren't
a cop, if you know what I mean.
What do you say we both just
forget about our freaking jobs?
Yeah, let's party, sure!
Yeah, that's the
spirit, old man.
Here's to you,
old buddy, old pal.
(gulping and laughing)
You're a great guy!
Lupin's friends are
still out there.
♪
‐I got nothin'.
‐Don't look at me.
I'm the enigmatic one, remember?
Now listen here.
Our sanctuary is under attack.
Two hostile males are
threatening to penetrate.
(giggling)
Hey, Lupin, where
are you goin', man?
I gotta pee.
What we need to do
is kill them, girls!
Slaughter them
like rabid animals
and then bring me
their heads, now!
♪
Nope.
Phew.
♪
Huh?
I want that damn treasure
and I want it right now!
Hey, I got an idea, maybe I
could dress up in a bikini.
Down‐‐and what, scare
them into submission?
‐Hey, at least I'm‐‐
‐Shhh!
Just behind those
rocks, flush 'em out!
Huh?
♪
‐Fujiko, how‐‐
‐Hold me.
‐Well I‐‐
‐Go on.
‐A most interesting development.
‐Oh, Mr. Lupin.
There are plenty of
healthy women around.
This girl happens to be ill.
Now please, come along,
your friend misses you.
‐Okay, but I‐‐
‐To say nothing
of all the ladies you
abandoned, you big tease.
(gunshots firing)
♪
Okay, bikini boy, cover me.
Damn it, I'm good.
Whoa!
♪
‐What's that noise?
‐Fireworks in your honor.
That's a nice gesture.
(indistinct conversations)
We could use a little more help.
♪
(chuckling)
Say, what's goin' on?
Oh, it's nothing really,
they'll all be right back.
Move in!
♪
Here they come!
(panting)
♪
Just a little more help
and we'll have it licked.
♪
(indistinct conversations)
‐They taking a break?
‐Mhm.
Have some more.
Oh man, this is ridiculous.
How many of 'em are there?
♪
Damn, it sure would be nice
to have Lupin here with us.
But as we're here to rescue him,
of course that
statement's absurd.
♪ Should all acquaint‐‐ ♪
♪ ‐‐quaintance be forgot ♪
What happened to her?
Ooh!
Hey, wait, that's not
a very pretty one!
Would you gentlemen excuse
me for a moment please?
Sure, yeah, course.
Hey, that wasn't
nice, here you go.
(gunshots firing)
Oh crap.
It's that aging gas stuff.
‐Fire two!
‐Let's go!
♪
♪ A man saved a turtle and
followed him all the way ♪
♪ Yes, he followed him home ♪
‐Where's Mr. Lupin?
‐Hm?
‐He's always up to no good.
‐Huh?
Oh no!
♪
My God!
Take a look at you now.
Well, I must say, it
couldn't have happened
to a more deserving pig.
‐Can I please just go?
‐Sure, take a hike.
But I still want a present.
A really, really big one, okay?
Goodness, a pig to the very end.
Very well, I'll give you
the biggest one we have.
It could even double as a
casket for you pretty soon.
(laughing and groaning)
Hey.
I don't like the sound of this.
And don't say anything,
you know what I mean.
That's 'cause I have
a degree in Jigenese.
Hey.
(door creaking)
Take him, he's all
yours now, boys.
‐Holy crap!
‐Poor Lupin.
♪
Hey, guys!
Whoops, hey, where's
everybody, hm?
Hello, anybody, hm?
Hm?
Hm, look at all the
funny masks in here.
I wonder what they...
Hmm, hey!
I just got a real funny idea!
Ahhh!
Hey, Lupin, hold on a minute.
Whatever you do,
don't open this thing.
It's full of that old age gas.
‐Guess again, guys.
‐Hey, man,
‐you made it in one piece.
‐Welcome back.
Thank you.
‐Look what else I found.
‐Fujiko.
The one and only, in the flesh.
I don't get it, how
did she get in there?
She was after this.
Yeah, what's that thing?
Oh, well, just the
real treasure is all,
and they oughta be missing
it right about now.
"Sorry to bail,
it was a real gas.
Well, not really,
but it will be!"
‐Ah!
‐Oh!
(clock ticking)
(screaming)
(coughing)
Doesn't make any sense, I mean,
why go to such elaborate lengths
to protect what's basically
a moonshine recipe?
Oh, this ain't liquor,
it's a narcotic,
and an incredibly
addictive one at that.
‐To enslave the mind.
‐Yeah, that's right,
but it's reserved
exclusively for us men,
which just ain't cricket,
if you know what I mean.
By the way, it seems that
they got Zenigata too.
Did you see him in there?
Oh crap, I forgot all about him!
Pops must still be in there!
Hey, where is everybody, hello?
Hey, you two, don't you know
there's a monster on the loose?
Ahhhh!
‐Huh?
‐Hm?
(yelling)
Sorry, just a little jumpy.
Hmm.
Now, what was I doing before?
Oh yeah, I was with Lupin!
Lupin!
Hey, where'd he‐‐hey, Lupin!
Hey, man, what's
going on, you okay?
Oh, I just can't
help feeling guilty
about what happened
to good old‐‐
‐Lupin!
‐Huh?
Hold it right there, don't move!
‐Speak of the devil.
‐Hey, wait up!
‐You are under arrest!
‐I'm good now.
Let's split.
Hey, I said wait!
That's an order, Lupin!
Hey, wait up!
Lupin!
♪ Lupin the third ♪
That's Fujiko's aunt
there, believe it or not.
A pretty bad temper,
but a pretty good shot.
She strong‐arms me
into joining her plot
to pilfer some booty
the Nazis forgot.
It's called Auntie Ballistic,
make this heavy hot,
and enjoy your new
life as an astronaut.
Catch ya later, or possibly not.
♪