[WARMASTER] Ahh...
I made boom‐boom in my diapey.
[FLASHIKA]
And some wee‐wee.
Aww... Thank you.
Are you going to change me, too?
Not now. We'll have to wait.
Take another look
at his special skills.
Okay.
Those aren't special.
They're ridiculous!
[SEIYA] This explains why
he couldn't leave the capital.
[RISTA]
Uh?
Father! Father, I'm here!
Father!
[WARMASTER]
Rosalie! I missed you so much!
Can you change me? [cries]
Stop staring, you fools!
Kill any remaining enemies!
Or tend to our wounded!
[SOLDIERS]
Ma'am! Yes, ma'am!
[WARMASTER] I beat 'em,
but now I'm itty‐bitty!
Please try to calm down, Father.
If you're a naughty boy,
the monsters will come back.
[WARMASTER]
Monsters are scary.
[RISTA]
Uhh...
[ROSALIE]
What are you gawking at?!
Your dad is just the
cutest little baby is all.
This is a curse
from the Demon Lord!
It's in no way cute!
‐‐[RISTA] A curse?
‐‐[WARMASTER] I'm scared!
[WARMASTER]
Pick me up!
[RISTA] What else can
you tell me about the curse?
[ROSALIE sighs] Listen.
I've got my hands full now,
but meet me at the
castle in two hours!
Sure, guess we'll see ya then.
Let's investigate
the town in the meantime.
I'm sure someone else would
know more than this idiot.
[ROSALIE]
Ugh! What'd you say?
Yeah, I think
we'd better go, Seiya.
[ROSALIE growls]
[SHOPKEEPER 10A]
Landlocked fish, right here!
[SHOPKEEPER 10D]
We got deals, deep and cheap!
[SHOPKEEPER 10B] Warmaster's
special! Five percent off!
Here's to our man,
the Warmaster!
[RISTA]
I'm guessing they don't know
about the whole babyfication
thing goin' on.
I wouldn't think so.
He's a lot cuter this way.
All they know is he took
out that last Heavenly King,
which just leaves the
Demon Lord to contend with.
It just doesn't seem
real to me, though.
[gasps] Look, a bar!
Seiya, why don't
we pop in for a bit?
You think we should
dull our senses
right before the
biggest fight of our lives?
I just thought we could
take in the festive ambiance.
Like hearing and
smelling drunks?
Besides, there could be a brawl
where someone gets stabbed
to death with a broken bottle.
So... hard pass.
I've never met such a
pathological worrywart.
[BUNNY GIRL] Come up
and see me, why don'tcha?
[MASH]
A bunny girl!
[ELULU]
Is her mom or dad a bunny?
[RISTA]
What about going in there?
Casinos are always fun,
so whaddaya say?
I don't gamble.
And frankly, I'm surprised
you'd assume any differently.
[RISTA grunts]
It could be worth it!
There's actually a
pretty good chance of getting
some kind of awesome weapon
or piece of gear if we win!
[SEIYA]
Rista.
If you truly think we can get a
weapon that'll be effective
against the Demon Lord
as a prize in a casino,
then your brain
must be the size of
the little ball
in a roulette wheel.
You're one to talk about balls!
[ELULU] The casino
sounds pretty cool to me!
Come on, Seiya,
having a tiny bit of fun
isn't gonna hurt, ya know.
Plus, I think it would make
Mash and Elulu really happy.
[SEIYA] Our time would be
better spent at a weapon shop.
You're supposed to be a goddess,
so why don't you think
about the world a little more?
[RISTA] Ugh! I'm always
thinking about it!
Which is exactly why we
need to take a breather!
Oh, please. It's really
no wonder why Valkyrie told me
that you were
a third‐rate goddess.
Why are you bringing
Valkyrie into this right now?
It's not like I don't already
know that she's better than me‐‐
she's stronger, higher ranked,
and even sexier!
Let's calm down, Rista.
I am extremely calm!
And I'm cool!
Hello, sir. Are you interested
in some Greater Medicinal Herbs?
They have triple the
effect and healing power
of the regular kind.
[SEIYA]
If you're lying about that,
I'll burn your shop down, okay?
It's the truth! But I don't
appreciate the threat,
so do you wanna
buy some or not?
[SEIYA]
Hm... I'll take a thousand.
[RISTA]
You don't need those!
I mean, I am a goddess
with healing magic, Seiya!
[ITEM SHOP OWNER 10A] Hey!
My greater medicinal herbs
are way better than any
ol' restoration magic!
No way!
My magic's a billion times
stronger than your dumb herbs!
We'll see about that!
Hey, come here, man!
You look pretty beat up.
I am‐‐had a run in with
the Demon Lord's
monsters earlier today.
Scrapes on his arms
look about the same.
So why don't you
and I have a race
to see who can heal him quicker.
Eat my healing dust!
[ITEM SHOP OWNER 10A]
Let's go!
[RISTA growls]
[RISTA] Take flame
to this man's wounds
and cleanse him
with my Megamic Power!
[WOUNDED MAN 10A]
Wow.
Those GMH healed me
up insanely fast.
[RISTA]
Fine, I lost.
Great job Goddess of Healing.
Hey, I'll take some of that GMH.
Actually give me all
that you have in there.
[ITEM SHOP OWNER 10A]
All right, thank you!
[RISTA] This is bull! My magic
is awesome! I want a rematch!
[MASH]
It's okay, Rista. Try to relax.
You still have your
little doll thing, right?
[RISTA] Oh, shut up,
you stupid mushroom,
mashed tater, whatever you are!
[MASH] Hey. It's not my
fault you suck as a goddess!
[ELULU]
Mash, that's too far!
You need to apologize to Rista.
[SEIYA]
Cut it out. Let's get going.
[ROSALIE] Before we
go in and see my father,
there's something
I need to talk to you about.
But first, I want to know what
happened to the legendary armor.
It was eaten by
a massive turtle.
Say what?!
It's not time for jokes!
Look, I don't do jokes.
But the point is, the thing
doesn't exist anymore.
But how could that've happened?
I'll spare you the details.
What's done is done.
Anyway, what did you
need to talk about?
Well, it's about my father.
The Warmaster, Wohlks Roseguard,
has been fighting off demons
for over 30 years.
Earlier this year,
as he was turning 80,
he headed off to
defeat the Demon Lord.
But along the way,
and for unknown reasons,
he was turned into an infant.
My men and I had to rescue him.
[SEIYA]
Okay.
Is there some other
point you're getting at?
[ROSALIE] My father...
doesn't have very long.
[MASH, ELULU]
Hm?
The Warmaster... is very
respected throughout the land.
I just want this
time to be peaceful.
Whenever he returned
from battle
he'd be tired,
but he'd always pick me up
and give me a pat on the head.
He'd be so warm and loving.
[ROSALIE]
All I'm asking is if Father says
he wants to fight the
Demon Lord alongside you,
please tell me that
you'll persuade him not to.
You don't need to ask me.
Last thing I want is an
old geezer slowing me down.
Okay. I see.
But please...
...don't call him that!
You have my thanks,
Goddess and Hero.
I appreciate you coming here.
After killing the Heavenly King,
I don't remember what happened.
But that aside, now that the
Four Heavenly Kings are gone,
are you planning to attack
the Demon Lord's castle?
I am.
But I don't really need
your help with that, okay?
[RISTA gasps]
[WARMASTER gasps, chuckles]
I suppose that you don't.
Why would you seek
assistance from an old man?
Father.
Huh?
[ROSALIE] You've done more
than your fair share already.
The hero will finish
what you've started.
[WARMASTER]
Hmm... Indeed.
Perhaps I could stay here
and show the fair goddess
around our legendary cathedral
instead of trying to
fight a young man's battle.
[MESSENGER 10A]
I have an urgent message!
[BOTH gasp]
[MESSENGER 10A] Survivors
from the Demon Lord's army
are attacking the capital!
I must go stop them at once!
‐‐[ROSALIE] Father!
‐‐[SEIYA] I'll do it.
‐‐[BOTH gasp]
‐‐You're the king after all.
You should probably
stick around the castle.
[WARMASTER]
But I‐‐
Don't sweat it, pops.
Just show the goddess your
awesome cathedral or whatever.
[RISTA]
What the heck?
So now I'm just supposed to
teeter around with baby grandpa?
[SEIYA] Since you two have my
stuff, you should come with me.
‐‐[MASH] Oh, yeah.
‐‐[ELULU] Sure...
‐‐[RISTA whimpers, sighs]
‐‐[WARMASTER sighs]
[WARMASTER]
Many years ago,
I heard a legend
about a goddess appearing
to someone who'd save the world.
I was so taken by it
that I built this cathedral.
I suppose I thought
of myself as that hero.
But now it seems that
my role won't be so grand.
[RISTA] Your people
definitely see you as a hero,
and you're much more heroic
than a certain someone. [sighs]
Are you and your hero not
getting along very well?
That's putting it mildly!
"You're so useless!
You suck, bro."
Ugh! He's always
putting me down,
and it makes me wanna
punch his perfect face in!
Oh, I see.
Sometimes the more
talented a person is,
the more twisted
their personality can be.
But let me ask you something.
As a goddess,
are you aware of the reason
why the gods are
able to live eternally?
No, all I really
know is we can't die.
[WARMASTER] The soul
currently in your body is‐‐
let's call it a virtual soul.
Your real soul
is stored in a room
within the Divine Realm
where time stands still.
If you were to
die in this world,
only your virtual soul
would be affected.
As long as a goddess's real
soul is in the Divine Realm,
she will continue
to live on forever.
By the same principle,
if a summoned hero were to die,
he would simply return
to his original world
where his real soul remains,
safe from harm.
You know a lot about this, huh?
[WARMASTER] Well, I've learned
many things in this long life.
In fact, I've
recently discovered...
...there's a magical item
that relates to this subject.
Oh, really? There is?
[WARMASTER] Yes.
It is called Chain Destruction.
[RISTA]
Uh...
[WARMASTER] A powerful
and frightening thing.
If it's used to
destroy a virtual soul,
it causes a chain reaction
that eliminates
the real soul as well.
So if this item
really does exist,
then both Seiya and I
could actually die for good?
[WARMASTER]
Correct.
I happen to know
that the Demon Lord
has already created
a Chain Destruction.
[gasps]
[WARMASTER] Not only that,
he's successfully produced
the ultimate weapon
with which to apply it.
[WARMASTER]
A weapon that can shatter
the soul of a hero
and kill a goddess.
I give you God Eater‐‐
a deity‐slaying sword!
[RISTA gasps]
[WARMASTER] You are
going to die, dear goddess.
As long as you're in this world,
the hero can escape to
the Divine Realm at any time.
I must block his retreat.
[RISTA] But I don't understand.
Why are you doing all this?
Obvs, because old age sucks.
When I went on my journey
to end the Demon Lord,
I thought it would bring
about my end as well.
However, the experience
left me a changed man.
The Demon Lord had
seen through everything.
He knew that my failure
to realize my life's dream
had cultivated a darkness
deep inside my heart.
His power was
absolutely overwhelming.
I found myself in complete awe,
like a newborn babe seeing
the world for the first time.
He had given me this rebirth.
And now I worship
the Demon Lord.
The one who brings
death as well as life.
But since I once venerated you,
I will show you mercy
and make your death
swift and painless!
[WARMASTER yells]
[gasps]
Well, well. Such quick reflexes.
[RISTA whimpering]
[RISTA screams]
[RISTA] Hold on, is this
guy really gonna kill me?
[RISTA screams]
No. No way.
This can't be happening.
[WARMASTER]
Hm? Are you afraid to die?
Even though you're a goddess,
I suppose you're
still a young girl.
You poor scared creature.
No, please! Help me, Seiya!
He can't.
Now, return to
nothingness. Begone!
Come on, Seiya!
[RISTA]
Aw, man.
Honestly,
I kinda hate that we were mad
the last time we saw each other.
‐‐[arrow whizzes]
‐‐[RISTA gasps]
[WARMASTER gasping]
I can't believe my father
would try to kill a goddess.
Are you okay, Rista?
Master said he
shouldn't be trusted.
[WARMASTER gasps]
It's you!
[RISTA groans]
[WARMASTER] Well, I'm surprised
you decided to show up here.
[SEIYA] Keep your creepy
old hands away from her.
[RISTA gasps]
I need her safe,
because if I didn't have Rista,
I...
I wouldn't be able to go home.
[RISTA]
Oh, yeah, I guess that's true.
[RISTA groans]
[MASH, ELULU groan]
[MASH]
Whoa, you all right?
[RISTA]
What're you guys doing here?
Seiya said he was
worried about you
and made us come back to check.
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐[WARMASTER] Is that so?
Do you have some sort of
precognitive ability, Hero?
All I can do is explore
every last possibility.
The hell does that mean?
[SEIYA] What if that
Heavenly King, Eraser whatever,
was faking his death?
Or what if he really did die,
but then he came
back as an angry ghost?
What if the Demon Lord has
some weapon that can kill gods?
What if when you
went to kill him,
he gave you the hypothetical
god‐killing weapon.
And what if you had
decided to use that weapon
to kill the goddess so you
could trap and kill me, too?
Now, what if you, the Warmaster,
are my real enemy?
[RISTA] Whoa. If that's
his internal monologue,
then how does he sleep at night?
Oh, well, that's my Seiya.
And what if that goddess
is some kind of imposter?
[RISTA]
No! No! I'm the real deal!
[WARMASTER laughs] So all
this wasn't the result of logic,
or cunning, or even intuition.
You came back just because
you're pathologically cautious.
[ROSALIE]
Father! Please stop this!
[WARMASTER]
Don't interfere, Rosalie.
If you do, I will not
hesitate to cut you down.
Father.
[WARMASTER]
It has been my lifelong dream,
but the fact is,
I was never destined to become
the hero that saves the world.
So I will simply have
to take joy in being the one
who slays that hero!
Watch out!
That sword will kill you and
destroy your soul back on Earth!
You'll be dead‐dead!
Huh. I'll just have
to kill him, then.
Mode: Double Eternal Sword!
[gasps]
[ROSALIE]
Father!
[RISTA]
Ew. Gross!
[WARMASTER laughs]
It seems that my frail, old body
is on the brink
of withering away.
If I can reclaim
my former glory,
I'll offer everything
I have to the Demon Lord.
Along with the God Eater sword,
he gave me this this
Demon Spirit Orb as well.
[WARMASTER cackling]
Wait, so now he's a Demonkin?
I must say this
Double Eternal Sword of yours
is quite the
formidable technique.
However, I've already
adjusted to it.
[GROUP gasps]
[WARMASTER]
Style: Evil Light!
[gasps] Eternal Sword EX!
[grunts]
[WARMASTER] Oh, you defended
yourself with just one sword.
I bet you've never really
had your back against
the wall before, have you?
[RISTA] When did he pick up ol'
goth goddess's ultimate move?
[WARMASTER chuckles]
The Demon Lord
told me something.
He said that the
world you come from
is relatively peaceful and you
don't know what war really is.
So, boy, I'll gladly show you
the sheer brutality of battle.
[SEIYA]
I wanted to save this
for my fight
with the Demon Lord.
[RISTA] Huh?
What are you do‐‐ Ah!
[RISTA]
How freakin' heavy are those?
How the heck did you even
find enough room on your body
to fit all of those things?
[SEIYA]
Spare Platinum Sword Plus, now!
Comin' up!
This is gonna be hell on
my arms, but, oh well.
It's now time for
Double Eternal Sword EX!
[RISTA] Oh, since
he took of those weights,
he should be hella fast.
This'll be a breeze.
So, you ready,
or you need a minute?
Well, actually I do,
but I will be ready soon.
Mode: Double Eternal Sword EX
Phoenix Blade Meg‐‐ Let's go!
The attack name was
too long to even finish?!
Who cares!
Stomp his brains in, Seiya!
Heh. Engage Style: Evil Light!
[RISTA]
This is crazy!
Even my goddess eyes
can't follow them!
But... I'm pretty sure
Seiya has the upper hand?
Your strength is incredible!
But too bad for you.
It's not enough.
I've adapted.
[SEIYA grunts]
[RISTA]
Elulu!
You need to cast your quick
spell to make Seiya even faster!
‐‐[ELULU] I can't!
‐‐[RISTA] Huh?
I've already cast it on him.
I did it before the fight,
'cause he's so cautious.
Oh, no.
[ELULU]
He's gonna be okay, isn't he?
He's gonna make it, right?
Of course he is,
he did say he was perfectly
prepared like always.
[gasps]
[RISTA]
Uh‐oh.
He didn't say the damn catch
phrase this time, did he?
Rista! I'll help him!
Me, too. We'll stop that demon!
‐‐[SEIYA] Stay back!
‐‐[GROUP gasps]
[SEIYA]
You'll die!
[grunts] Crushing Evil Light!
[RISTA]
Seiya!
[WARMASTER chuckles]
Your overabundance of caution
and timidity may have kept
you alive for this long,
but you will not survive this
fight on those traits alone.
[SEIYA]
Phoenix Thrust.
[GROUP]
Uh...
It won't be enough! [yells]
[ALL gasp]
[ELULU screams]
[WARMASTER]
Are you learning, boy?
This is what it
truly means to do battle.
And in this moment, you're
frozen with pain and fear!
[RISTA]
Seiya, move!
[gasps]
How can this be?!
You should be
crying out in pain.
Why are you not
begging for mercy?
You may want to pretend
that nothing's happened,
but without that arm,
you have no chance of winning!
I'm not the only one
here who's missing an arm, bro.
[WARMASTER gasps]
[WARMASTER groans]
I used the Ninth Valkyrja,
Counter Break.
It takes a designated body part
and returns any damage inflicted
back to where it came from.
I may have no sword,
so I'll use my fist!
Phoenix Thrust!
[gasps]
[WARMASTER groans]
[WARMASTER] I don't believe
this. What the hell is he?
He behaves like a warrior who's
faced death time and again.
[WARMASTER groans]
‐‐[RISTA, ELULU] Seiya!
‐‐[MASH] Master!
Go on and fix my arm, Rista.
The herbs I bought
won't be enough.
[RISTA gasps]
Yeah, of course I'll help.
That's gotta hurt pretty bad.
Hurts like hell.
Least I didn't pass out.
When you got that little
scratch from the reaper,
you made me heal you so fast.
You got all whiny then.
I thought you were soft as tofu.
You're missing the point, Rista.
Getting healed just means I
have a better chance of winning.
[RISTA giggles]
[WARMASTER cries]
Oh my god, this feels like a
million bees stung my shoulder!
Hear that? Your old man's
crying like a baby.
He doesn't deserve
to be called my father!
Rista, go and heal
the geezer's wound.
[ROSALIE gasps]
I guess I can do that.
Oh. My most humble
thanks, fair goddess.
[RISTA]
Okay. He's all healed up.
But, uh...
[SEIYA]
Great. That's it for us.
Rosalie's gotta
take it from here.
He is not my responsibility!
He sold his soul to the
Demon Lord, and I won't‐‐
He's the shame of the kingdom.
He tried to kill the goddess,
and destroy the world‐‐
‐‐[thudding]
‐‐[ROSALIE groans]
[SEIYA] If there's something
you need him to know...
...you're running out
of time to tell him.
[WARMASTER]
Sweet Rosalie.
[ROSALIE gasps]
Daddy still loves you.
[WARMASTER]
I'm so sorry.
Father, I‐I forgive you!
So, please, just this last time,
pat my head like you used to.
Father.
[WARMASTER]
My darling Rosalie.
I love you very much.
[ROSALIE crying]
[RISTA] Three days later it was
announced that Wohlks Roseguard,
the mighty Warmaster,
had passed away from old age.
The throne now
belongs to Rosalie,
who should make
a pretty decent leader‐‐
as long as she keeps
the barking to a minimum.
[RISTA] Hm. Thanks
for everything, Seiya.
[MASH]
He okay?
[ELULU] Yeah, he's been
asleep for a few days now.
He's fine. His wounds
are totally healed.
[ELULU, MASH]
Hm...
You guys should stop worrying
and go have some
fun in the city.
[ELULU]
Huh? Are you sure?
Yeah, check out the casino.
You know this weirdo
will just wanna train.
[BOTH]
Rista...
I told you two to stop worrying!
I think we can agree
this guy who walks around
like he's got a stick up his
butt does enough of that for us.
When he wakes up
from his lil' nap,
I'll make sure he
doesn't throw a fit.
After all, he is my lackey.
[MASH]
Look behind you.
[RISTA]
Hmm?
‐‐[SEIYA] I'm your what now?
‐‐[RISTA yelps]
Anyway, we need
to talk about our plan
before we go fight
the Demon Lord.
Okay, everyone listen carefully
as our wise leader
makes his big speech!
[MASH]
What about the casino?
Have you got mashed
potatoes for brains, kid?
This is the worst time
for fartin' around like that!
[MASH, ELULU groan]
I barely made it out alive
from that Warmaster fight.
That means I'm gonna
have to train even harder
if I really wanna take
down the Demon Lord.
[RISTA]
Yeah, that's a great idea.
You train your little heart out.
[MASH, ELULU]
Ugh...
[SEIYA]
But before I start training,
let's take a little
time for some RnR.
[MASH, ELULU gasp]
Hold on a sec.
What did you just say?
I said rest and relaxation.
It won't be any big deal
to take a couple days off.
You're saying we
could go play around
at the casino
or something? Seriously?
[SEIYA]
Knock yourselves out.
That sounds amazing!
You gotta come with us, Seiya!
[SEIYA]
Yeah, I've earned some fun.
Seiya...
[SEIYA] First, I'd like to look
for some synthesis materials.
But we can head out for
some laughs later tonight.
[RISTA] Finally! I've been
wanting to blow off some steam!
I mean we were due
for an amusement park,
or beach or hot springs and just
let our brains turn to jelly!
[ELULU]
That sounds scary!
[RISTA] Ya know, we're always
training, training, training,
or fighting, fighting, fighting!
But not today!
We're gonna party
ourselves stupid!
[MASH, ELULU]
Oh, yeah!