Yeah, mind running
that by me once more?
Elulu will fulfill her
destiny of becoming Igzasion
by offering up her life.
Wait! Igzasion is
some kind of weapon.
What's that gotta do with her?
[LEVIAE]
Everything.
This weapon will
defeat the Demon Lord.
The blade shall only manifest
when a Dragonkin girl born human
sacrifices her life in exchange.
Screw the legend!
Elulu shouldn't have to die!
[LEVIAE] Seventy percent
of the world is already
under the Demon Lord's control.
‐‐[BOTH gasp]
‐‐[RISTA] Seventy?
Hordes of monsters
devour the innocent
while evil Demonkin
burn down entire towns.
Giants have been destroying
one castle after another.
Some small villages remain,
but almost every kingdom
has been overthrown.
The one surviving stronghold
is Roseguard Castle.
Any safe locations you've
seen recently will fall soon,
if they haven't already.
With all the back and
forth to the Divine Realm,
we haven't really had a chance
to assess the
situation properly.
[LEVIAE]
'Tis only a matter of time
before the whole world
is under their control.
If the Demon Lord is not slain,
Gaebrande will be doomed.
Elulu.
I must admit, I envy you.
You are the power that
will save us from this evil.
The sacred sword to
strike down the Demon Lord.
One of the highest honors
among the Dragonkin!
Thank you. It's my pleasure?
[LEVIAE]
The sacred sword ceremony
shall take place tonight.
Feel free to spend the
remaining time you have
among your friends.
Are you sure about all this?
All this? You mean...?
[MASH] It would be
awesome to save the world,
don't get me wrong.
But... do you have
to die for that to happen?
If that's my destiny,
then what choice do I have?
She said that it was
a pretty big honor, too.
[MASH]
Maybe so, but still.
[ELULU] All I've ever
wanted was to be helpful.
This may not be how I pictured
it, but my wish is coming true.
Elulu...
Hey, Rista!
The only reason you came here
is to save our world, right?
That means my sacrifice
will be for a goddess, too!
Kinda.
[RISTA] I didn't realize
how bad things were until now.
I know my mission is
to defeat the Demon Lord
and save this world,
but at what cost?
Hey, Seiya?
[ITEM VENDOR 06A] Yes, sir!
We call these speed seeds!
Won't find a product like
this in any human market.
For every seed you consume,
your speed increases
for a solid ten minutes.
[SEIYA] You better not be lying.
If so, you'll regret it.
I'll sue your scaly ass.
[RISTA]
You're so selfish!
Maybe try considering
someone else for once?
You know,
take Elulu for example?
[SEIYA]
What's to consider?
She's gotta do
what she's gotta do.
[BOTH gasp]
[SEIYA] Why should I even
have to say anything about it?
[ELULU]
That's true.
You're right! This is
my destiny, not yours!
‐‐[MASH] Elulu!
‐‐[RISTA gasps]
[music playing]
[LEVIAE] There is no
need to stand on ceremony.
The villagers who
prepared this feast
would be saddened if
you did not partake.
Fine, but where's Elulu?
The chosen one is getting ready.
She will be with us soon enough.
That's good to hear.
[RISTA sighs]
‐‐[DRAGONEWT BOY 06A] Hiya!
‐‐[BOTH] Huh?
We made cookies!
Please try some!
Sure! Thanks so much!
We did our very
best making them,
so I hope you'll try one, too!
Eat one or suffer!
[BOTH]
Hm?
It is time.
‐‐[RISTA] Uh? Huh? Ha?
‐‐[SEIYA] Mm.
[MASH gasps]
[LEVIAE]
And now, it is upon us.
Let the sacred sword
ceremony commence!
The Dragon Abyss‐‐
within, the magic circle created
by the first Dragon Emperor.
Once the girl leaps, her flesh
and blood will be assimilated,
transforming her into Igzasion!
The blessed blade
will bring with it
an end to the Demon Lord!
[DRAGONEWTS cheering]
[RISTA]
Poor Elulu.
No. Not yet. Stop this.
Well, I suppose
this is goodbye, huh?
Oh, and Seiya?
I'd hate to rust,
so make sure you polish me
once I become your sword, okay?
Child! Make haste!
Throw yourself into the Dragon
Abyss and fulfill your destiny!
[DRAGONEWTS shouting]
[MASH]
Is this really what's right?
Oh, Mash.
I don't care if
she's saving the world.
I can't let her do this!
[MASH gasps]
[MASH]
Move it!
[MASH grunts]
[MASH]
Let go of me! Hey! Stop it!
Mash! Oh, no!
Please, listen!
My dear, you're not having
second thoughts, are you?
Shall we encourage her?
[ELULU gasping]
[RISTA]
Hey, let her go!
What you're doing
now is just murder!
[DRAGONEWT 06A]
This is a blessed day!
[DRAGONEWT 06B]
Into the Abyss!
[DRAGONEWT 06C]
Igzasion!
This is like a cult mentality.
[MASH]
Don't do it! Elulu!
[DRAGONEWTS]
Igzasion! Igzasion!
[LEVIAE] Come! Let us cast
the girl down into the Abyss!
‐‐[ELULU whimpers]
‐‐[DRAGONEWT GUARDS laughing]
[gasps]
[DRAGONEWT GUARDS groan]
[LEVIAE gasps]
[LEVIAE]
What have you done?
You're here. But why?
I said I shouldn't
have to say anything.
What? Do I gotta
spell it out for you?
You're supposed to
carry my equipment.
You can't do that if
you're a stupid sword.
I don't care about either
one of their destinies.
They made a commitment to me.
Yeah, but if Elulu
doesn't become Igzasion,
what are we gonna do?
[SEIYA]
It's fine.
We don't even know if this thing
is real, much less all powerful.
[DRAGONEWTS gasping]
How dare you?
The first Dragon
Emperor foretold it!
And you believed him?
You do realize
that makes zero sense.
Sounds like some lame
lizard on a power‐trip.
What?! You impudent buffoon!
[laughing]
[LEVIAE gasps]
What do you find so amusing?
Surely you're not as
absurd as this "hero."
Surely you intend to save this
world and thwart the Demon Lord!
Of course!
I swear to you, we will still
find a way to rescue this world!
But we refuse to sacrifice
the life of our friend
in the process!
There's some way to defeat
the Demon Lord without Igzasion.
And if anyone can
do it, Seiya can!
Such a shame.
You are as daft as
the hero you champion.
You think nothing of our
plight and only of yourselves.
Our world may already be lost.
Screw you, you hag!
The real selfish
one here is you!
[MASH grunting]
Elulu, just hang
in there‐‐ [groans]
[RISTA]
No!
Mash, are you okay?
Huh? This is weird.
[LEVIAE chuckles] Thankfully,
I am rather cautious.
I had a hunch
this might transpire,
which is why the
food you ate earlier
was laced with a paralytic!
[DRAGONEWT BOY 06A laughs]
Those cookies we made you
had that paralysis
stuff baked into them, too!
No spell or antidote
can counter this.
Why, even the goddess
has been affected!
[RISTA gasps]
[RISTA]
None of us can move?
[LEVIAE] Now then, let us
proceed with the ceremony.
Will someone take the initiative
and cast Elulu into
the Abyss, please?
[DRAGONEWT GUARDS chuckling]
Get outta there!
No! Stop! Get your
damn hands off her!
[gasps]
[DRAGONEWT GUARDS groan]
[LEVIAE]
What? He can move?!
Impossible!
How are you even
standing at all?
Your special ingredient
can't work if I never ate it.
[DRAGONEWT GIRL 06A]
Liar! I saw you eat a cookie!
Yeah, but did you see me hurl it
back up like five seconds later?
[BOTH gasp]
[SEIYA]
The thought of some slimy lizard
making my food was grody
enough to make me barf.
[DRAGONEWT BOY 06A]
Hey, that's rude!
[SEIYA] Says the twerp
who just tried to poison me.
I was onto you long
before now though.
Besides, as a rule,
I only eat food made by that
indecent immortal over there.
[RISTA]
I have so many feelings!
I mean, not actual feelings,
what with the
poison and everything,
but paralysis can't
freeze the heat between us!
[RISTA cackling]
[RISTA] Seiya, I'll make
you a million snacks
if you keep lookin' like one!
[LEVIAE]
You leave me no other choice.
I have no wish to get violent
with he who shall
bear the sacred sword,
but I will do what I must.
Seems I must knock some
sense into your unoccupied head.
Fine. Come at me, bro.
So confident.
However, you should
not underestimate me!
Behold the magnificence
of the Chosen Dragonkin.
Dragon God Metamorphosis!
[RISTA yelps]
[LEVIAE roars]
[RISTA screaming]
[ELULU whimpers]
[RISTA] Bleh! That HP hurts!
She's too strong!
[laughs] The scales of a dragon
are tougher than any
metal known to man.
Ordinary swords don't "cut it"
in any sense of the phrase.
You may have fought monsters,
but we dragons are
in a league of our own!
‐‐[SEIYA] Yo, Taters.
‐‐[MASH gasps]
[SEIYA] You packed that
thing in this bag, right?
Yes, sir!
[LEVIAE]
Inconceivable!
How does someone like you
have a Dragon Killer sword?
I would have to be
pretty freaking stupid
to willingly walk
into a dragon's den
without some sort of
dragon slaying weapon.
[RISTA laughs] I don't
think I've ever been so happy
to have such a paranoid hero!
[MASH]
That's awesome, Master,
but where'd you
even get that thing?
[SEIYA]
Synthesis, duh.
I used a platinum sword,
a strand of hair
from you and Elulu
since you're both Dragonkin,
and then I helped myself to
a hundred of Rista's hairs.
[RISTA shouts]
A hundred?
How did you get your hands on
that many of my precious hairs?
By plucking them from you while
you were sleeping, of course.
[RISTA gasps]
Run that by me again!
You did what
while I was sleeping?
[RISTA]
Oh, that jerk!
He's lucky he's hot
while he's ignoring me.
Get it together, Rista.
He needs to concentrate
on fighting. Calm down.
Remember, after
all this is over,
you're gonna make
him spill his guts!
Atomic Split Slash attack!
[LEVIAE groans]
I did not expect so much damage,
even from a Dragon
Killer! And yet!
[grunts]
[ELULU gasps]
[LEVIAE grunts]
[LEVIAE]
Not bad.
[RISTA]
Hey, be careful!
You wouldn't wanna
crush the main ingredient
for your super sword!
Really? Nothing says
the girl must be alive
when she enters the Abyss.
All that is needed is her
flesh and blood, nothing more.
You suck!
Yes, I see.
You will protect the girl
no matter what the cost.
What a shame.
I am rather cautious though.
[gasps]
No, Elulu!
What's your scaly
butt up to now?!
[LEVIAE chuckles] I triggered
the Death Sentence Necklace.
The instant its black
light encircles her neck,
Elulu's life will
be snuffed out!
[RISTA gasps]
[LEVIAE] Enjoy your last three
minutes amongst the living.
A cursed item?
Curses aren't cautious at all!
[LEVIAE]
The child is destined to die.
I act to save our entire world!
Screw you!
[SEIYA]
Hey.
Listen, Lamezilla.
You're not with the Demon Lord,
so I'm giving you
one fair warning.
Lift the curse you
put on her or else.
Oh, you fascinate me.
Issuing such threats even
though I hold all the power.
The sword ceremony is fate!
To lift the curse and defy fate,
you will have to kill me!
Sounds good.
Then I guess I can
stop holding back.
Phoenix Drive!
[LEVIAE yells]
[RISTA]
He's frying her to a crisp!
Let's see.
Snap dragon!
He's nearly got her
down to half her HP!
[LEVIAE laughs]
[LEVIAE] There is no denying
how strong you are, hero.
But it will take more than brute
strength to reverse a curse!
[LEVIAE] I have activated
my Ultimate Wall
and assumed this glorious form!
Your attacks will now
have the same effect
as a light, passing breeze.
[SEIYA] Then I'll just
have tear that wall down.
[gasps]
[LEVIAE]
Wh‐‐
Aw, he looks like
a lil' hamster, but sexy.
[SEIYA]
Speed seeds, baby.
[RISTA] A second Dragon
Killer? Seriously?
This is my spare one.
I like to have a
backup just in case,
but I can also use it for this.
Go! Double Eternal Sword mode!
[RISTA] He's combining
the Eternal Sword technique
with a bag full of speed seeds
and dual Dragon Killers?
[LEVIAE chuckles] If you
believe yourself ready, hero,
then come on!
[SEIYA]
Sure thing.
[LEVIAE gasps]
[RISTA]
Go, Seiya! You're doin' great!
[RISTA gasps]
I don't get it!
He's barely even fazing her!
[LEVIAE chuckles]
[LEVIAE] My Ultimate Wall is
the supreme hardening technique.
Take pride in the
insignificant damage
you have managed to cause.
Speaking of futile...
The child has nearly
succumbed to the curse.
There is no saving her.
Why not cease this
senseless struggle
and accept the inevitable?
Seiya. That's enough, okay?
[RISTA]
Elulu!
I appreciate it.
I can see how hard you're
fighting to save my life.
But you can stop
it now‐‐ [gasps]
[RISTA] Oh, no. Maybe she
is destined to be a sword.
It just doesn't make sense
that we'd have to go so
far to save this world.
[LEVIAE] It is time
you admit defeat, hero,
just as it is time Elulu dies!
Justice will prevail!
[SEIYA] You're right.
Justice will prevail.
[LEVIAE] And just what
do you mean by that, hero?
[LEVIAE gasps]
[SEIYA]
And you call yourself cautious.
Gimme a break.
[DRAGONEWTS gasping]
[LEVIAE] Stop this at once!
Cease your advance!
Lift the curse, and he'll stop!
It's not rocket science!
[LEVIAE]
How perplexing!
Why go so far to protect
such a useless whelp?
The only worthwhile contribution
she could ever hope to make
would be in the form
of the sacred sword!
Otherwise, she is
nothing but scum!
She's not scum.
[RISTA, MASH, ELULU gasp]
She hauls bags.
Scum can't do that.
It's true.
[RISTA] Well, that may not have
been sweet or even very nice,
but at least it was genuine.
I guess I'll
speak my piece, too.
Release her!
Or kiss your
dragon butt goodbye!
[LEVIAE groans]
[LEVIAE]
All right! I forfeit!
The curse has been lifted,
so halt your attack!
[ELULU groaning]
[LEVIAE]
Fool! The only thing I lifted
was my Ultimate Wall!
You shall die, too!
Dragon Breath!
Double Wind Blade!
[LEVIAE gasps, groans]
[LEVIAE] True, I may
have lost my footing,
but I still have my wings!
[LEVIAE gasps]
[LEVIAE]
No! My wings!
But‐‐ But how?
[yells]
[ELULU grunts, gasps]
Yeah, that went well!
That nosedive must've ended
both Leviae and her curse!
[MASH]
Elulu!
You're okay!
[MASH gasps]
‐‐Sorry!
‐‐No, don't worry about it.
[MASH]
I think I'm still paralyzed.
[ELULU]
It's fine.
[MASH] How long before
this stupid drug...
Just curious.
When exactly did you
damage Leviae's wings?
It was before she activated
her Ultimate Wall ability.
I had a feeling she'd switch
to defense pretty early on.
My normal strategy would've been
to take her out hard and fast.
But her HP was almost god tier,
so I had no choice
but to improvise.
I focused on backing
her into a corner
and cutting off
any means of escape.
This forced me
to deal with her wall,
but it also supplied
me with a distraction
she couldn't help but fall for.
And here I was thinking you
couldn't get any more cautious.
Well, I had a source monster.
Uh?
Helped shape my strategy.
That dragon lady sure
was a lot like a Nurikabe.
You're clueless about slimes,
but a bro‐it‐all about Nurikabe?
Yeah, that and Hyosube.
I can't believe
that crusty lizard lady
thought she was cautious.
If it were me, I would've
had my Ultimate Wall up
back during the feast.
[RISTA]
Right,
because that wouldn't have
been suspicious at all.
[DRAGONEWT 06A]
Leviae. How can this be?
What are we going to do?
[ALL gasp]
[LAGOS gasps]
What is that?
[RISTA]
Oh, look!
The magic circle in the Abyss
must've turned
Leviae into a sword!
[SEIYA] She did say that
Igzasion required the flesh,
blood, and life of a female who
bore the blood of the dragons.
As bogus as it sounds,
she's become a sword.
Which would mean...
[ELULU gasps]
[SEIYA]
Get Rista to heal you.
Elulu's flesh and blood
are part of the sword now.
[DRAGONEWTS gasp]
[DRAGONEWT 06A]
How positively divine!
[DRAGONEWT 06B]
No doubt about it! Just look!
That's it. Igzasion!
The blade that will
defeat the Demon Lord.
Pretty sweet accomplishment
you Dragonkin just
nabbed for yourselves.
There's nothin' like a win‐win.
But Leviae just tragically
met her demise. [gasps]
She would have wanted
to offer her life
if it meant saving the world.
She even said so herself
when she was alive.
Well, I suppose that's true.
So it's a win‐win.
No one is sad.
Really? Because I feel sad.
You guys got what
you wanted, right?
So if you have Igzasion and
you know it, clap your hands.
[RISTA sighs] And we're
right back where we started.
Thank you so much, Seiya!
I've never been that
scared in my whole life!
Knock it off, short stack.
[ELULU gasps]
You good?
You know something?
Please don't laugh, but when
they told me I was going to die,
I was most sad about not being
able to talk to you ever again.
Whoa. I felt the same!
[RISTA] Is it just me
or is there some serious
chemistry in the air?
Love and adventure do
tend to go hand‐in‐hand.
Hey, guys, I have an idea!
[ELULU, MASH]
Huh?
[RISTA] Why don't you
two go on ahead of us?
'Kay, but why would we do that?
You just said you like
talking to each other.
Besides, Seiya and I need
to have a little chat also.
[MASH]
Oh, okay.
Right. We'll wait
over by the entrance.
Aww! Isn't that the cutest?
Not my thing.
Whatever!
We really do need to have
a little chat though.
It's about your Dragon Killers.
So, uh, you plucked
out 100 of my hairs?
[SEIYA]
So? What if I did?
I swear, if you make me go bald
because of your stupid sticky
fingers, you will regret it!
You didn't do anything else
while I was asleep, right?
What do mean by that?
[RISTA gasps]
Well, you know, there
are all sorts of things
that can happen while a lady
is unconscious and vulnerable.
I'm not like that
and you're not a lady.
[RISTA grunts]
That doesn't make it okay!
You can't just steal
someone's hair, you freak!
You're lucky I'm
not pressing charges!
What do you think
would've happened to Elulu
without those two swords?
Quit being so dramatic.
Hold up! We are not done here!
I think we are.
That sword.
It's not really Igzasion, huh?
[SEIYA]
What?
Did you forget I'm a goddess?
I can sense that weapon
is severely lacking
in sacred power.
You just might be smarter
than you look, blondie.
Because you're right.
This thing isn't Igzasion.
It's a Platinum Sword
Plus I made myself.
You lied to an entire
village about that sword.
Wanted to put
their minds at ease?
You know this is gonna have to
stay our little secret, right?
[RISTA] I know. I'm just
wondering if Leviae was right.
What if Igzasion
is the only weapon
that can defeat the Demon Lord?
Then we'll just have to
kick his ass some other way.
I mean, you said so
yourself, didn't you?
I was kinda caught
up in the moment.
It's gonna be okay. Have faith.
[gasps]
[SEIYA]
Let's go.
The dragon brats are waiting.
[RISTA] All right,
that was definitely
the most un‐Seiya‐like
thing I've ever heard.
Maybe he's tired and
not thinking straight.
Once we get back to the village,
we'll catch up on some sleep.
Hey, we got company.
Like a lot!
[KAIZEL] All is in readiness,
precisely as you commanded.
The hero will be of no
significance to you now.
[XENOS LORD]
Good.
We will now have the ability to
destroy even the gods of heaven.