[ARIA] Hmm, sounds like
a bit of a predicament.
Yup.
He's got the strength and stats
to take out a Heavenly
King pretty quickly.
But all he does...
Blast the pecs, crunch the abs,
and wail on the glutes.
That sexy meathead probably
has muscles for brains, too.
I understand your frustration,
but he can't keep
that up forever.
So you mustn't worry yourself.
[gasps]
[RISTA]
Holy G cups, how is anybody
supposed to concentrate
around those things?
I mean, I know I'm not
sporting salad plates,
but she's got me beat
in looks and experience.
[RISTA sighs] Being a wannabe
big shot is getting old.
I just wanna take control of
Gaeabrande and be more like you.
I may have a high rank,
but you shouldn't want to be me.
[RISTA] Don't be so
modest, you're perfect!
You're Ariadoa,
the super‐veteran,
saver‐extraordinaire!
You've summoned heroes to, like,
300 worlds and saved them all!
Not quite. Unfortunately,
there was one I couldn't save.
Well, one out of 300
is still incredible.
I could totally
live with that ratio.
[ARIA]
But they can't, Rista.
The people who lived on that
world‐‐many lost their lives.
We can't afford
that kind of mistake.
Yeah. You're right about that,
but you know what I mean.
It was just a difficulty
level B world.
So the mission should've been
very easy for me to complete.
And yet, I still
made a crucial error.
You tried, and uh...
Oh, forgive me for
bringing the mood down.
I'm going to fetch us more tea.
Would you like some?
Yes, please. That sounds good.
‐‐[door opens]
‐‐[BOTH gasp]
So this is where
you've been hiding.
[RISTA]
Hey!
So I can't walk in on you
but, uh, you can do it to me?
[clattering]
Look! You see what you've
done by startling poor Aria!
He's fine.
I mean, I'm fine.
[RISTA gasps]
[RISTA] Is she a chump
for his looks, too?
Stupid womanizer‐‐
no worse, goddessizer!
Hello. You must be the hero
that Rista summoned here.
[SEIYA]
And you are?
My name is Aria. I'm the
Goddess of the Seal, Ariadoa.
You appear to be
in quite a hurry.
Is something the matter?
I've been exercising
to boost my level.
But as hard as I try,
I can't get it up.
Yes!
[RISTA] He's hit a
wall on working out.
You shouldn't worry.
That kind of thing actually
happens to a lot of guys, Seiya.
Its time you stopped
beating on yourself
and start beating the monsters.
Combat? I don't know.
It sounds awfully
risky if you ask me.
It's like a hero's entire
job description, so...
Ya know, instead of all that,
how about you make me
some dumbbells and stuff
to help me get swole?
You've gotta be kidding me,
Seiya! That is not the problem!
You need to go out
and get some experience
or you're gonna
hit the wall again.
Well, what do you suggest I do?
[RISTA]
First, clean out your ears
and then go fight
some creepy crawlies!
[ARIA]
Oh, I have an idea.
What do you think about
having one of the gods
in the Unified Divine Realm
help you out with some
training exercises?
No disrespect, Aria, but
that sounds like a crazy idea!
[ARIA]
If he's going up against gods,
there's no risk
of getting killed.
And he'll gain more XP than
from fighting small monsters.
It's my backdoor loophole.
I do like the aspect
of minimizing the risk.
[RISTA]
Aria, come here a sec!
Are you sure you
can promise him that?
I didn't know that
gods were even allowed
to take part in training.
[ARIA]
It doesn't bother me,
and I'll also double
check with Ishtar
to make sure there's no problem.
[RISTA] That's great, but who's
gonna do the actual work?
Neither of us knows
a thing about fighting.
I'm a healing goddess and
you're a goddess of the seal.
We're both clueless.
It just so happens
that I'm looking at
a god training his heart
out right over there.
[RISTA]
Huh?
Him?
[CERCEUS grunting]
[RISTA] He kinda disrupts
the whole "serenity" vibe.
But he refuses to go and swing
that thing somewhere else.
[CERCEUS grunting]
[RISTA] He's stubborn
Divine Blade Cerceus.
Yes, but perhaps he'll
be persuaded to help us.
[RISTA sighs] This isn't
adventure or saving a world.
[ARIA] You're working
hard as ever, Cerceus.
Well, well, well,
if it isn't Ariadoa and
Ristarte, and good ol', uh...
I'm guessing that
you're a human?
You must be a hero
they've summoned.
Look here.
It's not a good idea for
a human to go walking around
the Unified Divine Realm,
even if you've been invited.
[ARIA]
Cerceus, we've come to ask you
if you would train
this hero for us.
Since you're such
a high‐ranking goddess,
I suppose I have no choice
but to honor your request.
But still...
Listen up, human.
I need to warn you that
my training is very intense.
I have serious doubts anyone
but a god would be
able to handle it.
Yeah?
We'll just see if you're still
this cocky after we spar, bro.
You'll be too busy crying like
a little girl to talk smack.
What? You're gonna
eat those words,
you emo‐looking
piece of diaper bait.
[SEIYA] Just shut up
so we can get going.
Huh? Uh... yeah, with pleasure.
What the realm's his problem?
[RISTA] Whoa, Seiya's already
got him on the defensive.
I just hope his mouth
hasn't written a check
his butt can't cash.
Cerceus the Divine Blade
isn't some low‐level nobody.
This training sesh may
be a lesson in humility.
Not necessarily
a bad thing for a hero.
First off, why don't you
show me what you can do?
[yells]
[CERCEUS grunting]
[CERCEUS]
Ah.
So you can keep up with me
for a few seconds at least.
[CROWD chattering]
[RISTA]
I'm worried about Seiya,
but I if I go over
there and check on him,
I know that he's just
gonna moan about it.
[RISTA gasps]
[RISTA]
Oh, Cerceus!
So, uh... how's he doing?
[CERCEUS] Hmm. For someone
who gives so much lip,
he can actually back
it up for the most part.
It's impressive.
Ya don't say!
But he still can't hold
a candle to my skills!
[RISTA] Wow, some encouraging
news, for a change.
I know how to pick 'em!
I'm bored. What am I
supposed to do all day
while Seiya's busy with
his super‐special training?
[RISTA gasps]
[CERCEUS muttering]
[RISTA]
Hey there!
How are things on the
ol' training scene?
Oh, well, uh,
just fine, I guess.
[RISTA] Yeah. I'm not
totally buyin' that.
Two days‐‐that's all it took
for that cheeky bastard
to build up a terrifying
amount of power.
Ah, that does sound like Seiya.
He's got that XP boost
skill thing going on for him.
[CERCEUS grunts]
If I went all out, I'd wipe
that smug look off his face.
You could, but I think it
would go against the rules
of the Divine Realm if
you used your godly power
against a human like that.
[CERCEUS]
Yeah.
It might actually be
worth breaking the rules
if it meant I could win a round.
Huh? I didn't quite catch that.
Uh, nothing important, really.
I just said, he's kind of
a decent competitor, is all.
[laughs, coughs]
Is this getting a little
awkward, or is it just me?
[CROWD chattering]
[RISTA]
Huh...
Uh?
[CERCEUS sighs]
[RISTA]
Excuse me, Cerceus?
[CERCEUS]
Huh?
[RISTA] Have you lost
a couple of pounds?
Not on purpose.
Well, never mind.
So, uh, how has the
training been coming along?
Oh, uh, it's not so bad.
Okay... But, like,
"not so bad" in what way?
I'm saying it could be worse!
'Kay, forgive me for prying,
but I'm gonna need quite a bit
more information than just that.
I summoned him,
so he's my respon‐‐
[CERCEUS yells]
How about you drop it
and let me eat in peace?!
Fine! Sorry I asked!
‐‐[GODDESS 03A] Hear that?
‐‐[GOD 03A] 'Course I did.
[GOD 03B]
So loud.
No, uh, I'm sorry.
[RISTA]
Huh?
The big guy was looking
kinda sickly yesterday.
I wonder if he's taking
the day off or something.
I'll deliver these snacks
and check in on Seiya
while I'm at it.
Don't mind me,
I'm just sneaking in to get
some nori for my rice balls.
Help yourself.
[RISTA] ♪ Get the nori,
get the nori for my balls. ♪
[RISTA humming]
[gasps]
[yelps] Whoa! Cerceus?
Shh. Keep it down!
[RISTA]
Is something the matter?
Because it kinda looks like
you're hiding under there.
It looks that way
'cause it is that way.
[RISTA]
Oh.
You need to listen
carefully, okay?
This guy, your hero? Nut job.
It's true. I'm well aware.
[CERCEUS] I told him that
he's done enough training.
But he says, "nope, not yet!"
That's all he ever says,
and he won't let me go.
He's relentless. I haven't
had a chance to rest.
That explains a lot, honestly.
I even told him that
he had gotten three
times stronger than me.
But he won't stop till he's
a hundred times stronger.
It's insane.
That guy's a berserker.
No, a berserker probably
has more of a heart than him.
He's... He's like
a super berserker!
This is where
you've been hiding.
‐‐[CERCEUS gasping]
‐‐[RISTA screams]
I said that you could
go and eat lunch,
but it doesn't look like
you're eating to me.
Oh, sorry, I can explain.
I, uh, was impersonating nori.
‐‐[RISTA] Huh?
‐‐Yeah!
[RISTA] That might be the
stupidest thing I've ever heard!
Oh, yeah? You're
done now, right?
Not yet. I clearly
have more work to do.
I'm more like wilted
seaweed at this point, so.
[SEIYA] We've wasted
too much time already.
So we're gonna have to power
through with no more breaks.
No... No breaks at all?
Sorry, sir, but I'm spent.
Please. No!
He's lost it!
[CERCEUS]
I hate this sword!
[CERCEUS grunts]
[CERCEUS]
I never wanna see it again!
The Divine Blade
really hates his sword?
[CERCEUS]
I can't even stand to look
at those damn hard,
pointy things anymore!
[RISTA] He's still
talking about swords, right?
I despise them!
[gasps]
[CERCEUS]
Somebody, help me!
[RISTA]
Wait! Seiya!
He doesn't wanna do this!
[ARIA] I've been
looking for you, Rista.
Ishtar wants to
have a word with you.
[RISTA]
Hm? Seriously?
[ARIA] I don't know about what,
but I'm sure it's important.
I'm really, really
sorry Cerceus,
but I gotta go now.
Just tough it out
a little longer!
No, wait! Please don't leave
me alone with this psychopath!
So, Ristarte, I understand
your hero has been training
with one of your fellow gods?
Yes, he has.
But apparently, Cerceus
has decided to just give up.
In all honesty, he's having
a full‐blown meltdown over it.
[ISHTAR chuckles]
Not too surprising.
Cerceus used to be quite
a fainthearted man.
[RISTA]
Huh? Hold on.
Are you telling me that
he's a reincarnated human?
I mean, I always just
kinda took it for granted
that he was born a god.
No, in fact, he was
once a human swordsman.
Of course, when he was reborn,
he lost all memories
of his former life.
But those feelings etched
deeply into the soul‐‐
they do have a habit
of being persistent.
After having such harsh
demands wear him down,
it seems that the weaker part of
his soul was exposed somewhat.
In that regard, one could argue
that the experience
has been good for him.
Things can have a strange
way of working out.
Seiya wasn't the one
being trained, after all.
[chuckles] Enough about them,
let's get to the real reason
I asked you to come here.
I need you to travel on to
the next town immediately.
The next town? Has something
else happened on Gaeabrande?
The village I chose for
you as a starting point
was a relatively
safe place at the time.
However, the Demon Lord
was aware of our plans
and sent a powerful
enemy to greet you.
And now I can sense
that the next village
is in imminent danger
of attack as well.
[RISTA]
Why does it seem like every time
she looks into the future
it's something bad?
There will be some
very important allies
anxiously waiting on your hero's
arrival in the town of Seimul.
Really? I wasn't expecting that.
It's true. So I ask that you
hurry to meet up with them.
Do you think you could
do that for me, Rista?
Yes, of course!
I'll get right on it!
Okay, no matter what
kind of a stink he raises,
we are going, and that's final!
Gird your loins!
We're goin' to Gaeabrande!
[RISTA gasps]
[RISTA yelps]
[CERCEUS groaning]
Why are you going
full primate on him?!
You need to cut
that crap out right now!
I didn't ask for your
opinion on my technique.
It's part of the
training anyway.
Yeah? Well, color me surprised.
This is what you guys do?
You train him on
your back like that?
[RISTA gasps]
Why is he just laying there
sobbing and not saying anything?
You need something or what?
Yeah, in fact I do.
Gaeabrande is in
immediate danger.
So stop whatever
you're doing here,
because we're going right now!
[SEIYA]
Whatever. Fine with me.
I think I've gotten all
I can outta this guy, anyway.
I am... perfectly prepared.
That's right. I'm 100
percent ready for this.
Great. But first...
...apologize to Cerceus
before the trauma fully sets in!
Okay, this town
is called Seimul.
According to Ishtar,
we have allies waiting
for us at the church,
so let's get over to them.
[TOWNSPERSON 03A]
Everyone, hurry!
[TOWNSPERSON 03B]
Get out while you can!
[RISTA]
Hold on a second, please!
Is something happening?
[TOWNSPERSON 03C] Krain Castle
to the northwest has fallen!
This town's about to be
flooded with the undead!
[TOWNSPERSON 03D] You should
just keep on movin', lady.
[SEIYA]
So, what are the undead?
Obviously, they're dead things
that can move and attack,
like zombies, for instance.
They're pretty hard
to beat with just swords.
Well, then how do
you kill them, Rista?
Fire spells and splashing them
with holy water is good, too.
Ah, holy water.
[ITEM VENDOR 03A]
Holy water.
If you're dealing
with those undead,
you'll need to get
yourself some of that.
[RISTA] So glad you
shopkeepers are still around.
We can't let the undead
keep us from makin' a living.
[ITEM VENDOR 03A chuckles]
You'll need all you can carry,
'cause ya don't wanna run out.
[SEIYA]
You're right about that.
I'll take a thousand.
Hey, buddy, I know you said
you don't wanna run out,
but this is overkill.
I mean, you just gotta splash
a little bit on each one of 'em.
You're not gonna be
dunking 'em in this stuff
or anything, ya know.
That's the reason it comes
in those tiny little vials.
I don't think ya could
carry that many on ya.
Even if you could, the weight
would definitely slow ya down.
And besides, I don't
have anywhere close
to a thousand of those
vials in stock today.
Well, then you better
order some right now,
'cause if not, I'm gonna
tear off that ascot, broseph.
We'll just take ten!
It's not enough.
It is, too!
Besides, I'm starting to sense
those undead guys
getting closer.
We gotta hurry and meet
our friends at the church.
[SEIYA] Heh. They'd better
make it worth our time.
[RISTA] Listen, when I talk
about meeting our friends,
you're supposed
to get all hyped up!
Please, don't be a jerk.
Ah! Who's there?
My stars... You're a goddess,
aren't you? You must be!
There was a sign from
God that you were coming,
so we've been anxiously awaiting
your arrival ever since then.
These two are descendants
from Dragonkin,
which means they have
dragon blood in their veins.
They will be teaming
up with our hero
and together they'll
defeat the Demon Lord.
[RISTA]
Dragonkin descendants‐‐
exactly the kind
of allies we want!
[gasps]
Greetings, brave hero.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Father Marth. Pleased
to make your acquaintance.
Ah!
[groans]
Hey, whaddaya doin' that for?
That stuff's for the bad guys!
[SISTER]
Oh, Father!
[MARTH gasps, groans]
Seiya?!
[MARTH yelling]
[RISTA]
Ew.
Hang on. Doesn't
that only happen
when it's used on
undead creatures?
Crazy. So the hero was
able to tell he was one?
That's totally amazing!
[MARTH growling]
[MARTH]
I should've expected the one
who killed Chaos Machina
to be so cunning.
My plan was to
slaughter the lot of you
once I'd gained your trust,
but this changes things!
No matter. I can still wipe out
all of you in one fell swoop!
My undead power was
bestowed on me by Deathmagla,
one of the Demon Lord's
Four Heavenly Kings!
And now I shall use
it to destroy you!
[MASH grunts]
Bring it on, ya bastard!
Yeah! You gotta
deal with me, too!
How long has Father Stank
Mouth been at this church?
Uh, he came over as a
missionary from Krain Castle
just a couple of days ago.
[SEIYA]
I see.
So this dude's not one
of the local townspeople.
What are you doing?
Get over there and help our
friends make him dead again!
[SEIYA]
You don't have to yell.
For your information, I've
already immobilized the enemy.
[MARTH yells, gasps]
[MARTH]
What's happening?
Look at that. Even
when I tear you apart,
you don't bleed. You just
sound constipated.
Are they all like you?
[MASH]
When the hell'd you cut him up?
[ELULU] I didn't even
see you draw your sword!
[RISTA] I never saw him
use his sword, either.
Maybe whatever he was doing with
Cerceus was actually training.
But what I really don't get...
[RISTA]
Hey, how could you tell
he was one of those
undeads anyway?
[SEIYA]
I used my brain.
[RISTA] Duh. So, like,
how did you use it?
[SEIYA]
The priest was the oldest
and most feeble person here.
He'd be dead soonest,
which means he'd
also be undead soonest,
so I gave him a little shower.
You're saying you used logic
and reasoning to destroy him.
I don't get it!
That wasn't logical at all!
Oh, isn't our little hero
so damned clever?
Well, Deathmagla's undead
army is gonna come put an end
to your stupid
victory celebration!
‐‐Huh?
‐‐[MARTH chuckles]
And I'm not talking about
just a couple of zombies.
Tomorrow morning
there'll be 10,000
ready to eat your
brains for breakfast!
Ten thousand undead coming?
And they'll be here
by the morning?
[SEIYA] Yeah. Thanks
for translating everything
that we literally
just heard, genius.
I'm going to need
to clean this mess up.
Since cutting you up
didn't shut you up,
I'll have to be extra thorough.
[gasps] Everyone, run!
Huh, but why?
[SEIYA grunting]
[ELULU]
What's he doing?
[RISTA]
Just run! Trust me!
[SEIYA yelling]
[SEIYA]
Maximum Inferno!
[RISTA]
And there he goes!
[RISTA groans]
[RISTA] He always goes
overboard on the cleanup,
but the fight is like
an afterthought. [gasps]
Is "cleanup" even
the right word?
He just blew it up.
The historic church of Seimul
has been reduced to rubble.
You're welcome, Sister.
I single‐handedly saved
all of you for free.
[RISTA] Yeah, 'cause you
wiped out the whole church!
And the poor nun probably
just died from the shock!
That's one way to do it.
This guy's pretty weird, huh?
But lucky for us,
he's super strong.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Hero.
My name's Mash. I'm a warrior
with Dragonkin blood.
And I'm Elulu. I've known Mash
since we were both little kids.
I'm a mage, and I also
have Dragonkin blood in me.
How about we all
work together, okay?
What's your name, Mr. Hero?
Seiya. Seiya Ryuuguuin.
Uh?
[ELULU gasps]
[SEIYA]
Hmm, this one's human.
Uh...
What're you doing?!
Him, too.
[SEIYA]
Cool. Human.
Probably not a good idea
while she's unconscious.
Uh!
Hey! What did you
pour it on me for?
I had to be sure you hadn't
turned undead at some point.
‐‐[RISTA] Yeah? Like when?
‐‐This guy's got a trust issue.
Uh‐huh, more like a problem.
Huh?
Hey, wh‐why are you
staring like that?
[ELULU]
Yeah, what's the deal?
You're being super
creepy all of a sudden!
[RISTA] If these two are
supposed to be our allies
on this adventure,
we gotta see those stats.
This isn't what
goddesses and heroes do!
[ELULU]
You're really scaring me!
[RISTA] Not all that
impressive, to be honest.
They don't have a fraction
of what Seiya's packin',
but I guess they
have room to grow?
It'll be nice to have these guys
on the team, don't ya think?
Urgh.
No way.
But they have Dragonkin blood,
so once they go through all
the steps and learn Dragon
Metamorphosis, they'll be fine‐‐
No way.