[MASH grunting]
[RISTA gasps]
[ELULU gasping]
‐‐[ELULU] Oh! Mash!
‐‐[MASH] Hello!
[ELULU] Thank goodness!
I was so worried about you!
[MASH]
Uh, where am I?
Safe and sound at Seimul's inn.
To recap, you went
unconscious on our way out.
That's really all
there is to the recap.
‐‐[door opens]
‐‐[ALL] Huh?
Well, look who
decided to wake up.
Thanks. You didn't
have to save me,
but I'm glad that you did.
Dry your tears, little diaper
baby. We're moving out now.
You get to carry my stuff.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[RISTA] They're supposed
to be his allies,
not his personal sherpas.
Yay! I love toting things!
This'll be fun, Mash, right?
You know, this whole
ordeal's taught me
a very valuable lesson.
Our levels are leagues apart.
Anyone with eyes could see that.
That's why...
[MASH] ...I want to be
your part‐time apprentice!
While remaining a full‐time
bag boy, of course. Please!
[SEIYA]
Just carry my things
and don't embarrass
me, or yourself.
[MASH] Your benevolence
knows no bounds!
[ELULU] Thank you for
all your help, Seiya.
[MASH] You idiot!
You refer to him as Master!
[RISTA]
Not my ideal kind of party,
but I guess things could've
turned out a lot worse.
This might seem
kinda out of the blue,
but there's a place I'd really
like to take you to, Master!
Oh! I bet you're talking about
Dragons' Den, aren't you?
Why would we go there?
According to Nakashi
Village lore, 16 years ago,
a dragon descended from the
heavens, carrying two babies:
Elulu and myself.
[ELULU] Legend says we're
to team up with a hero,
and defend Gaebrande
from a terrible evil.
It's said we need to break
the seal in the Dragons' Den.
Only then will we be granted
a mighty weapon
to aid in our quest!
[gasps]
Oh, Seiya loves a mighty weapon!
Yeah. But I'm already packin'
three enhanced platinum swords
thanks to your premature
balding issues.
We can discuss your
hair hoarding later.
Besides, just when you think
you have the very best,
something even
better comes along!
I think we should check
this thing out for ourselves.
‐‐Forget it.
‐‐[OTHERS] Uh!
We need to make a major pit
stop before we go anywhere.
You're kidding me. Seriously?
[ELULU] Wow! We're really
in the world where gods live?
Whoa! This is insane! [gasps]
They have rings
floating over their heads!
Are they angels?
Would it be okay
if we go exploring?
Don't be dumb.
We came here to train.
[RISTA]
I don't see him anywhere.
You'd think someone
so big and bulky
would be a lot easier to spot.
[CERCEUS gasps]
[yelps]
Whoa, what's with the apron?
[SEIYA] Care to tell us
what the hell you're doing?
Oh, hey there, Seiya!
Not sure what business
you could possibly have
with a retired swordsman
such as myself. Heh.
I mean, blades are dangerous.
There's a good chance
I'd bleed out if I got cut!
[RISTA] The Divine Blade
is afraid of swords now?
Great work, Seiya.
[CERCEUS]
But! Not to worry!
I've been keeping busy
by learning how to bake.
Here's a cake I just
finished! You want a bite?
Nah, bro. That's gross.
How can you know
without tasting?
I worked so hard on this.
I'll bet you'll have a bite!
Uh, hard pass.
It looks like it tastes
like sweat and sad.
[CERCEUS]
How would I even bake that?
I'm gonna need you to focus.
Look, I didn't come here to
dump on your lame hobbies.
Tell me.
You still have your
day job, don't you?
That should come first.
What's my day job?
[SEIYA]
This, obviously.
[CERCEUS] That's not my
day job‐‐it's a nightmare!
[MASH] This guy seems
a little unstable.
[SEIYA]
Relax, pee pants.
I won't be the one you
train this time around.
He will.
[RISTA]
Look at that.
Seiya's almost being what
some would call considerate.
[SEIYA] I can't entrust
my bags to a weakling.
My equipment would
be ganked for sure.
[CERCEUS] Got yourself
an apprentice, did ya?
Uh, mind if I see
your abilities?
Sure, knock yourself out.
You weren't using that
pesky Fake Out skill
just now, were you?
I'm afraid I wasn't. [gasps]
Kid! You're in for
some intense training!
I'll run you so hard your
muscles will have muscles,
little guy! [laughing]
What is your deal, man?
I think the chains on your
mood swing just snapped!
[RISTA] Back to normal after
he see's he outclasses Mash?
Man on the outside and
fragile flower on the inside.
Sweet if it wasn't so sad.
[HESTIACA] So. You're asking
me to teach this young one
in the art of
flame magic, correct?
I'd greatly appreciate it,
if you could.
[HESTIACA] It's our divine
duty to support humans
attempting to save their worlds.
I'd be delighted to help you.
Um, thank you.
My name is Elulu.
It's an honor to make
your acquaintance!
[HESTIACA] Such pretty
red hair. Much like mine.
[ELULU gasps]
Let's try and calm
those nerves down, yes?
[SEIYA] Okay. That takes
care of those two.
All that's left to do now is to
find someone who can train me.
[RISTA] I was wondering
how long it'd take
to bring it around back to him.
[RISTA gasps]
Oh, I'm so sorry‐‐
[VALKYRIE]
Hey, blondie!
Ya need to watch
where you're walkin'.
Even a scrub goddess like you
should be able to manage that.
Valkyrie! Please forgive me!
It won't ever happen
again, you have my word!
That reminds me.
You got stuck bailing out
a world with an S Class
rank, didn't you?
That's pretty
ambitious for someone
who can't even put one foot
in front of the other.
[RISTA]
Well, you might have a point.
I mean... [yelps]
Good thing your bouncy plumpers
more than makes up
for your faults.
And you've got some big faults!
[RISTA]
Please stop.
I'm not a piece
of fruit, you know.
‐‐All right.
‐‐[RISTA grunting]
I guess I'll let
you off the hook.
But be more careful from now on.
[VALKYRIE laughing]
I feel violated.
[SEIYA] You get picked
on in this world, huh?
I do not!
Valkyrie just treats
everyone like that!
[SEIYA]
I gotta say,
I sensed some serious power
coming from that exhibitionist.
[RISTA]
Please don't even think it.
That was Valkyrie,
the Goddess of Destruction.
She's the most fearsome goddess
in the Unified Divine Realm.
There's no way she'd train you.
For a human,
talking to her is enough
to risk instant annihilation!
[SEIYA]
Hey, chain‐kini. Train me.
[screams]
I know you're not talkin'
to me in that tone!
The fact that you're
a hero won't stop me
from tearing you apart!
Yeah? I wish you would.
[RISTA]
Please lock it up, Seiya!
How 'bout you apologize
and we can be on our way!
Apology? But what would
be the point of that?
Since I'm gonna scatter his
remains across the entire realm!
No! Have mercy!
[ARIA]
Oh, pardon me!
[gasps]
[RISTA]
Aria!
Valkyrie, please.
I bid you stand down
and refrain from fighting.
As if I would!
This level of insolence deserves
a punishment equal
to a thousand deaths!
The mortal you keep
threatening is a special hero
who was summoned to save an S
Class world in the utmost peril.
Please put your anger
aside and let this man be.
In deference to myself, the
high‐ranking goddess, Ariadoa,
please, unhand him.
[VALKYRIE] If you're gonna
make a big scene about it,
I'll let 'im go,
but in return...
...I get to give
those chest moo‐moos
a nice massage sometime.
Uh! Okay.
That was a whole new level
of senseless, even for you!
Seiya, you really
are something else.
Hey, I got a question.
Do you talk smack to
everyone or am I special?
[gasps] I meant no offense.
So, rumor has it, you're on the
hunt for a new divine trainer.
I may know of a candidate,
if you're interested.
Meet the Goddess
of War, Adenela.
In terms of combat,
she's a little more
advanced than Cerceus is.
[RISTA] Ah. It's nice
to meet you, Adenela.
[ARIA, RISTA]
Uhh...
Well, then...
If you're not too busy, would
you mind training up this hero?
[ADENELA]
T‐Train?
[laughing]
You want me to train a human?
You're kidding. [chuckles]
[RISTA] I'm gonna need
to see some goddess ID,
because this girl is...
Disgusting.
Disgusting as hell.
[RISTA] You're not
supposed to say it out loud
even if we're all thinking it!
Hey, you know, I find some
small joy in training.
Sure. I'll train the human.
[RISTA, ARIA gasp]
[ADENELA giggles]
I see you were able to
follow my movements just now.
I wonder if your mind
is as sharp as your sight.
Will you be able to learn
what I have to teach
and master the divine speed
skill, Eternal Sword?
Or will your body give out
and leave you sobbing
like a spanked baby?
[cackles]
[RISTA] I did not sign up
for this nightmare fuel!
Maybe we should look
at other options!
Let's give it a shot.
[RISTA]
Give it a what?
How is this the one thing
he's not cautious about?
You made this Internal Sword
move sound pretty legit.
[ADEMELA giggles]
It's Eternal Sword, actually.
[SEIYA]
Blah, blah, blah, let's do this.
[ADENELA]
I‐I like your style.
[ADENELA giggles]
[RISTA sighs]
Thanks, Aria.
I'm in your debt again!
It's fine. I'm happy
I could be of some help.
[CERCEUS]
That's it! Now one more time!
[MASH]
Okay!
[MASH grunting]
They're getting along
better than I expected.
[RISTA] And I know I don't
have to worry about Elulu
since she's with Hestiaca.
My only concern is
getting this food to Seiya!
Huh?
Shouldn't you be
somewhere training a hero?
[ADENELA]
I'm taking a break right now.
Seiya is still practicing
on his own though.
How's he handling all
that Eternal Sword stuff?
He's truly amazing.
Unlike any hero I've
ever encountered before.
And I think that...
You think what?
[giggling]
Yikes! Let's dial
back the freak face!
I just remembered something
that happened in training.
Seiya. He really amused me.
Hey, grunge bucket.
Break's over. Let's go.
Right. I'm on my way.
[ADENELA giggling]
[RISTA]
Uhh...
I forgot to give him his food!
[RISTA] I hope everyone's
staying productive!
[gasps]
It's rare to see the pair of you
share a meal in the cafeteria!
Shroomy here
wanted some bro time.
I thought the least we could
do was spend lunch together.
He's been teaching me all about
the kind of mindset he
has when he's in a fight.
Yeah? I'm kind
of curious myself.
[SEIYA]
Not now.
Dark‐and‐Dingy's waitin' on me.
Good talk! Thanks, Master!
[RISTA]
Don't forget we're heading back
to Gaeabrande tomorrow!
[RISTA]
So!
What were you going to say
about that fighting mindset
stuff or whatever it was?
Uh... It more or
less boiled down to
doubt everyone and
everything at all times.
Even your close friends
and family members
may be trying to kill you.
What a hysterical, paranoid,
and delusional thing
to fill an
impressionable mind with.
[MASH] Oh, there was
another thing he said!
"Remember, Mushroom.
I suspect you just as
much as everyone else."
Man, how cool is that?
Great, now the universe has
one more disciple of Cautionism.
[ADENELA giggling]
[RISTA]
Is that you, Adenela?
It is! I don't believe it!
Kudos to whoever
did your makeover.
Well, truth is,
I was embarrassed by
how I looked before.
I want to look nice for Seiya.
[RISTA groans] Another
enamored deity bites the dust!
If he'd slay demon lords like
he slays goddesses, we'd be set!
[ADENELA giggling]
[RISTA]
I hate to be a bother,
but we're kind of
on a time crunch.
Could my hero pick up your
special skill at a later date?
The Eternal Sword? He mastered
that technique already.
[RISTA gasps]
He what?
That human has a gift.
Yes. The size of which
is truly something to behold
and acknowledge.
And best of all...
[ADENELA laughing]
...he can...
[laughing]
...keep up with me!
[RISTA]
Ugh.
I'm not sure why, but she makes
me even more uncomfortable now!
[MASH]
Thanks for everything!
[CERCEUS]
No, I should be thanking you!
With your help,
I've managed to put that
berserker nightmare behind me!
[RISTA] His level
his risen dramatically!
Could Cerceus actually
be a half‐decent teacher?
[MASH]
Hey, Elulu!
[ELULU]
Oh, hi, guys.
The hiatus is over!
So are you ready to go?
Because the sooner
we head out, the better!
[ELULU]
Um... right!
[RISTA]
Hm?
Hold on.
Her stats are basically the
same as they were on day one.
[HESTIACA]
Rista.
A word, if you will.
Look, let's be blunt.
Flame magic eludes that girl.
[RISTA]
Ohh. That can't be right.
She's trying her
little heart out.
Magic depends largely upon
the talent you're born with.
And sadly that girl wasn't
born with any talent at all.
[RISTA]
Aw.
[GODS chattering]
[RISTA]
Seiya!
Can we finally go now?
Sure.
Once the creep queen shows.
She said she had something
she wanted to give me.
Seiya!
Wha‐‐?
[ADENELA giggles]
‐‐[RISTA, ELULU scream]
‐‐What the heck?
Hi, Seiya. I've been
doing some thinking,
and I've decided
to join your party!
You better be talking
birthdays over there,
because this party only
has room for one goddess!
Well, If I can't be a teammate,
then perhaps an escort?
I just want to be by your side!
[RISTA]
It's love! I'm gonna vomit!
[ADENELA] Here. This took
me five hours to make.
I used my heart as
the main ingredient!
Please, eat every bite!
[RISTA]
Uh‐oh. Goth goddess has it bad.
Wait a sec. Seiya hates cake.
Grossness. Cake sucks.
[RISTA]
Yes! I called it!
[SEIYA]
Look, you're great at training,
but you knew what this was.
It's not me, it's you.
And all cake can go
straight to hell. Period.
Sorry 'bout ya.
[ADENELA]
He... really doesn't want it?
Hey. Don't be so rude!
‐‐[ADENALA cackling]
‐‐You jerk.
Don't you know love‐struck
girls are super fragile?
How 'bout you just
open the portal?
Hey, you two.
Better have all my stuff.
[RISTA]
Cold front passing through.
Doorway to the
other world, open!
[BYSTANDER GOD 05A screams]
[BYSTANDER GOD 05B yells]
[ADENELA]
It's fine. Everything's fine.
You just don't want
anything to do with me.
Just like you don't want
anything to do with cake!
[ADENALA laughing]
[SECURITY GOD 05B]
We need backup!
[SECURITY GOD 05A]
She's way too powerf‐‐
I am perfectly prepared.
I am 100 percent ready for this.
Seiya! Now is not
the time, okay?
You have an ETA for when
we'll get to the Dragons' Den?
Well, being a Dragonkin lets
me sense we're getting closer,
so not far now.
[ELULU grunting]
Come on!
Whacha up to back there, Elulu?
[ELULU]
Just practicing.
If a monster appears, I want to
use my magic to help Seiya out!
I don't need your help.
You're a baggage handler.
So just handle my baggage.
Huh?
Oh. Okay. Heh, heh...
Have you ever heard
the phrase "kid gloves"?
[MASH]
Ah! An orc!
Nice! A chance to put all
my training to the test!
‐‐[PHOENIX screeches]
‐‐Huh?
[ORC 05A stammering]
How? That big bird
came out of nowhere!
It literally beat
me to the punch.
That is my Automatic Phoenix.
[ALL]
Huh?
[SEIYA] This thing detects any
monster within a 50‐meter radius
and automatically
attacks it on sight.
Whoa. That sounds like some
stellar remote fire magic.
Yeah. Leave it to you, Master.
But I wouldn't mind
taking out the next enemy.
Whoa! Watch out!
Here comes a tree goblin!
‐‐[MASH] Sweet‐‐
‐‐[PHOENIX screeches]
Take that!
‐‐Fire Arrow!
[gasps] Rude!
[SEIYA] Everything level 30
and under is killed instantly.
We can win without fighting.
There's no greater
strategy than that.
[RISTA]
He could at least let the kiddos
feel like they're doing
something useful.
But's it's kind of
comforting to know
he's got another special
skill under his belt.
Hmm.
That's the most obvious
Fake Out I've ever seen!
Nothing a little
willpower can't change!
Hngh! Time to unleash
my amazing Megamic Power!
[RISTA groaning]
Huh? What the heck is happening?
Hmm. They're kind of
cute in a weird way.
[screams]
[RISTA]
That hurt!
Hey! Pull yourself
together, Rista!
[RISTA]
...the absolute worst!
[SEIYA sighs] I thought you
would've learned by now,
but I'm not one to bro‐and‐tell.
Pull a stunt like that again,
and I'll destroy your head.
You do know we're on
the same side, right?
Aw. I better not sneak
a peek for a while.
[SON 05A]
Come on in!
We welcome you
to Izale Village.
[SEIYA grunts]
Ah! Throttle back, turbo!
They're just harmless dwarves!
They're classified as monsters,
but most actually
lead peaceful lives!
You sell torches,
Billbro Baggins?
Yes, we certainly do.
Are you going out to
the dragon den, stranger?
So you've heard of it.
[KILL CAPUL]
It's in the rocks out east!
But the only thing you'll
come across is a dead‐end.
That's it!
The entrance is sealed, but I
bet Elulu and I can fix that!
Hey, I've got a
pop quiz for you.
How many torches will we need?
[MASH]
Hmm... Fifty of 'em!
[RISTA] He's tainted
this poor boy's mind
and corrupted his common sense.
[SEIYA]
Wrong.
We'll need 500, minimum.
He meant to say five!
She doesn't have any
risk management skills.
[ELULU gasps]
[ELULU]
Hey! Reese.
Look! Look!
[MASH]
Mine, too! Must be close.
There!
[RISTA]
That's it?
Good thing we didn't
buy 499 more torches!
[SEIYA]
Forget that. Check this.
[BOTH gasp]
Okay, Elulu! Let's do this!
Yeah!
[BOTH]
Uh?
[SEIYA grunts]
Uh, you good?
[SEIYA yelling]
I'm lost. What the
crap are you doing?
By making my joints the
paragon of flexibility,
I'm able to repeat the actions
of slicing, thrusting,
and sweeping
at incredibly high speed.
This is the Eternal Sword!
The chained‐attack blade!
Whoa. That attack
demolished the seal.
I guess we really
are useless after all.
No! You shouldn't feel that way!
Without you two,
we would've never even
found a seal to decimate!
‐‐Huh?
‐‐[RISTA] Okay!
[RISTA] So where's this big,
bad ultimate weapon hiding?
[ELULU yelps]
[LAGOS] You've done
well to come this far.
Welcome fellow
descendants of the dragons.
[MASH]
Whoa. What the‐‐
[LAGOS] Brave heroes,
step into the magic circle.
It shall transport
you to Dragon Village,
where you will
be given Igzasion.
Igzasion?
Is that how we're saying it?
Time to hop a ride
on the glowy platform
and get this adventure going!
It's kind of like a
homecoming, isn't it, Elulu?
I might just die
from the excitement!
Let's not do that, okay?
Okay. We're in the circle now.
[RISTA grunts]
[LAGOS] Excellent!
Dragon Village awaits.
[ALL gasp]
[LAGOS] Uh, I think there were
some technical difficulties.
We received a lizard.
Cool. Nothing abnormal
to make note of.
I am confident
this is not a trap.
[LAGOS]
Welcome to Dragon Village.
Huh?!
[LAGOS] Your shocked
response is only natural.
My people's dragonewt appearance
is drastically different
from that of the human race.
I am referred to as Lagos.
If you would be so
kind as to follow me,
I shall take you to
our leader, Leviae.
The village you see before you
is a continent located
far across the western sea.
Magic circles are the only
means humans can travel here.
It seems young Mash
and Elulu have returned!
Mash looks so dashing
now that he's older.
[DRAGONEWT 05A] Yes!
And Elulu is simply adorable!
Say, if we're
originally from here,
why do we look so different
from everyone else?
We dragonewts
came into existence
as children of both
dragons and humans.
However the more
reptilian‐seeming among us
have more dragon
blood in their veins.
[SEIYA]
So these guys look human
'cause they got the weaker
end of the DNA strand?
[ELULU, MASH gasp]
[LAGOS] No. Mash and Elulu
are choice individuals.
They are Dragonkin who
shoulder a tremendous destiny.
[LEVIAE]
I'm pleased that both of you
have safely returned to us.
Your companions
are also welcome.
I am Leviae,
the reigning monarch and
mother of Dragon Village.
Listen well.
The Demon Lord's conquest
continues even as we speak.
Although the threat is
imminent, you needn't worry.
You Dragonkin have chosen
the correct place to prepare.
Please step forward, young Mash.
Huh? Me? For real?
I will show you how to
transform into a dragon.
[MASH gasps]
[MASH groaning]
[chuckles]
There, by becoming a dragonewt,
your abilities have
improved considerably.
Huh?
You look cool!
[RISTA]
That's amazing!
Your ability ratings
literally went up tenfold!
Yeah, but you better
keep your distance.
I can't promise I won't attack,
since you look like a monster.
[MASH]
That's so messed up!
On the plus side, now you can
carry more of my equipment.
[MASH]
Ugh...
With proper training,
you may one day transform from
a dragonewt to a Dragon God.
Then your skills will
reach unparalleled heights.
Yeah! That sounds good to me!
[ELULU]
Um, Your Majesty.
Could you maybe show me
how to transform, too?
But why? It serves
you no purpose.
[gasps]
Oh. If you say so.
[LEVIAE]
Worry not, child.
Your role in this
endeavor will prove
even greater than
that of young Mash.
Wow! Do you really mean it?
Yes, my dear.
You are fated to
become Igzasion,
the most powerful of weapons.
You will fulfill this destiny
by offering up your life.
Huh?
Like... a sacrifice?
That's not okay!