We are the Roseguard
Imperial Knights.
We heard a hero was headed
into this cave and hurried here.
Oh, that so?
[KNIGHT 06A] The knights under
the command of Captain Rosalie
are engaging the Demon Lord's
forces at Olga Fortress.
We ask that you come with us!
Okay.
We did come here to
save the world, after all.
So let's get going.
[SOLDIERS gasp, chattering]
[SOLDIER 07C]
The rumors are true!
[SOLDIER 07A] It's like
having a hundred more men!
Is there anybody in this
world who doesn't need my help?
I was hoping for, like,
five seconds of down time.
[KNIGHT 06A]
We will gladly lead you
all the way to Olga Fortress.
[SEIYA]
I'd rather you didn't.
Just tell me what
direction it's in.
[KNIGHT 06A]
North by northwest.
[SOLDIER 07D]
Whoa! He really can fly!
[SOLDIER 07F]
No ordinary mortal can do that!
[SOLDIER 07G] That's why
heroes are better than us.
I believe he can
bring down Beel Bub!
Who's this Beel Bub
you're talking about?
[KNIGHT 06A] A demon
that looks like giant fly.
A swarm of those disgusting
creatures led by Beel Bub
is causing massive
casualties at Olga Fortress.
So we're in for midair combat.
We'll do a little recon first.
Tater tots, on me.
Rista, grab the
other one, would ya?
No problem.
[ELULU]
Ow!
[MASH gasps]
Oh, wow!
Being able to fly with
you is incredible, Master!
Something doesn't
look right up ahead.
[Huh? Maybe it's a raincloud?
[BOTH gasp]
[RISTA] That's a huge
swarm of flies! Gross!
[SEIYA]
Hm.
Three to four hundred of
those flying poop‐eaters,
all over level 30.
So the Phoenix is out.
Let's stay back
and see what happens.
[RISTA]
Yeah, I'm good with that plan.
[BEEL BUB]
Bow down before us, humans!
[GROUP gasps]
[BEEL BUB] Tremble at
the overwhelming might
of the Demon Lord's
airborne shock troops,
the Aerial Assault Flies!
I'm thinking that
must be the boss bug.
His ability stats kinda suck,
so he's not a Heavenly King.
[RISTA gasps] That speed rating
is kinda outta control though!
[SEIYA]
He disgusts me.
Huh?
[SEIYA] I mean, like,
how can he talk with that mouth?
I don't even wanna know.
[RISTA yells]
How does that help us
counteract his
stupid fast speed?
[ELULU]
Look over there!
Those Roseguard soldiers
are being targeted!
[ARCHERY CAPTAIN 07A]
Release!
It looks like even
the minion flies
all have pretty decent
evasive skills as well.
[ROSALIE grunting]
[BEEL BUB]
Now, it's time for something
I like to call
Reverse Fireworks.
Say what now? I don't get it.
[BEEL BUB chuckles]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
‐‐[squelching]
‐‐[ELULU gasps]
[BEEL BUB] I was thinking
about calling them
Beel Bub's Blood Bombs,
but that seems corny.
Hmm. There's no fire,
but you get the idea.
Now, where's that hero?
Is this not enough to draw
him out? I can kill more.
I can do this
all day, am I right?
I wondered why the
fortress hadn't fallen,
but he basically just told us
what was up, so that's helpful.
I love it when they
just tell us like that.
Master, are we gonna
stand around here and watch,
or are we gonna
swat these flies?
Slow your roll, turbo.
Normal flies move faster
than the blink of an eye,
and these are some
kind of demon flies,
so they probably move
unbelievably quickly.
Now's not the time to act.
[MASH grunts]
[SOLDIERS groaning]
[RISTA]
Elulu, stay behind me, okay?
[ELULU sighs]
[MASH]
Huh?
[gasps]
[ROSALIE] Oh, thank goodness!
You've come at last!
Listen up, soldiers!
The hero and goddess
have finally arrived
to save our world!
Now, stand tall!
Prepare to storm
the demon's lair!
Captain Rosalie,
please calm yourself!
First, we need to regroup
and let the men rest!
We can rest only after
we've avenged our fallen
brothers in arms!
[CARLO] I know the thirst
for blood vengeance well.
But you must realize
the situation we're in.
Our remaining soldiers
are beyond exhausted.
Besides, the hero's
just barely arrived.
[ROSALIE grunts]
I suppose you
have a point, Carlo.
Let's head back to the fortress.
There, we can discuss a strategy
to finally defeat these
flies with our hero.
Captain Rosalie.
[ROSALIE] However,
once that meeting is done,
we're heading back out!
That is an order,
you understand?
What are you
waiting for?! Move it!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, ma'am!
[MASH]
Wow, that place is massive!
[CARLO] Olga Fortress
is at a strategic location
on the imperial border.
In addition to strong walls,
the garrison's elite archers are
stationed up in the ramparts.
[SEIYA]
Heh. Well, those flies
could definitely break
through if they wanted.
[CARLO] Clearly, their
objective was to lure you here.
They wouldn't go any
farther than the fortress.
But even if they did,
the empire is protected
by the great Warmaster.
Who's that?
His name really says it all.
He's the greatest living
warrior in Gaeabrande.
[SEIYA]
Yeah, if that were true,
he could be saving
the world instead of me.
I don't buy the hype.
[CARLO] Forgive me,
but present company excluded.
The Warmaster's absolutely,
without a doubt,
the mightiest man
to ever walk this land.
However, he can't
leave the capital.
[BAHT] Captain Rosalie!
Must you be on the battlefront?
You are next in line to the
imperial throne, after all!
Which is why I should
be in harm's way.
I'm my father's daughter.
A true warrior!
[CARLO]
Um, excuse me. They're here.
The hero and his courageous
party have now arrived.
‐‐Oh!
‐‐Your greatness is inspiring!
We do appreciate your help.
Come and have a seat.
[BAHT]
So without further ado,
we must formulate a strategy at
once to eliminate these flies.
[SEIYA]
Slow down, big guy.
I would like to
guarantee our safety first.
One of the Demon Lord's henchmen
could be right here
with us in disguise.
‐‐Wait! Do you think so?
‐‐[OFFICERS gasp]
All I'm saying is
the possibility exists.
Well, I suppose there's
a remote chance.
Besides, even if
the enemy's not here,
they could've planted a
bomb to blow us all to hell.
‐‐There's a bomb in here?!
‐‐[OFFICERS gasp]
All I'm saying is
the possibility exists.
Yes. I suppose it does.
But even if there's not,
I'm almost positive someone's
listening in on this meeting.
[OFFICERS gasp]
[ROSALIE gasps] Carlo!
Search the ceiling now!
Right!
[SOLDIER 07L] Sir, 23 soldiers
have searched high and low,
but the entire area above
this room is not only empty,
but remarkably clean!
There's no sign
of an intruder, sir.
Huh?
All I said was
the possibility exists.
[ROSALIE]
I've had enough of this!
What's more than
just a possibility
is we are not getting
any fighting done!
We don't even
need to strategize!
The hero and I will
stand at the fore
and charge into the
creatures' lair! That's that!
But Captain Rosalie,
we can't be‐‐
[SEIYA]
She's right.
Huh?
Oh! So you agree
we should charge in?
[SEIYA]
Don't put words in my mouth.
What I agree with is this
meeting is totally pointless.
I know what my next course
of action needs to be.
So what do you plan to do?
To leave.
[OFFICERS, ROSALIE]
Huh?
[ROSALIE]
Huh?!
[SEIYA] I'm gonna go
back to the Divine Realm...
'Course that's it.
A classic Seiya move.
[RISTA sighs]
And here I was getting excited
to start an adventure.
[ROSALIE]
This is utterly ridiculous!
You're kidding, right?
[SEIYA] I'm never kidding.
It's not my style.
You're seriously
going to abandon us?
[SEIYA] Cut the drama,
I'm just leaving.
‐‐But why?
‐‐Makes no sense.
He's chicken?
[OFFICER 07A]
Well, he's not a hero.
Everyone, relax, I speak Seiya.
He doesn't mean going
off to train for long.
Probably no more
than three days.
What the hell?
But the fortress will
be destroyed in that time!
No, listen, in the Divine Realm
three days is,
like, an hour or so.
‐‐[ROSALIE growls]
‐‐That's not too unreasonable.
But why would you even
need to train for this fight?
I saw the goddess's wings
with my own two eyes.
If you can already fly,
you're ready!
Huh? Who, me?
Goddesses don't fight.
They only support.
[RISTA]
Hm?
[RISTA] Whoa, is he
actually sticking up for me?
[SEIYA] But don't get me wrong,
she's completely useless.
She just kinda
floats like a balloon.
Now that I think about it,
a balloon would be more capable.
[RISTA] Ugh! Hey, I oughta
punch your balloons!
Flying's no big deal.
I can do that.
Oh, is that so?
[SEIYA] That doesn't
make us less screwed.
Look, I was watching
the battle earlier.
[ROSALIE]
Wait, what did you say?
You were watching?
While my soldiers
were being slaughtered,
you stood there
and watched them die?
No, that's not true!
We wanted to help, but at
the time, it was just too late!
[thud]
[ROSALIE]
It's not about timing,
it's about helping
or not helping!
I want to know if the
hero saw what happened
and did nothing to help!
[SEIYA] That's a dumb
question if you ask me.
If nothing will help,
why would I do anything?
My men were murdered by demons!
You're a hero,
doesn't that affect you?!
[SEIYA]
What would change if it did?
Best thing to do was
not get freaked out.
Stay calm and keep my guard up.
This "hero" is hopeless.
By definition a hero
is supposed to be brave!
But you are not a hero!
You're just a mopey coward!
Rosalie, I know Seiya can
come off as an unfeeling jerk
who's afraid to
get his hands dirty,
but that's how
we've made it this far.
He'll kill those demon flies,
but only when he
knows he's ready.
So would you please
just be patient?
This training will
only take an hour.
And why should I?
[gasps]
[RISTA]
Ugh, valid question...
[ROSALIE] Over a hundred of
my men were popped like grapes.
[gasps]
[ROSALIE]
Have some empathy!
[RISTA] I know it's a horrible
thing to go through, but‐‐
[ROSALIE] You can't know
how precious life truly is
because you don't
have to fear death!
Since you're a goddess, it will
literally never happen to you!
[RISTA]
Ya kinda got me there.
So don't speak to me on
matters of life and death!
[RISTA grunts]
You're not exactly coming from
some kind of moral
high ground, lady.
Say what?!
[SEIYA] Your men didn't
get killed by accident.
All that stuff is on you.
If you had been able to
come up with a strategy
that didn't suck,
they'd still be alive right now.
You scum! You'd better
take that back!
‐‐I should kill you!
‐‐[OFFICERS gasp]
[RISTA gasps]
[ROSALIE grunts]
[ROSALIE groans]
[ALL scream]
Whoa, time out!
Seiya, in what kind of world
is hitting a woman ever okay?
You need to get down on
your knees and beg her...
It was self‐defense?
[ROSALIE]
How dare you!
[ROSALIE yells]
‐‐[thud]
‐‐[ROSALIE] Ow!
‐‐Ow...
‐‐[thud]
Oh! You bastard!
‐‐Ow!
You slap like a girl!
‐‐[thud]
‐‐Oh, you'll pay for this!
[thud]
[whimpering]
[RISTA] Is there no shred of
feminism in this day and age?
I knew he was
kind of old‐fashioned,
but this is the bad kind!
[ROSALIE]
All right, that's it!
You are dead!
I'll slice you to pieces!
Captain Rosalie,
control yourself!
You're a fraud.
You are not a hero.
[snorts] You're
just a jerk face!
‐‐Apologize, you caveman!
‐‐[ROSALIE crying]
Nope, she was
coming in hard, bro.
Look at her! You made her cry!
[ROSALIE]
I'm not!
I'm not crying!
You're crying! [cries]
The way that I see it,
she should be apologizing to me.
[RISTA]
The way I see it,
you're an embarrassment to
men and heroes, so apologize!
I don't need a stupid
hero, so just shut up!
I'll go take care
of them myself!
[RISTA] You do have incredibly
high strength, for a human.
[SEIYA] The Warmaster
may be your father,
but I guess ability
ratings aren't genetic.
You're just gonna
get yourself killed.
[growls]
[ELULU gasps] She's starting
to growl like a dog.
I oughta chew your face off.
[SEIYA] I think she's
rabid, so leave her alone.
[MASH] Hey, Master, are you
sure you shouldn't apologize?
I'm sorry, but
I don't do apologies.
Open a portal. Let's go.
[RISTA]
Ah, uh, sure?
[ROSALIE growling]
Yeah...
[RISTA]
Jeez, that growling.
Is she a dog?
Okay, find our happy place.
We're leaving, but we'll
be back in an hour.
Try not to bite anyone
while we're gone.
[growling]
[RISTA]
I know you, um, have your ways,
but don't ever do
anything like that again!
There's no excuse.
[ELULU] I was scared you
were gonna kill each other.
[MASH] All that slapping
was pretty intense.
[SEIYA]
I couldn't stop myself.
It's like all of that
crap that she was spewing
triggered my slap button.
Don't care.
[SEIYA]
The way she thinks is BS‐‐
hell‐bent on moving forward
when there's no
chance of winning.
Besides the casualties,
it makes you look like an idiot.
[RISTA] Hm. Yeah, it's pretty
much the exact opposite approach
from how you like
to do everything.
So, uh, you feel like
taking a little breather?
[SEIYA]
Great, another dumb question.
[gasps]
I figured out how to deal
with that demon bug infestation.
Well, if you need one
of the gods around here
to help you with something,
I can hook you up.
Like the god of Patriot
surface‐to‐air missiles?
What? There's no god for that!
How about the god of guns?
We might actually have
one of those somewhere.
But although Gaeabrande
has a lot of ways to kill,
there are no guns.
If we're the only ones
with guns, we win.
[RISTA] Listen, Seiya,
it's just not gonna happen!
Guns literally
do not exist there!
Well, if the guns and
Patriot missiles are out,
that leaves us with bows.
[RISTA] Great, because
I know the Goddess of Archery.
She's in the Verdant Forest,
which is a little
ways from here.
[SEIYA]
Cool, let's go.
Maybe she can
teach me something.
[RISTA] Mm. She's
practicing right up ahead.
[RISTA] Please pardon
the interruption, Mitis.
Oh, Ristarte. I don't
see you here often.
Is there something
I can help you with today?
Well, I was telling
my hero friend here
about your amazing
skill as an archer,
and we were hoping
you wouldn't mind
sharing a few tips
with him to up his game.
You're supposed to be the best,
so how many arrows
can you shoot at once?
Ever heard of buttering
someone up first?!
It isn't really
possible to shoot
more than one arrow at a time,
but I can shoot
in quick succession
to mimic simultaneous fire.
Shining Arrow!
That was so fast, I bet the
tree never even saw it coming!
After centuries of training,
seven quick shots is my limit.
Just seven shots?
How 'bout hitting something
that actually moves,
do you think you'd miss?
[MITIS]
Um, no, that would never happen.
[SEIYA]
Really?
I wouldn't be the Goddess
of Archery if I missed.
Unfortunately, that kind
of speed and precision
is impossible for
humans like you.
Yeah, we'll see.
Why don'tcha teach me
a thing or two first?
[MITIS]
Before we begin,
you need to be able
to use a magic bow.
If that proves to be too much,
there are other types of
lessons I'd love to teach you,
personally.
[RISTA] Does that mean
what I think it means?
I just wanna learn
how to use the bow.
Elulu, you know how to use Fire
Arrow, don'tcha? Teach it to me.
You're good at
a lot of things, Seiya,
but I don't know if you can
just pick it up just like that.
[SEIYA]
Just do it, okay?
The first step is to
stretch out your left hand
and visualize a
flaming magic bow in it.
‐‐Like this?
‐‐Now picture an arrow
in your right‐‐ [gasps]
You're going too fast!
But the next step is
really the toughest part
of the whole process.
Hitting the target is where all
of the skill starts to come in.
[ELULU whines]
[SEIYA]
Huh. That was easy.
[ELULU]
Well, for you, maybe.
[MITIS] My word, you are
surprisingly quick to catch on.
I understand why she chose you.
I'd be happy to start
training you right away.
[ELULU groans]
Well, there goes my dignity.
[RISTA]
Don't let it bother you.
That guy's a freak of nature.
Well, since we're
waiting on him,
how do you suggest
we pass the time?
[RISTA]
What did Seiya tell you?
"You kids can go to the
cafeteria and eat candy
or whatever the hell you do."
[RISTA]
Sounds like him.
I don't wanna just sit around,
so could you introduce me to a
god who'll help me get stronger?
Yeah, I don't mind
finding someone for you.
Do you want one, too?
[ELULU]
Nah, not today.
I'm gonna do the candy plan.
I'll join you, whaddaya
say we eat some macarons?
That sound good?
[MASH]
Hey, look, it's Cerceus!
[gasps]
Hey there, big fella!
[CERCEUS] Oh, no,
if you're here, that means
that psychopath's
here, too, isn't he?!
[RISTA] Seiya's training in
the Divine Forest right now.
Did something happen?
[CERCEUS]
Are you kidding me,
or did you forget
about all the stuff
that went down with him
and Adenela last time?
She's a wreck to begin with
and now she's ten times worse!
[RISTA]
Totally slipped my mind.
So what has she
been doing, exactly?
"S‐S‐Seiya. I‐I‐I'm
gonna k‐k‐kill you."
She skulks around
like that all day.
It's like hearing the
worst hip‐hop DJ ever.
[RISTA]
It's that bad, huh?
It is! It's really
not funny anymore.
If she sees him around,
she's definitely gonna
gut him like a fish!
[RISTA whimpers]
[ARIA]
I'd heard she was upset.
I tried to cheer her up a bit,
but she didn't
want to listen to me.
I wonder if Ishtar
could talk to her
and try to smooth
things out a little.
[ARIA]
I'd keep her out of this.
I'm just afraid Seiya's
gonna get shanked!
[ARIA] Adenela's strange,
but she'd never do that.
And in the
unlikely case she did,
knowing that hero,
he wouldn't even be fazed.
Well, I don't really
wanna test that theory.
Not to mention, go through
all of this with him
just to have him
get killed by some
side‐eyeing goth
goddess with a grudge!
I'm guessing she's
not the best goddess
to ask to help with
my training, huh?
But what should I do instead?
If you stay here,
it's all you can eat candy.
[ARIA]
Young man.
I can sense that you
have some dormant powers.
[MASH gasps] You mean the
Dragon God Metamorphosis?
They say, if I can
work hard enough,
I'll be able to
turn into a dragon.
[ARIA]
Sounds like you have a seal.
If you want my help,
I can release it for you.
[MASH]
For real?! You can do that?!
I'm all for learning new things,
but that sounds
like cheating to me!
[ARIA] I'm just teaching
him the proper way
to unlock a power
he already possesses.
It's another form of training.
[RISTA] Okay, if you say it's
fine, then knock yourself out.
Don't worry about me, Rista.
I'll just keep doing
what I'm best at,
which is shoveling candy.
[ARIA]
Oh! I can see that you have
some hidden talents as well.
I would be able to draw them
out for you, if you'd like.
Uh, really?
If you think I can do
something cool, then teach me!
Draw it out, drag it out, rip it
out, whatever you need to do!
[RISTA] Aria's always the
best for a good pick‐me‐up.
She even sees potential
in Elulu. Hmm.
I'm sure she's
right that Adenela's
just a harmless whack‐a‐doodle.
But still, I think
it's best for me to go
and talk her down a little.
Hey, sweetie, it's your old
friend Rista checking in!
[RISTA]
Are you home?
[gasps]
I guess she's out.
[screams]
[RISTA]
Oh, she's out, out of her mind!
‐‐[RISTA shrieks]
‐‐[ADENELA cackling]
[RISTA screams]
R‐Ristarte, if you're
b‐b‐back here,
then that means one thing.
Y‐Your tight bodied friend
is b‐back here, too, huh?
N‐No, I came all
by myself this time.
I don't know where he is!
[ADENELA]
Oh, oh. Is that true? R‐Really?
Oh, yeah! I haven't
seen him in a while!
So what do you need, anyway?
It's nothing,
don't even worry about it!
Then why did you come in?
[RISTA]
Oh, well, I was just
looking for some
decorating inspirations.
You've got such a unique style.
But I'm not sure I could
pull this off as well.
Ah, hah, hah...
Yeah? Really?
[RISTA whimpering]
[RISTA]
Seiya!
So, how's it going?
[SEIYA] She's done training me,
but I should have it
totally mastered by
tomorrow, maybe sooner.
[RISTA]
That's awesome! Anyway!
Just make sure you
don't set foot outside
this forest and run
into Adenela, got it?
And why should I be
worried about that?
[RISTA] Just do what I'm asking
you to do for once, okay?!
I'll bring the shorties back
here tomorrow and we'll leave.
[SEIYA] You're way more
annoying than usual today.
So what crawled up your butt?
Please, I'm just asking
that you stay here
and try not to run into Adenela.
Do you really not know that
she's standing right behind you?
[RISTA]
Uh...
[ADENELA cackles]
‐‐[RISTA screams]
‐‐[ADENELA] R‐R‐Rista,
I had a feeling
you were lying to me.
So I d‐decided
to follow you here
and f‐find out the truth!
Hold on there,
just take it easy.
I can explain everything,
just calm down!
It's okay!
Now, I'll kill him. Yes. I will.
He's gonna pay!
[RISTA] Oh, no! That's
the Eternal Sword stance!
She did not come here to play!
Go on and draw your blade
if you're m‐m‐man enough
to fight against a woman
who's t‐ten times
the warrior you are!
[SEIYA]
Hey, I know you're fine,
but how you doin'?
Long time no see.
[ADENELA]
Wh‐What're you talking about?
You‐‐ You can't t‐t‐treat
me like you did the other day
and just expect me to act
like n‐n‐nothing happened!
You gotta pay.
Ah, what is up with your hair?
S‐Something the matter with it?
She's gonna pierce
your spleen, you idiot!
You do own a comb, don't you?
S‐S‐Stop t‐t‐touching me
with your warm m‐manly
hands like that.
Now, isn't that better?
[RISTA] Hey! C'mon,
Captain Boundary Issues!
[ADENELA]
Y‐You‐‐ I‐I‐I‐I...
I forgive you!
[RISTA]
Eh?
What happened to
all that psycho rage?!
Did he pet it out of you?!
[ADENELA]
I‐I just can't help myself.
It's clichéd, but I can't
stay mad at someone so hot!
[SEIYA] Adenela, I need
to get back to my training.
You being here is distracting
and it brings me down.
So hurry on outta here now.
[ADENELA]
A‐All right. L‐Love you.
[RISTA]
Wow, that's horrible.
I mean, he's hot, I get it,
but have some self‐respect.
[ADENELA giggles]
...knowing that hero,
he wouldn't even be fazed.
[RISTA] Yeah,
she really called that one.
Maybe I get carried away.
[RISTA sighs]
[SEIYA] Outta the way.
I'm training here.