So... what now?
[KILKAPUL]
Hero.
You are not like most mortals,
and I believe you may even
have stood a slim chance
of defeating the Demon Lord.
But we'll never know because
your journey ends here.
Wait. Are you gonna fight him
without your monster buddy?
You misunderstand me.
This old body would be
no match for the hero.
Which is why...
[RISTA grunts]
...I would like to
show you something.
[gasps]
[ELULU yelps]
[RISTA]
Ew! It's horrible!
[KILKAPUL] You may recognize
them from a previous encounter.
These are, in fact, the heads
of my wife and young son.
A sad, but necessary measure
to ensure your defeat.
My next step
requires their deaths,
the entire village, and my own.
The ultimate
sacrifice must be made
to invoke the most powerful
summoning magic in the world.
I call on the
hyper‐conceptual reaper,
Krosde Thanatus, to manifest!
Uh... I don't think
he's gonna make it.
Rista, open up a portal
to the Divine Realm.
What? You want me
to do that now?
[SEIYA]
I don't see a portal opening!
[RISTA whimpers]
[RISTA]
So it's hyper‐conceptual
because you can't
read the stats or what?
Like, it's just a
bunch of gobbledygook!
[SEIYA] Hm, I can't make any
sense out of his stats either.
Do you think
it's using Fake Out?
No, doesn't seem like it.
I'm pretty sure those
are just its regular stats.
[RISTA]
I don't know what that means!
[SEIYA] It means that
thing's gonna kick our ass.
Have a taste of my
Double Wind Blade!
Got 'em!
[SEIYA]
Where's the damn portal?
Why? You just slashed it up.
[RISTA gasps]
Whoa, now there's
two of those things?
How is that possible?
[SEIYA groans]
[RISTA]
It just landed a hit on Seiya?
Maximum Inferno!
[SEIYA] Rista move your
ass and open the portal!
[RISTA]
Oh, yeah! On it!
‐‐[MASH] Master‐‐
‐‐[ELULU yelps]
[RISTA, MASH gasp]
[ELULU yells]
[RISTA] Tossed them in like
he was takin' out the trash.
No thanks. I'm far too
delicate for‐‐ [groans]
[RISTA groans]
Did you really have to kick me
through the portal like that?
Oh, no! Are you okay?
I think I'll survive.
But I'm hurt pretty badly.
I can fix you up.
Show me where it hurts.
[SEIYA]
Fine.
[RISTA]
Uhh...
Is it one of those things
that feels worse than it looks?
Earlier, I was at 300,000 HP‐‐
this wound took me
down another hundred.
You're such a baby!
I won't fight unless
I start out at max HP,
so heal me!
[RISTA] Jeez, do you
need a diaper change, too?
So what was the deal
with that thing back there?
That was crazy, wasn't it?
It goes against the
rules of living things
and magic and all the things.
[RISTA] We need to
come up with a strategy.
It can't get us here,
so let's figure that out
before we go ba‐‐ [gasps]
[RISTA]
No way!
It's breaking through
the dimensional barrier?
That freakin' thing
is unstoppable!
There's gotta be some kinda
way to take it down, right?
All right, Seiya,
I'm sure you've already
figured out its weakness,
so you wanna share
that info with us?
[SEIYA]
No clue.
[RISTA yelps]
[SEIYA] I have absolutely
no idea how to beat it.
[RISTA gasping] If Seiya's at
a loss, we're totally screwed.
What do we do?
I'm freakin' out here!
[FRAALA, ORAND, KIORNE]
Hold it right there, foul demon!
[RISTA gasps]
[RISTA]
Nice!
Now we've got some celebrity
god‐power backing us up!
[FRAALA]
Wretched beast!
Prepare to feel the
divine power of the gods!
Tornado Chips!
[ORAND]
Roaring Black Thunder!
Ice Dazs Haagen!
[GROUP gasps]
All their attacks
didn't even faze it?
[ELULU]
Hey, Rista!
[RISTA]
Huh?
That scaredy cat coward!
You're not cautious,
you're chicken!
You can't run away
from everything, ya know?
[FRAALA, ORAND, KIORNE yell]
Hey, guys,
it's still following us!
Keep running!
Seiya, wait for us!
You don't belong here, demon!
For your trespass you face
the invincible fists of Arx!
‐‐[thud]
‐‐Ow! My face!
Game over, man!
[ELULU cries]
I am Kebono!
Now feel the swift
and humiliating power
of my Divine Hundred Hand Slap‐‐
[KEBONO groans]
I regret nothing!
[GOD 09B]
You won't get past me!
[GOD 09C]
Ah, damn it!
[GODS groaning]
Somebody's getting rambunctious.
Hmm.
Hey there!
Feast your eyes on this!
It's my latest creation of
culinary art and I think‐‐ Ugh!
[SEIYA]
Outta the way, lady!
[whimpering]
No! My cake! [cries]
[ADENELA]
S‐S‐Seiya.
I‐I'm so glad
to see you're back.
Do me a solid and deal
with that thing chasing us.
Then you can deal with me,
if you know what I mean.
[ADENELA gasps]
Oh, I know.
[ELULU yells]
You're messing with
the wrong hunk, pal!
Now! You're gonna pay!
Get you some, goth goddess!
Uh‐‐
Completely useless,
like I expected.
You strung her along
just to throw her away!
[ADENELA whimpers]
This sucks!
Agh, we can't run away from
this thing forever, ya know!
But what else can we even do?
[SEIYA]
Unclench, will ya?
[RISTA] Obviously you have no
idea how to beat this creep!
[SEIYA] I don't, but I do
have a plan ready just in case
we come across an enemy
who I don't know how to beat.
A backup, backup plan.
[RISTA]
Huh?
[SEIYA] She may look like
some kinda post‐apocalyptic
S&M reject, but she's
an artist at heart.
She's probably painting on top
of the temple roof right now.
[RISTA]
I don't know who you mean!
Wait. Valkyrie?
You think that she's gonna fight
this mega‐stalker on our behalf?
[SEIYA]
Kind of.
There's no chance in hell
she'll agree to do it
if we just go up and ask her.
Therefore...
[gasps]
[VALKYRIE gasps]
All right. Just what I wanted.
Well, it's on...
[VALKYRIE]
No freaking way.
I've been working on that piece
forever, and I was almost done!
Are you ready?!
I'm gonna paint my next
picture with your blood!
You should get back.
How'd you know‐‐ Urgh!
[RISTA]
Holy...
Or maybe I'll smash you
into a million little pieces
and use 'em to
make a mosaic instead.
Feel my Shattered Break!
[gasps]
[VALKYRIE]
The hell? Is it a ghost?
Well, that's fine by me.
Try this. It's my
Fourth Valkyrja.
Eat my Astral Break!
[RISTA]
Uh‐oh.
Even the strongest goddess in
the Divine Realm can't stop him?
[VALKYRIE laughing]
By Ishtar! Grant this order!
She just unleashed her
suppressed divine power,
so it's about to
get real ugly up in here.
She's totally maxed out!
Huh, the other gods all seem
pretty weak compared to her.
But, to be perfectly honest,
I've been really unimpressed
with everyone here up until now.
Time for Omega Valkyrja.
Gate of Valhalla!
Huh? What'd she do?
I have no idea.
Well, that's a
super creepy move.
[laughs]
[RISTA]
Nightmare fuel!
It's not every day that I use
an inescapable, destructive
technique that transcends
the very fabric of reality.
But sometimes you
gotta kick it up a notch.
Whoa, are you okay?
[VALKYRIE]
Don't come near me, Rista!
[gasps]
[VALKYRIE]
It's happening... Here goes.
[RISTA]
What's happening?
[screams] She's
got splatterreah!
Gate of Valhalla uses
the caster's life
force as a catalyst.
That kinda boss move
would definitely rip
a human into bloody ribbons.
How can I help you?
Uh‐‐
That's the stuff, baby.
I could get used to this.
Oh, yeah! Right there.
Um, is your team S or M?
So the Order you activated
wasn't to use your technique.
It was to deal with
the recoil afterwards.
[VALKYRIE]
Yep, to make sure I bounce back!
Fine now? Great.
Since you're the one who
brought that monster up here
and ruined my painting,
you're the one who's
gonna have to pay the toll,
which is gonna cost ya one
handful of bare boobage.
[RISTA]
You're own bare boobage.
Boob pro quo. Awkward.
Pick one!
Wow. Thank you!
[RISTA] Maybe under
that cold, prickly shell,
you're a man who'll
fight for my honor.
Or maybe he can't
stand the thought
of someone else
having extra fine,
divine, dirty,
touchy‐feely time.
[RISTA groans]
That's not how you
get to second base!
All this time,
you were the one for me.
Take me back to your place right
now and train my brains out.
You want more training?
I mean, I know you like
to be ready for anything,
but we still have a job to do!
And we're gonna do it.
But the foes keep getting
stronger, so I should, too.
You can't pull off
the kinds of crazy things
that Valkyrie can.
If you even tried that
Gate of Valhalla move,
it'd turn you into spaghetti!
[gasps, groans]
Little Miss
Firm Cheeks is right.
There's no way a regular human
could learn a Valkyrja
in the first place.
Well, I'm not a regular human.
You don't give up, do you?
I know you don't think
about anything but training,
but you can't even imagine the
kind of spanking I'd give you‐‐
If you whip that out,
you'd better use it.
Uh, please stop.
[SEIYA]
I can take what you got.
[VALKYRIE]
Oh, so you like it rough?
[SEIYA]
Yeah, 'cause I need someone
who's gonna make me work for it.
[VALKYRIE]
All right then.
If you think you can take it.
But listen closely,
there's no way I'm teaching
you how to do Gate of Valhalla.
Teach me something else.
[VALKYRIE]
Be at my place in ten minutes.
Uh, they're talking
about training, right?
Is it okay with you
if we go back to Aria's?
[ELULU] I really want
to pick up where I left off!
Fine with me. Go and have fun.
[MASH, ELULU]
Thank you!
[RISTA sighs]
I guess you do need to learn
some new destruction moves.
Not like we have
much choice now.
I mean, the ultimate sword
and legendary armor
are outta the picture.
Like they say
back in your world,
this is really some
hardcore kinda sitch
we've stepped in, isn't it?
Whining about it
isn't going to help.
So I picked up a piece
of the legendary armor.
Is that a chunk of adamantite
the terrible turtle
thing was snacking on?
It's not enough for armor,
but I can use it to synthesize.
[SEIYA]
I'll call it Adamantitor,
the indestructible sword.
It may not work
against the final boss,
but it's the best sword
there is right now.
Amazing work, Seiya!
Way to make that lemonade!
You're the best!
Get off me, Rista.
[RISTA]
Aw, you don't have to be shy.
I said get off of me.
You're carrying around my hair,
so I know you're a little
sweet on me. [giggles]
[SEIYA]
Listen.
Hm? I'm right, yeah?
You're ripe.
You're really stinky.
Seriously?
What do you mean, like, what
kind of smell is it, anyway?
Hot garbage.
I have to go and take a bath
right this minute before I die
and then come back
because I can't die.
Just go bathe.
I'm going over to Valkyrie's.
[RISTA] Hey, Cerceus.
Bath time for you, too?
Couldn't just walk
around the rest of the day
covered in cake, could I?
The whole idea was
for it to go in my face,
not get smeared all over it.
[RISTA]
That's fair. Was it any good?
No, of course it wasn't any
damn good, it was way too salty!
It tasted like tears!
[RISTA]
Oh, right. Sorry...
[CERCEUS sighs]
Hey, that reminds me.
Ishtar was looking
for you earlier.
Do you know what she
wanted to talk about?
If I had to guess, I'd say it
was about that demon you let in.
Like, I'm 99 percent sure.
[RISTA] Ugh, I'm gonna have
to see her, smellin' all funky.
Well, Rista.
I'm glad you stopped by.
Hey, look. I'm sorry about
that whole reaper drama.
[ISHTAR]
Oh, don't be silly.
That was not your fault, dear.
Besides, Valkyrie took
care of it, didn't she?
It's not even an issue.
Then why were
you looking for me?
[ISHTAR] It appears that the
last of the Four Heavenly Kings
is making a move
down on Gaeabrande.
He's leading a demon army
to overthrow the capital.
No. Rosalie's in trouble!
There is simply
no time left to spare,
so you must return
to Gaeabrande at once.
Yes, ma'am. I'll go right now!
[ISHTAR]
Uh, I mean...
Hurry, but you still have
time to take a bath, I'm sure.
Perhaps it's your long journey,
but you smell a touch gamey.
[whimpers]
[ARIA]
Whoa, Rista.
What's going on with your skin?
Oh, a sunburn.
I'm just a delicate,
sweet‐smelling
little flower, after all.
[RISTA] I don't stink! I can't
stink! I will never stink again!
Well, enough about me.
How did Mash and
Elulu's training go?
Excellent! You're in
for a big surprise!
[RISTA gasps]
He has mastered
his metamorphosis,
and she was able to upgrade
her Haste spell to Quick.
I'm very proud of both of them.
We have been working
our tails off here!
We want to help Seiya
as much as we can.
Wow. That's awesome.
You guys are great!
[ELULU] We couldn't have done
it without Aria to teach us!
[MASH]
Yeah! Thank you so much!
[RISTA]
All righty then.
I gotta get my butt in gear so
these rug rats don't show me up!
I'll prove to Seiya I'm
more than just a pretty face!
[RISTA]
Excuse me! Coming in!
Agh!
[RISTA]
Wait, wait, wait!
I knew you two were
playing around earlier,
but you're really not
supposed to be doing this!
Put some underpants on, now!
Once again, you don't get it.
We're just training in here.
Oh, can you blame me?
What's the point of
having a beefcake around
if you can't grab
yourself a slice?
But still!
Hot sweaty, sweet relations
between a goddess and
a mortal is forbidden!
Ugh. You have no clue
how things work around here.
This is why
I can't stand novices.
I may not have much,
but I am trying as
hard as I possibly can!
I've been working
like crazy all day
to make this
so I can help Seiya!
What is that thing?
Some kind of gross doll?
Was it in the trash?
Looks like it was woven out
of oily golden thread.
Wait. You gotta be kidding me.
Did you‐‐
[RISTA]
I sure did!
I made this doll out of hair
that I pulled out
of my own head!
And I've dubbed her Lil' Rista.
[VALKYRIE]
You're outta your damn mind!
[RISTA]
I figured it would come in handy
for Seiya's synthesis skill.
So I yanked them out
in little clumps.
It hurt so bad, but worth it!
The level of psychotic
just doesn't work for me.
I won't squeeze
your boobs again.
Hey, Rista, you feelin' okay?
I don't really think this
is a great look for you.
[RISTA] I just thought
this would help Seiya
when he needs it.
But now that
I stop and look at it,
this is restraining
order level crazy.
[RISTA cries]
I'm sorry!
Stop it. It's disgusting.
Don't leak it on me.
I just want you to like me!
Seiya, how can I
make you like me?
[SEIYA] Cleaning up
your snot would help.
But why, out of all
the goddesses here,
would you choose that old,
ugly pain freak over me?
That was just Valkyrja training.
Remember, I told you
that you didn't understand
what was going on.
You cross your heart and
swear to God you mean that?
That is so stupid.
You are a god.
Okay then.
It's pretty unbelievable,
but still, I trust you.
[SEIYA]
Mash, put this in my item bag.
[MASH]
Uhh... sure. If you say so.
Well, anyway,
did you get enough training?
Oh, yeah,
what about you, Master?
[SEIYA]
Mm‐hm.
That's great news, 'cause we
gotta get back to Gaeabrande!
Apparently, the last Heavenly
King is attacking the capital!
[SEIYA]
Okay, let's get going.
[RISTA] Looking back, I was
just too worked up to notice.
But Seiya never
said his catchphrase:
"I'm perfectly prepared."
[DEMON LORD ARMY snarling]
[BHAT] Don't let those
creatures douse your courage!
Remember, what we're
all fighting for today
is the future of Roseguard!
Wow. It's turned
into an all‐out war.
We've been eagerly
awaiting your arrival, hero.
The Heavenly King
Eraser Kaiser has been marching
his elite force of
the Demon Lord's Army
towards our city walls.
The men who met them
on the battlefront
have been made to
retreat in terror.
The fight has finally
come to our doorstep.
So it's a do‐or‐die
moment here?
[SEIYA]
Hmm.
That one gives off a completely
different aura from the rest.
He's the one in charge.
[RISTA]
Eraser Kaiser.
Besides our
interdimensional stalker,
he's the strongest enemy
we've faced so far.
I challenge you to send
your mightiest human
to face me in battle.
Or are there only
weaklings in your kingdom?
[SEIYA]
Hmm.
[SOLDIER 09A]
The Warmaster!
[SOLDIER 09B]
Show them what we're made of!
[SOLDIER 09C] This fight's
as good as over, boys!
That guy's the greatest
warrior in the capital?
Yeah. He's kinda old,
don't you think?
They sent out a dusty old fart?
I had asked for a fight,
not a sacrifice.
[RISTA] Seiya, you need
to go and help him!
Actually, I don't think I will.
[RISTA]
Huh?
If it's a sacrifice you want,
then that's what you'll get.
Witness the power
of my Evil Six mode!
[WARMASTER]
Crushing Saint's Light!
Ow. What? No way.
But you're just a human,
not even a hero!
[SOLDIERS cheering]
Whoa! Crazy!
One‐shot grandpa.
[MONSTER 09A]
Fall back!
[MONSTER 09B]
Retreat!
Purify with Massive
Saint's Light!
[RISTA]
Now those are some stats!
[SEIYA]
A human can get up there.
Fair goddess, it is an honor
to meet you at last.
If this old man has stolen
your hero's thunder,
I humbly ask forgiveness.
Oh, there's no
need to apologize.
I'm actually extremely grateful
to you for defeating
that Heavenly King.
That old dude is like a
walking force of nature.
He took out that big,
six‐armed monster thing
like it was nothing!
If you can wield this kind
of power, why aren't you
joining the battle to
take down the Demon Lord?
Long story.
[RISTA]
Okay...
[WARMASTER groans]
[SOLDIERS, RISTA gasp]
This can't be.
It's starting to happen again.
Please, clear the area, now!
Get moving!
[RISTA] This guy is looking
like death eating a cracker.
Maybe he's sick and
can't leave the capital.
This is his condition.
Our brave Warmaster
is infantilizing!
Huh?
Uh?
Mommy, I made boom‐boom
in my diapey again.
[GROUP]
Uhh...