[RISTA humming]
Wow. I can hardly
believe Master said
that we should go out
and have some fun for once.
Yeah. I was super surprised.
[MASH]
Let's hit the casino, you guys!
[RISTA] Not just yet.
The casino is a nighttime spot.
Besides, we should
save the main course
till after the snack joins us.
[ELULU]
So what now?
We've gotta get
you guys looking fresh,
and the first step is
ditching those filthy outfits.
But this is the only
thing I have to wear.
Ain't nothing money can't fix.
‐‐[ELULU] Yeah?
‐‐[MASH] Really?
Come on. It's time
for some retail therapy!
[ELULU, MASH]
All right!
[ELULU]
This is so cute!
Although, I'm kinda
feeling this one, too.
Hey, look!
Cool leather jacket, huh?
I spy a bathing suit section.
Lots of pool parties here?
The beach is pretty far.
The hot springs are close.
Really?
[SHOPKEEPER 11A] They're
a big attraction in Orphée,
especially the mixed male
and female bathing pools.
Yeah?
[RISTA] Which means Seiya and I
can share a hot bath together.
Oh, man, I think my brain
really is turning into jelly!
Hey, Rista, you feelin' okay?
[RISTA gasps]
Yeah, just checking
out these bathing suits!
Pick out some
for the hot springs!
‐‐[MASH] You mean it?
‐‐[ELULU] Sounds fun!
[chuckles]
[RISTA]
Hmm, these are all so tacky.
I guess I've gotten spoiled
by the high fashion options
we have in the Divine Realm.
Well, this is a more of a
"sword and sorcery" type world,
so... I'll just grab
the best option.
[RISTA grunts]
[RISTA]
She definitely heard that.
This little two‐piece
is in your size.
I think it's gonna look
unbelievably cute on you!
Oh, thank you.
It's totes adorbs!
[RISTA]
I suppose it could be worse,
and when you look around,
it seems like they
may actually be trying.
[SHOPKEEPER 11A]
I think this one will suit
you perfectly, miss.
[RISTA]
Uh, well... It's nice.
Where's the top?
Nowhere. This is a topless model
for the girl who wants
to let it all hang out.
I'm sure it'd look
simply wonderful on you.
[RISTA]
She did overhear me earlier
and now she's trying to make
me look like a complete idiot.
This doesn't qualify
as a bathing suit!
It doesn't even cover the boobs!
Just a little much for you, huh?
It does take a certain type.
What do you think of this?
Our new single‐breasted model.
It's just perfect!
I'm not some trollop!
I'm classy!
I'm sorry,
but it's the new style.
Just try to think of it
like wearing an eye patch
when you've actually
got two good eyes!
It's simply a fun,
carefree little piece.
It's a far cry from
a cosplay eye patch, lady!
Have you ever
actually seen anybody
just chillin' with one
of the girls hangin' out?!
Calm down, Rista.
Surely a goddess can handle
a little swimsuit shopping.
Yeah, but all this
chick is showing me is
the crazy,
super racy‐type stuff!
If these aren't your style,
I have bottomless suits
in stock. Wanna try one?
If you're suggesting suits
without a top or bottom,
why not just say "go nude"?
I'll find one
on my own, thank you.
And Mash, do you mind
grabbing one for Seiya? Ugh!
Oh. Sorry to pry,
but does this Seiya person
happen to be your
boyfriend, by any chance?
Damn right he is!
[MASH, ELULU]
Uhh...
Uh, Rista. That's not true.
[SHOPKEEPER 11A]
Then you might want this.
It's a brand new
open front concept
that some find flattering.
‐‐[ELULU gasps]
‐‐Hard pass.
I'll take it!
[MASH, ELULU gasp]
Say wha‐‐?
[RISTA] Seiya's no elephant, but
I'd sure love to see that trunk!
I'll take one of
these, too, matey!
Yeah, I can slip into this
on a long, steamy night.
‐‐[MASH] I don't get it.
‐‐[ELULU] Why at night?
[RISTA] It's best if you kids
don't think about it too hard.
I was completely hammered off
my ass when I sewed those two.
I never thought anyone
would actually buy them.
I guess I was wrong.
In honor of your
daring fashion choices,
you get a great deal!
Thanks, sister!
[SHOPKEEPER 11A, RISTA]
Hm.
[MAN 11A] Great stuff
at unbelievable prices!
[ELULU]
Ohh... The food looks so good!
I'm so hungry.
Hey, how much longer till we're
supposed to meet up with Master?
Oh, he said that we won't see
him until later on tonight.
So I guess we'll have to
wait for him at the castle.
Let's pig out in our
room till he shows up
and then we'll hit the casino!
[BOTH]
Oh, yeah!
‐‐[RISTA] Hey!
‐‐[GUARD 11A groans]
Look alive, soldier!
[RISTA] So after the casino
we'll stop by the bar,
get a little loose, and then
it's time for the hot spring.
We'll put the rugrats to bed,
so Seiya and I can
have a little fun.
[RISTA giggles]
[RISTA] Who cares?
If Valkyrie can do it, so can I!
Seiya!
Hey! You ready? Let's party!
Uh...
[MASH] Guess he's still
out running errands.
[RISTA] But... it's gonna
be dark pretty soon.
He was pretty clear.
He did say sundown and he's
not really the type to be late.
Well, maybe he's having a hard
time picking something out.
[MASH]
He is a perfectionist, ya know?
Oh, yeah, he sure is.
[RISTA] An hour went by,
and then another.
We waited patiently,
but our hero did not return.
You haven't seen him?!
[ITEM SHOP OWNER 10A] Mm.
Oh, that guy with you earlier?
I haven't seen him since you got
creamed by my medicinal herbs.
Don't bring that up!
But Seiya told us he was gonna
get some stuff to synthesize.
Maybe he went to
someone else's shop.
Hey, are there many other
item or weapon shops in town?
Yeah, I can think
of a few of 'em.
Have I seen a handsome man?
Sad to say, I haven't.
Nobody like that in my shop.
I haven't had a single customer!
[ELULU] Doesn't look like
he's been back here yet.
[MASH] And nobody in the
castle has seen him either.
I have no idea
where he could've gone.
Hey, Rista.
You don't think he went to fight
the Demon Lord alone, do you?
[RISTA]
Huh?
No, Seiya wouldn't do that.
It's completely the opposite
of something he would do.
He barely got through
that Warmaster fight alive,
and he needed time to think.
He mentioned something
about training, too.
And the Demon Lord has that
scary Chain Destruction thing.
So if Seiya loses, he's dead.
I'll bet he's just
over preparing,
since he's overly cautious.
If he's training,
where's he doing that?
‐‐[thud]
‐‐[BOTH gasp]
No clue. I just don't know!
[RISTA] I didn't wanna
do this, but here goes!
Hello?
[RISTA] Huh? Aria,
what are you doing here?
Where is Ishtar?
Seiya's run off somewhere
and I need to find him ASAP.
Oh, what's wrong?
Come with me.
Ishtar is expecting us.
This is the room where
time stands still.
[ISHTAR]
Rista, I'm so glad to see you
and your two young
Dragonkin friends as well.
[ISHTAR]
Under normal circumstances
you would be forbidden
to enter this chamber,
but this is an exception.
Is this the place where the true
souls of all the gods are kept?
[ISHTAR] Rista, I know why
you've sought me out today.
I'll get straight to the point.
The very moment our hero
left the company of your party
he headed to the
Demon Lord's castle, alone.
[BOTH gasp]
But that doesn't seem like him.
He'd never take on that fight
without obsessively
training first.
The stakes are way too high.
This Chain Destruction thing
could destroy his soul!
Not only that...
Yes, such a powerful weapon
could eliminate
your soul as well.
Seiya is very aware
of that particular risk.
In fact, that is precisely
why he chose to go without you.
Huh? Do you mean Seiya
went to slay the Demon Lord
because he was worried about me?
[RISTA chuckles]
That can't be the reason.
I mean, he's always
putting me down
and saying things like
I'm not a real goddess.
He doesn't even like me.
[ISHTAR] It's true he's
ill‐mannered and sharp‐tongued.
But in his heart,
Seiya's a caring young man.
Since he began
his hero's journey,
protecting the people
he truly cherishes
has always been at the
forefront of his mind.
[RISTA]
That's not true.
No, that can't be‐‐
Seriously? He really
cares about us?
[ISHTAR]
Indeed.
You may remember that
Seiya initially resisted
the two of you
joining his party,
but that was because he didn't
want to lose any comrades.
He treated you with
cold detachment,
and always tried
to keep you away
from battle for the same reason.
He struggled to balance
his concern for your safety
with his mission
to protect Gaeabrande.
That's why he rescued you, Mash,
it's why he saved Elulu
in Dragon Village,
and it's why he
risked his own soul
being destroyed by the Warmaster
to get Rista out of harm's way.
I still don't get it!
If his main motivation
has really been
to protect me and
the kids all along,
he could have taken us
back here and trained‐‐
That would be pointless. He
doesn't need further training.
Because the strongest goddess
here has already trained him?
But couldn't he have worked to
raise his level a little more?
[ISHTAR] Look, due to his
Extreme Fake Out skill,
you were never able to
perceive his actual stats.
But I can show you
what he's been hiding.
Wait a second.
He's already maxed out?
[ISHTAR] Correct.
He cannot progress any further.
Incidentally,
these are the same stats
he possessed in Dragon Village,
which means his overall ratings
have not increased
at all since that time.
It's been that long?
Seiya has attempted to
compensate for these stats
by learning new skills,
such as Shining Arrow
and the various Valkyrjas.
This stands as more
evidence of his concern.
But still, he never
said anything about it.
Because that wouldn't
change the situation.
All that would lead to
is unnecessary worrying.
He felt there was more
than enough of that already.
[BOTH gasp]
[RISTA]
No. He can't!
With those numbers
there's no way
he can beat an
S‐class Demon Lord!
[MASH]
But Master has Igzasion.
I‐If he can use that with
the Valkyrjas he's learned...
[RISTA] That sacred sword
he has is just a fake.
Say what?
But he synthesized it with
Elulu and Leviae's blood!
[RISTA] The sword he got
back then was not Igzasion,
it was just a fake to
keep you from worrying.
‐‐[MASH] You're kidding.
‐‐[ELULU] Oh, no.
His skill level has
stopped rising, too.
He has neither the sword
nor sacred armor.
That's exactly why he learned
Valkyrie's most
advanced technique.
It can strike down the enemy,
but the cost is one's own life.
The inescapable Valkyrja:
Gate of Valhalla.
No! Valkyrie told
us that she would never
teach him how to do that move!
[ISHTAR] You witnessed
their destruction aura
investiture
ceremony, didn't you?
[RISTA gasps]
That's how she
gave him the ability
to pull off the
Gate of Valhalla?
Seiya's willingness
to risk his life
to save a world that wasn't his
was enough to convince Valkyrie
to trust him with her
sacred Omega Valkyrja.
But if Seiya actually decides
to use the Gate of Valhalla,
there's no way he'll
be able to survive
what it's gonna do to him!
[ISHTAR] He's determined to
succeed where he failed before.
To protect those dear to him
and to rid himself of
the specter of the past
that has haunted
his subconscious.
To seek redemption.
[RISTA]
I don't understand.
You're telling me all this stuff
and it doesn't
make any sense to me!
Why are we so important, and why
would he need to redeem himself?
[ISHTAR] I can answer
your question, but first,
there is something
that I must ask you.
Tell me, Ristarte,
do you possess a goddesses'
courage to learn the truth?
[TIANA] Does he ever listen
to a single thing we tell him?
I can't deal with this!
[COLT laughs] This is how he
handles everything, isn't it?
Do you actually think
this is funny, Colt?
[ARIA] Relax, Tiana. I'm sure
it'll work out in the end.
It always does, right?
Whose side are you on, Aria?
I just don't think we should
encourage his reckless behavior.
[ARIA] Oh, try not to
let it get under your skin.
[RISTA]
Whoa, Aria, is that you?
[ARIA]
Yes, it is indeed.
And what we're watching
right now is the B level mission
to save a world called Ixphoria.
Ixphoria?
[gasps] Is that Seiya?
[SEIYA] All right, guys,
let's go wipe out the Chimera.
[TIANA]
Hold on, Seiya, we're not ready.
The Chimera's level
is way higher than ours.
We should probably take
some more time to train.
We don't have time.
Sooner we fight, sooner we win.
Besides, I've got a strategy.
Well, could you please
share it with the rest of us?
[SEIYA] Yeah. Let's do
our best. We're fine, relax.
[TIANA gasps] That's the
dumbest thing I've ever heard!
That is not a strategy!
We need to be 100 percent
ready to win no matter what!
[SEIYA] It's gonna be okay.
Everything will work out.
What? We have to take
this battle seriously!
Wait. Seiya,
where are you going?
We're not ready! Seiya!
I don't think
this is a good idea!
[ARIA] Way back then,
Seiya Ryuuguuin was the hero
I'd summoned to take
control of Ixphoria.
What? Then why haven't I
heard about this before now?
Our mage, dressed in
the robes, was named Colt.
The girl‐‐that was
Princess Tiana of Ixphoria.
She was our party's healer.
She joined up with Seiya
along the way to help
defeat the Demon Lord.
[RISTA]
Huh?
[CHIMERA snarls]
[roars]
Colt, use your wind magic!
On it! Here goes!
I'll find an opening
and finish this in no time!
[COLT groans]
‐‐Oh, no!
‐‐Tiana, I need heals!
Okay, just hold still!
[ARIA] Wait, Tiana!
You need to heal Seiya first!
He's down to his last two HP!
What?! Only two? [yelps]
There's a huge
hole in his chest!
Oh, I'll be okay.
I know this looks pretty
bad, but weirdly enough,
it doesn't really
hurt that much.
I'm starting to feel like
this is all just a crazy dream.
You feel that way
because you're about to die!
It's so hard to believe.
He doesn't seem like
the Seiya that I know at all.
No. Although things
were looking grim,
we still made it through.
[roars]
[panting]
Look at that, we won!
You should look at us instead!
We're all in horrible
shape right now!
Yeah, we have been better,
but it's good we beat him.
You think this is good?
Poor Colt had
his leg ripped off!
Tiana, please,
hurry up and heal me.
All right, you guys,
the Golem is our next target,
so we'd better get moving.
[TIANA]
Hey! Did you hear me?!
Colt's got a bloody stump
where his leg used to be!
So weird. Are you
sure that's even Master?
He reminds me of Rosalie.
[ARIA] This is how
Seiya used to behave.
He hated waiting to level up.
All he wanted to do
was keep moving forward.
He foolishly believed that
his innate fighting ability
would be enough.
Even though his rating was low,
and despite the fact
that he was never prepared,
he always managed
to defeat the enemy.
So none of us really
worried all that much.
[RISTA] Sounds to me
like he was more fun then.
Maybe that old Seiya actually
celebrated with his
friends after a victory,
instead of freaking out
about the next fight.
[ARIA] We all relied
on Seiya in those times,
and he relied on us.
‐‐[TIANA] Seiya.
‐‐[SEIYA gasps]
All we gotta do is
beat the Demon Lord.
Yeah, and we're headed
out first thing tomorrow.
You should make sure to
get a good night's sleep.
[TIANA] Oh, I'm way
too nervous to sleep.
Hey, are you sure we don't need
to go to the Sage's village?
[SEIYA] We already have
the weapon we need to win.
So let's not go out
of our way for anything.
But we can get some information
about the Demon Lord there,
according to Aria.
I just wanna beat the Demon Lord
and save the world
as soon as I possibly can.
[TIANA gasps]
You're always in such
a massive hurry, aren't you?
You never make time to
train or anything like that.
Are you ever gonna
tell me why it is
you're in such a crazy rush?
It's not that complicated.
No special reason.
Jeez, every time I bring
it up that's all you say.
This quest ends tomorrow,
so I gotta know why!
What's the real
reason? Just tell me!
[SEIYA sighs] The longer
the Demon Lord is alive,
the longer the people
of this world will suffer.
That's all there is to it.
That's why we
have to end this now.
Okay, it's actually
a good point.
I would have never made it this
far without your healing magic.
Sorry to keep putting you out.
I know that I ask
a lot sometimes.
It's fine, really.
I'm sure things'll
all work out in the end.
So go on and say
what you always say.
I always feel better
after hearing it.
It's gonna be okay.
Everything will work out.
[DEMON LORD groans]
[SEIYA panting]
[DEMON LORD growls]
[SEIYA yells]
[DEMON LORD groans]
Way to go!
And just in the nick of time!
[TIANA]
Is he dead?
[ARIA] The Demon Lord's HP
reads zero! It's over!
Thank goodness.
Ya see?
It's gonna be okay.
Like I told you.
I know you said that,
but you really didn't have
take things down to the wire.
That was close. My MP's at zero.
For real. I'm a goddess
and I nearly died.
[TIANA, COLT laugh]
[thud]
[gasps]
Colt, No!
[COLT groans, screams]
That's impossible.
He was dead just a second ago.
[DEMON LORD cackles]
‐‐[ARIA yelps]
‐‐[TIANA] Aria, no!
I have the power
of an extra life.
Take one and I'll rise from
the dead to have my vengeance!
[ARIA]
This can't be happening!
If only we'd
consulted that sage.
You have to run away
right now! Please, go!
[gasps]
Goddesses are chock
full of nutrients.
I feel so much better
than I have in years!
[SEIYA grunts] Tiana, can you
use your restoration magic?
No, I'm sorry.
My magic's all gone.
There's no need to apologize.
[TIANA]
Seiya.
You were right about everything.
We should've been
better prepared for this.
‐‐[TIANA gasps]
‐‐[SEIYA] Run!
[screams]
I think you'll make
a tasty little snack, girl!
[SEIYA]
Stop! Please, just let her go!
[SEIYA groans]
No. Please...
Seiya.
[DEMON LORD]
Hmm?
‐‐[TIANA screams]
‐‐[DEMON LORD] What's this?
I can sense the faintest
signs of a new life
coming from this woman's belly.
[gasps]
That's your seed growing
inside her, isn't it?
I think I'll have it
for one last appetizer
before the main course.
This mother and child
will be the perfect sacrifice
to usher in the new world!
Please, no!
Stop! I beg you!
Don't do this!
No!
I believe that
we've seen enough.
It wasn't Seiya's fault.
It's mine.
If only we'd gone to the Sage's
village and learned that secret.
As the goddess, I should've
made that happen.
Hey, are you okay?
[ELULU]
Rista!
[RISTA gasps]
[ISHTAR] Have the memories
that once lay dormant
in your soul
re‐emerged, Ristarte?
The poor Princess whose life
the hero was unable to save‐‐
that was you,
before your rebirth
as a goddess of
the Divine Realm.
[gasps, cries]
[ISHTAR] Thanks to Aria's wish,
as well as the good deeds
Princess Tiana
performed during her life,
you were reincarnated as
the goddess you are today.
It was no mere coincidence
that you chose Seiya
to bring salvation
to Gaeabrande.
Fate drew your souls
back together again.
Of course, as with you,
Seiya has no memory
of your shared past life.
But regardless,
the extreme guilt and
regret he felt on that day
has been etched deep
within his soul.
When he was once again
summoned as a hero,
those impressions resurfaced.
They were revealed
in a single word.
What do you mean?
[ISHTAR]
Do you remember when you were
first getting acquainted he
used the word "Properties"?
[gasps]
Properties.
Yeah, I thought he was
just being difficult.
I imagine it was
largely subconscious,
but this‐‐ This was
the image in his mind's eye.
[RISTA]
So that means.
Seiya is quite sharp,
and from this small
passage recorded here,
it seems he was aware he'd
been summoned once before
and of the tragic end
he'd suffered.
[RISTA]
I have to go.
Why would you leave right now?
Obviously, because
I need to help Seiya!
Hold on, please don't go!
Rista, I can't stomach the
thought of losing you again.
Although, I'm thankful for
everything you've done for me,
I can't stay here.
But, Rista.
I can't sit back while Seiya
puts himself in harm's way.
[ARIA gasps]
At this point, the Demon Lord
has the power to destroy gods,
so I would not fault you
for staying behind with us.
In fact, I recommend
you do stay behind.
Seiya took measures to ensure
your safety. That was his wish.
Will you defy him?
[RISTA]
Yeah, you're damn right I will!
[ISHTAR gasps]
This portal that you've opened
leads to the Demon Lord's castle
where the final battle awaits.
You realize that by entering,
you overstep your role
of support goddess.
I know that.
I'll face those consequences.
‐‐[MASH] Rista!
‐‐[ELULU] Wait up!
There's no reason for
you to risk your lives.
So if you really want
to go back to Gaeabrande,
get Ishtar to send you
when this is over.
[MASH]
Don't be stupid! We're going!
The only reason that
we're still alive
is because Seiya helped us out!
So we're gonna help him!
Really?
I realize there's no point
in trying to stop you.
[RISTA]
Yeah.
All I ask is
that you be careful.
I'll do my best.
[RISTA]
Hold on, Seiya, I'm coming.
I'm not sure I'll
be able to save you.
But I'm your friend,
so I have to try!
The least I can do
is not let you die alone!