[RISTA]
Hold on, Seiya, I'm coming.
I'm not sure I'll
be able to save you.
But I'm your friend,
so I have to try!
The least I can do is
not let you die alone!
[RISTA gasps]
The air feels so weird.
It's like I can sense
that Chain Destruction thing.
[ELULU] Uh, guys,
I don't like this place.
[MASH]
Is this the Demon Lord's castle?
[RISTA] Yeah, we're
right in the heart of it.
And that means what's next
will be the final showdown.
There's no doubt.
[crash]
[RISTA gasps]
[RISTA]
Seiya!
[chuckles, grunts]
Oh, no.
Please don't do it, Seiya!
Omega Valkyrja.
If you use that move,
it's gonna kill you!
Gate of Valhalla!
[XENOS LORD grunts]
Seiya! [grunts]
[XENOS LORD grunts] You broke
through my anti‐magic field!
[laughing]
[grunts, gasps]
[SEIYA]
A Valkyrja's not magic.
So whatever little barrier you
put up was destined to fail.
[XENOS LORD]
A Valkyrja?
This can't be. [groans]
But how?!
The only thing that can cause
me bodily harm is Igzasion!
This must be some
kind of illusion,
some trick to make
me believe‐‐ [groaning]
[XENOS LORD screams]
[XENOS LORD yells]
[RISTA]
Whoa!
I thought we had him!
He's clawing his
way out of the gate!
No, this is not good.
[XENOS LORD] You shouldn't
trifle with me, human! [yells]
[SEIYA]
I'd never trifle with
an S‐ranked Demon Lord
of Gaeabrande.
But I have considered your
responses to this situation.
[SEIYA grunts]
Try this Phoenix Thrust!
Seiya really does
need the sacred sword.
[XENOS LORD] You claim
to take the fight seriously,
yet still try to prick me
with this needle?
Begone!
‐‐[MASH] Master!
‐‐[ELULU] Seiya!
[SEIYA]
Eternal Sword EX!
[XENOS LORD] I told you
your attacks won't work on me,
but you foolishly
refuse to listen!
[XENOS LORD groans]
[XENOS LORD]
No!
This isn't the sacred sword,
so how can it cut my flesh?
Wait. What is that?
[SEIYA]
Heh.
No way! It's the doll
I made from my hair.
This is so embarrassing!
I get it now! Master used
his Synthesis technique!
Looks like he used it on
the spikes in the gate!
[RISTA gasps]
[XENOS LORD gasping]
[SEIYA] An infernal sword
not of this world.
Valhalla Thrust!
‐‐[XENOS LORD groaning]
‐‐[SEIYA yelling]
[GATE OF VALHALLA 12A laughing]
You took him out! Way to go!
You good?
[RISTA]
Seiya!
It's already getting to you.
Just try to hold on, okay?
[SEIYA]
Rista.
You used some kinda shortcut
to get here, didn't you?
Whatever happened to following
the rules of the Divine Realm?
[RISTA] What?! Why the hell
would you bring that up now?
If you die here, you won't
be able to go back home,
don't you remember?
That's true, but I still
beat the Demon Lord.
[RISTA] You're the most
cautious person in the world.
How could you not
have figured out
how to beat him without
dying in the process?
I don't know, but...
‐‐[ELULU gasps] Seiya!
‐‐[MASH] Master!
[RISTA]
I won't let you die here.
[MASH, ELULU]
Rista!
You're not getting away
with this, understand me?
You already stood us up!
We were supposed to
go out and have some fun!
All I wanted was
to have a few drinks,
play around, hang out at a hot
springs in our bathing suits,
and actually enjoy a little
time together for once!
Order! Release all
the healing power
possessed by the Goddess
Ristarte, right now!
[ISHTAR] Ristarte,
you have violated the rules
of the Divine Realm
by using a gateway
to move to your final location.
It's possible our tribunal will
strip you of your goddess
ranking, and I cannot shield you
from this punishment
if you go further.
I don't care.
That doesn't scare me.
I've made my peace.
Plus, I'm pretty
sure this is why
I became a goddess
in the first place,
so I'll deal with
the consequences!
[ISHTAR]
Very well.
As long as you understand
what's at stake,
I'll grant you all
your divine power.
Whoa, so cool!
Rista's really
amazing, isn't she?
[RISTA] I may have
failed you in my past life,
but I believe I
was given this power
to make up for that failure.
And now, I'm gonna save you.
My healing skill is stronger
than the Gate of Valhalla.
Hear that? I learned from you.
This time I'm
perfectly prepared!
[ELULU, MASH gasp]
Something's going wrong!
The more you heal him, the worse
his wounds are getting!
It's okay, 'cause I'm gonna
save you. I promise I will.
Both of us are gonna have
a happy ending this time...
...right, Seiya?
Wow, you just saved
his life, didn't you?
Think so. The recoil from
the Gate of Valhalla is over.
[SEIYA grunts]
‐‐[MASH] Master!
‐‐[ELULU] He's all right!
Hang on. I'm still
alive, aren't I?
Yeah, you are! Thank goodness!
It's all thanks to Rista!
It's just like
you're a real goddess!
Hey. I am a real
goddess, thank you.
[ALL gasp]
Did you actually
save my life just now?
Sure did. It was all me.
[RISTA]
Hey, what's the matter?
[SEIYA]
Hard pass.
Aw, come on, don't be so shy!
I mean, after all we've
been through together?
We're like the definition
of soul mates now!
A little smooch is the
very least we could do!
Cut it out, okay?
I have no idea what
you mean by that.
[RISTA]
You don't have to pretend
like you don't feel it, too!
As a goddess,
I command you to kiss me!
If you don't back off now,
I'm gonna punch you.
[RISTA] Wow! Since you're
such a tsundere type,
this actually means that
you love me, doesn't it? Ahh!
You only act like this because
you're embarrassed how strong
your feelings really are‐‐ Agh!
I warned you, didn't I?
Jeez, punch‐drunk, you think
that was a tad excessive?
You do know that if I die here,
I can't come back either!
[SEIYA] You say that
like it's a bad thing.
I should slug you.
[SEIYA]
Then again...
...it's pretty impressive
that you were able to heal me.
All right.
I'll admit you're slightly more
useful than a medicinal herb.
Abusive and a jerk, too!
[ELULU]
Wait.
Hey, Rista.
Do you know why the Gate of
Valhalla hasn't disappeared?
[GATE OF VALHALLA 12A groaning]
[XENOS LORD]
I'll take you all down with me!
Annihilate you and this
entire world in one fell swoop!
Judgment Zero!
[RISTA]
What was I thinking?
I should've known it
wouldn't be this easy.
And that ball of black light
has the power to destroy
the world twice over!
Everything on this planet
will be turned to dust.
That means us, too.
This is it.
Not on my watch.
[gasps]
[XENOS LORD grunts]
Gate of Valhalla!
Don't do it, Seiya!
Once more!
[RISTA gasps]
[GATE OF VALHALLA 12B]
[XENOS LORD] Damn you!
Beaten by a lowly human?
You'll pay for this!
[XENOS LORD yelling]
[laughing]
[MASH, ELULU gasp]
So is it over this time?
Ya know, for good?
Now don't get
yourself all worked up‐‐
both he and the first gate
have been swallowed.
That thing's talking to us!
[laughs] The Demon Lord has
been taken from this world
and thrown into the void.
Time to collect my payment‐‐
the life of the caster.
That is the cost
of summoning me!
No way! Don't worry, Seiya!
I swear I'll save you again.
[gasps] What's happening to you?
This is different
from last time.
‐‐[ELULU] Seiya!
‐‐[MASH] Master!
[RISTA]
Seiya!
Oh, no!
He's falling apart faster
than I can heal him!
You were far too naive.
It's extremely foolish to
believe that a mere human
could ever escape the Gate of
Valhalla's toll more than once.
Shut up, Gate Face!
Hang in there, Seiya!
[RISTA]
I need to concentrate
and focus all my
energy into healing him!
[RISTA]
Why is this happening?
Seiya just saved this world!
Don't kill him!
[GATE OF VALHALLA 12B cackles]
I don't care what he's done!
I'm just a servant
of the underworld,
here to collect payment.
Chain Destruction doesn't
exist in the Divine Realm,
so if we go back there,
maybe Seiya won't die for real!
He should be able to go back
to his original world if
he dies, so open up a portal!
[RISTA]
can't.
Look, if I take my focus off
healing him for even a second,
he's gonna fall apart.
[MASH]
No!
Hey, squirt, thanks for helping
me out with the Warmaster.
Save your strength.
If it weren't for
your support magic,
I probably would've
been killed in that fight.
But now... you're dying.
If I had turned into
that sword, you'd be fine.
You wouldn't have to give up
your own life for this!
I'm sorry.
Well, bro,
now that the Four Heavenly Kings
and Demon Lord are history,
there's no one in this
world that you can't beat.
You're gonna need
to work with Rosalie
and keep things
safe around here.
You can't just leave us, Master.
Please stay.
I never even got the chance
to properly thank you!
Stop it! Stop talking like that!
I said I would save you,
so that's what I'm gonna do!
[SEIYA groans]
But why? You should be healing!
Why is this happening?
It's over for me, Rista.
You can't give up!
Don't let it end like this!
I failed you in my past life,
but I'm a goddess now!
This isn't right.
It's okay.
You did the best that you could.
[RISTA]
But it wasn't enough.
A goddess should be able to
save her friend's life, right?
[RISTA]
I'm useless.
I can't help you when
you need it the most.
I'm so sorry.
[SEIYA] It's weird.
This feels familiar...
...like it's all
happened before.
I get it now.
It's you.
You're why‐‐
You're why I'm here.
[RISTA gasps]
I'm so glad that I was actually
able to save you this time.
[RISTA gasps]
So you're really leaving?
[RISTA]
Mm.
Thanks to all your work
in defeating the Demon Lord,
Gaeabrande's been saved.
We should throw
a parade of honor
and give you a huge
reward at least.
Don't worry about that,
and besides, the one who
really deserves the praise
gave up his life for this world.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
But let me say one thing.
Huh?
[ROSALIE]
He may not have cared about
what others thought of him,
and he could come off
as somewhat harsh,
but Seiya always stuck to
what he truly believed in.
And the way I see it,
that's the defining quality
of a bona fide hero.
It's true.
And everything he
accomplished on Gaeabrande
was something no ordinary hero
could've ever dreamed
of pulling off.
[RISTA] For their part in
defeating the Demon Lord,
Mash and Elulu, our
little Dragonkin friends,
were both knighted by Rosalie.
I know you're gonna
do great things.
Thank you.
Master saved this world,
so I have to do everything
I can to keep it safe. [gasps]
[ELULU laughs]
Don't worry,
'cause I'll be
watching over him.
[RISTA] Hmm. Well, that
does ease my mind a little.
You really gonna
go back home, Rista?
I am. I can't stay
here forever, ya know?
[ELULU]
I'll miss you!
I'll miss you, too.
[ELULU]
Come back and see us sometime.
We can go to the hot springs!
We still need to hit the casino!
You're right.
Sounds like fun to me.
You promise?
You'll really visit?
Yeah, of course I will.
[RISTA]
All right, this is it.
[ROSALIE]
Goddess Ristarte.
[RISTA]
Huh?
I'm having trouble
with Father's death.
But the strength and courage
you've shown is a
real inspiration to me.
I'm not that strong, but...
I know that I owe it to Seiya
to be the very best
goddess that I can be.
That's what keeps me going.
Guess that's how I should
approach things, too.
I have to lead this
empire forward.
I know it will be
in good hands with you.
But all I ask is that you make
sure to take care of those two.
Don't give them any
crazy orders, okay?
I'll keep that in mind.
[RISTA]
Hm.
Now give our savior
goddess a salute!
[RISTA gasps]
The two of them looked
so grown up just now.
I'm so proud of
how far they've come.
[SEIYA]
Huh.
So you're just gonna
slack off again.
Seiya?
[RISTA gasps]
[RISTA panting]
[gasps]
[RISTA]
He's really gone.
[lock clicks, door opens]
I could swear I locked the door.
[ARIA] Locked doors mean nothing
to the goddess of opening seals.
[ARIA]
Sorry to drop in unannounced.
Ishtar is asking for you.
[gasps] Okay, thank you.
I'm coming.
[ARIA] Goodness.
Looking a little rough.
Let me fix your hair for you.
You know, if I had to guess,
I'm pretty sure that Ishtar
needs to speak with you
about opening
that shortcut portal
and releasing your goddess
powers back in Gaeabrande.
Yeah. I know I'll
be punished for that.
I knew I was breaking
the rules when I did it.
You needn't worry.
After all, that world was a
level S and you still saved it.
I'll try to make sure
that's taken into consideration.
Now you're looking much better.
[RISTA]
Hmm.
Honestly, I wish I felt better.
R‐Rista, I really
hope that you're doing okay.
Oh, I'm sure I'll be fine,
but I appreciate
your concern, Adenela.
I know you were fond of Seiya,
too, so it means a lot.
W‐Well, I'm way more concerned
about you than I am about me.
I'm sad, but it's
probably nothing
compared to what
you're feeling right now.
Hey there, Rista.
I heard you were
down in the dumps,
so here's something
that might help.
At least your taste
buds will be happy.
I'm trying a new thing
with this frozen cake.
Y‐You really think a cake
is gonna make it better?
Have you lost your damn mind?
Huh, uh, sorry. I, uh...
[ADENELA]
N‐Now, Rista, d‐don't force it.
It's so delicious. Didn't
know I liked protein cake.
Well, this one's
actually a frozen cake.
Then I guess I'm a fan
of frozen protein cakes.
I think you may be
misunderstanding me.
It's not a protein
cake of any ki‐‐
[whimpers]
O‐Okay, still it has protein.
Yeah, of course!
There's plenty in there.
Gotta build those muscles!
I think if you cut back
on that a little bit,
the next one will turn out
way better, but thanks.
[MITIS] Oh, no, in my opinion he
should add even more next time.
Personally speaking,
I can't seem to ever get
enough of that manly protein!
You should go back to
your forest right now, Mitis.
If Ishtar sees you,
she'll get angry.
Let me enjoy myself a second.
I was only out
here looking to see
if there was a
hunky new hero, so...
[ARIA]
Mitis!
Oh, you bitties are just no fun.
Bye for now, Ristarte, I hope
you have a wonderful day.
You, too...
[MITIS panting]
I really wouldn't worry about
this too much if I were you.
[RISTA grunts]
Nice work, Ristarte.
Really pulled it off.
I heard what
happened to your hero,
but I don't regret
teaching him that move.
That's just what it took.
Guess so.
Man, you really look like crap.
But to be honest,
that's a step up for you.
[RISTA grunts]
That a compliment?
I'd like to paint
your portrait sometime.
But only if you promise
you won't look like a kid
who just lost her lollipop.
[ISHTAR]
Rista,
I'm extremely proud that you
were able to save Gaeabrande.
And seeing that you've
returned home safe and unharmed
makes me very happy.
Thank you.
[ISHTAR]
My feelings notwithstanding,
the Divine Realm
tribunal deliberated
on your violation of rules
and has come to a decision.
Whatever the punishment is,
you must accept it.
Excuse me. Although
Ristarte broke the rules
regarding protocol,
she did save that world.
I ask that you give her
success due consideration
when handing down the penalty.
I have considered that,
and your punishment will be
to save the double
S‐difficulty world Ixphoria.
[ARIA gasps] But that's a world
that's already been conquered
by a Demon Lord!
He killed our hero,
gained immense power,
and turned the whole place
into a demonic realm!
Please allow me to
go there in her place!
I will not.
‐‐[ARIA] I beg you!
‐‐[ISHTAR] Take heed, Rista.
While on your mission
to save Ixphoria,
your divine powers of healing
will be unavailable to you.
If the mission fails,
you will forevermore lose
your status as goddess.
But, Ishtar, that world has
already taken so much from her.
Isn't there some
other way she can atone?
It's way too harsh!
And if she doesn't
have the power
to meaningfully
support her hero,
saving a world as far gone
as that one won't just be hard,
it'll be completely impossible!
I don't see it that way.
In fact, I don't believe it will
be impossible in the slightest.
[ARIA]
How can you say that?
And what kind of hero could
realistically save a hellscape
that's under the control
of a bloodthirsty demon?!
[ARIA gasps]
[ARIA]
Please forgive me.
[ISHTAR]
When the second Gate of Valhalla
was used to defeat
this last Demon Lord,
it also swallowed up the effects
of the Chain Destruction.
[ARIA]
So what does that mean?
[RISTA gasps]
[ISHTAR] Ordinarily,
when one fails a world,
they can never return to it.
But...
[gasps]
Ristarte,
in order to take back control
of the double S‐level world
Ixphoira, you must summon
a hero from this list only.
No exceptions.
[RISTA gasps]
[ISHTAR] The ability
levels have been reset
to less than a thousandth
of what they were.
I think he'll do just fine.
Thanks!
[RISTA] Written at
the bottom was something
I once thought of
as a disadvantage.
Now I know it can
take down a Demon Lord
and save a world on
the brink of destruction.
A trait that kept me alive
despite all the danger.
And a mindset that
can only be granted
through reflection
on one's past mistakes.