[ARIA]
See? It all worked out.
Yeah. Maybe I
overreacted just a bit.
Well, Adenela is a goddess.
She knows better than to
take a human life like that.
And Seiya is capable of handling
just about anything by himself.
[RISTA] Hm. I wish I could be
as levelheaded as you, Aria.
It's so weird.
You'd think I'd know Seiya
better by now, but I don't.
Uh, well, I could only
make an informed guess
because you talk
about him non‐stop.
Speaking of which,
let's change the subject.
Hey, there, Mash.
You mind showing Rista
what you've been up to?
[MASH]
Um, sure.
Oh. What did you do?
[ARIA] I released one of his
Dragon Metamorphosis seals.
By gaining a dragon appendage,
his attack power has
jumped several levels.
Yeah! Ya like that?
Pretty cool, right?
Uh, well, you say cool,
I say kinda creepy,
but it's your arm, so...
What's so creepy
about it, Rista?
I know, right?
By itself, it's awesome!
But with the rest of him,
meh, not so much.
What's wrong with
the rest of me?!
Tell me how you really feel!
That's not very nice, you two.
Mash has worked very hard
to achieve his special skill:
The Comically
Colossal Dragon Claw!
What is this,
Bust Mash's Balls Day?
Mash, you really
need to slow your roll.
Eh, heh, heh.
Why, you...
‐‐Uh, okay. Also pretty creepy.
‐‐[MASH] ...little goober!
You're so dead! I never...
Wait, I recognize this spell.
Yes. It's support magic
that slows an opponent down‐‐
Delay.
No way.
The dormant power you sensed
in Elulu was support magic?
[ARIA]
Correct.
‐‐[yelps]
‐‐Fix this!
Speed me up!
[ELULU] Okay, fine!
Let's turn things up a notch.
Eh, heh, heh.
[MASH]
Uhh...
You knew damn well what I meant,
Elulu, and this was not it!
You've had your fun,
so change me back already!
Enough is enough...
She can also cast Haste?
When did she learn one spell,
much less its counter?
She acquired these new
talents fairly recently.
I suspect your
desire to help others
was the cause of this
exciting development.
[giggles]
[MASH] Do you understand the
words coming out of my mouth?
No, because I'm faster
than the speed of sound!
[crash]
Yes! I think Delay and Haste
are just what Seiya
needs for support!
Good work, both of you!
Why does the sadist
get all the damn praise?
I expect to see both
of you again sometime.
By then, Elulu will
know more magic, and, Mash,
you'll have mastered
your Dragon Metamorphosis.
‐‐Right!
‐‐Yep! I can hardly wait!
Oh. I would've
come to you sooner
if I'd known you could help
boost their strength like this.
[ARIA] Mm‐mm. Everything
you've done has had a purpose.
Thanks to the experience
these two had gained,
their talents were able
to blossom beautifully.
[ELULU, MASH]
Hmm.
Yeah! We're gonna
be tough to beat.
Especially with Seiya's
new bow abilities.
Did you just say bow?
Please don't tell me.
Mitis isn't the one teaching
him this time around, is she?
Yes. Only the best for Seiya.
That and I'm pretty sure
she's the only archery goddess.
[ARIA]
How could you be so stupid?
That woman is
utterly terrifying!
What? Uh, you mean like even
more terrifying than Adenela?
The two don't compare
in the slightest,
and that's putting it mildly!
Do you know why she was banished
to live in the Divine Forest?
[RISTA]
Mm‐mm.
[ARIA]
She's a nymphomaniacal goddess
that will prey on
any hero summoned.
If they cross her path,
she abducts and
sexually devours them!
‐‐Guhh!
‐‐Sexually?
It's the reason Ishtar drove
her out into the forest!
Allowing men anywhere near
her is absolutely forbidden!
[RISTA]
But they're just training!
I swear. I saw it myself!
[ARIA] Mitis must be
savoring her quarry
and waiting till the last day.
I bet she's ready to explode!
Oh, no, no, oh!
[ARIA] Sexual relations
between a goddess
and a human are forbidden.
He won't come back from this.
It's a one and done situation!
One and done?
For a stupid hookup?
What are you still doing here?
Go find Seiya this instant!
And step on it!
[RISTA] I refuse to allow my
one in a hundred million hero
to get booted for divine booty,
unless it's my divine booty!
I take it back!
I take that back!
If I twist my ankle running
in wedges, he is gonna pay!
Seiya!
[gasps]
[RISTA] Uh, so... You guys
just hangin' out, or...?
[SEIYA]
I mean she is.
She asked me to
give her ten minutes
to get ready for something.
Apparently, it's Bondage 101.
[MITIS chuckles]
Think of this exercise
as one last test, Seiya.
Use a volley of
three light arrows
to score hits on these ropes.
That shouldn't be too
challenging for you.
Oh. So this is like a final
exam for all of your training!
But freaky!
[MITIS] If you succeed,
my naked body will be released.
You will then catch me and learn
from my vast carnal knowledge.
Vast, huh? That's a weird flex.
[MITIS]
I've been patient.
These past three days have
been nothing but torture!
Especially with a man as
handsome as you are. Hit me!
Do it, Seiya!
Release me from these ropes
and then release me
again with your body!
[RISTA]
Sounds messy.
Seiya, step away
from the nympho!
[SEIYA]
Don't nympho boss me.
[RISTA]
Your call, but remember,
succeeding means letting
her sloppy bits go free!
[SEIYA]
I'm not worried.
Seiya! You just discharged
right in her face!
[MITIS groans]
I realize she's
immortal and all,
but you just don't go
for the head like that!
‐‐Have you lost it?
‐‐[BOTH gasp]
[MITIS]
Oh, Seiya.
That's not the kind of
foreplay I had in mind.
[MITIS grunting]
[MITIS chuckles]
Here's a bondage tip:
Never put yourself in
a position you cannot escape.
[gasps]
No, sir! Eyes off.
[MITIS] If I were to give a
grade for that last shot,
it would be a failing one.
[grunts]
[MITIS] I hope you're
ready for your retest.
[RISTA]
Seiya, pull out!
Now then, prepare yourself,
because I'm going to attack.
Try to stop me. I dare you.
Think of this as
a more intensive
and hands‐on part
of your training!
[RISTA] Naked training
is not a thing, please stop!
[MITIS]
Ready...
...go!
[MITIS screaming]
[MITIS groaning]
[SEIYA]
Three Shot Shining Arrow.
[RISTA]
Ugh. I threw up in my mouth.
[MITIS chuckles]
Goddesses do not die!
You can't stop me
no matter how hard you are!
Uh, do all goddesses
have a side like this?
Pretty sure she's
a demon in disguise!
[yelps]
[RISTA]
Get your lust eyes off Mash!
An appetizer before the
main course sounds divine!
I like 'em when they're young.
Age is just a number after all!
Run, Mash, she's
gone full pervert!
[MASH whimpering]
[MITIS yelling]
[MITIS]
First, I'll strip you down!
Then I'll lay you down!
And finally, I'll wear you down
until you're too
exhausted to move!
[screams]
I knew Taters would
be your next target.
Someone as thirsty as you
will drink just about anything.
[MITIS groans]
Five Shot Shining Arrow,
for her pleasure.
[MITIS panting]
To be penetrated
so many times...
I don't know what
any of her words mean.
It's weird. What pain
makes you happy?
Huh‐uh! Not appropriate!
Oh, yeah. That was amazing.
I'm completely spent.
Seeing you shoot five shots in a
row unmade me in a glorious way.
You're the best
I've ever had, Seiya.
I am perfectly prepared.
I am 100 percent ready for this.
Ugh. If I never see
that vulgar goddess again
it will still be too soon.
Wait. Why is it so quiet?
[CARLO]
Ah! So you've returned.
Captain Rosalie
decided to head off
toward the flies'
lair by herself.
What? Why'd she do that?
I mean, we said
we'd be right back!
Bhat and the others are going
after the captain on horseback.
We should follow
them immediately.
[SEIYA] So predictable.
It's only been an hour.
I highly doubt she's
run into trash breath yet.
It's possible.
‐‐[SEIYA] Chill, bro.
‐‐Huh?!
[SEIYA]
We'll catch up to her.
Hm. We'll keep a lookout here.
[RISTA]
Perfect location!
We can see them and their
lair, but they can't see us!
[RISTA gasps]
[RISTA]
It's her! She's an idiot.
A brave idiot,
but still an idiot.
That's Light's Blessing,
which must be one of her skills.
It's protecting her
from those mob attacks.
She just became
the perfect decoy.
[RISTA gasps]
Cool. Now I can
snipe Beetle Face.
You predicted this?
That's why we came here instead
of going straight for Rosalie!
You know you can swat more
flies with honey and what not.
Aw, crap. Way to go, Rista.
[RISTA]
Huh? What did I do?
[SEIYA] Flies have an
exceptional sense of smell.
They came over 'cause
you're stinking up
our lookout with
your goddess stink.
What stink would that be?!
You're joking, right, Seiya?
Hey, you guys smell anything?
Uh, you don't smell
that strong today.
Not enough to be
super concerned about.
So I do stink?!
[ELULU] Uh... It's like
an old lady's laundry?
[SEIYA]
All of you shut up!
It's all or nothing.
I'm going for a headshot.
[RISTA]
Can you do it?
That was the lamest
question ever. Uh‐‐
Oh, look! We found the hero!
We were wondering if
you would ever show up!
Mister! Please, will you be
quiet? The flies will hear us!
Ahh! I offer you
my sincerest apology!
Now you're you being
even louder, dude!
Hate to break it to you, Master,
but those flies are
gunning straight for us!
Stay calm. I'm still on it.
I was ready for something
like this to happen.
I'm Rosalie Roseguard,
the Warmaster's daughter!
Hey, Beel Bub!
Come and give me a fair fight!
[RISTA screaming]
What's she thinking?! Stop!
Not a problem.
Saw that coming, too.
[RISTA]
I'm starting to wonder
if there's anything
you didn't see coming!
‐‐[ROSALIE grunts]
‐‐[SEIYA sighs]
[ROSALIE]
You stupid fly‐jerk! Let me go!
[RISTA]
Did your psychic powers tell you
the Warmaster's daughter
would get taken hostage?!
[RISTA shrieks]
My boob! Sweet charity!
I get you're frustrated, but
don't take it out on the ladies!
I'm not.
I just lost my decoy
and I need another one.
Go be useful for once.
Um... you want me to be a decoy?
I got a plan.
You have to buy me
some time, though.
[RISTA] You're really
putting me on the spot here!
How am I supposed
to distract them?
You could say, "Nice
weather we're having, huh?"
Just like that.
Nice weather we're having, huh?
Remember, don't take your
eyes off What's‐her‐face.
If you can do that,
we'll be good.
[RISTA]
Okay, fine!
[RISTA grunts]
[SEIYA]
I'll clear a pathway for you.
Don't worry, stinky. Just fly.
Oh, right.
Thanks for the backup!
And would you please
stop calling me stinky?!
Stop right there!
[BEEL BUB]
Ah?
Judging from those wings,
you must be a goddess.
If you're on Gaeabrande,
that means you have
that meathead hero with you.
[RISTA] Yeah, well he wanted me
to relay a message: Let her go!
[BEEL BUB]
Not to worry.
I was just using this girl
as bait to lure the hero out.
[RISTA] Wait! You're
seriously gonna release her?
[BEEL BUB] Yes, but only
once I'm considerably higher.
In honor of your
hero's downfall,
I'm preparing
a Reverse Firework!
[BEEL BUB]
Any thoughts?
Is this not an excellent height
for you to make
a beautiful firework?
[ROSALIE grunts]
I'm gonna make you
apologize for the men
you killed if it's
the last thing I do!
[gasps]
[BEEL BUB] Considering
you're about to join those men,
I'd say you're in no
position to demand apologies.
‐‐You bastard!
‐‐[RISTA] That's enough!
Your hero said he
would be back by now!
Is he still training?
Not in front of the bug!
[BEEL BUB]
Huh? Training?
That means he's planning to
attack me with a bow and arrow?
[RISTA] Oh, well that's just
great! He's a psychic, too!
[BEEL BUB] Guess I'll
have to gain more altitude
to really set this one off!
[ROSALIE grunting]
[RISTA grunts]
[RISTA] He's flying
higher so magic arrows
have no chance of hitting him!
Way to be the worst
distraction ever, Rista.
[ROSALIE grunts]
[BEEL BUB chuckles] Now, to
treat myself to the sight of you
exploding into tiny
red and pink pieces!
Hmm. I'll have to fling you
to the ground as hard as I can
so she can't catch you.
[RISTA] If he throws
her with all his strength,
I'll never catch her!
Hey, coward!
Get back on the ground
and fight me like a man!
[BEEL BUB] I'm not a man,
I just dress like one.
The only thing you'll
be fighting is gravity!
[RISTA]
Ah! I'm out of options!
[RISTA shrieks]
[BEEL BUB]
Uhh?
So, nice weather
we're having, huh?
Life above the
clouds, am I right?
[BEEL BUB]
Um, what are you talking about?
[RISTA] Hngh! I have no idea!
Any time now, Seiya!
[BEEL BUB grunts]
[yells]
Gotcha! [gasps]
[RISTA] Whoa. Didn't factor
in the weight of your armor.
It's pretty heavy, but I
think we're gonna be okay.
Sorry about that.
[RISTA]
That was Shining Arrow.
Somehow, Seiya managed
to reach him, but...
[BEEL BUB]
Doesn't make any sense!
Even magic arrows
don't have that range!
I've done my research,
and it's not possible.
Oh, yeah? Why is that?
[BEEL BUB] I factored in
the effective trajectory
when I flew this high up.
I don't care what
magic arrows he's using,
there's no way they
could span such distance.
[RISTA] My hero is one
in a hundred million, Bub!
Get used to disappointment!
[BEEL BUB] However gifted
he is, it's still unlikely.
He doubtlessly flew after us
until he was close enough
to fire off a shot.
Like a stalker outside a window,
he's hiding somewhere
in the clouds as we speak.
[RISTA]
His brain may be fly‐sized,
but he's just as
perceptive as Seiya.
[BEEL BUB]
I am the fastest of all
the Demon Lord's
forces in the air!
You may call me
the Lord of the Skies!
[RISTA] I have no clue
where you are, Seiya,
but you better not
miss him again!
[BEEL BUB]
Oh, hero,
I would exceedingly like
to see your bow skills!
I won't even hide from you!
Scale of one to ten‐‐
how confident are you in
your stupid hero right now?
Um, I'd say a ten?
I mean, he said
that cheesy line.
[RISTA gasps]
[RISTA]
Seven lights?
Is that a Seven
Shot Shining Arrow?
He's trying to one‐up the
goddess of freaking archery!
It can't be avoided!
[BEEL BUB chuckles]
Rolling Dodge!
‐‐[RISTA gasping]
‐‐He evaded all seven!
No! Is this when we lose? Seiya!
[RISTA] Geabrande is basically
the ultimate difficulty level.
[BEEL BUB]
There you are.
I'm coming, hero!
Seiya, watch out! You're
no match for him in the air!
[BEEL BUB chuckles]
‐‐[thud]
‐‐[BEEL BUB groans]
[BEEL BUB]
That hurts.
Holy hole.
[BEEL BUB]
This bites!
Huh? Are those magic
lights or magic birds?
[RISTA] That kind of technique
definitely belongs to Seiya!
But when did he use it?
‐‐[ROSALIE] I get it!
‐‐[gasps]
Once Beel Bub dodged the arrows,
they became birds and
flew back like a boomerang.
I think you're right!
I bet it has
a ridiculous name like
Transform Automatic Garuda!
That's my Seiya!
[BEEL BUB]
Damn you!
I'm gonna be the firework now!
[BEEL BUB screams]
[RISTA] What goes on in
that beautiful head of his?
Even though he outdid
Mitis by two arrows,
he made a backup attack
just in case they missed!
Seiya Ryuuguuin‐‐
the only guy tough
enough to save Gaeabrande,
while staying cautious
every step of the way
and lookin' damn fine doin' it!
[BHAT] Thank goodness
you're safe, Captain Rosalie!
Yeah.
[MASH]
Master!
That was fan‐freakin'‐tastic!
[ELULU]
It really was!
That bug‐brain
didn't stand a chance!
Hey, hotshot! Pretty slick move.
The Transform Automatic Garuda!
What are you
babbling about now?
Ah, sorry. That's just
a silly name I came up with.
So what's it called?
You know, that move
when your light arrows
turn into birds
and ricochet back?
Oh. You're referring to
Boomerang Birdie Boom Boom.
What?! That's awful. You
can't seriously call it that.
I didn't think of it
until just this second.
Ah. Great! Feel free
to use my name, if you want.
[SEIYA]
I don't want to.
It's way too long and
stinks as bad as you do.
You're so mean!
Nothing about me stinks!
Uh‐‐
The title of hero
doesn't suit you.
Your victory was
anything but chivalrous.
A true hero is someone
who strikes down his
foe without trickery‐‐
just like my father does.
[RISTA]
Now, look.
Rosalie, the only reason
you're standing here right now
is because of Seiya!
You could at least thank him!
A little help here?
Just try not to be offensive!
Nothing I say will make a
difference, so let's drop it.
Yeah, but... [muttering]
Barky just likes the
sound of her own woof.
[ROSALIE]
What was that?!
[growling]
Ah! She's losing it again!
[RISTA] Whether it's shooting
arrows or slinging insults,
Seiya's lethal in
everything he does!
[ROSALIE]
Gah!
Okay. Time to take out
the remaining flies.
Tater Tot, Short Stack,
let's see what you're made of.
‐‐[MASH gasps]
‐‐[ELULU] Really?
You're letting the kids take the
reins? That's so sweet of you.
Sure. It's not like I'm
not blind or anything.
I can tell they've been training
and have not only leveled up,
but also gained abilities.
Yeah! We have!
It's true!
[SEIYA] Hop to it. I wanna
see maximum effort out there.
I'll make you proud,
wait 'n see!
Yeah! Wait 'n see!
[MASH, ELULU]
Uhh....
Nice.
[MASH]
Master...
[ELULU] I feel betrayed.
So very betrayed.
You're up, Short Stack.
Speed Taters up
with your haste magic.
Oh, sure.
Uh, oh...
[SEIYA] Perfect. Now use dragon
hands to collect fly corpses.
Okay. Cool.
[MASH grunting]
Nice. This method is
much more efficient.
It's also really
entertaining me.
[SEIYA] Hmm. Good enough.
I'll take it from here.
[MASH, ELULU]
Huh?
Cast Hell's Fire!
Am I a dragon or a maid?
[RISTA]
I don't even know what to say
to them in this situation.
[ROSALIE]
Eliminating the stragglers?
[RISTA gasps]
Isn't that beneath you, hero?
I'm not the biggest
fan of your attitude,
so you can take it
with you when you leave.
Captain Rosalie,
we need to tell them about the
you‐know‐what before we go.
[ROSALIE] I was getting
to that, okay? Gah!
We may not see eye‐to‐eye,
but there's something
you should know.
Listen up.
In a shrine near the village of
Izale, there is a suit of armor.
This legendary armor will
help you defeat the Demon Lord.
I'm sorry, it's legendary?
Not just legendary. Ultimate.
It was crafted
by an ancient sage
who foresaw our current crisis.
Our plan was to inform the
hero as soon as he appeared,
but the flies sidetracked us.
The knights of Roseguard
have kept watch over the years,
justly protecting
the sacred treasure.
You all must be grateful,
and I really can't blame you.
[SEIYA]
Sounds sketchy. Real sketchy.
Are you positive
it's not cursed armor?
How could anyone curse it
if it was always being watched?
It wouldn't be sacred anymore!
Never know. The armor
could be cursed,
sacred, and legendary
at the same time.
[ROSALIE]
Yes, there is!
How can someone as irritating
as you be dubbed a hero?
That armor should be worn
by a gallant and noble man
who's proven himself,
like my father.
‐‐Yah!
‐‐[BHAT gasps]
[BHAT]
Please excuse us, Mr. Hero!
[RISTA]
Before anything else,
I say we go to that
village and snag this armor!
And maybe get some
rest while we're at it?
I could use a break from naked
goddesses and fly monsters.
Yeah. A nap sounds
pretty good to me.
Whatevs. I used some
MP for my magic bow.
I say we stop at the
inn so we can recharge.
[RISTA]
Oh, joy!
No. But we were just here.
Whoa. They leveled
an entire village.
Hey, look! Over there!
[MASH]
That's the item shop!
We have to help!
[KILKAPUL]
Well, well, we meet again, hero.
You can sheath your sword since
I'm the one who
summoned this creature.
[RISTA]
Huh?
[KILKAPUL]
It's an Adamantoise‐‐
a gargantuan demon I brought
forth from a whole other world.
Hey, pee pants.
[KILKAPUL] If you're
going to call me a name,
I prefer you use...
...Summoner Kilkapul,
one of the Four Heavenly Kings.
We bought supplies from one
of the Four Heavenly Kings?
[KILKAPUL]
Thanks to my crystal ball,
I've been observing you
and your motley crew,
bearing witness
to your adventures.
You've had your fun,
but I think you've meddled
in Gaeabrande long enough.
[RISTA]
That humungous turtle.
That's why you summoned it!
You're trying to take out Seiya!
You assume much, though
you were right in one regard.
Adamantoise is
here for a reason.
[RISTA]
And that's the reason?
[KILKAPUL]
Yes.
The sacred armor is now nothing
more than a pile of scraps.
It was made from adamantite‐‐the
strongest metal in Gaeabrande.
Ordinarily, no one
would be able to break it.
No! Come on!
[KILKAPUL]
I destroyed the armor
before you could get your
filthy human hands on it.
[RISTA]
Just our luck!
We're oh‐for‐two in the
legendary equipment department.
Hero, unlike most mortals,
you had a slim chance
of defeating the Demon Lord,
but I guess we'll never know
for certain since
your journey ends here.