[RISTA]
Hey, wait for me, would ya?
[RISTA coughs]
What's wrong with you?
[MACHINA grunts]
[RISTA]
Huh?
[MACHINA chuckles]
A smokescreen?
You're a squirrelly
human, aren't you?
[SEIYA]
We need to get out of here!
Hurry and make
that portal thingy
back to the Divine whats‐it!
[RISTA]
Yeah! Here we go!
We're almost there!
You can't escape!
[MACHINA grunts]
[RISTA yelps]
Casting Hell's Fire!
[MACHINA grunts]
[RISTA grunts]
[MACHINA chuckles]
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
I suppose I'll just have to make
sure we meet up again real soon.
[RISTA groans]
[RISTA panting]
Th‐That was way too close!
[RISTA]
Seiya?
[RISTA yelps]
Whatcha do that for?
[SEIYA]
I need to train, like, now.
Get out.
What? More exercise?
Well, I don't have a choice.
You saw how strong she was.
Way tougher than that slime.
She is one of the
Four Heavenly Kings.
[SEIYA]
I'm gonna stay in this room.
I'll leave when I'm ready. When
the time comes, I'll buzz you.
Till then, stay away.
[RISTA]
Whaddaya mean by ready?
[RISTA grumbling]
[yells] I've had it with
all this waiting around!
Time to use this
thing Aria lent me.
I beseech you, oh,
magical crystal ball,
seer of 3,000 realms.
If danger runs free,
show it to me!
Hey, are you two stalking me?
[yelps]
[MACHINA]
I feel like I'm being stalked.
A note for the goddess and hero.
The two of you
better show up soon.
Because if you don't,
this little town is history.
Please! Don't do this!
I'm begging you‐‐
[MACHINA] I'm slicing
off everyone's heads.
Let's say, one resident
every ten minutes.
[TOWNSMAN 02A whimpers]
‐‐[TOWNSPEOPLE scream]
‐‐[RISTA gasps]
Oh, my. The red fountains that
humans make are just so pretty.
So let's paint the town red!
[gasps]
I thought I told you
not to come in here
until I called for you.
Well, this is urgent!
It's bad. Chaos Machina
is on a rampage.
The bloodshed won't stop
unless we do something to help!
We have to hurry back.
Nah, bro.
I haven't finished
blasting my quads.
There are people dying, and
you're blasting out quads, bro?
Calm down.
Didn't you the tell
me that time passes
way more slowly
in the "Divine Realm"?
That may be true, but it's not
like it stands completely still.
So what kind of ratios
are we workin' with here?
I'm not the goddess of maths.
Ten minutes on Gaeabrande‐‐
that's like 16 hours for us.
[SEIYA]
What's the problem?
We totes got
plenty of time left.
Even if you're right, a hero
should move a little faster
when there are lives at stake!
[RISTA grunting]
[MACHINA]
Now, let's see.
Who's up on the chopping block?
I think this lucky man
will be next. [chuckles]
Oh, no!
Papa! No! Don't hurt him!
How... How cruel! It's too much!
Open! Doorway to
the other worl‐‐
I said I didn't want to
leave until I'm good to go.
Are you kidding me?
Nina's father is
about to be killed!
What? Hey! Did you hear me?
I did. Not yet.
Listen... I get
how scary this is,
but your stats give you at
least some chance of winning.
And I'll have your back with my
recovery magic, so don't worry!
Who said I was?
Please! If you die,
then you just get sent back
to where you came from,
but if they die, that's it‐‐
there's no coming
back for any of them.
[NINA]
No! Stop! I'm begging you!
Don't hurt my papa, please!
[MACHINA]
Oh, don't worry, little girl.
You won't feel lonely
because you won't be alone.
After I'm done
dealing with your daddy,
I'll make sure you
join him right away!
‐‐[MACHINA cackles]
‐‐[NINA crying]
[RISTA]
Don't you care Nina's in danger?
This girl gave you
her lucky flower charm!
How can you just
keep doing nothing?
Yeah, now that you mention it.
[gasps]
[SEIYA]
Huh. I think my hunch was right
about this item being cursed.
May be why we ran into that
beast in the first place.
[gasps]
[RISTA]
I blew it.
I totally messed up.
I never should've summoned
you to begin with.
'Cause you're really
just afraid, aren't you?
Is that why you've been
acting so cautious?
[RISTA]
Well, is it?
Huh?!
You coward!
[RISTA]
Who cares how powerful you are?
You're the worst hero
I've ever laid eyes on!
[SEIYA]
If I die, the town dies,
and it won't be long till
the whole world follows.
[RISTA]
Huh?
[SEIYA]
Get it now?
I can't afford death.
That's why I've been
training so hard.
Wait, what are you
suiting up for?
[SEIYA]
Isn't it obvious?
No... No way!
He did all that in such
a short amount of time?
It's enough to
defeat Chaos Machina!
I'm perfectly prepared.
I'm 100 percent ready for this!
Great! That's more like it!
I'll make a path
to the town square
so we can rescue
them straight away!
Doorway to the other‐‐ [groans]
[RISTA yells]
Owie, what'd ya do that for?
Idiot.
Make it somewhere farther away.
Otherwise she'll finish
off that guy and dumb kid
as soon as she sees us.
Huh, you got a point,
but would you mind holding off
on bopping a goddess
on the head?
Oh. Sure.
I should be more careful.
[RISTA]
Huh?
I wouldn't wanna pick
up any cootie germs.
My hair is clean,
you six‐year‐old meathead!
[NINA]
Stop it! Please!
Don't do anything bad to Papa‐‐
[NINA yelps]
[yawns]
Ten minutes is a long
time to wait, huh?
[MACHINA]
Know what? I've changed my mind.
Let's make it five minutes.
Unfortunately, that means
time's up, pops!
[NINA]
No!
[MACHINA]
Blame it on your no‐show hero!
‐‐[rustling]
‐‐Huh?
[SEIYA]
Wind... Blade!
[SEIYA grunts]
[RISTA]
Huh? When'd he get that move?
[giggles]
Yes, I had a feeling
you'd come back eventually.
Way to leave a girl hanging.
I guess this hero's not
just short on chivalry.
Oh, that's a little
rich, don't you think?
You're a bully who takes
advantage of the helpless!
So say the sneaky creeps
who tried to ambush me
while I was distracted.
[SEIYA] Who said that you were
the one I was trying to hit?
[MACHINA]
Hmm?
[NINA]
Papa!
Thank goodness!
I'm glad you're okay!
Thank you for saving my life!
I owe you one, sir!
[SEIYA grunts]
[TOYA gasps]
So that's how it is.
I see now, I see.
You guys played me
and I totally fell for it.
[MACHINA gasps]
[MACHINA] What is this? It's
like he's a different person!
His ability level outranks mine!
[RISTA] I see. So you
can scan targets, too.
Whatcha think?
Nice stats, am I right?
If you want to throw in
the towel, now's your chance.
All right then.
Seems like I'm gonna have to
take this a bit more seriously.
‐‐Ha?
‐‐Release!
[MACHINA chuckles]
Oh, you thought
you'd won already?
Well, I've got some bad news.
Real fighters who
play on expert mode
always have a little something
extra hiding up their sleeves.
Um, Seiya, watch out.
All of her numbers skyrocketed.
C'mon, just when I thought
we'd finally caught up!
Okay, time to show me what
you're made of, big boy!
[MACHINA grunts]
Ready or not, here I come, hero!
[MACHINA grunting]
She's fast!
Swingin' that sword
like a bad metaphor.
[MACHINA] So you can still
keep up with my moves, eh?
I wonder if you're
one of those guys‐‐
the type with a sharp intuition.
[RISTA]
Yeah, that's right!
Having greater stats
doesn't guarantee a big win!
You can't underestimate
battle instinct and strategy!
[MACHINA]
Tch. How troubling.
A troublesome hero, indeed!
I'm sure I'll beat you, but I
would prefer to be double sure.
Get ready, here comes
my special technique.
I call it "Demonic Curse."
Did ya hear that? Be careful!
Here's a secret.
A real, real fighter
who plays on expert mode
always has a little
something extra
hiding under the
little something extra.
She doesn't sound like
she's messing around.
What could she be up to?
Hey, what the realm
are you doing?!
[MACHINA]
Oh, you'll see.
It's the Demonic Curse,
of course! [chuckles]
With this overwhelming power,
I shall deliver
death to the hero!
[MACHINA grunts]
[gasps]
[RISTA]
I'm so confused.
[RISTA groaning]
Uh, hold on.
Micro bikini demon
isn't her true form?
[MACHINA yells]
[RISTA whimpers]
You gotta be kidding me!
It's stronger than
a D‐Class Demon Lord!
Even with Seiya's combat
smarts, this looks bad!
Do you now understand
the difference in our power?
Surely even you agree that
you've no chance of victory.
Just one blow!
One blow is all it'll take
to separate your
head from your body!
[RISTA screams]
[RISTA] I had no idea Gaeabrande
would be such a terrible world!
[MACHINA chuckles]
I'm sorry.
Please forgive‐‐
[gasps]
What? Impossible!
How could this be?
[RISTA]
Hold on a second.
Seiya's stats are
too low to survive that!
Did I misread something?
No. Then it must be...
...the Fake Out skill!
Time for me to give
him a quick scan.
[RISTA]
A lock?
He's definitely using Fake Out.
That sneaky little meathead!
[RISTA]
Again?!
How rude! Why, you!
It's not like I'm
perving on you!
Now I'm really
gonna keep looking!
Megamic Power!
Come on. [groans]
Oh, goddess, my eyes
are about to pop out!
Gotta dig deep, Ristarte!
You can do it,
put your mind into it!
[pants] You did it girl,
you finally got the goodies!
[RISTA gasps]
What is all this?
These figures are almost
five‐‐no, ten times higher!
He's got more skills, too!
Wait, there wasn't enough
time for that to happen.
So then...
...he must've
started using Fake Out
after his first
round of training.
He was already stronger than
Chaos Machina from the get‐go!
He was just grinding
this whole time!
This guy is unhinged!
I mean, he's a complete
and utter nutjob!
Huh. Guess you're
tougher than I expected.
[MACHINA]
Whatever.
I'll summon all my magic
into my fist using this ability!
The Demonic Delete!
Turning you and this whole
pathetic little town into‐‐huh?
Where'd you go?
[MACHINA gasps]
When did you learn
the Flight skill?
How is that even possible?
[RISTA] She's one of
the Four Heavenly Kings.
Very powerful...
...but she's careful, too.
She would've defeated any
normal hero by this point.
However, she picked
the wrong one this time.
'Cause now... this hero?
Wha... Not the
Magic Sword technique!
Isn't that an upper‐tier skill?
[SEIYA]
It is!
It's called Phoenix Drive!
[MACHINA groans]
[RISTA]
Oh, yeah, this hero...
...is unbelievably cautious!
[RISTA giggling]
Seiya!
What are you doing?
Don't make me get the hose.
I'm celebrating!
I thought we were
done for back there!
[RISTA]
Man, oh, man!
He smells good enough
to eat! [snorts]
[SEIYA] Get off. You'll
give me a disease.
I am not gonna get you sick!
Come on, just let me have this!
I swear, I'm perfectly healthy!
[RISTA] Honestly, though?
I'm a little upset with you now.
Why have you been hiding
your Fake Out skill?
[SEIYA] I figured if you
had the ability to scan me,
then any enemies might
be able to do the same,
so I made sure to gain
that skill before any others.
[RISTA]
So you had it from the start?
I get keeping your true
level away from baddies,
but don't you think you
could have at least told me?
I mean, I am your
partner after all, right?
Even if you kept
your big mouth shut,
there could be a brain monster.
One peek into your head
and we'd be screwed.
Oh, no, a brain monster?
That sounds really scary.
But I know that you
would protect me!
You're supposed to be a goddess.
Aren't you immortal?
You don't need protection.
[RISTA]
Not the point!
Cut it out or I'll cut you.
Go right ahead!
Tear me to pieces!
[SEIYA]
Hey.
Uh?
[TOWNSMAN 02B]
Hey there, Mister Hero!
[TOWNSWOMAN 02A] We're so
glad you saved our town!
[TOWNSWOMAN 02B] I can't
believe you beat that beast!
[TOWNSMAN 02C]
You have our eternal thanks!
He's got the face of a nobleman!
Yes, and he's so tall
and handsome, too!
Hello, I'm Jamie, and
I run the fruit stand!
Please, go and help yourself!
Oh, thank you, Jamie!
Greetings, I am
the mayor of Edona!
It would be my absolute
pleasure to throw
a banquet in your honor,
so please join me at my manor.
A welcoming party sure
does sound nice. Wanna go?
No, I still have things to take
care of, thank you very much.
[RISTA] I bet he's heading
straight to the next town.
How gallant!
No wonder I'm falling for him!
[RISTA]
Uh, hey... whatcha doin'?
[SEIYA]
Being safe.
[RISTA]
Aren't those the charred remains
of the mini bikini demon?
[TOWNSPEOPLE chattering]
[RISTA]
Uhh...
Oh, no.
Casting Hell's Fire!
Not again!
[SEIYA]
Hell's Fire!
Hell's Fire! Hell's Fire!
[RISTA]
Enough with the fireworks!
She's a Heavenly King.
If a single cell remains,
she might regenerate.
I must obliterate her!
[RISTA]
Stop it already!
You're scaring everyone off!
[SEIYA]
Hell's Fire‐‐
‐‐[SEIYA] Nice.
‐‐[RISTA groans]
‐‐[SEIYA] Time to finish it.
‐‐[RISTA] Wha...?
[SEIYA grunts]
[SEIYA]
Now! Maximum Inferno!
[TOWNSPEOPLE scream]
[RISTA] What are you doing?!
There's nothing left but ash!
[TOWNSMAN 02D]
Please, the shops are on fire!
[TOWNSMAN 02E] Look, over there!
Poor Jamie's on fire, too!
Knock it off! You're
gonna kill the fruit guy!
[JAMIE screaming, groans]
[RISTA] By the power
of the Goddess Ristarte,
may the wounds of this
innocent man be healed!
[SEIYA]
Maximum... Inferno!
[RISTA]
Hey! How long ya gonna do that?
[MAYOR 02A]
Please,
I humbly beg...
leave our town at once!
How did things end up like this?
You were more like
a Demon Lord than a hero.
One kid threw a rock at me, but
I bet you didn't even notice.
[SEIYA]
We saved them from certain doom,
and yet they treat us
so heartlessly. Lame.
You're one to talk, buddy!
Poor, sweet Jamie didn't
burn himself, ya know!
Not my fault.
Oh, wow, you really
are the worst.
[TOYA]
Um!
I'm sorry.
We shouldn't have made you leave
after you rescued everyone.
Oh, no, there's no need
to apologize, I mean,
your town did burn, along
with... a few people, so...
[TOYA]
It's not much, but here!
[SEIYA]
Ooh, money.
You shouldn't be
so greedy, Seiya.
Try to show some restraint.
What gives? This isn't
very much at all.
If you got any more,
then cough it up!
You're no better than a thief!
Here, sir, it's all I have left.
[NINA giggles]
Hey, Mister!
You might be a little weird,
but deep down inside
you're a real good guy!
Oh, Nina.
You're sort of right,
and sort of wrong.
He's not a good guy,
just super weird.
[SEIYA] You... You do
realize I'm right here?
You burned down their
town and robbed them!
I'm being charitable!
All right!
Let's head off already!
C'mon, say goodbye.
Thank you, Miss Nice Lady!
Thank you, too, Mister Weirdo!
[TOYA]
Um, sweetie?
Let's not address
people like that.
Listen, don't you
think you should
start acting a bit more heroic?
[RISTA]
Oh.
Look, you still have
that pressed flower.
Didn't you say it was
a cursed item or something?
Well, that might not
be such a bad thing,
given our circumstance.
If it attracts enemies,
then it might be
more convenient for
me to hold onto it.
[RISTA]
Huh.
‐‐[SEIYA] What?
‐‐Oh, it's nothing.
[RISTA]
Yeesh. I really don't get him.
He's so weird.
[RISTA] Okey‐doke! Our adventure
is just getting started.
Off to the next town!
No, we're going
back to the Realm.
More training?
Are you kidding me?!
When the enemy learns that
we beat a Heavenly King,
they'll send stronger
forces our way.
Okay, but if we don't
go to the next town,
then we won't be able
to score any good weapons.
Yeah, I would like to
buy some new armor, too.
Could you make some for me?
You can make beds and stuff.
[RISTA] I can only create
things in the Divine Realm.
Bringing anything from
there is forbidden.
And excessive assistance to
human is against divine law.
So you're useless.
[RISTA] Wow! I healed Jamie's
burns, in case you forgot!
Medicinal herbs
could've done the same.
In other words,
your value to society
is no greater
than that of a leaf.
Are you comparing me
to stuff on a tree?!
In any case, I'm due
for some more training.
Hurry up and open
a portal, plant‐lady.
[RISTA] All right,
all right, I hear you.
Wait, what did you call me?!
Good. Let's go.
We've just taken
a few steps forward
and then a dozen steps back
for the second time.
[SEIYA grunts]
[RISTA] A weirdo hero.
How is this gonna work?